From PR News in Washington, I'm kicking and screaming for golf outings.
Inscreations, children cry, troops fines, growing dissent against President Bush's no-child law.
One man says it's about time.
Security police prison arrested, detained, on our king clerics, tribal suicide kidnappings.
Taking a look at figures on Wall Street, 2, 5, 6, 7, 7, 8, 9, 10, 12.
This is PR.
Inside a courtroom in Wichita, Kansas, protesting Jewish settlers took turns lashing out at PR News, Washington.
Let's go to the Gigolo Club over in Yancey.
They've got a...
Some genius, powerful, smart.
I say this calls for action, and now, nip it in the bud.
Ah, shut up.
Here it is, kids.
Are you tired of being a square? Are you tired of a dull, dull, dull existence?
Well, for one dollar.
The tenth pot of a sawbuck.
Try kelp's cool tonic.
The life of the party.
He's right, kids. It's a gasser.
Step right up, folks. Be somebody. Be anybody.
Only trouble was, nobody got killed.
No, Mr. Boob, that's me.
B-double-O-B, Boob.
The reason for this hearing is to promote outrageous filth.
Pornography. It's outrageous filth.
So I'll be looking.
Hey!
Weaver!
Starring Barbara the Weaver.
Something has just come up.
Oh, boy.
Ooh, get a kiss?
Sure.
Watch.
Hey, the ass is...
Oh, a little squircums.
To the dog.
And a squircum.
Yeah!
Oh, squircum fun.
Yeah.
Mom?
Oh.
Get over here.
Mom?
He's a local boy.
Uh, he's just terrific.
He's our new leader.
Leader?
He's like too much.
Like too much what?
He's one of the truly great swingers of all time.
We now present Bob, internationally known founder of Bob University.
Sitting down down down rising.
Up up up up.
You know, Filipino boy.
I always... I knew it. He's nice fella.
I had another talk with a young fella yesterday.
And... I knew it. He's nice fella. I had another talk with a young fella yesterday.
And as I probed him, I found out he could have, uh, fooled me.
He didn't know.
It's hard probing that and you get to pull things out.
Strange about people.
And, uh, you can think things.
Did you know it's the hardest thing in the world for a man in analyzing his own impulses to know what Filipino boy wants him to do?
Do the dang job.
Never leave it unfinished.
Don't walk out and leave an unfinished job.
Then...
Job.
And then, you know, I've learned a few other little things too.
You did his hard-on, Bob.
What?
Sounds good, doesn't it?
If you'll pay me a thousand dollars more, I'll be glad to come.
You know, a little chill went up and down my back.
Wait a minute.
You have just heard Bob, internationally known founder of Bob University.
This program is sponsored by Bob.
The history of sexuality is as long as the history of man.
From the glory that once was grown, sexuality has been both despised and idolized.
Though nothing new, sexuality is having an upsurge since the war.
Whether it is an actual increase or merely an increased public acceptance is a point to be argued.
One male out of six is sexual.
Sexuals no longer hide in shadows, giving secret signals of recognition to each other.
But rather, they have joined together into groups or clubs in an attempt to seek freedom.
Hopefully we'll be seeing you again soon.
Tear down, and the other job is done.
In the valley of Moab.
here is the prohibition of sex.
The Moabites.
The Moabites themselves.
Get out.
Get Moab out of your mouth, boy.
We got some lambs to slaughter here.
First you whip your dictionary out.
Then you put your Moab in your mouth.
Put your Moab on it.
Come on.
Then you put those lambs on the altar.
You just slit them a little bit right there underneath the throat.
It's kind of nick them.
It's nicking.
Or the blood.
It's sticking in the nick.
The bit of nick comes out.
The blood starts flowing down that glycine.
It's blood.
The blood.
But it's the blood that cleanses.
It's the blood that makes things right.
It's the blood that provides the ultimate salvation to which you've attached yourself.
All these years.
It's the blood that we make that special antidote for you.
You know, those bats that get on your face.
You know what they do to your face.
Special bats.
Put your dictionary away now, children, and we'll tell you about the bats.
That book is kind of heavy.
It's a heavy book.
The frontal cerebral fornicating bat.
And the ejaculate.
We won't talk about them.
No, we can't.
We can't talk about them.
We can't get too specific about them.
We can't talk about what those bats do.
You may as well just stick your finger in a light socket.
But the Church of the Subgenius provides the only way.
It provides the only proscribed and tested by time instructions for de-beaking the prairie squid.
Which is all the practices that you'll need, children.
Yeah, I talked to my step-neighbor-in-law.
By those bats.
Porky was telling me that story one time about Moab.
And he was, well, I hate to say it.
I hate to tell you this.
But Porky didn't say no.
He forgot to say no.
So he was not in the state of mind he might have been in other lives.
He had launched ahead in years.
He had launched ahead in oh Lord knows how long.
He'd never been in a doctor van.
Yeah, he never realized the glories of the doctors and the priests and the bats.
Accordingly.
He'd never.
His own.
Ever.
Boy, that's a little doggy.
Quick on that.
Oh, sorry.
I knew who was coming down tonight.
Well.
Well, that was Willa Dobbs, friends.
A guest hosting on an ancient subgenius radio show.
With Dr. Philo Drummond and Pope Sternodocs Kee Kaver as guest stars.
That was on an hour of slack back in the 80s.
I wasn't even there for that show.
Heck, I'm not even here for this show.
Which is number 1,000.
1013.
Well, that spells ayob.
Anyway, this is a sexy episode.
If only because I've been tossing sexish audio files into this one folder until it
equaled 600 megabytes which equals one show.
One sinful show.
And we'll be hearing more Bobulous collages from Mr. Fernand and Andy Lemur, from Reverend
Norrell Preff.
All kinds of devos.
And more Philo and Sternodocs.
And this background music here is by Lemur Devotee.
So listen up and you'll find slack.
Or else you'll learn what it is or who it is that you need to get slack.
Imagine me needing someone.
Back on Earth I never did.
Oh, there were women.
Lots of women.
Lots of love making.
But no love.
Oh.
That was the kind of world we'd made.
So I left.
Because there was no one to hold me there.
Did I tell you about Stewart?
Now there was a lovely girl.
The most precious cargo we brought along.
She was to be the new Eve.
With our hot and eager help of course.
I can accommodate either sex and any combination of people.
I'm also programmed with all the appropriate sexual expletives.
A large catalog of moans, groans, howls, squeals, grunts and purrs.
Really?
I'm not programmed for disinformation or lying.
What else can you do?
I also have a number of pleasure features, including three vibration stimulators placed strategically in the oral, anal and vaginal orifices.
My nipples are programmed to harden under manual or oral stimulation.
I salivate, secrete and spurt appropriately.
An android for all seasons, huh?
And there's a beautiful girl.
And there's a beautiful girl holding a paintbrush.
And there's a beautiful girl holding a ticket.
High boots, hipster miniskirt.
Brief.
Very brief.
She's neat.
Petite.
Swinging gaze.
Fear.
Wild.
Long.
Straight.
Couldn't be much bigger.
The big sex pact.
And there's a beautiful girl all over it.
There.
It's creamy.
Looks like she's ready for a happening.
I'm a lesbian.
The sociologist says I'm a self-absorbed narcissist.
One troubled individual.
Willing to destroy any institution.
The destruction of human life.
Put that down.
Don't you feel that I'm a lesbian?
Don't you feel it rather interesting that every time you have a story about terrorism it is linked to Christian extremists.
Christian extremists teach us violence.
Weeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee.
Osama Bin Laden is their great hero.
Yes.
Christian extremists blew up trains. Christian extremists assassinated film producers.
Christian extremists blew up a crowded shopping center.
And the Christian extremists, it's always Christian extremists.
And it's time we recognize it and begin to deal with it.
I'm a lesbian.
Take your stinking paws off me, you damn dirty ape!
Fornication, sodomy, fellatio and cunnilingus, unbridled concupiscence on every street corner.
Lord sir, you make me quite nervous.
Indeed, ma'am, it is not so bad as that.
Indeed it is, sir. I wouldn't venture nearer the Capitol than Litchfield.
Buggery, incest, bestiality.
And it was a splendid day.
I believe the buggery took place in the conservatory.
Or was it the laboratory?
It was an extraordinary buggery!
The way they took place back there in the lavatory?
It wasn't in the lavatory. I thought it was in the conservatory.
But that buggery was the most extraordinary buggery I'd ever experienced.
They scoffed. Oh, they scoffed!
It was a...
Oh boy, little did they know.
I believe it was in the aviary.
I've got pictures.
I've got pictures of it.
It was a conspiratorial buggery, which was brought about by lack of faith in Bob Children.
The
Rel Zacconico
The Rel Zacconico
Theams
Therem
I really do.
When a man
loves a ticket
he can't
keep his mind on nothing else.
He'll stay in the barn
for the good
thing he's found.
In his
inside he can't
see it.
She can't do
no wrong.
Rose Arlen Red is his best
friend. He can't put her
down.
When a man
wants a ticket
he
can't
stay
behind
to
count on
the
lights.
Rose Arlen Red
his mind
on nothing
She lays them on the eggs she had
Tells the farmer there's nothing going on
Believe me, she's cocky just cause she said
When a man loves a chicken
People think that it is wrong
Shouldn't stick his beak in where it don't belong
Just when a man loves a chicken
I know exactly how it feels
Hey baby, baby, baby
I'm your cocky doo-doo
When a man loves a chicken
I know exactly how it feels
He shacks up into his house
With the good things he's found
When a man loves a chicken
People think that he's insane
But all he can do is wing it
For the one he loves
Just when a man loves a chicken
He's got a good reason to be a chicken
In the morning, I would immediately get annoyed.
I'd just think, roosters, you know.
Why do I have to even think about roosters?
I'm already, it's, I just got up and already I'm thinking about roosters.
I don't want to think about roosters.
You may be angry.
What's the matter, Colonel Sanders?
Chicken?
I found a way to cook chicken deep down.
And get that crispy, real crispy chicken crust.
Yet it's entirely different.
No, no, no.
That real crusty, real what kind of damn?
Crispy crust.
You don't want me to sing, do you, for Christ's sake?
I'm not getting anywhere with this damn thing.
Okay, fine.
I hated the colonel with his wee beady eyes.
And that smug look on his face.
Oh, you're gonna buy my chicken.
Oh.
In the face.
...
But this reminds me of a porno movie I saw in the 70s.
Yeah, that's where we got the...
It sounds like that poignant, heart-rending story
of the woman with the world's largest breasts
who meets the man with the longest dick.
It was so tragic,
I could barely make myself watch the whole thing.
So sad, so fresh, the days that are new.
They were just such parodies of human things.
Of exuberance, of life and life efforts.
I'm not kidding you, his dick was like this long.
It's just way beyond normal.
It's incredible what they can do with special effects these days.
I walk down the block
and I see walking towards me
a beautiful young lady.
And the closer she gets to me,
the older she starts to look
and the closer she gets to me,
the more virtues she leaves behind
the further she ventures from her youthful past
and the closer she gets to me,
the closer she gets to her own death
and mine!
And I see it!
And I pity her for the things that I know.
Personally.
And I pity myself for the times when I didn't think fast.
And I pity her more for the humdrum thing she is wearing.
And I smile as she sniffes when she realizes I am staring.
And I feel so ashamed for the arrogant way that I scrutinize.
I can tell her that I am not alone.
I can tell her that she is my age.
And the further she gets from me,
she lessens her chances of becoming my bride.
the more I love her.
All kidding aside,
and the further she gets from me,
the further I am taken back
to the days of my sister's friends in high school.
And the further I get from my sister,
And the further I get from her,
The closer she gets by a band called The Billy Nayer Show.
Nayer is spelled N-A-Y-E-R
because there's a billynayer.com.
Reverend Magdalene turned us on to them.
They did this incredible movie called,
called The American Astronaut, which just came out on DVD.
And all I can say is, yeah, it's BillyNayer.com.
You'll be hearing more from all of that on Hour of Slack.
Husband, is that you? Where are you all at?
Good evening to you, madam. Would you care to join us?
You get no joy from him.
I loved her dearly once.
But she's a whore.
Not by necessity of a bank commission.
Well, she owns 51% of the bank's stock, for Pete's sake.
Don't tell me your wife believes all that Luther Hegg's hogwash.
With all her heart, she came home last night and vibrated for an hour.
The father of that little girl, she didn't know anything about Bob.
She was begging me to tell her about Bob.
She paid me $20 for one word of Bob.
I gave her a silver-bonded dictionary.
She gave me my first dictionary.
She was only 13 and I was 83.
Now that's time control.
Yeah, back when we went back early, way back in time,
we went back to a couple of amoebas, flipping our flagellas around.
Next thing you know, we're progressing through time.
She ended up in a freezer bag.
If I recall my course of events,
I believe that it was dinner time in Dobbs Town.
Yeah, dinner time.
Wasn't it?
Or maybe supper time.
I don't know.
Supper time in Dobbs Town.
Dinner, supper.
And she'd suffered a serious freezer burn.
And it was all because of her lack of faith in Bob.
She wouldn't put her soul, after brunch, in Bob's hands.
She couldn't bring herself home.
She couldn't face the facts.
Then after lunch, we have lupper,
which is kind of like a brunch between dinner and supper.
She had problems with a bit of the genius dogma.
She had problems with slack.
And sinner is not the sinner you would think of.
It's actually a meal that we have between dinner and supper.
Sinner on rise.
Supper.
Puffer.
At night, late at night, we have puffer.
And then we sin.
We just sit there and sin.
That's all we do.
We don't have to do anything.
For the Church of the Subgenius, we think sin.
It doesn't want to eradicate sin.
It's not because we want to.
It's because we have to.
The Church of the Subgenius have to.
Because we have to bear that sinful burden of mankind.
Justifies sin.
Of the normals, the pinks.
You know, they're sinning all the time.
It's their sins that we kind of ride on like the luck plane.
Like a wave in the luck plane.
Riding like cosmic surfers.
Ah.
Looking at the words and the ways of Britney Spears.
A religious leader.
The way she's used her body.
Offers us sexuality all the time.
Gee.
But you know what?
Britney Spears flaunts her sexuality in all of its forms.
Now, what do you say?
An adulteress!
Is it right to kill her?
Go now.
I am so quick.
I'm so quick.
Plop, plop, plop, plop, plop.
All over the ground.
Creates another feeling in me, perhaps.
And also, perhaps in you.
And that is a feeling of enormous awe.
Awe.
Enormous awe.
Britney Spears.
She flaunted her body in ways that creates another feeling in me.
You know and I know Britney Spears kissed Madonna, another woman, on live television.
Her body.
Throw her down as a tool.
Come on silk sheets.
Illicit sexuality.
Over here.
Here.
Caught in the act.
Britney Spears bent two feelings in me.
Two feelings in you.
Fool for Britney Spears today.
I was praying last night.
When an angel broke the light.
He said, I'm gonna have to put you on hold for a time.
I said, hold like hell.
Let me talk to the boss.
He said, sorry, slow down.
Sinner, it's the boss's day off.
And I realized this.
That the wages of sin was two bucks an hour and working weekend.
I was ignoring the fee.
He was lashed to the cross and cried, help me get this son of a bitch off.
I said I would if I could.
I can't so I won't.
Well I wouldn't want you messing your hair up so don't.
And I realized then.
That the wages of sin.
Was all the lumber you can carry.
All the nails you can bend.
The wages of sin.
The reward of fear.
It's worrying and threatening every second of the year.
And heaven is guilt.
No sex and no show.
That I'm not sure if I really wanna go.
Oh.
Just the waiting.
экспaire accordion
You've been taught to ask.
Those three snares
Every second of the day
The church and the state
You've got a country kind
One gets your body
The other gets your mind
Mary, Mary Magdalene
How about a date?
You've been wasting your time
Staying up so late
Your boyfriend's dead
The word is you're a whore
Just about then I heard a knock on the door
And I realized then
That the wages of sin
Was a bad reputation
And too many friends
The wages of sin
The Rainmakers, Wages of Sin.
Friends, we also heard some Philo Drummond and Sterno Kekever,
Pope Sterno Docs, and some clips via Jacques Pate,
and great cutting by Noral Preff and Fernand and Andy Lemur.
More of that coming up, and also coming up, Nicky Death Chick.
It is written that man does not live by every word that proceedeth out of the mouth of God,
but by bread alone.
We invite you to study the scriptures,
with us to learn about bread alone.
We would like to hear from you, and we pray in the name of bread alone.
Thank you for listening to this message.
There I am.
Thanks again, and may the love of bread alone
abide in you and yours forever and ever.
Amen.
Oh, you are healed.
Go forth and sin again.
Oh, yes, I think I've had quite enough healing tonight.
Every one of you, you must remember that the conspiracy guilt demons inhabit your ass.
And if you can't get me to sin,
spank you, you can always pay someone else to do it.
Thank you very much.
Reverend Nicky Death Chick.
I heard that you were feeling ill.
Headache, fever, and a chill.
I came to help restore your pluck,
cause I'm the nurse who likes to...
Stage two.
Warm liquid goo phase beginning.
Warm liquid goo phase complete.
Stage three.
Sir, sir, I pulled the trigger.
Fire away, my dear.
Oh!
Hello, I'm Hurley Mann, and I wrote a book called...
Cleavage and Swords.
Joy for everybody.
Admire her character.
Even if she doesn't have any.
Admire her...
Cleavage.
You like the way she handles her...
Cave man.
Act confident.
Cleavage.
Even if you aren't.
What was his name?
You mean the one you couldn't get to...
This is the second time that you've laid hands on me.
When you're slapped, you'll take it and like it.
I was sure that he would ravish you.
But he was not long enough with you to complete a full ravishment.
But I'll warrant he offered you some gross indecencies, am I right?
No, indeed, sir.
He was most genteel.
Showed you his virile member, forced you to touch and play with it on pain of death and so forth in the usual way.
No doubt.
No, I assure you.
Nothing of the kind.
Strange.
I heard only the other day of three...
Ladies in a coach who were subjected to the most unspeakable indignities.
The first offender...
Please.
I am not well.
Come on.
Well, love takes a backseat to life
When a man runs away from his wife
That's when you know he's dead
That's when you know he's in the world
When a guy tries to run up his mate
But she's gone and it's getting late
That's when you know he lost his girl
So it happens all the time
Don't get low, just stand in line
Take your turn, now make your move
And crush that dog
With a ton of love
When a woman takes a backseat to man
She has to tell him where to go if she can
And she decides to wear his ring
So it happens all the time
Don't get low, just stand in line
Take your turn, now make your move
And crush that dog
With a ton of love
Times a girl with the face of a clock
Will have to go until you can't stop
She comes from above with a ton of love
With a ton of love
As if you didn't know, that was Devo from the old days.
And you're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
At the age of 12, I received my first scribe.
At the age of 14, as a roastery named Vilma ritualistically shaved my testicles.
There really is nothing like a shorn scrotum.
It's breathtaking. I suggest you try it.
You know, we have to stop.
Say, did you see the skid marks out here?
They go at a direct right angle to the direction of travel.
And let the record show that Mr. Hank Hill really knows his pornography.
Thank you, Your Honor.
I shall be sorry to see you swing, I shall.
I miss you, Mo.
Oh, the chaplain sends his apologies.
He was going to come and pray for you, but he's been took up himself.
Robbing the collection and buggering the altar boys.
Well, every man to his taste.
Oh yes, Lord, make it hard, Lord.
You and I come together.
Right now, right now.
Right now.
Oh, oh, oh, have a life.
Now listen to this.
Change your thinking.
Come.
Begin to come.
Done.
Blood on the doorpost.
Eat that all night.
Bondage and feeble premature.
Follow me.
I'm the head behind.
I'm going to tell and I will.
Now listen close.
Take it.
Number one, let me tell you something.
Heaven.
Member.
My dear member.
Stop it.
I don't know.
We are as.
We are what we think we are.
You are what you think you are.
Stop it.
And let me tell you something right now.
There's nothing wrong with one.
My dear member.
For what you tasted.
Now listen close.
Listen to me.
Direction.
Our.
Power.
Hello.
Let me tell you something.
Listen to me.
Bah, bah, bah, bah, ha, shanda.
You realize it's your food.
Even now I am touching you.
My dear member.
Great power.
Our.
My dear.
Great.
Now let me say something to you again.
I want you to remember.
Cuss a candle and go with the flow.
Number two.
Gah, bah, bah, bah, bah, bah.
The power of the tongue.
Open your mouth wide and I will fill it.
I got to get your mouth open.
Hello.
Listen to you.
Listen to me.
I'm talking to you.
I am cannibal.
A cannibal.
Dog.
Monkey.
We become carnal minded.
I found out that secret place.
I don't know if I passed out under exhaustion or what in my closet, but I was in there a long time.
I have dick, dick.
It just starts coming out of your mouth.
Get it in your soul.
No!
And then you touch my erection.
Now listen to this.
You've got, let me tell you this one thing.
Be like a tree.
You've got, my dear member, natural, brute, almost animal.
The blood pressure goes down.
There it is right there.
There's blood pressure, blood pressure, blood pressure.
You stabilize.
Put a little bit of oil.
Pour it in again, pour it in again.
All . . .
I, I, I, I . . .
After about an hour of that, I can't forget this.
I can't forget this.
I can't forget.
We'll just use it, it'll grow.
Those devils, those lying devils, they get on television and radio and newspapers, they'd
say all-
The devil tried to get me believe the very lies!
The devil tried to get me to believe the very lies!
Ho!
Favor!
It grew.
I just can't have it.
Believe it!
Woo-hoo!
What do you want?
Day every day, every day, every day, every day, every day, every day, every day, every
day, every day.
Oh!
Woo-hoo!
Dumb and blind to everything around you.
Are you ready?
I am.
Pervert.
The grand wizard of the clue club's claim.
Nonsense.
I'm going to give it to you.
Now listen to this.
I want you to open your mouth.
You need to make a check out for $5,000 and send it in today.
Get some more meat here in this.
Get your mouth open.
Some more meat.
Right out of check today.
Six, six, six.
I'm going to give it to you.
You must win it.
When something's going wrong.
Now whip it.
In the shape.
Shape it up.
Get straight.
Go forward.
Move ahead.
Time to detect it.
It's not too late.
To whip it.
Whip it good.
When a good time comes around.
You must win it.
You will never live it down.
Unless you win it.
No one gets away.
Until they whip it.
I say whip it.
Whip it good.
Crack that whip.
Here's the best to slip.
Step on the crack.
Break your mama's back.
When a problem comes along.
You must whip it.
Before the creeps come along.
When something's going wrong.
You must whip it.
Now whip it.
In the shape.
Shape it up.
Get straight.
Go forward.
Move ahead.
Try to detect it.
It's not too late.
To whip it.
In the shape.
Shape it up.
Get straight.
Go forward.
Move ahead.
Try to detect it.
It's not too late.
To whip it.
Whip it good.
Whip it.
Done up by CD Truth.
A great band from nearby here in Cleveland.
And more about them.
them at cdtruth.com. That's from the devotional commemorative release, not necessarily beautiful,
but mutated. You know, friends, some people over the years have considered our subgenius material
offensive. Our religious subgenius material offends some people. Imagine that.
What do you think about them wimp subgeniuses on the coast that were upset by the preponderance
of protruding blue-veined throbbers in the new Stark filth removal? What do you think about that,
Philo? How about some of the subgeniuses out there on the west coast? They just couldn't deal with
the new Stark filth removal. I mean, what do they got?
What do they got against it? What do they got against those things sticking out everywhere?
Nasty. Is that what they think it's like? Juvenile. But it's something you would do if you were a
manly thing. They can't see us or hear us right now. The little faraway subgeniuses still fighting
those old canards.
The best British accent should read that one. We just got this in the mail this week. I think it's interesting.
You have to self-censor yourself.
See, we can't send a signal to where they are. They can still send a signal back to us, though.
The latest church magazine is none of it. You can't make any excuses for the rape-fixated fantasies.
I can't even read this guy's writing. You try to pass off as a celebration of sexuality.
That's so you.
Human. That's so human. As much as I've enjoyed the subgenius stuff over the years, I don't want to receive any more of your and your contributors grow out of this adolescent arrested sexuality.
Beep. You've lost it. Chris Aton.
Well, Chris, let's just dissect this.
First of all, I want to say we're all missing. We didn't put out that last word.
That's right.
That was a blatant attempt of the Citizens for Normalcy or some other underground organization to discredit the church of the subgenius
by publishing that filth, that horrible, horrid filth that we will take no credit for whatsoever.
Although if we did, we would be gladly aligned with it. We would support it to the fullest degree.
But unfortunately, I can't.
I can't take credit. Neither can would Reverend Stang if he was here. It's just a it's an unfortunate thing that they did such a good job of of imitating our style.
But I have to admit now, before we take any more unnecessary heat, although we were trying to pick up the profits as well as we could, which is you would you would you would normally expect that from us.
But I have to admit right now, we had nothing, nothing whatsoever to do with a horrible, filthy start.
Which was the end of the day.
We had nothing quite such a good afternoon.
We hadn't even had a pandemic, we thought we'd stitch up some work for the phone calls to come in the
We're thinking obviously the best way to put it, you know, the worst thing is to use some old American Rubiki on them.
We have a lot of important details here.
I haven't gotten to this detail, but I think make them look fantastic.
It has won me over the world.
Does that say good news and it's good news.
We would have abandoned this immediately.
Okay, you're a shot.
It looks like shot.
He says, you're not stuff.
How can you call the primary excommunication with the X's and the word of Bob stuff?
That just relegates it to some type of mundane fecal tissue.
Okay, and then he says, you're stuff.
It cannot be equated.
You're stuff used to be.
Now, masters of time control don't even, we don't even need the used to be.
What is this used to be?
Masters of time control have no need for such narrowly confining used to be.
Used to be.
Clever, funny, and intelligent.
We've never been clever, funny, or intelligent.
There's no such thing as claim to be clever or intelligent.
Look at the word.
It's subgenius.
We're not geniuses.
Clever.
I mean, if you take clever and intelligent.
And what is clever but just a simple machine?
We're like the LEV office.
It's just ER.
It's a simpleton.
Take all of that.
We have nothing more complex than the basic wheel, inclined plane, and lever.
That's the most complex we get in our, in anything we may even consider.
So, calling us clever, or funny, or intelligent is just a, it's just an insult.
Okay, and then look at this word here.
The.
He starts the second sentence of his letter with the word.
A three letter word.
Why would you write?
The.
I just can't.
Okay.
The latest.
The.
The latest church magazine.
How does he know it's the latest church magazine?
Did he get one, did he get this morning's magazine?
I guess not.
Did he get the one we put out this afternoon?
No.
Did he get the one that we're working on right now?
I can't believe this call.
Has he got the one that we're going to do next week?
The.
The latest church magazine.
Read the letter.
What else?
What else do we have?
I just can't believe this.
Never is.
Read the letter.
Is none of these.
None of these what?
Brent, it's all of those.
None of them.
All of them.
It's only three or four of them at the same time.
It's a dozen of them as we sit here and eleven of them in the morning first thing.
Unless one of them gets wet and starts to swell up and he puts it in that box.
What's he going to do?
Does he have that oaken box?
Does he have an oaken casket?
Does he have the arc of the bleeding head of Arnold Palmer to put it in?
What's he going to do when it starts swelling up?
I just can't believe this.
None of these.
Okay.
Another three letter word.
You.
Huh.
I used that one there to start the
flawed like a O chick
The keer
the
collaborating
The
210-577. Northwest Airlines says they found ordinary skin and bone cells,
but employees and some outside observers say they found PR news in Washington.
You sound really pretty. Let me tell you what I'm wearing. I'm wearing brown pants,
an old navy crew neck, and a pair of red Skechers. Did I mention I'm also wearing a
UGO baseball cap? I'm lying on my floor playing with my model trains right now.
I'm making tracks, baby. Oh, just lay back and listen. I'm small, but I know how to choo-choo.
You could be my jungle gym and I'll swing around and climb. Let me get my trampoline, baby.
Choo-choo. Imagine my tiny body crawling all over you, boo.
Feet.
He'll sneak my way all up inside and through you.
You like that, don't you?
So don't be afraid.
It won't hurt much.
Bob appears to be just a head.
You never see him with arms and legs anymore.
You might call him a head of his time.
But what else if it's Bob?
You don't need arms.
You don't need legs.
You don't even need a brain.
Because all you really need, friends, is slack.
That's all anybody needs.
When was the last time brains got you a good job?
No!
Lying on your resume or somebody else dying gets you a good job.
When did being smart get you success on a date?
Well, actually, if you're like me, that's about the only way to you.
But, nonetheless, you know what I'm saying.
Kevin Fox, hi.
Before you do this, I've decided to meet my assistant.
It's a five-minute, easy version.
The wrongs warn you of a game.
First, you say,
Ready?
2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
Walk those legs out.
5, 6, 7, 8.
3, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
4, 2, 3, 4, 6, 7, 8.
5, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
Down all the way to the back extension.
Ready?
Game, game, game, game, game, game.
2, 2, 3, 4, 3, 2.
Straighten those legs out.
4, 3, 3, 4, 5, 2, 3, 4.
Stand up and ready for the easy.
Come side to side.
Left, right, left, right, left, right, left.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
Drop down to side extensions.
One leg to side.
Game, game, game, game, game.
2, 3, 4, 3, 2, 3, 4.
4, 2, 3, 4, 5, 2, 3.
Green meat for me.
Spread out so far and wide.
I'd rather get allergic smelling.
But.
The stars.
Fresh.
Crap.
Do you know your daughter well?
And do you know she's dreaming?
Talk to her soon.
Boy, do you know your daughter well?
And do you know she's dreaming?
You know as well as I.
She stays higher than the moon.
And do you know your sister well?
And did you know she's drinking?
Do you know your sister well?
Talk to her soon.
Boy, do you know your sister well?
You know I think she's losing.
You know as well as I.
She stays higher than the moon.
You broke my heart.
She's a child.
She's everywhere I see,
my wife's wherever I see,
I yearn for where she goes.
I guess.
I'm cut out to be each other's episode of my life.
Show up the nightly radio or your sister mean.
One more message.
I'm gonna search around and keep a safe spot for you.
Twoelo.
And do you know your brother well
In the company he's keeping
Do you know your brother well
Talk to him tonight
Or do you know your brother well
He's very, very strange they tell
Probably he'll go to hell
Unless you steer him right
Thanks for the information
Thanks for no thanks
For the information
Cause information's got your number too
Yeah
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa
Well, yes, I know my daughter well
And yes, I know she's dreaming
Yes, I know my sister well
That's the way it goes
I know my sister all too well
Yes, I know she's drinking
How do I vision her
For something she already knows
And yes, I know my brother well
And the company he's keeping
Yes, I know my brother well
He sings a different tune
Oh, yes, I know my sister well
Yes, I know my brother well
I've heard it said he's queer as hell
Pray that he's in love as well
Higher than the moon
Thanks for the information
Thanks for no thanks
For the information
Cause information's got your number too
Well, thanks for the information
Thanks for no thanks
For the information
Cause information's got your number too
Oh, yes, I know my sister well
And yes, I know my sister well
Thanks for the information
You can get more about J.R. Bob Dobbs and the Church of the Subgenius from subgenius.com.
And you'll find copies of this show archived there in different formats.
You can hear more Norrell Preff by going to norrellpreff.com.
That's N-O-R-E-L-P-R-E-F dot com.
And while we're dot comming, let's praise Bob.
Hold it. I think you're going to like this picture.
Love, that Bob.
Starring Bob.
Bob.
Bob's an absolute genius.
Bob?
Where's Bob?
Well, honey, I don't know where he is, but I'll tell you this.
Wherever he is, you can be sure he's got his armor and some cute little titty.
You'd have to beat him off.
Bob.
Bob was up the creek.
Which reminds me, where's Bob?
Does he have any news of Bob?
Bob.
Love, that Bob.
Oh, Bob.
Bob, you will wear a pair of shoes.
Carry plenty of oxygen.
Bob.
He is gorgeous, isn't he?
Oh, Lord, I do just throw my fingers through his hair.
Now, here's something to think about.
Who cares?
If your love hurts you.
Please.
Do it.
Who cares?
Hurts.
Did you ever think about how important it is to.
If your love hurts you.
Head hurts.
Come out.
Hurts.
Who cares?
And here's a funny thought.
Head.
Who cares?
Do you have a bathroom problem in your house?
Eat it all.
Eat it.
Who cares?
Hurts.
There was no progress at birth.
Patients suffer with a lower level.
They are such a scann bad whore.
We are only the psychics.
I don't think it's just me.
Those of you who say I'm like that aren't faithless.
However, if that were true, there will be a limit.
Amazing.
There are devils.
There are people like just just people.
Who sayretimet.
But we just say it's a life of us this are human beings often tell us to be living out of our lives.
he shall be self-righteousness. Heaven's Lord, the body of we are lost in such folly. None of us
would build a home with special doors for each member of the family. We all use the same doors.
And of course, for which is large enough for the biggest one of the family, is large enough for
the smallest too. It is large enough to permit the biggest as well as the smallest sinner to enter
if he but come, but come, but come, come, come, come. Some doors can be entered only after a
specified entrance fee is paid. Some doors are open only certain hours of the day. Doors enable
us to seek shelter from the storms of life. It makes all the difference in the world which side
of the door we're on, the inside or the outside. Which side of the door are you on? Most doors
permit us to carry anything through them as we enter pass through heaven's door
what a joy it would be to come enter in heaven's door is still wide open won't
you enter while you may
opportunities for open wide
we go big oh yeah
we
Oh
Blackbird singing in the dead of night
Take these broken wings
And learn to fly
All your life
You were only waiting for this moment to arise
Blackbird singing in the dead of night
Or when in my mind the men come in their six black shiny ships,
do they come in your mind too?
Very funny, I agree.
Very, very, very.
Yes.
Very funny, diarrhea.
Very runny, diarrhea.
Yes.
Irritation.
In the rectum.
Constipation.
Hemorrhoids.
Married.
Constipation.
Hemorrhoids.
Married.
Irritation.
In the rectum.
It's not my job.
I am.
I'm on fucking fire.
That's the way I feel.
I don't expect to go to sleep for a year.
I'm on fucking fire.
And what we saw tonight was a physical phenomenon,
an inexplicable physical phenomenon.
That's the way I feel.
I don't expect to go to sleep for a year.
I'm on fucking fire.
I bet you don't know what to do in case of a nuclear attack.
You know what to do?
You put your hands behind your head,
put your head between your knees,
and kiss your ass.
goodbye
definition
of indecent
if it's long enough
hard enough
and far enough
it's indecent