Okay, they're watching. The audience is listening or something, recording. Everything's going fine. No problem.
Hello, Mr. and Mrs. America and all the ships at sea.
Flash, the Church of the Subgenius Festival in Wisteria, Ohio, is now raging in its third day.
Is it the third day or the fourth day?
Well, it's...
It depends on how you look at it.
According to the conspiracy calendar, this is only the beginning of the third day.
But radio-wise, this is day number five.
We've done four previous shows.
The fifth day of these award-winning subgenius podcasts.
And we're joined this time by Reverend Fox from Orlando, the Orlando Clench.
Yes, you can tell us what it's like down there.
They made money.
They did the revival.
They did the revival last Saturday.
And it was the first profitable revival in a century.
Well, you can't do it right the first time.
What did you do wrong?
Pretty much everything.
If you just kind of let everything just go and just let Bob slide into the bright holes,
then the revival just kind of fills with that natural slack cheese.
Ew.
And it's, you know...
Aren't you sorry you asked?
That slack cheese.
But there is no stigma to this slack cheese.
No, it's quite well on a sandwich.
We've been ingesting slack cheese sandwiches for the past several days up at a...
Let's table the controversial subject of sandwiches for the moment.
And now we seem to...
Bob came to a shrieking halt along with the show in its golf cart.
We should do one of these shows on a golf cart traveling around.
Yeah, we ought to.
That's...
That sounds like just the thing.
And how come they get the cart and we have to trudge our foot?
Well, because this isn't Burning Man, that's why.
Why, I ought to...
Burning Man, there's...
You can ride around on a truck doing a television show.
Yeah.
Remember on the mobile living room?
Yes, yes, we've done that.
Chuck, what's his name, sets up an entire...
Chuck Serino.
Yeah, he sets up a whole TV studio.
Well, those aren't government drones above Wisteria.
I'm pretty sure that's all private television stations.
Getting ready...
Everybody for their new fall lineup.
Secret Lives of Subgeniuses on NBC.
Everybody line up and fall.
Well, if you can tell the things in the sky looking at you are machines,
those are the ones you don't have to worry about.
A friend of mine recently informed me that when you see, quote,
hawks flying around overhead,
especially when you're driving to some little activist meeting,
that's Obama's spies.
Those are...
They're actually drones.
He just noticed hawks.
They look like they are devilishly realistic robots that look like birds.
Obama's army of hawks and vultures.
This friend...
An owl.
...was not kidding.
No, of course not.
She really felt that she was being followed around by Obama drone hawks, fake hawks.
And she had some way of telling them apart.
Oh, that was...
Real hawks only travel in pairs.
Not true.
There were three.
Of course it's true.
I read it on my Facebook feed.
It's like I have my own Alex Jones buddy.
Well...
She's real nice.
Who knows what's up there these days?
But a lot of people never looked at the skies
until they felt a certain sensation of being watched.
And then, of course...
They just want the attention.
That's what Facebook is all about.
They wish someone...
Why did they need the NSA?
There's Facebook.
Everybody's bragging.
about their every sin and treasonous act.
And shaming everyone who is possibly worthy of contumely.
Yeah, vying for Big Brother's attention, or Big Sister's attention.
Or tattletailing Little Sister.
Right, yeah.
I'm going to tell Big Brother what you did, Little Sister.
Yes, it's electronically possible now,
but fortunately one is able to put up informative posts
and take down all the ones that are less so.
There sure are a lot of people quoting Orwell now
who I'm pretty sure never read any Orwell.
Quoting?
Well, what you hear all the time is,
it's already 1984.
It's like, no, if it was 1984,
you wouldn't know what the phrase 1984 stands for.
That book wouldn't even be discussed.
All of that would have been buried.
Put down the memory hole a long time ago.
Stop snoring, sleeper.
Double plus ungood.
You can tell a real conspiracy dupe
by their overuse of the fact that
Orwell was a very bad of them.
Right.
How about Orwell's Shooting an Elephant?
That's an unforgettable essay.
Don't be so sure about that,
because I don't remember it.
Oh, really?
Yes.
You remember it, though, right, Susie?
Yes, I do.
He shot an elephant.
In his pajamas.
And what it was doing in his pajamas,
you'll never know.
But seriously, stop me if you've heard that one before.
Too late.
No, George Orwell...
The aristocrats!
...did write an essay called Shooting an Elephant.
Yes, I think it's called Shooting an Elephant.
You can Google it on your little...
Google.
Yeah, right, exactly.
Just reach in your pants and tickle your Google,
and it'll tell you everything.
And if Eric Weir had been a Canadian,
it would have been Shooting a Beaver.
Susie, you can't be on the radio show without a microphone,
and to use...
Because we only have three,
you either have to...
Take the breath, man,
and lay in next...
Get close to Dr. Howe.
She can share mine like two straws in the drugstore.
There's a...
Yeah, we've got lots of chairs.
...straw store.
Look, I'll turn up mic number two real loud,
and you guys can just both be halfway into it, okay?
Well, I see someone plastered a Monster High sticker
on this microphone.
That means it's mine.
Yes, I've been...
I've had a great time.
I got the sticker book of Monster High,
the tiny stickers,
and so if you see any implement or money,
wallets, Dobbs heads laying around
with this MH logo, the glam skull,
or these silly-looking teenage monster girls,
that's mine!
But those are sexy dames, Reverend Stang.
Aren't you...
Don't you think those Monster High girls
have something to offer in that...
Why do you think I've got them plastered on me?
You do have them on everything.
They're monsters, they're girls.
Yeah, it's...
Stang in love.
We did this already.
We did this already, though.
A couple of...
And poor Abnorm Nihil hates the Monster High.
Why?
Well, it's...
Because he hasn't seen any of the cartoons yet.
That's the only...
Well, of course, when those girls...
Hasn't bothered to check out...
...graduate from Monster High,
they'll get to go to Monster College.
Monster Sorority.
Why are they trying to ruin necrophilia
by making it cute?
You think they're obnoxious now.
Everything has to be cute to sell,
as Disney proved a long time ago,
but even the resurrected dead
are just cute teenagers
in the...
In Monster High.
Now, look, you guys...
I'm still digging up corpses to violate them
because it's just...
I object to the cutesifying of necrophilia.
It's wrong.
This is not working.
When you use the mic,
you go like this,
and when Susie does it,
she goes like this.
Well, I'm accustomed to holding it right here,
right against my lip.
Well, she's a radio professional.
That's different,
and she gives it
just a little breathing space.
If I get it too close,
the whole thing's in.
Of course, I'm here to pop the mics.
Well, we'll just have to try to deal with it,
make do, as it were.
Anyway...
Well, she's cheating.
She said she wasn't going to do any of this stuff,
and now she's doing it.
Take your shirt off!
No, no, that was just...
Okay.
There we go.
See? There you go.
But we just ruined the illusion
that we're all nude,
that we've been trying to...
She'd give you the shirt,
and she'd wear it off her back.
...foist over onto the actual radio audience.
Yes, it's true.
She absolutely just revealed herself.
Oh, no.
We've got to get rid of those things.
Those are a bad habit.
They are.
For you new people,
these got overused the last two days really bad.
For a shock radio,
there's not enough of them.
Oh, the crazy, wacky drive-time radio.
Well, we don't have to do it.
We're number one in Detroit.
And at Wisteria.
You know,
all the time.
We're on every channel.
Your best option at Wisteria.
Whatever happened to Kill Bob Radio?
DJ Shaver isn't coming, is he?
They killed it dead.
There you go.
You've got to pick your name,
your radio station carefully, friends.
Kill Bob Station, K-I-L-L.
Used to be,
whatever DJ Shaver is here,
we had...
Well, it might still happen.
You could listen to the same horrible crap
in your car while camping.
I never understood the point of that myself.
But then,
most of you don't have to look at my boss's face
all day long, every day.
I love Bob.
Yes, they do.
You get a little tired of hearing
Take Me Off to Space
over and over again.
It's like working in a supermarket
and hearing the same Muzak tunes all day.
Or the beeping of the machinery.
Or some, at Walgreens,
some set-up, stand-up sales display
that plays the music.
The same electronic jingle
over and over again.
You wonder why they have such strained
expressions on their faces.
And think of the poor parakeets
and parrots that have to live around
sounds like that.
Princess, we met a bird
that perfectly mimicked
an elevator door opening and closing.
All right.
Because it had been stationed
next to an elevator for its early life
and now it sits in a store
making elevator sounds.
Now I have to tell a perfectly true
parrot story.
Since you've brought up the parrot meme.
And this is all true.
In fact, I won't even tell all of it
because it takes forever and ever to tell.
But my sister used to have a parrot.
Now wake up, Stang.
Named Chumlee.
It was found in New York.
It had been mugged.
It was found wandering in an alley.
Actually, there's no point
to telling this part of the story.
But what part there is to tell
is that it lived a long and happy life.
And Chumlee,
many parrots have a special phrase
that they say.
And usually they say small things.
But Chumlee had a long sentence
which was,
Help, I'm trapped in a parrot's body.
Only to say it,
he had to work himself up into hysteria
to get all the syllables out.
So this parrot was constantly
squawking and shrieking,
Help, I'm trapped.
I'm trapped.
Help, I'm trapped in a parrot's body.
A parrot's body.
And so on until you threw the cover
over the cage.
Well, this parrot,
finally died of his wounds.
And my sister needed another parrot.
So she went and looked
all over the state of New York for it.
And she wanted an Amazon blue front,
which is what the late Chumlee was like.
Looked sort of like a giant parakeet.
Like a parakeet, but big.
But she couldn't find
a blue-fronted Amazon.
And finally,
near her own house,
there was a trailer park
where she found a parrot.
Which was a blue-fronted Amazon
and was quite good.
A female, unlike Chumlee.
But this parrot did not talk.
However, its life in the trailer park
had been interesting
because it could imitate
a crying, unattended baby
that was never picked up,
that lay screaming in its cradle.
And you would swear
that that baby was in the room gasping.
You could hear every detail.
It was a superb imitation.
And you would think,
Oh my God, someone do something
about that baby.
And then immediately afterwards,
there's no baby.
You can just relax.
It's just the bird.
My sister played a recording
of a laughing baby
over and over again.
So the bird would take that up.
But it never did
because a parrot picks up
what is passionately uttered.
This parrot, Gracie,
also did, in perfect fidelity,
a visit from the police.
First you'd hear the sirens coming
and then the car scrunching
on the gravel
and the bang, bang, bang
on the door
and the police radio.
People screaming
and running around.
And it took about 20 minutes
to do all that.
Well, finally, recently,
just last year,
Gracie also died.
And this was sad.
My sister also has dogs
and all sorts of animals out there,
a menagerie.
And she had a new puppy.
And Gracie had a heart attack.
Parrots do.
And so they put her
in the parrot carrier
to take her to the veteran.
And just as they did,
she did her last sound effect,
which she'd been working on,
which was the barking
of the new puppy.
And then expired on the spot.
Well, that is sad.
But here's the reason
I'm telling this whole story.
My sister couldn't stand
looking at the empty parrot cage
and decided to get another parrot.
Immediately, she heard
about an Amazon Bluefront
in a parrot store nearby.
I mean, a pet store.
So she went there
and the store was open,
but it was empty.
So she went in
and the guy seemed
incredibly glad
to see her.
And offered her
an incredible deal
on this expensive parrot.
And she was about
to go home with it.
Then she thought,
wait a minute,
something is wrong.
And they said,
yes, all right, okay.
We have to tell you,
this parrot is a disaster for us.
And we would practically pay you
if you would take it out.
Because somebody taught it
a long time ago
to scream,
fuck you,
at the top of its voice.
And it shared a roost
with another parrot.
And they would say,
and swing back and forth.
And soon they were both screaming,
fuck you,
as they swung back and forth.
Then all the birds
in the store
were taking it up.
And these old ladies
would come in
to buy a little budgie
or something
and they'd be horrified.
And they would rush
out of the store.
And the store was losing
its business.
And just as the guy
was telling this,
because he had to say,
fuck you,
all the birds in the store
did take up.
And there was a huge clash,
clatter of birds
screaming,
fuck you,
in a really angry way
at the top of their voices.
Because the parrot
will pick up
what is passionately uttered
and make that
its special work.
So she didn't get that parrot.
And I think she's got another one.
Why not?
That would be a selling point.
I would have to have that parrot.
It may still be available
if that store is still open.
I'd have to move next door
to a store
There's a YouTube,
a really sad YouTube,
video of a bird
that repeats
this abusive family argument.
Because there's passion.
Did you see that one, Susie?
It's really sad.
Yeah, it's,
you can't really
make out the words.
It's like you're hearing
a fight in another room.
Yes, they don't do the words.
They do the emotion.
This horrible, bitchy woman
goes on and on
and on and on and on.
Like the visit from the police.
And then at the very end
you hear this
beaten down male voice
kind of going
Yes, dear.
Oh.
I had a sister
with a talking bird
and I made a parrot
and parakeet training tape
in 1980
that had phrases on it
like,
I can think.
I have a brain.
Help me escape.
They make me say things.
They make me do things.
They keep me in this cage.
Please help me.
I can think.
I have a mind.
They make me say things.
And a guy,
G. Gordon Gordon
had a brain.
I sent that tape
to both of them
but they probably
neither one of them
even tried it.
So I'm glad to hear
that somebody else
taught the bird
to do that.
To the one that was
you know,
begging you
to help it escape.
What do you do
if you're left alone
with a bird like that
and it's like
the Turing test.
How do you know
that it's just been trained
to act intelligent?
And for that matter
how do any of us
know each other
as it's just been
trained to do that?
The audience don't know
that I'm just a bird
right now.
It does take away
these tropes
and what are we left with
without our tics
and responses
and tics and nats.
Exactly.
Well,
I had seen
an Attenborough program
where liar birds
were reciting
or not,
they were singing
the sounds of chainsaws.
Liar birds?
Yeah.
They ain't got a truth
a bit about them.
A truth a bit about them.
They ain't got.
The interesting thing
about the parrots
is that they often
use the words
grammatically
as they should be used.
They are using them
to communicate.
Like they'd say
hello and goodbye.
They never say goodbye
when you appear
or hello when you leave.
And Chumley would say
I'm hungry
and want to be fed.
Or he would also say
you want a bite?
Which meant that
he wanted a bite.
Right.
Yeah, my wife does that.
Would you like dinner now?
That means she's hungry.
Rawr!
As long as you're hungry,
it's okay.
Well, but maybe
we could use parrots
as a recruiting thing.
The avian brain
is more complex
than it was thought to be
just 20 years ago.
The people I know
that have owned crows
claim that they're as smart
as a four-year-old child.
Oh, corvids are super smart.
My four-year-old brain kid
plays Minecraft.
I don't know.
He plays Minecraft
and creates cow launchers with it.
I haven't seen a parrot do that.
Well, you've got to let him
out of the cage more often
and they enjoy those excursions.
Well, we don't let the kid
out of the cage.
I need more laptops for crows.
More money into
crow laptop development.
It's interesting
when the parrot
is out of the cage
and walks
rather than flying
as it walks
with its nails
clicking on the floor.
It sways from side to side
and it sub-vocalizes
like Popeye.
You can't hear
what it's saying
but...
Muttering frustratedly.
Doing that sort of thing.
It's a hilarious sight to see.
They get drunk
and act like drunk people.
Well, alcohol affects them
the same way as us.
Gordon would hold a beer
up to his big parrot,
Jasper,
and Jasper would lap it up
and half of it
would run out
the hole in its beak.
Their beaks aren't designed
to swill beer.
Right.
So he'd dribble beer out
but he'd get enough beer
that it would make
him belligerent.
He would stagger around.
His wings were clipped
so he couldn't fly
but he would stagger
drunkenly
like a cartoon character
and he'd climb up trees
and bully other birds.
Pick on them.
Oh, that's ugly.
Yeah, he was like
a nasty drunk,
Jasper was.
And you should have seen
Gordon.
Jesus Christ.
It describes a lot of people
walking around here last night
stalking with their wings up.
Oh, I had to.
Drunkenly.
Princess Wee and I,
oh, I was going to play
a piece from that.
Princess Wee and I
were up a little too late
last night
because unexpectedly
the rockers started jamming
and there was
some really good guitar playing
by the son of Sinfaltimus
and Hazel of the Windmills
and such
and the drumming was good.
And then there was
Ward Furr
playing bass
and I believe
he's never played bass.
So he was supplying
the doctor element.
But when we heard that,
Princess Wee and I
heard that and thought,
oh, that's doctor music.
It quit being a normal jam.
This is really special.
And we started singing
the Doctors for God theme.
And no one else
could hear us.
This all happened last night?
That's why, yeah,
this was last night,
but one in the morning.
Dancing to that CD player.
Everybody,
we weren't,
there were no
vocal mics up there.
Princess Wee,
I'm just going to play
about two minutes of it.
Very well.
No, really,
this is the
Six Fisted Tales of Connie,
which is every jam band
that forms at X Day,
plus Pooh Water Towel,
which is the unusual pairing
of Princess Wee
and me singing.
I don't usually do that.
This is our third song
by Pooh Water Towel.
Let's hope this plays.
Yeah, I don't know.
Yes, after this big intro.
The Doctors,
the Doctors for God.
People will sing it.
For what?
Doctors,
the Doctors for God.
The Doctors for God.
Kind of a catchy one.
The Doctors,
Doctors for God.
We're doctors,
doctors for God.
We're doctors.
We were doctors
for God.
We're Bob.
We were doctors.
I tell you, doctors.
We're Bob.
We are doctors.
Doctors.
We're Bob.
We are doctors.
I tell you, we're Bob.
We're doctors.
Yes, friends.
Next day is officially Robert.
I mean Bob.
And the music has attracted some very large-feigned face-fucking bats,
which I've been getting pelted with.
They could have had their way with me just in the middle of that song.
I had my mouth open so much.
They have widespread wings like fruit bats,
but they have the bodies of, well, other bats.
And they go right through the face.
The other thing on that CD is Wee Ma Ma and Princess Wee
doing their rude song duet.
Last night.
You probably have a better copy.
Did everyone catch that one?
That was a remarkable moment.
That's family bonding on.
Yeah, to quote my mother-in-law.
Not bad for 80-fucking-7, huh?
I couldn't believe it.
This morning she said,
Now, did I embarrass you?
I said, no, but I may have been acting like I was embarrassed to be in character.
Mortified.
How could you use that language in front of my audience, the subgeniuses?
They've never heard things like that, Mrs. Queen Mom.
So we'll go back to the monster music in the background.
Yes.
Monster high.
Oh, you seem relieved.
It's just monster movie music.
Okay, that's fine.
That's par for the course.
Just have to skip ahead.
As you know, the official academic productions of composers are zilch zero, goose egg zero, nothing, nada.
But the music that was composed for monster movies contains them.
Most impressive composing and orchestration of all 20th century music.
The true sublime is approached by these musical offerings.
And recently, a series of recordings played by the Moscow Symphony Orchestra has made many of these beloved classics of yesteryear spring to life.
Like the complete soundtrack of Castle of Frankenstein.
I have a house of Frankenstein.
Well, where do people get classical?
Well, I think it's in the music.
It's not that type music anymore.
Orchestral descriptive music outside of movies.
There's not that much going on.
From a weak classical music radio station.
Real classical music now is unlistenable doctor crap.
With a pulsating disco signal right next to it that completely overwhelms it.
Yes, the wimpy university classical music station that only plays for three hours out of every day.
The same guitar music by Julian Bream.
And that's...
That's about it for radio.
Because these are not the best times for radio.
But maybe we're going to light a fire under regulation media.
And start a new revolutionary type of entertainment.
Dr. Howell, that's called podcasting.
Oh, I do that too.
I know all about that.
Yes.
Everyone has been leaving them pogs out.
Well, I'm casting them.
In case they...
They grow.
Like certain seed-bearing capsules or fruiting bodies which catch on your trousers and then release themselves miles away.
Hey, Susie, take this mic over here.
You have...
Okay.
How did Sarah Palin get here?
My goodness.
The fox is leaving...
I can see Russia from...
Oh, well.
Well, there she goes.
That was inspirational.
And...
Sarah Palin never said she could see Russia from...
I read that five times a day on the internet.
I just have a very bad habit.
Hair-sailing.
Of skipping right to the comments.
Just skip the whole article.
Just read the comments.
But she did say she could see Russia.
I mean, the whole idea is she can deal with Russia because Russia.
I can see Russia.
It's right over there.
When I'm not killing wolves from a helicopter with a high-powered rifle, I can see Russia just fine.
And...
And they can see her.
Oh, she has remote viewing powers.
That must be it.
A lot of people believe in remote viewing.
Because the Russians thought there might be remote viewing.
The CIA tried to find out about remote viewing.
And thus we have that amazing movie, The Men Who Stare at Goats, being based on a true damn story.
It's kind of a boring movie, though.
Guys just staring at goats all through the movie.
But it's authentic.
No, you're thinking of the Andy Warhol.
Andy Warhol version.
There's also the...
Goat, it was called, yeah.
It's called Goat?
Yeah.
No, Men Who Stare at Goats was a nice, funny Hollywood version.
Then the Andy Warhol factory version is called Goat.
Yeah.
Or was that the Bales brothers?
The audience stares at a movie of a goat for 24 hours.
Well, they can be interesting.
That was big in New York in the early 60s.
In fact, they can be loathsome.
It was better than Ass, surprisingly.
A goat will always fool you.
A goat can fool you in terrible ways.
La, la, la, la.
Now, I've been doing some bird experiments.
I've been doing experiments with chickens lately.
Yes?
Just what are those?
Yes.
I've been...
A couple of hens were entrusted to my care.
And I've been carrying out experiments with them for the past month or so.
And they've already...
Their learning capacity...
It's incredible.
They've already taught me to do several tricks.
And they provide eggs?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I'm doing ass-to-mouth with chickens.
Well, that's certainly...
Did you just say you're doing ass-to-mouth with chickens?
No.
It's just my hearing.
Dang.
You're on the...
ATM.
I'm doing ATM with chickens now.
My hearing is getting so bad.
I feed them and they feed me.
It's pretty good.
It's a pretty choice.
I've never had an animal...
That gave me parts of its body to eat.
Well...
Willingly.
The trick of picking chicken is picking what chicken to pick.
Which is good because I couldn't just cut off one leg on them because they'd just be...
You know, old Bessie's down to only one limb now.
Wow.
Every ex-day that loses money, old Bessie has to lose another limb.
That's why, if you're listening to this radio program,
you need to contribute to the program.
You need to contribute to the Subgenius Foundation.
The old Bessie Fund.
To save old Bessie.
She's crawling...
She's pulling herself along using one forelimb.
The most pathetic thing imaginable.
She's really heavy.
Yeah, it's horrible to watch.
Rolling along on that improvised platform with the squeaking wheels.
Frankly, we're tired of the sight of her.
Your money can help.
Yeah, and yeah, that's one more limb and...
I don't know what, she won't be able to move herself at all.
Then we'll have to hire some Croatians to push her.
Wow.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We can't just keep her up here all the time.
And let a goat pull her.
Oh, that's good.
Yeah, let a goat do it.
The one thing that the Church of the Subgenius does have is goats.
They're all in Texas, but there's 40 or 50 of them.
And if the econocataclysm comes before ex-day, God forbid,
everybody run to Stang Ranch in Stangsville, Stang County, Texas.
I'm serious.
There's enough goats there to keep us all alive for about a month.
Yeah.
But we have to be...
And we have to, but we'll have to band together to fend off the cannibal rednecks surrounding Stang Ranch.
To band together.
We have to be better cannibal rednecks than they are, basically.
Facing the terrors of nature.
Oh, that sounds easy.
Uh, yeah.
Unfortunately, the only one who knows what he's doing is my brother.
All these movies have attacks by radioactive rednecks as part of the apocalypse.
You've got to expect this wave is coming of the desperate Pobuckers who didn't prepare,
as you did, like the ants in the fable.
And so, like a legion of maddened grasshoppers, they are upon you.
But now that we're so close to ex-day, we can reveal some of these awesome facts.
If you were just paying attention, you heard about the subgenius goat army,
which is ready to be unleashed on an unsuspecting state of...
Whoever expects an army of goats.
The war goat.
That movie is...
It's loosely based on this.
People laugh, but, you know, they've weaponized dolphins and stuff.
Yeah.
Goats can live on just about anything.
Mm-hmm.
And, uh, if you...
What's that video game where the goat simulator...
Good God, man.
Goats can do incredible, amazing things.
It's not the goat stimulator?
You made I play that whole thing the wrong way?
Well, you're not supposed to know about the goat stimulator.
There is such a thing as the...
We never got out of the barn.
It's not all punishment.
There's...
There's the pleasure principle involved, also.
I have a photograph of my niece suckling a little baby goat.
She's actually taking it out of a bottle.
I was just about to ask.
But it appears to be sucking on the pipe of the Dobbshead shirt she's wearing.
Oh, good Lord.
Well, uh...
It's the cutest little picture of a goat sucking on Bob's pie.
Do these goats get milked with any regularity?
That's kind of personal.
By the kids.
Oh.
And the baby goats.
Okay.
But not by humans.
All my nieces and nephews and the baby goats.
Yes.
Humans who milk goats can encounter a nasty surprise.
My fam...
It's not like we slaughter these goats and eat them ourselves.
We sell them and I don't know what happens.
You make them commit suicide and then...
Yeah, we play that music I just played long enough.
The goats kill themselves.
I can't hear it.
Huh?
I hear no music staying.
Oh, now I do.
Okay, well, there you go.
I'm keeping it down low.
But will the audience hear it in the future or will they just think that there's a radio
playing in the next room?
If I can hear it through these headphones, anybody can hear it.
Perhaps your headphones are differently calibrated than the headphones that the rest of us are
wearing.
The blue ones are the most powerful headphones, but I am the weak link in this tree.
Well, I tell you, you need a little bit more audible background music.
I'm guessing.
I'm guessing what you guys are saying, okay?
You said something about open the door and let the door down.
No, I said turn the music up a little bit louder so we can hear what the musical theme is.
You said something about we get some beer for the giant meme.
That's not a bad idea.
You sound like Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Either that or I'm losing my hearing.
I'm not kidding you.
It's getting to be like the world is a mad list.
He's a little hard of hearing.
Like Professor Calculus.
I hear the words, but I misinterpret them.
I hear the words are different.
I make out like every fourth word.
You can put together just about any damn thing you want.
Where do you think Church of the Subgenius came from?
Word association or nerd association or both?
Nerd association.
There was one day when we picked up one of those, Philo and I picked up one of those
giant dictionaries, the really huge ones, and just started flipping through it.
I started at random and looking for words.
There's one, epopt.
That means like a liter or a, okay, that's perfect.
It means one who is anointed.
An epopt is anointed and thus is the head of something.
And uh...
Did you just say you have a lump?
Yeah.
We read in the 23rd Psalm, thou anointest my head with oil.
And they used to do that.
The oil they would pour on the people's heads.
Actually, it contained cannabis extract.
The oil that was poured on King David's head in ancient Israel.
Now recent developments have had people who are in the religious right also performing
this ceremony.
They're so devout that they have their head anointed with oil, but they're not going to
have any marijuana-infused oil poured on their heads.
And so John Ashcroft, former attorney general, said, John Ashcroft, former attorney general,
of the United States, had his head anointed with Crisco.
Pure trans fat was poured on the head of the kneeling, blubbering attorney general designate
of the United States.
So that's how he doesn't get it stuck up there.
But, you know, people used to cook with that stuff all the time.
Now they understand it's bad for the body.
It's bad for you.
It's really bad for you.
You've heard John Ashcroft sing, right?
Yes, he was a singer.
Yeah, with Jim Jeffords, Senator Larry Craig, the restroom king, and Trent Lott.
The singing senators.
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Oh, yes, it was terrible.
Barbershop type stuff?
Well, songs of various kinds.
Religious songs?
Pop songs?
Beat songs?
You know what?
We're in the digital age.
So Google singing senators and a torrent of unseemly noise will affront your ears.
I saw a picture of them covering a live performance where they're all grooving and it's the most
egregious mincing and nobody is mincing and apparently living together.
Are they snapping their fingers as they sing?
Trent Lott looks like he's got both heels together and his knees bow-legged.
These right fingers turn out to have a...
Sort of like Gilbert Shelton drew them.
Many of them have a musical or a Terpsichorean influence.
After all, didn't the Hammer, Tom DeLay, go on Dancing with the Stars and start swirling
around it?
Right-wing ragers.
Yes, it was frightful.
Horrible.
How come none of us have been on Dancing with the Stars?
Oh, we're not stars.
Well, we've got two left feet but...
Because they're too smart.
Dancing with...
Stumbling with the subgeniuses.
We're subgeniuses.
The new reality show.
Hey, guess what?
I had the opportunity to blow off another reality show just before X Day.
And what happened?
I got an email from somebody.
It seemed kind of like a form letter.
It was, I'm blah, blah, blah with MTV's Real TV.
And we're casting for a show about people who started their own religion.
And...
Dear blah, blah, blah.
You will be proud to know that the Subgenius Foundation actually has a history of not
even talking to reality TV people.
I did write back to the Sky News.
And I said, you may want to look at our website a little closer because...
If you dweebs knew even the slightest thing about the Church of the Subgenius, you'd know
that there's this thing called X Day.
You would not.
And this is the one time of year when they cannot be contacted to appear on MTV or...
Well, I've been...
We've had brushes with snarky TV shows even before reality TV.
You and me both have had people come in and film us being subgeniuses.
And then they...
Yes.
It just makes everybody look stupid.
Them and us.
The way they put it together.
And they have the hot lights on us too from their silly movie.
There was that time you asked me if I'd show my tits we could get a Howard Stern booking.
I'm glad that fell through.
We couldn't even get booked at Howard Johnson's.
Well, you know, actually I was going to be...
I was in New York and Bleepo Abernathy was Howard Stern's engineer for years.
In fact, occasionally you'd see him.
You'd hear Stern and Robin complaining about Bill's patchouli oil.
Bill was Bleepo.
Anyway, Bill had it to...
He goes, Stang, I think I can get you into Howard's show this afternoon.
And then he called me back when we were on the way and said, forget it.
Some guy's jumping off the Brooklyn Bridge and Howard's talking him out of it.
Janer again.
Janer got it again.
No, we...
Yes.
We dodged that bullet.
And...
There have been a couple of times when out at Starwood somebody was casting, we're looking
for a show, we're going to have a show about a witch and a druid and an idiot all living
together.
Jesus.
So we've really tried to steer clear.
Typical subgenius men.
I did tell...
I told the guy, I said, if you want to...
You're interested in doing something in depth on subgenius, it's an amazing story.
We do some wild stuff and we've also got lots of footage from years and years of it.
But...
I don't think we're what you're looking for.
Because what they're probably looking for is, yep, I started this white supremacist religion
just yesterday.
We're going to build a whole city in Antarctica.
You know, that's what they're looking for.
What about the Unarius Society?
They could contact the remnants of the Unarians.
Yeah, they're still going strong.
I'm so surprised.
And they are spectacular too.
Even without Ruth Norman.
Ruth Norman was the backbone.
She cast a large shadow.
I imagine Tyrannosaurus.
Tyrannosaurus, the evil overlord, is also dead.
How do you get those suits that they wear, those space outfits that the Unarian society
wears?
Disco satin.
We should make our own version.
There's a lot of disco satin.
Yard sales, I thought.
Someone in black is calling us out.
Yeah, I think these guys were looking for the Unarians and the Breatharians and...
They were looking for people who didn't know they were a joke.
Right.
To make a joke out of them.
I actually said to the guy, we're making fun of people who don't even know that we're making fun at all.
And that makes enemies.
And it's not good television.
Honestly, it goes over people's heads.
And often it goes over the host's head.
And Maury Povich, which we played at the very beginning of this, he was actually pretty cool about it.
That was one of the few good ones.
Sure, he's seen them come and go.
Yeah.
Down in the blackness of the void.
And the very, very first TV thing about us, it was on Showtime What's Up America.
That shot at the first subgenius convention in Dallas in 1981, I think.
That one was good, but the director was a subgenius.
He was a born-again subgenius, Reverend Larry Silkus, who has a story in Three-Fisted Tales of Bob and co-wrote Ghosts of Mars.
John Carpenter's least one.
Wonderful movie.
Yeah, I didn't see that one.
The music is great.
In fact, there's a YouTube of creating the music for Ghosts of Mars.
It's much better than the movie Ghosts of Mars.
The music kicks ass.
Well, maybe you need to see the director's cut version.
I'm not interested in circumcision one way or the other, Dr. Howell.
I'm not going to get one.
You keep trying to talk me into it.
I'm not going to do it.
Do they forget that they're on Mars?
It's going to take too long.
There's that many dicks.
Can you imagine?
Yes, well, but while one is healing, the other one can be peeling.
Well, if they're circus-sized, they're huge.
If you take those Mexican sex pills, yes, they...
Spanish fly.
Irritates your urethra.
That's such old technology, Stang.
Today, they have that entirely...
Yeah, but they just use the bar pills now.
So does a bottle brush.
More of that kind of pill, Bob.
By the way, does anybody have any of those Bob pills?
I have one.
I'll take a Bob suppository.
At that Bob suppository building?
You can fit those in?
They're huge.
And the hooks just...
Why does he make them that way?
Horse pills.
Because it feels so good when they stop.
But they can't come out once you push it in.
You have to wait for it to dissolve and then work.
You have to make each hook out individually.
Well, that kind of teaches you how you're going to have to behave
when the bats come over the horizon.
This is a rough trip, Bob.
You can't just yank the face-raping bat off.
You've got to, like, lie there until the bat takes its pleasure.
And then you better have that antidote pudding.
It's only polite.
Quick.
Don't carry it.
Your antidote pudding, a glass jar,
because chances are you'll get all butterfingered
and drop it and smash just at the moment you need the pudding.
Yeah.
You'll be down on your knees trying to lap up
face-fucking bat sperm antidote pudding
while the bat's still trying to finish his job on your face.
Kids, you know, learn from the professionals.
Don't just go out into this half-assed, half-cocked.
That's how they end up after using a prairie squid without de-beaking.
But I don't have to tell you guys this.
I've got a tramp stamp on my upper palate just for the bat.
You all do have the decoder pen, so you already knew about this.
Yeah.
San Jose license plate, eh, Susie?
Mm-hmm.
You know, for the subgenius, the word conspiracy has multiple applications.
It's a conspiracy.
When capitalized as THE conspiracy,
it refers to cultural pressure to conform to the consumer norm,
to act, look, and think in a normal way,
and the growing tendency for human experience to become commoditized,
so that what was our free birthright of unmediated direct experience
can now be neatly packaged and sold back to us for a profit.
In subgenius pamphlet number one,
the word is introduced as the acronym,
conspiracy,
cliques of normals secretly planning insidious rituals aimed at controlling you.
Conspiracy.
As Revelation X explains,
and I'm not going to read it, but it's a conspiracy,
and where is Revelation X?
I don't see it for sale on our table.
Out of print.
Oh, out of print.
Well, you can still find it on the internet.
How much is it there, I wonder?
Some days it's 35 cents, and some days it's $1,000.
Well, you really have to-
Those Amazon programs kind of bounce up and down.
They're doing it on purpose.
I'm not kidding.
Yes, I've seen my own books sometimes zoom to a huge amount
and then drop to a pathetic amount.
That's when I buy them.
As Revelation X explains,
our current global crises are no accident,
and all conspiracies are inextricably interwoven,
all twined and tangled together.
You see, it's not just one little conspiracy,
like the JFK conspiracy,
or the no longer having the cool product that only you liked at the store conspiracy.
They're all the same conspiracy.
But attached in an orthogonal way,
not easily apparent to any but a trained subgenius observer.
And those all died from observing.
From looking too much into the abyss,
because the abyss looks right back and radiates their innards.
They don't talk about how good looking the abyss is,
but that's why they get stuck in there.
It's fascinating.
Why are you leaning closer?
They're so close, they fall in.
It's worth looking at.
It draws you in or out, depending on your point of view.
Not to be confused with that movie, The Abyss.
No, that was different.
Or a new abyss.
Although that has a great line about the conspiracy.
No, to you, everything's a conspiracy, hippie.
Hippie?
Everything is.
Yeah, every 80s sci-fi movie had to have one stoner character who was right.
Like The Thing had the hippie.
Yeah, Palmer in The Thing.
Who was named Palmer, who went on and on about aliens.
You've got to be fucking kidding me.
And in fact, it turned out to be true.
But these characters never seem to fare well in these movies.
To satisfy some atavistic audience desire to see hippies crushed and humiliated,
it always happens.
Oh, the black guy always gets killed too.
Toke on this, hippie.
Blam.
But his name was Hippie in that particular movie.
Yeah, in that movie, his name was actually Hippie.
It was H-I-P-P-Y.
Y, too.
And only an idiot writes it that way.
It's like Batwoman.
Thank you for saying so.
It is so.
Thank you ever so much.
That's how they spell the Batwoman title.
She was a hippie vampire.
Eleventy Meow called me an idiot for spelling it P-I-E.
Who said you were an idiot for that?
The stupidest idiot that was ever said it's $35.
Well, but it's correct.
Because when you spell it with a Y, it simply means that your pelvis is too wide.
That is not what we're talking about.
Right.
And it's a great plumper model who goes by that name.
Well, no doubt the Silbrick A in her case is well deserved.
BBW seeks BBC.
That's all it is on the internet now, BBWs and BBCs.
Wow.
Look it up, kids.
Everyone loves British television.
You'll find it hard to turn away.
I got into a discussion as to the relative merits of X-Hamster versus Red Tube and Aloha Tube.
Those are free.
They're free giant faucets of pornography.
They're free.
It's like they're...
What's the slogan?
No ads, no bullshit, just porn all the time.
And how does a hamster figure into this?
How does a hamster figure into it?
They never found the hamster.
Well, it's X-Hamster.
Oh, a former hamster?
They've never been able to get him out.
Yeah.
They're still up in there.
This is supposed to be entertaining?
Aloha Tube is another one.
But yeah, you can watch Pobuckers in their trailer courts having fun.
Sex with each other.
I try not to think about that.
No, it's hilarious.
It's great.
I can't drive through the rural parts of the country anymore without thinking, did I see
them doing a three-way in that trailer court on X-Hamster last week?
If that trailer's a rocket.
Porn has ruined porn for me.
Not everybody seems to enjoy watching amateur pornography.
I'm not talking about the professional stuff.
That's fake.
They need a cameraman.
They can't use their hands because one hand is holding the camera.
Right.
That's terrible.
You want the pornography that's filmed like a selfie.
No, you don't because it's-
I do.
Oh, all right.
Yeah, don't get very- I want the amateur stuff.
I want the real thing.
The ones with the ugly people.
The real people.
The for real down home.
Bulldaggers, cocksuckers, motherfuckers.
Well, look at it this way-
The subgenius porno.
You want to see famous performers or famous subgeniuses and so forth, but with such unrelenting
close-ups, it might be anyone.
It might be somebody from a gas station.
That's what I'm looking for.
The real thing.
You know, remember I was on a kick of looking at microbes through a microscope for about
three years.
That's right.
What happened to that anyway?
Some difference.
I just switched from a microscope to-
Have you retired your microscope?
You no longer-
... tend to nonstop-
... view the sex lives of animals-
Same thing.
... in a drop of water.
You could watch these hideous squamous creatures having sex-
Now you're talking.
... and they'd simply divide.
Yeah.
Or you could watch a microbe.
But on the internet, you can likewise watch hideous squamous things having sex.
They happen to be human beings.
But it's almost as interesting in an anthropological way as looking at the animalcules was.
Have you ever looked for and found dinosaur sex or pterodactyl sex?
Only with sports cars.
Yes.
Yes, I have.
The performers wear the costumes and in the pterodactyl sex when the guy flaps his wings
all during it-
Oh no, I haven't seen that.
I can't masturbate.
They're-
With the tiny arms, yes.
So they have the-
Yeah, poor Tyrannosaurus Rex.
Yeah.
It makes them angry and fierce.
That's why he's so ferocious.
You can tell they used to beat off all the time and they're still beating off.
But they can't beat off the guy, so they're not doing that anymore.
If you can't get them and God punish them by giving them those little stubby arms that
wouldn't reach your hoses.
Their arms have a different function.
And their arms contain the-
To a Christian, that's proof of the Lord.
The finger, the forefinger and the thumb.
This is the Tyrannosaurus's arm.
The first digit is digit number one.
The second, number two.
And the reptiles lose during the evolutionary process the other three fingers.
They're not pronated like this.
They're more like this, so they catch like this.
So they're clearly good for something.
They're like that, though.
They could hold one of those beer glasses.
They could hold something, and it's been estimated that they have the powerful strength of a muscular man,
which is not much for a dinosaur, but we're talking about tiny little arms in the front.
They put toes on them, and he could hold a beer glass.
They had to feed each other hits.
With his toes.
Another reason why birds can't be dinosaurs is because...
Why reach the joint like that?
Bird arms lose the fingers from the other side,
and embryologically it's not possible for a feature once lost to be completely regrown genetically,
something which is known as Dallow's principle.
So with the avian hand, you lose this finger first, then this finger,
and the bird wing is based on the remaining finger.
So that's the bird because these two fell off?
Well, you could put it that way.
That's another thing a Tyrannosaurus couldn't do.
No, a Tyrannosaurus couldn't do that.
Could not flip you off.
No, not flip you off.
It would be doing the equivalent of that.
Doing the Lindy Hop, which was large and earth-shaking.
Pity the poor two-fingered Tyrannosaurus.
Two beans has the solution.
How it happened.
It's the wrong finger going up, but that's the best he can do.
So you see...
So the world of science brings us so many open doors and windows and toilet lids...
For people to throw their garbage through.
...for the subgenius radio's ministry hour of slack, which is coming up on the end of an hour.
Yay!
Thank goodness in about five minutes.
That's right.
All that means is I've pushed off...
One hour closer to the end of the world.
I know it's going to come this year.
This hour flew by, and we hardly began.
When there were so many wonderful things we could have told you,
if we hadn't frittered it all away, talking of inconsequential subjects.
But if you'll stay tuned...
We're going to tell great truths.
Yeah, we'll tell those all right.
And great useful things.
Yeah, we'll do that, yeah.
You better make a note of it.
Please, make a note of it.
Because we'll probably get distracted by some old monster movie.
Like what you really need to put on that rash.
Some weird fact of zoology.
Some tangent.
Or a comic book.
Yeah.
No wonder this church never gets quite as far as science.
And that's a good thing.
They don't get distracted with the comic books.
And monster movies.
They just strictly focus on being fucked up idiots.
Well, they have to be the originators...
We're all half-assed, fucked up idiots.
...of all their propaganda.
And we gladly take what fits into our picture from anywhere we can get it.
So we are better syncretists than Scientologists.
Nor do we insist on our specific doctrine being accepted.
Because, in fact, we are.
And any thing, any old thing that any old subgenius proclaims is instantly immutable subgenius doctrine.
But then there's also the sacred doctrine of erasability whereby the subgenius can later come back and go,
No, I didn't say that.
That was stupid.
I'm gonna rub you out.
No, we don't misspeak.
We've got something in place that just eraditates it.
Yeah.
Speaking of sacred doctrine of erasability, and this will all come...
...clear later.
For those who manage to be awake when the world ends at 7 a.m., which I can tell you right now is less than half of you that I'm looking at right now.
You get a...
You will get whether...
No matter what happens, I've got a special prize for you.
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
Well...
Actually, we have several special prizes for the...
They're so special.
...those who make it.
And we're trying to lure you down there.
Although we had a pretty good turnout the last couple of times.
That's right.
The one thing...
The one...
I'm beginning to think...
Actually, Dr. Dark noticed this.
What is the one thing that has been in common every X-Day for 20...
This will be the 20th time.
Stang.
Stang has been there apologizing.
And Dr. Dark.
Oh, yes.
And Dr. Dark making puns.
Dr. Dark and me are the only two people that have been at every single one.
You've been...
You've only missed one.
I missed one.
I missed 2004.
Yeah.
And...
I'm only half a woman.
Oh, now.
Wow.
You're at least five-eighths.
Hey, it's a top hat.
Everyone can enjoy that.
Oh, five-eighths.
Easy.
I take a seven and five-eighths.
Anyway, it's like maybe this year...
Y'all would understand if Dr. Dark and I...
It would be to help ensure the saucers coming if Dr. Dark and I just simply...
Could you be the reason they're not coming?
...slept in or laid in bed up at...
He's in an RV and I'm renting a bed and breakfast.
Oh, gee.
Shameful, shameful, shameful.
For a few slothful moments of slumber.
I'd stay...
I'd wake up for the saucers, of course.
You would give up your birthright for a massive...
But I'd set the alarm to go off at five till seven and I wouldn't have to drive down the
You'd give up your stateroom on the saucer for steerage just so you can snooze and slumber.
No, no.
I'm trying to guarantee that the saucers come by sacrificing.
I so love...
You know, I only have to get up that early once a year.
Behold, he that keepeth Israel shall neither slumber nor sleep.
But I'm trying to get out of even that.
And it's...
It's...
I'm doing it for you.
But I know that...
What sleazy, sinusoidal slumber.
The one thing that they all want to see at 7 a.m. if it...
They prefer to see saucers.
But if they can't see saucers, they damn well better see Stang humiliated.
Well, they might see stars.
And let's hope that doesn't happen this time.
Yes, no one wants that.
I've gotten pretty good at it, though.
I'm sad to say.
No one wants to see Stang crawling and backsliding and trying to explain and...
Take it out on that.
Nobody likes that.
That's why this dummy is here.
That is the real goat.
You want to know why a goat?
We have to have one to draw off malefic thoughts of frustration, bitterness...
Just as I need you here to get the mosquitos...
Keep mosquitos off of me.
Because you're so delicious, Dr. Brown.
I know.
I got everything that they need as part of their nutritious breakfast.
They shun the blood of Stang.
Now, this says, Stang keeps the subgenius concept of conspiracy free.
And he's fresh with his satire on those conspiracy theorists that believe mass shootings like
Sandy Hook are part of an elaborate Obama-slash-Illuminati hoax to seize guns and invoke martial law for
the New World Order.
Comments?
Yes.
That's just a yes answer.
Yeah, but, I mean, you're supposed to have comments on this new piece of provocation
from the academic world.
This so-called dissertation on the Church of the Subgenius here, entitled, Rhetorical
The Church of the Subgenius, Kenneth Burke and Comic Symbolic Tinkering.
Hey, it worked.
Reverend Lee Cipher got his doctorate off of that thing.
Well, you see...
Doc!
Turn your head and cough.
Go figure.
Hey, oh, I have a comment.
We were ending the show.
Oh.
This is...
This has been our Slack number 1500 blah, blah, blah, blah.
And subgenius.com.
And we can cut to the baby bear thing after that.
And I'm gonna stop this.
Stand by.
Now that'll halt the little bastards.
Oh, is this on?
Two, one.
It's on.