When I started to learn how to walk, you said, don't keep trying, give up.
When I got frustrated because I couldn't tie my shoes, you said, don't keep trying, give up.
When I didn't make the baseball team, you said, don't keep trying, give up.
And now, I say to you, keep trying, marijuana.
You can get free drugs.
To learn how, call 788-A-MESSAGE from ONDCP and the Partnership for a Free Drug America.
This is the Institute for Motivational Research.
A place devoted to the intriguing business of finding out why people ticked her.
Why should we fear anything?
That's right, there are four stages in a butterfly's life.
Egg, the caterpillar, the chrysalis.
Bob.
Bob Bob Bob
The Hour
of Slack
Well my friend, listen.
The Spirit of God
make you all
a straight line.
Not a line,
straight line.
Straight line,
line,
straight line,
life,
spiritual,
man,
spirit,
guaranteed.
This is
a very important statement.
I want you to hear it.
The internet
made me so goofy
and lethargic
where I couldn't think,
I couldn't study,
I couldn't control anything.
I was just like,
marriage,
bad news.
If you were in here
this morning
and you're dealing
with the internet
and you're hiding it
and you think you're doing
a good job of hiding it,
you're not hiding it
from the Lord.
And it's corrupting you.
Well no,
I've got it under control.
Because Jesus said,
this is how you deal with it.
Fornication
and pornography.
Yes.
Uncleanness
and lack of
licentiousness.
Yes.
Gushing
and there's
sexual pus
and junk
all coming out of it.
That's his desire.
To be sexually
oozing
24 hours a day,
7 days a week.
Licentiousness.
Just unbridled,
uncontrolled
sexual excesses.
That was something
he invented.
Next is
worshipping
oozing
sexual excesses.
Can you worship
your brand new
shiny sexual pus?
You bet.
Can you worship
fornication?
Yes.
And in our society,
how easy it is
to worship pornography?
So much.
What do you think
will psychiatry help?
Yes, it's an emergency.
.
Download some
rock bitch videos, folks.
Go to your,
go to whatever file sharing
you're doing before
they make it illegal.
.
I mean description
can be found
that you can
make up your own
description.
It's mouse over
and windows pop up
to tell you exactly
what you're about
to do.
download and everything.
It's very handy, I think.
Just think how you've archaicized our language
with what you just said.
I am seduced by the UI of it all.
See, once again, your parlance
is like 21st century, Daddy-O.
I can't hip to that.
Did you hear what he just said?
What he's saying is that the artists shouldn't get any
recompense for their work, but that we
should all get everything for free
while we can, which is certainly what I'm doing.
I have downloaded
everything. I could
possibly even see
to download, whether I wanted it, whether
I cared about it, just because
I could. Just to keep my computer
busy and to feel like I was getting my money's worth
for that DSLR.
I don't care if it's child pornography.
Well, actually, I wouldn't. I would not
knowingly download child pornography
because if you have ever
had it on your machine, he will come
and
puff and puff and blow your door down.
How about let's
take a little trip over to the door
here where it says,
Arbacht Marked Fry, or something like that.
Arbacht Marked Fry.
It's funny, the subgeniuses were asking,
how do I permanently erase stuff
from my hard drive? I mean, I know that just
throwing it in the trash and hitting delete
doesn't really do it.
And in fact, you have to overwrite
that thing two or three times
if you want to hide something.
Now, I'm just
the opposite. It's like, I wish
somebody would pay attention to the
cool stuff on my hard drive.
And that is the problem. No one is
interested. And that is
the sour slope we've slipped down
from the orchard heights. The only way you can get that
child porn off your web
your computer is blow up your
hard drive. Now you take the hard drive
out and have it installed
as one of the heat shield
tiles on the shuttle.
Next to the sock drive. And when it comes back
in through, it finally gets erased.
And they come back through the atmosphere.
But that's only during the touch-up
cycle. That's what Pee Wee should have,
done. Yeah. Twice. That's what he should have
done twice. And what did he do the first time?
Nobody knows that. The whole space shuttle,
all those tiles are really hard drives
of people trying to get rid of their porn.
That is probably
true. Because now
Big Brother can stick his snoot right up
your snoot. They're going to make a big old
bonfire out of it. A huge
Arbite mixed fry bonfire
where there'll be a lot of galopping and goose dumping.
That means work shall make us free, right?
Doesn't it? And isn't that true, though?
Doesn't work really make you free? Especially if you're
slaving away for some jackbooted
swine. Yeah, like Bob
Dobbs. That's who I've been
slaving away for all week.
I kind of dig it, actually.
It's not a bad job. Doesn't pay anything
at all. You have to pay them, but
it's kind of cool.
Sure, man.
I love you.
Put them down now.
What am I doing?
I'm in a
trash.
Pick them right away.
Trash.
I will
kill you.
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen, to this edition
of the 700 Club. I'm ready
to pull the trigger.
So that's what we're looking at.
A lot of blood being spilt all
over the place.
And I think that this is going to be
nasty.
With us today is a man who is just a
sleaze.
And he's going to
be a real pain in the ass.
And the reason they wouldn't kill him
was because he had the checkbook.
Before we get into that, let's see what's
in the news today.
Here's a French elf.
Thank you, Pat.
Most Americans say they're looking to
invade Iraq within a month.
But the French elf had to come over and
over and over again.
Up close and personal.
And that would be pleasant.
Photos of Iraqi officials moving in and out,
in and out, in and out, in and out.
Uh...
Come to have plenty of partners.
It's the way it is.
Which offers these words of praise.
This is a disgrace.
In and out.
Uh...
Come.
And then I will kill myself.
Uh...
Oh, yes, baby.
A little bit of ESO.
Swamp radio from WCSB Cleveland.
And before and after that, the great Fernanda Nande-Liemer,
who did the Bob song there and the cut-ups.
All those cut-ups.
Well, except for the El Queso title song.
We love the El Quesos, friends.
And welcome to Hour of Slack 879 of a sexy theme.
Generally the same.
Last time, friends.
Very generally.
And coming up, lots of sexy-liemer.
Chop, chop, chop.
Sexy, fat, hairy white.
Some cuts from the good Reverend Cheatham in Australia.
And...
Bug porn.
Yes, bug porn and some wild rice butt will also be on the schedule.
Uh...
Nevertheless,
there are no weapons of mass white rice butt.
That information will make its way to President Ashley.
Okay, Chris, okay.
You would say buttocks.
I think that's buttocks.
Um...
Buttocks.
Butt.
And, oh, by the way,
it's God that gives you money.
Or that new automobile that you need
if you call
in the next 15 minutes.
I only have the golden medallion.
It will remind you of the scripture.
Thou shall remember.
It's God that gives you wealth.
Or he gives you money to get wealth.
And now, make that call.
Hallelujah.
Prayer.
Make that call.
Hallelujah.
All right.
Like that.
Yeah.
Now.
Thanks a lot, dude.
You're the best.
Thanks a lot, Tony.
Take care all the way.
All right, all right.
All right.
Don't miss your next video.
I'll see you all then.
Bye, everybody.
Bye.
Bye!
Bye, everybody.
Stretch, two, three, four
And pull, two, three, four
Step it up, and three, four
Feel the burn, two, three, four
No pain, no gain, and three, four
And touch those toes, and three, four
I'm working out
I'm working out for my lady
Oh yeah
I'm working out
I'm working out for love
Hey, talking about working out, you know, I like to keep my body in shape
You know, the shape of a barrage balloon
That's how all my very sexy lady friends like it
You know, big and firm, with plenty to grab hold of
Anyway, to get myself an even better knee
You know, I got in with one of the experienced weight trainers down at the gym
You know, private tuition
Greg, his name is
Big muscle-bound bloke with blonde hair
When I first saw him in the changing room, I was gobsmacked
I don't think I'd ever seen such a big member in there before
And you're talking about a membership of 600, you know, he's massive
His very sexy lady friend, Debbie, used to train there too
Now, she happens to be a very keen weightlifter
Likes nothing more than to show off her weightlifting techniques with the barbells
I tell you what, I've never seen a woman jerk one like it in all my life
Mind you, her snatch was very disappointing
And personally speaking, I thought it looked a bit messy
Now, fortunately for her, Greg was always at hand to sort her out
He'd usually stand in front of her and make sure she got a firm grip of it when she went down, you know
Great to watch, he was
Particularly when she'd puff her cheeks out and, you know, push it up as far as it would go
Well, Greg was a great trainer
Really keen to get stuck in, you know, get on the job
He was a very hard man, you know, but he was behind me all the way
Getting stuck in
And that's what I like
Because, you see, I've always been keen on that
I had a job at a sports centre once, did I tell you?
That's where I met Geraldine, right?
We were both working there
She was a very sexy young lady friend of mine
Both working at the sports centre
And I was moving some of the Fiverside football equipment
When I accidentally emptied my ball bag in the corridor just outside her office
Well, she heard the commotion and caved straight away
You know, to give me a hand
Now, after that, I didn't see her for ages
Because I spent quite a time working at the Firkin Fudge Company
Where I got on really well with my fellow fudge packers
Hey, the laughs we had filling each other's boxes
You know, with rubbish and all that
So often, the box had to be cleaned out
Before you could start all over again, you know
Great days
Anyway, from there, I went to Jessop's, the grocer's
And that's where I bumped into Geraldine again
I was just packing the fridge full of margarine
When she walked up to me, tapped me on the shoulder
And asked me if I'd give her the stalk that I had in my hand
Well, she said she usually had flora
But thought she'd try a different brand of it
And for a change
So, stalk margarine it was
Well, after that chance encounter
We started courting
And nine months later, we decided to get engaged
Hey, I tell you what
I just couldn't wait to get down to the jeweller's
You know, to get something special for her
To slip onto the third finger of her left hand
I tell you what
When I went home and gave it to her that night in bed
She was absolutely ecstatic
The thing was
She said she'd never expected me
To present her with such a sparkling ring
Then, after pushing her finger towards it
She wriggled it in slowly
Until it would go no further
I'll never forget the look on her face
When she smiled at me and said
It fitted like a glove
Well, unfortunately, the relationship didn't work out
You know, but that's life
And, you know, you win some, you lose some
The way I look at it
There's always another very sexy lady friend around the corner
If you keep yourself in shape
And that's why I'm working out
Yes, working out
Working out
I'm working out for my lady
I'm working out
A fat, hairy white, dear friends
The great, fat, hairy white
And now
Le-le-le-le-le-mil
But why do squirrels need to survive in the wild?
They need to starve
In the wild, they're nuts
And that requires a lot of effort
So where's the best adorable, ravenous rodents?
How about Squirrel City?
Sneaky squirrels also show their cities all over our world
She learned to run this assault course by trial and error
She's only thirteen
But it took her a few days
This certainly did fail the thinking test
As we'll see, the squirrels is a free lunch
So the arms man began as Evermore to try to stop them from stealing birds
Some people, they
As the distance of time
And they may try to
To stop them
Baby
These little guys
They're
Mary
And Justice
This boy
We'll never
Get
Have
Moری
Cheese Jr.
Oh, oh, yeah.
Oh, oh, yeah, yeah.
I understand.
My breasts expand.
And I've had that syndrome for like 25 years now.
Wow.
Expanding breasts.
I'll be perhaps in the laboratory working on my works or my later obara, as they call them.
Or I'll be bowling.
Or just like trying on a pretty skirt with a poodle on it.
And the next thing you know, my breasts will start expanding as big as the sun.
Is that what that huge shadow was that covered it?
Yeah.
I can do more than cast a shadow.
It wouldn't take quarters.
I can hire one if they know what to say.
I wanted, that's all I wanted was chocolate.
Casting is easy.
I just wanted some hot chocolate.
You just look at their faces.
You look at their feet.
You see if they're right for the part.
I've been very naughty.
You know our love was special.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Like a million suns.
I said I'd buy you a sailboat, baby.
Then we could see the world again.
Just you and me.
We had a love we said would never die.
But now it's time to say goodbye.
We had a love that grew its wings to fly.
Now you have to dry your crying eyes.
Try your crying eyes.
How many eyes are gonna cry tonight when I say goodbye to my potato?
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh.
Tell me what you want me to.
Tell me what you like.
Tell me what you need me to.
How many eyes are gonna cry tonight when I say goodbye to my potato?
More than one brown eye is gonna cry tonight when I say goodbye to my potato.
Yeah.
Oh, oh, oh.
I treat you like a queen, you meant more than the world
Take you to the finest shop, stress you like a girl
And peel your panties off, yeah, we can do it like that
Baby, feels like all night, so tight, dynamite
But then I had to push you out and things wasn't the same
Your love was wild, now it's tame, baby
I don't want to see you cry
So I have to let my colon say goodbye
P. Diddy loves his potato dearly
That ain't a worship, most sincerely, baby
Come on, yeah, you know it feels so right
But I love you more than anything
Now I know I don't feel so right
And the seagull stole my toupee
The day I decided I would have to say goodbye
I don't want to see you cry
And I lied when I cried, it was not for you
But out of fear that I had disrespected my rectum
And that's not hip-hop
How many eyes are gonna cry tonight
When I say goodbye to my potato?
More than one brown eye is gonna cry tonight
When I say goodbye to my potato
Potato
How many eyes are gonna cry tonight
When I say goodbye to my potato?
That sweet potato
Potato
How many eyes
by the LK
So don't stand up
All-Stars, dear friends, the greatest of all the new school subgenius bands.
And you can download more El Queso All-Stars under the other name of Interbulator at station.mp3.com
slash interbulator, that's spelled E-N-T-U-R-bulator.
And now, our how-to department.
Really, the only way to get rid of child pornography is to fill your computer up with adult pornography
all the way until it's completely maxed out.
It won't take anything else.
Erase all that, then fill it up again with adult pornography, and you're clean.
You're fine.
Everything's cool.
Animal sex.
You know, you're like Hooters.
Bug porn.
Or late night TV.
I have mine loaded with bug porn.
Wouldn't that creep out like a cop if he came into your house and seized your computer
and found out you just had millions and millions of pictures of bug porn?
Well.
And they were all the same one?
That freaked him out the last time.
Bug porn, one dollar.
And ten.
Bug porn.
One dollar.
How hard it is to escape the constant clamoring of insect pornography commercials.
Yet.
To those who see through different eyes, the world is not what it appears to those less attentive.
To some few discerning ones, even God's tiniest creatures can be seen to indulge ceaselessly
in mindless microcosmic reiterations of man's eternal battles and his passions.
Between viruses, bacteria, and our own immune systems, as above is so below.
And some see below the belt of the allowable, deep beneath the underclothing of the forbidden.
Some see into the microconspiracy behind the macroconspiracy.
And some like what they see.
But just as in our so-called human world, the winner takes all.
For only the winner's genes are passed on to future generations.
Yes.
The conspiracy rules is the rule of the universe.
The world is now a place where the unknown is the world.
Now, maintained in artificial wounds, aided by technology only guessed at by earth science,
what might have remained the errant seed of harmless bug porn enthusiasm, grows instead
into the all too familiar larval stage, then to a pupa, and finally into a perfect clone
simulacrum of your child.
Your neighbor.
Your boss.
Your spouse.
All those people shopping at the mall.
From the tiniest, most seemingly harmless conspiracy, to bigger conspiracies, to the
final conspiracy.
Dobbs Co.
Bringing slack to the slackless, and life to the lifeless.
And the Bible says your body is the temple.
He lives, the Holy Spirit lives, in your body.
God can get the glory out of your body when your body is the temple.
Well, isn't that special?
Oh, oh, oh, God.
Oh, yes.
Well, isn't that special?
Oh, oh, oh, God.
Yes, it is!
Listen to this song.
Years of this candidates
haftly day to day talk beefed up in direction, there's only hope in god restore our situation.
What prophet would do?
Hells crease.
Where are youНАЯ usted?
Who's check?
And I am well pleased.
If God didn't want us to play with these rats, why didn't he make them savage men?
The female body is the most beautiful thing in the world.
I've been having bad thoughts.
Really bad thoughts.
Most people confuse evil with their own trivial lusts and perversions.
Two-legged devils, you own your way to hell.
Well, two-legged devils, sinners can get themselves an awful mess.
Every Christian is sinless.
Are you a saint or a geron?
Could it be Satan?
The only normal and natural and spiritual thing to do is what we ought to be doing all the time.
Holy cow!
Oh!
Oh, God!
Wow!
We're just a little buttercup, aren't we?
Every Christian is sinless.
Two-legged devils, you own your way to hell.
Two-legged devils, you own your way to therefore.
Whoa!
Two-legged devils, you own your way to hell!
Two-legged devils, you own your way to hell.
Two-legged devils, you know your way to hell.
He lives!
The Holy Spirit lives in your body!
the Holy Spirit who lives in your body.
Here's a cheap%
each like water crane Com some people
よ الل daを
Your body is the temple!
Are you a sinner, God?
Every Christian is sinless.
The only normal and natural and spiritual thing to do
is what we ought to be doing all the time.
The Holy Spirit, the what?
I'm going to put it in one hole and then in the other.
I'm going to do it really fast.
Who Sins of the Flock by Reverend Ed Fred.
And now, some ESO Swamp Radio from WCSB Cleveland.
He loved her butt.
He hated her cooking.
Do you feel different?
We have placed some leaves and pieces of newspaper under your seat,
Mr. Goss.
Gus Grissom.
Ready to blow off?
We will begin counting you now.
One.
Backwards from ten.
Ten.
Nine.
No, I'm afraid we're about to ignite you.
You can't get out.
No, no chance.
It's New Year's Eve and you're going bye-bye.
Where?
Did they?
Did they go to the...
Did they go to the moon or did the moon come to us?
Did you see that moon?
Go away.
Nobody ever walked on the moon.
They ran around in circles, ate dog treats and...
changed phone numbers.
But no one ever walked on this moon or any moon you know about.
Blow up!
You see, as artists, we just need to express ourselves.
Mm-hmm.
Go, Wyatt.
You're so funny.
Whoa, Davey.
Hello there.
I'm George Putnam.
I'd like to begin with a fact.
It is this.
Obscene literature is a $2 billion a year business.
That's $2 billion.
For 800 distributors.
It is big business.
This traffic continues to increase and flourish.
It is profitable business.
Through this material, today's youth can be stimulated
to enter the world of homosexuals, lesbians, sadists,
masochists.
Big business.
It's smart.
It's thrilling.
It provides kicks.
It encourages children to use the library.
It's an illustrated, detailed course in perversion.
It can be obtained by writing to Perversion for Profits.
Box 12, Cincinnati, Ohio.
You got here the ladies' stockings, panties, bras, that stuff?
I'm away.
Okay.
We start on pictures?
All yours.
You shall be put to death.
You want to try it, Poki?
We're sorry.
Love me tender, love me sweet.
Mmm!
Never let me go.
Sorry.
You have made my life better.
I'm alive, please.
I'm dying to love you so.
Visit the SAC bar now.
Love me tender, love me true.
Now.
All my dreams fulfilled.
No employees.
Follow my darling.
I love you.
No inventory.
I'm dying to love you.
I always will.
And no selling.
I'm dying.
I always will.
Your call cannot be completed and dialed.
No, thanks.
I prefer grass.
At San Quentin.
The A&P!
A friend of yours always travels with him to the A&P.
My church's bus is snowing!
No need for sightseeing!
And me with Iverson.
If anything I ate will burn?
Nope.
Fuck!
I've had enough of your fucking left wing elbowing!
Stop the fucking 하지만in'!
Bis Castle got the joker!
She shows she's alright by fighting off the crane mechanism.
Nope! That's wonderful!
This lecture was presented on June 1st, 1962.
By Fernanda Nande-Lemore.
The
Patti versus the mere Humes is the name of that musical composition by Heart Ignition.
Yes, the same Heart Ignition who does that incredible artwork on Alt.Binary Slack.
And now, Michael Pepe.
Did you know that the Boston Strangler used to chase Michael Pepe around the park?
Well, that's true.
When he was a kid.
I was surprised.
You know, he strangled everyone but me.
And I was going to speak out.
Really?
What happened?
What happened to the caller?
Did the caller leave?
And also, Michael Pepe did a sex show as a teenager to make money and didn't know that you weren't supposed to actually do sex.
This now can be said.
My parents are my last son.
And so, yeah.
I guess the guest caller.
I was good, but it was very cheap.
And how much money did you make?
You had to be there 11 hours a day and you got like $100 or something.
It wasn't...
That's pretty good money for those days.
1978.
Yeah.
Just...
Just before you moved out here.
Sorry, 70...
I'm sorry.
$100.
Early 70s.
It was about $6 back then.
Yeah.
It was actually $75, $76.
And...
Yeah, $100 back then.
Make a cheer, man.
$100 back then was worth about $5 now.
And listen to maniacs.
It cost $5.
Yeah.
This is when I went insane.
To be on the show in America today.
$100 today is worth about $20 tomorrow.
I realize it.
It's a hangout at donut shops.
$20 now is worth about...
It's only worth about 3 cents a hundred years from now.
$40.
I'm worried about people writing down what you say.
Now, didn't Pee Wee Herman also do that for a living at one point?
Yeah, he kind of came down as well.
There you go.
That's right.
We're waiting for you, boy.
But now, the real Wild Young Gypsy Girl is about to start.
It is unlikely that a Wild Young Gypsy Girl like this will ever be made again.
But this is the Wild Young Gypsy Girl who will film it now.
The real drivers are in the Wild Young Gypsy Girls.
And the command force of Wild Young Gypsy Girls.
Records every second of the action from the Wild Young Gypsy Girl.
But now, it is unlikely that a Wild Young Gypsy Girl like this will film it.
Now, the camera's roll as the actual Wild Young Gypsy Girl is not the same unique Wild Young Gypsy Girl as the repeated Wild Young Gypsy Girl.
All the excitement of the same Wild Young Gypsy Girl.
The spectacle.
The grand adventure.
The real Wild Young Gypsy Girl.
But now.
Can you imagine an entire opera being built around Mary Magdalene?
Viel près de María Magdalena.
Núως.
Goen by El這 Beispiel Anto Audience Come by El antonino if you like
Awwivido por el sueño
Is a prostitute?
Fast forward
A time when God loves theHow do you get from heaven to hell?
How do you get from heaven to hell? fatherrucking death life? coming back to earth
It adds so much more excitement to bring in a street-walking prostitute and have her say
as she does in Superstar.
That feels nice.
I don't know how to love him.
He's a man.
He's just a man.
And I've had so many men before.
Really?
Mary Magdalene.
Mary Magdalene was a prostitute.
Should I bring him down?
Should I?
Should I speak of love, let my feelings out?
I want him so.
Really?
Let me try to cool down your face again.
I'm sorry.
I'm built too few problems I can't answer or touch and yet you insist on my总裁 to
Do you agree?
Mary Magdalene.
Mary Magdalene was a prostitute.
Should I bring him down?
Should I speak of love, let my feelings out?
I want him so.
Let me try to cool down your face a bit.
That feels nice.
So nice.
Mary, that's good.
Mary Magdalene.
Mary Magdalene was a prostitute.
Really?
Mary, Mary, Mary, Mary, Mary, Mary, Mary, Mary, Mary.
Mary Magdalene was a prostitute.
I don't know how to love him.
He's a man.
He's just a man.
I don't know how to love him.
That feels nice.
Mary Magdalene by the Jelly Eaters.
What are you going to teach me first, Master Kwan?
Inspirational music that is absolutely riveting.
See for yourself.
An angel appeared to Mary on a glittery cloud of angel wings.
This angel brought fair Mary news.
You'll give birth to the King of Kings.
Well, Mary gasped and Mary stared.
She'd never seen an angel and she was scared.
The angel said, my virgin maid, there's no reason to be afraid.
The angel smiled.
My virgin child, you've been touched by the Holy Ghost.
Above all women, you've been blessed.
Be a nut.
And now, friends, you're hearing in the background the amino acids who played in our Akron revival.
You can hear more of them at TheAminoAcids.com.
That's www.TheAminoAcids.com.
That's the amino acid.
TheAminoAcids.com.
Kes Vidolav gemacht jut minion.
Kes Vidolavatie doch vooral.
guitar solo
Betty, I'm afraid I can't make this living, eh?
Ask them later anyway.
Got a dozen diamonds in the paper.
Oh, gosh, what a bunch of...
I have a list of folks to interview.
Say they saw you flying saucer last night.
That's when the mic's all dead?
The Amino Acids.
Now, Dave, you've converted to the Church of the Subgenius, is that correct?
Oh, well, there's no...
There's no conversion table involved.
You just take one cup of metric water...
Right.
...and place it in some boiling pans...
Okay.
...add three pounds of metric salt...
I see.
...and there's your conversion table right there.
Well, that's pretty amazing.
I didn't think it was that easy.
Well, you...
Actually, you also have to spend 30 bucks.
Now, Reverend...
You have to be born that way and spend 30 bucks both.
You can just spend the 30 bucks.
Now, I'm more interested in that loophole.
The one loophole...
...that you're actually having...
...having sex at 7 a.m. on July 5th.
You don't have to pay the 30 bucks.
What?
I think you said that.
I found that in an old tape.
I think that loophole had hair around it.
That's how he found it.
No, I was listening to some old tapes, and out of your very mouth, you said...
Hello, my name is Natalie.
...the only way around the $30...
...or having your card...
...the only way you don't have to have your card at 7 a.m. is if you're actually having sex.
Well, if I said that, then pick up...
...on it, man.
Now, is the party going to stop by and see if we're carrying our card?
No, I'm saying.
Or is old W...
No, you're saying.
Is the party going to check your card?
Who's checking the cards?
I need to know.
It's a genetic thing.
They check.
It's a scanner that's hardly even physical.
Just call it magic.
It's not even physical.
It's just kind of a scrambler that kind of exists more in the metaphysical plane.
Oh, it exists all right.
They can tell.
They can tell who's in the book of life.
And who's in the subgenius foundation database.
Well, they can tell all they want, but I'm keeping it a secret.
You know what I'm saying?
And they're going to tell Mr. Cheney tomorrow, and I'm going to get a great big fat check.
And you might go to jail.
I think Cheney's a hot-looking dude, man.
I like Cheney.
I like the way he kind of like grins out of the side of his mouth, man.
That is so freaking hot.
And the way he had to wear the fishhooks in his nose to play Phantom of the Opera.
He is.
I mean, I'm not generally like a gay dude or anything.
But, man, I see Dick.
Cheney and I start getting a woody, man.
Oh, Dick Cheney.
Cute guy.
I thought you were talking about Lon Cheney Sr.
Okay, so.
Now, he was hot.
People call me.
The hunchback of Notre Dame.
Imagine that 80-pound hump of rubber strapped to his back.
He knew how to.
It was real suffering in those days.
In the days of stunt.
Oh, those toothpicks weren't enough to cause a scar on a rep.
Those bags of water weren't stunt bags.
Those were the real actors being tortured and mangled and brutalized.
Brutalized.
They weren't stunt bags.
You're saying they're real bags.
On Mexican land, I've been gone.
Stunt bags of water with sticks.
Well, are you listening on the internet, then, Johnny?
Well, I'm trying my best.
It's breaking up quite a bit.
Is it?
This is actually the only way I could listen to the show was to make a long-distance phone call and sit on the phone.
Well, if you're on unlimited minutes, you can just sit there.
I'll lock you on.
Well, I'll tell you what.
We've got forehead paste on all three of us, and we're sort of sticking together right now.
What do we got here?
Oh, we're almost out of time.
Well, you know, when you stay on the phone like that.
For a long time, it also serves as a colonoscopy.
Have you talked to the people at A3 and 3?
I've tried to several times, but they only speak Yiddish now.
Well, they're still psychic.
Don't forget that part.
They still are psychic, especially if you're using it as a colonoscopy.
Well, we're all wondering how we can get our hands on some of that delicious ESO music as well as some WCSB paraphernalia.
We've never had any in all the years we've called the show.
We have no paraphernalia.
How about some good old CSB paranoia?
Well, you send me an email.
I can hook you up with ESO.
That's right.
Chaz at subgenius.com as well as subgenius.com catalog.
You'll find ESO information.
There you go.
Give it to me.
Very impressive.
Amazing!
Yeah, that was the kicker.
Listen to the sounds of hell and take a trip into a prison of nightmares.
It's worse than a prison here.
Chain gang women.
A world where men and women live like animals.
Emotion danger is shocking as it is true.
Don't miss chain gang women when you live like an animal.
Anything goes.
When you leave, take me with you.
A crown of the nation.
The slut invertebrate nuns of Dobstown.
Oh.
The invertebrate flatworm slut nuns of Dobstown.
They're soft.
Do you like soft women?
I like them.
Only $40 you come in.
We have no bones.
I like them.
I like them like a portabello.
Oh, boneless women.
Boneless.
Jello jelly girls.
Do they put them in the can?
Female fillet.
She crawls on her belly like a snail without a shell.
And you can do that to make like a consommé.
What a trail she'll leave for you, buddy.
Only $40.
Come on in.
You don't want to miss this show.
What are you?
Some kind of a wuss?
Come on in here.
Only $40.
Best show in Amsterdam.
I could go for a mollusk.
Mama?
Live on stage right in front of your face.
They do it with bugs and snails.
Subgenius Hardcore.
He's like the, uh...
Subgenius Eyes bring you the hottest subgenius adult videos and DVDs.
Yes, it's true.
Those horrible porn banners on the sub site that Stang deliberately cultivates.
He whines and complains that they are needed to make money for the site.
But, uh...
Satisfy every twisted...
We could advertise...
...their incredible collection...
...miniature...
Now, now, now, what are you talking about, Reverend Hale?
...of rare subgenius footage?
When you go to the sub site, uh...
Yeah?
...site, you know?
Find Bondi...
...have these porno, uh, things there...
...very...
...which, uh, help pay for the site.
Are you talking about some kind of art excuse or real, just straight pornos?
No, those banners.
Oh, okay.
Those banner ads in the sub site.
Yeah, I have not actually ever looked at it.
Never.
Well, maybe they got rid of them.
I don't know if you...
You haven't seen them, have you?
No, they got rid of them.
I just must have, uh, hallucinated it, that's all.
Yeah, it was a dream.
Yeah.
Because...
Even Stang couldn't stand it anymore.
Even Stang wouldn't stoop so low.
And you two are dreaming about...
No, Stang wouldn't stoop that low, but he just wouldn't stay there very long.
Okay, let's watch a little Stang puppet stoop now.
There, and then he stands up, now he's doing a bow.
Now he's walking off stage.
Now, what we've done is we've reached a little tiny puppet subgenius show...
...right at intermission.
We did.
It's, uh, it's really entertaining.
Intermission?
Really cute.
Yeah, it's good.
I'm not sure I understand it.
And then, well, now you go out for miniature coffee and donuts in the miniature, um...
In the miniature golf course miniature restaurant.
That's right.
And then you come back in 12 minutes later and the show starts again.
It's really cool.
That's it exactly.
It's a 4-inch video.
Subgenius Media is a fabulous collection of subgenius women from all over the world.
Good luck to our departing travelers in traveling over possibly interdicted bridges and snow.
Some of the hairiest subgenius girls on video see those stinky, sweaty subgenius women.
...shut down.
...and they're tired of close...
...only coming your way is the stinky road of...
...contact with the fashion models.
...the stinky road of...
...so are we.
...transports.
If you're tired of that, then you need to call right now at April 4th, April 425.
We've had enough of that ourselves.
We're actually in our own...
What's that area called?
You know, they've, um...
...where'd you go to sleep?
...exotic land.
...now the boffins have developed an onion that doesn't make you cry when you cut into
it.
I know.
What will science produce next?
Okay, all you driving around town pot smokers, call us right now, April 4th, April 425.
Up to now...
...and all you guys in red Camaros with mullet haircuts...
Oh yes, dear friends, some KPFA sub-show from KPFA Berkeley with Dr. Howl-Puzzling-Evidence,
Dr. Philodrumon, and before that, some chief-em-thieves.
Well, there will be a woman at the head of every nation in the world.
...but models are no less reserved...
How do you get to be a head of a nation?
...and now, please...
Be a woman.
...as you are a nation, too.
Huh.
...it's gonna be a lot of work.
I get it.
I...
It seems like it would...
Well, I'd make a terrible woman.
...the same...
You don't know about that, now?
...you got the right hair for it.
...which nothing can better be contrasted.
Well, the hair on his chin, but it's in the wrong place.
...if he would know that.
It would be great womanly hair, but it's just all...
...hear on his regular hair.
...It's arranged wrong.
...it's gone gray, too.
I like the hair on his ears.
...the rest of his skin that we can see is the thickness of the naked eye.
Well, the hair around his ears will bleed if you cut it.
That's not just hair.
Oh.
Those are his forgotten appendages.
Oh, the undiscovered appendages.
I remember my forgotten appendages.
Poor crazy Bonnie.
She just couldn't stop lunatic room.
The ghost of excesslessness must pass.
Returns to haunt us.
In these horrible recordings from Doc Stock 1 in 1983.
The saddest, sorriest, most disease-ridden festival of the arts.
A young woman named Lori's birthday party.
The umbrella.
Oh.
But you know, the other one that...
Was here.
The Hour of Slack.
From the Church of the Subgenius.
For more information on the Church of the Subgenius,
write for free information from P.O. Box 204-206, Austin, Texas, 78720.
Or you can send tapes and things, CDs, whatever, to me, stang, at subgenius.com,
by email, or...
to post office box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio, 44118.
And friends, this music in the background is the amino acid.
It's a...
Ugh!
Tinkerbell, where'd you...
I am Captain Hook.
I am your father, Peter Pan.
Come to me.
Come and sit upon my pegged lap.
I will tell you the stories of seven legs deep.
That would...
Ugh!
parfois?
Sometimes?
Problems.
Symptoms.
Finances.
Marriage.
Children.
Cancer.
Their disease.
Sinus infection.
Problems.
Sinus cavities.
Ears.
Sickness.
Infections.
Again, painful gallbladder surgery.
Gallbladder.
Toes.
Foot.
Ankle.
Pain.
Pop.
The Achilles tendon.
Pain.
Pop.
Tendon.
Fungus infections.
Infections.
Gone.
Diagnosis.
Cancer.
Damage to the femur.
Femur.
Chronic condition in your sinuses.
Cancer.
Femur.
Sinuses.
Drainage.
Infection.
Esophagus problem.
Esophagus.
Fear.
Not in her ear.
Ear.
Infection.
Pain.
Ear.
Ear began to pop.
Pop.
Infection.
Affliction.
Serious ear infection.
Infection.
Medication.
Dangerous hospital.
Dangerous.
Medication.
In Jesus name.
Amen.
God prayer.
God.
Believe.
Healing touch.
Believe touch.
Prayer.
Believe God.
Miracle.
Jesus God.
Believe.
Miracle.
Jesus.
Faith God.
In Jesus name.
In Jesus.
Believe.
Healing.
Healing touch.
Trust.
Heal.
Thank you.
Healed.
Yes.
God healing.
Delivering.
Faith.
Power.
Love.
Word.
God.
Heal.
Healing.
Jesus.
Heal.
God healing.
In Jesus name.
Thank you.