Quatu, Virada, Nicto
Quiet numbskulls, I'm broadcasting
My electronic signals are psychological
Ultimate destruction of the systems, purely melodic
Listening causes hypnotic
Trances to leave your thoughts clotted
Lost in a dream unspotted
Insanity from my creation, now retarded
You're all with Corky in a sitcom plotted
Oh, my friends, prepare to take the hand
Of that pipe-smoking man, Bob
And let him lead you and your ears
Down the primrose path to slack
For the subgenius radio ministry
Hour of Slack
Uh...
Yeah...
Yes...
You know, it's not nearly enough for you to believe in Bob
You must suck his entrails with your psychic firmament
You must live in Bob's own depleted spaces
In his own world
Suck with Bob's spite
To droplets and
possibilities
What is the level of humanity such that we, as humans, might be able to tell egos,
able to tell
a place or a world that is asymptotically in batshells and impulse podía beijuana-drowned?
Soon enough, the family will change from a greasy green to a bright, beneficent blue.
Blue?
The Assyrian army camped outside Jerusalem, ready to conquer and level it.
But most of the army died in their sleep one night.
But so the Lord ended that threat.
And there's other stories, like the prophets of Baal, Queen Jezebel, Goliath of Gath.
These weren't just innocent bystanders.
These were enemies who felt the wrath of God's backhand.
When tough love must get even tougher.
God's backhand.
When evil plays rough, God can play rougher.
We're not talking about tennis or ping pong or any kind of friendly sport.
We're talking about God fighting for his people where someone can really get hurt.
But that someone is your enemy.
Who'd have no qualms about it.
God's backhand.
Yet as strong as it ever was.
It will solve problems that nothing else does.
God's backhand.
When you need it.
When you need something more than just defense.
God's backhand.
Will send evil flying over the fence.
And this is Michael Pepe again.
As soon as you turn your back.
Everything in the universe snaps itself inside out with a hideous sucking motion.
The only reason you cannot call the world impossible is because it is only through the world that you know the concept of impossibility.
You have been led to believe that everyone feels he or she may be the only living consciousness.
But you are in fact the only one for whom this is true.
The fundamental structure of reality is totally transformed every instant.
But it provides you with a phony memory that it has always been the way it is.
Since you are always at the exact center of an infinity loop.
There is no such thing as movement, location, space, or time.
You are a row of electrochemical events.
You are a sequence of events taking place in your cerebral body.
Nothing has meaning in itself, but everything can support any meaning.
If you could glimpse for even a moment the real meaning of existence, your brain would be neuroanatomically destroyed.
You cannot conceive a thing for which you do not have a word.
Everyone's perception is radically unique.
But leads them to believe it is more or less similar for everyone else.
You have always been listening to this tape.
You cannot remember a time before you were born because there was no such time, nor any other.
It has always been this moment.
Death could occur inexplicably any second.
And there is no other chance.
But there is still a moment.
The moment of the world.
The oddness of the world exceeds the imagination by an infinity.
It has produced this talking about it.
This talker.
This labeling of it.
This labeler.
The concept of labeling.
The concept of oddness.
The word oddness.
The concept of a word.
The word word.
The word concept.
And the concept of a concept.
Consciousness is not a continuous state, but a momentary surfacing for variable periods at random points.
Your next awakening could be 20 years from now.
Nothing can be proven to be true.
Because reality is composed of infinitesimally small moments, there is no such thing as an event.
The reason people are untrustworthy is because their cerebral processes are fundamentally random ones.
During the night, every ego in the world changes bodies, inheriting also the memory.
Old age is not a gradual, but a catastrophic process, and could strike at any moment.
Dreams are the reality for which the real world is.
The real world is a dream.
There has never been a time in history when men have voluntarily used less than the greatest possible military technology against their enemy,
and allowed a great technology to fall into disuse and ignorance.
Therefore, there will be a full-scale nuclear holocaust.
You are dreaming this moment.
The universe will continue to expand until there is not enough matter per unit space to provide the gravity necessary for regeneration,
and it will slowly die out.
When you finish listening to this, everything will be different from the way it was when you began.
Again, your new memory will conceal this from you.
All events occur at random.
The universe is...
one of an infinite number of universes,
the closest of which is undetectable,
being a billion universe lengths away.
Only what you are experiencing right now exists.
Love is the feeling that another person is really yourself.
You are about to make the first conscious decision of your life.
Oh...
Moment of om
...
or Reverend Michael Pepe,
and you are listening to the Hour of Slack Radio Ministry.
Michael Pepe, dear friends, from the old hour of Slack number 106.
We're dredging ancient hours of Slack now.
And before that, friends, God's Backhand was by the great Richard Hackley,
posted to altbinaries.slack by the great New Monet.
We've got a lot of new stuff that was posted to that news group
by Reverend Artemiya Salina and by Reverend Why Ask Why Ask Why.
And because, friends, we've moved.
Listen, listen to the ambience in this room.
This is our new studio complete with everything, everything.
Anyone could, even a keyboard.
Listen to this.
I've got this keyboard.
I can just.
It is white and new.
And beautiful.
It has been painted with the sweat of Lonesome Cowboy Dave used for paint.
The subgenius storage facility in the tomb of the faceless Bobby have been done.
We finished the shelves.
We filled them halfway with the ancient crumbling subgenius tapes and video
and text and artwork extracted from the previous abyss.
We've lifted up the roll top desk, the rack, the hour of slack production table heard here.
Oops, there went my.
That just knocked out my.
Oh, there it is.
And we can even create.
Well, you know, I'm not finished moving that castle, though, Dave.
There's still all the boxes of souls and the canisters and stuff that are in that.
That basement of that dungeon of that other cast.
They're the special vampire.
I mean, it's the undead fluids you keep to keep.
I mean, that's not myself.
Well, I mean, it's firm bank.
That stuff wasn't all that complicated.
And what a joy to your mother.
It was when you took the whole sperm bank in your hands with that pair of blue sunglasses,
that pair of John Lennon sunglasses and paraded off down Main Street anywhere.
You have seen that silly day, you know, as well as anybody.
Wink, wink.
But that sperm bank is a bunch of.
Nitro frozen nitrogen containers that keep the sperms immobile and frozen from fighting.
Yeah, because these are super sperms.
Of course, genius little farts that can that will literally eat their way up into whatever egg female egg is nearest.
Well, they blind primate.
They blinded some.
Yeah, they go in the wrong way.
It's like a mini meteor in space.
You see that movie Mission to Mars.
They're all partying.
Suddenly the guy's got a.
Hole in his hand and there's a hole in the fuel tank.
Well, there's a tiny atom sized meteor going near the speed of light.
Just happened to intersect with their spaceship.
Bad luck.
That's the way a subgenius sperm will just shoot right through.
Because it's like a piranha.
It's like the piranha of sperms.
You know what I mean?
It's more than just a.
It's like a tadpole with millions and millions.
It's like the fish of sperms, which it's funny.
That's a funny metaphor.
Because candura fish is a fish that swims up your urethra to eat its way into your heart.
Whereas the sperms usually go out the other way.
And so does your heart.
One of them canduras might, you know.
How often have we all fallen out of love after that final emission?
All of the.
You know, that goes out of your heart and comes back into your emissions.
Well, that's the problem, isn't it, Dave?
So often love starts out as an emission.
You emit love and it goes in.
But then it.
Sort of comes right back at you.
And it's just your own love coming back.
And there's.
And that's it.
It just went in a big circle.
Yeah.
And you get left on sitting on the curb with your hat in your hand all limp.
Going, oh, I've been.
I've been dumped again.
Dumped again.
I'm just a sorry old.
But friends.
No matter what.
Sorry.
The deer parts and the fisheries.
Man eating chimes and moods.
What's going on, man?
I don't get it.
It's more.
More than a happening or something going on.
It's a whole.
It's a whole band of.
Things have seeped in.
To our psychic consciousness.
Yeah.
Are you.
Right.
Those of you with.
Plural.
You read through.
Could please.
If you could.
Please.
Could you.
If you.
If you could.
Please.
Just remove your garments there and place them next to the vacuum cleaner.
And those of you with a single.
Single scars where the urethra is wars.
Please just step to the side.
And now.
A little.
Now.
You know.
You.
Your.
One.
Is not alone.
On this cosmic.
Meddling.
Earth has been inhabited.
Ground.
Stop.
For millions of years.
By hundreds of different races of aliens from space.
Both.
Benevolent.
And.
Hostile.
Have you ever noticed that no two UFO photographs show the same.
Hubcap.
Many of the saucer.
Jogging.
Are simple.
Humanoids.
Like.
Us.
Space.
Nazis.
Who do little more than freeze up car motors on lonely country roads at night.
And occasionally rape or mutilate humans.
Or.
They usually look like.
Ears.
Elves.
Or dwarves.
And are of relatively minor importance.
Since Bob himself has faster stations than they have.
They only frequently break the rule of don't let the earthlings see you.
But there are far other more confusing things.
Managers mass grade.
They pull on their kebab kits when I can't climb my heels.
Which I'd choose your hair.
And where have you gone to get this for us?
Wait.
You have got your purinder.
Always both of my fucking ears.
New NFL teams gecko stickies.
Everything else is def tectonica and-
There got to be.
I've got absolutely no decimals for內
Just do whether you're drunk or not.
Damn dineya name is not Michael Williams.
I believe you know of something on my top Umwelt MP3.
I believe your car's purel-
And Bob.
Dozens, perhaps hundreds of entities speak through Bob.
Many voices.
They also listen and see through him.
And many even go to him for advice on handling humans.
Bob is a wide open channel they can log on to for the divulging of past lives, secrets, and ground rubber.
Oh, here it is.
There's our chance.
Yes, friends.
It's incredible.
We even managed to move the iron lungs and maidens up here into this new studio.
And at this point, friends, I am up to my testicle in Tesla coils getting ready for the final bye-bye to Earth and the Pink Boys on that day when we are ruptured.
July 5th, 2001 for X-Day.
Incidentally, friends, I wanted to mention that I have dibs on X-Day.
I've got dibs on the Grand Canyon, including Flintstones Bedrock City.
On Monument Valley, Utah.
I think Pocus Lilith already got Devil's Tire in Wyoming.
I've got all the furniture in the West Wing of the Rijksmuseum in Amsterdam.
Doc Frog can have the Vermeers.
I don't want any violent showdowns to mar what should be our most glorious time of looting.
Remember, friends, after X-Day, anything not made by WOM will be a collectible.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I've also got dibs.
On the Vatican, Mecca, Chichen Itza, the entire red light district of Amsterdam, the pyramids, the Sphinx, the Alamo, so that no one else may desecrate it but me.
The New York Museum of Natural History, the Smithsonian, the British Royal Museum of Natural History, Goudy's Cathedral in Barcelona, the Cleveland Museum of Natural History, Black Rock Desert and Playa, Carlsbad Caverns, the Petrified Forest, the beach where they film those Harryhausen movies in Spain, Angkor Wat, the Watson.
The New York Museum of Natural History, the New York Museum of Natural History, the Capitol.
Rock City, Tennessee.
All the Anasazi ruins.
The Playboy Mansion.
The Dobstown Mansion.
The Victoria Theater in San Francisco.
The Texas School Book Opository and Dealey Plaza.
Brushwood.
Epcot Center.
The Forbidden City in Beijing.
The Kremlin.
St. Petersburg.
Pigeon Forge.
Dollywood.
Graceland.
All the Ripley's Believe It or Not's and Madame Tussauds.
The Winking Lizard Tavern.
Big Tex from the Texas State Fair.
All the Big Boy Colossi.
The Enchanted Rock near Austin.
The Antique.
Ackermanchen. And, uh,
friends, all of these things will be
the backyard of my new
escape vessel.
My new house on X-Day.
July 5th, 1998.
Friends, be ready. Check
sub-site, www.subgenius.com.
Oh, yeah, and I almost forgot.
The entire studio lots
of Universal, Paramount,
MGM, and everything
in Industrial Light and Magic.
Although, really,
friends, I guess I don't need those,
because we'll be
able to think the movies
and, whoa, we'll print
them out in 3D Spell-O-Vision
and feel around!
Praise Bob! Praise Bob!
Everything worked! The study
of mutation and the public
sphere of the unknown can again
proceed.
Incidentally, friends, I should mention
that the new subgenius address,
my personal post office
address, will be
given at the end of the broadcast.
And, although we're still,
the church is still working
out of Dallas, you send your orders to
Dallas, and I send my
orders to you from here
in Cleveland Heights. That's
post office box 181
417 Cleveland
Heights, Ohio 44118.
And that music there was
by The Bishop.
A wonderful
new tune called
Dance of the Rockets.
Uh,
yes, yes,
yes, yes.
Whew!
Yes, it's truly
a cliche. It came from
heaven in the first shipment
in the Rockets.
If you think they'll use
too much, complain elsewhere.
They are holy
instruments of instruction
from here in the headquarters.
We could be what we really are.
Humans together,
subject to the trauma of birth
and the fear of death,
to pain and loneliness,
disease and loss,
ecstasy and pleasure.
We could accept
our vulnerability, which would allow us
to feel it and,
in turn, would help us to feel
all of what we have to deny
when we try to be invulnerable,
impregnable.
Consider the root of that word.
.
Woo-hoo!
My fiery friend, are you feeling better?
I think a plutonium injection and a shot of steam in the right place will wake you up.
And we're on our way.
We're only three and one-half blocks right now from the Ericksonian Glass High Security Art Compound.
They have not found me yet, thank goodness.
I'm still just a nameless building with a cow skull and cross glass cutters over the front door
as far as the...
Local art police are concerned.
Oh, there's one of their cars.
You heard that young girl scream?
She was thought to be an artist also.
The mortar flies into a flame and instantly frizzles into a heap of protoplasmic sludge
so the collars are burned and seared by the blistering truth revealed over the air
by the doctors.
Oh, precision.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
I heard some puzzling evidence there and some glass madness doing that art security thing
and Dr. Howell ranting and some Wellman mixes from...
KPFA and Berklee reprinted from old hour of slack number 106.
Friends, and now the boredoms with the sound all around us.
Followed by G. Gordon Gordon.
Wellman.
Wellman We're not pissed to go back no more.
We are not pissed.
We will not name it Mr. G. G. G. G. Room Report.
Se 있다 lpflicht.
I'm here.
I'm pissing around, pissing around, pissing around, pissing around.
I hear puzzling evidence.
Don't go to him again.
Don't go to him again, okay?
So what, Mr. Dobbs? We're in shape for the finals.
No, really, Mr. Dobbs.
And by the way, Bob, just where is that long promised bucket of pills?
And tell me, Bob, what's this slack business?
Shouldn't the hierarchical slack holders be making unearthly dividends on a regular basis by now?
Or is it wrong?
Just.
It's really too much fun, Bob.
Is there a war on here?
Well, there is a war on here, Bob.
And whatever happened to too much is always better than not enough.
Has there been inside trading in the Souls repository in Dobbs Town?
Oh, come on, Bob. Remember us? Remember the old guys?
We used to sell froth mixture for you way back in the good old days.
We've heard the old Dobbs head snake oil routine before, Bob.
We know all about the bleeding head of AP.
But when will it come is what we want to know.
So when shall the fabled...
...flut plane tilt?
And when shall things at last begin to flow to all, all, all of us...
...who despite the perilous times in which we do live, plead unto you still, Bob?
Next day's coming closer, Dobbs.
You haven't got all the time to the end of the world, have you?
Hadn't you better just get cracking, Mr. Dobbs?
Don't you think it's time to get your ass out of party mode and back up the crack?
Hmm.
Mark Mothersbaugh, The Big Boss
This is Mark Mothersbaugh. Mark Mothersbaugh, The Big Boss
And, um...
Hajime Tachibana
Uh, and Nancy Ferguson.
This is a pretty unusual little, little recording here.
Thanks to Byron Werner.
Breaking citizens of the world!
We are so happy to be here with you today for Mr. Ituchi's NFL!
Mr. Ituchi's NFL
Mr. And the LA A- Thank you very much!
Please, everyone out there
Let's start off this weekend with Mark Mothersbaugh here.
Y'all always welcome me around
Living by Dr. Smith!
I hope to see you next week!
to me
it doesn't matter to me
cause there's something
bigger than what you see
there's something
important that is waiting for you
oh yeah
knock it off
tell a good story people
tell me nothing
do that's what I'm waiting for
it doesn't matter to me
oh yeah
cause there's a train
for a new destination
and a tenant for a new destination
and I tell you my friend
you better count the years
deadline coming
I don't care
if you ever change your underwear
it doesn't matter to me
cause there's something
bigger than what you see
it doesn't matter to me
oh that's
No Matter by Mark Mothersbaugh
and Nancy Ferguson
Nancy
Nancy Ferguson
and Nancy Ferguson
and Hachibana
what's that guy's name
Hajime Tachibana
I only know him as Tachibana
and the rest of this song here
is by Tachibana
a Japanese fellow
pretty hot stuff
Hi
the
is
named
Hatchibana
& let's meet
the
live
You are lovely, hair like lovely glasses
Your hair is so beautiful, I can't believe it
Baby, baby, baby
From the top of the mountain
Good, good
Kill the horse
The horse is dead
Roxadam Hussein's ass
Tomorrow, tomorrow, tomorrow
That's right, that's right
Tomorrow, tomorrow
Tomorrow, tomorrow, tomorrow
Good night
Thank you
Give me the antidote or kill me
None are so blind as those who have no heads
Come on, man, spit it out
Don't lick the taste of that, I'm not doing that again
Oh no, no
Another insidious quote inserted here
Don't attempt to adjust the controls
We are no longer in control
Smaller children should ask an adult to help
All your space art belonged to us
Why does it hurt when I pee?
Help, help, I can't take it anymore
Praise Bob
Yeah, hallelujah
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Hey, you remember the first time we raided the Bob mansion?
The Playboy mansion of Bob?
Oh man, God, you could just smell the women
He was roasting some over an open fire
Remember that?
Well, it wasn't a real fire
That's what I mean, they smelled so crisp and crackly
Yeah, those polyps
Polypurethane vinyl fires
They're not real but
Boy, they look so good with those apples in their mouths
And just
Bob caught us
He always does
I don't find I never have to do that again
No, you don't want to get caught in that web
What did they call that?
A job?
Yeah, he made us get a job
God, that was awful
I hated that
Finding in the basement
But there were a lot of naked female clerks to help us there
Remember?
Remember Lonnie and Jeanette?
Jeanette, the one with the bright red hair and the little teeny tiny sharp teeth?
Yeah, and who's the one from the whale farm?
Oh, Betty Jean.
Bertha?
Betty Jean.
Big Bad Bertha?
Big Bad.
Big Bad Bertha.
Do you remember the captain?
Do you remember the guy from...
Oh, yeah.
Arr, arr, arr.
Arr, Bob should be timbered.
He's Bob this and Bob that stupid.
I hate those Bobby idiots.
You know, 65 years old, should be someplace in Florida or Arizona, but he's still in the
wheelchair giving commands.
But he's just gotten turned on to Bob, so he was in that phase.
He was in that for year one phase where everybody's actually...
Look, there's that man Bob.
He found it.
There's another shop that's Bob's TV repair.
Oh, there's Bob's used car.
Bob's everywhere.
I got Bob on the brain.
And there's nothing wrong with having Bob on the brain, friends.
As long as you can purge it.
Every now and then.
Just every now and then.
Until they were locked up with the fish, which was no mean feat.
The fish themselves were some 300 pounds.
Some of them weighed in excess of 700 pounds.
Each and every fish was equipped with a dynamic facial structure.
The kind that could tear apart pieces of rock with one grimace.
These were the fish that Bob had selected.
His mighty fighting sperm.
To spread like a mankind of...
Cardium throughout the depleted universe.
So you could just take it up to your room and do whatever you want with it.
You know what I mean?
Sit back in that old bungalow roll away bed and watch the subway go by.
Take one last drink from that bottle of port.
Pick up the gun.
Look at it.
Put one bullet in.
Spin the chamber.
Put the gun down.
Pick it up again.
Spin the chamber again.
Put it down.
Look out the window.
It's just seven trains going by.
Ah, yes.
Life is beautiful.
Maybe a few more crackers and I've got a little mustard left to put on them.
For a while.
The End
A lunatic is on the grass
Remembering games and these chains and laughs
Got to keep the loonies on the path
A lunatic is in the hall
The lunatics are in my hall
The paper holds the folded faces to the floor
Every day in the table, every day tomorrow
And if the dam rings open, many years do still
If there is no room above the hill
And if your next one is on the roof still
I'll see you on the dark side of the moon
The lunatic is in my head
It is in my head
You raise the blade, you make the change
You rearrange me till I'm sane
You lock the door, you lock the door
Throw away the key
There's someone in my head but it's not me
And if a cloud bursts up and I ring your key
And you shout and no one sees the key
And if a man or an interest plays a trick too
I'll see you on the dark side of the moon
Woo, woo, woo, woo, woo
One, two, three, four
And if a cloud bursts thunder in your ear
And you shout and no one sees the key
And if a man or an interest plays a trick too
I'll see you on the dark side of the moon
Woo, woo, woo, woo, woo
guitar solo
bass solo
drums solo
guitar solo
bass solo
drums solo
mostly playa
drum solo
conventional jazz
drums solo
and other instruments
zabки
I can't think of anything to say except
I think it's
MOLLY!
Dear friends,
this music is by
Dr. Chris Gross
and
Men in Black.
But you know,
you know
an exquisitely
sharpened hatred
for the pink boy is
of course an emotion
not difficult for subgeniuses
to harbor.
If the truth be known,
this hatred does not abound
in every subgenius soul.
It relies upon too
many mysterious and hidden
patterns of life and
chance to flourish luxuriantly
everywhere.
Real hatred of the
sort of which I speak,
hatred so
pure and obdurate
that no sympathy,
no human warmth,
no flicker of compassion
can make the slightest nick or
scratch upon the stony
surface of its being.
That is, that kind of hatred
is not common to
all subgeniuses.
Because many conditions are
required for the full
fruition of this hatred,
for its ripe and malevolent
growth. Yet none of these
is as important as that at one time
or another that subgenius
must live in some degree
of intimacy with the
pink boy, the human.
That he may know the object
of his hatred, that he
become knowledgeable about the
mediocritons of wiles,
his pink duplicity, his
subgenius and his ultimate
depravity. For without
knowing the pink boy at close
hand, without having submitted to his
wanton and arrogant kindnesses,
without having smelt the
smell of his bed sheets and his dirty
under drawers and the inside of his privy,
and felt the casual yet
insolent touch of his women's
fingers upon his own yeti
arm, without seeing him
at sport and at ease
and at his hypocrite's worship
and at his drunken
mildness and his lustful and
adulterous couplings in the
hay fields and the condos,
without having known all these cozy
and familial truths, I say,
a subgenius can only
pretend hatred.
Such hatred is only an abstraction
and a delusion.
He finds himself trying to hate
pink boys, but he
will come to understand that he's hating
imperfectly without that calm
and intelligent and unrepenting
purity of hatred.
Which I have described and which is so
necessary in order to
murder.
A man's world,
but it wouldn't be
nothing without a woman
or a girl.
So,
remember the call
to take us
over the road.
So,
I'm going to
who was a
man made a train
to carry the
heavy load
man made the
electric light
to take us out
of the dark
and man made the boat
for the water
just like,
just like Noah
to take us
to the sea.
this is a man's world
but it wouldn't be
nothing
without a woman
or a girl.
Man thinks about
a little bitty
baby girl
and a baby boy
and man makes
him happy
cause man
made some toys
and after man
has made
everything
everything he can
you know
that man makes
the money
to buy
another man.
This is a man's
world
this is a
man's world
but it wouldn't
be nothing
nothing
without a woman
or a girl.
music
You are...
The Residence, dear friends.
Live in Chicago, 2001 from Reverend Chris Lee.
And before that, me reading from the diary of Nat Turner.
Braindale with music by Chris Lee.
I mean, no, Christopher Gross.
Chris Gross.
Brain Damage was that song there by The Squirrels.
And of course, we've been hearing some Einstein Secret Orchestra
with Lonesome Cowboy Dave and host Chaz Smith.
Perhaps some Radio Patapoo from Amsterdam
with Reverend Yitze and Pope Black.
Random Speak from Or Kill Me Radio.
Cryptology from Stang 64, Flow Spark.
This background music is called Subgenius.
By the band C-Rox.
And now, Doug Valentine.
Now that we've gotten to this level,
we're going to just go right down to the very bottom
and do something, a song about something
that everybody is very familiar with.
It involves hair.
It involves blindness.
And it involves...
You can figure out the rest.
The good times, we've had.
Pocket billiards in the back row at the movies.
Now people might call it a sin.
But I'll just buy me some popcorn
that I'll hold in one hand
and have a date with my mom.
Again.
Now in the evening
all the boys go out gambling.
But I'll just stay home
and say I can't go.
I've got a nice paradise
paradise.
Here to play with.
And I'll do
the one hand shuffle
real slow.
Five fingered stud
in the bedroom.
Strip solitaire
with my friend.
Deal a jack
off the bottom.
My hand beats the straight.
I've got a date
with my mom.
Again.
Each goddess
has brought us closer.
My fingers have erected
a shrine.
I know
you.
Like the back of my hand.
And I'll love you
until I go blind.
We've had a fistful of trouble.
Your thumbs were opposed at the start.
Arthritis.
I'm not sure.
Bursitis.
And that hang down.
And the time
you shook hands
with that tart.
But then
you caught me
with a hoover.
The cream cheese
is found
on my skin.
I saw a mirror.
But I remembered
our promise.
At Niagara Falls.
And had a date
with my mom.
Again.
Everybody sing along.
Each goddess has brought us closer.
Each goddess
has brought
us closer.
My fingers have erected a shrine.
My fingers
have erected
a shrine.
I know you.
Like the back of my hand.
And I'll love you
until I go blind.
Your pregnant paws
will be showing.
So soon I must ask
for your hand.
I know you.
I'll just rent a tuxedo
without any pants.
And have a date
with my mom
again.
I'll have a date
with my mom
once
again.
guess you
Mr.
achievement.
And which
Ballantyne,
can you
downtime
with
the
and get the bong.
If you were here,
he'd go out and get the bong.
But then I'm thinking to myself,
I think,
why do they say the thing of it?
Why can't they think of the word
that they're trying to think of
and then not say thing of it?
What do they mean by the thing of it?
What is the point of the thing?
What is the object being talked about?
What is the true definition of thing?
Is the thing an unknown
or is the thing unknown
that's currently just locked away?
What's the deal?
You ever thought about that?
I don't, no.
Why don't you?
Because that's your show.
Hey you, I really don't,
except to just keep on
trying to spread that mighty wheelbarrow
full of bob across the barren plains
of America.
Yes, doctor.
Ding dong.
My name is Vivian Spud
and I've got something I'd like to ask you, doctor.
Well, don't just stand there, boy.
Ask away and we'll try to answer your question.
Well, something has always puzzled me
ever since I was a bee spot
back in Indiana, doctor.
Why does the porcupine
weigh as big as yours?
Because Hoosier boys
oughtn't to get off their home soil
and come traipsing out where they're kind.
You know, Phil used to ask us that too, but...
It's not the kind of answer
we can put on the air.
That's the problem.
Ooh.
See, hear the clamoring masses here below us
of sub-deans wishing for church air.
Ho-hum, they say.
They're looking for spiritual guidance
in a time of confusion.
A time of worse things than that.
You know what I mean?
We're back here at the studio
trying to clean up the mess after the explosion,
but we didn't.
We did get Bob all over two billboards
right by Tower Records,
and we did take an authenticating photograph,
which, as it comes out,
I will send you.
And you can see Bob spread out all over Berkeley.
And I was relating to you on the tape
and may come up later anyway
that I've been putting Bob all over California.
You can see those stars so clearly
it's not ball-like on Earth.
Look at that cloudy planet go by.
It's really inspiring.
I'm glad to be talking to you here.
I heard some more puzzling evidence in there
and some phylo drumming,
but friends, I promise to give you the post office box,
the sacred post office box,
for information on the Church of the Subgeniuses.
Of course, as always,
Bob at post office box 140306.
That's box 140306 in Dallas, Texas, 75214.
If you need to send tapes and stuff to me,
Reverend Ivan Stang,
will you just send those to P.O. Box 181417,
Cleveland Heights, Ohio,
444.
888.118.
And it's all available at www.subgenius.com.
Yeah, Bonnie Winston tastes good like a cigarette.
Thank you.
Yes ma'am.
I don't know.
I sit down,
shut my eyes.
Don't you know they're bigger than a Miz?
No, no, no.
C'mon dude.
You try it.