Tune in again next Sunday at 10 o'clock.
I'm going to bring you a piece of that green cheese for sure.
I have a bucket!
No trouble.
Just get set and get going.
According to the recording, everything's going fine.
Fine. No trouble.
Welcome potential initiates and remain with us for the next 30 minutes.
Bob?
The message is now part of and registered in your subconscious mind
every time you say, see, hear, or think.
What about slack?
That's your key phrase.
It will trigger the entire message without your being aware of it.
Welcome to the subgenius radio ministry, Hour of Slack.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
This is Reverend Ivan Stang,
sacred scribe of the First Orthodox Omega Fist Temple Lodge of the Church of the Subgenius,
with Pastor Buck Naked of the First Orthodox Temple Lodge of the Church of the Subgenius,
the first naked church of the subgenius.
The opinions expressed are not necessarily those of this radio station.
Before the sermon, a message concerning Bob Dobbs,
living avatar of Slack and saint of sales on planet Earth.
Are we controlled by secret forces?
Amen! Amen! Amen!
Amen! Amen!
Almighty and everlasting Bob,
who came down among us to make heaven under earth,
lighten our darkness.
Oh, instrument of God,
grant us thy peace.
Almighty Bob,
who destroyed all devils
and created angels,
behold,
his glory.
Behold the truth that abides in us.
Reveal that truth unto that maker.
I reveal my innermost self unto my God.
Unto my God.
Dear friends,
It must be clear to you that this simple teaching
diffuses truth in the very lasts of humanity,
but how did God lead the foundation for the fullness of His
being?
Well,
first of all,
accept your pledges as our amazing volunteer test drive begins because you
can tell just just what you need around these parts here in Texas far out away
from those Sodom and Gomorrah's of New York and LA the pink coasts we need to
protect that which is native to our land friends such as kno in the non station
it's not like those others and it's the only one where you're gonna get the pure
message of slack and the word of jr. Bob Dobbs at all on the air in Dallas Texas
right doctors
which which microphone are you on buck okay well since it's all mononucleosis I
can't tell which ear it's going in but friends that's right the pledge drive
begins at midnight tonight and we'll start talking about money you know we
love to talk about money because this is a church a subgenius church listen to
that music there
but that's
beautiful that's buck on his auto harp joined by Reverend Glenn Carlson but the
soup electric it's look out that was those those sounds you hear some of the
bills that come into this station these guys aren't on the air for free
don't play ads and they play well you know when you turn this station on you
don't know what you're gonna hear whether it's gonna be
a
you
are
off
know it's gone folks
hello doctors is there anyone else here is this station completely empty
you know you've got the microphone all right folks I'm just gonna have to change
my endless box of cassettes
you a cop
Oh, yeah, everybody. I've got to do everything myself around here.
This is ridiculous. I don't even know how to turn these machines off.
Look at this.
I'll do it.
Folks, this could be some sort of a conspiracy.
Stop. That's it.
Thank you, dear friends, for contributing your prayers towards the breaking of that cassette recorder.
And you see, it's things like this that prove that this station needs money
because people like us come in here and we can't get the machines to stop running
and we just start hitting.
Red Room Stang, I'd like to break in here for just a second.
Please do.
During the next show, the show after Hour of Slack,
he's going to play a tape and it's going to tell exactly why KNON is under siege
and the situation.
The station has been socked with some unusual problems
that we're going to let you know about from without.
This is the serious message.
This is the message of...
Right.
This is the actual pressure that some forces within society are putting on KNON.
I don't know exactly how specific they can let you know what's going on.
The conspiracy, Buck, is never a very specific entity.
Right.
I'd like to remind our listeners that...
It's all one conspiracy.
That Coke and Pepsi are on the same side.
They want to take away your Slack.
They want to take away our station.
That's incredible.
They just want it all.
That's what I've been hearing.
They've got two stations right by here now and they want to make it three.
What the heck.
They want it all.
They want it all, friends.
I think they're trying to shut us up more than they're trying to.
Abnormal.
Probably better than most people.
Friends, that's what they say.
Yes.
Your time shall triumph.
Now, at last, the step-by-step process is revealed.
But only if you send your checks and your lovely...
Well, what is the deal with the situation?
With the amazing...
Dig through the Bibles in here and the pamphlets.
Right.
You send $5 to KNON, you get their newsletter.
And if you mention this show, you get a free...
Subgenius pamphlet number two.
That's right.
The new one.
And for $20, you get the bumper sticker and the newsletter.
Friends, this is an amazing bumper sticker that will bring you a great deal of trouble from the conspiracy as soon as they see you.
So you know it's a romantic sort of amazing thing to do.
The only faith that promises action, thrill, success in sex and business.
But only, only if you do.
Buck?
Yeah.
What do they do?
I mean...
Okay, $20 bumper sticker mailed to you.
Plus the pamphlet, right?
Subgenius pamphlet number two?
That's right.
All right, Doug, this is brand new, though.
This is not what you've already got.
This is something you haven't seen yet.
$30, you get the bumper sticker, the pamphlet and the t-shirt.
For $40, the bumper sticker and the t-shirt will be mailed.
Or whatever.
Otherwise, I guess it's going to walk over to your house or something.
Anyway, real important.
Mention Hour of Slack so we know which show you're listening to.
I don't know if that makes any sense.
Actually, we don't care.
We'll smell your money.
We're with you.
As long as it smells like it's for Bob.
The material may not be reproduced.
Do the same thing over 21 years.
Because people like you are helping us stay on the radio.
You can't buy a mirror.
You can't buy a miracle.
But you can certainly stand behind a miracle ministry.
Like a bunch of...
It's on the radio right now.
Right.
Really now, are you guys in this cult business just for the bucks?
And I wouldn't infer that our secondary state is Antichrist.
But I'm telling you that preparations are being made.
And that the very door of the day of the wrath of God is...
In your hand.
And that if you plan to get saved, you'd better do it now.
There will be a day not in the too far distant future in which Antichrist will be revealed.
And the mark of the beast will be introduced.
And people will have a number in their hands and in their foreheads.
So our demand for energy will be met from our own production and our own conservation.
Come on.
Also in your literature, I noticed connections with aliens.
And the god of wrath who visits us every once in a while and talks to...
We've got to drop this name in here.
Bob Dobbs.
The high muckety muck.
Never behold, he cometh with clouds and every eye shall see him.
Space vessel identity unknown.
I could show you a flying saucer and you'd swear it was something that I'd got from the air.
You'd show me a real flying saucer and you'd say...
I got it from there.
I'll give you a...
At least, Joe...
I'll give a thousand dollars to your religion if you can produce one flying saucer.
At least, Joe, that is my opinion of what I think you would say.
And I've seen a lot of saucer people.
And, uh, but I can't talk about it, you know, because...
Back in the zoo.
So we just gotta wait, you know, until 1985 and then...
Oh, yeah.
Freeze those cats in the street.
The crew of the UFO is an especially designed...
Hey, listen to this.
...robot...
Sorry.
...with oil and fire.
Disintegrated, Captain.
Human God.
Oh, yeah.
One more round of turn.
Yeah.
Man.
Women!
Oh, my goodness.
Eig.
Oh.
Hello?
Everyone makes mistakes.
Let her go, Bob.
Whoa.
They say the bigger the headache, the bigger the pill, baby.
But if I saw her now
I'd be a fool
What?
What's the use of pretending?
I can't stand this anymore.
Chandler said you went over to Georgia Street to see that doctor.
Yeah, that's right, Ed.
Short visit.
Poor guy.
Pretty bad, huh?
No, the guy's really a mess.
The beat and it walked up to the epileptic and said,
Oh, I don't hear the music, but no, baby, no.
I hope you like that nonsense.
I try to make the audience a part of the entertainment
and they go along with it all just great.
That chatter with the doctor is no phony bit, really.
It's just the way it happens.
Make me take off my clothes and make me go out normal
and I have to go outside and change before I come here.
Do you love your parents?
Yeah, I love them, but they're...
In countless schools across the land,
mere infants are taught all about contraceptive techniques
and are provided with a plastic phallus in the classroom.
Well, I don't worship, reefer.
To me, it's just another thing to do.
Hey, Jones, we just got in this African sensimedia hash.
I thought maybe you'd like to smoke some, our father.
Here.
Startin' heavy.
How would be thy name?
Are you good?
Are you jaded?
Has all enthusiasm faded?
Me?
Me!
Are you one of those people ?
Shut up! I'm not done talking to you!
Vick?
I don't need a popeee?
You're triple nuts.
Operates an echo chip.
Resonating fog.
Metaphone.
Something that rather resembles a perfectly silent phone.
I'm getting tired.
I don't know if I can keep up.
But I believe I actually enjoyed it.
To the last mutant.
Mutant.
That's me!
Me!
Ape!
Civilized men were so frightened by talking apes.
Let it get away, Doctor.
But how does one control a 400-pound gorilla?
I'm a doctor, not an animal trainer.
That thing's got the mold as long as my middle finger.
Oh, no!
You think the unthinkable.
This radiation is beautiful.
Yes, Doctor, it's beautiful.
Please!
Cover your faces!
That's the doomsday bomb.
Do you know what that means?
Do you understand?
Illusions!
Who pretend that aboriginally he was a respectable standing.
Hey!
He was no...
Our Slack radio ministry.
Here are the numbers to call.
The old classic number.
823-7490.
Or you can try.
823-8801.
823-8883.
If all numbers are busy...
Well, heck, we won't give that one out yet.
So, 823-7490.
Or 823-8801.
Or 823-8883.
Light up the phone bags for us.
Our Slack radio ministry.
We need gifts for the pledge drive.
And we do have volunteers to take your calls.
That's right.
And not all of this money...
We're not going to give it to the church of the subgenius.
In fact, none of it does.
This is all strictly to keep the station on the air so that you can hear all those other shows that I'm sure some people would rather hear.
Because this is at times a dangerous show to listen to if you're trying to understand exactly what's going on.
You have to listen very closely.
That's the tricky part.
... so much so that young Master Shemmy, on his very first aboutch, at the very dawn of the day, said,
seeing himself such and such, when playing with thistle words in a garden nursery, Griefer Trophy or at Fig Street 111 Shovel in Old Holland,
would we go back there now for sounds, pillons and cents?
Would we now for annas and annas?
Would we for full score eight in a Loretta?
For 12 blocks one bob?
For four testas one gross?
Not for a dean or...
Not for Joe.
Dictated to, of all his little brethren and swisterines,
the first riddle of the universe.
Asking, when is a man not a man?
Telling them, take their time young friars and wait till the tide stops,
for from the first his day was a fortnight.
And offering the prize of a bittersweet crab,
a little present from the past,
for their copper age was yet unminted, to the winner.
One said, when the heavens are quakers.
A second said, when Bohemian lips are the best.
A third said, when he know...
When hold hard a jiffy.
When he is agnostic and determined to.
The next one said, when the angel of death kicks the bucket of life.
Still another said, when the wine's at wit's end.
And still another, when lovely woman stoops to conk him.
One of the littliest said, me me send when papa papa at the harbour.
One of the wittiest said, when he yate ye ablou kooken
and he's mere zee self so sooken.
Still one said, when you are old, I'm grey,
full with sleep.
And still another, when wee dead a walkner.
And another, when he's just only after having been semi-sized.
Another, when, yea, he hath no mananas.
And one, when those pigs they begin now that they will flies up into the luft.
All were wrong.
So Shem himself, the doktator, took the cake,
the correct solution being,
I'll give it up,
when he is a...
yours till the rending of the rocks,
sham.
Shem was a sham.
And a low sham.
And his lowness creeped out first via foodstuffs.
So low was he that he preferred Gibson's tea-time salmon,
tinned, as inexpensive as pleasing,
to the plumpest roe-heavy lax,
or the friskiest par of smoked trout that ever was gaffed between Leaslip and Island Bridge.
And many was the time,
he repeated in his bottle-ism,
that no jungle-grown pineapple
ever smacked like the whoppishest sugar out of Ananias's cans,
Finlay's and Galston's,
Callahouse's,
Angans's,
So many great things, it just goes on and on and on and on and on.
That's, um,
that's from Finnegan's Wake.
And it's, uh,
it's a big book.
Great big thick book.
People read it.
They get lost inside of it.
And we've got special signals attached to the tapes that we play on this show.
That reach out and lock onto your mind.
It's funny, isn't it?
This is, uh,
Reverend D.K. Jones.
Uh, in New Jersey.
Great subgenius.
A song called Midnight Ramblin'.
I don't mean just black night.
All right.
I mean you black-hearted men and women.
Yes!
I'm Midnight Ramblin'.
All Midnight Ramblin' faces are not black.
But they're armed.
It is as black as midnight.
I'm talking to you.
Hold up, men
And women
You bank robbers
You say so
And you bank robbers
And kidnap
All right
I'm talking to you
And we got some people in the church
Yes, sir
Stayed out just as late
As a midnight round
I don't know what time
Brother
Cut in last night
Yeah, brother
Yeah
But you haven't told why they had that
Sister Bell, why did they have him at?
He was in jail
I thought he was in jail
Somewhere
Yeah
In jail
And now, Sister Jordan
Where was your husband?
My husband, he got home last night
And he was in jail
I told him I was in jail
He told me not to tell you
Oh, well, he don't have to tell me
I'm not holding court
So I'm just talking to you
He's got to tell the judge
And the jurors will tell him what to do
Him what to do
All right
And in return, if you don't mind
He'll get six dollars
Eight
Ah, ten
I'm talking to you midnight ramblers
Yes
Stay with us tonight
Just to rob and steal
All right
Some of you are so raucous
Come on, come on
Well, you will steal from yourself
All right
I didn't, I didn't, I didn't, I didn't
Sister Bell, Kate Bell, Kate Bell
Kate Bell, Kate Bell, huh?
Who was left?
Well, I don't know
I don't give out with my sister
Uh-huh
Oh, yes
I'll whip somebody else
But he's got an answer for himself
Yeah, he is
I went out there for him
But he's got to stand for himself
Yeah, he is
I'm sorry
Come back
Well, I stopped running
I'm not running
Hey
There was something I couldn't do
Oh, on the ground
After he like
He had it
He didn't
I don't know
I don't remember
Oh, I spent all afternoon
Looking into this
No, no, no
Winning American
All right
Let's run
Oh, it's everyone
Last time
I came from there
490. Come on, call us.
Light that sucker up.
Just a little bit of money, friends.
Oh, you're trying.
Can you prove that you can part with
that which has enslaved you, my
friend? Can you reach deep
into that most holy and sacred
of receptacles on your whole body,
that most sacred orifice,
your back pocket, and pull out
that deepest part of your soul,
which is your wallet, dear friends.
Pull that wallet out and
pull out that credit card.
Call in that Visa card
number. Yes, the
beast computer in Belgium will
take that number down and that money
will go to this lovely station.
I've got another number. We've just gotten a call.
Please, send us
your wallet. 823-
8801. Light that
one up now, please. Someone out there. I know
you're listening. The radio ministry is reaching
into your gland, your soul gland,
your sex gland, your money gland.
823-
8801.
8-8-8-0-1.
Friends. Light it up.
Friends. Light it up. How much?
Oh, yes. Yeah, light that money
out. And when it gets here, for
once, we won't burn it. You know, usually
we at the Church of the Subgenius take
your money and burn it, so a little bit of your
soul smoke floats up
towards heaven, so the aliens in
outer space will know that Earth
is still worth saving, but
this time, we'll spend the money on
microphones
and more broadcasts
and more broadcasting equipment for the
station. And not only that, but just
the numbering. Yes, let's have the numbering.
823-8801.
Light it up.
Light it up. Because there's nobody
else in Dallas that is about to play
Captain Beaver.
The black paper between a mirror breaks
my heart.
The moon
frayed through dark velvet lightly
apart.
Steals softly through
sunshine.
Steals softly through snow.
The wild goose flies from winter.
Breaks my heart that I
can't go. Energy
flies through a field.
And the sun softly melts
a nothing wheel.
Steals softly through sunshine.
Steals softly through
snow.
The black paper between a mirror
breaks my heart that I can't go.
The swan and feathers don't roll
their spine.
They live
200 years.
Of love.
They're one.
Breaks my heart to see the cross
of the sun.
Their bodies fly down.
When the clouds rise their tails down.
Rain Bowls carry the star of the moon,
mix goggles,
sex Helios.
They fly through the night,
Likeuuuueng.
Wait.
If these things help me,
spell this out in thecheckers.estate.
There's alsoapprentice.css at gegeben,
And why?
Record Search Knight,
The black paper between the mirror breaks my heart but I can't go.
Steal softly through sunshine, steal softly through snow.
Everyone rise for the anthem.
Dallas, Fort Worth, Arlington, Mesquite.
Lancaster.
Bland Prairie.
And speaking of Grand Prairie,
ah yes, thank you Michael Wallace for making the first pledge of the K-O-N,
some genius pledge drive.
Well, you gotta call 823-7490
and help us continue to keep our slack and K-O-N in general on the air.
823-7490
Ah yes, dear friends, once again, reach down deep and call us up,
offer your credit card number or set up this amazing bank draft system
where they can pull money out of your checking account every month
without you ever having to think about it or maybe ever even knowing about it
if you're drunk enough when you pledge in and you forget about it.
Don't forget that you ever even did it.
823-8801 is our second phone number.
823-8801, we may have a second pledge right now.
Call and pledge now.
823-8801.
If this is how he wants to go out...
I don't have a way to say it except that I just went out of bullshit.
Yeah.
.
Well, I told you
And I don't know what you got to do
But I'm not your picnic cake
Not your picnic cake
I like budget
And I might like a good buffet
But I'm not your picnic cake
Not your picnic cake
I like budget
And I don't know what you got to do
But I'm not your picnic cake
Don't forget the eight
I'd love to go on a picnic
But I'm not an eight
No, I'm not an eight
I'm not a picnic
But there was a giant female subgenius here
To tell you
To hold the show for us
To squeeze out the
Squeeze out the
Call her
You give off a good phone
Hi kids, welcome to Subgenius USA
We don't care if you're single, double, triple, top, duple
Women tuple, sex tuple, septuple, hop tuple
Men tuple, that's a tuple
Disinventionals
This is a special message
That's right
We're not wasting time
We know we're sexist pigs
We know we're all screwed up
Sexist!
Yeah!
We're just sexist pigs
And I don't care who knows it
You can't use those words on the radio
It does not work
You don't want to use those words
There's too much male energy on your show
You can call us up and tell us we're other stupid or anything
Listen to music
Smell our nader parents
And relax
And if you're 11
We're really good guys
And we really want the best for all of us
Come here, you grim hawking
Careful not to trip over your own show
Stoke the cauldron higher
If you only realize that we really want you to be happy
Henbane and Nightwart
Drag it to
Even though we are
A little squirt
Sexist
Yeah
Thing
It's the little squirt show
We're the little squirt
That's right
All we do is squirt
No oozing allowed
No
Until someone comes down here and does it for themselves
What a silly show
Yes, if you think you've got a better show
You bring it to the air right now
Throw in the night worm of the dark
You come right down here to
Throw in Mobius' Tethoris
I was going to say KGO
But we're not allowed to use those callers
Or KPFA
Or any of those
KFAT
No, we can't talk about KFAT
KPOI
KOR
I don't know
Just write a letter to the station
And completely say
Dr. Hal said the bad word
Yeah
I didn't say anything
And some of those other guys helped
And whoever they are
They should be thrown off the radio
Because they play stuff like this all the time
Hey, I'm clean
I'm innocent
They're trained operators
I demand a fair trial
Reason sketched
That's right
You may play this whole thing
Trial by tape
They play old records
And then make trial by tape
All over themselves
Repent
Well, I told you
And I don't know yet
It got through
But I'm not your pink ape
What?
I'm not your pink ape
I live in a luncheon
Where you're eating food for April
I'm not your picnic ape
That's not your picnic ape
When you go on a picnic
Don't forget the ape
I'd love to go on a picnic
I don't want to go on a picnic
I'm aluminium rod hitting
But I am not an ape
I know I am not an ape
Oh, I'm not an ape
Not me
That's right
I should've said not I
I told you that I never could
Not even gone
You won't go on a picnic
Male Moderator 1 Well, that's all right
You got a chance
Hey, hey, hey!
That was quite funny
Oh, yes, dear friends.
That band, the guy that does that puts out a magazine that quotes from senile people.
He works in an old folks' home, and he records their wisdom and puts out a magazine of it.
But he also has this band called the Duplex Players, which we just played.
He records these guys and then uses them as lyrics to these beautiful songs.
So you see, they don't let anything go to waste in America today.
Oh, yes.
Folks, call in with that pledge.
823-7490.
You've got to do it.
Otherwise, you'll never hear.
Fill their minds with questions.
Oh, yes.
That's very, very interesting.
That's not interesting at all.
Oh, yes.
That's very, very interesting.
That's not interesting at all.
Oh, yes.
That's very, very interesting.
No, no, no, no.
Oh, yes.
That's very, very interesting.
I think we're very close to isolating the molecules that answer that question.
Oh yes, that's very, very interesting.
Well, look what's coming out of that hole in the ground.
A little bull quirk.
That's very, very interesting.
Do anything musical.
Okay, that's a rather fantastic question.
Very interesting, folks.
Very interesting.
Okay, friends, now the board's just not lighting up.
Now we need to give these numbers out again, and let's have those pledges.
823-7490, friends.
823-8801 and 823-8883.
Remember, you're not just pledging it for Bob.
You're pledging it for the station that keeps Bob on the air.
So let's have that board light up.
Let's have them pledges.
Those $1 pledges.
Those $50 pledges.
Those $100 pledges.
Those $10,000 pledges.
Folks, we only need a few of them.
We only need...
We only need 10 pounds of $100 bills to keep this station going, friends.
We only need six $10,000 pledges.
But I'll tell you what, it is getting very serious, and it involves legal situations.
And we're not just asking you to give money for Bob.
In fact, this is one of the few times when we're asking you to give Bob's money to somebody
else.
That's right, friends.
And that's usually against our religion.
That's how serious the situation is.
And this...
Well, you know what happens when this station goes off.
If this station were to go off the air, and these are not hollow threats, man...
And here's Buck Naked with a special offer, friends.
A hot offer for you people to pledge your money.
Okay.
Tell you what.
Do it now.
I want a $20 pledge, and you get a free button.
JR Bob Dobbs.
And I want you to call this special number.
EIEIE.
823-8883.
Call it in within the next five minutes, and you get that free button with your $20 pledge.
And all the other stuff you get.
What else do they get?
They get a newsletter, the KNON newsletter, which is actually not the drab little rag
that you would think.
It's insane.
I've seen it.
It's amazing.
It's entertaining.
Yes.
It's actually something you can keep.
It's yours.
It's yours forever.
Forever.
They get pamphlet number two, right?
Right.
They get subgenius pamphlet number two.
We've got to bring down a whole bunch of the brand new ones.
Well, why don't Buck Naked's special handcrafted church buttons, friends, for the first $20
pledge?
Face of Bob at 823-8883.
That's a special offer pledge.
Call it in now.
Light that second up.
Free bat rides every day.
Howdy, friends.
I'm Lord Jim Cravington for Medieval Motors, your friendly truck stop and transport service.
For more of this and other great things to come, go to MedievalMotors.com.
We've got the Gryphon, the Minotaur, or the Sporty Little Camel Leopard to suit your imaginary
travel needs.
And, gosh, what can I say about these little guys?
Yes, it's your all-new cardboard Vampirettes, the economy transport that's got them all
guessing on the other side.
We've got continents and peninsulas of new and used transfigurations and a secret rose
garden of perfect values.
So get your ass in gear and your oxen in here so as we can trade indulgences with the best
and get you on your path.
Now, we're just a painful mile off the freeway of lost hope
at the intersection of down and out avenues
in the Citadel of the Angel.
How you doing?
A lot of the good old boys are here tonight.
We'd like to welcome you down to the television mission.
Don't forget, if all you can do is sit at home,
then try to keep yourselves awake and dial the phone.
Call in for pledges.
Call in for pledges, yes.
We have a lot of our special beauties
answering the phones this evening.
And the best thing you can do
is dial this number that you see on your screen
as quickly as you can
with a contribution to the television mission.
Don't forget to call in a pledge.
Talk about Jesus.
Talk about Jesus?
Well, you never know who's going to be here this evening.
We're waiting for him.
Yes, well, it's one... I know you are, son.
I know it's one of the real positive qualities
of the television mission
is we just never know who's going to drop by
and we just never know who's going to drop by
I mean, it's a lot of folks have been...
The band is here.
The band is getting set up.
The band is ready.
And I'm here to tell you that it's time, ladies and gentlemen.
I want you to hold down your applause as long as you can
because it's time you heard from Red Greenback and the Blue Boys.
Don't forget to call.
The number's on your screen.
The Red Greenback and the Blue Boys
The number's not on your screen.
The number is on your speaker.
And that number to call is 823-7490.
And if you don't call, something very, very terrible can happen
not only to you and to the airwaves of Dallas,
but to all the life force which covers this great green globe.
If this station were to have any worse problems than it already does,
it could be pretty bad, friends.
It could be as bad as what happened tonight.
And thank you to Danny Ferguson of Arlington
for your pledge to the sub-G.I.B.
to nothing but continue our great temple.
It's done.
Thank you.
ROLmb umket pre
but don't give nvitt November 2019
on KCON Billiards Public SP,
Difficult in to art haben wir dar
Because we keep am ah path Basijas
We take your hor fazla
I'm sorry.
They had private eyes, but public fists.
Full tanks, but clean consciences.
And tonight's story is only typical.
Car Hook.
Starring Dirk Yogurt as Dick Private, Private Dick.
Tonight's chilling story.
Roller Maidens from outer space.
Saturday morning.
I'd just locked myself out of the office for a cool weekend.
I promised to be gin-soaked and hand-rubbed.
At least that's what I figured she'd meant when she said,
Let's get drunk.
Let's get drunk and refinish my furniture.
Anyway, it was the way she said it, you know.
Real husky, like a lead dog in a snow job.
And I wasn't about to be left out in the cold.
Damn nation.
Ah, well, I figured it wouldn't hurt just to answer it.
A private Seamus is always hungry.
I hadn't been exactly flush,
and this might just be the ace in the closet
that put some pizza in the pantry.
Go ahead, something said to me.
Answer it, she'll wait.
So I did.
Only to wind up holding the anchovies in more ways than one.
Dick Private, Private Detective.
Ah, Mr. Private.
That's right, pal.
My name is Regular Boinklin.
My wife, Ethel and I have been opposite you for many years on another network.
Oh, yeah.
The Ethel and Regulus show. I've heard of you.
What's the matter? Swallow your car keys?
No.
Lock yourself out of the house?
Want to know how to make an attractive bookend out of a shoebox?
No, nothing that exciting.
But look, look, look, you've got to get over here.
Well.
Right away.
You're just a couple of channels away.
You can make it.
Nobody ever made it before.
No, come on. It's really weird over here.
Well, it ain't no Swiss picnic over here, pal.
But you don't under, under, understand.
It's terrifying. Nothing is normal.
Well.
We all seem to be dreaming the same dream.
Well, that's true.
That's true.
And there's all these strange balls of light in our neighborhood and...
Hold it.
Glad to.
Now hold it up to the light.
Oh, okay.
You was right. This was serious.
This is serious. This is extremely serious.
Friends, we need your help.
I've never seen so much light on these boards lighting up.
It's not the right kind of light, doctor.
God, these amiable simps don't...
It's not the right kind of light. We want that green light.
We want that light from that money coming in. That's what we want.
Oh, yes. We want to, we want to...
Friends, you don't know the purity of a 10,000 pound stack of dollar bills.
That's right, friends.
Or the savage horror of not having this station on the air.
So let's try again. The numbers are 823-7490, 823-8801, and 823-8883.
And folks, you get the newsletter, the KNON newsletter, the bumper stickers,
the free subgenius pamphlet number two.
That's pamphlet number two, friends.
That's right. Now, you subgenius members out there that are wondering,
where's my pamphlet number two? You'll get yours in the mail anyway.
But, oh, ye unsaved out there. Ye unsaved folks that could be, if you could but...
If you could but pay for this radio station that you're listening to and enjoying right now.
That's right. You pay for all the rest of them by putting up with the commercials.
That's right, friends.
You put up, you pay for all the rest of them by hearing the sound.
Same thing over and over and over again.
Things much worse than pledge drives.
Yes, yes there are worse things than pledge drives.
Friends, we'd like to thank Sherry Williamson-Fort Worth for calling her pledge into the hour of slack.
Thank you, Sherry. And you people out there that haven't called yet, those numbers one more time.
823-7490, 823-8801, and 823-8883.
Just put your finger on the line.
Just put your finger on the little button and push it.
Music
Yes, friends, well we're going to go right back on the air in order to...
In order to ask you to pledge your money to K-N-O-N, friends.
It's got to happen sooner or later or we'll never stop this show.
If you don't send money to K-N-O-N, we won't get out of this station.
The next show won't come on.
We'll keep talking in here until the station disappears, shriveled up by the conspiracy which will sap away the slack.
And you can stop that conspiracy, friends.
The slack of...
The slack of K-N-O-N, friends.
All you've got to do is give a little bit.
Reach into that checkbook.
Shove your hand into that back pocket.
Get out those wallet stretchers and see how far you can stretch that money into the direction of K-N-O-N, friends.
Cough it up. Cough it up.
823-7490 or 823-8801.
It was still a little bit...
When he talked about it, he said this is up in the east.
And I've got some super vision.
Anyway, I walked out of the door and looked up in the east and saw this bright star.
He didn't know what it was.
Barstow didn't know whether it was a star or a planet or a weather balloon or what it was.
And I walked out there in the backyard in my pajamas.
I looked at this thing.
And I saw some people coming out of that.
And I saw that damn thing.
Boy.
Pardon me.
You saw this thing.
Was it close by?
No.
It was way out there in the east in the sky.
Well, you could see people in it?
Yeah.
He said he had super vision.
He was out of that thing.
.
Man cannot participate in long space expeditions.
NASA has scientifically verified and kept very quiet
the fact that the unstoppable cosmic rays to which every astronaut has been exposed
destroys brain cells at the rate of 1% every four months.
Since the neurons of the adult human brain do not...
Ah, yes.
Yes, the punches are coming in, and here's Pastor Buck naked with a couple of new ones.
Mark Shopey.
Thanks a lot, guy.
And Sherry Williams.
Fort Worth.
Williamson.
Yes, of Fort Worth.
Thank you very much.
A big help.
All right.
Okay.
Cheers, like, to Rosalia.
Thank you, bird.
Ooh.
Who are you people that want to talk about...
About slack, friends?
There's not going to be any slack tonight until you send that money in.
You'll get that slack the minute you write the check.
You'll feel it flowing up through your ballpoint pen into your fingertips.
This whole show is to give you a beatific vision of slack, friends,
and I think that, you know, you're going to have to realize
that the luck plane to slant our way is going to have to have a little...
A little weight on one end of the slack plane, friends.
There's a little pile of $10 and $20 bills stacked up here and there.
You're going to have to go out there and shift that plane.
Yes, indeed.
Hey, dog, you ain't got nothing coming over your TV.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Because I love you.
How fun.
Forever.
Something wrong with Dad.
Something wrong with you.
You.
Hans, oh Hans! Hans, you are my lover.
Hans, Hans!
He is my lover!
My lover!
What?
Something wrong with you.
You!
Fast, bring it, change!
You! A revolution!
What is wrong?
This is a revolution!
Revolution!
Stop that!
Don't do that!
And I am going off for a beer.
Forget it. Forget it.
But...
The bird just isn't there.
Gone he was here.
In heaven again.
Now a planet.
In the fear of the dead.
See you in heaven again.
Red, red, the red.
God, rot the sucker, rot your hair.
You wanna be lonely?
No.
Go without me.
You.
I love you.
I love everybody, honey.
I love you so.
I like everybody to be happy.
I love it.
I give you them a...
The genie in there make it happen, I tell you.
God, you're the lord.
You're the lord.
Keep to me talking.
Keep talking to me singing.
I love you.
You're the way he is.
Why?
Everybody a rat.
I ask everybody to believe.
That's a thing.
Well, in the Bible,
they say
we were speaking in tongues.
Tongues.
I am a rat!
A rat!
Just a rat!
Let's go, girls.
The time is special.
Nowhere else.
I mean the time
I hold you.
Amen, praise the Lord.
There's a revolution
going on.
And it's to them.
Yes, friends.
Bob does love you.
And he'll love you more
if you'll join that pledge drive right now.
Dr. Stang, would you please
give out the numbers?
Yes, friends, that's
823-7490.
And get your pencil
because there's another one.
823-8801.
That's right.
And there's one more.
If you want to hear more bizarre, demonic sounding music
from the airwaves
or the inspirational, beautiful,
classical
songs of Bob,
why, you have to call
823-8801.
823-8883, doctor.
Or, doctor,
821-8579.
But especially,
823-7490.
Call in and deposit
the money.
That earthly check.
That offering.
That pledge.
All you have to do is promise it right now.
It's a non-pledge. You can't lose.
You're pledging it to KNOA and it's a non-pledge.
Ah, yes, friends. And it's so sad because our time
is already running out when we hear that music
at the end of these shows.
But, doctor, we've got a $40 pledge we have to give credit for.
Oh, yes.
Ah, yes. Wendell Scott of Dallas, thank you so much.
And may slack flow through your body.
May slack drip down your spine
and out every
side of your pants.
Oh, friends. Oh, friends.
We have to leave you for the next religion and so...
And so,
as we sign off, once again,
friends, send that money to
KNON and to the Church of the
Subgenius for the Home for Slackless
Children because that money keeps those
we hate starving to death.
And, uh, uh,
get your pencils ready because we'll be reading
our address for information
here coming up at the
end of the broadcast.
Oh, yes, this has been
Reverend Ivan Stang with G. Gordon Gordon,
Pastor Buck Naked, Buddy West,
and the folks who will be taking over
the show next week, Batman himself.
Ah, yes.
He'll play the amazing tapes. Oh,
friends. And that's
the Church of the
Subgenius.
P.O. Box
1403 06
Dallas, Texas
Yeah, or call
823-7490
823-8801
That's money.
Oh,
yes, dear friends, it's so
beautiful to
God to see that
phone line light
up. Ah, there it is.
Yes, more $40 pledges.
More paper slack.
Paper slack. We all need slack,
friends. Slack in the face
of the hideous conspiracy
that tries to shut down anything
that tries to talk
about the things that they
don't want anyone
to talk about. Stop them.
Oh, stop them. That's what they try
to do.
Ah, thank you, dear friends.
Drinking Budweiser
on TV
Swallowing
Redman
The day my coon dog
died
Reading the pamphlet
over and over
again
I was
drinking Budweiser
and Bob was on
the TV
The day that Uncle
and Bob was on the TV
got kicked
by a mule
I was with cousin
Junior
The DNA
backfired
I was drunk
I was plastered
I was drinking Budweiser
I was drunk in Budweiser
And Bob was on TV
Drinking Budweiser
Watching Bob on TV
Swallowing
Redman
The day my coon dog died
Swallowing Redman
I was reading the pamphlet
Over and over again
I was drinking Budweiser
And Bob was on TV