In obtaining this record, you have taken the first step towards self-improvement, toward attaining those goals that are important to you.
Not that this or any other record contains any magical powers, or that any spoken words have the power to transform you in any way.
The power is within you, within your mind, and more specifically, within that part of your mind of which you most likely are unaware.
The Self-Genius Power of Swagging!
I did get to be on his show, and here it is.
That turning point through the daily in-depth study of God's Word.
We are quickly lining up. We want to see you. We want to help you.
And I want you not to miss Dallas tomorrow night.
Please put it on your calendar. Get there. Be there.
It's going to be a night unlike any that city has ever seen.
And Dallas has seen some pretty strange things.
So don't miss it for anything.
And speaking of some pretty strange things, before I get to the rest of you callers out there at 1-800-821-TALK,
we've got some publicity.
There are some publicity seekers out there.
They are a strange bunch.
Maybe someday we'll do a larger show on them.
But I wanted to talk to them briefly because some of them plan to be there tomorrow night.
Yes, I am aware of them.
I have been sent their literature through the years and have never really talked to one of these particular people.
But some of you may be aware of the Church of the Subgenius and their God, Bob.
At least they have good taste, tongue in cheek.
And I've got one of their representatives on the line with me right now, direct from Dallas.
Ivan Stang.
Ivan!
Oh, Bob, at long last.
You are the current church leader of the Church of the Subgenius.
Well, I just work here, Bob.
I'm working for Mr. Dobbs.
Bob Dobbs.
Right, Bob Dobbs.
I'll tell you, I'm so glad to finally be on your show.
I've been listening for years.
Years?
Well, especially around Halloween.
I love your Halloween shows.
Now, how have I managed to fail by not getting through your thick head after all these years to get you from Bob to God?
Oh, you, Bob, you have saved me so many times.
I have converted over to Christianity almost every time I ever listen to your show.
And then go back.
Well, we believe in the short-duration personal savior phenomenon.
Bob Dobbs himself considers himself a short-duration personal savior.
Now, come on.
Now, you people have really had...
10,000 people ante up $30 a piece to join this internet religion, this religion of the
quickie printer, tabloid-style cigar-smoking, pipe-smoking God who will come to Earth soon
to take everybody away in pleasure saucers.
You've really gotten people to pay $30 a piece?
Oh, yeah.
Absolutely.
And we've sold about 100,000 copies of our books.
Okay.
So what now?
I mean, we've been around for 20 years.
Now, in a nutshell...
Now, for the people out there who've never heard of this sort of thing before, you are
what?
Well, the Church of the Subgenius is a religion that Bob started specifically to help the
mutants, the misfits, the disbelievers, and also those who would believe anything in our
fight against the conspiracy of the normal people.
But you're definitely not normal.
Nobody's going to ever accuse you of that.
Well, in that respect, I think we probably have a lot in common, Bob.
All right.
Touché.
You believe that the world is due for demolition on July the 5th, 1998 at 7 a.m.?
Praise Bob.
That is correct.
52 days from now.
And if it doesn't happen?
What kind of a question is that?
I mean, you think we're going to end up looking ridiculous like those poor little religious
nuts here in Garland right around the corner from me?
Remember the...
Oh, yes.
Yes.
God's Salvation Church.
Yeah, the Taiwanese folks.
Yeah, they happen to just be very, very nearby.
I went over there and gave them my $30 just in case, you know.
We've been telling people to have faith in Bob.
I figure I might as well practice what I preached for once.
Now, you say it's...
In your literature, you say it's not too late to be saved.
All you have to do is send $30 to Bob.
And I want folks to understand this is not Bob Larson.
This is Bob Dobbs the God.
Oh, Bob?
Yeah.
Yeah, Bob Dobbs is probably a lot cheaper for salvation than you are, Bob.
And you can eternal salvation or triple your money back.
It's not a bad deal now, is it?
Well, how do you know if you don't get it to get your money back?
Well, you'll have to cross that bridge when you come to it.
Now, some people...
Let me put it this way.
If you end up in hell as a result of investing $30 in Bob Dobbs' church,
he will meet you at the gates of hell with a check for $90 and a little booklet called
How to...
Enjoy Hell for Five Cents a Day.
It's $89.95, I think.
Now, other than having a good laugh and creating something out of minds that otherwise would
be wasted on something probably even worse than this, what are you people up to?
Basically, Bob, we've declared war on God.
Now, I know that that sounds...
I mean, that's kind of taken on a big job.
We've been pulling God's leg for a long time.
And that's a very large leg.
It takes a lot of nerve, and you damn well better be funny if you're going to do it.
But we have gotten so sick and tired of this invisible monster that everybody keeps talking about
that is so weak and pathetic that it has to be defended by illiterate little old ladies
and rednecks against jerks like me.
Now, what kind of a God is that?
We're just sick and tired of putting up with it.
This thing's been, you know, allowing...
Starvation and hunger and all this stuff all over the world.
We've just had enough.
They've been telling us for years we were going to go to hell.
What else could we do but start our own religion?
Are you guys going to be there tomorrow night?
Yeah, I wouldn't miss it for the world.
Now, we don't plan any kind of disruptions.
We're generally very polite folks.
Well, you're going to see God tomorrow night.
You're going to see God in action.
You're going to see the supernatural like you've never seen it before.
Then what?
Well, if I'm impressed, I'm sure I'll convert.
I've...
And put $30 in the offering.
Many gods have a lot of chances,
and I've worshipped many, many gods and demons,
but, you know, I always end up coming back to old Bob Dobbs.
Now, there are people out there who probably think
you are some secret friend of mine that I just put up to this for comic relief.
I don't know.
You haven't mentioned.
You people contacted me this week and said,
Oh, by the way, since Bob's coming to Dallas,
maybe he'd like to talk to us.
Oh, yeah.
We happen to have been, you know,
because our end of the world is coming up very soon,
we've been on kind of a big PR blitz.
And I'll tell you what, Bob,
it is a big relief for me to talk to somebody
with even the slightest bit of sense,
because mostly I've been on the radio with drive-time classic rock jocks,
which is the lowest form of life on earth.
You and I absolutely agree.
And I'd rather be talking to a fellow religious nut
than one of these normals, if you don't mind,
you know, present company excluded.
Yeah, yeah.
I have Richard on the line.
Richard, you called in a second ago to ask a question about this guy.
What's your question, Richard?
Yeah, I wanted to know if basically if this kind of thing was serious.
Oh, friends.
Oh, man.
I forgot how funny all that stuff was.
This guy called in who he was actually the guy from the alt dot.
Fan dot Bob dash Larson News Group,
which is not really a Bob Larson fan club.
They actually kind of make fun of the guy and so forth.
And this anti-Bob Larson guy called up and said,
Reverend Stang, what are you doing on the air with this adulterous radio preacher?
And I knew what he was talking about, Bob Larson.
Bob Larson has had some problems in that respect,
much like our current acting president.
You know, some guys just have these organs.
I'm sorry.
And I jumped in and said, you must be talking about me.
I'm sure you're not talking about Bob Larson.
And the caller said, well, basically they censored him.
Yeah.
He was totally, completely removed from all human reality.
Oh, but check out what Larson tuned in as he faded back in after the, you know, censored out stuff.
He fades back in going, well, you know, I've got a lot more nuts calling me than you have in your whole religion.
And, you know, friends, he's right.
And it's kind of a sad commentary, isn't it?
I've got more nutcases who listen to me than follow you.
And we're not going to glorify these idiots out there and jerks who try to take advantage of religious fanatics like you to attack sane people like me.
But, Ivan, I want to know, in all seriousness, how many people belong to your religion?
It's just you and a couple of buddies.
Where do you get the figure of 10,000?
No, we, Bob, quite simply.
Seriously, we have four books that have been published by Simon & Schuster, the first one being Book of the Subgenius.
It's still in print.
About 100,000 copies is sold.
I've printed, well, 60,000 or 70,000 copies of our little pamphlet, our equivalent of one of those chick comics.
And we have had at least 10,000 members sign up over, I mean, we've been around for 15 years.
Bob predicted that there would be millions of them and that we would have taken over the world by now.
But I think the conspiracy read Bob's prophecies, too.
And prophecy heeded is prophecy fulfilled.
And you are the sacred scribe of the church.
I'm the one, I'm the guy who has to do a lot of the dirty work, yeah.
I assign the sacrifices and that kind of thing.
All right, well, I tell you what, one of these days we're going to get you back and talk a little longer.
I would suggest, however, beware those little old illiterate ladies, as you refer.
I referred to them a moment ago.
Because there are some godly women of the Lord who deeply resent what you just said.
And they are going to kick your spiritual butt with the power of prayer if you show up on Friday night.
So beware.
Those people that you denigrate have got more spiritual power and common eternal horse sense.
And they're looking for you.
But this little finger than you've got in a lifetime of pursuing illicit religions.
And they're ready to take you on and they're ready to pray you into the kingdom.
So I say prayer warriors, my friends in Dallas, be there.
As you can see, it's going to be an interesting evening.
I got David on the line.
Hello, David.
Let's go from the ridiculous to the sublime.
David.
There are so many logical and thoroughly possible ways in which the entire tribe of mankind.
time could be wiped off the earth at any moment hey hey why don't you knock on that trap door
there and say y'all three times go ahead do it man okay y'all y'all no i'm not gonna say it the
third time because you know i won't get one i didn't think i was gonna that's right that's right
i know your tricks last time i did i had bad luck for 10 years man that's where old me mr
mr tooth decade that's right and then ultimately that was because of your truth decay when one
stops to think what a tiny little grain of sand this haughty world of ours actually is in the dark
sea of space the spectacle of man's inhumanity to man becomes a cosmic joke what's interesting to a
dog to run to a hunter with a pack to kill uh master uh uh mr bush says my opponent
wants dick it's wrong to cross against the cars and when i'm president we will tell scientists
that they can't lead the world against the computers
i want dick certainly the president's very large and very important
there you go large and important friends uh thanks lemur
and artemia celina
and welcome dear friends to hour of slack number 1614 and we're going to start with a rant
a rant called i have no ass and i must by roger n a
formerly known as the good reverend roger now roger n a
routique
boys there talking about more thrifting people and the
rd
i'm
Now, I normally do not soil myself with human politics, but it's impossible to avoid this
time around.
The moment you turn on the TV or the internet, an avalanche of raw sewage pours out and ruins
the carpet.
It's like a production line making assholes, one right after another, and there's no getting
away from it.
So, I've stopped trying, and so I'm going to do my part to push this bad puppy right
off the cliff.
It's not a time to keep a straight face, and life is going to be very, very hard on those
who aren't serious about having a good time.
And I plan on having a very good time indeed.
Who can blame me?
Actual, real, no bull.
Bullshit Nazis are coming out of the woodwork thinking their day has come.
The hills are alive with the sound of hayseeds and Klan members screeching and touching themselves
in triumph.
But the funny thing is, even though their guy won, nothing is working out for him.
The senate is a tangled mess, the courts are publicly urinating on executive orders, and
the people who voted for Trump are devouring themselves.
Oh, that's just the way things are.
spitting out bits of their own skin as they proclaim that America is going to be great again.
It is. You just watch.
Never mind that people in Kentucky don't look happy at their victory,
or West Virginia, or the suddenly impoverished cattle kings in Texas and New Mexico.
Never mind that some po-buckers are starting to mumble about their health care
as if they suddenly realized that all the things Trump said apply to them too,
and that this is real, not just showing those liberals a thing or two.
Richard Spencer got a flying elbow to the jaw,
and the alt-right started asking where the liberal tolerance went.
But we were all too busy laughing to listen.
A long time ago, a few crusty old subgeniuses talked about
the fact that we were all so busy laughing that we couldn't even listen.
The coming weird times.
Well, those times are here now, and they're going to get a lot weirder.
I'm okay with that.
I'm on the crazy train with the primates,
making choo-choo noises while the boiler overheats,
and I wouldn't trade it for anything!
Well, almost anything.
I'd kind of like for my aging parents to have health insurance and all that good stuff,
but since that isn't going to happen,
why not roll the state down the stairs just to hear it crash?
I've become an unrepentant wrecker,
and I make no apologies for it.
This is, after all, what 61 million people demanded.
They, being the idiotic hominids they are,
wanted an administration that would pay attention to them.
Be careful what you wish for, stupid humans.
This is exactly why you can't have nice things.
But you and I, dear listener,
we're Yeti, and we will not be governed!
We wobble.
We oscillate.
When you crush us in the fist of the state,
we just sort of ooze out between its fingers
and dance off down the street laughing
and happy slapping passing po-buckers.
They may have two million people under arms
and twice as many people under arms,
and twice as many police,
but we have Bob.
They may have the banks,
but we have slack.
They may have twelve aircraft carriers,
but we have Dr. Legame and G. Gordon Gordon.
Even if he had to leave the country for reasons best left unspoken.
Orton Nenslow once said that if you,
quote,
freak the mundanes,
they'll find ways to make sure you wish you were never born.
But they're doing that anyway,
so why not take them with us?
Why not skip merrily along into the apocalypse
with your pants full of shit
and a stupid grin on your face?
Anyway,
that's why I can't rant anymore.
Or kill me!
Well, kill Reverend Roger N.A., friends, actually.
He wrote that, I didn't.
But hey, here's a pertinent and brand new song
from an upcoming album, an unreleased album,
by Exposed Foreheads.
You're hearing it here first.
Push Me by Exposed Foreheads.
I understood you everything,
I want you to see
And we're free.
Or representing your paymentéré n房.
la muita n Health quiere,
suda a说?
Au revoir!
Bye bye!
Me cerro yo que voy
Yo elegante
I'm your family
You have driven me mad Wei
Hook her up, gonna raise the bar
Time's up, show us where you are
Step up, it's time to commit
Plane to sea, we all stepped in it
Let your pants down, gonna dance now
Lead me to the ledge, push me to the edge
Mark my words, time will come
Step up, we're here for fun
We want it now, we want more
We're not the droids you're looking for
Let your pants down, gonna dance now
Lead me to the ledge, push me to the edge
Oh-eh-oh
Hey!
Let your pants down, gonna dance now
Lead me to the ledge, push me to the edge
It's a joke, it's not funny
Open the cage, I'm not your monkey
Here's the judge, here's the steeple
Open the cage, free the people
Time's up, we won't behave
This ain't your new wave
Step up, it's time to commit
Claim to seed, we all stepped in it
Let your pants down, gonna dance now
Lead me to the ledge, push me to the edge
Oh-eh-oh
Let your pants down
Gonna dance now
Lead me to the ledge
Push me to the edge
Amazing!
Push Me by Exposed Foreheads.
And that band name is spelled starting with an X,
and the second word begins with the numeral 4.
And now we have another subgenius rant.
In fact, it's a live, all-new,
Subgenius 101 type of introductory rant
by Reverend Baby Bear,
delivered at the 2017 Winter Star Ball in Cleveland
at the Beachland Ballroom.
But it is sadly incomplete, friends.
Neighbor Joe recorded it on his phone,
but it ran out of batteries after five minutes.
And he started kind of late,
so he caught her just as she started explaining
the conspiracy.
This is THE conspiracy,
or, as we call it,
The Con for short.
And believe me,
they are in fact looking to con you.
The conspiracy lives within all of us.
Yes, you too.
And you, yes.
You, all of you.
And many of those responsible don't even know they're part of a conspiracy.
It's that insidious.
It's that need to squash the weird, the strange, and the different.
That need to shave off
all the rough edges
until you leave everything smooth and regular.
The idea that you can buy your way to happiness
if you only got that new car,
or the right brand of beer,
or picked up that new gizmo or gadget to complete you and make you whole.
But, of course,
your slack lies not within what you can buy.
Slack is here to set you free from the bonds of the conspiracy.
Free,
from the guilt and the insecurity and the falseness.
Free for $35.
All of that is free for $35.
Now what kind of a deal is that?
It's a good one by golly.
We're the only church to offer you your money back guarantee,
salvation,
or triple your money back.
If you find yourself at the gates of hell with no Bob in sight,
we will be there for you.
We will give you triple your money back.
The fact that we've never had to offer such a refund
should be proof positive
that what we are selling is bona fide and true.
Why,
could we possibly stay in business if we were liars?
Of course not.
Wouldn't the free market separate the chaff from the wheat
and we'd be on the cutting room floor?
Capitalism in action!
Praise Bob, this system works!
Praise Bob!
Now there is another important aspect to this church
that I would like to expound upon,
and that is X Day.
Now we all know that we're here for Starwood,
but did you all know that there is another weirdo festival
that takes place at Wisteria before Starwood?
Yes!
It's going!
It's called X Day,
and this year is the year.
It's finally,
1998.
Every subgenius worth his bath salts
knows that the world will end on July 5th, 1998.
We also know, of course, that 1998 has yet to come.
Otherwise, we wouldn't be here.
Duh.
The conspiracy has attempted to hijack the calendar
so we don't quite know what year it is.
But I am so very confident
that this year will finally be the year
that the Xists come
to sweep us up into the boundless pleasures of space
and leave the world a burning cinder behind us.
Yes.
There is another reason to get right with Bob,
aside from the wisdom of his infinite stupidity.
Bob struck a deal with a group of beings known as the Xists.
They were able to agree on a date,
July 5th, 1998,
as the time that destruction would befall
this benighted and belligerent dustball that we are all upon.
And that subgeniuses alone would be spared from this calamity
to be taken aboard the escape vessels of the sex goddesses,
or sex gods,
or amorphous shape-shifting aliens,
or whatever it is that you're into,
no judgement here.
And with them,
we would fly through space forever
and know the bountiful pleasures of slap.
It's so crazy, it must be true!
In...
Oh, thank you.
In closing,
if seeing advertisements for fast food
can cause your mind to go screaming,
screaming through time and space,
and break down into an existential crisis,
if watching a co-op worker twirl their hair
makes you feel like you're going to murder someone,
if the bland realities of this world
can cause mental trauma
until you don't know if you're crying from laughing
or laughing from...
Crying.
I'm crying.
Because the tape ran out,
and we never get to hear the rest of Reverend Baby Bear's rant.
About the only thing that's going to make me feel any better about that
is cheery music.
In this case, an instrumental by Reverend Robert R.
called...
The Goats! They March!
The Goats, The TheoryGills!
And they throw their own silly,
about sacred Luke!
zóþar!
.
. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . .
Thank you.
Is that a live one on the Satanist line?
Patch them through to me. I'm in the mood.
Thanks. Hello, this is Satan.
Can I help you? Hello?
Yes. Yes, real time.
Your altar is working. Prayer is
answered. Metroton here, aka
Satan. Hello. I hope you are well.
Use your head. I don't
need a phone, because I am the devil,
as you call him. As you have called
me. If you're a thinker, it's because
every atom vibrates, and we Archangels
can tune frequencies. Whoa!
Smart kid.
Okay. Satisfied? No hidden
devices anywhere in that ritual space you
just smashed up? And now stage
two, panic. Easy. Deep
breaths. Relax. It's okay.
Can I tell you a joke? You
cracks me up
how solemnly you fools always do the magic
right up until you find it really working.
Okay.
No, no. It always works. Just this
one time, I decided not to ignore
you punks with your hoary old orisons, and I
picked up. Please don't make me regret it.
Yeah, this is really.
You skipped ahead to the cynical phase.
The fawning worship is boring, but
not so fast. I will have
your respect. I am he whom you called
up. Metroton, the fired Archangel.
You're still
there. Well, thank you, since you addressed
me as sir. Yes, I'll take a few questions,
but no. No, no. I'm
not in the wish-granting business. Never was.
And this is not even my name.
You know who you get when you call up like this?
Not Satan. Sanitation.
This is my office line. I'm chief
of psychic discharge, disposal, and recycling.
No, the only joke
is how you humans can abuse the gift
of faith. One guy writes
down something he pulled out of his ass, and soon
you're all taking it like it's fact. This is a
serious problem you have. Like, call
in me the evil one? Like thinking
garbage men are made of garbage.
Well, good luck telling anyone.
Oh, psychic discharge.
Or karma clean-up? You could call us the
ultimate spa and recreation center.
Yeah, but listen, it is
no fun trying to force your way down
here. Got that? No guards,
no heroic struggles, just
suicides are plopped alone into a
hideous nightmare swamp.
Eventually they do, but
that's right, we don't burn
anything. The only hellfire
is a few fanatically devout
arrivals who immolate themselves with frustrated
blind faith and goddamn pride.
We try yelling over and over between
their shrieks, only you can stop this.
We can't. But, oh, you think
that's cool, huh? Jesus.
Yeah, I do, in fact. He and I
are on okay terms, and I'm still
employed by the same wise and wonderful
boss in a vital, mostly boring
career with duties and benefits.
I like it. The good life is the same
everywhere, kid. A mix of...
May I suggest you first
get a life before suggesting I've
sold out? I know, you wanted a big
badass rebel for chaos!
Welcome to reality.
No, you listen! I don't give one preacher's
toasted gonad, if you believe me or not.
You need to hear this. My staff and I lost
the human power contract because we were
just like you, young and proud and smart, yet
too dumb to know how little we really
knew. I'm glad we got schooled and moved
into garbage where more engineers ought to be put.
I'm sorry, I started dumping on you.
What's your name, son?
You're welcome, David. And again, sir,
I apologize. I bet too many
yell at you already. I can
do better. Little friendly advice?
Life's a constant balancing act,
like a seesaw rocking between
ideal and practical, self-defense
and giving. I'm no one special,
yet I am special.
Best way to find the sweet spot each time
is to start low-key, participating.
Two ears, one mouth? Chill
is best. Yeah, that says it. You're a
thinker. You keep a journal? Aye.
I'm really glad I met you,
David. You're a righteous dude.
Thank you, but don't get a big head about this, okay?
We met purely by chance, just
like winning the lottery. Well,
can't say I never even give Satanis the time
of day. Sometimes I do. At the
tone, the time will be
wasted! Tom!
Tom! Tom! It's only
teenage wasteland!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
That was
Reverend Watt D.
Falk, with
a call-in to Satan.
Thank you, Reverend Watt
D.
Falk.
And now we're gonna cut back to the summer of
2016, 19X Day.
Uh,
it's a bit with
Dr. Howell about a new
subgenius game that I had just
gotten in the mail.
This was recorded live in front of an
audience at Wisteria's
Cafe.
Tell him about the buttons.
The buttons. Tell him about the buttons.
Oh yeah, yeah, we got a, um,
oh wait.
We got a last minute
shipment in from the subgenius cafe
press shop
of the
very timely
don't blame me, I voted for Bob
button.
Which is gonna come in handy no matter
what, no doubt.
And we have ten of them.
I bought a ten pack. I think they're
four bucks a piece. We also
got some fridge magnets in that have the
Church of the Subgenius logo
drawn by
Hellswami Satellite Weavers
in 1979.
No, that would be
early 1980. Anyway, those are
available, fridge magnets in the button.
Oh, and here's something I need to
to both show off
and investigate. We'll all open this
together. This is a game
made by some people in
Austin called
Angry Ogre. Another
great Angry Ogre game. They
got permission to do a game called
Bob Balls.
They contacted me about
two years ago, I think.
It was a Kickstarter project
and I tried to
warn them, as I do
everybody. Don't expect to
make a lot of money off Church of the
Subgenius. We're not that
well known because the average
human being is not capable
of knowing of us.
That's why we're still
here. That's why they haven't
gotten, you know, done, ganged
up on us, which they could easily do. Anyway,
they actually did do their
game Bob Balls and I got a
I think they sold a grand
total of 29 of
them. I got
and I got a $135
royalty. But
I'm going to open this now.
It's not a
video game.
It's not a video game.
Uh...
We'll find out.
It's no longer insanely
collectible. I'm so excited. It's just like Christmas.
Woohoo! Oh, I wet
my pants.
Okay. Oh, look on the back
it has a green alien. It has a
green girl in a bikini on the back.
Holding
the Bob Balls box.
The official game
of Over Men Everywhere.
That's sexist.
The Bob Ball offers
a perfect combination of awesome
and balls in a
revolutionary mind-altering format.
This instant classic is a
reimagining of the longer to brew
hit game you've heard only whispers
about from another tier of
consciousness. Try to
save your mutant family and get them to
the pleasure craft before X-Day.
Beware, there's only enough room
on the love saucer for one family.
Well, they must not know about
St. Andrew's. Saucer built
for infinity. The other
will be condemned to fry
on earth with the rest of the normals.
So pull the wool over your own
eyes, grab some dice,
and praise Bob or
kill him. You've never played
with balls like this.
Wow.
That's pretty good.
Now,
the box comes out. Now he's
opening the box, ladies and gentlemen.
It's got skulls and
attacking people on
the rim. And there's
that symbol,
like a caveman.
A caveman trying to strike
a skull. He's trying to hit a skull there.
It could be the mindless primitive trying
to suppress the emergent
subgenius. Or it could be a
yeti trying to strike down
the imago of death.
And get this, it has a CD
with it. I had no idea. Songs
to play Bob ball
and to do other things to
too. Well,
maybe you better spin that platter
down.
They've done the printing in such a way
it's like green on orange. It's hard to read.
Bob ball intro,
yeti calls,
rob a bank,
bobby bubble,
baduino,
mario 2-ish,
bottle of beer, pirate dance,
tired of light and fires,
A E I O U,
hey hey mojo,
it goes on and on and on.
We'll see.
Here's the rule book.
It's not very long.
We like
short rule books.
We only have one real rule.
Fuck them if they can't take a joke.
Move each Dobbs head in a straight
line the number of pips
on the assigned die.
Hmm, okay.
You have three dice to roll.
Oh cool, look there's little plastic
dice with the Dobbs head.
Numbers on all sides
except for the Dobbs head. Dobbs head dice and then
some pieces white and some pieces
pink with Dobbs heads
in pyramids. But why don't you open up
the board, Stang? Let's see what the board
looks like. The whole game is built around
the board.
Open it up and
huh?
Well it's got an eyeball in the middle
of it. That's always a good sign.
Flying saucers on the borders.
That's a standard procedure.
It looks like the
Tholian web, if you'll pardon the
reference.
Let's push play on that. So
I don't know, I guess
maybe somebody can game test.
Yes, we have so many game
players here, maybe they'd like to
play Bob
Ball.
Hi, I'm Reverend Ivan Stang and this is
Bob Ball. Darn it,
it's fun. The official game
of Over Men Everywhere.
Bob Ball offers the perfect combination of
awesome and
balls in a revolutionary
mind-altering format.
This instant classic is a reimagining
of the longer to
brew hit game you've heard only whispers
about from another tier of
consciousness.
There's some Bob
Ball music. Bob Ball music
going on.
Well this is, this is fun.
To look
at anyway. Yes,
this will be the one thing that makes the fortune
that eludes the church of the subgenius.
Don't forget this, you left this out.
Can't play Bob
Ball without your pink pieces
and there you go.
Well which is it young fella, you want ice
to freeze or get down on the ground?
Mean to say, if I freeze
I can't rightly drop.
If I drop, I'm gonna be in motion.
You see? Shut up!
Okay then.
They close the doors at 6pm
and they move the money
at night.
The blends are drawn, everything's
in order. It looks like
we're right on time.
Everybody check
your watch.
Tie your shoes and get in line.
Tonight's
a night of our sweet
Bob has given
us great insight and wisdom.
So it
is again with a heavy
heart that I see Bob rendering
public service to the people
of this country for some
period of time.
And it is a hope
that we are going to be able
to help Bob
fulfill
one of his whims
which is to sit
down and write a book.
He will not
because that book is
entitled Bob Matters
and I am much
richer for it.
Mr. President, I yield the floor.
No time to find the entrance.
I'll just drive straight to it through the solid rock.
No time for opening windows.
Clark Kent may need a plane but Superman doesn't.
Here's Bob One for A1 Slacks.
Hi, I'm Bob One
for A1 Slacks and I'd like to take a moment of your time.
Thank you.
And I'd like to tell you about the nice folks
down at A1 Slacks. They handle a needle
just the way your mother used to and the results
are racers, capers, tapers and bummers
such as you've never worn before.
The Action Man's Go-Go Now Generation
Happening Slacks for the Go-Go Now Generation
Action Man on campus and off.
And remember, you can get a good education
and win valuable prizes too.
Thank you, Bob. You're welcome.
And now, back to our movie.
Wherever there is mystery, intrigue, romance
in all the strange and dangerous
places of the world,
there you will find Bob.
I got off a plane, got off in Spain,
pulled it out and did the same damn thing.
I claim all these garbage dumps.
Hallelujah!
Shut up!
Thanks to Leigh Murr for the collages
and to the Firesign Theatre.
And now,
the Rudy Schwartz Project.
And then this Democrat mayor gets up
he said, wow, I think it's
time to celebrate the glorious life
And that was Donald Trump!
Tra la la,
empty in the air,
everybody sing because
we're celebrating today.
Ho yo yo,
slippity dippity do,
it's time to celebrate
the glorious life of Donald Trump.
Take the time to ponder
what Donald Trump has done for you.
Your neighbors are the bottom
eyes, their assholes through and through.
Stop and think what
Donald Trump has done for us.
Everyone's a fuckhead,
their brains are full of pus.
Tra la li,
with the yoodle far.
Everybody gather up,
come on, don't pass the buck.
Straddles, get down from
Ain't it Seattle? Hop and skip and chomp.
It's time to be a sociopath
and vote for Donald Trump.
Part of the problem
and part of the reason
it takes so long.
Nobody wants to hurt each other anymore, right?
And they're being politically correct
the way they take them out.
Look at my African American over here.
Look at him.
Are you the greatest?
I love the old days.
You know what they used to do to guys like that
when they were in places like this?
They'd be carrying them on a stretcher.
Oh Lord,
I'm so sorry.
Ah, will we dance in knowing tongue?
The ghost of less
mathematics will rise up and sing the song.
Wompty doodle
puddle dum, he's completely
nude. Donald's got
a boner, that's because he's
not a prude.
Lock the doors and get involved, rise up
and take a stand.
Donald Trump's the guy to make America
great again.
Are you watching Infowars or
spittle on your chin?
Lubricate your rectum with your
fist and we'll disdain.
Tra la lu,
cock-a-doodle-doo,
he'll deport the Mexicans,
the Muslims and the Jews.
Tra hit-a-lee dum,
stuff your head inside your room.
Join the clap and gout your
sheet and vote for Donald Trump.
Hop and dance, good-bye
to France, it's Mussolini's second
chance. Twenty million
white supremacists can't be wrong.
Tra la la,
yuck-a-doodle-doo,
donnie trump and
Vladimir Putin, party hand in hand.
Ho, yo, yo,
slippity-dippity-slump,
it's time for
all the yelping cause it's time for
Donald Trump. Every
once in a while, man, say the
brains are full of glass. It's time
to hear the air revolve.
Vote for Donald Trump.
I can punch him in the face,
I beg it.
We having a good time?
USA,
who is here?
alright yeah, get him out, try not to hurt him.
USA,
if you do I'll defend
you in court, don't worry about it.
USA,
The Rudy Schwartz Project friend. A song
we're forced to love.
and now, back to
Ask Dr. Hal
at 19xDeadrill
for a
bonus point.
from Dr. Howell.
Well, pardon me, Stang,
but that last one was a five-bucker.
I know.
So I've got to do another short one.
Oh, right, right.
I'll make it a quick one.
Now, this one is called
The Story of Jim
Who Ran Away from His Nurse
and Was Eaten by a Lion.
That's the title.
There was a boy whose name was Jim.
His friends were very good to him.
They gave him tea and cakes and jam
and slices of delicious ham
and chocolates with pink inside
and little tricycles to ride.
They read him stories through and through
and even took him to the zoo.
But there it was,
the dreadful fate befell him,
which I now relate.
You know, or at least you ought to know,
for I have often told you so,
that children never are allowed
to leave their nurses in a crowd.
Now, this was Jim's especial foible.
He ran away when he was able.
And on that inauspicious,
suspicious day,
he slipped his hand and ran away.
He hadn't got a yard when,
bang, with open jaws,
a lion sprang
and hungrily began to eat the boy,
beginning with his feet.
Now, just imagine how it feels
when first your toes and then your heels
and gradually, by slow degrees,
your shins and ankles,
calves and knees are slowly eaten,
bit by bit.
No wonder Jim detested it.
No wonder that he shouted,
hi!
The honest keeper heard his cry.
Though very fat,
he almost ran to help the little gentleman.
Ponto, he shouted as he came,
since Ponto was the lion's name.
Ponto!
Ponto, he ordered with a frown.
Release it!
Stop, sir!
Put it down!
The lion made a sudden stop
and let the dainty morsel drop
and slunk, reluctant to his cage,
snarling in disappointed rage.
But when he bent him over Jim,
the honest keeper's eyes grew dim,
the lion having reached his head,
the miserably,
miserable boy was dead.
When Nurse informed his parents,
they were more concerned than I can say.
His mother, as she dried her eyes, said,
well, this comes as no surprise.
He would not do as he was told.
His father, who was self-controlled,
bade all the children round attend
to James's miserable end
and always to keep home.
He was a hold of Nurse
for fear of catching something worse.
Hilaire Belloc.
All right, let's go on with the $1 level of questions.
No, how about the $1 level of show?
This was Hour of Slack number 1614,
assembled in March of so-called 2017,
at Tarzana.
Sands Radio Station at
stange-ranch-at-sub-genius-dot-com.
And that's the website you can look
at to know anything.
We've been busy,
we were at South by Southwest last week.
We were treated like princes and
space princesses.
it was fabulous
some wonderful people are working on a documentary
about Church of the Subgenius
and they filmed us
us and Dr. Philodrum and Dr. Paul Mavridis
and I'm sure you'll hear some good recordings from that
when they're done
in the meantime, friends
let's end with a delicate instrumental
from the Psychoskeletons called
Idea Man
again, this is the Psychoskeletons
Thank you the Psychoskeletons
and this is that little last tacked on
internet part of the show
friends where I, Reverend Ivan Stang
exhort you to whip it out
go ahead and join the Church of the Subgenius
we aren't kidding about that
you get some great stuff
with your $35 ministership
including the right to be a real minister
and perform marriages, seriously
and booklets and bumper stickers
and metal pin
and decals and more booklets
and frameable certificates
really wonderful frameable certificates
I must say
to tell the truth
I think the best thing we ever did
was the book of the subgenius
or maybe Revelation X
or maybe the Bobliographon
but those last two are out of print
the book of the subgenius is still in print
you can get signed copies from us
at subgenius.com
well signed by me anyway
that's also my handwriting
on the padded puffy envelope
that brings your subgenius stuff to your door
yes I actually write that
hand write those
partly to keep my hands working
and partly just cause
so you see it's personalized
no it kind of is
when you join
and you read about the
members only part of the internet
not Facebook
but scrubgeniusforum
who is it that looks up your name
or remembers handwriting it
me
I'm the gatekeeper
are you my key master
I hope not
anyway
yeah that's it friends
think about looking into our books
our videos
in fact you can get previews of our videos
you can see the whole things
and brand new stuff
that's being cranked out by the Ministry of Slack
on Philo's special Roku channel
on television
yes on television if you have a Roku machine
and if you don't just look at Dr. Philo's page on Vimeo
or Vimeo or whatever the hell it is
I should know
I just went to South by Southwest
but I still don't know
uh
we did have fun
but
and they got their footage I think
so everything's fine
friends
thank you
for listening
and uh
bragging us up
when appropriate
praise Bob
and good night
bye