I come from Thebes, and the women of Thebes are warm-blooded, passionate, and we know what we want.
What?
The Self-Genius Power of Swag.
Bob.
The secret is obvious.
People that know me call me Kook, and I like it.
My real name is Shelley L. Dankert.
I've reached a point in my life, I'm 41, and I achieved this about two years ago, where I don't give a fuck what you think of me.
I really don't care.
If you're not in my life on a daily basis, kiss my ass.
I don't give a shit what you think of me, and my God, is that a good feeling or what?
It really is.
And so that's how I live my life.
Sorry to those of you who think I'm a nice girl.
I'm not.
I'm a bitch.
I swear, and I don't give a fuck who hears it.
I don't have children.
I live alone.
Oh my God, people don't know.
Kiss my ass, you fucking bastard.
Kiss my ass.
You want to really do it?
Here, take a look, assholes.
Look at that.
Look.
Eat me.
You suppose you'd like to share that with your friends?
Thank you so much.
What part of that do you not get?
You're dumber than shit.
You ignorant fucks.
I'll be happy to find you in my bedroom in the middle of the night.
You assholes.
Come on over.
I've got chips over here, because that's what I had for supper tonight with my, um,
ah, what do you call it, cheese dip.
God, I'm sick and tired of this shit.
I'm talking to all you namby-pamby pussies.
You want to call me unhinged?
I am.
You'd be right.
I'll fucking kill you, and I'll enjoy doing it.
Fuck you.
You goddamn motherfuckers.
Go to hell.
Shut up.
Shut your fucking mouths.
Get the hell away from me, you worthless bastards.
You're too fucking stupid to live.
So fuck off.
Dr. Legume did that.
He took that viral butthurt drunk lady's video and removed all the politics from it to turn it into an online dating profile.
He even added her photo and made it talk.
His YouTube channel is Dr. Legume.
That's D-R Legume with one word.
And, uh...
The title of the video is Shelly Dankert Online Dating Video.
Reminds me of quite a few people I know.
Anyway, friends, obviously this is one of our internet-only shows composed of audio that would be pointless if rendered fuckless and shitless.
And definitely not to be mailed to our beloved broadcast stations.
In this case, aside from that Legume work and the Lemur titles, it's all from 50 Next Day with rants by Dr. Legume.
Dr. Philo Drummond, Reverend Pockets, Reverend Suds Bashaw, and with a ton of excellent doctor music jams and improv singing by Reverend Angry Larry, Fat Mandy, and especially Priestess Pisces.
So, Mr. Drummond said that he would like to talk to you.
I don't know why I need this, but there's...
anaphylactic up here.
What? Again?
What song?
I'm going to read you some things I wrote.
Or co-wrote.
Now I'm also going to tell you that this
reading, some of these
pieces of this reading,
has some salty language in it.
So if you're a child, or you have the mind
of a child, or you're a child in the audience
you may want to leave.
You know, it seems like
everybody is trying to put
everyone else in some kind of group
these days.
And being a contrarian myself,
I'm physically unable
to even join a group.
Plus, joining a group
would be against my religion.
Why is it
that everyone wants to put
us
into a group?
This is the kind of stuff
that just
pisses us off.
This is the kind of stuff
that makes us hate them.
And since we're so pissed off,
I'm going to go ahead and
read you
this general official statement
of hate and pissed
off-edness.
Our hate is pure.
And as such, it's a beautiful
thing because we hate
all freaks, geeks,
white trash, whites, blacks,
dagos, wops, Jews,
spics, niggers, immigrants,
chinks, hypocrites,
rednecks, meskins,
handicapped people, gimps,
wimps, sissies, fags,
bullies, the French,
people with hair, assholes,
the beautiful people,
good-looking people, the ugly,
the fat, queers, non-queers,
Polacks, cooks,
public workers,
mix, limeys, frogs,
clorps, technocrats,
mediocratons, men,
women, children,
trees, animals,
nature, concrete,
anything fuzzy or cute,
buildings, plants,
milk, cows,
mothers, fathers, uncles, aunts,
cousins, politicians,
ideologues, opinionated
assholes, people with an opinion,
people with no opinion,
retail salespeople,
consumers, marketers,
advertisers, Americans,
Europeans, sons, daughters,
government, any organized group,
other people, ancestors,
descendants, Asians, Africans,
Australians, South Americans,
North Americans, business people,
people with no business,
any combination of ethnicities,
idiots, imbeciles, drivers,
bicyclists, Canadians,
people of Earth, people of any planet,
aliens, ghosts, monsters, the Earth,
it's all human.
and anything else we didn't mention except for the bald or balding people
they're okay in our book
тоже
who
ke
Thank you.
Alright, ladies and gentlemen,
I do have a rancher who is waiting in the wings.
She is super awesome.
She has done a lot this year to help us out
and she has been
my personal superhero
but she has something important she'd like to share
please give a hand for
Pockets
Thanks for waiting
but you know I've been thinking
so I think it's really important
stuff I've been thinking about
maybe we can not be here next year
be in our air conditioned saucers
that would be great
but you know I went home and I just kept thinking to myself
you know why are we still here
what did we do wrong
we should not be sweating
we should be gone, we should be on our saucers
is coming gone according to the con
we've all paid
every single one of us
we've paid our 10, 20, 30, 35 dollars
some of us have even
paid Bob multiple times
most of us are broke
we don't have a pot to piss
in
but yet for each and every single one of us
there's been that moment
where we gladly hand over
a small wrinkled wad of sin money to Bob
we give it to him
it gives us our slack
and then every year
here we are
we travel
we sit
we gather
we party
and we wait
and this year just like every year
nothing happened
I'm a little pissed off at you Bob
but what can you do
so
hey guys!
anyway
come today
tomorrow
the next day
we're gonna travel home
most of us are gonna feel good
we're gonna be slacked out
you know that post-X Day vibe we all go home with
but there'll still be that disappointment
that just you fucked us again Bob
so what do we need to do you know
I look at Bob
and I shake my fist in the air
and I get so mad
and I say damn you Dobbs
are you laughing at me?
fuck yeah he's laughing at me
but that's what I paid him for
sometimes I wonder am I the joke?
am I the one getting fucked?
fuck me the joke's on me
it's alright
sometimes
I tell myself Bob he's just a piece of clip art
fuck him
and with that I get even angrier
even if Dobbs is a lie
I remember something
the conspiracy is real
oh yeah
the con is more real than ever
the pinks they are pinker than ever
once I pull myself together
and I stop laughing at the fact that absolutely nothing is funny anymore
I realize that you know maybe Bob's is real
the Dobbs is not a lie
we just haven't been ready yet
I realize that there's all these horrible disgusting pinks that want to control us
they want to profit off of us
they want our freedoms
they want our homes
they want our vehicles
they want our uteruses
and they want your semen
and they want all of our money
sure Dobbs wants your money
$35 of it
and yeah Bob totally wants you to get screwed
but for pleasure
and even though I get so angry in my moments of just hysterical pinkness
and I lose my faith
it only lasts for a second
and I look around at all these hidden gifts
all these gifts that Bob is here
signs
proof
hard evidence
that Bob is real
and proof that our exes are coming
for example
have you ever just been riding in your car
sitting at your desk
and you just feel that warm breeze of an inverted queef
just blow through your pube mullet
and under the pants of your legs
you know just enough to where it just subtly caresses your genitalia
or you know tingles your balls
in that way that it's just too exciting to admit
that you got that feeling from a correctly timed fart
you all know the one
you know
great Bob
there's these instances that normals take for granted
they don't get it
they're embarrassed
they're ashamed of their amazing fart
oh how can I enjoy that so much
it's disgusting
fucking pinks I hate them
it takes real yetis to embrace these rarities
these proofs of that
Bob himself
I mean you know
the pinks just will never get it
that's why we're different than them
sigh
so you know
I guess what I'm trying to say is look around and open your eyes
and that third nostril and pay attention
when you find yourself enjoying these guilty pleasures
really just remember realize and tell yourself
this is slack
absolutely
when you fart just know next year 7am
our saucers are coming
so it's good to know that we're not wasting our time waiting
gathering here every year
you know it's great to know that our X day is coming
so I think knowing that it's really time for us to marinate on what we're doing wrong
what could we be doing that is stopping these pleasure saucers from scooping us up
and sweeping us off to planet X
it can only be one thing
we are not slacking hard enough
we're just not doing a good enough job
and I don't mean sitting on your couch in a pile of snack wrappers
staring at a tower made out of empty booze bottles
we are doing just fine at that I assure you
sigh
we're just not trying hard enough
you know we gotta stop the man from bringing us down
stuff's gonna happen
our important things are gonna break
some big corporation is gonna rip you off for that last $12.34 in your bank account
somebody on the internet is going to say something so vile
you just cannot continue for another minute without saying it
and setting them straight
but you know instead of going all crazy head and anti-slack
just blow it off
just laugh and know you're better
you're a subgenius
and that sum of bitch is gonna burn on 1 7 am
sigh
you know a good example I think my last example is
you know I was watching TV not too long ago
and between the continuous news and things we can't do anymore
and the total brainwashing lies
I saw a commercial
this commercial I lost sleep
it drove me insane
there were a bunch of whiny pink women complaining about
oh no
what happens when you have that itch that you just can't scratch
you know that itch on your coochie
lord knows can't scratch it
you have to walk around and suffer all day
and before my very eyes
this woman dressed in a cute everyday outfit
she sees her reflection in the store shop window
and in the reflection she changes
she's dressed like a rape victim
it's ridiculous
hunched over
hair in her face
hoodie pulled over to hide her identity
because her vagina itches really is it that bad
so what I'm telling you guys is seriously don't be rape victims
just don't
scratch that crotch itch
and feel the flow of slack that comes with it when you get that relief
who cares if the pinks might gasp and say oh my god they're miscreant just itch their genitals
just fucking scratch that itch
scratch it feel better
when we in a whole can learn to scratch that itch without any worries
then they will come
it will be our moment
the con will burn
the planet will explode
and there will be sex and acceptable genitalia scratching for all
it'll be amazing
so I stand here tonight friends and I beg you
scratch that itch
scratch it for lawns that mow themselves
vehicles that never break or rely on astronomically priced fuel
the stench of burning 1 percenters
scratch it for an army of wiener dogs pooping on everybody's lawn except for yours
scratch it for a digital model of Jabba the Hutt in Star Wars that actually resembles the one in Return of the Jedi
cats that are only friendly when you're in the mood
scratch it for always being able to trust that fart
scratch it for laundry that folds itself
scratch it for eggs that lay chicken nuggets of solid gold
scratch it for chicken that grows bacon for skin
definitely scratch it for beds made entirely from living titties
scratch it for slack
and when you can embrace those little treasures
our 7am will come
praise Bob
that's the emergency gesture
where we have to get out of this song as quickly as possible
you see somebody doing this
that means they're really desperate
they can't wait to get it
they can't wait for the song to be over
they start doing this
it's only done under great duress
if we wanna try to put our engine to sleep
I can't stress this enough to the up-and-coming and potential preachers out there.
You really don't have to fake a Southern accent.
First off, we can tell it's fake.
And the other thing is, it's offensive to Southerners.
We're not, Southerners aren't the only ignorant, racist assholes.
Every part of the world, every kind of person,
half of them are ignorant, dipshit, asshole, pinnates,
and half of them are probably fine, as long as you leave them alone.
So, no, you don't have to pretend to be as redneck, illiterate, in order to preach.
Just because some of us,
famous preachers like Jimmy Swagger, Jim Baker, myself,
happen to be half-literate rednecks,
trying to, the priest says Pisces here,
you know, trying our best to imitate Dr. Howell.
You know, that doesn't mean everybody has to pretend to sound,
I've heard subgenius, beginning subgenius preachers
that sounded like Billy Graham,
but they didn't even know who they were sounding.
They were sounding like a takeoff,
like a Saturday Night Live character they'd seen
pretending to be Billy Graham.
That's the opposite of subgenius preaching.
Who was it, Pockets, was it Pockets that said
we needed to be able to scratch our nuts any time we wanted?
I've been practicing that.
I've been working on that.
So that means if you've got a redneck Brooklyn accent,
or a horrible incomprehension,
or a sensible British accent, or whatever,
it doesn't matter.
What does matter is speaking loudly and clearly.
And scratching your nuts.
Your nuts.
Even when they're up here.
Whatever you have to scratch, go ahead and do it.
Not necessarily in the convenience store
while the policeman's standing next to you.
Why not?
Because the policeman may arrest you.
But.
It's not illegal.
Scratch my crotch yet.
I'm not so sure about that.
There's a, the law can be defined many different ways
depending on who the lawyer's playing golf with.
No, it's illegal for you to scratch my crotch.
Right.
It's silly to argue about what's legal and what's not.
Because if they want to get you, they will get you.
Well, we should take a.
It doesn't matter whether.
We've got this audience here and we should take Pockets advice.
So let's make, let's everybody practice.
Hold on.
We need to practice here folks.
I'm going to count to three and I want everyone to, you know,
Pockets was saying, you know,
you need to be able to scratch your crotch in public.
So everybody out there, I'm going to count to three
and I want you all to scratch your crotch.
Are you ready?
Hey, turn that camera around and point at those people.
I want you all to do it on the count of three.
One, two, three.
Scratch your crotch.
Grab your dicks.
Very good.
No, no, no, no.
You're not all doing it.
That's not scratching.
You're out of here.
You, you're out of here.
You.
Hey, you.
All right, let's try it again.
Out, out, out.
I don't care whether you don't have a crotch.
Oh, they say, well, I can't scratch my crotch.
I'm handicapped.
I don't have a crotch.
I only exist from the belly button up.
I'm sorry.
That doesn't, Bob doesn't care about your disabilities or what's relative to what.
Did you say that?
Did you scratch your crotch for Bob or not?
That's all there is to it.
Did you put that money in the collection plate?
That is all that counts.
It is not slack by dreams or words or faith.
It says not slack by faith.
It is slack by works.
Slack by works, I'm telling you.
Now, we originally put that cloth there, which Susie, Susie put the bloody hand in.
I don't know if you can see the hand prints on that, by the way.
We originally had that set there so that we could scratch our nuts without embarrassing
the audience.
But then Reverend Pockets did a whole sermon about how we should just go ahead and scratch
our nuts no matter who's looking.
And I've been working at that.
I don't know if anybody's noticed, but I've been going out of my way to scream when they
Meanwhile, Dr. Drummond and Dr. Howell go about the tricky business of regulating the
conventional medicine.
I'm going to show you a little bit of the conventional air flow of the fan without revealing
Dr. Howell's feet, as Dr. Howell is very sensitive about his feet.
And please don't look at them when he comes by.
It is improper for the audience to look at your feet.
I thought everybody knew that.
But if we have to roll up our plastic foot shield for Dr. Drummond, I will make that
sacrifice, too.
It's not something I've ever had to worry about.
I haven't had my shoes off since I was about three years old.
Is there any way we can, like, have film music?
You can grow on your feet, don't you?
Film music and background music on this show so that we don't have to talk or anything?
No.
When we tried to do background music the first day, it was just too loud.
Who said?
It was difficult to deal with.
Who said so?
A person in the audience who can hear and judge such things.
Paternoster.
Is this a special cookie?
I have no doubt that it is.
Maybe it's just one sitting in a sweet spot.
Is that a frop-loaded cookie?
I'll bet you it's as froppy as the day is long.
You want half?
I'll take half.
I'll divide and you choose.
Is that a Gary Gaborgfran cookie?
No, it sort of wipes away the taste of the octopus.
Now Dr. Drummond will imbibe the cookie.
It won't make any difference even if it was solid LSD.
You wouldn't notice any difference.
Yeah, you would.
His head turns colors.
I think it is solid LSD.
It tastes like it.
Dr. Philodrummond is now eating a cookie.
It's a cookie made of solid LSD.
That's all it is.
A well-crafted confection.
There's no sugar or flour.
It's got that telltale LSD flavor.
Yeah.
That's enough to kill an elephant.
Is that enough to get a hand on?
I can take five.
This is enough to flip you out.
Or am I going to have to talk you down later?
I'm thinking they have some Owlsley stuff in there.
How long does it take for this to come on?
In that quantity, I would think.
When do we start?
When do we get to the point where we're worrying, where we're not worried?
We're not getting high enough, fast enough, so we take the other half.
And then it turns out that was only five minutes before the first half really kicked in like crazy.
And then it started kicking in, and you immediately think, gosh, I wish I hadn't taken that other half so readily.
That happened to me only once.
How many times has that happened to you?
It happened to me once, the one and only time I ever had.
Don't leave me, Philo.
Keep me here, man.
It generally happens every time I have it in halves.
Dang, I'm having flashes, man.
It's trippy, dude.
This whole halving, that's a bad idea.
You should just take the whole thing and forget about the half.
Anybody got any Thorazine out there?
This half issue is...
Actually, that's what happened to me.
I was having muscle cramps.
We were finishing up the Book of the Subgenius on a deadline.
I hadn't slept in a long time.
I had to drive all the way across town.
And Dr. X said, there's this new pill called Quaalude.
Here's two of them.
These are real weak, though, so you should take both of them.
Well, I'm not stupid.
Or that stupid.
But I'm this stupid.
I took a half and drove to his house.
And I never felt it.
It was like half an hour gone by and I'm still having leg cramps.
I took the other half.
That's when the first half hit.
And I instantly dropped everything I was holding in my hand
and started making up stories about invisible people.
And I woke up in jail.
Yes, friend.
That's what it is.
That was the first and last time that I ever touched any drugs of any kind.
I've never ever since then touched any false drugs whatsoever.
Oh, I'm glad you said false drugs.
Is there anybody in here that took Quaaludes and actually successfully drove?
I don't know anybody that ever did that.
I know people that did Quaaludes and had a distinctive look to their car.
We called them Quaidents back then.
There's something attractive about it.
It's a weird, it's one of those kind of like a parasite.
You take the drug and it makes you want to drive but you can't drive.
Yeah.
I always give you a hint here, Dr. Drummond.
If the car that's got dents in it, the Quaid car,
if it's being driven by a good looking young woman,
it's a whole different thing.
Come get me, crow. Come get me.
You know that one?
Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
All right.
I think we're doing good on time.
We're having a lot of fun.
So we're, you know, the Aminas, I don't think I got to kick my ass for spending more time up here.
They're in Seattle right now.
All right.
They're on their way here.
Okay.
Very good.
So that's fine because we got plenty more material here, especially for an environment like this.
You know, here's a chance where we all, we get together.
We see people that we haven't seen maybe in a year, maybe in several years.
You know, circumstances come up.
People miss X days.
Families come and go.
Money comes and goes.
And sometimes it can be a while between now and the time that you see your dear Yeti friend.
And this song, this song is about that, that kind of friendship, that time that you see each other.
Well, and then you got to go.
I really miss you.
Until I see you.
Then I wish you go away.
I really miss you.
But then I see you.
And soon I wonder how long you'll stay.
You're going to open your mouth.
Something stupid come out.
And it's time for me to go.
And it's time for me to say so long.
I really miss you.
Until I see you.
Then I wish you were gone.
You said let's go out drinking.
Don't know what I was thinking.
It always ends up a bad time.
You start out with a bitching.
Something about your kitchen.
And soon enough I'm losing my mind.
Yeah, no matter how hard I try.
I can't fake interest in your life.
That's why I really miss you.
Until I see you.
Then I wish you go away.
I really miss you.
But then I see you.
And soon I wonder how long you'll stay.
You've gone fucking around.
Almost got us kicked out.
From my favorite place to play my songs.
I really miss you.
Until I see you.
Then I wish you were gone.
You're boring and you don't care.
Your story's going nowhere.
Besides, I think I've heard this before.
Yeah, no one's even listening.
But still you keep insisting.
On being really hard to ignore.
Yeah, no matter how I do as a friend.
Could you please just skip to the end?
Again, I really miss you.
Until I see you.
Then I wish you were gone.
Now you're in everybody's business.
With your ill-informed opinions.
Whatever it is, your way is best.
Of course, facts are out of season.
And you're immune to reason.
And all you ever give me is stares.
Oh yes, now I really think I've had quite enough.
I just let the machine pick up.
I really miss you.
Until I see you.
Then I wish you were gone.
I really miss you.
But then I see you.
And soon I wonder how long you'll stay.
You ever hear yourself talk?
It's more than a thought.
The things you say are patently wrong.
You only talk about.
You shit you wish you could do.
If you shut down your computer and put away your bong.
You never pick up the tab.
Or make anyone laugh.
The order of your body is best described as strong.
I really miss you.
Until I see you.
Then I wish you were gone.
Wish you were gone.
I really miss you.
Until I see you.
Then I wish you were gone.
Wow, wow, wow.
That one was St. Andrew the Impaled.
Live at 50 next day.
Accompanied by himself.
You can find Andrew the Impaled by googling said name.
He really does impale himself too.
We'll hear some of that in the next X-Rite Net Only episode.
We had enough cuss filled material for two of these special types of shows.
The gang game a little close.
Alright.
It looks like there's actually going to be jamming.
I see musicians getting up here which would be fun.
I'm going to take my chances.
Do you have any other old doctors who...
No?
Fucking old doctors!
You could try.
But I can tell you that you probably would...
Yeah.
Go ahead and try.
Hi.
Speaking as one of the old timers.
Been there, done that.
We're already fucked.
You don't need to go to the trouble.
There's a long, long line.
They're so fucking deep.
Go around the block and join the rest.
.
. . .
. . . . . . . . burada N-e learned enough.
.
05.
. . . . Obyi?
.
Futhermore.
No, that's the Forget-Tomorrow.
grass like in your home backpack.
.
Long hair, blue eyes, and a nice tiny.
So Bob, being the precocious nine-year-old that he was, said,
Connie, darling, tell me about love.
And he put on a little bit of Rick James.
Connie didn't really dig Rick James, but it didn't really matter.
But Connie knew exactly what she was after.
She sat him down on the couch and said,
Why don't you change this record?
I'm more of a Dick Dale kind of girl.
With the emphasis on Dick as she said it.
While Bob was precocious as a nine-year-old,
I mean, he really didn't get the hint, you know.
But, you know, Connie tried anyway.
And while he was trying to get the hint,
while the Dick Dale record laid,
Connie plotted to get laid.
And dogs really didn't get it
until Connie put her hand in his pants.
Well, Bob jumped up and was a little bit startled.
I mean, yeah, he's nine years old,
but there's this beautiful girl and she's got her hand.
And he's got her hand in his pants.
And, well, you know, he started feeling a little bit funny.
A little tingle down below.
And it reminded him of when he watched Charo.
So, well, Connie started rubbing around
and, well, he was like,
sure enough, before Bob even knew it,
she had unbuttoned his pants
and got them down about, you know, mid-five.
Bob was getting a little nervous
and his palms were starting to sweat.
And, well, he really didn't know what to do.
I mean, he's nine years old, for fuck's sake.
Well, you know, he's nine years old together.
There we go, right?
transition, uh, I love Jack.
He's only seven years older.
Look.
I'm about to kill him!
I'm fucking, I'm fucking, I'm fucking, I'm fucking, I'm fucking, I'm fucking, I'm fucking, I'm fucking corpse.
I'm running out of notes here.
I don't know what I've got on me.
I've only listened to the onlyockable tracks on 993.com in two weeks.
Yeah, and the last of them are called XO's Melody Tutorials.
.96.
Connie then put her face in his crotch.
And Bob exclaimed loudly,
Why are you licking my pee-pee?
And things began to get weird after that.
So she's down in his lap with her mouth on his nine-year-old cock.
As I said, he was a little bit precocious as a nine-year-old.
And as she's moving her mouth up and down,
and up, and down, and up, and down, and up, and down on his cock,
things got a little bit more than tingly.
But I happen to be fun.
Snatch.
Connie realized really quick that Bob really wasn't experienced.
And...
she was gonna have to drive this car.
Good thing was that she knew how to drive stick.
Connie climbed...
straddle Bob...
and slid herself down...
on Bob's lap.
That's nasty. That sounds nasty.
And you know what happened next?
Because Bob is a subgenius. In fact, he is THE subgenius.
And he's a true overman. And he is a yeti.
Connie quickly found out what happens.
When an overman loses his virginity.
She started out slow, of course. You know, not wanting to make things too rushed.
Because after all, the first time is always a little rushed anyway.
But that happened in other little snatches.
Before the big ones.
And as she was rhythmically...
to the tune of that Dick Dale record...
grinding and sliding and...
grinding and sliding...
two will be grinding at the tail, and one will be smashed.
She found out...
that Bob suddenly grew...
three more...
canines!
That the smash is imminent.
The snatch is at hand.
The snatch will come with any little help.
And that's what she was thinking.
But that did not come.
And the swords did.
And the
fred door slipped.
Well, it could but wheels...
just did not play.
All I know is that there might be
Things I've never seen before
The sun is starting to ruffle outside
The sky is turning black
And the wind is starting to thrust it back
And there was a sound in the distance that sounded
Like an oncoming freight train
All the birds stopped singing
Church bells were ringing
And the wind blew with great ferocity
And in a small town
In southern Texas
Miles away from the Gulf of Mexico
A hurricane of epic proportions formed
And Bob
Bob started singing
That was pretty good
And that
Is how Bob lost his virginity
Without further ado
I'd like to present
Reverend Suds Peshaw
Who has some words for you
Friends it's obvious
That I'm not the only one
Bob's teaching is very important to all of us
I mean hell
If not for those teachings none of us would even be here at this moment
But you know
It seems that a few folks have been
Getting some mixed signals
Here as of late
A few of them
Just seem to have turned away from the path of slack
And a few of them
Have even plunged into the depths of the earth
And have listened to shoelace eating jack fuck lotusy
And started following
The wrong Bob
I'm sure you've seen these around
The multitude of
False Bob images
That are cluttering up all our lives
Trying to drive us from the warmth
Of the one true holy pipe life
Friends
Do not
Be fooled by cheap imitations
Even a cheap imitation
Like saccharine
Has been shown to cause cancer in lab rats
Imagine what a cheap imitation
Of Bob could do
Even the massive array
Of reproductions
From within our own church
Could never hold the slackful might
Of the one true Dobson
Now you're
Probably wondering to yourself
Just how are we able to tell
These false idols from
The one true Dobson
From the real world
Visual aid
It's quite simple really
And I've even brought you visual aid
To help demonstrate
And it's so simple
That any of you out there
Have the capacity to understand this
You just
Look
For
The R
That's right friends
The C
The sacred R
More powerful
Than his pipe
More important than his slackful grin
More valuable
Than the total sum of the dots
Riddled across his face
Friends
Let you know one of the many
Secrets of this church
That it's so obvious
That nobody seems to grasp
This sacred R
Is the true secret
Of Bob's power
Slack may be the ultimate outcome
But the might of the sacred R
Cannot be denied
For without that R
Bob is powerless
Yes friends
Without that symbol our sacred
Salesman is nothing more than some
Random piece of clip art
That any poe bucker
Fucker could use
Without it
He's a mug
That you can use to advertise
Argyle socks
Without it
He could appear in a smears ad
For pink leisure suits
Or worse
They could actually remove
His pipe
And furthermore
He was stolen to
Sell pink sardons right Stang
Yeah
This ad actually happened but look how that
Turned out
The heads of the company were convicted of fraud
In the false Bob image
And allegedly disappeared somewhere in the Caribbean
Even the owner's own mother
Went to the slammer for this
That is true
Slack power radiating from that
Sacred R
This R has so many meanings
Especially if you're a pirate
Arrrr
It stands for the righteousness
Of subgenious rage
It stands for the ridicule
Of the guinea bobs
Who think they can take our sails
To a whole new level
It stands for Ragnarok
That's right friends
It grants us the power
Not to dominate the lesser species
But to decimate every last
Stink in one of them
But most important of all
Friends
It stands for registered
Trademark
For with that R
He's R Bob
Praise Bob
Yeah
Oh
R
R we got men
We are
We are drunk
R R
R we got men
R R we are a
R E are busy
R we must repeat
R R we are a
We must repeat
R ARE a
R We must repeat
R. Frohtis Suds Peshaw at X-Day Drill number seventeen
Also know as 15 X-Day
All the music from tonight's show it from
from the X-Day stage as well, mostly by the ever-changing jam band, heard in the background,
called Several Fisted Tales of Connie.
I think for most of what we're hearing tonight, the musicians were Reverend Angry Larry on
guitar and vocals, Suds Bashaw on guitar, Bishop Stick on bass, Dr. Sinister or Senator
Speck on drums, Trademark Gunderson of Evolution Control Committee on samplers, keyboards,
keyboards, and thimble-tron, and Dr. Drummond on sax, Reverend Hazel of the Windmills on
flute, and there were other people, but I'm not going to look at every videotape to figure
out who, but the vocals, as in this upcoming song, are mostly by Priestess Pisces, joined
in this particular case by Reverend Fat Man D, Price Bob.
This jam of beats motivates you.
It can give you a sexual feeling.
A girl can be turned on by the beats.
And here goes the circuit of beats.
It's a little bit of confusion.
It's the jowls of our hearts.
A little confusion.
Oh, hey, that's a sequence of four beats.
It's a feeling of defeat.
It motivates you to turn on the music of some of the players.
Oh, yeah, see, we're loud on the beats.
It landmarks what the Chinese call the
The ticket is a one-track windmill of whyMusic.
through two rounds.
Ooh, ah, ooh, ah
Yeah, it's right there, yeah
Ooh, ah, yeah
It's right there, yeah
It's right there, ooh, ooh, ah
Ooh, ah, yeah
Yeah, yeah
Oh, yes, ooh
Yes, yes, yes
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
When you were passing that prop stick
I didn't know you'd be passing my stick
My stick's prop stick
So, skiffing
Bulbous, round, bulbous, bulbous
I don't know if I can, uh, suck that, uh
I don't know if I can suck that hard enough
Ooh, ah, ooh, ah
I don't know if I can, uh, suck that, uh
Yeah, just like that
I don't know if I can, but I can
Oh, boy, darlin', you know
But you got it wrong
Ooh, ah, ooh, ah
I don't know if I can, but I can, uh, suck that, uh
Ooh, ha, uh, ooh, htill, for me, all that
I'm getting orgasm on the fucking moon
Just like that, just like that, just like that, baby
Just a little more
That was great, babe.
I'm a bit raw.
Fucking high.
That is so fucking high.
I gotta put this away.
I'm too high.
Ladies and gentlemen, give it up
for the amazing
newly married
sex god and goddesses.
The one and unfortunately
only Mr. and Mrs.
Mrs. Sodson Pisces
Pasha!
Without whom, none of this would be necessary.
You've been listening
to the Subgenius
Radio Ministry
Hour of Slack.
For free information,
write to
P.O. Box
Cleveland Heights, Ohio
or see
www.subgenius.com
Praise Bob!
Friends,
we're glad you listened to this show
and we're even more glad that some
listeners have donated enough to help us
keep on going for another couple of months.
Not just this show, but
subgenius.com and all the other
archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob
and want some of that slackback
to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com
front page or especially
the radio page or the catalog
store pages
and help out financially as best
you can. Now, we
know what it's like to be on the brink of
total poverty and we don't want any
subgeniuses to make their own situation.
It's worse. But some of you
still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a
big difference, even if it's only
once a month from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even
bigger difference.
All we're saying is that
blow jobs could
go the way of Steve jobs
if you don't pay dogs.
We also take checks
and money orders to
subgeniusfoundation.com
P-O-box
181-417
Cleveland Heights,
Ohio 44118
Thanks for anything you can do to help
let there be slack.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community