You cowardly bastard! You're not the voice of the people! I am the voice of the people!
The people speak through me, not you!
And we begin to tithe and make vows and give offerings, and it broke the slack over their lives!
Alax! Alax! Alax! Alax! Alax! Alax! Alax! Alax! Alax! Alax! Alax! Alax! Alax! Alax!
Yeah!
Back into your shell.
Time to begin to worry about size eight of the 90-minute tithe.
And now...
The Song!
Subgenius.
Our.
God.
What.
Presented to you by the Church of the Subgenius in the name of J.R.
Dull.
What am I supposed to do?
Kiss the charming prince?
I am not crazy, and I don't normally hear the cry of bats.
Well, you are either in possession of a very new human ability,
or a very old one.
Okay, hold that thought, whoever's talking on the phone.
We have with us tonight, today, right now, right here.
Mic is on, fellas. Get those headphones on.
We'll be right back.
Howdy.
Can you hear?
I can.
Can you?
Uh, yep.
Alright.
Yeah.
You might want to, you might want to get a little bit closer to the microphone.
I can hear voices, but then I always hear voices.
All we know is-
Don't look at me like that.
Maybe it's some radio signal.
I read about a guy who used to pick up broadcasts and a feeling in his tooth.
I believe in what I know.
That was a radio broadcast.
This is my faith.
It's coming from outermost.
And then see what you believe.
I can't believe what I believe.
As I believe, Reverend Sheldon DeWeer pointed out.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
This is your good host and prayer partner and the curse partner, Reverend Ivan Stang.
And, well, I couldn't come down to the radio station tonight.
So I'm producing the program from the skyscraper headquarters of the Subgenius Foundation.
And we're not transmitting the signal by telephone wires or shortwave tonight, however, no.
But by the sheer force of pure will.
Yes, Reverend Willa Dobbs, pure will.
Pure will.
The one you hear muttering in the background.
Hi, Will.
Yes, Will is so pure.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, sure.
He's about as pure as most of his fellow subgeniuses.
Pure as the driven snow from Siberian nuclear bomb tests.
And old Will, he don't get paid much in cash.
But his motives are more pure than that.
He knows that Bob has called him to.
And he knows that there's someone out there running out here.
You know he wants a heartless sacrifice.
And he'll do the job.
Don't you know, I don't blame that man for what happens.
You know, I hope you have.
And, uh-
Thinking about it, it looks like
He is just in some shoes recently 탄
Feels like a corpse that cangreat
Deldamn
I call her Lois
But I do not fear her I see all too cla'
CD from Negative Land, our dear friends there in Concord. And we got a tape of St. Jane or
Hyperclete delivering a new hate sermon to the masses in Boston last month. We got a whole
Brain Rock Radio Theater and Subgenius Foundation co-production, The Marriage of Lonesome Cowboy Dave
from WCSB Cleveland broadcast. We got some rare Fireside Theater from Bootlegs. We have Church of
New Faith and Michael Pepe, Princess Wiardo's Tops Up, Bottoms Down review. This is hour of slack
number 423, by the way. And Reverend Velveteen Sly and Sister Girlfriend from WORT Madison,
Morton Downey Jr. on Bob, The Swingin' Love Corpses, Dr. Howell's Howling Hilariously
Interplay with callers to the KPFA Berkeley Subgenius Show, and loads of ugly Wellmanization
media barrage re-collage from Pizzling Everdunce, as Dr. Drummond calls him. And I don't know what
else yet, but then, but then, who does?
And we are going to save the universe this time.
Mr. Smith, not a religious man myself, I'm sorry to say, but I will say this. If God has seen fit to bless you with this gift, you should use it.
Bless me?
You know what God did for me?
He threw an 18-wheel truck at me.
Bounced me into nowhere for five years.
God's been a real sport to me.
And I predict that our local American doctors will go on strike and be replaced by African witch doctors.
A man knows everything around him. Then one day he sees himself, and then he doesn't.
Who's there?
One in one voice.
One in one voice?
There weren't voices. There were more life. Thoughts.
It's just a gesture.
I've served seven years in this thing, so I'm ready to open the rock.
Can't you pick up your cues faster than that?
I can't do your show on our show, you know that.
They always try, but you see, they never learn.
Even plenarian worms can learn, but power is going to never learn to take their turn.
...political..
The government...
Yes, that's right.
This is the genius cult we're studying this morning.
An unusual group of true believers and animalistic worshippers,
generally from backwoods and remote portions of the country.
Rural Texas, Arkansas, and the darker woods of Iowa.
The desperate, the lonely, losers, pencil neck geeks, wimps,
the maladroit, those with yards, all found under the aegis of subgenius fandom.
In their own retreat, their private mountain fortress,
the Cool Ranch Davidians decide to tell their children
all about the revered J.R. Bob Dog.
My children.
You are this.
This is an authentic.
Bob Lecture.
One of the first of seven seminars given by Bob in 1956.
And look at them lap it up.
There they all are, sitting in the front row in Embryo, the Embryo Janer.
And why don't you tell us exactly what it's about?
Yeah, that's the Church of the Subgenius.
It's called the Final Solution to the Entertainment Problem.
And that's going to be happening tonight.
It's going to be at the Middle East Cafe at 9.
It'll feature subgenius preacher and anti-comedian, J.R. Hyperclete,
Reverend Brother Pope Cleve Duncan,
and special musical guests, the Wheelers and Dealers.
The admission is $5 or all your worldly goods.
And we want you to know that this is a love offering.
It is not obligatory.
However, if you're not loving enough, there will be an armed guard with a shotgun.
We don't mind spreading out.
We want to help our supporters who aren't loving enough a little bit.
But I've got...
My name is Janer Hyperclete, and I'm here in the studio with Pat McGrath.
I misspelled and mispronounced the names of all the Wheelers and Dealers, all my partners.
And we're here to confuse you with more disinformation.
I hope so. I hope so.
You can just hear the sincerity dripping off our every word.
That's right.
And that's what the Church is about.
That's what the Church of the Subgenius is all about.
Well, I mean, pretension is the wave of the future, and always has been.
If you want to go for this real person thing, I mean, hey, this is 1993.
You know, that's not going to fly.
Right.
So...
There's too much money involved.
The corporations behind it won't let it be spontaneous.
This, in point of fact, this is all on tape.
That is true. It's all on tape.
Anyway, so, Janor, you're a preacher for the Church of the Subgenius.
Just exactly what is the Church of the Subgenius?
Well, it started back in about 1978 when Ivan Stang was talking about...
Well, he had written a book that no one would publish, and he had made a film that no one would show.
And he was talking to his friend Philo Drummond.
And he was just kind of a struggling artist type.
And he was complaining, and his friend Philo Drummond said,
Well, the problem is that if you were a genius, you'd be rich and famous.
But if you were a normal person, you'd be satisfied with a 9-to-5 job.
Your problem is that you're some kind of a subgenius.
And that sort of set off some kind of light in his head that there were other people like him out there.
So he started the Church of the Subgenius,
which is a collection of...
Subgenius.
...outcasts, misfits, creative artist types, humorists,
superior mutants, and...
Mass murderers.
Mass serial killers, mass murderers.
We believe that the normals form a vast conspiracy against the different.
And our central belief system is that all abnormal people are superior.
And if they send in $20 to our P.O. box...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
That's commercialism. We can't do that.
This is a non-commercial radio station.
Yeah, I turned your mic off.
Anyway, I do have an FCC obligation.
And now, Crosley Bendix,
cultural reviewer and director of stylistic premonitions for the Universal Media Network,
with today's arts review.
To say that he's spicy, he takes good care of the Carl Green Command,
Hello, 아이셈
Each child has aaturon.
Life together.
That's Percy.
Hi- tiver,
love to scare ourselves for fun. Our fear for fun should not be taken lightly. When Dr. Hyde drank
that vial of bubbling bug juice on the set of Robert Louis Stavinsky's famous opera, he became
what we all fear most of all. Next to that thing in the thing, the internal monster within us all,
that nameless fear that hungers for nameless fears. Pretty good trick, that vial. But as any
scientist knows, the real test of any experiment is in its repetition. And I'm not referring to
reruns. I'm referring to this. This vial bubbling bug juice.
I'm going to drink this vial of Stavinsky's formula faithfully concocted from his original score in order to put a little, well, a little sense of apprehension into this otherwise rather dull and academic discussion.
I might as well finish it.
Now, let's turn to the special effects of special effects. After passing the cases of monstrously overpriced theater candy designed to numb our sense of reality, we sit with disbelief suspended as splitting rubber latex spurts crimson syrup.
And slimy leaping demons suck the cold sweat from our armpits.
Our internal fright meters record a level to qualify the success of this illusion.
What lies behind the appeal of illusory fear? We all know the answer.
It's the.
Lore of super reality.
As everyone who's ever been in a fight knows, violence is distinctively different state of being in which one is drugged with adrenaline.
Time stands still.
We seem to be more alive within a world of pure action.
And.
Uh.
The threat of intelligence in human affairs
are returned from this exhilaration with a sense of relief.
Others find the return to normal to be a let-down.
A return to a
meaningless, mundane existence, and they seek opportunities to return again into the super-reality of violent acts.
This knowledge, the personal power to transform and heighten reality with violence, is similar to our fascination with evil,
which is...
fascinating.
We are constantly faced...
changing...
faced...
faced, changed, faced with...
faced with the double fa...
double standard of love.
Evil.
Yearning for confronting...
yearning for...
yearning for confronting...
infection.
The things we would run from...
in the streets.
Dark, deserted streets.
Ah...
You've been listening to cultural reviewer and social critic, Crosley Bendix.
I predict there will always be more people, but there will never be more land.
I predict that population explosion will permit standing room only.
Every inch of our land will be occupied.
I predict we will live in floating cities sustained by anti-gravity,
huge plastic bubbles under the sea which draws oxygen from the sea itself,
underground tunnels and caves, plus the very center of Earth,
which will be a nation unto itself.
Right, you'll be taken up aboard what we call escape saucers
to what we call the laser dimensions,
while what we call the normals will be laser beams to death.
Now, I know someone who sent in $20 and they never got a reply.
Well, that's what we call slack.
That's what we call a journey to the bank account.
Good.
It seems we heard a lot about you guys in the late 80s,
you know, Devo and all that stuff.
But then we didn't hear from you for a while.
What happened?
Well, I mean, you've heard about a band breaking up and getting back together.
This is sort of like a person breaking up and getting back together.
I don't know.
I'm reformed, but not reformed, if you know what I mean.
That's out of sight now.
I don't need your sympathy. Come on.
You describe the members of the church and subgenius as being outcasts and abnormals.
And mass murderers.
And do you feel that you are an outcast yourself?
Well, yeah, I've always felt like an outcast in just about any given social situation.
And really, the only way I can feel like I fit in is by having my own show.
And even then, that doesn't really work.
Because I usually end up getting stage fright.
And, you know, in a sense, it's legitimate.
Because, I mean, how else could I react except with fear and contempt to anyone who would pay to see me?
But, you know, I'll never forget my fans because they made me what I am today.
A raving psychotic.
I truly hate my fans.
Of course, most of my fans are raving psychotics also.
You.
Yes.
Listening.
To this message is alone.
Check it out.
You're not alone.
There's someone out there in God's gray universe who really cares.
Who really cares about you and your feelings.
Who really knows you inside and out.
Knows your moods.
Your wants.
Your needs.
Yes.
Knows your special needs.
Your G-zone.
Your tickle spots.
Knows what you like and where you like it.
And that person is right there.
Right there.
Right now.
Right inside of you.
Quit looking around.
It's you, dummy.
You.
You're the one that you're looking for.
Yes, you.
You're the one that really cares about yourself.
Oh, I know.
Sometimes it might seem like you don't care about yourself.
Like with that three-pack-a-day habit.
Or your hygiene habits.
Or your days of tedious boredom.
Doing nothing except watching TV.
And lusting for young starlets and harlots.
Those things you can overlook, though.
Of course you can.
Why?
Because you love yourself.
And when you love something, you should stick with it.
Nurture it.
Make it grow.
And never let it go.
Marry yourself to it.
Ah!
Marry yourself.
Period.
That's right.
For just $19.95.
For the first three minutes, you can call up and we will marry you to yourself right on
the spot.
Right here.
Right there.
Right then.
Right now.
What are you waiting for?
Go ahead.
Pop yourself the question.
You've accepted, right?
You'd be a fool not to.
What person could resist you?
Two hundred and ten pounds of sleek fat on a five-foot-two-inch bod with hangnails.
Hey!
I'm a fool!
And if you want to change your size or shape, you are the person you've been waiting for.
So never be alone again when you're alone again.
Call 1-700-I-LOVE-ME.
That's 1-700-I-LOVE-ME.
1-700-I-LOVE-ME, etcetera.
Call now.
Marrying yourself is the perfect Christmas gift for yourself.
Oh, gee.
Darn it, I'm so tired.
What a life-changing commercial.
1-700-I-LOVE-ME. 1-700-I-LOVE-ME.
I'll do it. I've been single much too long now.
Pretty near 10 years.
Been single ever since Lucinda had left me for that left-handed dung-molder
in the fall of the house of Gusher.
I'm sure I can find someone who cares about me.
Me.
Do I take me to be my mate?
Oh, dear. That settles it.
Better get that jet-setting engine
to be my best man.
Hey, you, night-American holistic shrink and codependent.
You, shaggy poodle fondler.
What, what, what?
Lazy in the sky with fool's gold?
This better be good.
Me right in the middle of something.
Or someone.
When you coming back, psychopath finder, honey?
Soon, soon, my pretty.
Here, me just reel out some more,
and you can go another room and play with it.
Watch out when shutting door.
Okay.
Now, what is it this time, cowboy George?
Big news.
I popped myself a question, man.
And accepted my hand in holy matrimony.
I mean matrimony.
Can you believe it?
What question you pop?
When will I blow my brains out and how?
It's real cute.
Listen, man, I'm serious.
I asked myself to bury myself.
And I accepted.
This is so sudden.
I'm making a call right now to the 1900 telemarketing page
and he hates myself up to me.
Hey, I'm in love, engine cleaner.
Hey, I'm in love.
Hey, did you happen to see the most beautiful guy in the mirror?
Tell me I love me.
Tell me I need me.
Hey.
OHHH...
She doesn't Western girl make you hear that the only-
you say.
Oh, bros, this is not the way I make you feel.
Right there.
Where did Bracer say to –
where did Bracer suggest this group to go?
And where did Bracer suggest this group to go?
Here's a brief Gabrielle.
Been in a relationship for a lot with Br larger than that man,
but year over year things like being in a relationship with someone
just because they don't want to hook stuff on you.
Yeah man,
I'm spoken for.
Hey, Dave, can I do or say something to move this plot along, please, please, please?
I need some attention here.
Scabby, not now. I'm the main burner of this plot, baby.
Just to make some stupid remark in it, and then we'll move it along.
Oh, great. Just like all the other times.
Look, I just opened my skull when a railroad spiker stumbled on my left testicle
and fell into the basement of the RV.
Oh, woe is me.
Unpredictable.
Crepes and crepes.
You removed like a clitorectomist?
Scabby, can't you ever move the plot along?
Miss Nunez's stigmatization spotty are the bridesmaids for now.
Silent bridesmaids.
I'm sure Dave will write you in some more lines.
I am Dave.
The character Dave, not the real Dave Davis.
The real Dave is reading this, though.
Hey, hey.
So don't worry, folks. It'll all come out in a wash.
Okay, it's here in the script. It's here in the script.
It's ringing!
Uh, good evening, and welcome to the church of Our Lady of Telemarketing Sorrows, Incorporated.
I am the far-right, honorable Pastor Future with a present.
A present for you for calling this chapel of electromagnetic wedding bliss.
If you would like the dinette piece,
press 1.
If you would like a free hour stay in Newark, New Jersey, pay toilet,
press 2.
If you would like the bucket of beer brunch with Bavarian pretzels for half price,
press 3.
Or press 4 to disconnect this sacrament.
Thank you.
Are we ready to begin?
We are gathered around this receiver today
to join this person who is coming apart
in the state of monogamy moment.
This is the sacrament of matrimony with it, his or her selves.
As you know, the sacrament of matrimony is sacred and should not be entered lightly.
That is why this lovely single has promised to live faithfully to himself
and forever ready, steady, go.
Do you...
At the sound of the tone, please say your name.
Uh, low to the lefty, righty, middly, cowboy, L, G, Einstein, going, going, on and on.
Take.
To be your own lawfully wedded husband or wife,
To have and to grab, to kick and deal,
To nip and tuck, to stand and deliver,
To block and tackle, to drug, dishonor and disobey,
To drug, dishonor and disobey,
For as long as the both of you shall live,
So help you, chases.
I do.
And do you.
Uh, low to the lefty, righty, middly, cowboy, L, G, Einstein, going, going, on and on.
Take.
To wash and dry, to protect and serve, to lift and separate,
To moan and groan, to divide and conquer,
To bob and weave, and to be or not to be,
So help you, the mob?
I do.
If there's anyone here who objects to this union of one personality and two different personalities,
Speak now or forever hold your piece of meat.
If no one objects, press 1.
If someone else objects, press 2.
If you object, press 3.
To end this sacrament, press 4.
Oh, I'm sorry, I, uh, I just...
I object! I object!
Don't do it, lonesome!
Not now, Scabby!
Why, Scabby, why?
You're already married. To me.
I knew I'd move this plot along somehow.
Married to you? Impossible.
He married to career, or he married to my therapy or something, but not to you.
I can prove it. He married me at the Winden place,
at the cemetery last night.
I was carrying on, and he got fed up,
and took a shovel and went to the remains to be seen.
Cemetery dug a hole and married me.
I don't know what happened.
Scabby, I did not marry you.
I buried you last night. I buried you!
My brain snapped, and I felt compelled to bury you.
So there! You still didn't move the plot along.
Just press 1. No one objects.
Place the ring on your middle finger.
By the powers invested in me,
by the state of confusion,
I now pronounce you individual and self.
I hope the both of you are very happy.
You may now kiss yourself.
I'm sorry, Scabby.
Tell your friends about the Church of Telemarketing Sorrows,
and may you be blessed with many millions of possible human lives spilled on the floor,
or in Kleenex, or in your fuzzy sock.
Try these other services here at Our Lady of Telemarketing Sorrows.
Cloning yourself, burying yourself, and suing yourself.
Here comes the bride in a cowboy hat.
He married herself.
He thinks he knows where it's at.
Here comes the groom walking down the aisle.
With no brains in his head,
no wonder he has a smile.
I've done it.
We've done it. Me, by myself, and I've done it.
Aren't you guys going to congratulate me?
Where's your presents?
Where's your wedding presents?
Where's my presents?
Present?
No, listen.
Listen, this getting to be old hat.
Every night, you call this 900 number,
and then marry yourself,
and expect to get presents from me.
Okay, if that's the way you feel about it,
I'm going to consummate this marriage right here in front of both of you, swine.
Oh, baby.
The station wishes to apologize for this last bit of fluff.
We'll have the good time with you,
and in case not to air the rest of Lonesome Cowboy Dave's consummation of his...
And he's all day screaming,
kill me, kill me,
but they laugh and cook more the eggs
and cutting the knife more
and beating more
until they are bored.
Bored with me
and drag me back to my cell.
And it's not to my surprise.
My heart is beating,
springing the heat,
the sweat it fills my eyes.
I do not mind what I excrete,
cause I'm here to make a buck.
And those that cannot take the heat
can take the flake.
Forgive me if I hesitate.
It's incredibly fun to hear.
Incredibly fun to hear.
Incredibly fun,
yes I must say,
it's incredibly fun to hear.
We wrote it in the sky.
The smoke,
the smears of blood,
the geese with little biting,
little biting beaks,
little naily teeth,
the tearing and ripping in the brown ear.
Oh, I don't hear anything.
Oh, I don't know nothing.
I'm just locked up in this black box
and this big stomach in the dirt.
Music!
This is a calamity.
Dreams,
ruined dreams,
dreams,
a dream
within a dream.
Rory.
Dreams.
It drives people mad.
There is no answer.
I'll do anything you say.
She likes it that way.
What a tomato!
I'll do anything you say.
Dreams.
What a night!
Rory.
And you can believe me.
Because I never lie
and I'm always right.
And I'm always right.
God have mercy on their heathen souls.
Hey Bert!
Hey Bert! Come here Bert!
Where are you Ernie?
Oh I'm right here in my bathtub.
Oh I see. Okay Ernie, what is it now?
What is it now?
Well I am here in my tubby Bert.
Yeah? And that means I'm going to wash myself.
So what do you need me for?
What a silly question.
Am I gonna
delete
all of this?
Don't you
know that
I love you
baby?
Am I
gonna
delete
all of this?
Don't you
know that
I love you
baby?
This isn't the original one I had.
The first one I had was a lot
fatter and longer.
And it used to scare the hell out of me.
So where do they hide the pump?
The pump?
Yeah, where's the pump hidden?
Well the pump is hidden in a little gelatinous thing
that's kept behind your
sacroiliac.
No, no, the
squirtum.
It's what you get when you're older.
But that means you have to reach back there at the proper time.
That's right. And that can be
extremely embarrassing. Kind of like air shocks.
It's like honey, would you squeeze
this bulb for me? Well what I usually
do is just say I have to go to the bathroom and make
a little tink and I pump it up in there, see?
And that way they don't have to... I could see a lot of girls
like, you know, pumping it beyond
its capability.
I could see a lot of, you know, women getting together and talking
about, well, do you help him pump it up?
You know, stuff like that.
Well you should, you know. And then they talk about
which ones don't and which ones do.
And then they decide to make them divorce
you for not pumping it up the right way.
I hooked up an air compressor to that thing.
Choo choo choo choo choo
choo choo choo choo
Okay, honey, I hope you're ready.
Well you should see
some of the beautiful scenes of unicorns
and flying horses that I've done with
this thing, buddy. If you want to make fun, go ahead.
But I've done some pretty, pretty...
It doubles as an airbrush. Yeah.
It doubles as a van painter
par excellence. Especially on the snow. If you stand in front of a big
bank of snow, you can do a great
unicorn airbrush. That's right.
You mean those t-shirts you gave me?
Painting in the snow? Yeah. Oh, man.
That's how I did them.
That's the way to do them, man. I'm not gonna
waste this. One time when I was in the hospital,
they gave me a pill and it made me pee green
or blue or something like that.
That would be cool. You could make t-shirts
with that. I think they fed you some
soylent green or a common algae and
black etc. to disrupt your...
Soylent green?
Doo-doo is a bad word. Bad word. Bad word!
Doo-doo is a very, very, very
bad word.
No, it's not a bad word,
bad word, bad word. No, it's not a
very, very, very bad word.
Doo-doo is a bad word. Bad word.
Bad word. Doo-doo is a very, very, very
bad word. Doo-doo is a very, very,
very bad word. No, it's not a
bad word, bad word, bad word. No, it's
not a very, very, very bad word.
Doo-doo is a bad word. Bad word.
Bad word, bad word, bad word, bad word.
You are a bad boy, bad boy, bad boy.
You are a very, very, very bad boy.
I can't talk about that kind of stuff on TV.
But how, you ask, how are we going to combat these evils?
I will tell you, it will take very much money and resources to combat Satan.
We must educate the masses that Satan is everywhere.
I'm sorry.
You must remember that the evil, the Satanism out there is organized.
It's a strong monopoly.
It's a machine.
It's got lots of gas and lots of power to get its means done on Earth.
And that is how the Earth is.
That is the way society is run.
You need money and power.
And only that way can you get what you want done.
So you must send money.
We must grow.
We must become the strong.
We must be the strongest power source in the world to combat evil.
And this is Luke 12.
He said unto his disciples, more than anything else, beware of those fancies.
They pretend to be good when they aren't.
But such hypocrisy cannot be hidden forever.
It will become evident that yees and doh, whatever they have said in the dark, shall be heard in the light.
And what you have whispered in the inner room shall be broadcast from that.
And the hell stops to all to hear about the evil and Satanism about.
Now this president and myself have exchanged letters on the spread of Satanism, which is the root of all problems plaguing this nation.
It is a paramount problem.
And once the media wakes up and starts attacking this problem, it will be over.
And the problem, day after day after day, all people will not be saved.
The subgenius is Jehovah's pride tool.
The subgenius has a covenant with this deatoid.
Who is well-pleased when his subjects have the wisdom to obey him.
It is the chore of the subgenius to smite and eliminate the unwitting.
Slavish!
Nonpartners of Jehovah One.
The great unwashed.
The hoi polloi.
Them.
The conspiracy.
The mediocrity.
The strange normal.
The somnambulax.
Be me.
Disretard.
and...
Buddha!
Orange haired...
ear ring and the nose wearing...
BOO!
No, no, no, no, bring it out!
It's from the gut! No, it's one of those...
Actually the original...
Where that originally came from was...
BOO!
That was the original but it was...
since corrupted to...
SQUIRREL, YOU PIG!
And...
Now just the common everyday...
BOO!
Where it originally was a...
full gutted...
BOO!
Back script!
It's so wonderful!
You know, I just got...
As I looked out...
These five people paddling away in the...
I can tell that something's working here...
that's much faster than me...
It's true!
Each and every one of them is...
is adequately equipped...
to carry the torch...
of Bob Derp Blurbs...
BORDS...
THE END
EPIC VIDEO
The 4th part starts now!
I have some plenty of eachping快
...
Hip
is far beyond control.
The geeking tells you to aspirate,
but he's trying not to miss the goal.
I'm sweating as makes you horny,
well done and I think you're in luck.
Cause all of this crept from my dare
gives me the first of...
Yo, wash it there.
Everybody wash your ears!
You flush up that wax.
Your ear better, sister girlfriend.
I feel so much better now.
I can sleep live.
Oh, I hear coming.
Oh, I like to sleep.
I can breathe much better in here now.
Oh, that was so enjoyable.
Hey Susan, did you know
that I'm in with you
and the sock wash is possible?
Well, I'm just a...
I sure did, Bob,
and that means it's time for a game.
Right, so everybody listen
to the game along with us.
Is he washing his sock?
Ready?
Oh, Bob and the ladies.
One of these sounds is not like the other.
The U.S. military participation
in unique breeding experiments.
It's true, some years back
the U.S. military did participate
in some unique breeding experiments
with rodents.
They tended to produce a small, vicious animal
capable of incapacitating a man.
These animals were to be used abroad
to protect sensitive computer disk storage areas.
Apparently, the size of the animals
meant they didn't set off the alarm systems.
Eventually, a stable breeding strain
of a hamster-like rodent was established.
These were nocturnal, carnivorous,
and extremely vicious.
They formed packs
with a highly complex social organization,
a rodent equivalent of the baboon.
Reporter Pat Call
talked to a retired
Army veterinarian some years ago
who had seen a training film
of these animals
tearing apart a year-old steer.
Within 10 minutes,
a pack of 15 of these cyber rodents
had killed the cow.
The vet was reminded of pictures
he had seen of piranha
attacking horse carcasses in the Amazon.
As these things go,
the Army's priorities changed.
The breeding program was canceled
and the stock was sold
to a civilian company in Missouri.
The company intended to market them
for security,
in the private sector,
but went bankrupt shortly after in 1988.
The animals were allegedly destroyed.
Dog fighting, although illegal,
has always flourished
in Cochise County, Arizona.
Toward the end of 1989,
local authorities in Cochise
began hearing rumors
of dog-hamster fights.
One thing led to another,
and at the beginning of 1991,
authorities raided the house
of a man living on the outskirts
of Busby, Arizona,
where they found,
about 30 small cages empty.
Was Barney involved?
The man was arrested for drug possession
and confessed to breeding and fighting
what he called attack hamsters.
I think these were Norwegian warfrat.
He claimed to have purchased
his original breeding stock
from a man in Missouri.
He admitted that he had been tipped off
about the raid and had set the animals free.
Coincidence? We think not.
In May 1991, mutilated animal carcasses
began turning up in the Palomino's Hereford area.
Deaths of a large number of coyotes,
two calves, one horse, and a bobcat
were unofficially attributed to the hamsters.
At the end of September,
the remains of a man who lived alone
in the trailer in the Mosen Road area
were discovered.
Neighbors said he raised hamsters.
There were a number of empty cages,
but again, no animals were found.
A month later, the freshly killed carcasses
of what appeared to be a large dog
and two cats were found out
in a vacant lot in Sierra Vista.
Not a lot of evidence of what there is
is possible.
The keeper of a secret.
She just likes to play games.
A lethal drug and a watch.
One man amusing himself.
You want a plastic girl?
Yes.
It's not a game.
All add up to a strange encounter.
She was enticed into a struggle with a drug.
But no drug you ever had.
You risk everything.
You risk everything when you play
The Self Genius Hour of Swag.
Let me tell you something that I hope,
Reverend Stang,
while I know that you as the pope
of this religion are familiar with it,
Bob, who we refer to in our teachings,
Bob grew up fighting the stigma
of that Mayan dad of his.
You know, other kids made cruel fun of the,
oh, God, of that slope head of full-blood Mayan area.
And though Mr. Dobbs maintained dignified silence,
little Bobby, well, little Bobby got in a lot of scraps
battling for his dad's honor.
And it was shortly after receiving a blow to the head
during one of those fights that Bob began experiencing
precognitive visions.
Oh, that's another one.
Now, I got to tell you, this troubled childhood
had a telling effect on this sensitive kid, all right?
He became, thanks to the pharmacies,
where as a chronic alcoholic at the age of six,
I went into hibernation, waiting for the computer god
efforts to murder me and the brokerage officers to relax.
Early in 1969, secretly, the computer god
controlled and manipulated gangster government,
issued a warrant for my immediate arrest and incarceration
in a maximum security insanity prison
to be cured forever before I could go
before any parroting puppet happened.
And then, when Rob gangster judged to give testimony...
So-called Christians that just go to church on Christmas Eve
are not Christians at all!
Let me tell you, my friend, they will burn in the fiery depths
of hell all the hotter because they come in
and have the gall to try and show the pretense
that they are Christians.
For that, they will burn twice as hot as any evening.
Oh, I said I will!
One wing of our barn!
Into this life
We were destined
To make it right
It's predetermined
And this is our fate
We're singing this song
So you can relate
We are going to save the universe
This time
We are foreground
We are grown-up men
We are all past
We hate to reason
That is our mission
We are going to save the universe
It is our past
It's obvious
That you still ask
We are going to save the universe
This time
It is HatseN
It's obvious
If life can't wake you up
You can't wake to you
My Attention
This pops up
When I expect
Your puddles
And say
Sir please
It's so quick
And every touch
So that it'll cut through
Because the alien is here
We don't matter
So it's not the same
We're in control
And we are more than a band
We are gone
Inside the universe
It's a dive
Well, maybe next time.
Thank you.
We were looking at that earlier.
Did you hear that the Catholic Church is going to begin advertising on MTV
to try to recruit young males?
It says, look at it.
Well, they're copying us.
They're copying the Church of the Subgenius.
Reverend, Reverend, look here.
If you notice, this is...
Emojons Anonymous.
Hand out to new members.
So if you become a member of the Catholic Church,
that's the first thing you get
is welcome to Emojons Anonymous.
Well, you have a new member.
You were talking about how it wasn't nearly as good as the old one.
And now you can wrap this around it.
The other guy, he had it cut off.
I'm hooked into a constantly regenerating process.
The people that I went to see
were very near...
What's the name of that college in Vermont?
Farmer's Branch.
It was upstate in Vermont, near Farmer's Branch,
where there's a blue lawn.
Downstate, really.
And it seemed that these people were offering this thing
on a one-time basis.
The Farmer's Branch fighting moose.
Yeah, more downstate, really.
Is moose the same for plural, moose?
Mooses?
No, it's moose-eye.
Moose-eye.
The moose-eye.
Two of them are moose-eye.
The Farmer's Market moose-eye.
The deadly moose.
The Farmer's...
No, the Farmer's Branch moose-eye.
See, a branch is what they say down south for a creek or a river.
Dead branch.
Or in Vermont.
Or in the creek.
You ever been down to Dead Branch Pass?
I never drank dead branch water.
Hey, boy, see any moose?
No bottle of Dead Branch Pass.
Pass out, we call it.
Yeah!
Pass out on Dead Branch Pass.
Well, it's time for the karaoke part of the show now.
I think the Reverend is going to do...
Oh, look, they have 12 steps.
It's a 12-step program for Emotions Anonymous.
First step number...
Step number one.
Do they seriously want...
Yes.
People who are too emotional or...
We admitted we were powerless over our emotions,
that our lives had become unmanageable.
That's number one.
Oh!
I need somebody to get Edward Munch out of here.
Here's number two.
There he goes.
Came to believe that a power greater than ourselves could restore us to sanity.
Wow.
Sanitation?
Restore us to sanity?
For God is clean.
He beareth not stinky boogers and juices that emit from him like...
This must be the work of the devil.
...we, his foul creation.
That is the work of the devil.
Here's a good one.
Number five.
Admitted to God, to ourselves, and to another human being,
the exact nature of our wrongs.
I'm dyslectic.
They felt too much, yes?
I believe in dog.
We have procreated slaw and divided amongst ourselves.
Oh, I have to go turn my tape over.
I have to go see the lucky worm.
Consult with Matt about a dog, you know?
Oh!
Point Percy at the porcelain log.
Can you?
What a, what a you.
So now save your really good stuff for now, because he'll have it on tape and then he'll use it on your show.
And then you can listen to it every week and go,
We were on The Stang Show again!
There is no good stuff!
Hey!
These are the subgenius devivals that are happening in our area in the next couple days.
Right here in Cleveland tomorrow, Friday, November the 12th.
Learn more about your shows here at
yardural естьKidsforum.ia
Bake a minimum cost to buy head in another year, veloy
put in a while.
…!
quien le llamas cojote
ора
saying, but he knew what you were saying.
Was he into drugs?
Yes.
But no drug you ever heard of.
What do you mean?
Special kind?
It's a long story.
The victory of ridiculous men.
And you can't imagine
the relief.
Tell them
no more games.
You want to play that game?
It's not a game.
My dear,
that's all it is.
Interesting to politicians
and
to the people.
And fanatics.
And they must find it.
Maybe kill for it.
Don't ask why.
Above all,
don't ask why.
I wouldn't want to lie now.
That is Bob's first million.
Bob's air of individuality.
When a man like you
paid a dollar
for one of these bumpers.
For ten dollars
for this amazing poster.
You know,
that was more.
It's true.
Bob's
offers
a bill for a ten dollar bill.
And it's ridiculous to think
that we're going to give it away
just because a bunch of lazy mutants
think they own the planet.
Dag,
Bob?
Hey, Paul, what do you want for Christmas?
Benny, what were you doing launching that bleeding ad on a Thursday?
Why was you wearing them big green straps?
You know you should not do that, Benny.
Take it easy, Doug.
Okay.
Doug?
Doug, I'm going to call a doctor.
No, I'm sorry, Bob.
We didn't mean it.
We didn't mean it to...
We won't call you anymore, Bob.
Please don't drop that bomb on us.
No, Bob, don't do it, please.
When's that bomb going to get here, Bob?
I already filled up my will.
Oh, no!
Oh, it was just a little one, Bob.
Meekie, Bob, Frock Bob.
Where in the world can Meekie be?
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
You're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
For free information on Bob Dobbs and the Church of the Subgenius,
send a self-addressed stamped envelope to...
Got your pencil ready?
Bob, Post Office Box 140306, Dallas, Texas, 75214.
That's Bob, P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas, 75214.
Stay tuned and praise Bob.
Oh, man.
Hey, don't really want to stop the show.
But I think it might be nice to know.
See, well, listen to this, man.
Look, look, look.
It's Christmas time, right?
And everybody's feeling all good, right?
And, uh, like, man,
I don't want to go off the stage without doing one of those,
one little number, all right, where everybody can join in.
Something like this.
This is this one bit I got off this old 16-millimeter film.
It's like it's in England.
Before East England,
it's in some club.
And it sounds just like bagpipes.
He's doing bagpipes, man.
Just look at this.
He's God, man.
Hendricks is still alive, man.
Hendricks is still alive.
He lives in Africa now.
He lives in Gambia.
And, uh, it's like he knew they were after Nixon wanted him killed.
But he had a look-alike.
There was a look-alike.
This guy named Randy Hanson.
Hendricks, now, he got his skin turned white.
And he's still alive.
And now he poses as Randy Hanson, the Hendricks impersonator.
But that's really Hendricks.
Brilliant.
I'm a bit proud of that.
Even Mitch Mitchell's been fooled.
But I found out.
I figured it out.
There was codes in the long version of Voodoo Child,
the San Diego concert.
Not the third San Diego concert.
The fourth one.
It's not on the album.
Oh, no.
There's a clue, cause he stops right in the middle of the song.
He talks.
You think he's talking about the cops.
But if you know these facts, it's like he's telling you what he's gonna do.
I got the-
I know this chick that said she-
I don't think she did.
But he did tell her that he was gonna do this.
He did not.
I don't know.
I don't remember.
tape of Hendrix and Morrison?
That was recorded in 1980, man.
There were no copies of that
before 1980. It's in a club in
France.