Yeah, this is Reverend Tanya and I live in Leipzig, Germany and believe it or not
I listen to WCSB all the time. Praise Bob. Praise Bob.
I see no reason for violence. If however you are confronted you may result
in some genius.
Bugs.
So now we can hug our fleas and ticks too.
American Ticks.
Don't kill flies with our nostrils.
It sounds like an American concept.
Really too much. Americans always overdo things.
Well, strangely enough it's pretty worldwide to tell the truth.
In fact we're going to Germany in a month just because some fans wanted to see what makes us tick.
Or maybe they want to kill us. I don't know.
I want to see the last places on earth.
Why are you here?
We're looking for the Marifesa Lupino Lumino.
A strange flower which grows only in Tibet and which it is said takes its life from the moon.
Is there really such a flower, Father?
There are some things it is better not to bother with.
Our coolies tell us the valley we want to visit is filled with demons.
Then we're right. This is the place. Get the ponies.
Right.
You are foolish.
But without fools there would be no wisdom.
Pax vobiscum.
My name is...
Ich heiße...
Ivan Stan.
Prinz V.
Ich heiße...
Ivan.
Ich heiße V...
Ich heiße...
My name is Dr. Weideberg.
The German alphabet.
Now we've done the alphabet.
Ich heiße Heisenberg.
Please repeat the German names for the letters of the alphabet.
Ich heiße V. Heisenberg. Dr. Heisenberg.
Ah.
A, B, C, D, U, S.
Practice spelling these words in the pauses.
Wuster, Machten, Etchen.
V.
Machten.
We're going to start from the beginning.
My name is...
My name is Kälber.
And...
My name is...
Kälber.
Praise Bob.
Do I understand you to say that we met in Tibet?
Yes.
And unless I'm mistaken,
we were both on a similar mission.
Yes?
Would it be intrusive if I should ask you
if you were successful?
In what?
In obtaining a specimen
of the Mariphesa lumina
the phosphorescent wolf flower.
Why, you know,
it blooms only under the rays of the moon.
This flower is an antidote for...
for what?
Werewolfry.
Lycanthropobia is the medical term
for the affliction I speak of.
And do you expect me to believe
that a man so afflicted
actually becomes a wolf
under the influence of the full moon?
No.
The werewolf is neither man nor wolf,
but a satanic creature
with the worst qualities of both.
I'm afraid, sir, that I gave up my belief
in goblins, witches,
personal devils,
and werewolves
at the age of six.
But that does not alter the fact
that there are two cases
of werewolfry known to me.
And, uh...
And how did these unfortunate gentlemen
contract this, uh,
this medieval unpleasantness?
From the bite of another werewolf.
These men are doomed,
but for this flower,
the marifasa.
Exactly what do you want of me?
Two blossoms
of the marifasa flower
in there
will save two souls tonight.
Tonight?
But I thought you said the marifasa
was a cure.
No. An antidote.
Effective only for a few hours.
But remember this,
Dr. Glendon.
The werewolf
instinctively seeks
to kill the thing
it loves best.
And, friends,
we are back
from our expedition
to Viseria.
Where we went in search
of the rare habifrop,
zippulops, marifasa, lumina,
lupino.
Which we did not get.
But, uh, we did find some
Bavarius marmosa.
More about that later.
Or maybe next show. I don't know.
The first half of this show will be
some recordings from our expedition.
Uh, hey!
I can't find the German drinking songs
CD, Princess Wynne.
Oh, no!
Yeah, that's from the library.
What shall happen to us if we don't have the German drinking songs?
We got a bunch, we got a bunch.
We can say things like
Guten Morgen.
Guten Abend.
Auf Wiedersehen.
Guten Nacht.
Echt
Eifelstein.
Du bist ein Schwein.
Ich hier ein
Eifelstein.
Ich hier ein Prinzess Wynne.
Die haben
die Welt gekampft.
Präs...
Präs Bob, bitte.
Bitte Präs Bob.
You better praise Bob. That's what that means.
You better praise Bob.
We gotta learn the German
for praise.
What is German for...
No, don't tell me, Dave. You'll get us in trouble.
No, yes, don't tell us, Dave.
Say it again. Say it again.
Huh? Praise Bob.
Um, okay.
In German.
Versen Wobet.
Versen Wobet?
I made that up. I couldn't think of a word for
praise in German that was funny.
Dave made something up.
Well, man, well, wonders never
cease.
I can...
shine all day.
Okay, um...
That sounded really authentically German, Dave.
All I gotta do is just, you know,
get in there and really stupefacken
and figure out the right...
I know it's a bit...
Okay, well, enough Sturm und Drang.
But you've got the Schledens really well.
Enough Sturm und Drang and enough
Stang und Drummond and
Lonesome.
German has some additional sounds
and letters. In German,
two dots called Umlauts
can be placed over the
vowels. However, the
Umlaut changes the pronunciation.
A Umlaut is
pronounced eh, O Umlaut
is pronounced ö, and
U Umlaut is pronounced ü.
Please practice
saying these German umlauted
vowels.
Eh. Eh. Eh.
Eh. Eh.
Good brochkin.
You don't know anything.
Nussbester span.
Grossbind, Grossbellar.
Grossbildbellar.
I'm Belskyn's killer.
Stefan Stank had coffee.
And I had chocolate.
Yeah, we're learning how to use the money
and say please and thank you and stuff like that.
And basically look like dumbasses.
They can instantly tell when they spew out a bunch of words at you
and you stare at them blankly like a dumbass.
They go, oh.
Oh, it's un Americaner.
Un taub.
Which means deaf.
I'm ready at all times to say,
Ich bin Amerikaner, un taub.
But I haven't had to yet because they can tell.
They just instantly can tell.
Probably by the fact that I'm dressed like a peasant.
As usual.
Although I do have my amino acids shirt on,
so if there's any amino acid fail.
I swear there was.
We were walking by the Thomas Kirch.
And this guy kept shooting.
He looked like a tourist.
He kept giving me the thumbs up.
And I looked behind me to see if he was maybe pointing to somebody else.
I couldn't figure it out.
I remember that.
Yeah.
I thought, maybe he's an old guy.
But still, so am I.
He could be some dude from Detroit.
Or a subgenius fan who's watched lots of amino acid videos that I shot.
You never know.
I've noticed a lot of attention being shown to that amino acid shirt of yours.
Really?
Yes.
People turn around and look at it.
Well, since it's on my back, I don't see it.
Right.
But it has bowling pins being knocked down on it.
Maybe that means something here.
You never can tell what means what.
No.
I just finished feeling up a naked lady carved in marble.
There are naked ladies carved in marble all over the place, along with the...
All over the place.
...horrible baby.
the scary babies and muscle men and lions and stuff.
But most of them you can't reach.
They're up kind of high.
They're on building facades.
So all you can do is take pictures of them.
You can't feel of them.
But this big statue we just saw had three babes just a little larger than life,
and you could definitely feel of them.
They chopped off all my hair.
They gave me a bob.
I trust that this look will hopefully get me more squash in the future.
I think you're, like, total genius.
No way, man.
Let me tell you something.
You.
are genius.
Oh yes, dear friends, that collage was by The Large, who is here with us despite this
wind in Leipzig.
Leipzig.
Praise Bob.
You pronounce it all wrong, man.
I'm deaf.
You never got it.
No, no, it has nothing to do with it.
You're just plain stupid, man.
That may be true.
We didn't call it the Church of the Genius.
Well, we're here with Reverend Tanya and Reverend Bucky Argyle.
Our hosts here and our guides know the language and the way around.
They know everything worth knowing, and The Large knows everything else.
We're out for a rainy, sunny walk on a rainy, sunny day.
This is one of those primitive cities.
This is one of those cities where the cars aren't allowed.
This ancient cemetery we're sitting in is, well, it's older than the ones we walked through
in Cleveland.
Mm-hmm.
These guys here that were born in 1790 and died in 1950.
I don't get that.
It must be all the healthy food, the good cheese.
The Large said he only came here for the cheese.
That's all he wanted.
That's the only reason he goes to Holland, not for the pot, for the cheese.
For the cheese.
Yeah.
It's so good.
We've been here, oh, what, less than a week.
Today's Thursday.
Oh, it's my birthday.
Yeah.
I turned 161 today, and we're going to go eat at a really fancy restaurant called the
Auerbach Skeller.
Which is our favorite.
which is our box.
Cellar.
And it's 400 years old.
Although I'm sure they've replaced some of the plates
and silverware and stuff.
Probably.
There's going to be some kind of a subgenius party
later in the week on Saturday night.
We're expecting at least four people besides us.
Bucky and Reverend Tatiana.
Reverend Tatiana is German and Russian.
And she sounds really sexy when she talks German.
She sounds really sexy when she talks in any language.
And Reverend Bucky is from Austin, Texas, pretty much.
So he and I are the dumbasses
accompanying royalty as they walk around Germany here.
But now Bucky is from Leipzig.
Yeah, I guess so.
He must have a green card and everything else.
He's trying to be from Leipzig.
Yeah.
This town is about as big as Cleveland.
It's the 12th largest city in Germany,
which I think Cleveland is now about the 12th largest city in the U.S.
And it used to be an industrial center
that was really rich but really polluted,
just like Cleveland.
Then the industry collapsed, just like Cleveland.
Also, unlike Cleveland,
it was under communist rule.
It was under communist rule for a long time,
and it went to hell.
But around 1989, all that changed,
and it's been dressed up like Cleveland
and fixed up a lot since then.
And it's full of great museums.
We went to the Anthropology Museum inside the Grassy Museum,
which isn't really very grassy at all.
No.
And only made it about halfway through before it closed.
Then we went to the Art Museum and saw a beautiful painting
by Flemish and Dutch masters and stuff from the 15th and 16th century,
back when people knew how to draw and paint everything except babies.
We must have seen a million baby jesu in paintings yesterday
that were all crappy.
They can paint women and men and tortured Jesuses.
We must have seen 190 tortured Jesuses yesterday.
Easily.
But there were that many baby Jesuses,
and they were all deformed.
Every single one of them, just scary looking.
They kind of, a lot of them looked like a bean
with arms and legs attached.
Yeah, really hideous.
And then there were the baby heads flying around
with little wings in some of the paintings.
Oh, the angel bugs.
Yeah.
So we have a lot more museums to go see.
It was really impressive.
It was immense.
The ceilings in that place were like three stories high.
Well, that's art museums for you.
They're a big waste of space if you ask me.
And especially the modern art section
with all the splatter crap, Jasper Johns type garbage.
It wasn't garbage.
I liked that stuff.
Garbage.
That stuff, any kid can do that.
But I can't say that I could do a hideously deformed baby
any better than those Dutch masters.
Or a tortured Jesus.
Man, there's a lot of tortured Jesus in there.
Mm-hmm.
But this is a pretty Christian town,
considering that they were under communism for a long time.
And the commies dynamited the big church at the university.
It's since been replaced by a much bigger
and more obnoxious church,
as if to say,
screw you, Ruskies.
You know, we could drive to Russia from here.
In fact, we could drive to Beijing from here.
You could drive just about,
I think you could drive to South Africa from here
if you took a ferry at one point.
Oh, it's interesting.
My feet hurt again.
God, my feet hurt.
It's such a walkable city, that's why your feet hurt.
We've been walking and walking and walking.
We didn't have to walk up the,
how many stairs?
500 stairs?
Yeah, and the new rat house,
which is not where they keep the new rats,
but the, actually the new town hall or city hall.
Where they ratify laws.
There's a high tower that we tried to get into today,
but we were late.
We have to go back at 14 o'clock,
or blow it off.
That's in a little while.
40 minutes, right.
Yeah.
But this cemetery is peaceful.
And incredibly ancient.
You can't really read most of the inscriptions
because they've been worn away.
Except for the really rich guys.
They got marble inscriptions instead of stone or concrete
or whatever they're using here.
Sandstone, it looks like.
Yeah, so whatever erodes the fastest.
Yeah, it's funny to walk around a place that has a building,
like an old hotel that Peter the Great stayed in,
right next to a Woolworths.
Yeah.
And a Burger King across from the Thomas Kerche,
where Johann Sebastian Bach played and ran things for 20 years.
He was the cantor.
Yeah, everything's all Bach-y around there.
In fact, to make it really sound like Leipzig,
we'd have to mix in some background street band playing Bach
or Schiller or something.
Or jazz or rock.
Mendelssohn lived here.
Richard Wagner was born here, but he didn't like it.
And he had nothing good to say about his childhood home of Leipzig.
It's similar to New Orleans in that you hear every style of music
as you're walking down the street.
Sometimes classical, but at St. Thomas Kerche, of course, yes.
Well, there's a lot of oompa music here.
Yes.
There's a certain amount of oompa stuff, it being Germany and all.
So, oh well.
I guess that is our testimony for now.
It's only 1320 in the afternoon.
See, I'm starting to get the hang of this foreign time telling.
Foreign slash military time.
Yeah, next I'll be measuring things in centimeters and kilometers.
And degrees in Celsius.
I haven't mastered that one yet.
Converting euros to dollars in my head has been kind of fun.
A cup of coffee was only about a buck fifty.
And the Bockwurst was about 220, something like that.
This is actually a pretty cheap town if you stay out of the really fancy restaurants.
Which we're going to go to tonight.
Hehehe.
And have lamb.
No, lamb is at the...
Hookah bar that we're going to on Saturday.
The subgenius party.
Yeah.
Okay.
Six to an even, over and out.
Oh, this guy was hilarious.
I'll take your word for it.
This taxi driver was hilarious.
He smelled everything that you should not do as a taxi driver.
Drive like crazy.
Insult other...
Well, here at least.
Insult other people on the street.
Smell like garlic.
And breathe heavily while driving.
So he was the perfect cab driver.
That's more of what I'm used to.
Driving crazy, breathing heavily, smelling like garlic.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
That's...
You know, I have to admit, once you go outside the ring, it looks just like Cleveland.
Yes.
Only with more white people.
Okay.
One, two, three.
Okay, good, good, good.
Hello.
Hi, how are you?
Good, how are you?
Nice to meet you.
Hi, how are you?
Hi.
Hello.
Please.
Oh, hi, hi, hi, hi, hi.
Reverend Rasta.
I'm sorry we were so late.
Hello.
Great to see you, man.
Great to see you, too.
You're taller.
No, that's just the shoes.
How are you guys?
We're good.
Younger.
You're younger.
How did that happen?
I found the secret to the universe, actually.
If you have five minutes of your time or something, I could share it.
I don't mind.
Okay.
Great.
Yeah.
Let's not forget.
Yeah, let's just not forget.
Yeah.
I've never been in a car.
I've never been in a hookah bar.
Me either.
You guys want to drink anything?
Houses, roses, Moses.
When I was a little boy, they let me smoke in the office while I was working.
I could make politically incorrect jokes and nobody would sue me.
Yeah.
Times are hard.
One thing I forgot to mention.
Similarities between Leipzig and Cleveland is they're, I think, about the same latitude.
Is that right?
I think so.
It's about as far north.
The weather is almost exactly the same.
It was unseasonably cool for once in Cleveland when we left, and it's the same way here.
It's probably about 70 degrees right now.
It's really, really nice.
So we lucked out in that respect.
Very much so.
Yeah.
We lucked out, period.
We just lucked out.
We really did luck out.
Praise Bob.
Praise Bucky.
Praise Tanya.
Yeah.
Yeah, I told somebody we won a trip to Germany, but I didn't tell them that we won the trip
by being funny on the radio or something.
Being a freak show, anyway.
Yeah.
There, that's the sum total of my German so far.
Ja, Kinder.
Ja, mein Kinder.
Actually, I've been picking up a lot of stuff.
I can order Rotwein or Weisswein.
Weisswein.
Und Wienerschnitzel.
We haven't actually done that yet.
Another Skellington.
An actual...on this tombstone we're looking at, there's an actual...a skeleton.
Skull head with crossbones, but it's in 3D and the head is turned.
Yeah, and there's a bat over it.
Yeah.
Bat wings instead of angel wings.
That's pretty cool.
And today you saw a poster of Der Frankenstein.
Well, I was kind of hoping to see Frankenstein's castle, but I think that's in Switzerland.
Also, I think it's entirely fictitious.
Oh.
And here's Peter, work again ...
Pink tranquility.
Black帽 sia, pink Betsy bails.
Some of these black Louisa shoes.
продолжается
MoreSUCCESSES
Now I think I'll just take one and let it rock through here.
built to look like they were 400 years old. Yes. There's a certain amount of
cheating done in these towns. For a fact. Plus, you know, in any given German city, about
half of the buildings got reduced to rubble during the war. So they rebuilt
them. Sometimes real modern, super modern. Sometimes they try to duplicate what had
been destroyed. So it looks old, but it's fake old. It's still kind of old. Older
than me, that's old. I'm a year older now than I was yesterday.
Here are real German, Austrian and Swiss cities which use umlauted vowels.
Practice saying the name of these cities.
Shevavish Hall.
I've never heard of that one. Shevavish Hall.
Okay.
Princess, we were live just in case you were confused by what was going on.
What was tape and what was us.
Me? Confused?
Well.
That's preposterous. And besides, we're being called to the great mass. Can't you
hear the bells?
Is that what that is?
Yes.
The great mass?
A mass of what?
A mass.
Yeah.
It's a thing that happens in a cathedral, dear.
Oh, I thought that was what Dave makes when he comes over for dinner. A big mass.
No. No.
It's different from that.
These are the bells outside of our lodgings, right?
Yes.
At Tonya and Bucky's place?
Yes. One Sunday morning as they were going on and on and on, I picked up your recorder and I held it out the window for a moment. Actually, this was through the window. There's one moment during it where the volume increases. That's when I opened the window.
I opened the window for just a moment and the volume pops.
Well, they had a great apartment.
Oh, amazing.
We didn't know what we were going, what we were going to be in for. And it all paid off. It was just great.
Oh, fabulous.
They're right in the middle of the coolest part of town. And their apartment is like, if you ever saw that movie Hostel, that's the way it is. And they have a Venus fly trap.
Yes. And I caught a flying feather.
I read it one day. And then I got to watch each day as the plant absorbed more and more of the fly.
Like, that's what Bob will do with us all someday. Just absorb us. And it's true that Reverend Bucky and Reverend Tatiana listen to WCSB, not really all day, but a lot.
Practically 24-7, 365.
They're listening right now.
Their machine is connected.
They're using VLC player to stream.
I can tell because it's, see, we can look at, we see you guys from here. See?
We can see you.
Our special WCSB live stream status is a two-way thing. As you can see, I didn't shave for this.
But it wasn't bell music from the 5,000-year-old bell and all the, God, they must have a great hunchback's union in that town.
To keep those bells ringing all the time.
But at times you could hear three different bands out of their window.
Playing three different kinds of music.
Hey, look, I see, speaking of music, let's see if this is Dave.
Hello?
It is.
It's Buf and Fomfenstein.
Was ist das?
Buf and Fomfenstein just called in.
Ah.
I see.
Not.
You refer to this as poppycock?
Which is a strange word.
Ja, ja. Ja.
How about a little jam session on the nose?
I was just kidding.
I wondered if you, since you returned, if your welt bekommt?
We can't, I can't understand you very well, but yeah, whatever you ask, the answer is probably yes.
Hey, uh.
I was wondering if I could call you back since I can hardly hear you right now.
Really?
Yes, well now I can hear you.
That's strange.
Well, yeah, just shove your ear closer to that little device.
Was it the church?
That's what all the listeners are doing.
Was it the church bells that were drowning us out?
No, I will have to call you back.
Oh.
Because you guys just, what you sounded like to me was, I don't know.
I think he's trying to tell us what we sound like.
Oh.
Can I give it a try?
Sure, Dave.
Shooter, call us back.
Try it again.
I'll try.
I'll try the other line now too, perhaps.
I'll listen to that beautiful background music in, uh, from, uh, our trip.
At one point, Princess, we heard a stink.
A string quartet doing the Lord of the Rings theme music.
And a few minutes later, uh, it was a clarinet player jamming with a didge player.
Yes, he was doing jazz riffs off of Happy Birthday to You.
Oh, that might pop up in this background music at some point.
This was a concert.
This was a concert right next to us, right, right in front of the big statue of Bach.
Bach.
I like the better, I like the statue of my hero, Gottfried Leibniz, uh, who's the Dr.
Howell of Germany.
And also, I like the stack of ancient cannonballs, because I like balls.
Oh, speaking of balls, let's see if Dave is back again.
Is it better?
It's fine with me.
Sounds good to us.
You guys are like way, way padded down on both phones.
I use the insignificant phone that the foreigners gave me.
Back when they first, you know, back in the first baptism, when you almost drowned.
I mean, back in the first, uh, when you almost drowned in the, remember?
You're gonna have to just turn the sound on your phone up, because we can't turn the sound of the radio station up any louder.
It's as loud as it's ever gonna get.
I know, maybe I'm just going deaf in the ear that's not responsible.
That's right, you're gonna have to pay that ear more.
Hey, uh, you know those cards?
The collages that we play on this show sometimes that are by The Large?
Well, The Large and his girlfriend Suvi came to visit us in Leipzig, and we met The Large.
And he is, in fact, tall.
I expected him to be fat, but he's not.
He's kind of skinny.
He's not fat.
He's large, and he's very, very weird.
Like all, I've heard that all Finns from Finland were weird.
But, uh...
They are weird.
This, The Large, we ended up renaming him for our own purposes, Reverend Lonesome Angry Cowboy Larry Talbot.
And Suvi is Reverend Suvi the Fluvi.
Because The Large, they speak really good English, with kind of a Finnish accent.
Got a nice Finnish on it.
But...
I can understand that, I heard that many times before.
He can...
Throughout my childhood.
This guy can do Finnish versions of dozens or hundreds of American and British accents.
And he even imitates you, Dave.
He does.
Yeah, he even, and he quotes you.
Hippahei.
No, that's...
The Finns used to always say hippahei.
Oh, really?
And they called my mother, their name for mother is Aitik.
How do you know these things?
Because there's a large fin population, the Sumalainen, sons of the Suomi.
Do they really...
In this town here.
Do they really have fins?
Yes, they used to have like ten sauna baths.
Wow.
You know, regular normal ones.
Yeah.
With normal signs and normal people hanging over the top.
Oh, I don't know about those kind of things, Dave.
Well, you're not required to anymore, that's why.
I don't know nothing about this normal.
Helsinki masker, or whatever you call them.
The large.
Yeah.
He's large.
Yeah, he can imitate you imitating other European accents.
And it's amazing, he actually pulls it all off.
It's just befuddling, but he does.
Well, the next time you see him, say mita kulu, or mita kulu, or mita kulu.
One of those three words.
Yeah.
Mitakulu.
He's probably listening now.
Mita, hey, mita.
Palio, mita.
Gitos, palios.
I have no idea what...
This is the clarinet and the didge.
...that's the stuff they say when they shake hands and argue with each other, you know,
when they...
You know what I mean?
Like the ordinal numbers.
The cardinal letters.
But...
We're listening to the didge and clarinet jam.
Of the large?
Of the large.
No, it was of just some street musicians that...
This town is...
They don't have cars in the touristy old town, but they do allow musicians everywhere.
And as we walked through, every time I heard one, I turned my recorder on.
Yeah.
Well, do they have the...
And then she didn't pay him.
...what they call the bald poopy knees?
And I didn't pay.
You know, like when you take...
When you wear a scruffed up blue jeans and you make sure that the knee comes out.
And your knee looks like a bald poopy.
Well, there was a lot of people sitting around waiting for you to give them money because
they had a dog and punk hairdo.
It's like...
Dog buskers make good dough.
I guess so.
There were a lot of them there.
There were...
You know, I sure noticed a lot of white people in that town, but they were some exceedingly
weird looking ones.
You know, they're like purebred...
And I think that you understand that they're...
I think that's the reason we done fought World War II in our American history.
Oh, man.
I got some great...
Some people gave us some great advice before we went.
Still one time.
Our friend, Reverend Pease, said that when you go to Germany, grab your crotch a lot
when you talk to the Germans.
It's how you make them respect you.
Now, is this true?
No.
I think that's baloney.
He also said, buy some leather shorts and one of those hats with the boars' hats.
The boars' hair thingy at the airport you'll want to blend.
And lederhosen.
You forgot the most important part of it.
I'm making sure you're wearing nice stockings.
Lederhosen.
I actually saw a lot of lederhosen in the stores, but it's very expensive.
Very expensive.
Very fancy, Doug.
And beautiful dresses for women that are traditional as well.
And they're also expensive.
What the hell's a drudgeon, Wayne?
Pardon?
No.
You said drudgens for women who are over 100 years old, like a corset or something?
Drudgens?
No, dresses.
We're all so deaf that we're just pretending to know.
We're all taub.
We're taubed out, and we're just pretending to know what each other are saying.
So you were faking German over there, and you're actually, was ist der time, meine Freund?
Ist es das Vier o'clock?
Well, you may have missed the earlier parts of the show.
Yeah, we kind of did.
Yeah, we did.
Especially in Prinzess.
We get drinks, the Weisswein, she starts speaking.
But you don't sound Weltbekomft.
Do you know what Weltbekomft means in Deutscher?
I don't know what Weltbekomft means.
You do?
I don't.
Oh.
It means world-weariness, or just when the world, like, makes you go, oh, man.
Oh, man.
I wish there was a slightly better world.
Which we know that is the hypothesis behind your frontal lobotomy.
Well, yeah, but it didn't work.
Not like it's cracked up to be.
Well, they're not supposed to work.
You're talking about the trepanning, right?
Not the frontal, it's not exactly a lobotomy, but it was a trepanation that went wrong.
Trepanation gone bad.
I always go wrong.
I reiterate.
You would.
It's never gone right one time past a six-month trial period.
And you know that deep within your heart of hearts.
Here's some more advice we were given by Reverend Pease.
He said, use the exit for all the attractions.
Oh, by the way, Ausfahrt means exit.
It is not the largest town in Germany.
No, not just the road.
But he said, use the exit for all the attractions.
And when confronted, say, I'm an American and all this stuff should be ours.
It lets them know you're a man to be reckoned with.
But with your blending in clothes from the airport, your confronter would most likely have thought you a German.
Once corrected in this manner, the said German will cheerfully give way and allow you to continue on your way.
I believe that's in their constitution, he said.
But they can't seize your land and property and put you in a camp.
At the moment's notice.
Well, that's in their...
You forgot.
They ran the communists out.
It's not in East Germany anymore.
It's unified Germany now.
I screamed.
Oh, and it said...
I was told, do not, under any circumstances, say anything about Nazis ever.
Because some are still hiding out and they can be cantankerous when exposed.
Or...
I've said too much already.
That's what my friends...
It's a national sore spot.
Just like the front of your head after the trepanation.
It's something that is there.
It won't go away.
It's painful.
But nobody...
Everyone refuses to acknowledge it.
My brain, you mean?
No.
The past, man.
No, comrade.
My friend.
The past.
Ja, comrade.
But you're talking about that.
No, see?
They don't like stuff like that.
When you make the little big hi-ho salute and...
Oh, no, no.
Pretend like you got a funny mustache.
They think you're mocking them or making fun of them.
Well, some...
You know what?
They actually do say Gesundheit.
Yes, they do.
And they're not kidding.
Yeah, but we still invented it just like cheese and rich crackers.
Like tacos and pizza.
They don't really do that over there.
Fishmongering.
Mongering.
Now, I was told...
Now, here's something weird.
Over there, Bud Light is a fancy import brand.
But, as my friend said, as Reverend Peace advised us, beer is free.
But in order to promote national health, it is customary to run from where you got your
beer while the server chases you for a few blocks.
This keeps everyone in shape and is great fun.
I'm so sorry.
Somehow I just don't trust Reverend P's advice.
Oh, I don't know. He said German food is heavy.
I would eat once on arrival and then weekly until you return to a more civilized part of the world.
I have never seen a more civilized part of the world.
Everything in Germany is engineered smarter.
We all know that German cars are...
Even the simple things like cups, they're incredibly over-engineered.
I'm talking about things like washers and dryers where there's no dryer vent,
but the water is collected in a little vessel inside the machine.
I'm talking about typer clips.
The Volkswagen factories have only two guys in them.
They turn out thousands every day, some huge number.
They're hardworking.
They're electric and stuff.
And all this stuff's transparent.
I mean, not only as far as their mission and all that commerce stuff,
but also you can see all the way everywhere.
It's like wide open.
It's wide open and stuff, and machines do most of the work.
I just don't see how you can say that it's not civilized.
You have toilets that have special engineering,
so you push one button for the little load and another button for the big load.
That's the toilet you're talking about, right?
That's the toilet I'm talking about, yes.
It's the bidet, actually. It's the aggressive bidet.
What about a really big load?
Then you have to use the washer and dryer, right?
No.
No, you use the high-tech paper clips.
Everything there is super well built.
Everything from the coffee machine to the refrigerator to everything that I saw.
Door handles, keys.
Now, Princess, we didn't see all of Germany.
We were just in Leipzig, which was voted the best city to live in.
In Germany.
Yes, I know.
We did spend...
How was the food, by the way, since I missed that part?
Was it delightful?
I mean, I know it's not good in Sauerbraten, but...
Well, I'll tell you what.
We had a meal at this 500-year-old restaurant that is so old
that it's featured in the beginning of the novel Faust,
or the play, I mean, Faust.
Faust.
The first scene of Faust takes place in this.
Yeah, in the Auerbach Stella.
Now, the cool thing about this restaurant is,
because it's featured in a story about the devil,
it has fabulous artwork by all kinds of people of times and places of the devil.
And that helped to soothe our feelings
after being exposed to millions of pictures of Jesus being tortured,
or the hideous baby Jesus.
Because the devil...
He looked pretty good most of the time.
He's talking not just...
Yeah.
Not just about artwork.
He's talking about enormous murals that are painted all around the room.
Actually, there's giant murals painted all over the place.
But there's like...
The Marriott is covered with full-color cartoon people.
Yes.
I mean, a giant building covered with thousands of cartoon people.
Like 20 stories high in brilliant colors.
And there's some graffiti artist named Snow
who managed to sign whole dilapidated buildings.
Yes.
Way up high.
Yeah.
Wow.
What a piker.
What a fishmonger.
Did you go to see...
Hey, do you like German Expressionism?
Did you go see any artworks?
Those cats, I think, were pretty hip.
I really do.
The German...
And they...
Did you know that they influenced Wachli Kandinsky?
Yeah.
And others?
I believe you.
Yeah.
If Dave said it, then you better pick up on it.
We did go see the art museum, and I really enjoyed it.
Reverend Stang didn't like the modern part.
No.
He liked the rest of it.
I like the stuff, the landscapes and things that look like things.
And people that look like people.
Unless they're tortured Jesus.
Oh, yeah.
Der Fuhrer's kind of art.
Not German Expressionism.
No, he goes for Der Fuhrer's type of art.
Yes.
It's a very nice-looking...
It's a very nice-looking building.
And...
Yeah.
Right.
Yeah, I like that.
In fact, if I ever got a time machine, I'd go back in time and buy Hitler's art.
But then if he had a customer, he wouldn't have become a Nazi.
That's true.
It's self-defeating.
It's that time travel paradox.
I've discussed this before, I think.
Yes, you have.
The Harold and Maude and Kumar meet Hitler.
But then when they get back to their time,
his artwork doesn't sell because there never was a World War II
because somebody bought his artwork, finally.
Now, just think if somebody bought even one piece of Van Gogh's art,
he would have quit...
Wait a minute.
I don't know why.
His stuff wouldn't be worth anything now.
If it had sold back then...
If Van Gogh weren't become a dictator and his lopped-off ear
would have been kind of like his monogrammed little mustache and stuff,
and rather than going in these big ranching diatribes,
and saying, you know, I'm going to sell this stuff,
stuff like that, he would just go up to the podium
and he would just glare at the audience for a while
and then go...
And then take his pants and run away.
It's not how they do it nowadays.
That's how they do it nowadays.
That's how...
Sorry.
Oh, one big difference between Saxony and Thuringia
and Ohio and Texas,
is that between the cities,
it's just farmland,
but there's no billboards.
None at all.
There's no ads.
It's like...
How can you call that country civilized
if they don't have commercials everywhere?
It's like being in an endless park.
I know, Dave.
You're just being resentful because of that time they...
That Hogan's Heroes episode that confused you so much.
Yeah, but just think how much they get paid.
You know, they get all the vacations all the time.
They still have producers.
And with less solar energy,
I mean, with less solar stuff,
they're going mostly solar energy now
and stuff like that
and kicking butt at it and everything.
There are solar panels on many buildings here.
Even most of Europe that we think of as poor
is a lot better than that.
I mean, it's a lot better than us.
Why didn't you move to Russia then?
If you don't like it here, huh?
Why didn't you move to...
Deutschland, there, Schicklgruber.
Yeah.
Yeah?
Yeah, Schicklgruber.
That's what I...
Whatever that...
I shouldn't say things like that
because I don't know what it means.
You don't know what it means.
You could be...
All I know is...
We're in very big trouble.
The president of the USA is named Schicklgruber.
That's an old fire sign.
Obama's secret name is Schicklgruber?
No.
It's not Quasimodo?
No, that's no.
Obama's secret name is Obabo.
Obabo.
Yeah.
He's the preseserp of Uninu.
Well, that should be a boon to the church of the subgenius, I would say,
if the president is named Obabo.
Well, it's not...
It's spelled O-B-A-B-O.
Like a liquid soap in the 1960s?
So you gotta kind of stretch it to get the Bob...
Yeah.
What, uh...
Makes me...
Yeah.
I don't know.
It makes me tingle inside.
Obabo.
Makes me feel patriotic.
What's the matter?
You don't like Obabo?
Are you racist?
Are you anti-presidential?
Do you have duck-webbed feet?
I have duck-webbed feet.
And fins, because I am a Finlander.
Yeah, the feet already have the skis on them.
So when you go to sauna, that way you can go right through the snow, see?
That's where mermaids come from.
Finland.
How do you know?
Because I looked.
Yes, you know why they call him the large now, huh?
Yes.
You saw him wear his fins.
You saw where the fins are.
No.
Lined up along that thing.
As Reverend Tanya so brilliantly said,
the large, when he said,
you ladies, you know what the large refers to.
And it took her two beats to say,
you must be referring to your nose, right?
Yeah.
So is there a human body or an erectile like the dysfunctional comments I just made?
Yeah, actually, the large is a foul-mouthed fin.
But if my reading of thriller novels is right,
they're all foul-mouthed like Australians.
Yeah.
Yeah, I know how Australians are.
They're large and they like to cause bar fights.
And Mexicans also like to cuss.
No, they like to cuss.
Not like you or me.
No, no, no.
Or on the radio.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Dr. Sinister has entered the room.
Yeah, I have.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I've been here.
I hope he's wearing, I hope he's dressed like the guru,
the guru Swami Deva with the weird, you know,
yellow toga thing going down there and sandals and everything.
And he's like making some kind of sign.
I live in Cleveland Heights.
Heights.
I'm a Heizer.
Did you know when that really means?
I'm really a, I am a beer belly.
Yeah.
You always, you know, you think you're ordering Wiener Schnitzel all the time and you've actually
been asking for anal sex.
You know, I think about, I think about what would have happened if, if World War I and
World War II had gone a little bit differently, then Vienna could have been.
The capital that ended up getting divided after a war.
And if JFK had gone to Vienna instead of Berlin, he would have said Ich bin ein Wiener.
Wiener.
Well, that really happened.
Did you know that?
Wiener.
When he said Ich bin ein Berliner, he meant he should have said Ich bin Berliner rather
than Ich bin ein Berliner, because that means I am a Berlin sandwich.
And that's where the joke from the hot dog got going and inspired you to create that
Wiener joke.
Okay.
You told me that where is the restroom is said, wo ist der Schlafzimmer?
Schlafzimmer is bedroom.
Uh-huh.
I was afraid that I was being set up.
You know, where is the.
Scheißhaus.
The bordello or yeah, where is the der Scheißhaus?
Du musst nicht im Schlafzimmer scheißen.
Das ist nicht gut.
Schlafzimmer scheißen.
Was du isst.
Du musst nicht im Schlafzimmer scheißen.
Ich bin ein Berliner.
I'm told not to do foreign language stuff on the radio when I don't know what it's
being said.
No.
Not when you don't know what it means.
Especially when subgeniuses tell you to say it to someone.
Well, that's why you have your, the original subgenius cunning linguist right here who can
translate these things for you.
Don't forget the power of Google, by the way.
Well put.
Oh, I had the bright idea of Google Glass with, set up with a translator program.
I was just thinking, I'm just going to go through the whole thing.
Like a speech, a speech to text, like it's, and then a translator so that you could actually
have subtitles.
Yeah.
Now I could use that for English personally, but yeah.
I keep the, uh, the closed captions on my TV.
Uh, you know, I, I don't want to, you know, everything, the speech is so quiet and the
music and the sound effects are so loud and I don't want to wake up the neighbors.
So I always keep the closed caption.
You don't want them to see the closed captions either because that would cause like a total
panic on the West side or wherever you are.
Right now, people would just like, it would freak out, man.
It would be dangerous.
We're on the air side right now.
Yes.
And we're approaching the end.
We air on the side of caution.
Yeah.
We're airing out now.
We're going to air out.
We've got about one minute left and this is the subgenius radio ministry hour of slack
number 1,482 this time.
And most of those weren't reruns either.
Yeah.
And if anybody needs the information that they need, it's at subgenius.com and I could
calmly put us back on the recordings.
I think I will.
So Dave, Dave,
Well, I'm going to miss you guys because I want to, after I get done going to the bathroom,
I'm moving to Germany.
By the way, my phone doesn't work at home.
So, well, that's just too bad.
Well, Dave's gone.
Auf Wiedersehen, Dave.
Auf Wiederhören.
Well, we're going to go see the Stasi Museum, I hope, because I need to have lots of helpful
hints for how to survive when the Tea Party takes over the USA.
Why are you mocking President Obama?
You're, don't you like your country?
Don't you like freedom?
Why do you hate freedom?
You don't like Obama?
What's wrong with him?
Praise Obabo, the prez of Serb.
That's the one we worship.
Obabo, the prez of Serb.
He's an AI that exists on the internet.
He's not a Kenyan communist.
He's not from Kenya.
He's not a communist.
He's not a socialist.
He's from Nigeria.
He's a scammer.
He doesn't have funny big ears like Jerk W. Bush had.
Right, no, Obabo is from Nigeria.
He does email scams.
And he has a birth certificate from Nigeria.
The paving in these towns makes me feel like I'm tripping.
Cobblestones.
I was going to say it looks trippy.
Yeah.
Because it looks.
It is.
That's why.
Sire, there is no more money.
We gotta get some money.
That dirty Purgish harker, that flacky wharton, Philip Duncan Burton, Perkaluma Burton, doesn't
wash the night away.
Beep, beep, beep.
Look at this thing.
He brilliant.
Even though I'm hearing this on YouTube right now, I can't believe I died.
El El roo dés.
Adios.
Adiós.
Good to see you again.
catalog store pages and help out financially as best you can. Now we know
what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty and we don't want any
subgeniuses to make their own situations worse. But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference even if it's only once a month from
enough of you. Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference. All we're saying is
that blowjobs could go the way of Steve jobs if you don't pay Dobbs. We also take
checks and money orders to Subgenius Foundation P.O. Box 181-417
Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118. Thanks for anything you can do to help
let there be slack.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community