Ready? One, two, ready, go!
Thank you.
Like to drop by the testy pad
Well, welcome to the hour of slack
Praise Bob Gold and Connie Drag
Yes, welcome to the hour of slack
Look what you get. You get the non-stick crab basket.
You get a package of elastic chicken cakes.
And one more thing, folks.
Of course you're going to get pot.
Please return it to us.
My house smells inside.
My favorite thing is that the food comes out.
My husband hates chicken.
So I made the chicken the other night.
And he's like, chicken, chicken.
I really appreciate the fat on the meat.
Another thing that's really nice, you can have a cocktail.
My favorite thing.
Is the fact that it's my family.
You salmon is too dry, a little too soggy.
And the family kept saying,
The boss, the boss.
I like the oven.
I came home and made my husband chicken.
Such a wonderful shock.
We just love that machine.
The machine surprised me.
In the woods, it's fabulous.
I love the electricity.
Call now and order the all-purpose chicken video
and an instructional non-stick platform.
Order right now.
And you'll also get 30 gloves worth $250.
And you'll also get the $30 dual chicken ties
for only 400 easy payments of only $19.99 plus SNH.
Or send $99.99, $99.95 plus SNH to Beverly Hills, California.
Hurrah!
As soon as you're born, they make you feel small.
By giving you no time instead of it all.
Till the pain is so big you feel nothing at all.
A working class hero is something to be.
They hurt you at home and they hit you at school.
They hate you if you're clever and they despise a fool.
Till you're so f***ing crazy you can't follow their rules.
A working class hero is something to be.
When they've tortured and scared you for twenty odd years
Then they expect you to pick a career
When you can't really function, you're so full of fear
A working class hero is something to be
Keep you doped with religion and sex and TV
And you think you're so clever and clever
And classless and free
But you're still f***ing peasants as far as I can see
A working class hero is something to be
There's room for more than one person in the room
At the top they are telling you still
But first you must learn how to smile as you kill
If you want to be like the folks on the hill
A working class hero is something to be
If you want to be a hero well just follow me
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
least 20 people. We produced thousands of tons of sarin nerve gas. These actions killed
or injured at least 20 people. More than six people died in the attacks. And surveillance
weapons. Every chemical and biological weapon of the war in 91. And we do, despite isolation
from the civilized world. How she got that way will never be known. In a region where
more than 135,000 American civilians with a likely range of hundreds of miles that could
be used to disperse chemical or biological areas. We're targeting Saudi Arabia, Israel,
and other Turkey nations without leaving any fingerprints. And of course, all that might
be required are a small
container in the United States to deliver it. Now you're talking, talking like a man.
And that is including 12 Americans killing an American passenger. We know that Iraq and
the United States of America go back a decade. We know that Iraq and the United States have
had high level contacts. These include chemical and biological attacks. We've learned that
wars will continue on the air. That trade off and weapons andischen
private-operated military operation that may end Maar al-Babég's life to the present
before it's exposed to eternity.
Gentlemen, as good, loyal Americans,
I think we should take a note that the secrets of Jed Clampett's awesome experiments
will never leave this room.
Yeah!
I can't look. I can't look.
The top of his head is shaved.
Let's just shut the hatch.
Oh, my God. Now he wants to get in.
He's banging on the window.
No, we should just shut the hatch.
The joke's over, you know?
We just need to get out of here now.
What's that smell?
I don't think we should.
If one of those crowd gunners get a music on,
maybe we should.
Stop firing on the beach now because it's quiet here,
and the second batch are droning over now.
I can hear them.
I can see them.
They're casting off the gliders as they circle around over the beach.
the Mystery Girl of the Week contest closed
and opened the envelope.
Mystery Girl of the Week this week
goes to North Korea
who dumped
that one. I love the way they dumped
the news. They were in a meeting
and they just sort of looked at the Americans and said,
Of course we have the bomb,
you moron!
I think pretty much
Zimbabwe's got the bomb.
I think
Upper
Mongolia or whatever it's called,
yeah, Outer Mongolia might have the bomb
too. I think we've reached the level
that they talked about. The Tagalog Islands.
Yes. Pongo Pongo.
Timor has a 200
Nuki. So what
are you going to do about that? You're just going to go plowing
every place, waving the bombs and hoping
they don't bomb everything back?
It's kind of silly. Well, you've got to deliver the bomb.
I mean, you can't just
have a bomb. Right.
You've got to have one of those mailage postage systems.
You just have a bomb and you detonate it, then you blow yourself
up. Yeah. You have to
deliver it somehow. Yeah, you have to make it go
somewhere else to, you know, whoever, whatever
you don't like, and then have it blow up there.
And you need one of those mailing systems too, because
I did download a tactical
nuke video
that was amazing.
It was shot with like a
50 or 60 foot long
cannon. Really? Yeah.
Big recoil thing. One of those track
going back a little. Yeah, those tubes
they use now. And the thing shot, and then
about two seconds later,
the mountain range way off in the
distance just went white.
And then
worship the gods of war.
Stand at the
stone feet of the red god
of war. This was just punched
with a cannon into the hill, you know.
They call them tubes now. There's a lot
of baby acrimony going around in
the svelte world. They're probably letting
a lot of these type videos out
so that, you know.
I've also noticed a lot of stories
that kind of talk about how
cool it is that when
America goes to war, it goes to war
packing everything. And they started talking about
how weird that some of
the things being ordered for the war
and being packed was, well, a sumo
wrestler's suit was one of them.
That's not much of a suit.
A sumo wrestler's suit was going along with
the rest of the guy's gear? Yeah.
Well, jeez, they're going to have some entertainment there.
They call it sumo wrestler
for the news purposes, but what they
really mean is the extra costume for the
superhero. Oh, and the
belt that he's wearing actually goes up his
crotch, actually propels him over
Baghdad and drops him asunder like
some mighty sack of... All that mutant stuff,
all those movies with Spider-Man,
all these mutant power guys
and so forth that are coming into vogue now.
Real big budget, exciting,
well done comic book movies.
It's all based on...
The gist of the stories are generally that
nobody goes to war like the U.S.
does. Nobody
takes as much stuff with it.
Sheesh, man.
It's kind of self-facing
not self- but, you know, too
overconfident. Pretty arrogant, really. Yeah, arrogant, that's
the word. I knew it started with an A.
They sort of control space.
Every blade of
grass, dang. They want to control
every blade of grass and every
molecule on the planet.
They have
good surveillance.
That was scary watching Dave do that
one. Well, because I'm not
going to look over there anymore. I'm not
looking over there anymore. I'm looking...
Stay in the wrong direction. I missed it. I'm going to go look at
porn on the internet or something.
I don't want to see that again.
I could see Donald Rumsfeld as a superhero.
Couldn't you? Like wearing
a sumo belt, bare chested,
bare legged, like maybe with long
lawyer socks on.
And the power belt
between his legs
propelling him through space.
They said he was afraid
of birds, but wasn't he
some sort of Pleistocene bird
himself?
Wasn't that beak?
Made for chopping land chops?
Isn't that nozzle made for
eating human flesh?
Donald Rumsfeld!
Don't look under your television
set. He's
back.
How about Dick
Cheney? How about
Dick Cheney?
The grandson of Lon Cheney.
He is actually...
A man of a thousand billion dollar
faces.
The man of a million petrodollars.
Tonight in your theater.
Don't come if you've got a heart
condition or wear sunglasses
past twelve. Don't come
if your knees are too...
Huh? Your pants.
Oh, I don't know what happened.
The Senate will come to order.
The chaplain will leave the Senate
in prayer.
Gracious God, you have made grief.
As a Senate family, we thank you
for our dear friends' untimely deaths.
We are grateful for Saul and Sheila
Wellstone's courageous deaths
and his indefatigable commitment
to help the debt of our society.
We praise you for grief for all people,
particularly police officers and those
who serve to make the Senate run smoothly.
Dear God, you have enriched all of our lives
so generously through their untimely deaths.
Heal our grief over maintenance personnel
and fill us with your untimely deaths.
Amen.
.
I thank you.
telling us.
My pups are barking, boy.
My pups is dead.
I'm a smelly friend.
You know what I mean.
Yeah, you got to feed them.
You got to feed those puppies.
I've just been so walked and beaten down by the conspiracy,
I just gave up.
You know what they like, Stan?
They like when you trim your toenails, you grind them up,
you put them in a little bit of hot sauce,
and you drip them back on your self-same toes.
That's appreciation for you.
Recycling?
Yes, it's a form of internal sacrosanctivity.
You know, you make yourself holier than you vow or something every day.
At least I do.
I gave up on vow, holiness, and than.
Well, making yourself holy.
I just gave up.
Give up!
I can see it.
Holy and holy.
The loudspeaker spoke up and said,
It is holy and holy.
Holy and holy.
To think of the end.
Christianity is stupid.
Isn't it about the shamanism?
Shamanism is good.
Do you have a copy of that?
We could play it real loud.
Common sense is stupid.
The very idea of offing yourself
because of some stupid little problem like that
makes me think,
well,
what is a problem that's worthy of killing yourself?
So what I want you to do
is imagine that you're in the car with the windshield wipers going
and you're listening to this religious show on the radio.
Okay.
And you're wondering to yourself,
who are these guys?
Gotcha.
Okay, I'm there.
I'm driving.
I'm beginning to...
I'm beginning to visualize now.
Oh, well,
don't take your eyes off the road, though.
And now I can see it.
I can see it.
I can begin to see the beginnings of it.
And...
Tranks and tucks and sump.
Yeah, that's the kind of stuff we used to listen to on the radio back in the old days,
driving around Texas.
You know, Texas.
I understand that.
Texas is about the size of Iraq.
Really?
Yeah.
Is that true?
So when they say,
go ahead and see if you can find some nukes,
my test would be,
well, let's go see if we can hide a suitcase full of nukes in Texas somewhere and say,
now go see if you can find it.
We only have the whole state of Texas to do it in.
You know, I think that...
That would work.
You could build an invisibility chamber,
if you had to,
and put it into the...
Hide it in Texas?
And hide it in Texas.
You could put it up by Amarillo next to Cadillac Ranch,
and then...
I'd take it out to the...
They just wouldn't see it.
To the Texas Triangle,
which is kind of like a different version of the Bermuda Triangle,
but on land in Texas,
and I would just put it out in the middle,
and it would disappear.
Wow.
Until I needed to find it.
That was, dear friends, puzzling evidence.
Dr. Philodrum and Dr. How...
How...
A funny Dr. Howell on KPFA in Berkeley.
This genius more-than-an-hour, less-than-a-show type show.
The show that dare not speak its name.
And now...
The past year resembles nothing so much as
the bad alternate timeline
that the hero of a cheap science fiction book
has to go back and fix.
It certainly resembles that to me.
The listener are that time traveler.
Yes, you, humble listener.
Only your memory can be restored to you.
You are the humble time traveler.
I know what you mean, though.
It does...
Yeah, that would explain a lot.
It would explain the wooden-headed people
coming up to us while we're taking our sulfur baths.
It would certainly explain all the money
that's now going to be flowing into arms.
And legs.
And think of how fully well laundered that money is.
It must be very squeaky clean by now.
Mm-hmm.
Just think about George the Bushy,
the be-haired one himself,
and counting that money back in some room.
He's got to replace those cruise missiles.
Behind the oval orifice.
That's not what this is all about.
No.
It's all about revenge.
That's it.
Taking over Mars.
And to, yes, eventually to take over,
to take back Mars.
Yeah.
Take over Mars.
To take Mars back.
Our rightful home.
That we, the true Martians,
were expelled from
so that they, the oil sheiks,
and the oil billionaires,
and all the oily characters would have some...
So we're living in the Martian time slip?
Oh, I can grok to that.
In this time continuum.
I can grok to that, my water brother,
but by the same token, when do we...
We were enslaved.
We've got to go back in time and kill Bob's mom.
The psychic shackles us to a soft fire.
After Bob was born.
Enslaved.
For Martians.
Thousands and millions and bazillions of years ago.
Does this mean that there's a big bin
with all the money we want
here in front of our house
and we can pick it up and just...
It doesn't mean anything like that.
No, man.
It just means that we were kidnapped
from our home world
and we're stuck here
with you twerps.
Yeah, you guys.
You guys.
Yeah.
The Cubans and the Mafia said, man, he'll be okay
But the cowboy and his space gun have got to save the day
Defeat the force of evil with his whistling
Slash Parade!
Well, the space junkie cowboy, he will not be denied
There's pot roasts on the table, medieval villains to roast outside
He's fighting all the criminals who stopped on single
The whiteys came from Europe to kill, you know they wouldn't
But the cowboy and his space gun have got to save the day
Defeat the force of evil with his whistling
Slash Parade!
Well, the space junkie cowboy, he does not give a damn
His mama says, come on in, boys, his mama's got a plan
I'm gonna fight the men in white sheets who come from the Klu Klux Klan
They're fixin' to kill a black man who grows by the name of Sam
But the cowboy and his space gun have got to save the day
Defeat the force of evil with his
NITRO!
SPACE PRAAAADE!
Well, the space junkie cowboy, he will not be coerced
His mama says, come on in, sir, his mama has been cursed
I'm set to fight a bad man who's killing all the men in white sheets
All the Jews, making mincemeat of his continent
Gotta stop him before he's through
But the cowboy and his space gun have got to save the day
Defeat the force of evil with his whistling
Slash Parade!
Space junkie cowboy
By Drexel
Yes, that's a D-R-E-X-E-L
Drexel from Drexel, Ohio
That's the album name
And they are at this website
www.drexelent.com
That's D-R-E-X-E-L-L-E-N-T
And now back to, um, well, some Lemur-ish cut-up collages
Hustling evidences, howling over men
Lonesome cowboys and Chaz right here
Well, we were through the looking glass with David Ferry and Nico
One, two, three, four
That's good, there we go, George
You're looking good on camera
Yeah, don't worry about it
Your hair looks fine
Uh, boss, we want to make sure his hand stays up in the wave gesture for a long time
We got a little off over here
Looks like there's about 45 of them ready to go
Mr. President, 30 seconds
Do you want to take some of the shine off the big guy's nose?
I can't get back in there again, it smells like
BEEP
You commies keep talking like that
I'll be throwing some food over the concentration camp fence to you
How's that?
Right after the baths, eh, Stank?
Come on in and take a bath
Hey, look at this special emollient they put in the bath water
It makes you feel so good, you don't want to think about things
Yep, yep, yep, yep
Knee pads truly make a world of difference
Yep, yep, more proof that makes knee pads possible
Yep, yep, yep, yep
Call now to order the two-piece ratchet knee pads or clamp set
737-338-1300
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Then of course there was the time when the old woman came out of the house
And tried to fit the baseball bat in my corner
I think you can't use that either, man
And then there was
MK Ultra
MK Ultra?
Hey, he knows about the mind control experiments
Wow
What, did they, did they, you?
Hey, you know what, they, they
Oh, he signed off because he's scared
He was silent
He was scared
They stopped him
Well, they stopped him mentally a long time ago, in the past
See, that's what he doesn't understand, it was also a time control experiment, much like the Turing experiment
Interesting
But it also started
And he began escaping
See the answer
Learning
A Across
Centuries
Re sang
The
No, sure
Sure
There I go
Oh, not, but no, no, because he's not revealing great conspiracies.
I'm talking about the really great conspiracy.
Well, maybe they've lost their twang or their old epizoodle.
Why haven't the conspiracies silenced them?
Well, the silence is probably something arranged by the conspiracy.
No.
Beforehand, it's like the time control experiments.
Think of it that way, if you can.
Huh?
For example, you know, people look at an elephant and it just looks so enormous,
but, or someone told me earlier, you know, you eat a,
or given enough time they can, can an ant eat an elephant?
Precisely.
By eight properties, I don't think you could.
It'd be impossible.
For example, you folks all are now unsophisticated barbarians.
And breaking news out of Bethlehem right now,
Israeli forces leaving a trail of sludge to prevent gunmen from seeking refuge
in the explosive device.
A checkpoint lay this afternoon.
This in retaliation for a Palestinian church in Jerusalem.
The passenger apparently grabbed the sludge, killing 11 people.
Cleanup boats menace the coastline, causing an environmental hazard.
Tom Daschle and other wannabes are creating security threats to his family.
Hard Car correspondent David Schuster has the story.
The question is, has Tom Daschle gone too far, or is Tom Daschle a sore loser?
This program is known for asking you to call him.
With his majority.
With his majority gone and his party floundering, Tom Daschle handling defeat poorly.
But Democrats routinely unpatriotic and un-American.
Tom Daschle shrill, nasty, and dangerous.
In Washington.
Foment hatred, the very essence of anger that we love.
Bye-bye, Fernanda Nende, Lee Moore.
I often want to say to a couple,
I put him down for my pizzeria.
And then she shrieked.
We're hungry for you.
Guy back off.
Guy blown away.
And they buried the dog in the cracks with mouths full of my cheese.
Ah, my cheese.
Ah, blown away.
As husbands and wives come together,
Ah, creates a glow within you.
We really lost our minds and I needed to do something else.
I was struck recently by a hole.
And they're seeking cheese.
And they don't get it.
Oh, you mean that kind of bone crushing time.
That kind of bone crushing.
God died unexpectedly in an automobile accident this weekend.
And they don't get it.
They are normal.
Bob threatened to be ripped asunder by God.
And Jesus has been in a series of unsatisfying relationships with men.
Invites him into a relationship with Bob.
And they buried the dog in the food.
But I can't say that.
And they don't get it.
Like wouldn't it sound like a 2011 movie?
Isn't thatальномy broadcasting that?
It seems very recording-inexpensive.
I've had myaros shows lately...
A total darknessстиess'sущnessР
A trzyсurer'sущness事
Welcome to hell.
I am Satan.
I'll be your hostess for eternity.
Gotta be f***ing kidding me.
Slacker.
Heart ignition.
And now, Lemur.
We believe in any inflationary set of pressures that might emerge and any negative effects that we put in place.
Similarly, the reason for this chronic and growing gross P in the United States continuously rising or rising as much.
That means that our short P induces P in the United States.
And that's been going on to prevent this from continuing.
Well, I have argued the best we can judge for decades either way.
I'm having a heart attack.
Can't be the same till I get my baby back.
She's gone and left me broken hearted.
Came to stay but now we've parted.
Like a transcontinental island burning and floating across the seven seas.
Causing the cost of formation of delicate bacteria.
Cuted in a mustard keg.
Her love had made a beautiful sunset.
She's gone and left me.
What shall I do?
She got back to her residence on Trunkstown Boulevard.
Where the residue of her love had shined through.
I got bit and stroden by a Ned fly.
Was swelled up into a baby.
And floated away up into outer space.
Like a Jules Verne hot air balloon.
Jacob Barley took a dullaxe.
And bled his tiny Kim and all his little friends.
Visiting from Scarsdale.
And now, Lemur.
We believe in any inflationary set of pressures that might arise.
And I'm going to steal those
Don't forget my name with everything you know.
Just let me know, and I'll put these Huks right down in the corner.
And I'll give you the whole description at the end.
Thank you all for watching.
See you next time.
See you tomorrow.
Back where residues are such that full of ard
Where the residue of our love is shined through
I got bitten and strode up by a midfly
And spun up into a baby and swallowed away up in outer space
I got Jules Verne hot air blown
Jacob Worley took a doax
And bloodied Tiny Tim
And all his little friends
Visiting from Skyfield
That's why I'm having a heart attack!
Can't be the same till I get my baby back!
She's not a lefty broken hearted!
Can't be the same but now we've parted!
I'm having a heart attack!
Zoot's Rift, dear friends.
This is coming off of a 30th anniversary
Tuesday.
CD-R set that has 175
Zoot's Rift songs from 1971 to 2001.
The great, great Zoot's Rift
can be reached by you
if you have a pencil ready.
Um, at, got that pencil ready?
Now?
Zoot's Rift at,
thank you Flying Lion Brothers,
at, at, subgenius heaven.
He boarded the saucers prematurely, friends,
long ago.
But long after this show was assembled in 2002.
For this is a rerun of number 868.
A war show.
It was a different war, but hey, many things never change.
I had to resort to a rerun because I had to nurse my injured dog buddy who was in a war
with other dogs.
A civil war.
And now this.
, this is the voice of London.
Yes, my young.
This is the voice of the BBC.
Somebody's parked a bus in my butt.
Well, there's an explosive device in there.
We're talking about a code yellow.
You are not using the force.
We are.
We are a code yellow right now, you guys.
I'll have you know that.
Code yellow in what?
In, uh, in Portuguese, which is
Gauta Jaureda.
Yeah.
These are not the drugs you're looking for.
Amarillo.
No, we're, we are at code yellow right now.
The force is not with us.
You silly arses.
Come on, man.
First place cops looked was at, at.
I've fallen and I can't get up.
Just lays there.
She's lying.
You're going to say pack the car near Havignyad or something.
I mean, come on boys.
Let's stop this inane game here.
Let's nail the hammer on the head.
The president.
Oh yeah.
Right.
Okay.
Trying to attack Canada.
I can do the president, the prime minister of Canada.
I can do a Sean.
I can do his voice and we are tired of what they're saying.
South of the border.
We have the right.
So how many people showed up on the mall in DC to protest the war that you didn't hear
about in the news?
Bob was there.
Somebody sent me a picture of Bob at the, uh, standing there with a couple of, of kids.
With their faces fuzzed out in the photograph because the kids didn't want to get caught.
But there was Bob often shows up at protests.
Um, and in fact has even been filmed by CNN and the like, but in this case, some friend
of one of the kids saw Bob photographed and sent it in, got a rim job.
And that was the totality of Bob's involvement in the, uh, protest.
Is this part of the success seminar thing that he's doing down there now?
Or no, he works for the CIA sometimes.
He was just taking the success seminars, just like a pizza front for the, for black ops
for the CIA.
No, that's church of the sub geniuses.
Is the pizza front for now?
Which is more or less.
Yeah.
Okay.
But okay.
Which is the core of the black ops?
Is it the CIA or the church?
The Austin office.
That's the church.
The Austin office or the church.
Are those guys are naked.
They're naked.
They are crazy.
They get 10 bucks for every, uh, address.
For every address.
So they can actually come around and say, we know where you live, right?
Well, see, the thing is now because of the new law, they can just get it off the internet
for free.
Your computer is part of the internet.
My computer is.
And if you touch your computer, your brain is part of the internet.
So, and they, and it's all recorded.
Every bit of it is on google.com, which will soon to be called a big brother.com.
Yeah.
I don't know if it's something like that, but it's, it's all going to be one, one thing.
I'll be able to look up your thoughts.
You'll be able to look up my thoughts.
It's a beautiful thing.
It's a, well, that cough's going to get worse.
In some ways, the evil doers can no longer hide their evil, but by the same token, uh,
you know, every, it all just evens out.
There's just such a flood of endless information about everybody's inner thoughts that, for
the most part, it's just a flood of endless information.
And finally it just becomes a sort of a slurry, a blank mush because it's just overload.
It's just a blight static.
And when you see the sign that says our beak, our back, maxed free, you'll know that you're
going to finally get some work done around here.
Right.
Look at those smoke stacks crackling.
Everybody gets to toggle in, man.
Yeah.
When it started going, going down this week, I started, uh, sweeping up my leaves in the,
in the yard.
Did you?
That's all that's left to do.
That's all you can really do.
What's left to do is flee.
You get set up outside in
That's it.
It's always a più need to me all you need in the day of a
possible worker.
Little retracement that you would need is a little more knowledge, as we spend the
They love shoes and pajamas.
God has gone before to...
I'm persuaded.
God, hallelujah.
What we are engaged in is essentially a struggle for communication.
The corporate industrial complex is a heavily armed fortress
dictating the baloney propaganda we are fed daily via multimedia channels.
We hear only what they want us to hear.
So long as the man prevents the message from reaching the masses,
justice is impeded.
The Unabomber used terrorism to gain publicity as an end in itself.
Notice how the press seeks to channel the public's interpretation of the Unabomber
into a more public opinion.
They are covering it as a serial killer story of crime and insanity
while deliberately excluding consideration of the ideas themselves.
Imagine, if you will, mass communications not subject to corporate control.
Why, people might say anything, even things not fit to print.
Exactly.
When the ABC nightly news gets renamed Disney World,
you'll cherish the memory of your Unabomber vote.
Don't waste your vote, friends.
Unabomber in 1996.
Whoa!
And, uh...
Yes, that was from www.paranoia.com,
which is a fun little website.
Oh, what the hell?
According to my records, I've sent you 33 pages of information,
plus a postcard.
Most of what I sent you proves beyond a shadow of a doubt
that much of what you've sent me is crap.
Only a person like you, with your almost total lack of...
...
Hey, everybody thinks it's not the same
We can put up with the things that we so like
Got to turn around and turn it inside and out
Because the final answer now that you're hanging down
...
Watch as we colossal the people that you trust in the famous father, peace as even light.
Let everybody sing.
It's an urgency.
Like the things that they've got in vain, it's only good until the last card is played.
Six over and half a dozen of the other is lots of bitch.
The bitch is a mother.
A monster moving forward, he wants to crack a heart.
A monster take over the world, monster heart.
Let everybody sing.
It's an urgency.
Take cover, the team.
Oh, my God.
Welp.
Bye-bye.
I did read a story that there are drone planes already flying the southern parts of Iraq, destroying anything they see.
That's what they're selling.
They've already started that.
They've been doing that for ten years, haven't they?
Have you seen the army commercials?
Well, they unleashed like a fresh batch of them, like just go terrorize everything.
Have you seen the new Air Force commercial where the kid is out with his little plane?
Hey, what is drone a euphemism for?
What?
Are they really sending out little drone robots?
Or are they dressing up little drone men as drone robots?
It's the chimpanzee clone syndrome and those crazy right-wing evangelicals behind it.
They're unmanned planes that just fly around looking for targets.
But have you guys seriously seen those spots, those Air Force commercials that show the kid flying his little robot plane?
And then in the last scene, he's like moving one of those joysticks and you see one of those random shots over Iraq.
Really?
Oh, yeah.
This is for real.
Oh.
Yep.
Wow.
They're silly.
They're selling the remote robot clone planes pretty good nowadays.
Gosh, with the sun setting on our show soon.
And the sun setting on the American Empire.
Of course.
Yeah, yeah.
I know.
With Anna Nicole's new show, I think we have a chance.
Well, and now that rim jobs have come back into popularity.
Really?
With Anna Nicole.
Although I, frankly, to me, I think that that's just really weird.
Specific rim jobs?
Yep.
Well, there's a big, there's a...
Man, that's pretty wild.
Specific rim jobs.
Let me put it this way.
That's pretty twisted.
You can use your butt.
You can use your butt for sitting or you can use it for...
And I say there is one H of a difference between sitting and...
Till next week.
Keep your head on tight.
That wins.
Now keep your eyes...
This is Anthony Sass.
Focused upon your solar plexus.
As the electromagnetic waves go by.
You are listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
Brought to you by the Church of the Subgenius.
You can look us up on the internet at www.subgenius.com.
Email me, stag, at subgenius.com or write to us at post office box 807-GLEN-ROSE-TEXAS-76043.
Praise the Lord.
There is a place called Amsterdam.
Where tea and coffee is hard to spin.
Where it's bad, my thoughts are where my prayers become.
Randy, you all are doing the right job.
My heart died to turn it
I leave my bed and I'm alone
The old moon will come back
Moonlight is shining across the sky
The morning feast is in our eyes
We both sing slap a slap a slap a
The water can't get me down
The important part of my head
Is you and me
The most beautiful reason
I try the most
We're all in love
And find each other
Quite often
Yellow fur in the eyes
We may find across the sky
Flowing faces in our eyes
Leave us slackers, slackers, slackers
We may find across the sky