Diet, fat, food and eating weight, eating TV, food, plate, eat, weight, fat, program, programs, lose, lose, weight, weight, weight, weight, my plate, plate, plate, plate, food, weight, TV, weight, weight, weight, pounds, pounds, pounds, pounds, pounds, pounds, pounds, technique, subconscious eating, weight, no control.
And welcome, dear friends, to the Hour of Slack.
Praise Bob!
For the next hour, sit quietly and we will control all that you see and hear.
Turn on the machine.
This is Radio Yerevan.
Wake up, puppet boy!
We are conscious of our responsibility and obligation to provide programs
which will be enjoyable, entertaining, and tasteful.
There is absolutely no other possibility.
Copyright 1986 by the Subgenius Foundation and the participants.
You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to...
The Subgenius Hour of Slack!
Gosh!
The practice of hallucinatory drugs was big back in then,
and they were here to help.
We're hearing these messages that the Beatles were placing backwards.
For those who believe in Bob, no explanation is necessary.
For those who do not believe in Bob, no explanation is possible.
It makes you feel like you're hearing the same tune over and over and over.
It's like the sound of the letter blue.
Never end.
Ever.
I dreamed he took his little monkey hand and began rubbing my...
My clintaurus very furiously.
He was saying things to me I couldn't understand.
And I started yelling back at him, and I poked him with that broom over there.
And the next thing you know, there was...
It's the witches!
It's the witches and the masturbation monkeys!
And Dave!
Ah!
Oh, good.
Now it sounds more like a commercial.
Well, we're glad to be back, aren't we?
Because that was just a five-minute short stop away.
It was like kind of a rocket away.
It was a thing that just didn't really, really happen.
I'm wondering if the caller out there from Birmingham, Allobingus, could maybe call us back.
You're talking about the last time you were for services in Iraq.
You were a member of the 100 IDs over there.
I guess there's a lot of idds and super egos somewhere in Baghdad.
But anyway, at least we'll take it straight from the horse's eye.
Somebody's got to make the decisions!
Somebody's got to keep the trains and camels running on time!
Someone must be.
Be the decision.
Are you yes or are you no?
Somebody's got to keep privates like you in their pants!
Somebody.
Private!
More!
More production!
More efficient machines!
More bullets!
More bombers!
More soldiers!
More war!
More!
Better!
Faster!
More!
Super!
Ultra!
More!
Production!
More labor!
More!
Comfort for slaves!
Check to check, I struggle.
Just to reach the next day.
More! Taxes! More plunder!
More! Arbitrary law!
More! Police to suppress!
More! Rules of law!
Lingering salary!
Something more!
More money!
Intığını!
Cyber justice!
Morenique!
More money!
slaves
Check to check
I struggle
Just to reach
the next day
Though my veins
are empty
The high hand
beats me more
More labor
more output
More comfort
for slaves
More increased
production
More
comfort for slaves
That's it.
A Yesterfriend's
man from the
CD called
Machine.
And you can learn
more on man
at www.beerforman.com
Man is one man
with one bass guitar
and one drum.
There is no band.
There is only
man.
Friends, we saw
man at the
Detroit Devival.
He's from Detroit.
And I
I hope that he gets
really rich and famous.
He acts like he
really doesn't want to.
And he's great.
We'll be hearing a lot
more man on this show.
But that song was called
More.
For a real change of
pace now, here's another
song called More.
One more more.
Which this CD came in
the mail the same day
as Man's CD.
But this one is from
Reverend Jimmy Ryan,
dear friends,
who from his new
album or band
or both,
Truth Squad.
Jimmy Ryan is the
guitar virtuoso
subgenius,
you might say.
In fact, his last album,
Legacy,
with the Flying Ryan Brothers,
was in the Grammy Awards
for Best Instrumental
Rock Band or something
like that.
So, More from
Jimmy Ryan.
More.
More for me, not you.
More than I can do.
More than this life I live.
More.
More than you can feel.
Hey man,
it's just a dream.
It's just the way it is.
I know it's not your fault.
Five things you don't need.
Money you don't have.
To impress people you don't know.
More.
More than I can stand.
More is my demand.
More.
And make no mistake.
More than I can take.
Hey man,
I know it's not your fault.
And it's like I said before.
More.
It's just the way it is, you know.
You're an original.
You're so unique.
More.
Just like everybody else.
More for me, it's true.
More.
So much more than you.
I just can't refuse.
More.
More than I can use.
So much more than you.
More.
Yeah.
Oh.
The way thisfere is harder.
True ugTruth unpleasant.
Oh, my God, why do you call yourself man,
when we get a reuse all the time?
And your life is different.
guitar solo
solo
The one with the most wise ways
Oh, oh, so I can win
Oh, everlasting sin
Oh, I just don't know why
Oh, till the day I die
Oh
Ah!
What bothers me is that they're marketing a video game now
called Prince of Persia, The Sands of Time,
where one of the features they're advertising is time control.
Really?
Wow.
That sounds like a libel story.
I'm disturbing about it.
It took a conspiracy long enough to rip it off, didn't it?
Yeah, well, if your character dies, you can wind time back.
Cool.
And you are the character, of course.
So we're learning how to control time in our own existence
just by focusing on a video game.
In the old days, it's very realistic.
They put away our real time control,
and they're selling us fake time control in a damn video game.
Wait a minute.
Okay, so you can somehow wind time back by doing things or something like that?
Is that it?
I think there's like some button or control key.
Got to find a secret room or something like that.
It's a control key, and then you go, no, and you're back where you started.
You know, in the old days, that used to be called start over.
Play again.
It used to be called play again in the old days.
Well, that's what it's going to be now.
In the new world, that's what it's going to be.
People are going to be asking to replay their lives and so forth.
Play again.
They'll be able to do it because of the implants.
Yeah.
When you get to the end, is there a play again button?
Well, you got to make sure you have a record apparatus implanted in the back of your skull.
And once you do, at the moment of your leaving of this body,
you get a number of previews.
And also, when you get previews from the next things coming up,
and trailers from what you already did, called this life.
Unfortunately, many people forget to punch the erase tab.
Well, some of them.
They put an erase tab on their brain and they go ahead and blank it all out.
And then overdub it.
There's the next life.
Right.
And overdubs right over it.
You've got two lives going on at the same time.
Well, that's why institutions are filled up with these people in chairs,
you know, wrapped to the chair and duct tape.
Well, I think that's what I want to do as far as being a criminal is concerned,
is I want to overdub my past existence,
and I would like the police state to come in and overdub me for my crimes.
That makes sense, doesn't it?
I just want better background music.
According to Bob,
the problem with time control is that to travel, like, for instance, into the past,
you have to, it's like a slingshot.
You have to go way into the future, stretch it real hard,
until you're way out in the future, then let go,
and it'll shoot you, it'll slingshot you.
Well, see, way, way, it's not a quantity that we can quantify.
There's another way to do that.
Way, way, what's way, way?
Wait, there's another way to do that.
The Silver Surfer proved that.
To go so fast and far forward that you break through the wall of inertia
and just pop back to the future.
To the beginning of time, or wherever you want to dump off.
Well, after you break through the wall of inertia,
you're just in the wall of momentum yourself.
I mean, I hate to sound so realistic, but, you know.
I don't know.
Once inertia flops by, you become part of Mr. Momentum,
who's a much harder guy to stop.
He's like one of those weasels.
You can't get a grip on it.
You can't wrap your teeth around it.
You can't smoke it.
You can't wear it to bed.
What do I know?
You can't buy a little glass of wine or give it a little sleeping pill.
But it'll sure knock you upside the head.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
You know, it's more than smoke.
Knock your head.
Smoke and banana.
One cannot see or touch the wind, and yet the wind has great power.
The wind may caress you while you know it not exists.
I mean, you know what I'm saying.
Just drop my drawers and let it run right at me right now.
We're not interfacing with the elements.
That's another illusion.
The servants ain't got nothing to do with it.
As long as it's in color, that's all I ask.
Well, it's colored.
It has many different colors, but it's not in color.
We didn't even see in 3D when I was a kid.
It was all flat.
Everything was flat?
Yeah, but as long as it's in color, man, that's virtual enough for me.
Kids don't know that.
They don't remember that.
They think, well, you know, before color TV, there was black and white TV.
But before black and white TV, there was only a two-dimensional world, a flatland world.
Your grandparents grew up in flatland world.
You had to get a three-dimensional being to write A on a piece of paper.
It was only since color TV was invented that the world...
And draw a line.
Yeah, it was only since color TV was invented.
That the world became three-dimensional.
In fact...
Only when we started breeding the people with the two eyes that you could even tell the difference.
That was a good idea.
Two instead of one.
And, you know, like, just think of like Goliath and some of these guys that had the one poked out.
Just think if you're in a battle, you could have...
You can't take that crap for granted.
They think it's all...
Oh, yeah, we've always had two eyes.
We've been gifted with two eyes.
That Bob or some other character didn't bestow them on us.
Of course he did.
Or else how would they have come into existence?
You know?
I remember when you were billed for color.
I remember when you were billed for having an extra eyeball.
Remember that?
What happened to the Cyclopses?
The Cyclopses went the way of Mother Westwind.
They just passed into the flying, into the air and never returned.
People think that's like a myth.
They don't know that there really was Cyclopses.
The Betamax.
The Macintosh.
Yep.
The American Empire.
Yes.
The Revolution.
Uncle Sam.
All those other extinct creatures.
The Flat Cyclops Revolution.
Freedom.
3D freedom.
Other dying things.
Liberty in 4D.
So to speak.
Oh, screw that.
Let's just come up with some formulaic pop idols and sell them as rebellion.
I tried, man.
What, the little bobbleheads?
I'm lucky if I can get, you know, five or ten CDs sold at a D-Bible.
I tried, man.
The Jesus Christ bobbleheads.
The Reverend Ivan Stang bobbleheads.
These are lovely gifts for anybody or anything.
Pop icon.
Idol.
Well.
No.
I guess we should.
Use the pink bob that Dr. Legume designed for Mojo.
Then he'd be as rich as Mojo.
You still.
You gotta, like, wait.
Leave that.
I think.
I think Jackson should be martyred and sanctified and consecrated in the blood of the lamb.
Brittany and Christina.
That's what sells.
If we could just find the perfect teat.
The perfect one tit and nipple.
It lasts a week, though.
The perfect tit flavor only lasts one week and then it begins to sag and then there's
a new tit flavor.
No, but then you got your money and you can.
What you are laundering is the munchkin.
Or the little people flavor of the entire universe.
You're not really copulating with what's great.
With what's superb and what's essential and quintessential.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
You're putting down bubble gum bands, man.
You gotta get sexy in your grill.
I'm just saying.
No.
Are you a snob?
Are you putting down stupid drill?
No.
I'm not.
I'm not snotting.
There's no mucus in my thought.
This is what I am saying.
Pop smears.
Is that they should take at least one tithing's worth and give not only to Bob, but to Bob's
minions and his denizens as well.
Why give it to a fat tit?
Or skinny like Michael Jackson.
That waif, that strange waif.
Look at all the money he's accumulated so he could engage in perversions.
We engage in simple perversions.
We don't need that much money, but we need some.
Dave.
His skin doesn't have any color either.
I know, man.
That's some sick ass shit right there.
His songs are just a little more hummable than yours.
I don't know about that.
Look at how he hums with that weird triangle nostril area.
Except for beat me to a pulpit.
But that's very you could I wake up with that coming in.
Yeah, that's a happy little ditty.
But we got decent recordings of the band the other night.
That's incredible.
Even your even even your band.
How strange.
Yeah.
Yeah, it was weird.
I cannot offer any solace to you people whatsoever.
I've been having blistering hot, lovely dreams.
I dreamed that I fell asleep in front of watching the subgenius quality channel network the other
night.
And I was hearing things like this.
Oh, we have a wonderful set of figurines here when we got the hundred and we got the new
military figurines, the 103rd ID disfiguring.
They're so beautiful.
And we've also got one looks like Jessica Lynch completely bare chested with an AK-47
in one hand and a box of condoms and a Bible in the other.
And also for the commemorative season, it's the 40th anniversary.
Let's not forget, we got the JFK bobbleheads that swing.
Oh, those are the bobbleheads.
Oh, the head goes back to the far right back into the far right.
And also these wonderful little squanto pumpkin headed children.
And we'd like to.
Oh, I'm watching my TV.
I'm a suspend my disbelief.
When I'm listening to the radio.
And I don't mind them lying.
Cause lying is what they'll do.
And I don't mind them trying to get in my head, too.
But when they come around and bring the electrodes to my town, slap them in my brain and then
they slap my body down, the fans are driving up and then the mind can blow them down.
And everybody's singing.
Everybody's singing.
And become unusual
Ooh
Governor on the mansion
And the cop on the beat
Ooh
I'ma suspend my disbelief
Watching my radio
Listening to my TV
I'ma suspend my disbelief
Ooh
And I don't mind them dying
Cause dying is what they'll do
I don't mind them dying
I have them in my house
I don't want them dying on you
When they come around
With their mind control devices
Ready to plug them in
And do all the things they like
And they put my head in
And they pull the hose out
And they jump around
Until I can't see anymore
Ooh
I'ma suspend my disbelief
I must suspend my disbelief
I must crush all my former beliefs
Lonesome Cowboy Dave
And now...
Nicholas wasn't on anything, I was certain of that.
And if I do get to sleep, Nicholas said shakily, I have dreadful nightmares.
He told me one of them.
In the dream, he was shut in a tiny cage under the Colosseum in ancient Rome.
In the sky overhead, huge winged lizards were searching for him.
All at once the flying lizards detected his presence under the Colosseum.
They swept down and in an instant were tearing open the door of his cage.
Trapped with death at hand, all Nicholas could do was hiss at the lizards.
Evidently he was a small mammal of some kind.
Once more the impression had begun to come over me by slow degrees that I was in Rome,
not in Orange County, California.
I sensed the empire without seeing it.
I sensed a vast iron prison in which human slaves toiled.
I saw as if superimposed on the black metal walls of this huge prison certain rapidly scurrying creatures in grey robes,
enemies of the empire and its tyranny.
A remnant opposed to it.
And I knew from a deep internal clock down within my own self that the true time was AD 70.
That the savior had come and gone but would soon return.
The grey robed hurrying remnant with a feeling of joy,
awaited and prepared for his return.
I was in deadly danger from the spies of Rome.
The Roman agents would kill me in an instant.
It was empire policy.
It was an ancient fight I was in, not a new one.
It had been fought without cease for two thousand years.
Names had changed, faces had changed, and the adversaries remained a permanent constant.
The slave empire against those who struggled for justice and truth,
not freedom exactly,
in the modern sense,
but for virtues obscured today,
buried under the bulk of an empire that embraced both the United States and the Soviet Union as twin,
equal manifestations.
The US and the USSR, I understood,
were the two portions of the empire as divided up by the emperor Diocletian,
for purely administrative purposes.
At heart it was a single entity with a single value system,
and its value system was the concept of the supremacy of the state.
The individual counted in its scales as nothing,
and individuals who turned against the state,
and generated their own values,
were the enemy.
We were the enemy.
We who wore the grey robes and waited with eager anticipation for our king to return.
Would we be able to survive against the Romans,
by stealth, since we had no worldly power until he returned?
Or would he return to find us gone,
or worse, assimilated into the customs of the empire,
our own memory of what we actually were lost forever,
or perhaps,
lost until, by his return, he could restore such memories,
reawaken in sleeping men a forgotten knowledge of who they were?
Rome was here now.
It had invaded the landscape, rising up from within it,
manifesting itself from its centuries-long place of inner concealment.
Rather than me being back in the ancient world,
Rome had revealed itself as the underlying reality of our present-day world.
Hidden still from the eyes of other Americans,
it was nonetheless blatantly visible to me.
The empire had never died.
It had only receded,
out of sight.
A reading from Philip K. Dick's Radio Free Album of...
It's All Crap!
Radio DJs and new strip malls,
the record contract and the softcore bond,
The music, television, chemical on,
the critics' choice in over-counted drugs,
It's All Crap!
I've been sharing the current in song,
the CD prices and the oil wars,
It's All Crap!
The new age wisdom and the smarter bombs,
the Microsoft turd and the liquor laws,
Gimme some more, gimme some more, gimme gimme gimme more,
It's All Crap!
More crap!
Hippie jam bands and the new self-help,
The pop-up ad and the smoking laws,
It's All Crap!
The new sitcom reality show,
The cheese taco steak pizza chemical nacho,
It's All Crap!
Milwaukee taco with the dumb fight song,
The gated clone housing with the phone,
The old facade,
It's All Crap!
Drunk dead hymns in the dress-up show,
The embedded breast of the bro-tux hoe,
Gimme some more, gimme some more, gimme gimme gimme more,
It's All Crap!
Man!
Again, dear friends, from the CD called Machine.
More on man at beerforman.com.
Incidentally, this music in the background is from Automatic Robot Fish,
which is the side project of Reverend Angry Larry of the amino acids.
Yes, Automatic Robot Fish.
And now...
Oh boy.
It's just getting worse every day.
We complain, but we never do anything.
Like, what could we possibly do?
Could we go to the mirror?
Complain louder!
Well, you know, more specifically...
We need to be louder.
The sufferers are fanning us.
Buy more amps, man.
A little tiny man with a huge beat.
The music will save society.
The dance music is different.
Buy bigger speakers and buy more Marshall amps, man.
We're gonna need them.
We're gonna have to buy them.
We're gonna have to series every amp in America together.
Could you imagine?
And we'll have Humvees to go around and do it.
Yeah.
And we'll have every amp in America...
Say that for a little bit, Camel Gear.
We'll be series linked together, and every guitar player in America will hit that one
big power chord.
Bill and Ted were right!
And then...
So on a little time ok?
And now I want sentence passed.
I want the death penalty.
I want to be executed according to the laws of the state.
I know my rights.
What right do you have to that information?
Mind control.
What?
Lady, you are out of your mind.
You are conspiring to commit mind control.
Mind control.
What?
Lady, you are out of your mind.
You are conspiring to commit mind control.
They put microchips in their heads, and then it works sort of like remote control.
They've been at it since World War II.
Oh.
Drugs.
Psychosurgery.
Mental medicine.
Manipulation.
Break them down.
Build them up.
They've been at it since World War II.
Oh.
Drugs.
Psychosurgery.
Mental manipulation.
Break them down.
Build them up.
You don't know paranoia, my friend.
You just don't know.
Three ways to die.
I choose the firing squad.
Can you do that?
Uh, Reverend Norell Preff did that.
And more about Reverend Norell Preff's work, and some of his work, at www.heavyconfetti.com.
And, uh...
Hey, where's my saw?
We're sawing now, baby.
We're chopping wood.
I remember the way the furniture used to be in here.
Ah.
Stang once spoke of the church of the subgenius.
What?
That old thing? Oh, that old thing?
He once spoke of it.
That tired, old, worn-out, old, dandruff-covered, grimy, mangy old church.
Tired as an old moley bag.
Tired old whore of a thing, an old mattress-back whore of a religion.
An old grandmotherly prostitute with moles all over her gizzardly gizzard,
and her craw is all covered with crusted things, too.
That church would spread for anybody.
And it has.
50 cents, line up.
It spread across the land and now across the world.
Oh, a lot of them went for it.
They like to dirty themselves, you know.
Yes.
It turns them on.
It gave them those blue pine foreheads, those wolfish faces.
Oh, everyone liked to lick the wisdom teat of the church of the subgenius,
but no one had the correct eyesight to see what was going on.
Yeah, but we've moved.
We've moved up to a better religion now.
The wisdom teat itself.
The religion of the conical Christ.
It just goes straight to the teat.
The wisdom, oh, oh, yeah.
There is no God.
There is no absolute.
There is no Bob for certainly, and there is no Connie.
There is only.
Well, there might be a Bob and Connie, but they're just going to rip you off.
Well, they're just like image crackpots in the background.
They're what you call the scenery for the scene.
You know, they're prop people.
Oh, they make you love being ripped off.
They teach you.
They literally do.
They aren't lying when they say they teach you to enjoy.
Enjoy it.
You're being ripped off every day.
You can learn to enjoy it.
That's true.
But you never do learn to enjoy it.
It feels like your forehead's being raped every second of your life.
No, no, I enjoyed it.
When I was a cult member, I enjoyed the hell out of being ripped off by Bob.
I gave him everything.
I knew I was being ripped off.
I know you did.
And I felt free, man.
I felt totally free.
But you know.
That's sick.
I just, to me, it was like I'll do anything to taste lobster and steak again.
And blood.
So I sold out.
Sold out.
And got this contract here and these handcuffs.
And you'll be coming with me, Dave.
Not at the same time, I hope.
I mean, we're grown up gentlemen.
We're not into that.
Like, you know.
Like, remember when you were little?
You'd all go off in the woods and maybe rape or burn one of the other children.
Speak for yourself, Dave.
We just did that with animals when I was a kid in Texas.
We didn't rape or burn other kids.
Just little animals.
They were ostracized children that you chose to call animals.
Yeah.
They weren't animals.
They might as well be.
Pobuckers are animals.
They had beaks and feathers and liverly wings.
And they had like little.
Pobuckers are as low as animals.
It's like if you eat a Pobucker face sandwich, that's no different from a bologna sandwich.
A Pobucker face?
Bob's eyes.
Well, what do they commonly use in the South for, you know, dressing for a face sandwich?
To Bob's taste buds, you're, to quote Jane, your grandma's face would taste as good as
a bologna sandwich.
It'd be all the same to him.
But have you guys actually tasted grandma's bologna face?
I mean, is, or is this just another one of those, you know, hollow pronouncements?
I honestly don't know.
I heard the old guys talking about it like it was a real thing.
You know how those guys are.
They'll try to blow your mind.
Yeah.
The barbershop subgeniuses.
They like this.
Bob's friends.
Those are G. Gordon, Gordon and Philo and those guys.
They're, you never know.
Very philosophically.
Like him.
You don't, well, yeah, but you don't know how much.
Kind of hardcore.
Talk.
I can't handle that kind of hardcore talk.
Okay.
Just cut that hardcore talk out now.
Okay, boys.
Well, we can't.
But the miracles are real.
I've seen miracles.
Miracles are hardcore.
I've seen the healings.
I've seen people vomit.
I've seen people vomit up their sickness.
I've seen people lose the sickness that causes them to walk so that finally they could crawl
out of that temple of Bob.
They could crawl again, my friends.
I've seen, I've seen people at subgenius church revivals.
Who have actually fallen down the floor and found their face in a baloney sandwich and
cannot turn their face to the baloney sandwich or their face to their bodies proper.
I've seen subgeniuses fall down and vomit out vile things that were the accruedment of
other lives, which did not actually exist.
They're picking up caca from other realms and spitting it out.
That's how they get up.
That's how they get high.
They fall down.
Yeah.
It's free.
That's what you call a sickening.
They snap fingers.
They laugh.
They bang.
They hit their head against hammers and things.
It's, it's, it's a thing that Bob teaches.
And most of them had very, very unfortunate childhoods and look at them now having a fortunate
adulthood.
They are the happiest people you'll ever hope to see because you know something?
They don't know something, you know, they do.
And they have that look on their face, that self-satisfied smirk because they've lost
those brain cells that torment you.
No.
Well, maybe not you, Dave.
But you.
I mean, yeah.
The generic you.
Rule number one.
The listener who still has a brain cell.
Never commit adultery with an adult tree.
Rule number true.
Uh, number, and rule number two.
Never commit vile acts of vileness with a subgenius humoral or any other person assigned
with papers.
I, I'm sorry.
I, I.
It's very complicated.
It is.
It gets more complicated.
It's also very interesting.
I can't read the fine print.
Well, it's, it's a legal nightmare.
It's become, the whole thing has become.
Just a legal nightmare.
A trademark and copyright nightmare.
A living death of, of plagiarism.
And shame.
Remorse.
Legal briefs and files.
Slacklessness is what it is.
Slacklessness.
It's because of the hypocrite.
The hypocrite.
Oh, he, oh, he talks, he talks big, big on Bob.
But can he act?
His teeth whistle.
He talks slack.
But does he, does he understand what slack is?
He would not know slack.
When a man.
He called up his urethra in the form of an Amazonian snake.
That's correct.
That is correct.
He wouldn't know it if Slack bit him from the inside and chewed its way up his kidneys.
He wouldn't know.
He wouldn't understand the thing in front of him if it stood behind him.
It's a form of fealty.
It's a form of loyalty.
It's a form of inverse freedom.
We need it.
He wouldn't know Slack if he was buried up to his neck in the middle of it with the ants chewing his eyeballs out.
Nope.
He wouldn't understand a single...
He wouldn't recognize the Slack he had at that time.
If he walked out of the window and the bug ran over his pajamas, it's not something easily understood.
No, they don't get it.
They can't get it because they're not born with the Yeti blood.
They don't have the blood coursing through their veins.
The snowman of the Himalaya.
The so-called abominable snowman.
To some, I'm sure he's abominable.
But to us, he's a beautiful thing.
Daintily, daintily, we step on each plantain.
And each door opens and Bob's face is there.
And yet, he eludes us.
He eludes us.
He drifts.
The elusive J.R. Bob dogs.
The more we smile, the more he grits his teeth and clenches that pipe down fast.
The harder you clutch for him, the slipperier...
The faster you run after him, the faster he gets away from you.
Oh, yeah, Bob's looking for clean socks, too, just like every indigent American in this society.
He saves you.
That is what...
If he lets you get close to him, where's your slack gonna go?
Straight up his pipe.
He's gonna smoke.
He's gonna huff it.
His dorsal pipe, my friend.
He's taking you on in a form, friends.
He's suppressing his own self so that he may meld with you.
He does not just put you on.
He takes you on.
He becomes one with you.
He wears you, and then he takes you off.
He wears you like an old dirty Brooks Brothers suit from Gentleman's Wear.
He wipes with you, and then he flushes you away to heaven.
To eternal slack, friend.
When you've been that which Bob used to wipe with, friend, then you know slack from inside.
Yes.
It's slick.
It's more than lies and cabbage, friend.
Slack can be slick.
100% truth in a brown paper bag.
And you want to soak that slack up with a fine, porous tissue.
No.
You want something gentle to get that slack.
You'll need a shovel.
Every drop, every little vestige of it, you will need a gentle yet porous tissue of slack absorbent tissue.
I think you need one of these star trusses.
I don't know what he said, but it's true.
It's so true.
I said you need a star-scrushing, star-scrushing screwdriver.
Dang to get in.
You need a double-ply slack-absorbent wipe, and that's what you are to J.R. Bob Dogg.
And you need that chainsaw and a bag of eggs.
When you feel that slack running up your leg and grabbing you and humping on your leg,
that's the real slack, baby.
That's the old dog you've been trying to...
That's loyalty.
Look how that thing loves you.
He humps your leg like a dog.
Slack comes to you just like that when you...
He's loyal like a dog, and he drinks out of the toilet like a dog.
When you have slack awareness, yes.
You shall.
And forevermore.
It's not a place that we take lightly.
You can drink from Bob's toilet, friend.
Yes.
He'll leave the lid up for you.
Yeah, Bob always leaves the lid up.
And the light on.
Well, maybe not the light on, but the lid up.
Yeah, watch out for them urinal cakes.
They can be toxic.
They can cause instant paralysis.
You can eat at Bob's, friends.
I think what I'm going to do is, uh, in my more normal and happiest, happiest basis,
I will put my head in this aperture here, the commode.
He will feed your need for...
Slap from behind.
I know all the rituals, damn you.
Let me get my head in here.
I think what I will do is just fly away from here.
You don't know!
I can see his face now.
I can see him in my mind's nostril.
My third nostril is opening.
Wow.
It's like a saint's day for all werewolves.
I can see palm trees and beautiful babes dancing and little...
Clarinets falling from the sky.
I see him too.
Look, it's wooden human in the front...
I'm getting confused again.
Somebody better...
He can sure play guitar, though, can't he?
Yeah.
Wooden human could really play.
Six on each feet, man.
Look at those fingers fly.
Yeah, Bob's fingers had wings on them.
Bob was part of one of the old dinosaur crew itself.
Used to fly like a pterodactyl.
And picked those strings like a chicken.
He'd bite them with his beak.
He was crazy, man!
He was...
He was crazy.
He was crazy, man.
I love that guy.
He gave his...
He gave something for me, man.
He gave for my snack.
He gave his wife for my snack.
He gave those...
Don't be cynical, Sean.
Sit down.
You're gonna believe.
You will never believe.
I can't keep from frying sometimes.
The supernatural.
This is a proof.
Signal, the famous Goldfarber gasoline.
Invite you to sit back and enjoy another strange story.
The supernatural.
This is a proof.
Signal, the famous Goldfarber gasoline.
Invite you to sit back and enjoy another strange story.
And more Nor-El-Pref.
And now, more Nor-El-Pref.
Sit down and say, okay, number two, then stick with me.
And as a result, you feel rejected.
You might feel uncomfortable.
We tend to hallucinate when we say, I feel bored.
I feel foolish.
I feel insecure.
How do you respond to that?
The guilt's going to come back.
It'll get you sooner or later.
It's back there.
It's deep.
It's dark.
It'll get you.
Good.
How stupid.
You can feel really bad.
You can feel disappointed.
You can feel frustrated.
You can feel angry.
You can feel hurt.
You can feel sad.
And remember, nothing in life has any meaning.
I feel like I was meant for something more than this.
I want to do something with my life.
I want to be somebody.
Craft and destroy freedom-loving people everywhere.
I feel like I was meant for something more than this.
I want to do something.
I want to do something with my life.
I want to be somebody.
Craft and destroy freedom-loving people everywhere.
We prefer to keep our powder dry.
What are your opinions on post-war planning and the peace show?
You know, a dictatorship would be a heck of a lot easier, there's no question about it.
No, I've always...
You know, a dictatorship would be...
What are your opinions on post-war planning and the peace show?
No, I've always...
You know, a dictatorship would be a heck of a lot easier, there's no question about it.
We prefer to keep our powder dry.
Boy, listen to those lovely guns.
There's nothing lovely about them, Trigger.
What?
As long as people anywhere can hear that sound,
we haven't taught anybody a thing.
Slogans, guns.
They don't settle anything.
They only lead to suicide.
Not only for kamikazes, but for the world.
That's the reason they let's teach the Tasha and all the rest of them.
Yep.
And maybe even ourselves.
What about what them French did to those poor Huron Indians?
I wouldn't blame the French for doing nothing after what happened.
The Huron Indians?
Yeah.
The Huron Indians.
The Huron Indians and Quebecers.
Yeah, what about them sub-Furrier Indians from Minnesota?
They got them all sick and they all died and the Iroquois wiped them out.
Chaz still feels guilty about this crap that happened hundreds of years ago involving people he's never met.
Stank doesn't know.
People he's not even related to, even descended from.
Stank.
Has nothing at all to do with it.
But he's still just feeling this terrible, terrible feelings over this.
We were lied to.
No, not evil feelings.
I want to see him rise up and, you know, wipe.
Hey, I think Whitey's done a pretty bad job.
In Ohio history, Stank, you don't know.
I think Whitey is really due for a, you know.
Whitey has been around not very long.
Whitey's going down.
I have firm confidence that Whitey's going down by his own hand.
He's going to be making beans by the old railroad tracks.
Who are you trying to kiss right now?
Whitey and Reddy.
I think you're in love with Frenchies summer, fall, winter, spring.
I think there's a beautiful Indian maiden who has her eye on you and you are trying to butter up to her.
No, I agree.
Brother's going down with him because he's, you know, right there.
If you guys would study Ohio.
Remember Ohio history, Chaz, how they made it sound like the white guys came here and nobody was here?
And now all this stuff is coming out.
There were thousands.
There were big towns everywhere.
They're just blown away.
Modern society.
Modern society's going down.
Just like, hey, man, you stole some of my pie.
I'll kill all 12 of you, you know.
And all this stuff is coming out now because everybody has Stang's attitude.
Oh, that happened so long ago.
Modern society's going down.
I haven't seen the Burger Kings closing.
I've seen them multiplying.
I've seen the multi-play cinema spread from town to town.
They aren't drying up and going away.
The Starbucks and bought.
Monsterbusters aren't disappearing.
They're growing.
They copulate with one another.
What happens when a Starbucks copulates with a McDonald's?
What kind of weird monster would you have then?
What happens when one of those little bugs, like the factory-made AIDS virus, gets out of control and wipes everybody?
The other day I got a two-headed hamburger.
Well, you can always pray and hope, Chaz, but in the meantime, you're just praying and hoping.
I actually know.
If you're not going to Fort Detrick, breaking down the doors with machine guns and saying,
Smash that file! I want the world like all dead now!
Then you're just part of the problem and not part of the solution.
If you look at the statistics, Africa really is getting wiped out, and it's moving through everything now.
It's just not in the news.
It's not moving through.
So that you don't think about it, and you don't think, oh, it'll never come here.
You've got to check your internet.
If you don't know what's going on, you know.
You're going to be living on batteries and old soap or something.
Dave, we're already living on batteries and old soap.
There's lots of people who never, ever get those diseases you're talking about.
They'll be just fine because they use people like us as doormats and soldiers.
It'll be the tribal people.
Doormats and soldiers.
That sounds like the name of a band.
Down in the rainforest.
Well, I think you should put your ghost shirt on and go down to that protest and charge them cops.
Put on your ghost shirt.
Save the world.
You will be invisible to the white man's bullets.
They will not be able to see you or shoot you.
Take your whale to the rainforest and set him free, baby.
Carve it up and set it free.
I don't need to do any of that.
Yeah, that's right.
Wait, what am I being a mediator?
Why do you have this need to tell me what to do?
Why don't you guys just start duking it right out here in the studio?
I'm just being sarcastic.
I'm not seriously telling anybody what to do.
I'm just being a downer.
I'm just being a sarcastic old.
Yeah.
I'm a man of tankerous.
Oh, devil's advocate bummer guy.
I see a balloon.
I've got this peen.
I've got to pop it.
No, actually, the anthropological computer models.
I'm the old beaten cushion man.
The anthropological computer models that are modeling humanity right now show a big, huge breakdown coming sometime between 2010 and 2020.
Well, of course, a computer's going to tell you that.
That's what you've seen Terminator and Matrix.
Okay, Terminator, Matrix.
That's telling you what's going on, baby.
No, it's just a big calculator.
That's all it is.
Calculating unrenewable and renewable resources and how fast they can do it.
The big computer succubus or incubus is going to come down and suck the bus.
Yeah, right.
Or it's going to impregnate us all with its, you know, thoughts, so to speak.
Hey, you need to go change its ink cartridge, Dave.
Right now?
Yes.
It's asking.
That beeping, that means you have to go change its ink cartridge.
The ink cartridge of the beast.
The beep sounds different, though.
The computer beast that runs the universe, planet Earth.
It needs its ink cartridge.
I think that's just the radio alarm clock for DJ A.
I think his forehead's waking up.
Oh, it's out of paper.
You need to go.
You just need to go put some new paper.
All right.
I can't believe anything.
I'm going to die.
Hey, Dave.
What does this really mean?
Hey, Dave, I'm collecting money for the rainforest.
That is so disgusting.
Give me some.
You're watching full.
Stop it.
No.
We're going to set the whales free in the rainforest.
Man.
God, what a great idea.
Give me money.
Free Charlie?
We're going to bring free?
We're going to bring mansion and the whales into the?
Charlie was innocent, man.
The pigs lied.
Man.
Charlie's innocence is a form of, it's a euphemism for the innocence of a mad murderer.
Of course, he is innocent in his ways, but he's not innocent of crime.
Hey, man, Charlie's just doing what Chaz wants to see done worldwide.
It's just end it all.
Hey, man, that's not us.
One pig at a time.
And you know, you've got to learn to act locally.
Wait, I don't want to see that.
I'm just.
I don't want to kiss a pig any time.
Hey, I don't want to see anything.
Say, go on, believe me, act locally.
We'll kiss your pigs.
That's what Charlie did.
Come on, man.
I don't want to see anything.
I'm just reporting the.
The snout bristles and everything.
Nobody needs that.
Guys, they're all local.
I think they have some kind of big generator like in that old Star Trek with Landru's blue
and red days when everybody go crazy on certain days with a generator.
Well, one thing we know.
I think they have that.
One thing we know from all the media we've seen.
When they.
The red glowing lights are evil and blue glowing lights are good.
See, that's right.
They co-opted the future.
And now we're part of the past.
They got it from the movies.
It's a.
But you'll notice when the glue.
When everything glows blue, that's going to be good.
But when it's glowing red, it's going to be really bad.
Look out for the lights.
Relax.
Drink the iced tea.
Have a donut.
Look at the beautiful blue lights glowing from the eyes of the singing children.
I see one little red light in the distance.
Children.
Don't be afraid.
Don't be alarmed.
Now it's going to be another half an hour before.
They ritually ring the neck of the baby meerkat.
I know one of the children is like.
He's a very happy and motivated child.
He keeps up with the rest of the children.
And again, this background music is by the Reverend Angry Larry of the amino acids.
In this case, under the name Automatic Robot Fish.
Friends, you're listening to subgenius radio ministry.
Hour of slack.
And you can find more about the church of the subgenius at www.subgenius.com.
Or you can write to us at post office box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
That's me.
Or for information about the church from P.O.
Box 204206 Austin, Texas.
877-720-Praise Bob.
Hamburgers.
rafted by nossa hostudeenda Agostina Thanks generalди607.
Evolution control committee, dear friends.
we came, we heard.
and Castiancorbinrando
We do appreciate what you old wobblies did for us, Dave.
Now you're being nailed up on those crosses, telephone poles.
I am so sorry that I broke your heart.
That's the last three nails we've got.
I love you.
You're going to have to nail that last one in yourself.
I'm hurting out.
What will you do when the government troops are coming for you
and the only thing you have to fight with is your nail gun from Walmart?
I'm not slurpy.
Sorry.
Nail guns and slurpees. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Thank you.
Okay.
We're going to have to go.
Bye.