Behold.
Go back to your compartments and resume the schedule.
The ship is off.
Wait!
No, I have something to say.
Listen.
Listen to what I have to say.
This is what I have to say.
The subgenius power of swat.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to smash the earth.
The cool green earth.
Fools!
Can't you understand?
Minnesota.
The land of the sky blue water.
Minnesota became the butter state.
Minnesota in the 20th century.
This is Minnesota.
I have never been to Minnesota.
Minnesota got lots of lakes.
Minnesota got plenty of lakes.
Look at them lakes in Minnesota.
Oh!
Lots of lakes in Minnesota.
I have never been
to Minnesota.
Oh!
i never been
to Minnesota.
n specific
I've never been to Minnesota.
I have never
I have never been to Minnesota
Minnesota
Got lots of lakes
Lots of lakes
Minnesota
Has got lots of lakes
has got lots of lakes
Look at them lakes
look at those lakes
In Minnesota
in Minnesota
Plenty of lakes
plenty of lakes
In Minnesota
Minnesota
Minnesota became
the Buffett meanwhile
The Rudy Schwartz Project did it.
For this episode, friends, number 1,842,
we're going to go back to the day before X day.
They got the sound system working better,
and the panelists on this live hour of Slack are Dr. Hal, Reverend Pease,
Reverend Fid Chooley, and yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang.
Fid first, and then Pease, actually.
A highlight, in my opinion, is Dr. Hal and I doing a duet on the song Cool Water,
but that comes later, as did Pease,
although those two things don't always happen in that order.
This microphone is on the left.
This one here is in the middle.
And this one's on the right.
Check one, check one.
Check two, check two, check two.
And check three.
Reclaimed coffee.
Dr. Fox, how are we looking on mix?
This is Test Chatter.
I'm merely talking into the microphone,
not to convey any actual information,
but merely to put audio into the mic
so that Dr. Fox can twist those robot nipples enough
so that we can get on.
R-E-Think Radio.
You're doing a really good show, Fid.
Thank you, Pease.
Do I need to...
Tell them about the bit.
Oh, the...
Yeah.
So Pease had this idea that was really funny.
He said we should do a bit.
And I was like, yeah, that is a good idea, Pease.
So...
I'm gonna chew the fat with Fid Chooley later.
Do we have the fat?
I've almost caught that chicken three times,
so just give me a couple more chances
and I'll have some fat.
I remember bits, but only bits.
Bits and pieces.
But yeah, I remember back in the day,
we used to do bits, but we...
Either we lost them or the exes took them one by one.
Along with things like my spinal fluid.
My hair.
My memory.
My morals.
All kinds of things.
All gone.
I'll get them back tomorrow.
You're still doing better than me.
Yeah, I need to...
I got some catching up to do.
I'll admit, since there's no girls here anyway,
I lost a couple of dicks over the years.
I still got most of them.
Oh, that's okay.
They grow back.
The main one works.
Well, at least for one thing.
Yes, peeing.
Everybody pees.
Okay?
Anybody with a functioning urethra
is allowed to join for free
for only $35.
Well, hey.
Shout out to Dobbs Chord
and shout out to freethinkradio.com.
We are piping hot.
Streaming.
Streaming piping hot.
Super.
Ooh.
Getting the stage set up
for the hour of slack
coming very soon
to an ear hole
near your face.
And I am going to piss my pants
live later on too.
So stay tuned for that.
Did you guys get all the fat samples
for the chewing event?
Well, that was Pease's job.
And, uh...
If I've learned anything
from this X-States,
don't put Pease in charge.
Right, okay.
Of anything.
Yep.
I got my plane ticket home
for Stang Ivan.
Actually, I should double check that.
Or get to the airport
at real early.
I don't know if they fixed
the return ticket or not.
Well, to be fair,
me and Fox put Pease
in charge of your ticket,
so I don't know
who the real dummy is.
Is it Pease
or is it us for putting
Pease in charge of your ticket?
Why not both?
That's what I say.
I'm sure they'll have Pease drive you.
He never screws up.
Yeah, you won't have to
how the world's gonna end.
It really better
fucking end this time.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Nobody made any plans
at all for after.
All the credit cards
are maxed out.
Why did I even bother
to pay for these new glasses?
Yeah, I've often asked
myself, why did I spend
all day paying bills
just before X Day?
What kind of idiot am I?
Well, Hal,
we're still managing
to get ourselves up
those three steps
to this stage.
Yes, well, this chair
will definitely cripple me
before long.
As I was saying,
it's like every X Day,
the X's take a little bit
or a little piece.
Yes, like old man death
who takes little pieces of you
while you're lying in your box
till you're all dead.
All gone.
Oh, Bob.
Won't you spare me
over for another year?
Don't you take my brain.
Oh, Bob.
He's Bob.
Won't you leave me sane?
Bob don't ever change.
He's Bob.
Wish I knew your name.
Always will be Bob.
I always thought that song
should have the percussion
of Chain Gang.
Yeah, it should have
that kind of thing.
Hitting rocks with picks.
Yeah.
We need the loop of that.
Bob had a woman named Connie.
She was a righteous friend.
She had a lot of friends
named Johnny.
When Bobby hit the trail.
He's Bob.
They told me to praise him
and they told me to pay him.
But I just want to be him.
Always will be Bob.
Hi, Bob.
Oh, Bob.
Bob was the god of the forest
who claimed his jungle bride.
His pet was a brontosaurus
that Bobby used to ride.
He's Bob.
Bob don't ever change.
Always will be Bob.
Or there's a dark and a shadow side of Bob.
That every subgenius knows is true.
I played that song on our slide.
Oh, yeah?
In the last two weeks, yeah.
Also, Papa Joe's fiery speech,
Five Minutes to Midnight.
I need to tell him that.
He's got...
Recorded in Germany.
In full dress.
I'm sure they loved that over there.
Yeah, it was nervy, actually.
Five Minutes to Midnight!
It was a wonderful rant.
Perfectly written.
Just to do it,
the Hamburg revival.
He's got friends up in the sky.
He's immortal and can fly.
Otherwise, he's just a guy like me and you.
There's a dead armadillo on the road.
And Bob's bumper,
he hit it fair and square.
There's a twinkle in his eye.
Not a tear as he drives by.
Cause mean old Bob Dobbs,
he just don't care.
So keep him in mind.
Keep on the grinning side.
Always on the grinning side.
Keep on the grinning side of Bob.
He may look friendly like your dad,
but you don't want to make him mad.
So keep on the grinning side of Bob.
Philo wrote that verse.
Yeah.
Well, you know,
those folks that want to do the Dr. Hal Art book,
maybe they should put the lyrics to your hymns
in there.
There's at least five of them.
Maybe.
Nobody ever sings those things.
But...
Oh, but we've seen two remixes of He's Bob.
That's true.
Somebody did make those.
I had them on my computer.
That is several computers ago.
I don't have them on my contemporary computer.
I actually have all the audio that I've ever digitized
all on one gigantic 18 gigabyte hard drive now.
So I can pull up just about anything.
If it's got a decent file name.
Like for instance,
if I type in Hal,
it'll pull up everything that every file name that has your name on it.
Hmm.
Which would probably be hundreds.
Why is it so buzzy?
I can call up anything that has an X.
Of course,
that includes sex and a lot of other things.
Secret codes.
All that xylophone footage you have.
X dash,
X dash D.
Just to...
X D.
You never know how the file was named exactly for X day.
Sometimes you save time and leave out the dash.
A dash of this, a dash of that serves seven billion.
There you go.
Just a spoonful of punctuation helps the medicine go down.
More Dobstown Weekly whiff reader headlines.
Ivan Stang's secret recipe for imitation skyline chili.
Well, that's pretty funny.
Oh, boy.
A brown paper bag.
Yeah.
With a big M on it for Mason's Masonic.
How beautiful.
Thank you.
Tainted frop stash endangers dozens, thrills even more.
Yes, we'll deal with that in a moment.
Paparazzi perplexed by Walter Kosmack's new fleet of anti-glamour drones.
I like the alliteration there.
Reverend P's greatest boner, Las Vegas actually shameful.
PMI.
Sexy swamp apes seeking sultry meetups.
Details inside.
You know, we had those back in Ohio.
The Loveland frogmen were a cryptid species that you had to worry about there.
Now we have the sexy swamp apes.
Oh, that's nothing like the Land O' Lakes frogmen.
Oh, no.
They, uh, they like the frog way.
We're being told to talk into the microphones.
Stage douche Argus Fox is instructing the...
performers to remember to articulate clearly into the microphones.
Reverend Stang, are you familiar with this, uh, publication, Mind Shaft?
Uh, no, I've heard, I've heard about it.
I haven't actually seen it.
It's what all the cartoonists are doing these days, and I'm in the next issue, the one that's coming out.
This one just came out.
Who's doing this?
Well, uh...
Contributors are Cromm, Christopher Mueller, Mary Flaner, Sophie Cromm.
Oh.
Uh, nepotism.
Sophie's got...
Dennis Kitchen, is he still alive?
He's still alive, and his drawings and cartoons look just like they always did.
Oh.
But, uh, we lost Jay Lynch and Skip Williamson.
Yeah, oh, I didn't know Skip Williamson died.
Skip Williamson was so upset that Jay Lynch died that he died.
Oh.
Yeah.
Oh, like, like two old dogs that just can't live apart.
2015.
Mm-hmm.
It was sudden.
The fellow in the bright nightgown.
Sudden is not so bad.
I've heard.
I mean, I'm...
No, actually, I haven't heard.
I'm just guessing.
Don't read Daniel.
Well, it says right here in the, uh, Dobstown Weekly whiff reader that Dr. Howell is...announced the new Universal Poet Laureate.
Yeah.
Well, it's gotta be true.
It's in print.
That news came out weeks ago.
That old...
Yeah, that's old, old news.
And if you haven't got your copy of the Dobstown Weekly whiff reader, you can acquire yours from the Info Sex station over at that pretty turquoise building.
Anything to eat but one donut.
And get your free art supplies from the stage.
That's right.
Your bag of free art supplies is waiting for you.
It's cold.
It's alone.
It's crying.
It says...
Don't provide...
How come I don't have a mommy?
Or do this.
Well, you can be that bag of art supplies mommy right now.
Come to the stage, get your free bag of art supplies, and get a doodling.
It says tangy barbecue sauce, therefore it must be tangy barbecue sauce.
Well, friends, it's...
Ah, yes.
Welcome to our strike number 1,800 and...
Exactly.
That, uh, innumerate designation.
It's all the same stuff produced from the same spigot.
Once again, live at X Day, in a new location, Land O' Lakes, Florida, the Land O' Id nudist
resort.
I thought it was the Land of Fid.
Well, I guess you could change all the signs.
Change them to what?
Land of Fid.
Says Dr. Fid Shuley, who's joined us on this panel.
Well, he made such a sacrifice with his, um, the attack on his legs and feet the other
day.
He was so bloodied, he should have been in Fox's Book of Martyrs.
That's right.
You've injured yourself horribly and didn't even know how you did it, right?
Uh, that's true.
That is true.
Um...
It looked like a catamount or a wildcat had leapt on your bare legs and scratched and
marred them.
I actually, uh...
But you can't remember it.
I actually died yesterday.
Um...
I die every night.
It looked pretty bad.
But I was having such a good time, I figured I'd hang around a little bit.
Not to let a little thing like death keep me from a good party.
Maybe you actually did pass and sunk into the swamp, which revised you as it did Lon
Chaney in The Mummy's Curse.
Lon Chaney, Jr., that is.
That's right.
Yeah, the Mummy, the Universal Mummy, was last seen in Florida.
He went to the South, yes.
Not only that, he was hanging out with a woman named Aunt Bertha, played by Virginia Christine,
who was Mrs. Olsen in all the coffee commercials.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Oh, man, wait until Sternow hears that.
He's really hot for Mrs. Olsen.
She had a movie career in a bunch of movies where just when you're not expecting to see
the lady from the coffee commercials, she pops in.
Like in Billy the King.
Yeah.
Like in The Kid Meets Dracula, for example.
Was that the coffee commercials where she was horrified that her husband asked for a
second cup?
The husband is going to kill the wife or something because her coffee is so bad.
My husband hates my coffee.
Well, it's mountain grown in the face of...
He never asked for a second cup of my coffee.
And then there's a scene of the clock ticking in suspense as the hubby drinks the coffee
and the wife is a bundle of nerves as she waits.
And then the husband finally moos at her.
Honey, that's good coffee.
And she relaxes out of her kitchen.
No beating tonight.
Yes.
You won't have to go to the special room tonight, baby.
I had that experience last night.
That is to Mrs. Olsen and Folgers.
Dr. Fox usually never asked for a second helping of my frop, but last night somebody gave him
some frop and he wanted some more and I was taken by it.
I didn't know what to do with myself.
I was going to kill myself again.
Well, practice makes perfect.
Dr. Fox never asked for a second helping of my frop.
At X Day they give you hamburgers for breakfast.
Hey, you know what goes good with X Day breakfast?
Bloody Mary's.
There's some free Bloody Mary service happening right now.
General announcement, if you want to get your thang twisted into a spang.
But the sun ain't even high over the yardarm yet, matey.
When we gonna start boozing it up with Bloody Mary's?
I don't know, maybe we are.
It's an exceptional set of circumstances.
An unusual holiday.
All the limitations kicked away.
Well, I'm gonna go acquire one for myself.
Because it's X Day.
This is it.
It better happen this year.
Who's with me? Come on.
Or else what, pilgrim?
Or else then I have to go home.
And then go back to work.
Well, whether your home is a cardboard box on the street or a palace on board the X's saucers, you will be home.
I can't wait for tomorrow because Princess Wee told me that my two older dogs are pining for me.
So the first thing I'm gonna do about 7.05 is beam my dogs up and have them rejoin me and Princess Wee.
Be careful they're not reassembled at gigantic size.
They already have.
They already have grown to gigantic size.
But the...
Oh, I'm thinking of the puppies.
Professor Deamer's Puppies Formula.
They don't miss me. Puppies don't miss me.
Just the old dogs.
In fact, last night I missed some of the show because I was on FaceTime trying to console the dog.
It didn't work.
The dog didn't recognize my voice over Wee's phone.
It's all right, puppy. Just come over here near the phone.
My Face... No, it's a FaceTime call.
So they can see me too, but...
But they can't smell you and so they know it's fake.
Yeah.
Now my old...
Oldest...
Previous dog, Dammit.
We brought him to Cleveland.
Really? That was the name of Chicken's dog.
Yeah, I know.
My dad named Dammit, Dammit, though.
And...
Constantly heard his name called.
It was hard. It was embarrassing in crowds, you know.
Dammit, come.
People look at you funny.
I started calling him Buddy.
There are children here...
Then he died and then I got a dog named Buddy.
Already named Buddy.
Anyway, Dammit would...
When I went off to the radio station,
sometimes Princess Wee would stay home.
My... I was recording it at home and my voice was on the big speakers.
When my voice came on live, the dog would snap to attention.
And he recognized it.
He could...
But that was on, you know, good speakers.
It was live radio, not satellite, you know, iPhone tinny little sound.
Poor Claudia.
Still...
Still waiting by the window,
staring at the driveway,
waiting for Daddy to come back.
I miss... I miss those dogs.
You know, at the end of the world,
the things that are most important to you come to the forefront.
And I think in my case, it's the damn dogs.
You know, I'm not worried about my human family.
I'm worried about my doggies.
They don't know what's going on.
They're just idiots.
They're so innocent.
Unlike any humans that I know.
Man's commencement.
They're just a bunch of mental species.
Did you see that movie Alpha?
No, I didn't.
But that's not the one where they had a computer-generated dog.
No, no, that's Call of the Wild.
Oh, yeah.
They used a real dog in Alpha that looked very wolf-like.
Yeah, Call of the Wild.
It would be a very realistic dog, except that it acts too perfect.
It poses in shots like a real dog would never do.
There's no nipple slips, no accidents, nothing.
And dogs are all about those.
That gives it the uncanny valley.
Well, one out of eight.
Bad, real bad.
Otherwise, it's a good, it's a fun movie.
I heard it was a good version of the story.
Yeah, but if only somebody who didn't have a real dog would be fooled.
Yes.
As realistic as it is.
I mean.
It sure got hair down pretty well.
Well, hell, they can fake anything now.
You don't even need millions of dollars to do it.
It's a special effect.
You can stick your face onto anybody using a damn phone.
Well, Lassie and Rin Tin Tin, let's give them credit, could really act.
I could stick your face on Rin Tin Tin and vice versa.
Please don't.
Rin Tin Tin has been sleeping with his ancestors for years.
Surgically, we can do that tomorrow.
A ghastly match up.
I got the peanut butter.
If you can hold Hal down, I can scrape it on the inside of the roof of his mouth with a popsicle stick.
Peanut butter not good for humans of advanced age.
The peanut itself, not a nut, but a legume that grows on tree.
Same with the cashew.
Almonds are alright.
Um, let's see.
Well, I brought all this dope up here, so we're going to smoke it while we meander as we do.
Smoke that dope.
If it's a tiny little pipe, there's, I mean, you have to keep smoking to get it out.
I'll be interested to see if gift memberships will save people tomorrow.
For instance, my kids never spent the 35 bucks.
They're grownups now.
Well, they have the document and the...
I gave them membership packs.
One Christmas I gave everybody in the family membership packs.
But there's only one.
Only my niece.
Has ever actually bought one.
And she's a regular listener to our slaps.
She would know who you are and everything.
But what happens if you didn't buy your membership pack yourself, if somebody just gave it to you, are you saved?
If you don't give a shit, if you really don't even believe in Bob like my kids.
As long as somebody...
Well, that's not black in their name.
No doubt the exes will listen to these records as well.
They will know how thorough they are.
Of course, there is that transfer of documentation, but a similar change happens in the germplasm at that time.
As long as somebody...
Latent subgenius...
Paid for it.
Because that's one of the more insidious uses of the membership packet is you can ordain somebody else against their will just by paying for a membership packet.
Just like the Mormons.
They can betray you after you're dead.
Yeah.
Yeah, you can save your dead ancestors.
Just like the Mormons do.
And like Coca-Cola, which brings their beloved ancestors back from the dead.
Or you can just take somebody that you know hates the Church of the Subgenius, send them your $35...
I hate the Church of the Subgenius.
I hate it.
Guess what?
Oh, you do?
Well, you're in the Book of Life now.
How do you like that?
How does that taste?
Does his name appear in the Book of Life?
Well, I can't find him here, Lord.
Maybe it's spelled...
differently.
Then with sorrow I say unto you, into the eternal fire, prepared for Satan and his fallen angel buddies.
You had a chance when I sent that boring preacher to your door and you laughed at him and turned him away and embraced this guy with the pipe.
Just better hope Reverend Pease wasn't the one who wrote your name in the Book of Life.
The recording angel does that.
You know, how come it's huge and thick like a dictionary when everyone...
Yeah.
...in the last judgment is automatically guilty and it's all a show trial.
Whose names are in that there Book of Life?
Mostly Neanderthals.
Mark Twain wrote about Captain Stormfield's visit to heaven.
He went wrong and has traveled through space and first of all ended up in alien heaven.
But he finally ended up in human heaven and he found the whole place was overwhelmed by what he called engines,
which were Neanderthals, primitives, cavemen, pre-Adamic men.
You know, they outnumber everybody else and so with their tom-tom beating and so on they make heaven resound.
I wonder if River World owes Mark Twain an explanation.
They have him in there, don't they?
Did you ever see the thing that's based on it?
I did.
I had an opportunity to watch it on the plane, but I didn't want to.
I would have had to watch it silent.
Which?
The River World show or River World movie based on Philip King.
I did see the River World movie.
Jose Flamen.
It sucked and on top of that they didn't show everybody naked.
Oh, that's terrible.
I especially wanted to see Alice Blesent's Liddell naked and having sex like in the story.
No, no.
It was a TV movie so it was lame.
Oh, well.
Made for TV, that says it all.
Say no more.
Yeah, very little relation to the book.
I mean, really.
There's a problem here about COVID and everything and putting our lips on this thing.
Do you have one of these?
I've got one.
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
Okay, great.
You know, I'm at work.
I don't frop at work.
Everybody's drinking on the job.
Really?
Well, you're shaming me.
But on the other hand.
Oh, actually, I used to back before 9-11, when you could open the radio station windows.
After 9-11, they locked everything up.
Total lockdown was as bad as COVID and no more fropping in the stations.
After COVID, they locked the station itself so no one could go in.
Right.
And then there was no stations.
But that worked out fine for me.
I was already locked out of work.
I didn't have any stations.
Doing it from home.
And I managed to get the stations to accept MP3 downloads so I didn't have to mail them
CDs anymore, which was expensive.
And most of them weren't paying anyway.
But it's free advertising.
The great thing about real radio as opposed to podcasts is somebody can hear it by accident,
just driving along in your car, putting it on scan.
And suddenly they'll hear this crazy stuff.
And that's really fun to think of.
And I've heard examples of that.
I've also heard it happening in reverse.
Thank you.
This one woman, she was actually the station manager at the Dallas station.
She was driving back from Austin.
And it was 9 o'clock Sunday.
And she thought, well, I'll listen to the hour of slack.
She turned on the radio.
But she wasn't anywhere near Dallas.
And she thought she was listening to my show for about half an hour before she realized
she had it tuned between a rock station and a preacher station.
A rock station in a hard place.
She was hearing rock music with idiot preachers and figured that was hour of slack.
So it's easy.
Yeah, I used to do the same thing with scrambled porn.
See, anybody can do the hour of slack.
You just got to pick what kind of stations to put the needle between so you hear both
of them back and forth.
Quick Watson, the needle.
Hey, bees.
Why don't you come up here and occupy this mic so I can procure for myself a-
You can go occupy.
Occupy X Day.
I'm going to go occupy a Bloody Mary.
Or be occupied.
That's funny.
Hey, do you scratch these things or do you peel them off in the front?
We could start a new subversive movement called anti-pie for anti-pink.
Anti-pie.
Well, they should know that we're anti-pink.
Wow, look.
Ice cold water.
Dr. Pease has been real careful about making sure people hydrate, especially when he sees
somebody stumbling along about to pass out.
Go follow along behind him.
Drink this.
Don't drink that.
Dr. Without a taste of water.
Cool water.
Water, water, water.
Keep a-movin' Dan, don't you listen to him, Dan.
He's a devil, not a man, and he spreads the burning sand with water.
Water, water, water.
Dan, don't you see there's a big green tree with the water running free, and there's water
running there for me and you.
you.
To
the shadows sway
and seem to say
tonight we'll pray
for water.
Cool
water.
And way up there
he'll hear our prayer
and show us
where there's
water.
Clear
cool
water.
Water.
Sons of the
Pioneers was the version I grew up with.
Yeah.
The hearing
aids are constantly shorting
out from sweat running into them.
So I put this umbrella made of
McDonald's napkin over my
left one. Speaking of McDonald's, there seems to be
an extra bacon
mix something here.
I feel foolish.
You can have that.
I'll have it alright.
Alright. Or you can save it for later.
There is no later.
I'll put some of this
I feel foolish because I saw you with the
napkin on your ear.
Time is
running out.
So it's a fabulous day here next day.
But there is no July 5th in
this building.
Yes, that's going to be a problem.
I can't believe
this. Look at my arm.
Insect. More water coming out of my arm.
There's a lot of meat in there, isn't there?
Yeah, it's going to happen.
That's why if you smoke frop like me,
you find your temperature was regulated.
Perhaps you've reached your
saturation level. I used to get
in Arizona when it was super hot.
I found if I smoked some pond ice.
Where did peas come from?
Suddenly peas are sitting next to me.
It's horrible. It's an X-Day
miracle.
The X-Day miracle for me was
the rain of prairie squid from the sky
yesterday.
God, that was so fun.
It was the torrential
rain and suddenly there were these
flopping, stinking
prairie squid.
Only they were
wet.
They actually weren't prairie squid.
Raymond Burr in his wheelchair. People were calling them walking
catfish. They were making their
way to the pool and we had to put
a stop to it. They were coming out
of the pond trying to get to the pool
because they wanted cool
clear water. They weren't
reckoning on the pouring.
Which I think would be bad for them.
In fact, I saved
one from poisoning. I saw you
with that net. I hope they got out of the house.
He resisted your attempts to save him
much like many of the subgeniuses.
Just like, well yeah.
I guess that was a pink walking catfish.
Inside. He didn't
want to be saved.
I don't need any more friends.
He really remembered that one, didn't he?
Yeah, he did. It was a wonderful
tale. Well, it's typical subgenius.
You know, it's like you don't want to go to some
party and meet new people.
Well, I think that's a thing.
We've all experienced that feeling
and probably all done the exact
same thing. You've got a friend that says,
hey, I know this guy. You're really going to
like him. He's so awesome. And you're like,
fuck, leave me alone. I've got all the friends
I need.
Well, what convinced me to go meet
the Drummond family was that my
sister-in-law said, well,
he's really into Captain Beefheart
and he collects comic books.
Of course, now that describes about half
the subgeniuses, but then
in 1976,
I didn't know anybody like
that. It's like, well, okay.
We go over to this
suburban house and there's
Philo Drummond and he
looks just as pink as
a newborn babe
with this corporate haircut
and a sportcaster mustache
and he's playing darts.
I said, no, he's a
jock. And he brings me over
and he says, here, throw some darts.
Let's throw some darts while those women
talk. And I go, I don't
know. I've never thrown darts.
I don't know anything about this. He goes, go ahead and try.
So I half-heartedly give it a try.
Bullseye! Right
dead center, my first try.
Total beginner's luck. Philo's
thinking, if you don't care, you'll hit
the target. That shark,
he's like a card shark. He's an expert
at darts and he convinced me that he's
a nervous amateur.
So we
both were suspicious from the
get-go. But then, he said,
hey, I found something cool the other day.
And he brought it out and it was like a chip track
or a John Birch Society
pamphlet. Something like that.
And I was like, wow.
He really, he's interested in the
same fucked up shit that I am.
And next thing we
knew, we were, he was
telling me about this
special person
that I had.
And I normally would have fled at that point
when he started telling me about Bob.
But he had such good frop.
That was the other thing.
That was the thing my sister-in-law
should have told me.
He's got real good frop.
I didn't even know what frop was then.
So it wouldn't have helped much.
But he gave me this stuff.
I guess I thought it was marijuana at the time.
So I tried it for the first time.
Well, that's all it takes.
One hit, you're done.
You're going to be high the rest of your life.
You don't ever need another hit.
Oddly enough, I see people just keep
coming back for more all day long
the rest of their lives.
Even though you don't get any higher generally.
You're kind of stuck
in one level of extremely
high all the time. Consistently.
Too high.
And the rest
as they say. But look at me. I'm fine.
Aside from my backbone
and my memory and my eyesight
and hearing.
I have a picture of health.
My lungs, allergies,
hospital visits.
Memory problems. You say you have memory problems?
You remember the money you owe me, right?
No, it's the money you owe me.
You see, that's the...
Yeah, there are some memories.
Some things are not lost in memory.
The exes have those
memories and we'll get them back tomorrow.
We'll get them back tomorrow.
Alright, that sounds fair.
I'll see you on the saucer, mister.
In the home. In the casino.
All debts will be paid.
Speaking of the saucer, you have a
especially exquisite
saucer plan for yourself with many
national monuments and
tchotchkes if I'm not mistaken.
Right, I've just got to beat legume to them.
Well, hasn't he got a head start?
Yeah, but
I guess the official chase
doesn't start until 7am.
Oh, okay. That's good. But he does have a head start.
Yeah. And he knows
exactly what I want the most. And he's a
devil. He's a devil.
In the end, he'll let me have him back
but he'll have to... I'll have to fight
him for him. They'll be on his ship at first.
Yeah, I know how he is.
You'll have to trade it for something.
Yeah, like my memory.
Sacred nose hairs, maybe
a strand of the sacred ponytail.
All of these will be
the currency of the future.
Relics left here on this
burning hulk of an earth.
I thought you'd forgotten
about the ponytail.
No, no. Circling back.
Circling back. He's jealous.
That's what makes it funny.
You circle back.
He used to be big.
I'm going to tell you something.
That is going to make the most fabulous keychain for me.
I mean, people are going to see
that. It's hanging out of my pocket.
You mean not on your belt?
You can have it. I'm going to
have a whole new body
tomorrow.
Now, I'm going to go for a robot body.
But I'm going to have an extra arm
for doing stuff when I'm doing stuff
with my regular arms.
I know what you mean.
You just need one right hand.
It only has to do one thing.
It's a pleasure saucer, by definition.
So you're going to need that extra arm.
Now, don't be foolish and just
get the arm. Order the hand
option.
Yeah, it needs a wrist. It needs a flexible wrist.
If you don't have the hand option,
it's kind of a waste of time.
Take the claw! Take the claw!
You get calluses.
Or you just get calluses.
After a while, everything
loses sensitivity.
I know how that is. Take my word for it.
He's right.
Some people
say they're just going to keep their regular
old body. Ragnar, among
others, strangely enough.
Yes. Well, have you
seen his body?
I've seen every bit of Ragnar's body.
What did he do to it?
He's a very large,
very pink
colored fellow.
He's a large sized
subgenius. His skin
looks like it has never seen the sun.
He'd come to X Day and
sunburn himself horribly in the
first hour.
Easy enough to do.
Invariably, he'd set up his tent
ineptly and it would
rain and soak everything, including
his brand new video cameras.
So forth.
Then he'd be sure that somebody else
had sabotaged it. Why did Bob
pick on me? I just wanted
to come here and have fun.
Well, Bob didn't, but some of his followers did.
Ragnar quit coming to X Day,
but I kind of miss him.
He was such a regular
and he was kind of a...
I don't know. He had
served one of the functions of peace
as a punching bag.
He was an acolyte. A classic
acolyte.
Like a vampire is familiar.
I was sitting there one X Day
and looked around and, oh no, Ragnar's here.
Oh no, here comes Ragnar.
He goes, Stang, I've got something for you.
He handed me $1,000 in cash.
Yeah, he had something for you.
That he had saved up from his
Pizza Hut delivery
job. And he gave me a whole
bunch of Pizza Hut plastic red
glasses, which turned out to be
my very favorite drinking glasses. These are great glasses.
I look for those things. I steal them
when I go to Pizza Hut. Those were more valuable to me than
$1,000. But at that point,
I changed my mind about him
instantly. I said, Ragnar,
it wouldn't be the same without you at X Day.
I really meant it.
I was thinking, well, maybe he'll bring another $1,000
next year. He ended up
running for governor of Kentucky.
And I think he got
23 votes.
That's a magical number, as you know.
His plan was to
solve the
war problems by
sending out robots
and
I bought dog mule soldiers
instead of human soldiers.
And I said, wouldn't that be kind of expensive?
How would the army pay for that?
And he said, with legalized
froth, of course.
It's like, oh, well, okay.
He's going to get all the votes.
And he got all 23.
He got the Discordian vote, I guess.
But 273 is common.
It comes up every 23 times.
273 is much more rare.
Now, 1303,
13013,
that's really
the most sacred number.
Thank you.
Well, but that's a different
type of number.
999 is a good one.
That was actually the number of the anti-Bob.
I think the most sacred number, though,
is 35.
measly dollars.
About $29.99.
We've got to raise it, man.
It's been $35 for 20 years
or something. I think we're going to suddenly
raise it. $35.50.
It should have been
$33,
but now we've gone past that.
But maybe that'll include postage,
unless it's overseas.
It costs $26 to send a membership pack
to England,
and $22 to send one
to Canada or Mexico.
Not that anyone's
ever ordered one from Mexico.
I think we had two members.
Well, you know, it may cost more
if they succeed in
describing the post office.
They put a little starburst on the cover.
It says, still only $0.35.
Oh, I remember still only $0.10.
Still only $0.12.
Still only $0.20.
When it hit still only $0.50
and it was half ads,
I quit buying comic books.
Also, I had a kid to support.
And read old comics.
The price of the comic books
outpaced the
normal allotment of ducats
and dollars that a young child might have.
So you'd start out
getting 10 or 12 books,
and then they'd raise the price
and you'd get down to $0.07 or $0.08.
And then, like you said, when it was $0.50,
well, Jesus, that's half my allowance
for this week.
No, I was 18 when it hit $0.50.
Well, now that those
children are adults,
they find that the same comic books
are still economically
out of their reach.
Having gained a bloated value.
Well, here's the funny thing, now.
All those $0.50 and dollar comics
from the
70s and 80s,
my wife inherited from a collector.
Jeff Rosenbaum,
who started Starwood,
was a crazy
comic book collector also.
He had Marvels and DCs
of
everything from the 70s and 80s,
and he kept them really nicely in these
plastic and these big
comic book boxes. He had a room
full of them. There's a room full of them in Cleveland.
I managed to grab
two boxes at random and take to Texas.
That's one reason my back is destroyed.
Those boxes were
extremely heavy, and it was the last day
before we left. It was like there was just
enough room left in the car to get
some comic books in. Have you looked in the
box yet? Oh, the box?
We managed to get the box into the house,
and I even read a whole bunch of the
Batman stuff. I hope they were good.
They were, but they're
still there, and
they were jointly
inherited by my wife and my neighbor
Joe, but Joe doesn't care about them.
I don't know how
we're ever going to get them back to Texas, though.
That's literally
tons and tons of
comics, none of which are worth very much.
Well, ship them at a low rate.
A low book rate or something.
Hey, look at this.
All right.
How many? I still haven't
scratched the one you gave me.
Three more dollars. I've cleared
40 bucks now. Well, I had
30 to start with, and I've gotten
another 10 bucks worth of these things.
Excellent.
I'm going to eat out tonight.
The luck plane is tilting in your direction,
Ivan Stang.
It doesn't happen every day.
It's $10 in payouts.
What about tripler lottery cards?
They're already rubbed.
That's how much one would have to pay.
You don't rub it again.
I'm about to rub
one of them
myself.
This is exciting.
That's an excellent scratching technique,
Dr. Howell. It seems efficient
and yet
adventurous.
Well, actually, whenever I have
an opportunity to scratch something
like this, which I find
irritating and unnecessary.
I actually use a little metal picture
of Bob that is
the perfect scratcher.
But I don't have that with me.
I hope it doesn't hurt
the luck involved. It's made at
Tucson Trade Engraving and
it's engraved on metal and it's
a reverse image of Bob.
I just put these things
I tuck them into my dog's ear
and then he scratches them with his hind leg
and let the dog do it.
Boy, those German Shepherd puppies
have turned out to be a bit of a terror
in that they
they're right at the age where they want to
see what
things taste like, especially if they've been
handled by me. They seem to
know it for a long time that
stuff on the floor was fair game
but things on shelves were
daddy stuff, don't mess with them.
But then they got more adventurous
and they tasted several
video game
controllers.
They really like those.
How old are the pups now?
They're about seven months now.
So they're going through
secondary teething right now.
And I would get a wash rag and
get it wet and put it in the freezer
and give them that to chew.
Because they're looking around for things to chew now
because it relieves
they cause a massacration.
I know they've got tons of stuff to chew.
My house is covered with dog toys
and cat toys and stuff.
And we give them new ones all the time.
But you know,
they want a taste of furniture.
The fossils.
Yeah, actually I did want to.
You wouldn't think a dog would give a hoot about a fossil.
I wouldn't.
Daddy's been playing with them.
German Shepherds are great dogs and they're so inquisitive
and so intelligent and
you're just going to have a whole awesome time up ahead of you.
Especially as they mature a little bit
and they take on their shepherd personas.
Well a good dog or a good cat will teach you
why you want a dog or a cat in the world.
In the first place.
Because they're so sympathetic and empathetic
and they're far more than you ever believed possible.
And so from then on you want every dog and cat
to hit that high standard.
And they often don't.
Well, those dogs are going to have some real treats
waiting for them tomorrow morning.
Very good.
Now you'll circle back to get everybody at the ranch, right?
That's what I said.
The first thing I'm going to do, 7-05, is get them.
Yeah. Because they're going to be here for a while. Yeah.
They're pining for me.
Princess Wee said that Claudia's just going,
she just stares out the window waiting.
I tried to talk to her on FaceTime yesterday
but it didn't work.
So yeah, first thing I'm going to do is beam up my lonesome dogs
and give them something to play with.
And then we?
Yeah, and then my wife.
And then I'll see if my kids,
I want to just see if my kids automatically get beamed up
or if their faithlessness leaves them down there.
But just for the sake of it,
for the sake of my grandkids,
I'll go ahead and probably beam up the whole gang.
Well, you're a better man than me
because I was going to go, you know,
tool around a little bit to get the feel of the saucer
before I went back to get carrots.
You won't have to.
You don't think so?
No, everything will be automatic.
Oh.
Everything will be automatic.
You couldn't go anywhere on it in an instant.
One will know before you think of it what you want.
Or as you're thinking of it, it will pick up on it.
I always want to say, she.
Just like the government.
Yeah, kind of.
Well, that's not the problem with it, you know.
After a while you're going, no, this is too perfect.
I'm freaking out.
That's the phase we don't tell everybody about.
All I want is a thought to myself in my own mind.
Do you want to know the secret of how to deal with that?
It's a very important secret.
What's that, Dr. Howe?
The secret is that you also put a spell on yourself
so that you don't know
all these things you arranged are going to happen to you
and you can just think you're very lucky and so on.
Every now and then you get a reminder.
But in your case, you see,
you don't let yourself know that everything is perfect.
Now that is a brilliant tip from the keeper of the mystic secrets
of the Church of the Subchangest.
That's why everybody goes wrong who makes a deal with the devil or whatever
because you cannot take satisfaction
when you know the game is rigged in your favor.
So first you rig it in your favor
and then you create limited oblivion for yourself
so you can enjoy it as if it's your actual just desserts.
And you forget that you sold your soul.
Yes, which is also good because you don't fret about it all the time.
That takes it off your mind.
You can worry about that later
when the devil takes you to hell for eternity.
He rises up through the floor at an inconvenient time
and holds the document and reminds you and so forth.
And you have to beg and wheedle for a little more time.
I know they say hell's going to be bad,
but what if it's not?
What if it's like super awesome and all your friends are there?
I'm glad I'm not involved in any of that stuff
because I'll be on the pleasure saucer.
But I wonder about all the other people.
Jack T. Chick denies it.
However, isn't it part of the subgenius lore
that the Christian heaven is subgenius hell or something like that?
You have to have subgenius hell as practice for subgenius heaven.
They're both fun, but subgenius heaven is so fun
you'd lose your mind if you didn't go through boot camp.
You tend to lose your mind anyway.
You have to be able to live with yourself forever.
The slightest flaw becomes a sin.
You're a child of an infinite size.
So you've got to watch out for that.
Only the part that is worthy of moving on to the next dimension or whatever.
Look at that. The thing that's supposed to protect my hearing aid is soaked.
Soaked.
I'd have to put a new napkin up there every 10 minutes.
Do you want a new napkin? I believe I might have one.
Yeah.
I'll get one.
I need to finish this bottle of water
so that I'll have something to catch the soap.
I'm sweating.
I can refill it in about 5 minutes.
I do like to remind people to please stay hydrated.
You've got to drink some water today.
We have a lot of fabulous barley beverages
that were donated by the Orange Blossom Beer Company.
They're fabulous. We've got them ice cold for you.
We want you to enjoy them, but we also want to make sure
that everybody has a good time. So drink some water.
Ironically, friends, good old Pease himself neglected to drink enough water.
Even though he remembered to drink enough beer.
And by the afternoon of July 5th, he was really messed up.
But then, what subgenius wasn't?
Which leads us to our closing song by the Swingin' Love Corpses,
a personal fave called TFBAB Bummer,
which stands for Total Fucking Badass Bummer.
The version heard by the internet audience will vary greatly
from that heard by our beloved broadcast radio listeners.
Afterwards, you must always learn everything from subgenius.com.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
It's a total fucking big ass bummer, man!
My dog got run over!
Bummer!
P-A-B!
Garbage is getting early,
we're getting in the garbage house!
Bummer!
It's a bummer!
80,000 people died in an earthquake in China!
Bummer!
Total fucking bummer!
It's a bummer!
There was a guy in California
that couldn't get his nut one night.
Bummer!
Total fucking bummer!
The guy in California was with his best girlfriend
and he didn't get his nut.
Bummer!
Real bummer!
I burned my finger the other day!
Bummer!
Fucking bummer!
I had to tear my band-aid off!
Bummer!
Real bummer!
Trillion dollar deficit!
Bummer!
contaminated good for a sad ass woman.
I'm sorry but bummer!
Well this was funny.
we can definitely RAW!
Iran has the hydrogen bomb!
Bummer!
TAKING A ambos.
BUMBER.
we take a bunch of RIPPING guys.
We none moms back up here.
Give them an actual RIPPING lake.
I.
You might even have more.
But what happens as good as.
I'm sorry but guilty of it.