Tonight, for your listening pleasure, the lovely Swinkle Sisters, Jim Morrisberry and his band of renown, and also the Tumbling Jakes.
So get ready, and get ready, because tonight's going to be a night you're not going to quickly forget.
No matter how you may try, it will be rerun again and again in your nightmares.
The show that will never die.
The Undying Show.
Afraid of fire.
Okay, we can now start another show.
It is done, and so, and so it can begin again.
Flying saucer.
Flying saucers.
Now, am I crazy?
Yeah, something like that.
So you saw some sort of flying saucer, is that the deal?
Are you crazy?
You say you saw some sort of flying saucer.
Some sort of monster.
The saucer.
Are you crazy?
Flying saucer.
I thought I was going crazy.
What are you, some kind of...
Okay.
There was a flying sausage, actually.
Dying sausage, I thought.
You were rather sauced at the time.
At a high rate of speed.
And what was once the hour of slack, slowly, gradually mutated into a radio synesthesia.
Which is still...
Full of slack and slackers.
Praise the Lord.
These times are not going to get any better.
This show is not going to get any better, my friend.
Is it still being simultaneously cast to the northern hemisphere?
At the speed of light.
I mean, out there to California, the big relay post in the ground with the pictures of Reagan on the bottom.
Well, I think through the wonder of podcasts, they could...
Couldn't they?
Couldn't they get it out there in California?
Well, the only pods in California I know about are the ones that, like, people that look like you come out of and stuff after they've made you go to sleep.
Like me?
Yeah, like you.
No, like...
Yeah.
Because they can duplicate these human specimens.
You know, we have to figure out who's fake and who's real.
And they do figure that out as you try to go up the ramp of the saucer.
And presto, there's a new person.
There are a lot of inauthentic, fake subs who are going to try to get aboard.
It's really tedious and irritating to have to deal with these people.
When there's this many pod clones, I just can't sleep at night.
You once were telling me about Planet X, Dr. Morbund.
Evil on Planet X is more than you could think of.
Evil stocks up.
Every night and day, they wait to see the evil they go through.
Do they come down in flying saucers?
Flying saucers are bearing on us.
We don't know what to do.
We're here all alone.
The planets are fading.
The blood is running.
And the lights were fading.
And they stalked us one by one.
This is the Man in Black.
Here for the Roma Wine Company of Fresno.
Fresno, California.
Good evening.
This is Cleveland.
And the program is Synesthesia.
I'm your host, Dr. Sinister.
And it is my great honor and pleasure to have some really fun people here in the studio with me tonight.
Reverend Stang, thank you for sticking around.
And Princess We Are Do.
And Dr. Holland Owl will be on the air momentarily here.
And Lonesome Cowboy Dave is on the line with us as well.
Thank you for holding, Dave.
I'm wonderful right now enjoying myself.
Hey, you know, it's...
Enjoy yourself.
That last hour of slack was the easiest one I have ever done.
Well, it really zipped by, didn't it?
I only had to say about four or five words, and even those were probably not necessary.
When you've got Hal and Dave on hand.
It was succinct.
Yeah.
And perfect.
Well, we were channeling the great former cultural...
Memes of the old world.
For the last time, perhaps.
Yeah.
I hope.
I would pray, except I'm afraid who'd be listening.
Besides the listeners.
I mean, they're bad enough.
We're better in this time.
I'm afraid that's all you will find is listeners as you pray because of the vast emptiness we pray to.
It does...
It, with a big capital I, does not exist, perhaps.
Maybe.
I don't know.
You're wasting all your time praying to something that doesn't exist?
I don't pray.
Well, then you're not wasting...
I'm not wasting your time on you.
No, I demand of the cosmos, and I'm denied.
Hmm.
Well, I guess it doesn't hurt to ask.
Besides, it might take the big ol' cosmos a long time to answer your request because there's so much inertia about getting into magnum motion to deal with your case on an individual basis.
Plus, even assuming your voice could travel at the speed of light through space, which, of course, it can't.
Well, unless you've got, like, the right kind of transmitter.
Yeah, like we do.
Yeah, we got that here.
Right now.
Most of us don't have access to that kind of transmitter, you know?
It's like, you know, in space, no one can hear your prayers.
The only transmissions going on around here are disease.
Uh-oh.
We have been intercepting your transmissions and have learned your language, Daddy-O.
And now for a word from our sponsor.
See, it's all atomic testing.
This episode is brought to you by Children's Chewable Lithium.
That's right, Children's Chewable Lithium.
Look for it in the cool blue box featuring Barry the Bipolar Bear.
He is making your abler by keeping your mood stabler.
That was pretty.
We got Governor Rockner on the line.
Is this you?
Well, good evening, Dr. Howell.
Good evening.
Oh, hello there, Governor Rockner.
I've been staying in Princess Mary.
How is sports land?
Ah, it is interesting right now.
Yeah, I know.
I will say this.
The Bard's pleasure saucer is that he is banned from his pleasure saucer.
No, wait a minute.
Let's not get off into some little...
Little minor trivial...
All that trash.
No, last night, last night I actually...
Boys in the band.
Last night I actually saw a guy who has been banned from X-Day before.
He was...
Careening down the street in a drunken stupor.
He was tearing up the dance floor at our WCSB anniversary party.
You mean he wasn't rolling in the gutter in unspeakable filth?
I think I never knew you'd be talking about...
Depends on your definition of rolling.
Depends on your definition of gutter.
It depends on your definition of unspeakable filth.
This is the guy with the walking light show, right?
Wasn't he degraded below the lowest definition of a human?
Were you there?
No, but I didn't think...
I'm trying to think.
The only person who would have been...
Been at that party who is on the banned list, besides the bands.
He literally had...
Great bands.
Who are you defecating on right now?
You should explain to the listeners.
No, we don't want to get into all that.
We're not defecating on anyone.
We're elevating ourselves.
It's not about the exclusion.
It's about inclusion for all.
No actual persons are involved here.
Every subgenius will be lifted up.
That's right.
But some will have their own saucers and others will...
It's true.
False.
Fake subgenius.
Subgeniuses may explode in midair like little bombs.
I mean, some saucers might be, you know, hundreds of miles in diameter.
Oh, that's a given.
And some other saucers might be hundreds of times larger than that.
My escape planet will contain upon it Wisteria, the campground.
And also Brushwood, the campground, however, will only keep the staff of Wisteria.
They can be made contiguous.
The staff of Brushwood will remain in a crater.
Left behind for...
Well, actually, come to think of it, I guess some of those folks were safe.
No, except for Frank and Darlene Barney.
Except for the original Barneys.
What about Barney Frank?
Not the friendly one that the children enjoy.
Barney Frank.
Yes, Reverend Barney Frank will be there.
Reverend Obama, believe it or not, has had his membership paid for.
The president?
Yes.
Why?
Don't ask me, but Reverend Chain Smoker of Australia always buys...
A membership for American presidents, and also he bought one for Sarah Palin.
Ah, okay, so as long as he bought one for, like, every president...
He bought one for Bush, he bought one for Palin, he bought one for the previous Bush.
So it's kind of like a blackmailing chip.
Reverend Chain Smoker will be at Exeter.
Just don't let the GOP Congress find out that Obama is a member, or we'll never hear the end of it.
But let me put it this way.
I accepted the payment.
I personally ordained Barry in my...
But I didn't really send the package to the White House, because I've already been through that with the Secret Service back in 1982 or something.
Yes, we don't care to repeat these old pleasures.
The membership pack does, in fact, if you recall, come with a drawing by Hellswami satellite weavers of Bob, Elvis, Buddha, and the Fighting Jesus, all attacking a Hydra,
one of whose arms is labeled...
Reagan or any president.
And that was the drawing that brought the Secret Service to my door in Dallas.
That was the drawing?
That was the drawing.
They said, that's in pretty bad taste.
We can't tell you not to do it anymore, but we hope you don't.
And the next week, People magazine reprinted that drawing in a glowing review of Book of the Subgenius.
And that's a true story.
Really?
Yes.
That's quite cool.
It's intimating that perhaps our media and our government might be sharing the same...
Same toilet?
No, we're saying that there are moles who have burrowed within who managed to save us from the consequences of our deepest folly.
Yeah, unfortunately, People magazine fired that mole, I'm sure.
Well, he had to take it on.
You know, like us, we destroy slack for ourselves just so we can bring slack to the slackless.
It's like show host syndrome.
Yes, you know we do.
We don't intentionally do it, but we have to do it to continue our ministry.
However, time is coming.
Shortly, when we can settle back, relax, and not worry about anybody else's slack.
Put those pampered feet up on the divan and smoke a pipe for a while.
Well, and you don't know what an ex-guy with long legs...
I can't believe how much porn there is on the screen right now.
Porn?
I need to look at the browser history here to see...
What's her phone number?
...some time here.
Mama, buy me debt.
I think I know exactly who's responsible for this.
That's subgenius.com.
We are going to be horribly...
Actually, you know what?
My workplace...
Dot com?
At the place where I work...
Dot com.
...the subgenius website is actually blocked.
Oh, yeah.
By whom?
Oh, it's blocked in a number of hotel chains.
It's a particular tentacle of the conspiracy.
I had a panicky, panicky day at the Grand Canyon thinking that...
At the Grand Canyon.
...thinking that my business had been taken down because when I got up that morning in the hotel to check things, subgenius.com was gone.
But isn't that a periodic fluctuation of the internet?
No, it's not.
It's that some businesses have less...
And the computer has actually crashed, apparently.
That's what you get for...
...subgenius.com trouble.
You were banned.
You were banned on not Motel 5 or whatever.
We can't mention that.
I know exactly who did this.
I know that there's somebody who's...
I'm not going to say it.
Well, you know...
Why give them any publicity?
I'm not going to say it.
Moles will be moles and foes will be moles.
Okay, come on.
Let's face it.
I've looked at the browser history when I see that...
Like, I type in...
I try to type in a URL.
And something really nasty pops up in the address bar as the auto-fill-in.
Which, of course, means I need to look at the browser history...
You know Bob has been in the studio.
J.R. Bob Dobbs just finished doing a show.
Do I need to get a sanitary wipe and wipe this chair down?
Oh, that's terrible.
You must do that.
Just before I left on my recent trip to Petrolia,
I noticed that on the internet they'd taken down many of Puzzling Evidence's videos
because of a complaint.
And they took down your commercial for the Church of the Subgenius.
What?
The short one.
Because it's supposedly of a...
Complaint.
What?
All this stuff was disappearing.
When I came back from my three-day trip, it had all been restored.
So this is like an effort that is not only continuous,
it's like peppery.
Kind of like a destabilizing...
Paul pointed it out to me.
What could I do about it?
I was leaving on a trip.
We have enemies out there who are so jealous of our slack
and the fact that J.R. Bob Dobbs himself has blessed us.
I know, it's true.
And what can we do?
We have to stand here with our heads bowed humbly,
naked unto the world.
But it doesn't mean that we have to get into this pissy internet type of flame war stuff.
Let's suspend all talk of who's banned and all this crap.
We do have one more caller on the line here who has not been banned yet.
But for those of you out there...
Oh, is R.C. is back?
Still young.
No.
An R.C. Coa?
I figure he's either dead, in jail, married,
or actually got a job.
This is me, Bernard Braithwaite.
St. Bernard, haven't heard from you in a couple of weeks.
Move on over.
Welcome to the program.
Royal Crown Cola.
It's a mad, mad, mad, mad cola.
Can do point fingers.
R.C., the one with the mad, mad taste.
And they do it constantly.
So, it's become a problem.
But what a night I picked to listen.
You picked a night to listen?
You can pick any night to listen.
Sir, listen along.
Whoa.
Oh, that one doesn't...
That one doesn't work very well.
Well, you know...
Here's the card.
My recent show, I...
I almost knocked everything over.
Had a scientific discussion going,
which I thought was so interesting,
maybe we could go...
You see, it's been asked...
All this talk about how the exists are going to fry Earth and so on,
and some people have sneeringly said,
where are they going to get the energy to do that, you know?
And how about these skeletonizer rays that they fire
that turn you into a skeleton, you know?
Well, that's like a...
How did God just rear back and pass a miracle
and order a whole mess of permanent?
Well, he had the Big Bang to work on.
But that's all over and done with now.
Where do they get the energy?
They get the energy from the pain of the pinks and humans.
But they get it from unlocking the subatomic world.
Right.
They tap the ether, which our machines cannot yet...
The model is the Martian beams in the War of the Worlds,
if you remember what Doctor...
Beams?
Beams.
The skeletonizing ray that Dr. Clayton Forrester explains in that movie.
He says that the mesons are directly affected.
But, of course, that's 50-year-old physics,
and today we know of gluons,
which, when they come unglued,
cause a general to disappear,
leaving a glowing skeleton, which itself disappears.
But the thing about this is that I'm trying to say...
They simply wink out of existence, so...
No, you don't...
They don't wink out of existence.
To leave existence releases an enormous amount of energy.
The amount of energy in atomic bombs is actually a very small amount.
A large general wearing a helmet and a sidearm and a suit
and having eaten a large meal, when discorporating,
releases more energy than all of the atomic bombs
ever created or exploded on Earth at the same time.
And smells just like bacon.
And that was the general.
That was one guy.
And the power of the explosion.
But then...
They start blasting trucks and tanks and so on.
This would be enough to blow the side out of our planet
with these energy releases.
And that is how the Exists will accomplish it.
Not as anything more than a byproduct
of the rays that they use to skeletonize the non-subgeniuses.
By scouring the ether,
dressed up as a Martian general...
Or a big-eyed beam from Venus.
Big-eyed beam?
I've been busy sniffing the ether.
There's really no charm involved.
Or a Masonic gluon.
And I've been sniffing the gluons too, yeah.
Well, then how...
Looks like a big-eyed gluon.
But sniffing gluons?
Well, I don't knock it if you haven't tried it.
Beat sniffing Masons.
That's right. Especially Masons.
Marsha Mason.
I actually had to walk home today and I had to kind of
relieve myself on a Masonic lodge on the way home.
Could you not do it when you got home, you disgusting fellow?
Didn't you have the energy stored within your body
that you could have kind of imploded yourself home
and done your business as you should have?
Why wait for the first Masonic lodge you see?
Your urinate for crying out loud.
Isn't this what they say? TMI?
Too much information?
Or does that stand for Three Mile Island?
Anyway...
Down there uncontrollably...
Or Fukushima.
And the horse that rode in there.
Right, right.
The colors are feuding.
We're all thinking the same thing at the same time
and we're connected in time and space by those same gluons
we use as Masonic particles.
And with the Masonic handshake which keeps them attached.
Yeah, but if you've got like seven heads or like seven tentacles...
You know what's really weird?
In the last couple of months I've been introduced to like
two or three people who gave me the secret Masonic handshake
when greeting me.
They're tapping you.
They're tapping you on the shoulder.
I couldn't believe it.
It's like, why? What the hell?
And I called them out on it.
I said it out loud.
Did you just give me the secret handshake?
It's a very subtle thing.
Those of you who know what it is...
Yeah, exactly.
The average onlooker is not going to notice it.
But...
Did you just give me the secret Masonic handshake?
Or are you trying to pick me up in the bus station?
That's the one where the middle finger tickles your palm.
The forefinger and the middle finger tap the wrist.
Oh.
You're shaking hands, but your forefinger and middle finger
will squeeze like the wrist, like where your pulse is.
You're going to die for announcing that on the radio, won't you?
But you know how I read that? I read it in a book.
It's like a handshake, but one step beyond.
Was it the book by Jay Kinney on the Masons that just came out?
No, no. This is a book that came out like 30 years ago
called Big Secrets by William Poundstead.
I thought Bozo's on this Bus was written by some sort of
Masonic scribe guy as a thing he was supposed to do
to get the donuts on time.
Donuts?
They had a class and they said, well, what do Masons eat?
What's their favorite food?
And he produced donuts and coffee.
And I started crying because I'd been there for half an hour
and all I said to him was, there was one guy with a pointy hat,
and he said, you're going to have to learn not to laugh at stuff like this
or else then we're going to... I don't know what we'll do.
Save your humor for the humorous.
I'm the humor for the humorless.
Believe it. We're all on the edge of a precipice
that we're not going to be able to climb back from.
There's a lot of tension winding up, but after X-Day,
that huge hee-haw of a laugh will escape and be heard all over the universe.
Well, I think Bob had perfectly timed Fukushima
to the time of X-Day and he knew it and we didn't
because we didn't go back successfully to kill him
at the previous moment, at which time he would have not.
And never mind. You know what I'm saying?
I just read today that there's a nuclear plant in Nebraska...
Note you're saying.
...who's, uh, they had like 2,000-foot-high concrete barriers
or something around it.
And with all the flooding along the Missouri River...
That's pretty tall.
Yeah, it didn't make sense.
I heard like 2,000-foot-something.
I'm like, what?
That's like half a mile almost.
Yeah, that's a real tall nuclear plant.
So that couldn't possibly be right,
but I saw that some nuclear power plant in Nebraska
is getting flooded now.
Yes.
Who knows what could come after that?
Why can't we have thorium-based nuclear power plants
in this country, which are much safer than, you know,
these deadly uranium and plutonium?
Well, I'm afraid there's just not time.
There's not time to build them, Rocknar.
...something safer than all that.
Is there an odinium on the periodic table?
I don't think so.
Did you notice that they...
There's a thorium, but not an odinium.
...they recently added two new elements to the periodic table
just within the last month.
Two new elements have been created.
Or an onanium.
Well, onanium.
See, that's...
Not conium.
Onanium from cannobitium.
And what about dobsium?
Yeah, dobsium-537.
That's one of the most radioactive elements there is and isn't.
But it only exists for a flash.
A flash that lasts quite a few million years
and an after-flash, unfortunately.
Yes, it's quite true.
But the actual moment of the burst,
which could be likened to the Big Bang itself,
is a micropulse of cosmic time.
But it's just enough time to get arrested for flashing.
You've got to hit it just right and then get out of the park
before the police arrive.
And, Dr. Howell, you know what a Dyson sphere is, right?
Why, yes.
A theoretical Dyson sphere.
What if you could have a Dyson sphere
that was in the shape of a donut
and instead of the star being inside the sphere,
it would be outside the sphere
but in the ring of the donut?
And the inside ring of the donut
contains the habitable, you know, biodomes.
To me, that just doesn't sound like
the most optimal configuration you could have.
Because it's the wrong shape.
It is convex where it should be concave.
Why do subgeniuses always carry things into...
comparing them to donuts?
Well, it's dollars to donuts
that subgeniuses will always use these simple expressions.
I always thought it was a sexual euphemism
for m-m-my lady's, uh, part, part, pa-pa-pa.
Well, I guess your mind was there before
the Church of the Subgenius ever established its beachhead.
Yeah, Donut Factory.
That used to be semi-insulting, but it meant, yo, bitch.
Donut forsake me, oh, my darlin'.
Is it dumb?
It's because we're all cops, that's all.
That's right. We are the only ones policing this area.
I'm sorry, I had a tender moment thinking about it.
Well, then we have to have a Tim Hortons nearby.
Uh, is that...
Are they nearby right now?
You can...
There are no Tim Hortons franchises in the Cleveland area that I know of.
Not that I know of either.
I think you gotta go to Columbus or Canada.
That's too far.
I wouldn't want to go into one without knowing where it was.
There's actually talk about a Tim Hortons opening up in Lexington.
Really?
What, no fran- what, no important franchises?
It starts with that, it starts with that, and next thing you know they'll be selling ketchup-flavored potato chips.
Ketchup-slavery patrols?
I'd like some of that.
I remember how saying in the original Arise video that Earth would be turned into one giant Stuckey's.
I'm afraid I have to stand by that statement.
Exactly, I stand by it too.
You're understanding that statement?
It's a Stuckey's for travelers in the cosmos.
Yeah.
They have these God Apple abomination crossover stores, which are like, you know, a combination, you know, like BP and Burger King or whatnot.
Most people don't even know what Stuckey's is anymore.
We can't say these commercial names.
Stuckey's was the old Speedway, you might say.
Long ago it was a franchise that was on the side of the highway that us oldsters grew up with.
That's right.
It was overpriced crap.
And bad food.
But it was a refuge from the hurtling highway.
I was shocked to see a Stuckey's on our most recent road trip.
An open, functioning Stuckey's.
Not dead, but liveth.
I've heard of them, but I'm too young to remember them actually.
But the thing is, these...
One of the items that they sell at Speedway is in the pastry aisle, and it's cheesecake.
And its barcode, the UPC barcode, ends in a 13013.
They are Bob's Cheesecakes.
The secret, sacred number of Bob's.
But you have to turn these cheesecakes upside down to get the number correctly.
And they are available at any one of the 1100 different Speedways in nine different states in the sky.
Well, would you mind making a run for us? We're here behind the microphones.
Really?
We don't want to turn this into an ad for your employer.
But it's... I wasn't out on a limb there.
They attract each other.
I didn't mention the price.
The doctrine is quite clear.
Earth will be turned into a cosmic Stuckey's after its present use.
Nothing goes unused.
That's not to say that you can be there and even get a job as a short order cook.
Our Earth will be completely gone.
But it will be a Stuckey's for wanderers in the cosmos.
What if it was also a crossover store that had the Kentucky Fried Humans in it?
Those are called the Thing.
Franchise, my friend.
Those crisped humans are called the Thing.
It's like those signs.
There are 38 billion signs that say the Thing.
Can you stop it?
But they have different names for it everywhere.
It's a cultural thing.
They're going to market them the way that the consumers like.
The Hunger Cobra.
Strictly from hunger.
I want to sell consumption itself.
Things that the consumptive will like.
Selling consumption itself.
The actual act of consumption.
Make people pay to make people consume.
Make them cough it up.
I guess the domain name is already taken over.
Consume.
This portion of the show is brought to you by Soylent Green.
Remember, Tuesday is Soylent Green Day.
Yeah, it's alright with the sauce.
Have you noticed the floors are made of copper and there seems to be a tunnel under the Earth?
A tunnel?
A tunnel under the Earth?
Well, you can't have a tunnel over the Earth.
That's axiomatic.
That's crazy.
Crazy talk.
Insane.
That's kind of crazy talk.
So it must exist then since the opposite could not exist then the opposite of something that doesn't exist must exist.
Bah.
Tautological paradigm.
There is a tunnel under the Earth and there's copper in my basement.
Or not, on the floor.
Speaking of tautology.
You keep talking like that you'll blow up the universe again.
I'd never believe it.
I've never actually blown up the universe before.
I've threatened many times but I would never actually do it on purpose until maybe, oh, I don't know, next week.
Well, hasn't there been like evidence that there hasn't been just one big bang but like several?
Well, I can imagine the universe acting like a concertina, wheezing in and out with a bang then an anti-bang and this raucous carnival music is that which entertains the gods.
Right.
There was a Futurama that depicted repeated big bang.
That's right.
Cartoons know everything.
To the lord it's that's just the backbeat.
Yes.
That's true.
Some cartoons.
Taste in music isn't better.
That Lawrence Welk-like polka.
Wonderful, wonderful, wonderful.
A senile space god.
Well, um, I think that's it for this episode of the Supernatural.
I guess that kind of wraps it up.
So maybe we should throw it open to questions from callers about X-Day
and how they plan to spend their last pathetic moments.
That's right.
216-6-7-0-VAL-F-E-R-N-E-V-E-S-T-E-S-K-E-S.
If you would like to get yourself on the air here, this is Synesthesia.
I'm Dr. Synesthesia.
I've got my special guest here tonight, Dr. Holland Owl and Reverend Ivan Stang.
And Princess We Are Doe, Governor Ragnar, and, of course, Wombat.
So join our conversation now in progress.
And Dr. Howell is so cool, he drinks his Ale-8 out of a Klein bottle.
Boy, I haven't seen any Ale-8 for some time.
That's ancient history.
Put it in the other side of the pillow.
Did you drink the wine of the ancient mariner?
Why am I having a sense of deja vu about this conversation?
I just heard the wine of the ancient mariner.
The caller.
Oh, well, the ancient mariner is an albatross around my neck.
When you went to Athens, Ohio,
did you check out the wine of the ancient mariner?
Did you check out the Kroger's?
Or did you just pass by and it's like, oh, it's a Kroger's?
Princess We and I carefully inspected the Kroger's in Athens.
But of course.
And not to advertise anybody.
I know what your question is.
Yes, there is a state liquor store inside there, and it is quite well stocked.
Well, I wasn't looking necessarily for liquor, but maybe for Ale-8.
Why would you ask?
Not probably.
You know, I can't say.
He was looking for a Pan Suma.
That's in Southern.
That's fairly close to Kentucky.
They don't sell Ale-8 in Northeastern Ohio, but you can get Werner's here,
which I understand is more of a Michigan thing.
Yes, Werner's Ginger Ale.
Werner's would used to be also an Ohio thing.
You know, let's see.
Here's the problem.
Rocknor is an Asian.
Yes.
I am a Strapalian.
We all have different certain foods.
Quite true.
Yes, I'm a Limonian.
I'm partial to Safeway's Refresh Diet Grapefruit Soda.
Want to welcome one more person to the program here?
Hi, it's Pisces.
Pisces?
I can't believe how long you've been here.
It's Pisces!
Thank you for finally, finally calling up after so many years.
Yes, folks, it's the delectable Priestess Pisces.
Yes, indeed.
I'm wondering if maybe just possibly this sex goddess could be made out of raspberry gummies.
Made out of it?
If you want her to.
I'm a petroleum additive.
I'm a huge fan of raspberry gummies.
Raspberry gummies and sure wine soda.
On the saucers, you will be making sweet love to raspberry gummy soda.
Is it too late to cancel my tour?
Endlessly.
And when you're rough with it, it'll bleed the soda.
Oh, that would be fantastic.
You know, got to get along.
Got to get along.
Pisces, I'm going to save this story and just tell it only to you, but what the hell?
I'll tell it to everybody else on the radio.
Sure.
Oh, no.
Going to betray your confidence, eh?
Why not?
I was walking to the grocery store yesterday, and I passed a yard sale, and there was two pairs of spiky high-heeled shoes, and they were selling them for like two bucks each.
I'm like, hmm, black patent and a zebra print.
Oh, cool.
Beginning your new career as a cross or a cheerful cross dresser?
Yeah, I was wondering.
Didn't you get best moves one X day at the Bobby Awards?
Yeah, the first time I ever saw Rocknard, he was wearing a grease-stained white bathrobe, a pair of tighty-whities, and he was eating a pork chop on a steak.
Now, that's a song title right there.
The first time I met Rocknard, and then in parentheses, he was eating a pork chop, standing on a hot dog, waiting for the bus to arrive.
Now, the first time I saw Priestess Pisces, she was wearing only her pants.
Very little.
And marker.
Black marker.
And a smile.
I had autographed parts.
I'm bringing my markers of all colors.
Big, prominent parts.
Decorate the parts of those who care to participate.
Anyone who clicks on the events, if you go to subgenius.com and click on the events, the first thing you'll see is a beautiful color painting of Priestess Pisces on X day.
Big, prominent parts.
With flaming mountains in the background, saucers overhead, and she's holding the head of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
The still-smoking head, I might add.
You know, the great thing about Bob is you can keep killing him over and over again.
So when I was posing for the picture, you know, we had to kill Bob first.
Not only can you, you must.
But luckily, he keeps coming back.
And you keep killing him.
So you have all those multiple opportunities for...
photo op.
Oh, yeah.
We can do that again.
And then you can argue
later on about the photographs
and 79% of the people
who I saw
of the original photographs
will mysteriously disappear.
And then people dressed
in black suits
and green underwear
will associate
with your doorway
and tell the bum
who is this guy.
And of course,
you'll have to answer them
and go inside
and answer a bunch
of questions.
I would tell everyone
not to do that
because once they
take that little radar...
What?
Don't answer the questions?
No, no.
Once they take the chips
out of your hands,
that's where they really are.
Then you're unprotected
and then you realize
there is no Bob.
This is all an illusion, too.
And you don't want to do that.
All right.
Let's keep this
theologically clean.
It's not that there is no Bob.
Dr. the Heretic.
Right.
It's not that there is no Bob.
That's not...
Dave is banned.
It's more that it's all
in your head.
It's not that there is no Bob.
It's just that
he's not really your friend.
Right.
That's kind of what
I'm trying to say.
It's a character, all right,
but it doesn't have
your best interest.
Well...
He's an exemplar.
His slack is perfect,
but it has to come
from somewhere.
Perhaps the slack
of those around him.
Exactly.
Like the X's
sniffing and snorting away
on the ether
and drawing in
the poo, poo, poo,
poo bunch
and the other mustard
and all the gases
that must eventually
come to an explosion.
He is alpha
and omega.
Omega.
Is mustard
simultaneously
the mouth and anus
of the universe?
The Fuhrer thought it was
and that's why
he singed his hair
and he became a great leader
because he had singed
his own hair.
That explains the mustache.
Yes.
That's why so many
of his officer class
used to wear half mustaches
to show that they were
the eighth member.
The Fuhrer was
going to come to X Day.
He gets invited
every year.
He's not a...
You're talking about
some of Bob's
half mustaches?
Bin Laden put out
a type saying
that now that
everybody's
thinks he's dead
he can finally
come to the U.S.
and attend X Day.
He's been a big
subgenius fan for years.
We've been laden
with a heavy burden.
He wears his hair
the way he does
copying me,
he said.
Yeah, that's right.
And it looks
very distingu.
And Sting
has beautiful hair.
He does.
You see,
that's part of
his saintly nature.
And he's going to be
so happy to be there
because contrary
to what people believe
he's not a fundamentalist.
He's not a fundamentalist
at all.
He drinks like a fish,
swears like a mongoose,
and argues like a pink child.
Just to keep this
straight,
we're not talking
about Sting,
but about Osama Bin Laden.
Osama, yeah.
Yeah.
Wait.
Wait, he drinks fish?
He's not dead.
He's not really alive
either,
but you know what I mean.
The Phantom Zone?
Yes, he drinks
goldfish, too.
Goldfish?
Goldfleisch.
Feist.
Back in his throat?
I mean,
they're crackers
after all.
I noticed
Pisces got excited
when she heard
about the drinking
of the fish.
Uh-huh.
Yes, well,
fishy women
are like that.
Especially the goldfish,
you know,
maybe he'll help
get rid of the Asian carp
and the Great Lakes.
Are you part fin?
I wouldn't put
a fin on that.
Well,
I wouldn't touch
that one with a flipper.
Actually,
that tail
has long
been exhausted.
I've had it
to the gills.
Speaking of fins,
our friend
Sven Serrano,
the Mexican-Finnish-American,
just finished having
a big X-Day revival
in Shanghai, China.
And did it go
swimmingly?
It sure did.
All the Americans
came because it was
finally something
cool happening,
so all the cute
consular workers
came,
according to Sven.
I saw the DVD
of the one
last year.
And how did
that look?
Full of
cute young
Americans.
Shanghai is like
a big tourist
trap, actually.
If you want to
really see China,
don't go to Shanghai.
That's what I've heard.
I actually have
an uncle in
Chengdu,
but I don't know
if he was trying
to make it.
Chengdu is
Xanadu.
That's where
Kublai Khan
decreed his
stately pleasure.
Wow.
All I know
is he went
to China
and met himself
a beautiful
young wife,
and married her.
Actually,
Chengdu is also
one of the other
names for Beijing,
I think.
Well, it's his
Chengdu.
Isn't Shanghai
a big old
whole house?
Certainly not.
That's the 1920s
they're talking about.
It was bombed
by the Japanese
and then
there were,
you know,
it was different
after that.
And it's all
going to get
bombed by the
exes.
Yes, that's right.
Well, not bombed,
but necessarily
the laser beam thing.
I'm going to get
bombed.
bombed as soon as
this show is over.
Oh, yeah,
laser beams
are so crude.
Exes technology
is so much more
advanced than just
crude human
laser beams.
Yes, that's
quite true.
Exes weapons
make laser beams
look like little toys.
Yes, I was
talking about
laser beams
look like
lima beams.
It's a
skeletonizer ray
that releases
vast quantities
of energy at once.
Boston-baked
beams.
There's going
to be some
kind of a
laser beam
fight or
a war at
Starwood this
year.
I just put that
into the program
guide.
Something happening
at the
Do you mean
pagans use
lasers?
I thought they
were anti-scientific
lug-outs wearing
wooden shoes.
They play with
toys just like
subgeniuses do.
I thought they
had to play with
hand-carved
willow bark
chileles.
That would
be pretty
awesome to make
a laser out of
a hand-carved
Chilean
willow
cinnamon stick.
Well, I ought
to play the
game.
That's all I can
say.
Fair weather
sailors.
It's only a
certain kind of
tree that you
can make the
lasers out of.
That is true.
This is true.
A laser tree.
Think about it
like this.
All you need
is a tree
and a ruby.
Well, that was
the original
Well, don't let
me keep you
back.
Get to work.
Right.
It goes back
to biblical
times in the
days of Suez.
When you think
of Moses and
the burning
bush was
actually a
wooden laser.
It was a
futile attempt
at first,
but he had
the right idea.
I thought that
was a sexually
transmitted disease.
And as we know
from Spielberg,
the Ark of the
Covenant was a
gigantic
skeletonizing
laser.
Right.
And it
bursts out of
him.
Wait a minute.
No, I
remember the
1970 Chariots
of the Gods
documentary,
and they said
that the
University of
Minnesota
actually built
a full working
replica of the
Ark of the
Covenant,
and that it
was actually
a condenser
that was
building up
hundreds of
volts of power,
and they had
to have it
dismantled.
Ah, yes.
And if it was
in Chariots of
the Gods,
friends,
then it
must be
true.
Eric von
Donaghan,
the greatest
scientist of
our time.
Yeah, that's
what the
documentary is
all about.
Everything is
on the
Internet now.
Hey, that's
right.
That's the
best thing
about the
Internet.
And the
worst thing
about the
Internet is
everything is
on the
Internet.
Yeah, I was
going to
say.
Actually, I'm
quite,
unfortunately,
there are some
things that
are not.
But you
can't have
everything on
anything.
Actually,
you can have
everything on
everything and
anything on
anything, but
not everything
on anything
something.
I'll have
one with
everything.
Actually,
just last
night, yet
another lady
requested that
I remove
her photographs
from X-Day
from the
Internet.
So not
everything is
on the
Internet.
Why?
Were these
photographs
compromising
in some
way?
Extremely.
And they
were on
the Internet?
Well, of
course.
Remember, back
in the years
before our
parents were
on the
Internet, the
girls of X-Day
were happy to
have their
pictures taken
and be shown
in the
baptism pool
and so
forth.
Then Grandma
and Grandpa
got on the
Internet.
Next thing
you know,
they're all
writing a
reference
saying,
I hate to
bother you
about this,
but could you
remove those
1,000 topless
pictures of
me?
I just told
my dad,
they were there
and Danny said,
okay, I won't
look.
He said,
he wouldn't
want me,
we can do
that.
Now, calm
down, gentlemen.
In my young
childhood,
resisted any
chance they
could to see
me walking
around bare
naked.
I think that
was one of
the most
important things
in their lives,
just seeing me
nude without
clothes,
standing in
the backyard
begging for
food,
arguing with
the damn
mutt,
who has the
best place
in the
doghouse.
Fighting with
the very
dogs for
each other.
A scrap of
sustenance.
Quantum.
Were the
dogs naked?
Was the
dog, is the
dog naked?
Oh, yes.
They're naked
as a
fur off.
Made naked
dogs.
You don't
have to put
scales on
a Pisces.
They were
already there.
A Pythoness
or Priestess.
Yes,
perfectly put.
Well, now,
I don't know
if we want
to do this,
but we could
also mention
our individual
special X-Day
plans,
since the
time is coming
soon, when
we will
know each
other's
most intimate
secrets.
So, who's
going first?
Which plans?
I mean, I
have the
secret plans,
but the
secret plans
are secret.
That's kind
of the
problem.
Yes, but
secret from
the dull,
vulgar,
cuddly,
chewing,
mooing crowd,
but not
from your
sharp,
subtenuous
friends.
to ruin
every memory
of your
favorite songs.
Who's
going to
do that?
Monkey Hive.
Monkey Hive is
going to
ruin every
memory of
every one of
your favorite
songs.
That's their
plan.
We've had
chicken head
visits, so I
don't know if
Monkey Hive can
have any
terror.
My favorite
songs are by
the amino acids,
so they don't
have any
amino acids.
Well, they're
not going to
be there this
time, though.
No, they're
not.
But Fat Free
has informed
me that they
will try their
best to
terrify,
shock, and
awe on the
level of the
amino acids.
You know,
you know,
Angry Layer is a
great guitar player,
but, like, Fear of
the Future is not
a hard song to
play.
Maybe we should
organize for the
Dr. Jam and
amino acids cover.
And as for
shock and awe,
that's an old
thing.
It needs to be
replaced with
Dr. Octopus and
George Bernard
Shaw, that is to
say, Ock and
Shaw.
Well, my fear
with Fat Free is
that Fat Free's
drummer keeps
wearing less and
less clothes every
year.
You mean fewer
and fewer?
You work up a
sweat playing
drums, though.
Oh, the
drums, the sound
of those drums
drives me insane.
The natives are
restless.
I mean, it's only
because it used to
get very cold.
Does it get cold
at night at
Wisteria like it
does at
Brushnett?
Oh, no.
No, it's a hot
hell of
simmering,
burning,
blazing.
No, and I
expect the nice
thing about
Wisteria is I
expect there will
be many more
boobs.
Boobs?
Well, I'm one.
Okay, my fingers
crossed.
Right.
It's going to be
hot.
Hot?
And the girls
will be hot.
The pool will
probably be the
best place for
relief.
Actually, it's going
to be rainy
some days.
But I heard there
was no pool, only
a filtered lake.
And why do they
have to filter it
anyway?
What's in there?
A lake monster?
Oh, you'll love
it.
You'll love it,
Dr. Howell.
You'll just love
it.
Don't you
understand what's
really afoot here?
They're luring you
there because you
know.
You know.
Well, I don't want
some pond monster
to suck out all my
vital juices.
I have enough to
worry about at this
shindig.
This is true.
And the pond
monster is filtered
though.
I mean, he's got a
filter, so he won't
cuss.
You know, it's a
clean pond monster.
I've never known
what my friend
was not to fail.
He's fine and
friendly.
Nature can cross
all barriers.
There's a woman
who calls herself
fish.
Oh, the
leeches?
No, no, no.
Not the leeches.
They're little
baby pond monsters.
Leeches.
I hate the leeches.
Sort of fish-like,
but sort of
got there.
Leeches.
They're very
small when we
saw them, but I
assume there will
be much bigger
pond monsters.
Pisces, one of
those monsters you
saw was a
salamander.
It was probably
about a thousand
years old.
You say you saw
some sort of
monster.
And that tadpole
will look very
different the next
time you see it.
I'm sure you
thought you saw
what you claimed
you saw.
Sometimes 200 feet
long are
existing.
You know, the
human mind's a
strange thing and
can play funny
tricks, but in
today's world, there
are no more
monsters.
We've put a man
on the moon.
What if we are
the monsters?
Well, I was
going to have to
get there.
I'm glad you
forestalled me.
That is, of
course, the
ultimate conclusion.
Somebody once
asked me, you
know, what about
this, you know,
we're actually the
monsters.
What good does it
do?
That's why I'd
send all the
monsters if I
wanted.
I'd send them
right to the
moon and back.
Well, that would
keep them out of
our hair for about,
let me see, 46
days, and then
we'd still have to
deal with them.
Exactly.
Can we get some
tickets on Delta?
They can fly
economy like the
rest of us and put
up with the
outrages that the
rest of us do.
The crying baby,
the kid kicking
the back of the
seat.
Now, monsters are
really going to be
rough when they get
back to Earth, and
they'll, you know,
they're going to
tear it apart like
Fin Fang Foom and
the gang.
I always remember
what monsters do,
and they're not
scaring people.
They blab.
They talk with
endless egotism.
For am I not
brutal?
Like, who cares?
Just do your
monster thing.
I am Groot,
lord of all
timber in the
universe.
Groot, by the
way, Dr.
Hal, was from
Planet X.
Really?
Yes.
Jack Kirby.
Then we'll be
seeing him again
on the show.
I guess.
Groot will be
back, and his
monster friends.
Was it timber
with arms wide
open?
Could I ask Dr.
Hal one question
about the
magnetics of what
we might call
underground comics?
You know, he who
controls magnetism
controls the
universe.
And also your
mind as well.
Well, what about
magnetic underground
comics?
I don't think they
ever installed
magnets in them.
You could shoplift
underground comics
without being caught.
In fact, I think
you were expected
to.
There was a
special issue
of the fabulous
furry freak
brothers that was
printed with the
same magnetic ink
they put on dollar
bills, actually.
I'm talking about
a person shooting
a pig with a
Nazi helmet on
in 1949 or
something like that.
I think it's one of
the rarest things
I've ever found,
and I thought it
was one of the
first underground
comics in that
sort of vein.
Underground comics
from 1949?
Yes.
Well, as we know
from the great
film God's
Cartoonist, one
of the first
underground comic
artists was the
great Jack Chick.
He's still in
operation.
He's still putting
out his comic.
Those little
pamphlets.
You know, one time
I saw a parody of
a Chick tract.
It was called
The Other People.
Yes, the pagan
parody.
There are many
parodies of Chick
tracts, and there's
a guy in San
Francisco named
Bob Fowler, who is
the archivist of
all Chick tracts,
and he also knows
about all the
parodies, and there
are a number of
them out there.
There's a great
anti-Christian one,
for example, called
The Greatest Myth
Ever Told, and
there's one called
Atoms and Evil,
which is about
Alexander Shulgin
and other pioneers,
and they're all in
that lovely Jack
Chick format of
the little pamphlet
with, you know, a
black field and
then an image in
red and inside an
easy-to-digest comic
that you can read in
just the amount of
time that it takes
for a bowel movement.
And Jack Chick
created this
format.
Chicks dig
Chick.
Chicks.
Chick tracts
get read.
Design for
extra meditation.
of God's
Cartoonist.
The Cartoonist, by
the way, will be
at the sex day.
That's right, he
will.
That would be
Kurt von
Busse von
Kirsteiner.
The Nazi
subgenius will be
there.
And we'll have
a high old
time.
Do you remember
the Terry
Schiavo Jack
Chick parody that
I made?
Holy cow.
I made you
in Princess
Week.
Now there's a
hilarious subject
in this comic.
It's probably on
some site somewhere.
America's
Favorite Vegetable.
It's probably on
subgenius.com
somewhere.
But they won't
let you eat the
vegetables.
Yeah, that's the
meaning of the
phrase.
She's valid.
Ask any
vegetable.
Back in your
salad days.
Well, now we're
a little bit
older and a little
bit further on.
We're tilting
windward, I think.
It's 2005.
We've been coddling
down the pike all
these years.
There's some
wear and tear on
the old
book.
A little bit.
Hal, I actually
remember reading
the phrase,
he who controls
magnetism controls
the universe.
That's why I
quoted it.
In the Sunday
Papers.
From Chester
Gould.
Yes, Dick
Tracy.
It was a
Dick Tracy
bait.
And boy, did
that strip get
weird for a
It was always
weird, but it
got super weird
when you had
Moon Maid and
they went to
the moon and
the little kids
with antennas
running around.
Didn't Junior
marry Moon Maid?
Yes, Junior
Tracy married
the girl from
the moon who
was rather sexy
except for those
little antennas.
But you could
get used to
them.
The kids all
had them too.
Moon Maid?
It's the newest
fad is getting
antennas.
But as Chester
Gould got older,
he got weirder
and he was so
chuffed that he
invented the wrist
radio that he
started inventing
other even more
unlikely things
like the TV
set in the middle
of your stove.
Now mom can
cook and watch
TV.
It's a TV.
It's a stove.
It's a TV and
a stove.
And the whole
comic would be
taken up with
this.
There's no
forward motion.
forward motion
In somebody's
private senile
room only he's
drawing it as
vigorously as
ever with the
thick black
ink lines.
Well and think
of Jack Kirby
when they started
letting Jack Kirby
write his own
comics as he
became more
famous.
And you got
things like
Devil Dinosaur
and Moon Boy.
Yeah.
OMAC.
One Man
Army Corps.
Those are some
of the most
bulldada things
in the world.
Yes.
Now let's
consider that
the most
vigorous and
famous products
of Kirby and
Lee supposedly
were done
20, 30
years ago.
When you're an
old geezer you
can't be expected
to have the
spring of
youthful creativity
leap forth in
all its glory.
It oozes out
if it's there at
all.
So let's not
run down Kirby
for these
anemic later
creators.
Kirby himself
said that he
created all
this stuff
and all the
colorist and
the dot man.
Did their work
and somebody else
did the dialogue
and he just
became more of a
crazed idea man.
That's what I was
getting to.
The dialogue was
from Stan Lee
but first the story
would be drawn
by Kirby
and according to
Kirby Lee would
just come along
and write in the
captions and that
was his contribution.
So in that sense
he wrote the story
but in a real
architectonic sense
Jack King Kirby
had already created
the story by
drawing everything
and only Lee
came along
and wrote in
the slangy
snappy
yak that was
in all the
By the way
I have to
compliment you
on your use
of the word
architectonic.
That was
Well the real
understructure
you know my
meaning here.
Absolutely.
You know
architect meaning
master.
Architect is a
master builder.
Tectonic plates
are the things
from which the
earth is built.
The master builder
that over
pertaining to
a master builder.
Well it's hard
not to think of
the underlying
foundations
at a time when
very soon they'll
all be whisked
from under us
by like a table
cloth by a cheap
magician.
And the
don't knock off
the gin and
tectonic.
Well no the gin
will stay on the
table but the
table cloth will
be whisked away
if he performs
this illusion
correctly.
Yeah well all I
can say is if
thoughts had minds
or words had wings
then we could
actually control
our destiny.
Yeah and if
your grandmother
had wheels she'd
be a wagon.
I don't know
that handshake
much when you
were talking
about the
masonic handshake.
Well they put
their hands on
your wrist
and they
tickle tickle
and either you
punch them out
or you recognize
that they're a
mason.
Like Jackie
Mason.
It's a roll
of the dice
all right.
I'm talking
about America's
freedom and not
just freedom to
buy greasy
french fries
by the side
of the road.
And you know
we are free
to love Bob
we're free
to wait
for the day
when it's all
over.
But let's not
be too cautious
let's embrace
this full heartedly
and full bloodedly
and be giving
and not miserly
because we're all
going to need
each other's
comfort in the
terrible times
that lie ahead.
I comfort
myself pretty
well.
It usually
takes about
two and a half
minutes.
Oh really?
Well thank you.
I guess
I suppose
there's no point
dragging it
all out.
We only have
to put up
with this living
hell for
until July 5th.
Yes.
Yes that's
all.
And then it'll
be moved to
another planet.
Well actually
Princess we
and I owe
a certain number
of people
another festival
after that
and we'll
have to move
Starwood and
Wisteria onto
our escape
planet.
But you know
that is after
all a
just a continuation
like the cracking
of ice.
We can dump
them out into
space after
they've gotten
their show.
Yeah.
We got your
money Bob.
Yeah.
The ones that
aren't subgeniuses
they'll be
ejected
into space.
Or turned
into
love slaves
or something.
I want the
money honey.
Well that's
always an
interesting debate
amongst subgeniuses
is oh do we
keep them
for pets.
Right.
That's the
evangelical
the evangelicals
versus the
holocaustals.
Not to mention
Jehovah One's
witnesses.
Well we don't
want to
dissuade people
by talking about
our theological
minutia.
There is more
that we have
in common
than divides us.
We must be
ecumenical
in these
last days.
Reach out
with that
extended fist
that stark fist.
Reach out
and smite
the conspiracy.
Clock the conspiracy
on the noggin.
This is your
last chance.
If you must die
then here's what to do.
Jump in Bob's pipe
and let him
smoke you.
For you are all
the dottle
that rains on the
roofs like fire.
Please smoke me.
Please.
Smoke me.
Eat me.
Drink me.
Yeah sorry
little man.
It sounds like
a good time.
I mean.
Didn't the
who do that
song?
Yeah.
Smoke me.
It's not good enough
to live right on the lake.
No it's sort of
light me.
Light me.
Smoke me.
See me.
Inhale me.
Exhale me.
Be enlightened by me.
I thought that was
the door.
Yeah but it ended up
with we're not
gonna take it.
One little
pamphlet.
One little book.
That was Allison.
Allison Wunderland.
It was like a
skeeball machine
and then
everybody played
skeeball
and then we all
took a bath
and we
sure.
We played
a skeeball.
And then
after we took
a bath in
canned beans
we ran through
a field of
poppies and
ended up
in the
Emerald City.
That's what it was.
Okay.
You first.
Who would not
want to live like that?
So if they have
like poppy fields
surrounding the
Emerald City
does that mean
that Seattle
is now in
Afghanistan?
It should be.
Well if Earth
is Mars
nothing is
impossible.
Sure.
Have you ever
tried
Afghanistan food?
Pickles anyway?
The pickles?
Well they were
going to come
but we don't
have them
nor the amino acids
but we do have
the Evolution
Control Committee
with trademark
Gunderson.
Fat Mandy
I believe
from Pittsburgh.
Vera Defects.
I mentioned
Fat Free
and Monkey Hive
already.
There's a
cult of
veer
and of course
the ever
ever beloved
and always
incredible
Duke of Uke.
That's right.
Hail Caesar.
Hail you.
I have heard
him in elevators.
They have included
his works.
Did he elevate
your mood?
He did.
Wham, pam, pam, pam,
pam, pam.
I want to be
sedated.
Yeah.
He does the
nicest ukulele
versions of
songs like
Anarchy in the
UK.
I had him as a
special guest on
my show in San
Francisco.
He rocks the
audience with
his versions of
those old
punk stalwarts.
Sure does.
He's still got
the spiked haircut
and the big
goofy glasses
after the
years.
He looks like
Elvis Costello
on Lubrizol or
something.
He looks like
someone stole
his spleen and
gave it to
Prometheus or
some devil.
Well, he's not
spleenless.
I also heard
that there will
be an Ask
Dr. Howe.
Well, there
could be.
I'll be there.
You can ask
me for all the
good it'll do.
Sure.
Ask Dr. Howe.
All right.
Actually, I have
the brochure.
The brochure
was printed
today.
Actually, for a
complete, for a
complete listing
of some of these
interesting events,
please stay tuned.
Those will be
coming up after
the top of the
hour.
We need to
pause.
And, of course,
it goes without
saying that the
views and opinions
on this program
are not necessarily
those of WCSB
or Cleveland State
University, but I
kind of had to
say it anyway.
And don't have
to flip the CD.
We've got to
flip the disc and
then we're going
to flip the script.
So don't say
anything funny.
Ask away.
Don't say bad
words.
I don't know if
you all want to
hang on the line
for a minute or
if you want to
try calling back,
but we've got to
pause here for a
moment and we'll
be back.
Did you ever see
a blue dog eating
mayonnaise?
We ever killed a
gopher with a
stick?
Attract ourselves
to that question
when we return.
The saucers
are coming.
The saucers.