So, I was like, you got a new spot?
Reverend Stangy's back?
Yeah, yeah, finally back.
Finally back?
Finally, glad to be back in Cleveland.
You know, I...
Actually, we have a sad show tonight
because a famous comedian
who was a big influence
on a lot of the subgenius type of humor
died just a couple of days ago.
He wasn't somebody I knew,
but he was somebody that I felt like I knew, you know?
Yeah.
Okay, okay.
He's a member of a group called the Fire Sign Theater.
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay.
It happens.
That's what goes with being a life form.
Hey, we all gotta go.
Go, go, go.
What are we doing?
Oh, yeah.
Tonight on the show,
we're gonna have the Thumb Brothers,
Hangnail and Sneaky.
They're gonna be with us.
Wonderful, wonderful.
Oh, the I Ching for this evening.
We might as well get to this
in the slow part of the show here at the beginning.
Deliverance.
When heaven and earth deliver themselves,
thunder and rain set in.
When the thunder and rain set in,
the seed pods of all fruits, plants, and trees break open.
The time of deliverance is great indeed.
That's wonderful to hear.
Very good indeed.
The Crawford brothers are gonna be here tonight.
The Crawford brothers?
Broderick and Joan, yes.
It's gonna be a nice time.
There's a Russian poet.
He's gonna read Leaves of Grass.
Yeah, Ubon the Terrible.
Ubon.
Ubon the Terrible.
That's a German pronunciation.
Oh, there's gonna be a music.
There's gonna be a musical group here later on.
The Dreadful Great are gonna be here.
The Dreadful Great?
Yeah, Winston Churchill, Franklin Delano Roosevelt,
Harry Truman, Adolf Hitler, and Abraham Lincoln.
Is that Adolf Hitler I or Adolf Hitler II?
Both.
Both. All three of them.
Good evening.
This is Louis Marshman speaking for myself
and my thousands of fellow professionals
who, like myself, are responsible for speaking to you
as I am at this time.
We are all involved in a national movement
that is the result of a global news emergency
of such magnitude that only now can we pause for a moment
to distort its proportions back to our own limited perspective.
The credibility gap now stretches beyond the international dateline
so that lies fabricated in the foreign press
are repudiated in our local papers the day before they appear
in the country of their origin.
The advance of science now allows us to bounce our information
off the planet Saturn, but none of it has returned,
leaving our global home bereft of news.
And so, concerned citizens like myself sit here tonight
with absolutely nothing of any importance to say.
Then let it be said, not to enlighten, but to inform.
Our generation has achieved failure at the cost of its own success.
And our great-great-grandchildren are paying for that powerful failure.
But they're too young to work in the dark,
so we must lend them the little immense energy left
to help them shoulder that important task.
The world is now a place of fear.
We have learned to hoard despair and make it pay great dividends.
The shadow of a chicken in every pot.
The freeways jammed with empty holiday cars.
One hundred million television sets turned to face the wall.
Yes, a rich land with cream in the coffee bread lines in their palms.
And yet, we have to face the wall.
But the memory banks are closing,
because our youth and the young at heart refuse to gossip the good talk,
refuse to dance on the grid, refuse to even pretend to be duped.
And a nation that can't be duped can't be made fun of itself.
I, and every other mind sewn together in this great circle of world thought,
gave up the declining years of their boyhood,
beat off every desire and phantom lover,
to conjure up all the little people on the billboards you've loved to eat so much.
Crunchy Caramel, Mr. Peanut, Captain Crunch, Snappy Tom, Little Bite-Sized Godzilla.
They're the children of my career.
Throw them in the gutter, and you drown my breakfast.
So come on, let's be kids again.
Let's listen to the radio and spoil our appetites.
Let's put on daddy's shoes and invent the atom bomb.
Or at least let's say we did it.
Or at very least, let's start storing up some respect for the people whose job it is to tell us about it.
Actors and soldiers are people too, you know.
There's one at your door right now, reading your number.
Let him in.
Just because he's got a snappy uniform on doesn't mean he isn't a cripple.
Just because I'm talking to millions of you doesn't mean I'm not lonely.
So give us a dime.
Or give us a call.
But for God's sake, don't give us away.
Thank you.
And now back to the news.
This has been an important editorial from the management of this radio station.
You're normally such a slacker.
It's the first time you've heard of him.
Shoes for industry.
Shoes for the dead.
Hi, I'm Joe Beetz.
Hey, what chances does a returning deceased war veteran have for that good paying job, more sugar, and the free mule you've been dreaming of?
Well, think it over.
Then take off your shoes.
Now you can see how increased spending opportunities means harder work for everyone.
And more of it, too.
So do your part today, Joe.
Join with millions of your neighbors and turn in your shoes.
For industry.
Yes?
That was a nice break.
You have some correspondence?
Shall I read?
I could read finally after all three weeks of promising.
I shall read a Richard Brautigan poem.
Real fast and loud.
Fast and loud.
Let's hear it.
I like to think, in the sooner the better, of a cybernetic meadow where mammals and computers live together in mutually programming harmony like pure water touching clear sky.
I like to think, right now please, of a cybernetic forest filled with pines and electronics where deer stroll peacefully past computers as if they were flowers with spinning blossoms.
I like to think, it has to be, of a cybernetic ecology where we are free of our labors and joined back to nature, returned to our mammal brothers and sisters, and all watched over.
By machines of loving grace.
That's a nice idea.
I like his head.
He has a nice head.
Then I drunk a gene physic and got drunk.
I met Jake, my son.
And he says, Father we'll have a good time.
Here comes Mr. Brodeck.
He is an oakum fiend.
Smoke's oakum.
Every night he got a million dollars.
Last night he says, Father I feel bad.
I think I'll go to St. Louis.
Then he took a silver pencil filled with white water out of his pocket and shoot it in his arm and he got a million dollars.
And in two minutes, he was governor of New York.
One more shoot, and he would be president of the United States.
He gave me a shoot once.
I got so foolish, I paid the rent.
I go back to Yale with Peter Bergman.
And when I first got there, I connected up with the Yale Dramat.
And Peter wrote the lyrics for two musicals that I did while I was at Yale.
And we maintained a connection after Yale that eventually led to my getting together with him
in Los Angeles when I was out there after doing a show called The Amorous Flea, a musical there.
And I discovered he was the Wizard of Oz doing this late-night talk, counterculture, phone-in show
on KPFK, listener-supported radio.
And that's where I started playing with him on the radio.
Met the other two guys, Phil Lawson and David Osman.
We discovered we were all fire signs.
I'm a Leo.
He was a Sagittarian, as is David Osman.
And I was a Leo.
And Austin's an Aries.
So we quite foolishly named ourselves the Oz Fire Sign Theater,
which later just became the Fire Sign Theater.
It is a constant source of confusion and happiness to many people.
Now, patient, you have ten seconds to tell us what you've got and beat the Reaper!
I'm shaking feverishly.
My hands are all...
I'm turning yellow.
My God, I've got jaundice.
Jaundice it is!
Give it to me!
So when you first met him, do you remember what you thought about his personality?
Yes!
I mean, he was bursting with creativity and smart as a whip and very gregarious and outgoing
constantly all his life.
And that never changed.
He was just the kind of person that you liked being around because he was...
always in...
He was informative and funny.
Peter was also very lefty and very opinionated.
Yeah, when...
At Yale, he was like a...
He got a B.A. in radical ideas.
What can I say?
He was a Rhodes Scholar at some point.
You know, I don't know all of his history, but I know that he was involved in studies of labor and politics.
And he remained fixated with that vision all his life.
Now, according to Wikipedia, it says that Peter claimed to...
You've coined the word love-in in 1967.
Yeah.
Yeah, he had a...
This is part of the promotions for Radio Free Oz.
And he had an event in Elysian Park.
I participated in it, pretending to be a Russian expatriate poet named Yuri Gafnov.
And he drew a huge crowd, thousands of people.
But he did.
He called it the love-in, coined the phrase so far as I know.
Yes, friends.
As you probably...
Peter Bergman of the Firesign Theater boarded the saucers prematurely.
On March 8th, he died of complications from leukemia.
He was born in 1939 and was 72.
And he was doing Firesign podcasts up until the day he died.
Friends, the Firesign Theater kept me alive when I had no girl for that.
And they accidentally gave me a career to boot.
Speaking for all the old-timey radio subgeniuses,
we probably owe Firesign Theater more than we do Robert Anton Wilson,
the Zap comic artist, Ray Harryhausen, or the Mothers of Invention.
Maybe even as much as the old Warner Brothers cartoon people.
And that's saying something.
The weird Saint Jeroen of Amsterdam told us on tape,
While you're alive, you better make a...
lot of noise, because when you die, you shut up like hell.
Saint Peter Bergman lived that way.
Praise Peter.
His biography is on the FiresignTheater.com website.
Theater spelled with R-E at the end, not E-R.
And I'm going to read it.
I didn't know a lot of this.
Peter Bergman was born in Cleveland, Ohio.
The day after Russian invaded Finland and the day before Winston Churchill,
Peter's hero, turned 65.
Peter's comic career began in the 6th grade,
writing comic poems for his mother for library class,
a penchant that developed into co-authoring the 9th grade humor column,
The High Hatters, and his own creation,
Look and See with Peter B., for his high school newspaper.
Peter's audio career was launched in high school
as an announcer on the school radio station,
the radio system, from which he was banished
after his unauthorized announcement
that the Chinese communists had taken over the school
and that a, quote, mandatory voluntary assembly
was to take place immediately.
Russell Rupp, the school principal,
promptly relieved Peter of his announcing gig.
And this is very similar to my high school radio history, by the way.
Rupp was the inspiration for the principal poop character
on Don't Crush That Dwarf.
Hand me the pliers.
While attending high school,
Peter formed his first recording group called The Four Candidates,
turning out a single titled Attention Convention,
parodying the 1956 Democratic Convention.
It received airplay in Cleveland and Pittsburgh.
At college, Peter was managing editor of the Yale Comedy magazine.
He wrote the lyrics for two musical collaborations
with Austin Pendleton,
a close friend, incidentally.
of Princess Wee's family,
both of which starred Phil Proctor.
He graduated as a scholar of the House in Economics
and played point guard for the liberal basketball league,
whose members have since lost their dribble,
but not their politics.
Peter spent two graduate years at Yale
as a Carnegie Teaching Fellow in Economics
and as the Eugene O'Neill Playwriting Fellow
at the Drama School.
Quite a fellow.
After a six-month stint as a grunt
in the U.S. economy,
he went to Berlin on a Ford Foundation fellowship.
There he wrote and directed his first film, Flowers,
and connected with the living theater,
a major influence on his art.
Peter worked briefly in London with Spike Milligan
and the BBC
of Goon Show Famousness
before returning to America in 1966,
where he secured a nightly radio show
on Pacifica's KPFK in Los Angeles.
Radio shows were his first,
Radio Free Oz,
around which the Fireside Theater coalesced and gestated.
Peter coined the term Love Inn in 1967
and threw the first such event in April
of that same year in Los Angeles.
That event ultimately drew a crowd of some 65,000 people
blocking freeways for miles.
This so impressed Gary Usher of Columbia Records
that he offered the Fireside Theater
their first record contract.
In the 1970s,
1970s, Peter diversified his comic career as president of a film equipment company.
They made the first affordable flatbed editing table, the Showcron, which I used for years on
my day job as a film cutter. He also helped produce a machine for viewing angiocardiograms
and measuring the blockage of the arteries of the heart. In the 1980s, Peter turned to film and
tape, producing the comic feature J-Men Forever with Phil Proctor, as well as producing television
shows that featured members of Firesign. Starting in 1995, Peter began turning the country as a
quote, high-tech comedian, unquote, delivering lectures and keynote speeches to computer-oriented
companies and conventions. He worked on publishing the website for one of the candidates for mayor
of Los Angeles. His latest venture, in association with St. David Osman,
started in the summer of 2010, the podcast revival of Radio Free Oz. So ends the bio.
Thanks for everything, Peter, and I do mean everything. Were it not for you and your friends,
there'd probably be no Church of the Subgenius, but not with me running it, and possibly no me
at all. We only met once, but you were there when I needed you, long, long before that happened.
I owe you big time. Catch you on the flip-flop.
It's all right, it's all right. The electrician called the plimey.
Ah, I have an address.
You do have an address?
I have an address where one can send away and buy the best hashish and cannabis indus.
Ah!
No repeats. That's it.
No repeats?
That's it.
You aren't saying anything more.
Best hashish and cannabis indus.
Did anybody win the contest yet?
Oh, did anybody win the contest?
No, we have a few letters.
We have been having letters from lots of people.
Here's one, for example.
Gentlemen, never lower Tilly's pants.
Mama might come home.
Commonly thought to mean Vietnam is a TV show.
Actually, it's slang for spiteful.
gyrose gesticulate electrically.
No.
That's not it, and neither was anything else.
Which twins the clone?
Well, the answer may surprise you, but not...
Salamander.
If you say this enough, a terrarium should slowly start to form around you, within you,
without you.
Around it by a thin, thin, thin, all-digital shell, and inside, it's delicious.
In fact, these are the only genuine, genetically modified, semi-organic whole beef halves endorsed
by the Firesign Theater themselves.
Don't believe me?
I wouldn't.
Just ask this one here.
Well, you know, Harv, the greatest thing about these little honeys is not...
Here, look at this.
Just pull the wings off, and they don't scream too much.
They're the perfect snack for Todd or Maude to accompany the next broadcast of the Firesign
Theater Fools in Space on XM Satellite Radio.
And, uh, when would this be heard?
A clem?
I don't know, but, uh, I'll bet this announcer does.
The richly textured sounds of the Firesign Theater's Fools in Space can be heard Saturdays
at 9 p.m. in the East, 6 p.m. in the West, Tuesdays at 3 p.m. in the East, 12 noon in
the West, and Thursdays at 3 a.m. in the East and midnight in the West.
And to aid those who are legalists, perhaps the next quadrennial manual should have printed
on the cover in large letters, this is not God's word, but a necessary.
Crutch.
Here, here.
Time for that.
What?
This was on the table when I walked in tonight.
I gotta watch what they leave on the table.
Why buy a farm, Orgy?
Now that you're out of high school and you've come here to the bank to find out what to
do with the rest of your miserable little life, I'd like to ask you the question that
all financial counselors are asking people like you, why buy a farm?
Mr. Jones, why should I buy a farm?
I'm glad you asked, Orgy.
Some men buy farms for a livelihood, some for preservation of investment capital, and some
for a spatula.
Orgy?
For preservation.
Other men want farms because of a strong desire to return to the modernized version of the
environment they lived in and enjoyed as a boy.
We're flowing through the estate over your grandmother's paisley shawl.
I like the way you talk.
Hello, dear friends.
This is Eric Burton.
Yes, they did take away our music, but now you can have it back on these three wonderful
voice prints of the city.
The 60s.
All your magic memories of flying over the music capitals of the world will come rushing
back with the first twang of a lead guitar.
Now listen to all the monsters of the 60s at once.
The Rolling Who, Derek and the Taylors, Clive Beadle, Bing Crosby Stills and Ogden Nash.
Songs like I've Got My Hand on Your Mouse, Helicopter 59, Tight Shoes, I'll Be Gumping
You, and hundreds of others.
Goodness gracious.
Great God almighty.
It's like having now right in your living room.
So don't wait till the midnight hour.
Send 15 seconds in code or credit to Rocker Roll Memory Bank, Hong Kong, New York, York.
In the light of that, I should like to read a revolutionary statement for our time, which
I found here.
That's the bourgeoisie.
March for one.
Okay.
Here it is.
No power to anybody.
That's right, drughead.
That whenever any form of government becomes destructive of these ends, it is the right
of the people to alter or abolish it and to institute new government, laying its foundation
on such principles and organizing its powers in such form as to them shall seem most likely
to affect their safety and happiness.
That's what it says right there.
You know what, drughead?
So I think it's time.
Why change it?
Yes.
You know what you can do?
What kind of a man is it?
You can forget it.
You remember that old high school phrase, forget it, kid.
Well, that's what you can do.
If you forget the government, it'll go away.
Right.
For an Irishman like myself, it's rewarding to see a potato like you in such a position
of industrial responsibility.
And now, ladies and gentlemen, and particularly the ladies, this station takes great pleasure
in bringing you that little Frenchman who's been tickling your face.
The palates all over this universe.
Our own fresh chef.
Hello, lady.
Take off your dress, slip into someone comfortable, and tie up your little apron.
Be ready for some French cooking.
And I'm your host, the French fresh chef.
Today, ladies, thank you.
Bonjour.
Bonjour, chérie.
Today, ladies, potatoes in syrup.
You will need one half pound.
One half pound of slag.
This is skinned slag.
That is, you know, you mustn't pick the pulpy ones, although it's spotted with gray.
It's needlessly expensive, and you won't be satisfied.
We need an ounce of very sweet, dry, crystallized sugar.
Two pounds of potatoes, soft with yellow skin.
And, of course, wine of sufficient quantity.
We are now ready to begin step one, the peeling.
Take it off.
Take it all off.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Now, step two.
Integrately, ladies, gently.
Disengage and take the potatoes into small dimensions, like this.
Let them to cook during ten minutes in boiling wine and hot oil, lightly perfumed.
I'm using my favorite wine, of course, on the Thunderbird label, Nippon Cadet, Oat 69.
Now, step three, ladies.
Taste them.
Mmm.
And pour the potatoes in cold water to make goose pimples.
Ah!
Good.
Now, test them again.
Then, and this is very important, that you do it loving them.
You must ep-loosh them.
Finally, slip them into a casserole.
Cover it with this crystallized sugar.
Oh, the entire potatoes, please.
Remember now, cover them with water and let it set for sufficient time to be very sweet,
just until the potatoes become transparent.
Serve them cold.
Like dessert.
That's it, ladies.
Eat hearty.
And until next week, my sylvan beauties, this is the fresh chef.
Oh!
Saying bon appetit.
Ginsberg!
And this is the grand gCAR.
Conservatist time!
No problem!
Have a good weekend.
And I've wanted you this year and to pay trás Healing Greece where ever.
Now, in misty desert with And the
GD that
may
brick
That's me.
To
What you
heart
You
Can
see our boy at the back.
Dog food for the doggy?
Well, doggone it,
we've got all six varieties
of martyr brand kidney and beef offal.
Talk to Charlie Cranepool,
Ed's dad,
at our liquor department
about Choice USDA
bourbon and rump roast
cocktail party mix.
Last and least,
there's plenty of seasick
fresh produce
at our vegetable counter.
Don't worry about the flies,
we won't weigh them.
So weary shoppers,
take the lift out of life
and drop your load
on the giant toad.
We give double discounted
multiple identity stamps!
Oh, this is the department
of Christmas presents
I forgot to give David.
Wow.
Down Mamory Lane.
For you, David.
Phil Yottamotto.
A small cellophane bag
of what I think are
Chinese non-psychedelic mushrooms.
Labeled Cloud Ears.
Cloud Ears?
Cloud Ears.
It was the war
against the cloud clam.
That was the booty.
Oh, that's nice.
Being sold now in Chinatown
in Los Angeles.
I'll pin it up above my desk
along with the rest of the ears.
Right.
Thank you.
As ears go by.
It's an old...
Come in.
Huh?
I'm not expecting this.
Oh.
It's U-Band the Terrible.
Hello.
Oh.
Hi there.
Send me over.
Clayton.
Thank you, thank you,
thank you, thank you.
Maledets, Tavareschi.
Oh, it's so nice
to have you here.
Prekrasna.
How are you, Terrible?
Oh, wonderful.
Listen, I've got
some great poems
from the Russian Underground
that I'd like to read
for you today.
Prekrasna.
How are the subways?
Horror show.
What a horror show.
And they're just like
dvoryets, you know,
which is the Russian word
for palaces.
They have magnificent statues
of strong men
and beautiful women.
Not necessarily in that order.
Strong men
and beautiful women?
Yes, and pictures of Lenin
and all those other
groovy cats.
Lenin all hang out,
isn't that what it says?
Yes, that's what it says
in Russian.
Prekrasna.
And I hang them
on the grocery wall.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Well, folks,
what can I do for you
today?
Mr. Liverface,
you're a butcher.
You're up to your knees
in fresh-killed meat
every day.
What's the best food
for my dog?
Give him what every dog
loves to eat.
Cat.
Cat?
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
No, I'm serious.
There's enough proteins
and minerals
in a teeny kitty's body
to keep a big dog
healthy and happy
all day.
And there's a full litter
of kitties
in every can
of my Mr. Liverface
dead cat dog food.
Well, that's good.
That's all right
for our little doggy
Ronnie, Mr. L.
But what do we feed
our cat?
Dog.
Not Ronnie.
Not Ronnie, wife bait.
But there's a full pound
of ground pound hound
in every can
of Mr. Liverface
dead dog cat food.
We'll take one of each.
You are one of each.
Oh, dogs and cats,
cats and dogs,
your pets can eat them all.
They run through my yard.
I whop them
with a stick
and I hang them
on the grocery wall.
Oh, oh, oh.
Well, I think it's wonderful
for a Friday.
I really got into that, too.
Everybody should go by
and see that.
Fried chicken stand
right in front of the old zoo,
you know, and you get
these weird legs,
but they're all covered
with batter.
That is a chicken, chicken.
That's hippopotamus
as they serve.
Oh, come on.
Oh, yeah.
Every once in a while
you'll get them.
A tongue stick
that weighs 800 pounds,
I tell you, this is chicken.
It's got batter on it.
An ibex.
$1.90. Half pound of ibex. Something that looks a lot like a sheep head, right?
Right.
Or a zebra foot.
They got a little batter on it.
This is a leg.
You want to know
how the Eskimos feel about it?
This is how the Eskimos
feel about it.
The Eskimos have a word for it.
Right.
Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun.
The greatest peril of life
lies in the fact
that human food
consists entirely
of souls.
Hmm.
All the creatures
that we have to kill and eat,
all those that we have to strike down
and destroy
and make clothes for ourselves,
have souls like we have.
Souls do not perish
with the body
and which must therefore
be propitiated
lest they be destroyed.
Lest they should revenge themselves,
Sonos,
for taking away their bodies.
Why without propitiating
next to the eagle
and thinking about that?
Man, Jesus.
Souls flowing everywhere.
It's a constant flow of souls.
What is?
When propitiating.
Propitiating?
Yeah.
There's a...
Are you drunk again, Pastor?
Yes.
Yes, I am.
You've gotten
bummed in the vestry again.
Yes, I am.
No, I got a bum in the vestry.
Yes.
I got a bum in the vestry
and I got a...
I was one of the brave soldiers.
I was doing picketing.
Picked so many chickens,
I was afraid
to go to bed at night.
Yeah.
I was afraid
I would lay there.
While I was fighting
at the Battle of Santiago,
15 balls pierced
my manly bosom.
And didn't kill you?
No.
How was that?
They were codfish balls.
Oh, man.
One ball went right through me
and killed another man.
They had me arrested
for murder.
Murder?
They said it was through me.
The other man got killed.
I was where the bullets
were the thickest.
They were just rolling
all over me.
Yes, there was a hole
in the middle of the wall.
In the bottom
of the ammunition wagon.
Poor Vintage Schumer.
Uh, the...
All the passengers
was heaving.
Yeah?
And if that wasn't enough,
the captain gave orders
for the ship to heave, too.
Oh!
Har har har har har!
That's one of those...
Oh, my God.
That's a good one.
My God.
That's a...
That's a good one.
You got your job.
No, no, Phil.
Phil.
You got your job.
You're stuck.
Phil, Phil, Phil.
It's a good one.
You're driving good.
You are...
You are thinker.
You are so smart.
You see...
You are...
You got surprise for you.
You got the biggest surprise
coming.
That's a good one.
You are...
Oh, my God.
I get you good.
That's it.
Get you good.
Oh.
That's another language lesson
from the Firesign Theatre Hour Hour.
He's got to drive home
through sector 13
to get to where you live
in an hour now.
Yeah, you got to talk
like that in sector 13.
Yeah, you got to...
Oh, you're not getting
my car, you big surprise.
You can ride with me.
All right.
Easy, easy rider.
Those of you going through
12, you'll have to use
the old Peter Lorre accent
to get through the night.
That's right.
Sector 12.
Let me through.
I've got to get home.
My children are burning.
You go through there
and you get to sector 11.
Ronald Coleman is the image
in sector 11
to get through the city.
There's a far, far better thing
I do than I have ever done.
Tis a far, far better world
I leave than I have ever left.
My father, oh,
I'm ready.
Conflicted to him only by marriage.
There's a comma in there.
It doesn't apply...
That's right.
That's it.
Then you're home.
There's Robert Q. Lewis.
I think.
Everybody listened to Robert Coleman.
Robert Q. Kelly.
Greetings humanoids
and hominids.
There is good news.
Kimmy beans р
Burns king's ees
dialogot topabees
Per Ubu, kindest and cruelest of all kings,
bestow upon you regular hearings of the Fireside Theater's
Fools in Space.
Saturdays at 9 p.m. in the East, 6 in the West,
Tuesdays at 3 p.m. in the East, noon in the West,
and Thursdays...
Yes, yes, yes, thank you, your lordship.
Thursdays at 3 a.m. in the East, midnight in the West,
only on XM Comedy Channel 150.
Up yours, too.
Dialogue lesson number 72 from New Vaudeville Jokes.
Oh, come on, man. I haven't seen that. I know, I know.
Seen what?
The cars in the little cubes.
Yeah, the visions. Everybody has a movie.
I saw them in a movie.
I have dreams about people throwing long metal spears now, man.
When I go to bed at night, just before I go to bed,
I put myself in some place like a fantasy world.
And as I begin to drift off,
sometimes I see myself liked with Gandalf
and making the trip against the darkness,
and now I've got this thing with the spears.
Oh, yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, metal porto.
Piki, piki, piki, piki, piki.
Hey!
Piki, piki, piki, come and get it.
Come and get it.
Laugh a minute in the pork barrel.
Here we go down the Primrose path,
Gonna open up that door.
that never closes and visit with our good, kind, Buddha friends,
Mutton Chops at the Mutton Chop Shop.
Hey, Mutton Chops!
That's right.
That's what happened to the Indians.
Their virility went down the drain.
They didn't even have modern plumbing.
Ah, mutt.
It's a condition of the peddling system.
That's what it is.
You know, the Depression's hurt everyone.
Even the mills have closed down.
They did?
I didn't know that.
Oh, yeah.
They moved out.
They left the furniture and everything.
Oh, my goodness.
The streets, you know.
We know the streets.
The streets?
Well?
They told me they were heading for Bird City to go into the headache business.
Oh, well, you know, frankly, I always thought the little mills boy was a little soft in the head, you know, I thought.
Don't say.
No, I just did.
What makes you say that, Chops?
Well, the writers.
Well, I can agree with you.
Oh, that's good.
That's what it says here, anyway.
You know, just the other day he come in here to steal gumballs,
and he bought this big container of chocolate ice cream, you know?
Yeah.
No, he stands there and he takes the top off in the container, see?
Yeah, yeah.
Then he pushes his face right in the ice cream, see?
Standing there right in front of me, and he says,
Look, I've invented the spoon.
Uh-huh.
He's crazy, all right.
Crazy as a loon.
Yeah, you should have thrown him out, you know.
I did throw him out.
You did throw him out?
That serves him right.
Oh.
Oh, Mr. Mott.
Oh, Mr. Chops.
Oh, well.
Here comes Mrs. Gunderson.
Mrs. Gunderson.
Yeah, who that is.
Mr. Mott.
Oh, right all the way up.
Oh.
Do you?
All the way up Spine Hill.
Well, well, well.
Just here, let me rest my arm here on the...
You just sit down there, Mrs. Gunderson.
I'm looking for some liver.
Liver, are you?
I'd like two pounds of liver and a crock of urine, if I could please.
Oh, just a second, Terry.
Before you get to that, Mott, would you hand me some of those police-slung shots and billies?
Oh, well, yes.
Oh, yes.
They're right over here.
And I can take care of that with you.
You take care of old Mrs. Gunderson over there, okay?
Yeah, yeah.
The very...
Mrs. Gunderson's liver.
I'll get those police hooks.
What were those?
Police-slung shots and billies.
Yeah, I can...
I can...
She can find that.
How about get a couple of decoys, Ducks, while you're back there?
Oh, yes.
I'll just sit down here on the classics.
Yes, sure.
Are these lard containers supposed to be here, Chops?
That's Vaseline.
Lard containers.
No, no.
That's the cow Vaseline.
What about the paprika?
The cow Vaseline.
What about the paprika there?
Oh, this paprika, Hungarian warm, it goes next to the chives, freeze-dried.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
And I forgot to tell you now, we need a reorder, you know, on number 237.
The very...
Oh!
Have you got...
Have you got any batteries for the electric belts you sold me?
Oh, you...
You've been wearing...
You've been wearing them electric belts?
Yes!
Oh!
Or do they do anything for your...
For your manly virility?
Yeah, for my...
They do.
Yes!
Oh, I've been...
How many of those can you get for like $10, which is what I got to spend on them?
Electric belts?
Electric belts, that's what I want.
Well, look, here's a 295 peerless vapor bath cabinet.
Oh, yeah.
Like our brown bath cabinet number two.
Or maybe a milk oil sheep dip.
I think that we should have some of those.
Do you have any low hawks?
Low hawks?
No, I don't, Mrs. Feberstam.
I'm afraid that we ate them all.
Oh, no.
Yes, well, times have been hard.
We sent out for an order of slug festers, and we got back instead those car hooks.
Oh, listen, baby Timmy's got the dropsy on his eyes.
Tell me something.
Yes, I'll tell you anything.
I understand that your grandmother's strung out.
Strung out, yes.
Yeah, I walked by her house the other day.
I noticed she's walking around.
She's got all clothes.
She's hanging on all the lines.
I've been out there for over a month.
That's because she's got the weeps.
Is that what it is?
She's walking around the house naked, you know.
Yeah, that's right.
Weeping out of every pore in her body.
Well, I hope she gets better.
I hope she gets better.
Oh, just a minute now, bud.
Listen, that's, um, uh...
Inovner, I thought you were supposed to be back at the smokehouse smoking.
Why, don't hit on me, Mrs. Fendon.
You're the only slave I've got.
Well, I'd come in to see if you got any junior warden's females.
Or pills for female disease.
Nabner, Nabner, that's what you come in here for.
Little Nabner.
Well, maybe you could give me some of that Dr. Hammond's knife and brain pills.
Is this for your mistress there, Nabner?
Yeah, I'd like a couple half dozen of genuine German herb laxative tea, too.
Well, that's up on the top there.
You get it up there, you can find it.
Mr. Mutt, would you pick me up a cup?
A couple of gross police-slung shots and billets.
Oh, we sold those already.
They's already gone, I'm afraid.
Mr. Mutt, this lever is spotted.
Oh, it's all right, as long as it's not gray.
I mean, I'd like one of them double-action revolvers.
I think I'd like one of them new-sized double-action revolvers.
Well, listen, we got to get some new ones.
I think maybe I'd like a couple of those.
Well, there's a gross of them up there.
...frontier and target revolvers.
There's no way he's out there in L.P.D.
I can't even move.
That's why I'm here.
Oh, by the way, if I have time, I should mention that NPR show with the Church of the
Subgenius interview has come out.
And it's not bad.
It's part of the show called To the Best of Our Knowledge, which you can find at ttbook.org
and search for Ivan Stang Church Subgenius.
You can hear it and download it there.
I was pleasantly surprised, because out of a 40-minute interview, they kept my mentions
of puzzling evidences and Susie's shows.
And there's a nifty little weird mix near the end.
With clips from old hour of Slack, including Lonesome Cowboy Dave and Reverend Televangela.
As I predicted, they removed my mentions of Dr. Drummond, Dr. Howell, and other major
co-subfounders.
Thank you.
And now back to this.
Hey, I get it.
You're not the professor anymore, you down.
I'm not.
This is a free university, you bum.
All right, if I'm not the professor anymore, then who's the professor?
Well, who wants to wear the hat?
Is it something else?
Who wants to carry on the great tradition of education?
You bums, you kids.
I'm dropping out.
I am running for president.
President of the United States.
Do I have to listen to this?
Leadership and power is deformed and abnormal.
Let's hear it.
Power must be the element in all the people.
Thank you, Jesus.
Leadership must be addressed to all the people.
And the president must be curious to lead them.
Keep power as an atmosphere, an in and out stream.
Our good feelings about people.
Some really fine growth.
Apply leadership to life giving, greater existence and rapid growth.
It's Japanese.
Sincerity of power and the leadership with enthusiasm.
Eats electricity.
The people's desires are simple.
Lasers stop him not.
Whole towns in water.
They need no fears, no hate, no doubt.
Visions of ending.
No envy to waste their power on.
All town surprised.
They want poise, enthusiasm, sincerity like their body of power.
As a wonderful backbone.
Fear and cattle fall down together.
No meat.
To make life hold.
To indicate the magnitude of life.
Then to change this power into leadership.
Power makes our wants in taps and shakes.
Thank you, Robert.
That's graphs in proportion.
Thank you, buddy.
Leadership positions are body in our hands.
Thanks, John.
And our wants are acceptable.
And thank you, man.
Perhaps a source in waiting for the electrician or someone like him for the politician's speech
about three quarters of the way through the record.
I, as president, the news press.
Power like a drum and leadership like a violin.
All doubt needs is the change of ideas.
Take enthusiasm as an example.
Enthusiasm has the ideas of certainty, faith, realize, and optimism.
Pick out any idea.
What are you talking about?
Compare ideas.
What?
With the one idea left, you have no doubt.
And without a doubt, we have enthusiasm.
Yes.
As the unusual idea in good leadership, it revamps leadership to the—
Who am I?
And inflate its power in the right element, our kind of enthusiasm.
What is reality?
I was talking yesterday.
It's as easy as a bridge.
With Bobby.
Power and leadership like a twin.
And I would say here on the astral planet forever, if you want to.
Of the United States of America.
Yeah, and they said, well, we did it once upon a time.
My name is Ed Groves.
Yeah.
what I've been playing comes from the fourth episode of the Firesign Theater Radio Hour Hour
from February 15, 1970, when I was in the 11th grade. I got it from the book and MP3 collection
Duke of Madness Motors, assembled by Reverend Taylor Jessen, and available from Negative Land's
Sealand Records, negativeland.com or firesigntheatre.com. This contains Firesign's
first three years of shows from 1970 to 72. The newer sounding promos for the now defunct XM Radio
were written and produced with the Firesigns by our very own Reverend Bleepo Abernathy,
who's usually the voice that introduces the Hour of Slack. He's deservedly proud of how well their
work meshed. XM, however, was too pink for Firesign for me.
Oh, and this is a good place for me to read an excerpt from that book, Duke of Madness Motors.
Quote,
Yesiree, friends, these guys are some funny. Definitely ha-ha funny, but also funny dramatic,
funny poetic, funny dada. It's movies for the mind that have only ever been matched by the
likes of Ken Nordean, Gene Shepard, and Joe Franchi.
You can hear the tradition continuing every Friday morning on Negative Land's Over the Edge
series on KPFA and shows from the Church of the Subgenius, like Puzzling Evidence and The Hour
of Slack. Where this kind of radio survives in America, it does so only through the grace of
a similar comedo-religious ecstasy and probably the fact that the host isn't being paid.
The best shows in this bulldada format, even though they may have been on the air for decades,
still carry through every minute of every hour a whiff of what was in the air when Firesign was
broadcasting in 1970. If not necessarily the scent of the medicinal herb the boys were so fond of,
then at least a general and lasting feeling that the person behind the microphone
can't quite believe that he's getting away with this shit.
That was from Duke of Madness Motors, that segment by Taylor Jessen, Reverend Taylor Jessen.
When we announced Bergman's death in Subgenius Internet Land, there were many poignant responses,
of which I shall now read a few in Dr. Memory of Pete. Reverend Louie Louie said,
sometimes you beat the reaper, sometimes the reaper beats you. Let's all ritually let the air
out of our shoes in tribute to one of the originals that made it all possible. Joe Provo said,
as long as we inflate his so he can cross the river,
sticks. And Reverend Felix Automaton said, I shall fly my fly at half mast. Unknown said,
I've got a case of Bear Whiz beer and every one I pop will be raised to the memory of Mr. Bergman.
Good night, clown prince. Jay Lee said, there's one less bozo on this bus.
Bill Trujillo said, back from the shadows again. Rick Bell said,
waiting for the electrician no more. Goodbye, my friend. Al Bryant said, Peter is gone,
but Kenny G still lives to blight our lives. Can't fair. How can you be in two places at
once when you're not anywhere at all? Morgan Lewington said, shoes for the dead.
Blake Michener said, pretty much everything I heard of Firesign on the Hour of Slack was
exceptionally good.
Bob is smoking him now as it must eventually be for us all. Arthur Ratnick said, he is certainly
embarking on a journey that may well change his life forever. Kathy Thomas said, he's already
beatified, so his saint titles settled. Reverend Mark Morey said, in a just universe,
this would be as newsworthy as the passing of Bob Dylan will be. Jeff Sykes said,
thanks to them, the letter E will always stand for excellent, and I will never run out of gas.
Congratulations, Peter, on making your escape to the pleasure saucers. We'll miss you.
Michael Moon Bear said, meet you at Bob's Berserko Lounge.
Katahdin Legume said, R.I.P. Stan Lee. Thanks for Batman.
And if you want to say goodbye,
you can go to FiresignTheatre.com slash Peter Bergman.
And if you look at YouTube under Peter Bergman Firesign, do a little search, you'll see a
wonderful video tribute or two. At some Starwood several years ago, a bunch of us performed as the
Firesign clones and reenacted three of the classic albums on stage, reading from the scripts in
Firesign Theatre's big book of plays.
If you had a lasting memory of the story and what people were saying the story was to you,
you've got to put it in front of your eyes.
What you're reading is about,
the inspiration that comes from your own beliefs,
from your own personal 느낌이 andthan you'rebank.
From your own topic to any other topic,
the story's going to be the next one.
This is a two-line line from Mark bemis,
Hysterical yoga, yuck-yuck, yoke of egg, egg shell, ego shell, yoke, new yoke, literally the sleeping servant.
God bless Gary Snyder.
Juleps were first invented, as I suppose, in Arabia, and my reason is because the word julep is an Arabic word.
It signifies only a pleasant potion, as is vulgarly used by such as are sick and want help,
or such as are in health and want no money to quench their thirst.
Let me give you that address again, friends, for the best hashish and cannabis in dukes.
Here, right?
No, it's FCC time.
Space charge, a gathering of electrons near the cathode of a vacuum tube.
You know, radio.
Okay, it's time for lids of grass again.
My business has gone to the wall. What business are you in?
I'm a paper hanger.
Oh, 1934.
Yeah, ach tun yuk tun, we all scream.
Putsch off, buster.
Putsch off, right. Beer back in a minute.
Okay, Peter. All right, everybody.
Shot the principal and made a movie.
Goodbye.
Time once again for the Howl of the Wolf movie.
Today's feature, High School Madness, has been preempted in order that we may bring you the 13th annual Awards Show Awards Awards Show.
The award-winning awards show that awards awards to outstanding awards show.
And for our awards show awards, awards show pre-show.
Which, incidentally, has coveted more than just...
Just a few awards.
We switch you live to our correspondent, Manny Milk, who is standing by foaming at the mouth at the San Luis Obispo Poe Buckers Foam Dome.
Manny.
Seems like there might be some technical difficulty with our foam dome.
Oh, Manny's got bad leverage.
Oh, it's swell. That leaves us free to talk about...
Yes, sir.
A foam that starts with an F.
Oh, a fire sign theater.
Oh, yes.
Those madcap, wacky rapscallions have traded in their goofballs for sensible shoes.
And have...
Organized themselves to the point where they now do a live show.
Can you believe it? Every month.
There's another fire sign theater. Fools in Space again.
Real soon.
On XM Comedy 150.
And, uh, he wouldn't have any of those little growth clusters around, would you, Mike?
No, that's...
Ed.
Stop torturing me, Ethel.
Saturday nights, Tuesday afternoons, and in the wee hours, Thursday morning.
Only on XM Comedy 150.
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho.
Well, golly, what'll they think of next?
Them fire sign theater fools in space fellas ain't really going away.
No, no, they just set in a spell.
They just grab your corncob, do the same.
It's XM Comedy 150 right here.
I'm sitting on my corncob.
Because we're subgeniuses.
Subtitling by SUBS Hamburg
My friends are all crazy.
They're mad as loons.
They talk all at once.
It's a hundred tunes.
You hear them at night as you push down the highway
Like loons landing, elusive loon fly away
And oh, can it be true
Y'all feel free to just join in
That there's no rest for the wicked
And oh, peace for us too
Amazing what sounds you can get out of a banana
Now the laughers and screamers, their cross talk is incredible
It's all you can do to believe they're inedible
And policemen and doctors hover round the edges
As they drag in new converts and make them sign pledges
And oh, can it be true
Well, that there's no rest for the wicked
No peace for us too
Now me and my sweetheart have tried to escape
We're secretly in love with each other
And we're sending it out to all the men here
Don't you talk all at once
So you'll wind up right here
And oh, can it be true
That there's no rest for the wicked
And oh, peace for us too
Peace for us too
Alright, one more verse
A passage of loons to their home in the sky
Don't tempt me a bit
But think I'll pass it right by
So listen up friends now
You've heard my sad tune
Don't be tempted to talk all at once like a loon
And oh, can it be true
That there's no rest on the wicked
No peace for us two
Y'all sound beautiful
Well, I don't know
I don't know how far out in space you have to get to get that far out, friends
Hey, that's quality on this show, you know
Beyond the orbit of the asteroids
We're lucky we're sponsored, I tell you that, Hilario, you know
Now that football's been outlawed by the interstellar console
There's things in my genes
There's some part of my codon that says, thanks, I did it
And you know, I still want to go back and make it happen
I can't
That song, Loons
Was by Phil Austin
From Year of the Rat album
Yes, friends
Radio Free Oz is off the air
And you better get used to it, kids
This trend of large mammals dying
Has actually been going on for some time
It's funny how indestructible and immortal
Most people, including me
Feel when they're young
On the one hand, when I was like 25
I was sure I wouldn't live past 45
My forebrain was sure anyway
My middle brain felt like Superman, though
The problem is
Sickness and cell deterioration notwithstanding
Any of us could die any time
And everyone in the world
Except those paying subgeniuses who live until X-Day
Will die
Some lucky subgenie
Such as Leguin
And G. Gordon Gordon
Get to die multiple times
But this kind of luck is reserved only for killers
And both of them happen to have been hitmen for Bob
I've seen too many 30-year-olds
Suddenly croak from cancer or accidents
I've watched old people croak
Right in front of my very eyes
I've nursed people who were three-fourths dead
And going down fast
And what I got from all this is
If you can still stand your parents
And old friends
Spend as much time with them as you can
As Lonesome Cowboy Dave and I worked out
After Chaz Smith died
We should treat our friends like they're already dead
We tend to be much more forgiving of dead people
Than live ones
And that's maybe not the best approach
But this hour of slack from subgenius.com
Will now close with Peter Bergman's
Truly Innocent Story
And inspirational last words to us
From his last podcast
Made March 6th
Two days before he unexpectedly
Boarded the escape vessels
Take heart, dear friends
We are passing through the darkening of the light
We're going to make it
And we're going to make it together
Don't get ground down by cynicism
Don't let depression darken the glass
Through which you look
This is a garden we live in
A garden seeded with unconditional love
And the tears of the oppressed
And the tears of the frustrated
And the tears of the good
Will spring those seeds
The flag has been waved
It says occupy
Occupy Wall Street
Occupy the banks
Occupy the nursing homes
Occupy Congress
Occupy the big law offices
Occupy the lobbyists
Occupy yourself
Because that's where it all comes together
I pledge to you
From this moment on
Whatever it means
I'm going to occupy myself
I love you
See you tomorrow