From PR News in Washington, I'm described as a person of interest.
Meanwhile, President Trump says White House officials says Pierce Horst says Trump offered PR to gag the victims and their families.
Everyone at every level of government.
That's PR's suspicious reporting.
The Dow is 10-24-7-24.
It's unclear when President Trump plans to announce this is PR.
Boys and girls, your attention please.
Presenting a new exciting radio program featuring the thrilling adventures of an amazing and incredible personality.
The Self Genius.
Power of Swag.
Abnormal Perversion.
Oh yes, dear friends, thank you Mr. Fernandez and Andy Lemur for the titles and news.
And tonight, we're continuing the epic two-parter call-in show with the...
The resurrected Lonesome Cowboy Dave and myself, Reverend Stang.
But first, well friends, we survived the Texas deep freeze of 2022.
I may have saved Texas, although I'm not sure that's good.
Now, we were pretty traumatized on this exact date last year when the temperatures in north-central Texas stayed around 10 degrees Fahrenheit or colder for days.
And millions...
Millions of us, including everyone at Stang Ranch here, were without power, heat, or water for days.
It was really miserable.
Hundreds died, mostly of stupidity, like burning furniture indoors and suffering carbon monoxide poisoning.
Our house's plumbing was saved because we lived in Cleveland for decades and knew to leave all the faucets running.
This year, friends, I was smart and spent 500 bucks on a general...
A generator.
And some space heaters.
However, I was also stupid and didn't order them soon enough.
In fact, they probably won't be here until tonight.
But the fact that I spent all that money prevented the winter storm from being so disastrous.
If I had not spent that 500 bucks, there would have for sure been terrible rain, sleet, and ice knocking out power stations all over the state and wrecking the infrastructure again.
By my spending that money, however, subgenius sympathetic magic kicked in, making my purchase suddenly pointless, simply by preventing much worse weather.
As Dr. Uncle Onan Canabite said, rival cults put the simp in sympathetic magic.
The Church of the Subgenius practices pimp-aesthetic magic.
Anyway, I saved millions of lives of Texans.
Again, whether this is actually a good thing, that's debatable.
Anyway, we dodged a bullet.
Ted Cruz...
Oh, thank you, thank you.
Thank you, my fellow Texans.
Ted Cruz is probably in Cancun again, but he probably also set up a life-size stand-up photo of himself next to a window in his Texas house.
To fool reporters.
Anyway, we're fine.
The snow and ice is melting away.
And the fact that I have this expensive 5,000-watt generator sitting on my porch should prevent my having to actually use it, maybe forever.
I have to credit Reverend Pease for the theory about the generator purchase stafing off its own necessity.
Another bright idea.
Reverend Pease had was that we should make Hour of Slack exclusively available only on Spotify.
Then sit back and watch heads explode.
Very funny, Reverend Pease.
The dogs and cats are all okay, as is Wee Ma Ma, age 92.
Princess Wee's getting some help since her mom is technically in hospice now and the government pays for daily nurse aides.
Once it knows you probably won't be needing them for much longer.
And in other news, business is terrible.
We raised the ordainment kit price for the first time in 20 years by 10 bucks, which apparently is way too much.
Subgenius.com.
But enough of this.
You don't want to hear any more of this.
You want to hear me read the beginning of our newly published subgenius mystery novel by Reverend Teeters LaVerge.
Called The Agent and Mr. Dobbs.
The recording is not new.
And yet here it is.
I have a manuscript here.
This was turned in by Reverend Teeters LaVerge of the Church of the Subgenius.
He's been, well, I'll just read it.
The title is The Agent and Mr. Dobbs.
And actually the manuscript is from October 1962.
But these papers were found on the body of a transient party clown in the city of Albany, New York in 1989.
The papers had been meticulously taped back together after an apparent attempt at shredding them.
Some pages are missing.
The party clown was determined by the county coroner to have been killed by a police officer.
He was killed by being force-fed copious amounts of silly putty.
Some of which still had a cartoon imprint of a pleasant yet disturbing face of a smiling man with a pipe clenched between his teeth.
Now here is the manuscript.
As I said, this is from 1962.
So you'll have to forgive some of the dated terminology used by the agent who wrote this.
I'm skipping over a part where he was dropped off at the Dobbs house or mansion.
The knocker on the huge oaken front door was a rather heavy, rusty iron piece in the shape of a dollar sign.
I banged it down thrice and awaited an answer.
Soon the door creaked open and in front of me stood the tallest colored man I have ever seen.
Even taller than Agent 541.
However, he had a very high, squeaky voice that resembles a certain cartoon mouse.
He asked me my business and I replied that I had an urgent appointment with Mr. Dobbs.
The man answering the door seemed fairly out of it too and replied back that the sky was pretty damn blue today.
Again, I had to wait a few minutes until he asked me my business.
But before I could answer, he was ushering me into the cavernous building.
Once inside, I noticed that it was rather well-appointed with both new and antique furnishings,
which to my eyes seemed to come from all corners of the earth and were set about in no discernible pattern.
There were piles of paper and stacks of money everywhere.
What caught my eye, though, was the incredible amount of junk laying about the place.
This Mr. Dobbs, it would seem, had a habit of collecting useless objects found by the side of the road.
Finally, after walking through many hallways, I was shown to a door and told to walk in.
But I was expected.
I did as told.
The room I entered was the most sane that I had so far seen.
A typical den that any well-cultured man may have in his home.
Mr. Dobbs was sitting in a large leather room.
He was wearing a leather armchair with his back to me, a billow of smoke coming up from his front.
I slowly walked over to him.
He said nothing, but with his right hand he motioned me to sit on a folding metal chair adjacent to him.
He seemed to be engrossed in a television program.
It was Leave It to Beaver, a wholesome program.
Suddenly he began to speak.
I do love this show.
That Ward Cleaver is one relaxed man.
Connie doesn't like me to watch this program.
She thinks it's pornographic, but that's why I like it.
He fell into a deep silence, intently watching a commercial and nodding his head in time with the jingle.
When the commercial ended, he turned to me and asked,
What can I do for you, young agent?
I noticed then that even though the upper half of his body was clad in a dark suit with white shirt and dark tie,
the bottom half of his body was clad only in wingtip shoes.
I thought that was very disturbing and put me off for a moment,
but I'd been warned by my handlers that this Mr. Dobbs had many tricks up his sleeve,
and I took this as his way of making a person uncomfortable.
I regained my composure and told him,
Mr. Dobbs, the agency I work for has a request for you.
When suddenly Mr. Dobbs got up out of his chair and walked over to a well-appointed wet bar
and poured a tumbler full of what he claimed was the finest scotch,
saying it was from Malaysia or Canada.
My memory begins to get hazy here.
It was not scotch at all. It smelled like grape,
but tasted for the life of me like gasoline.
He bade me to drink.
Knowing that he's an important partner, I tried to force down a sip.
Then Mr. Dobbs did the strangest thing.
He started to do what I believe is called a hula dance,
yet he was humming some tango to himself.
Even though I was warned,
I can't abide a half-naked man dancing in front of me.
Yet I was transfixed.
I know now that I must have been drugged.
He danced for a while, too close to me for my waning comfort.
My heart beat faster,
and the rank smoke from his pipe seemed to make my head swim and my vision fade.
I thought I was about to faint when my heart nearly burst
as I felt a pair of hands starting to massage me.
I looked up to see a beautiful blonde with a perfect perm smiling down on me.
I took this to be his wife, Connie.
She said,
Don't fret. Bob likes to dance on Fridays.
She continued,
Now, now, dearie, we mustn't mess with our company.
Mr. Dobbs ignored her and continued his lewd dance.
Connie bade me to ask Bob what questions I may need to ask.
I started out by getting straight to the point,
reminding him of the troubles with Cuba.
Mr. Dobbs then did the queerest thing I'd seen him do yet.
He ran over to a big wooden box on the bar,
opened it, and pulled out a huge novelty cigar.
He then proceeded to insert said huge novelty cigar up his...
...neither port.
The cigar spontaneously ignited,
and Mr. Dobbs blew smoke rings out of his ear.
Surely this was an illusion or a hallucination from my drugged state.
I found myself mesmerized by Mr. Dobbs' antics.
Connie's back rub and the scotch I found myself taking a liking to.
Connie's hands reached down to my lap
as I watched Mr. Dobbs preach about economics and Cuba and war
and how it all tied together,
all the while bent over with a huge cigar puffing away in his...
...netherworld.
And that is the last I remember of that evening.
The ensuing lie detector tests and truth serums have borne that out.
I awoke the next morning, late, I believe,
with a cool breeze fluttering through pastel pink curtains.
I had the worst hangover I'd ever experienced.
I cannot fully describe the sensation.
It was somewhere between getting a root canal and the high of three martinis.
I was startled to notice that Connie was still alive,
and that Connie Dobbs was nude lying next to me.
I tried getting up but soon regretted it by the dizziness it caused,
and worst of all, I saw what was laying next to Connie.
All I saw was its shoulders and a cheap bouffant wig on its head.
Its skin was grey.
I don't mean sickly human grey.
I mean grey as grey can be.
Its body shape was all out of whack too.
Then I had fleeting memories of a wild sexual encounter with Mrs. Dobbs
and something else.
I remember having intercourse with orifices that were not human.
I must have shuddered, for Connie rolled over and picked up a glass of some clear liquid
off the nightstand and two tablets.
She demanded I take them, for they would make me feel better.
I inspected the tablets, and though they resembled your basic aspirin,
they were had embossed on them the word PILS spelled P-I-L-S.
Afraid of being drugged again, I tried to hide them in my cheek,
but when I drank the liquid, they just slid down my throat.
Within minutes, reality started to fade and some sort of orgy began.
The last thing I remember was Mr. Dobbs, dressed as a clown,
with no pants on of course, attempting to take my virginity.
I still have nightmares about this, but as they say, my country, right or wrong.
Weeks passed that I have little memory of.
I know nothing.
I know this only because of the date in which I was retrieved by the agency.
The Dobbses and their minions kept me pretty well...
fropped up, as they called it.
The next event that I have any clear memory of was of taking a ridiculously long elevator ride
deep into the earth at the Bobco Mining and Soylent Green Consortium in Wyoming.
We must have been on that elevator for three hours.
One of Dobbs' minions took my watch during the orgy and refused to give it back,
saying,
Bob doesn't pay enough and he had to get some stuff for a weekend party
he and the Kennedys were having with one Dr. Oswald.
When we finally alighted from the elevator, to my surprise,
we were not in some mine shaft as I expected,
but in a huge vaulted warehouse full of novelty goods
that were being stacked and sorted by strange short men shrouded in sack rags.
Bob claimed that they were ex-Nazis, scientists,
working on some, quote,
super-duper extra-secret, unquote,
project for the government.
I could clearly see that they were not men at all,
but slaves of some unknown species.
By this time, I had found it to my better judgment
not to doubt Mr. Dobbs, at least not out loud.
We took a golf cart type of vehicle down a long, winding corridor.
Mr. Dobbs not once paid any attention to where he was driving.
He decided to, at that time, ramble on and on
about some mysterious substance he called slack,
all the while puffing insanely on his pipe,
the bowl of which soon glowed a bright red.
During this journey, we ran over three of Bob's slave men
and nearly hit countless others.
Mr. Dobbs was oblivious to each, quote,
accident.
I put that in quotes for each one of the slaves we ran over,
I happened to notice had been pointing a weapon of some sort at Mr. Dobbs
right before his eyes.
And this happened before he mindlessly ran over them.
This mysterious Mr. Dobbs may have some sort of
second sight or is just incredibly lucky.
As you'll see, I believe it has more to do with luck
and some sort of strange time control powers
than with anything else.
Mr. Dobbs' underground office was a horror.
I can barely describe it.
It was a total mess and stank of the tobacco
that he constantly smoked.
In fact, I never saw Mr. Dobbs
without that infernal pipe clenched between his teeth.
It was only after a few minutes of adjusting to the stench and the mess of the office
that I saw something that horrified me.
The place had several severed human heads strewn haphazardly all over.
Now, I've seen some terrible sights in my life,
and I suspect that if I'm on the Dobbs case, I will see worse.
But what made me gasp was that the heads were not of random humans,
but of public figures that we would all recognize.
I saw the heads of, and this section was carefully cut out of the original report,
and one was actually singing.
It begged me in the tenor to please kill me.
Surprisingly, in the state I had been in, I did not faint.
Instead, with all the smoke from Bob's special tobacco mix, I started to laugh.
This got Bob all worked up.
He started to jump around inanely and laugh.
He then proceeded to use one of the heads, not the singing one,
and then he started to sing in a most foul manner.
Bob bade me sit down on a chair that was stacked high with papers.
I looked at the stack and back at Bob, wondering what he expected me to do.
By this time, I'd begun to get in the spirit of the situation
and laughingly knocked the stack of papers on the floor.
Mr. Dobbs didn't seem to mind.
In fact, he stared down at the mess I made and said,
thanks, picked up a sheet of paper saying he'd been looking for this contract for quite some time.
The glyphs.
The glyphs on the sheet were of no known human alphabet that I have ever encountered.
For some reason, this worried me and reminded me of the slaves I saw working for Bob
and that dreadful night with Mrs. Dobbs and that strange gray creature.
I did not have much time to consider the implications,
for Mr. Dobbs wadded up the paper, tossed it in a corner, and told me to follow him.
This time, we did not take the vehicle, but instead walked down dark and dank corridors,
which had a gradual downslope.
Being without a timepiece, I cannot estimate the amount of time we walked, but it seemed like hours.
Here, I must admit, my perceptions of time had been warped by constant exposure to Bob's tobacco.
Mr. Dobbs finally guided me to our final destination.
What I saw in that final circle of hell I cannot, I will not reveal.
Through all the pressure that the Agency could bear against me, a loyal, true blue agent and American,
I found it in our best interest to see if we could find a way to get out of this mess.
I found it in our best interest to keep something secret, even from the boss, the man in the dress.
I do this for the good of our nation and out of fear,
for what Mr. Dobbs revealed to me was so horrific, so humorous, so bizarre, so unchristian,
so baffling and dangerous, that I hyperventilated through the inane laughter
that was my only defense lest I totally lose my mind.
The last thing I remembered that day was Mr. Dobbs dancing around my prostrate body.
He was prancing.
Really.
And mimicking my insane laughter with his own even crazier chortles.
He spoke no words.
He just laughed.
But his laughter seemed to speak volumes to my inner mind.
I laughed.
I wept.
I urinated in my undergarments, for Mr. Dobbs had somehow relieved me of my slacks.
When?
I do not recall.
And friends, at this point, I, Reverend Stang, must cease reading from the document,
The Agent and Mr. Dobbs, brought to us by Reverend T.
Peter LaVerge.
I've gotten a little ways into Part 2, and it goes all the way up to Part 6 so far.
However, I have a piece of music here that I think will be extremely pertinent to the
subject matter.
This is Reverend Angry Larry.
You know I live a life of danger for the FBI.
Keeping tabs on our names and on the news.
I'm the land on the sea and the sky!
And every single night, before I go to bed I get down on my knees and say, Bob, I'm a
secret agent man.
Secret agent man.
They give me a number, but they take away my name.
I'm a secret agent man.
I got one hell of a job to perform for the U.S. of A.
Got the responsibility of our nation's top security.
But every night and day, I salute the flag and say, Thank you, Connie, because I'm a
secret agent man.
Secret agent man.
They've given me a number, but they take away my name.
But every night and day, I salute the flag and say, Thank you, Connie, because I'm a secret
You know they got me doin' this, doin' that, a little bit of somethin' else.
Fightin' cavities of evil, safeguarding America's health.
But I didn't have any money, and now I've got to do what they told me to do.
Afternoon pass
I don't get up off my ass
Thank you Stan
Cause I'm a secret agent man
Secret agent man
They giving me a number
But they take away my name
Secret agent man
They giving me a number
But they take away my name
And that was an excerpt from the new subgenius novel
The Agent and Mr. Dobbs by Reverend Teeters LaVerge
Now available in a limited numbered special
house
A hardcover edition of not quite 50 copies
With a price to match
At subgenius.com
Now some cheapskates may need to wait
For the paperback version due out
Someday
But now let's go back to the pre-recorded
Visit from Lonesome Cowboy Dave
Recorded a couple of weeks ago
At Tarzan's radio station
At Stang Ranch
And interspersed with some
Subgenius history
And Sheridan colloquial
Take it away
Us
Oh this music in the background
By the way
Is from the Empire Jazz Orchestra
Praise Bob
My heart was full of song
From up with them
Sorry I didn't mean to break the flow
So to speak
We had the song from
Hello Dolly
Was echoing through this big hollow
Castle earlier today
Yes
Oh boy
Princess Wee's mom
Wee-ma-ma
Was watching Hello Dolly
Cranked up
Boy she likes to crank up her rock and roll
And if the door's open
You can hear it everywhere
I peeked in and saw Barbara Streisand
In this fabulous
Production scene
It just was mind-blowing
The costumes
Oh I would love to make love to her nose
But that's up into your nose
Well is this your nose?
Oh this yes
What has happened to your nose?
Asshole
Fire sign theater quote
That's what we should do
We should cut to fire sign theater
Turn this FM off here
Radio off
Over here
Okay
I'll get the TV
No no no
Leave it on for a minute
What has happened to your nose?
I've just returned from Rome
What?
Yeah I have seen this before
Go ahead turn it off
Well that's it
Here's your keys
Goodbye friends and happy motoring
Back on the freeway
Which is already in progress
Whew
Well
Here goes
Nice feel
Let's see
Oh how can you be in two places at once
When you're not anywhere at all?
I think I'll give this old baby a spin on the freeway
Wrong way
Entering freeway
Here we go
Emergency parking
Merging bus is ahead
Giant slide 19 holes underground parking
Midden Hills retirement paradise
Oh
Easy access?
You're done
Goldoni Attlee
Strasburg Lane 1 mile
Spadometer has only got half a mile on it
Bible Shield N-0
Two miles
Antelope Freeway North
I want to go north or do I want to take the
Let's see the Gamora Expressway West
Shadow Valley Condoms
If you lived here you'd be home by now
Antelope Hills selected living comfortable easy okay
Antelope Hill selected living comfortable easy okay
Antelope Freeway this lane exit open
Yeah I think I'm going to go to the freeway
I think I'll take the old Antelope less traffic
Easy street
Antelope Freeway 1 mile
Clean up Armenia
Get a hair lift
Antelope Freeway 1 half mile
Chili Avenue open
Let's see what they got in this car
Let's see we got lights, wipers, defrost, temperature and climate control
Antelope Freeway 1 32nd mile
Let's see what kind of climate I can get
Winter Wonderland
Spring Fever
Antelope Freeway 1 1 mile
ARRY
Manamps
Oh, my God.
You can.
Daddy, I've lost the Lincoln box.
That's all right.
I've got an erector set.
Show off.
Throw a towel over it.
Do some push-ups, Pablo.
It'll go away.
Hey, what are you guys doing in my car?
The fox trot.
You can have the next dance.
But throw him the fox.
This animal is sick.
Yes, it is a catchy little number.
Uh-oh, I think he's caught it.
Doctor, give him something for his car.
All right, all right.
Here's a quarter.
Oh.
That's not much.
Not much of a car.
I need a gas station.
Did I pass one?
No, no, but the fox did.
Squeeze him right there.
Maybe he'll pass another one.
No, no.
Gasoline.
Oh, my boy, if it's drugs you want,
the old doctor can help you out.
Right this way.
Hey, get your hands off me.
I don't want to leave.
Then roll up your arm and bend over.
Do you want regular or premium?
Oh, this is ridiculous.
You guys are nothing but a pack of cards.
Drink me.
Must be some way out of this.
I'll change the air.
That's what I'll do.
Let's see.
What have I got left on the climate control?
Uh, dust storm?
No.
Tibetan wilderness?
Land of the pharaohs.
That sounds great.
All right, all right.
Here we are in the land of the pharaohs.
Oh, no.
Well, we'll need to take a break.
We'll talk with the natives.
Does anyone here know a little Egyptian?
Bill, Bill, come on.
You're good at languages.
Yes, come on, Bill.
Yes, yes, yes, indeed.
Yes, yes, yes.
That was it.
What?
Yes, indeed.
Yes, a little Egyptian.
Yes, everybody knows I'm mad.
Served my every need.
Did a grand job on my ankles, too.
Now, hold it right there.
Glad to.
Now, I think I'll hold it over here.
Oh, boy, it's nice out, isn't it?
Yes, I think you ought to leave it out.
Hey, hey, hey, look, fellas.
Fun's fun, okay.
But look, I gotta find a place to stay.
It's gonna be night soon.
I'm tired.
What's the matter with that dude?
I'm lost.
And I wanna go to bed.
Oh, my bony boy.
In the Estonian mountains,
we used to go to sleep
leaning up against a windfall.
I was but a mere prat then.
I'll never forget the time a snake
slithered into my wife.
I wasn't but knee-high
to a merry grasshopper then.
Oh, no, no, look, that's all very interesting.
But the sun is going down.
Oh, no, no, you're all confused.
The horizon is moving up.
Hey, listen, come on, you guys.
Help me, please.
I know, I know.
Let's stand him on his head.
Here you go.
Hey, hey, hey, put me down.
Relax, relax.
Easy, boy.
Ah, you see?
Now it's morning.
Oh, he's no fun.
He fell right over.
Hey, won't somebody please help me?
Easy, easy, my lad.
At times of dexterity like this,
my wee native compendium,
Mohamit,
used to pray to the divinitize.
His little brown froggy body
equivorate my loins,
chanting a stream of ancient Egyptian holograms.
What?
Diaphragms.
No, no, no, no.
Hieroglyphs, that's it.
Do you remember any?
Will they help?
Anything at all?
Yes, of course, of course.
Let's see.
It was a jackal-headed woman
with her eyes kimbo,
a king sitting sideways on his throne,
a drip with gold,
chippet nose uplifted,
and a dachshund.
All engraven on the pyramids of massy size,
with the body of a lion,
paws that refreshes,
a tail told by an idiot,
and the head of a fox.
The pyramid is opening.
Which one?
The one with the ever-widening hole in it.
I'm saved.
I'm going in.
No, don't do that, son.
It's dark and dirty in there.
Oh, but mom.
It's full of bees and spiders.
You might poke your eye out
when your father comes home.
I'm going in, mom.
There's a vacancy.
Good evening, sir.
Welcome to the only nice motel in town.
How long will you be with us?
Just for tonight.
Very well, sir.
You'll find it's very clean here.
Just fill out this card.
Oh, thanks.
Oh, look, it's dirty.
Somebody's already used it.
There's a name on it.
That's all right.
Well, I couldn't get you to believe
my name is Mr. and Mrs. Johns,
could I?
Well, of course you could.
It's nice to have you with us,
Mr. and Mrs. Smith.
Run.
Hey, aren't you Mr. and Mrs. John Smiths?
From any town in the USA?
Hello.
I'm Joe, boy, and this here's Ed.
Hey, I'm not really Mr. and Mrs. John Smith.
Well, that's okay.
I'm not Joe.
And he's not Ed.
Hey, fella, how about bending a couple
in the doodah room?
Yes, sir.
To catch my meaning,
if you get my drift.
Thanks, fellas, but I'm kind of tired.
Hey, desk clerk, can I have my key, please?
Sure.
What about G7?
Get it, Jimmy.
I can tell by the pound you're tied.
You're an American.
Well, so am I.
Hi, bub.
Howdy.
How do you do?
And while we're on the subject...
Yo, wazoo!
What's that all about?
What's it all about,
Mr. and Mrs. John Q. Smith
from any town USA?
Well,
it's about this long...
And about that wide...
And it's about this country...
About which we're singing about.
I was born
an American.
I was raised
And I'll die
an American
in America
with our
meaning.
The end.
Oh, that was hilarious, wasn't it?
You like that transition I did?
Fire Sign Theater,
they're the greatest.
They were so much better
than anybody else
until, of course,
until we came along.
Is there any kind of
gaseous energy escaping
from your house right now,
you know?
Huh? What? Say that? What?
Oh, the gas is erupting
from your nostrils.
I mean,
you just sound like
you're making so much fun
that you can hardly hold it in.
That's Princess Wee,
not me.
Oh, okay.
Remember, she's the Robin Givens
to my Howard Stern.
She excuses my excesses
with her gay laughter.
Yeah, but Robin Givens
used to carry a gun,
a shotgun.
And if...
It's starting.
Well, she's...
Wah, wah, wah.
Hey, we figured out
where that wah, wah, wah,
what inspired that noise
in the score
of The Good, Bad, and the Ugly
by Ennio Morricone.
It's Coyote.
In the movie,
which I was watching last night,
it starts with these bad guys
in a really run-down
train station or something,
and they're about to go in
and kill Duco.
And there's a coyote,
a lone coyote going,
wah, wah, wah.
Mm-hmm.
And it suddenly comes
to the title music,
and that's the noise.
Wah, wah, wah.
Ah!
Blondie?
Don't die, Blondie.
Don't die.
I'm your friend.
Please don't die.
Please.
I'm your friend.
Come on, baby.
Come on.
Blondie?
I'll help you.
Don't move.
I'll be right back.
Okay?
Did you notice those scenes before?
No, no.
When I was watching the movie, I heard the coyote.
When I was a kid, I didn't even know what a coyote sounded like.
I grew up in the city.
Out here, you can't escape them.
No.
And this is kind of like the Wild West.
It's definitely coyote country.
Until you get to the highway, then it's just goddamn suburbs.
Pinkland, normal town.
Out here, we've got a horse.
It ain't much of a horse.
It's a real old horse.
But there actually is a horse here.
He's a good-looking horse.
And a whole bunch of goats.
Yeah.
Oh, massive goats.
Good goats.
Goats are fun, too.
So mighty.
Great goats.
I am goat.
Well, once upon a time, we all were, you know.
We all came from Mammy Goat's uterus, or Chicken Pie, whatever it's called.
Mammy's Chicken Pie?
We all came from Mammy's Chicken Pie?
Yeah, the goat.
The goat woman.
Who looked a little bit like Adolf Hitler in her younger days.
And was constantly warned away from the rest of the kids.
Oh, you're quoting that famous Doctors for Wotan song,
Louie Louie, Are You a Girl or a Goat Woman?
Yeah.
I should cut to that, except that it's really horrible.
Louie Louie!
Louie Louie, Are You a Girl or a Goat Woman?
I didn't know.
I wanted to say better.
But the science said she, the goat woman.
And I did it.
I tied my fencing rope and I saw her and there she was.
Oh, the rug!
And the most beautiful of all.
She left behind on the stage as she danced.
Tiny pellets.
Garth pellets.
And I knew she was the girl for me.
Louie, Louie.
I am a girl.
Oh, my.
No, no, no, no.
No.
Well, that's why I played for that reason itself.
I'll just re-record it.
Louie, Louie.
Louie.
Uh-uh.
Are you a girl or a goat woman?
Uh-uh-uh.
And then I saw her at the carnival in the freak show.
She was so beautiful on her hooves and her beautiful goat woman breastage.
And I looked back in the dressing room and there were little tiny pellets and droppings of it when I fell in love.
Now you're talking.
Louie, are you a girl or a goat woman?
Nah.
Man, that's it.
That's just a 100 proof.
Yeah.
Now, that was the cover of Louie, Louie, Are You a Girl or a Goat Woman by Pooh Water Towel.
The original was Doctors's for Wotan.
Princess, we and I are Pooh Water Towel once every three years when we record a song.
We've got to record Buddy.
Yes.
The rock opera.
We do.
The doc, the doc, the prop rock.
Dog opera.
Well, here we are.
The rock opera.
Sitting here with the microphones, we should do it.
You know what?
I even have that karaoke cut of Tommy ready to go.
All right.
We cut it down to 17 minutes instead of an hour and a half.
It's based on Tommy, of course, the rock opera.
But it's Buddy.
Buddy, can you hear me?
And so on.
That was back when Buddy escaped.
I'm a different dog now.
He's a different dog now.
Hey, man.
That's a different dog, man.
Stay away from him.
Like me.
He's a different dog now, man.
Yeah.
Yeah, you got me wrong.
I'm a different dog now.
You got me wrong.
I didn't do it.
See?
Old Bob will sell just about anything to just about anybody.
What's he sold you today?
So, there's a great quote.
I wish I had come up with it.
That it's easier to act your way into a new way.
Than to think your way into a new way of acting.
So, how important the external is to changing the internal.
It wasn't possible to measure happiness or to compare happiness across individuals.
We would look basically at consumer preferences.
Yeah.
So, we would certainly go back into different ways.
You know, we would
Well, we had our first apocalyptic experiment with nic
So, what they tried to do
And so, wherever you look, you realize that you have the technology all this time.
And people have been using this v drives for that whole long time.
And now, they're screwed.
views on them partly cloudy skies with a high near 22 some lingering light snow flurries still in the
air partly cloudy tonight with a low of 12.
are you suffering from information overload
um
All right.
All right, it's all over.
We're all happy now.
We're so happy.
We all love each other.
There's evidence that human connection also modulates or can affect one's autonomic nervous system.
Human beings must be in the loop before someone is killed by a drone.
But it's in the machine.
My replica.
And it doesn't need people.
It's me, your computer.
I can't turn it off.
We need to talk.
I can't put it away.
It's in me.
It's computer.
Together.
You're me.
Don't get freaked out.
Destroy.
It can decide by itself whether or not it kills somebody.
Huh?
I don't see a good reason to believe that we would survive.
Don't get freaked out.
Yeah.
Okay, yeah.
I still think it would be fun to talk to a robot.
There was all kinds of experimentation and fun going on there.
All kinds of experimentation and fun.
The answer to why is my brain like this is because your brain is like this.
And that's all there is to it.
There is no more.
Bummer.
Close your eyes and pretend with me for a few seconds.
This is not a rerun.
Not a rerun.
It's bye.
Oh, well, in my paper, it's bye.
Alert.
Greetings, Bob.
Hello.
This is Bob.
I'm out of the moment.
If you leave your name and your telephone number, I will call you back.
You know, I waited for somebody to say Bob.
You're fired.
I got the power.
I got the treasure.
And you have a flight to catch.
Huh?
No.
Closer to me.
Long live the king.
You shall not pass.
That's it.
No more Mr. Knife Guy.
This is what life is like.
At a...
At a bottom line...
level, you know, and I'm not going to make you cut through a lot of other stuff to get
through it. Here's what it is. There's no gimmick about that. It's straightforward.
It's strong and it's elemental.
This wouldn't be a great way to do that on Earth, but it's really a very efficient way
to do it.
Well, when? Right now?
Now? Go ahead.
No, no. What are you waiting for? If not now, when? If not us, who?
No, neither one of those two are all right right now.
I have to go lay down in the toilet for a while.
Well, Dave, it has been an hour and one minute
of show.
Yeah.
I'll probably chop it up into two shows.
Oh.
You handsome dog.
Yeti, say something.
He does. He does talk.
He does.
No, that's not him. That's her doing it.
No, I'm trying to get him to do it.
I had a dog.
That's how he talks, though.
White?
I'm just saying I had a dog who saved a kid from drowning.
You did?
Yes, he did.
He jumped right in. They got me out, all right.
And then the dog got in there and got the kid.
And the kid put his arms around the dog's neck and swam him in.
And the dog shook.
And everybody that was watching the horrible event applauded and went, yeah.
Was this when you were a small kid?
No, this is when I was a 20-some-year-old kid.
And thought I was the world's greatest athlete
and would go running far, far, far away.
And I was running far with my dog.
And we came upon a place in the river that there was a, what's it called?
Oh, I forget what they call that.
A water.
When the water sucks back up under and pulls you down.
You get about five feet away from the dam.
And then it pulls you back under.
The undertow.
An undertow.
And I was there for a much longer time.
And the EMS people had to come.
And dig me out.
But my dog did save a kid's life.
The kid was going, please, mister, help us.
Please help us.
And you didn't do anything.
But the dog understood what the kid was saying.
Well, kind of, yeah.
Yeah, I thought, oh, we're so much smarter than dogs.
Recently, on a training film,
I saw a dog deliver, what's it called?
Chest smackers.
Now, see, doesn't Dave say,
ruff, ruff, ruff, ruff, ruff, ruff, ruff, ruff, ruff, ruff, ruff, ruff, ruff, ruff?
Just that?
A little bit.
Yeah.
That's when I can't hear.
I can't understand him.
I can hear him.
But it doesn't.
How about this way?
I moved it like a microsecond to the left.
There you go.
Is that okay now?
Yeah.
Okay, well.
I usually talk pointing my mouth just slightly to the side of the microphone.
phone. That's what I have to do.
So it's not popping the peas like
a bunch of puds and
puddlies.
You wouldn't believe what that looks like on
the waveform.
It knocks everything else down because I've got
an automatic volume limiter on here
and the peas
just make everything drop out for a second.
I've seen
what the plosives do.
Plosives are a pain.
Poppity peas.
Peas.
Oh,
we just wrecked
that recording
and that song about
pee-pees.
Whatever.
At least Reverend Peas will be proud.
He'll go, oh, I see you finally mentioned me.
It's about time.
He will say that.
As if it wasn't about time to begin with.
You know?
It's about time.
It's about space.
It's about two minutes.
Craziest place.
Starring Ruth Buzzy
who lives over
to Stephenville now.
Believe it or not, Ruth Buzzy lives in
Stephenville, Texas. Not far from here.
Goodness. That's right down the street.
Oh, she's my babe.
Who else? Bob Denver
and Chuck McCann. Now, why can
I remember who was in that horrible
crappy kids show
and I can't remember
your W-2 form?
Mmm.
Oh.
What?
I think we all know.
I think we do know. We know exactly
why. Let's just not
dwell on it. Let's not focus on that.
Friends, you've been listening to the Hour
of Slack here on radio station
insert station here
in the
beautiful city of Bill
Kate's voice should say the town.
And that is
that's all folks.
Says
Porky Pig. Some non-stutterer.
I'll speak
to you once again soon.
I hope so.
I hope so. I really
hope so. I hope so too.
I hope the
snow melts someday there, Dave.
That would be helpful
in recovering my senses
and my other stuff like that.
Yeah.
Yeah. Me too.
Okay, man.
Okay.
Okay, woman.
Okay. All right.
Jesus.
Enough.
I bust her.
Okay. I'm going to hang up.
Oh, he hung up. See, he does that.
Oh, look what Julian from
Trailer Park Boys is saying
to me on a message. I get notifications
from Julian of Trailer Park Boys.
Hey, dummy. The
mobile is ready. Hurry up and
get your ****.
That's what it says. And he's right.
Oh, well,
should I turn the sound on for the
Trailer Park Boys game? It's the same
as their TV theme. Here.
Here.
Baby,
it's the arriving life.
You know Lollipop.
Thank you.