Oh
But let's leave things of this world behind and walk now down the path of Bob for this brief minute of slack from the church of the
subterranean
of genius.
Friend, the devil is tearing the family apart.
But what the devil uses to do it with is nine to five jobs.
Conspiracy, corporate, pink situations where mommy and daddy get up in the morning and
go to work and they kiss the kids goodbye.
It's the first time they see them during the day, kiss them goodbye, kind of a simultaneous
goodbye and hello.
Then they get home about seven o'clock, ticked off to use the polite term after a long drive
back out to the suburbs.
They get home, they kiss their kids hello and good night and they go to bed.
And the other churches dare to say the breakdown of the family is because the kids see a little
tittering, stupid, sexy gags on television or because of the new permissiveness where
men are allowed to do things with other men.
That's a bunch of holy hooey, I say, my friend.
I say, oh, why not legalize pornography and ban work?
Work is what takes the parents away from the kids.
Most of these kids these days grow up.
They don't have parents.
They got some kind of robot scarecrows.
No, friend, let there be slack.
This is the worst crazy sect I've ever been in.
You'll soon detect, friends, that this episode, number 1850, is a rerun of coincidentally
number 850 from 2002, a time when I was still ambitious.
I was desperate and robust enough to go gallivanting all over the country constantly like a crazed
cowboy preacher, doing live shows in bars and occasionally theaters.
That time is past, but that's okay because you can still learn how to spell the name
of Bob.
I needed to watch this episode for the Seb No, my friend Bob, the had made this type
that everybody said Bob watched too many times.
He suspended the film by not following his father, Josh.
So we just dropped it, Ken.
I actually got rid of that show, but I was ändging alone, so I survived.
Number 1950 back in back, back in the day, used BJ and cunt.
We got some quality
We got more flowers for them.
Nice one.
He was working on building a tree at home with us, didn't he like going to run the hood
scheme.
Bettler, before he used a Human Rest Rune.
It's been a while.
He was doing what I use as a fresh level.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, B-O-B.
Pony, Pony, Pony.
B-O-B.
Big Bob.
One, one dollar.
One dollar, one, one dollar.
B-O-B.
Big Bob.
B-O.
B-O-B.
Big Bob.
Beep, beep, beep.
Beep, beep, beep, beep.
Beep.
Beep, beep, beep.
Oh, nein.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, nein.
Yes, friends, that was a total remix of B.O.B.,
the song by Dr. Onan's Wotan Band that everyone always thought was Devo.
And for not bad reason, as you'll soon see,
as we progress into this great spaz music month on Hour of Slack.
Yes, this and the next couple of shows will be mostly music, friends,
almost like real radio shows.
But wait until you hear what has been crammed full length into the church of the subgenius.
Indeed, friends, all the cramming made this particular show late.
And I don't apologize.
During the last few weeks, we, that is, yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stank,
have spouted and spewed our way through the subgenius revival in Indianapolis
and then the week-long 5X Day Drill
and then the week-long pagan hippie event Starwood
and then the wedding at Ground Zero in New York City of the sex executioner from Noir
and his lovely bride, Andrea.
And then, then, friends,
devotional or Devo convention in Cleveland last Saturday
and last Sunday, another revival, by some accounts, the greatest yet,
in Akron, Ohio, crucible of mutation.
And at each of these subgenius events,
about a dozen people each handed me CDs to play on this show.
And I downloaded some of my all-time, old-timey music favorites
from Blob.
And I also downloaded some of my old-timey music favorites
All manner of songs and songs, friends, that I couldn't afford when they were LPs,
but now I can in their illegal MP3 bootleg form.
And so, tonight, and coming up, we have new and old,
from Occupant, Little Theodore, The Great Groovy Neptune,
Johnny Cash, Mark Mothersbaugh, Captain Beefheart, Onan's Wotan Band,
Sister Melodious Chops, Elvis Costello, the original cast of Guys and Dolls,
and this great new band that played at the Akron revival,
heard in the background, called the Amino Acids.
And perhaps most startling and X-rated of all, friends,
a new album, actually a two-disc set from Reagan's Pollock.
Yes, Reagan's Pollock's new album, er, er, set, Love Overdrive.
It's kind of a best-of.
And before I play this Reagan's Pollock song, I should mention that this is a new album,
and it's a real album, available on Amazon.com with slick packaging,
including liner notes by none other than me,
and the famous folk singer, Bob Dylan.
Very strange, friends, but so is Reagan's Pollock.
This song is called,
Develop Revolutionary Consciousness.
Oh!
Desire is evil and I hurt like a gas-soaked dirt
In this swamp of my unborn be-gum
Ooh!
I am starved for the touch of this snake
I will die if I don't have a taste of the poison arrow
Surely with the force of my years of education
I can fend off the needs of the flesh
Ooh!
With the blood of a yak on my lips I scream,
Ah!
Ooh!
And I know that the face of my dear throne
Is a metal mask like the acid line
Ooh!
Face of Lana Turner
Bearing down like a horrible machine
Rushing my fragile skull
La-la-la-la-la-la
Ah!
Ah....
Hi-yah!
Yah
Y沈
Yeah!
Thank you.
You can't count on God for Jack.
He pretty much told me so himself.
They call you Lady Luck,
but there is room for doubts
and time to be brave.
Sometimes you have a very unladylike way of running out.
You're on a date with me.
The pickings have been lush.
And yet before this evening is over, you might give me the brush.
You might forget your manners.
You might refuse to stay.
And so the best that I can do is pray.
Luck, be a lady tonight.
Luck, if you've ever been a lady to begin with.
Luck, let a gentleman see.
How nice a dame you can be.
I know the way you've treated other guys you've been with.
Luck, be a lady with me.
A lady doesn't leave her escort.
It isn't fair, it isn't nice.
A lady doesn't wander all over the room and blow on some other guy's dice.
So let's keep the party polite.
Never get out of my sight.
Stick with me, baby, I'm the fella you came in with.
Luck, be a lady.
Luck, be a lady tonight.
Luck, if you've ever been a lady to begin with.
Luck, let a gentleman see.
How nice a dame you can be.
I know the way you've treated other guys you've been with.
You can be a male with pride, acted normal lies, or even an empty kid.
You've got a right to be a tsundere.
You've got a right to a playboy then.
You've got to be a dame to eyelid in a game of parkour.
The way you act cut sheets.
You've got to try to fit your hide into yourself before someone dies.
And it's a line you take, go look at yourself, and see if something suits me.
Luck, be a lady.
win
Luck be a lady
What's the matter, roll the dice
Roll it up, roll it up, roll it up, roll it up
Right, ha!
Robert Alda and the Guys
from Guys and Dolls
the 1950 original Broadway cast
and yes, that was Bob singing
Starts with a B
I don't know what it is
I knew it when I came in here
Ends with a B
No, don't tell me
10 seconds, Bob
Bob!
Well, it's really great to have you on the show tonight, Bob
Isn't that fantastic.
I have long since heard you sing
some of your own songs
I'm gonna get me a drink
Okay, here it is
Is that Ross?
www.neptune.itgo.com
More from them coming up.
And now, Occupant, friends.
Occupant is really Onan Canobite, the great subgenius, and his friend Mitch.
And this song coming up is an old...
It's actually a song by Devo, which you won't recognize unless you're a real spaz like me.
Occupant.
Nothing had done in a fifty-five dodge.
Didn't mean to do it.
But a sidewalk run in the room, they summoned him, the one he had to lose it.
After you mow down, down in Cape Town, got the Occupant.
I can mow down the Robotech sound, you've got to move your feet
It's a retro sound, you can spread around the way the Spartan boys used to do it
Now it's time to show that we're all before an occupant's here to prove it
I can mow down, down in Youngstown, bodies in the street
I can mow down, noon in downtown, bodies with no feet
I can mow down, down in Youngstown, bodies got the blues
I can mow down, noon in downtown, bodies with no shoes
An acid head blue and a fifty five dodge didn't mean the doing
Bodies in the street
Sidewalk boy in the noonday, something the one he had to lose it
I can mow down
Lord, I can mow down
The manager of the largest establishment
He pats them to the back
And puts them to the right
But I never thought they'd put me in the
Good squad
They come to look you over
And they're giving you the high
Good squad
The white suits are called out to play
You better say goodbye
Some grow up just like the dads
And some from up to tomorrow
Some go drinking with the lads
Some don't grow up at all
You must find the proper place for everything you see
But you'll never get to make a lampshade out of me
I could join a chain of males
Or be the best of the league
But I'm looking for a lucky girl
To put me in the peak
They pats them to the back
And puts them to the right
But I never thought they'd put me in the
Good squad
They come to look you over
And they're giving you the high
Good squad
The white suits are called out to play
You better say goodbye
Baby, father
I'm doing so well
I'm making such progress now
It's hard to tell
Been in a little dedication
With one eye on the clock
They got you under medication
You could be in for a shock
Thinking of the alibis
That everyone's forgotten
Just another purpose but gone to the right
They pats them to the back
And puts them to the right
But I never thought they'd put me in the
Good squad
They come to look you over
And they're giving you the high
Good squad
The white suits are called out to play
You better say goodbye
Music
You can't give up hope just because it's hopeless.
You gotta hope even more and cover your ears and go,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Give me that old Thai religion.
Don't give me no affliction.
That old Thai religion.
It's good enough for me.
It's good enough for you.
Well, come out to show them.
Come out to show them.
Come out to show them
Give me that old time religion
It's good enough for me
Without your new affliction
Don't need your new restriction
Give me that old time religion
It's good enough for me
Moonlight on for my heart
Nobody wants to play with me
Just because I'm never happy
All the other kids are going up and down slides
While I sit here and philosophize
I've got a world of my own
I see things as they are
Nobody can tell me what to do
Not even you
Nobody wants to play with me
Just because I am not friendly
All the other kids are going up and down slides
All the other kids are playing funny games
While I sit by myself and examine my brain
I've got a world of my own
I see things that you don't
Nobody can tell me what is good
Though you wish you could
Nobody wants to play with me
Just because I am not sexy
All the other kids are fooling around
But I'm several miles above the ground
I've got a world of my own
I see what is not there
Nobody can tell me how to feel
I know that's real
Nobody wants to play with me
Just because I have no family
All the other kids have wives and jobs
While I lay in the gutter and think and stop
I've got a world of my own
I see sadness and dirt
Nobody can tell me what is right
Try to fight
Nobody wants to play with me
Just because I'm old and ornery
All the other kids have grandchildren
They chatter and they squabble
But I ignore them
I've got a world of my own
I see all that I am
Nobody can tell me why I live
You have nothing to give me
But only your love
Now I have your life
Somehow there is a love
That I knew long ago
The reason I live
professionally
Yahoo.com.
I should spell Theodore.
It's spelled F as in Frank.
Y-O-D-O-R.
Little Theodore.
Here's another address.
3277 Raleigh Street.
R-A-L-E-I-G-H.
3277 Raleigh Street, Denver, Colorado.
80212.
For Little Theodore at Yahoo.com.
And now, friends, well, you're hearing in the background the Amino Acids who played at our Akron Revival.
You can hear more of them at TheAminoAcids.com.
That's www.TheAminoAcids.com.
And now, friends, a song with, for some reason, deep personal meaning to me.
I'm not sure why.
The King.
El.
Fist.
Oh, I used to be disgusted.
And now I try to be amused.
But since the winds have gotten rusted.
You know the angels wanna wear my red shoes.
But when they,
Told them at the side of the parking
That when I viewed it I could not refuse
And I won't get any older
Now the angels wanna wear my red shoes
Oh, I was watching while you're dancing away
I look at Frank shooting an echo and sway
I'm calling everybody who wants to be your friend
You know that it still hurts me just to say it
Oh, I know she's disgusted
Oh, why's that?
Cause she's feeling so abused
Oh, there's too bad
She gets tired of the lust
Oh, I'm so sad
But it's so hard to refuse
Can you say that I'm too old
When the angels have stolen my red shoes?
Oh, I said I'm so happy I could die
She said trapped in and left with another
guy
That's what you get if you go chasing out the vengeance
Ever since you got me punctured this has been my sentence
Oh, I used to be disgusted
When I tried to be amused
Since the wings have gotten rusted
You know the angels wanna wear my red shoes
But when they told me at the side of the parking
That's when I knew that I could not refuse
And I won't get any older
Now the angels wanna wear my red shoes
I won't get any older
Red shoes
The angels wanna wear my red shoes
I'm walking in a wonder wonder land
Asked for some water all I got was sand
There's a nine pound hammer beating in my skull
Laying down tracks on the road to hell
I'm walking in a wonder wonder land
There's a nine pound hammer beating in my skull
Laying down tracks on the road to hell
Here
There we walk back
For the cat
Here
He sat His und helpless head
Silently
But don't worry
A David hadn't shed
And I have
To trap
My wild
And needy
Mine
humanity
To be
Such an
immense
Thunder
They stare
Like a
ghost
To keep
Praise
Dance
The mathematics of the equation just don't add up.
It's a paradoxical situation.
And while my cock is in elation, my soul is in purgatory.
And praying to the demon god at Radio Shack to give me peace and make the neighbor's dog stop telling me to murder the innocents.
In the twilight of the night.
In the cracks of the sidewalks in New York City.
The Great Groovy Neptune, dear friends.
www.neptune.itgo.com
A new CD from The Great Groovy Neptune called Turpentine Enema.
Proof that there's still hope in Texas.
And friends, stay tuned for yet another killer remix of a classic tune by Dr. Oneg.
Onan's Wotan Band.
Followed by a new, traditional Celtic song about computer online affairs by Sister Melodious Chops.
But now, Onan's Wotan Band.
Do you remember Dr. Melodious Chops?
The song about a famous screenwriter, 따가EEEEE
And the director .
And now on to the包括 Sheetbane
Onan's album is also the disco Grammy Award for Best Singer of the Year.
Craving for allons samen
It functions as a sex relationship
So will it be our also dis இரう
Think about when you're using sex devices, think about when you're walking through the woods, when you make out with the girls, when you beat up tubular hoods, think about.
Big steps!
Here it comes.
He's coming, bud.
Go coming.
Take your slack away
He's Bob
When you see a flock of birds, think of Bob
When you just run out of words, think of Bob
When a ring falls round your car, when you hear a given holler
When you write checks for one dollar, think of Bob
When you ride to the subgenius, think of Bob
B or Fox, one four or three or six, think of Bob
When you cast your mojo hexes, when you ride to Dallas, Texas
When you're all die-lexing, think of Bob
One dollar, one dollar, one dollar, one dollar
You're a cunt
Slack
Don O B
Big Mac Bob
Slack
He's coming to take your slack away
One, one, B O B
He'll take it too
That Big Mac Bob
Heaven in the sky
One dollar, one dollar
That's right, just send a shrew
One dollar, one dollar, one dollar
One dollar
One dollar, you get Bob
You get a lot more for your money
Heck, one dollar, you get Bob
Think of Bob
Yeah, think of Bob
Think about Bob
Yeah, he makes us
Think of Bob
Everybody's thinkin' about Bob
Everybody wants to think of Bob
Yeah
Oh, think about Bob.
Think about Bob.
Yeah, we're thinking about Bob.
Yeah, Bob's think about Bob.
I'm Bob.
No, I'm Bob.
Listen here, Malachi.
Hi, Kai. Time for a religious donation.
Hand over your wallet!
But, Lord, we are a poor and simple folk.
Poor? Aw, crap.
Well, some maids like to tend the fields, others will tend their children.
Some will buy a DSL to find a man who's willing.
There's something about the online world that makes me want to care.
And I will go with flights unfurled to meet my Charlie there.
Well, some will wear their sexy things and turn the lights down low.
Some will grab a brew or two and drink them as they go.
But, they are not the kind of girl to go for a motor party.
But you won't, or if you will, I'm going online for Charlie.
Well, some will fly to Cameroon to quench their loving flame.
Me, I'll sit inside my room and summon up your name.
So get your fingers ready, dear, I'm going to be your queen.
And light a candle too.
And if I'm known, you may not hear, but I'm coming online for you.
He sends me streams of thrilling thought.
He opens up my gate.
He touches me where he should not.
And I can hardly wait.
Some like fear the strains of heart.
Others the beat of a party.
You're ready now.
But I don't care, just let me start.
Going online for Charlie.
Charlie.
That was Victoria Ganger and Revelry.
Also known as Sister Melodious Chops.
With a song about online love affairs via the internet.
From ancient Ireland.
Their website with samples is www.revelrychicks.com.
From a new album called Highly Irrevelent.
My dear consort, the princess to which I am consort, Princess Wee Ardo,
is one of the two backup babes singing in Revelry.
And friends, I'm Bird Dog.
I am bird dogging that stuff.
I am bird dogging that Princess Wee.
You know, because there's some dirty dogs out there, my friends.
There are some, my male, my buddies, my man friends.
If you got it, bird dog it.
Because there's some dogs out there.
Here's Johnny Cash.
Wanted man in California.
Wanted man in Buffalo.
Wanted man in Kansas City.
Wanted man in Ohio.
Wanted man in Mississippi.
Wanted man in old Cheyenne.
Wherever you might look tonight, you might see this wanted man.
I might be in Colorado or Georgia by the sea.
Working for some man who may not know who I might be.
And if you ever see me coming, and if you know who I am,
don't you breathe it to nobody, cause you know I'm on the lam.
Wanted man by Lucy Watson.
Wanted man by Jeannie Brown.
Wanted man by Nellie Johnson.
Wanted man in this next town.
Well, I've had all that I've wanted.
Of all the things I've wanted.
Of a lot of things I've had.
And a lot more than I needed.
Of some things that turned out bad.
I got sidetracked in El Paso.
Stopped to get myself a map.
Went the wrong way into Juarez with Juanita on my lap.
There's a lot of things I've had.
And I went to sleep in Shreveport.
Woke up in Abilene.
Wondering why I'm wanted at some town headway between.
Wanted man in Albuquerque.
Wanted man in Syracuse.
Wanted man in Tallahassee.
Wanted man in Baton Rouge.
Wanted man in San Jose.
Wanted man in San Pedro.
Wanted man in San Diego.
Wanted man in San Diego, and wherever I go.
Wanted man in Chicago.
Wanted man in San Diego.
Wherever you might look at night, you might see this wanted man.
And worse awaits you at the Church of the Subgenius.
Got that pencil ready for an address?
That's www.subgenius.com or
The next hour of Slack, friends, next week will be the Devo special.
Every year after the devotional, we cover the great devos.
And so we shall this time again with the greatest covers ever, ever, ever.
Praise Bob.
Heaven and hell.
Yes.
I tried to get a concept.
Right, right, right.
And big brain.
Heaven.
That's fascinating.
No, no.
And.
That's.
Jesus Christ.
The.
In the Jesus Christ.
The Jesus.
Or.
Big Jesus Christ.
And.
Jesus me.
And then.
And then it.
To.
Was.
The.
In a.
The Satan himself.
In a huge house overlooking the ocean in the tropics.
Sure.
Right.
Well, that was fun.
Now for eons of loneliness.
And.