Ah, yes, there.
You see that coin?
That is insured for $10,000.
See how it seems to gather the light and draw the eye?
Yeah.
I get great repose from these things of age and beauty.
They soothe one and seem to induce sleep.
Sleep.
Close your eyes, my friend.
Hello, everybody.
Look out!
Shut up!
Come in.
$772,000.
Shut up!
$341,000.
Shut your face!
Is that correct?
Yes, it is.
$61,000.
Thank you.
Shut up!
That will be all for the present.
Very good.
The Subgenius Powerhouse.
Watch.
Excellent.
And at the top of the show, we've got a very interesting guest to be sure.
Reverend Ivan Stang.
He's the founder of the Church of the Subgenius and the book,
The Subgenius Cyclopedia of Slack, the Bobliagraphon.
That's right.
Stick around.
You're going to say, what?
Of course, the question is, who's Bob?
Well, Bob's an interesting guy.
He gets high on the real thing.
A full tank of gas and a clean windshield.
All righty then.
First off...
Worried about covering the lower half of your body?
Here's Bob One for A1 Slack.
Things go better with slacks and trousers.
Things go better with slacks.
Hi, this is Bob One.
And I wonder how many of our go-go-now-generation-action-man-on-compass realizes
how important it is to keep the lower half of your body covered
without disguising the fact that it is indeed the lower half of your body.
Well, there's nothing like a pair of trim-fitting A1 slacks.
They're better than skirts and a lot warmer, too.
Thank you, Bob.
You're welcome.
And now, back to our movie.
Looks like we're going to find more and we expect it.
Bob.
I know who he is.
Fred hissed.
So what?
Said Nobby.
He's a raving genius.
He is a loony.
Yeah.
Well, they say there's a thin line between genius and madness.
He's fallen off it then.
But Terry Pratchett went first.
Thanks to Lee Murr for the song and intro,
Reverend Zontar for the ancient fire sign theater actual radio ad,
and Frankenstein1970 from 1959.
Welcome to Hour of Slack number 1143,
a Bob Renewal reintroduction to that most important thing in the world,
for those who might have briefly forgotten.
The first in a series of shows using categorized bits of the recordings
from a dozen recent Lives of Genius outreach events,
hither and yon, which it has taken me many days to chop up.
Besides the collage work of Noor El-Pref, Lee Murr, and yours truly, Reverend Stang,
we'll also be hearing from the Winter Star Devival of March 1, 2008,
John Hell's show on Pirate Cat Radio from last December,
a puzzling evidence show from Berkeley on February 22,
and a radio synesthesia show from WCSB Cleveland on March 9,
and a Denver, Colorado talk show excerpted from Rick Barber's show on KOA Denver,
and also some real radio ads from the fire sign theater, more of those,
prompted by Zontar.
We're hearing Bonobo's Convergence in the background, recorded live last X-Day.
And I think that's all.
Oh, Bonobo's Convergence will be at next X-Day, Drew.
We've been on the road a lot, friends,
and I've just now chopped all this audio into millions of tiny bits.
And also tonight, I'm working in some audio swipe from a great movie called Slipstream,
directed by Anthony Hopkins,
which makes David Lynch look like Michael Bay.
And we even have some new songs.
And next week or two, it'll be all politics on the show, friends.
Yes, I'm afraid so.
So let's bask for now in pure, untainted bobbery, at least for this week,
starting with what the curious heard as they approached the giant subgenius circus tent
at Winter Star 2008.
Last March 1st.
Ladies and gentlemen, step right up.
Welcome to the subgenius medical curiosity show.
It's all real, all here, all alive.
And it's all on the inside.
See the smart boy who can't keep a job.
See the pretty girl who can't get a date.
Alive and on the inside.
We have diseases that are spread through sexual...
Congress.
We have debates settled by fisticuffs.
We have people famous for being famous.
And they're all inside.
Alive, alive, alive.
See grown men and women talk to an invisible monster that lives in the sky.
See your own body become ever more fragile before your very eyes.
Feel the horror as schools turn innocent children into innocent adults.
Listen to shock.
And listen to shocking tales wherein you pay to work.
They're all here on the inside.
We have pictures of a salesman who smokes a pipe.
What other religions charge all worldly goods for what we offer at a discounted and guaranteed low rate?
Eternal salvation or triple your money back.
Read words on a cathode ray tube.
And attend amateur religious satire performance art.
Get slack.
And feel alive.
On the inside.
I wish I could say that I wrote that.
But actually that was recorded outside a freak show by Dr. Onan Kanabite.
I don't think they ought to live for that one.
Anyway, that's what happened on this date in history.
Well, we're going to talk about something that you may not know about.
And those of you who have heard of it, you might find this most interesting indeed.
The Church of the Subgenius, founded in 1953.
And although its current popularity is traced to the publication of Subgenius pamphlet number one in 1979,
it's found quite a bit of acceptance, especially in underground pop cult circles,
embraced on college campuses, in the underground music scene, on the Internet.
And because the tenets of discordianism, the Church of the Subgenius is often described as,
as a syncretic offshoot of the belief.
However, members state that the organization developed on its own with the publication of Subgenius pamphlet number one,
also known as The World Ends Tomorrow and You May Die by Reverend Ivan Stang, who is our guest.
And Reverend Stang, good morning.
Well, I praise Rick, praise Bob, and happy birthday, Dan Quayle.
Dan Quayle.
It's not true, but it's alleged that, of course, you know, he was head of the space program during Daddy Boy.
Bush's era.
And there was.
Appropriate.
Yeah.
And there was, there was, there was this, this kind of this, you know, almost underground, shall we say, legend,
that Dan thought it would be a good idea to send a mission to the sun, but because it was so hot, he thought we'd do it at night.
There you go.
See, and that's my kind of guy, you know.
All right, Dan.
We always considered him a sort of an honorary subgenius.
Well, you.
Even though he never officially joined up, he somehow, he definitely was, was not a genius.
He certainly not.
So we knew that he would qualify for our august organization.
Indeed.
Tell us something about the Church of the Subgenius, and by the way, who is Bob?
J.R. Bob Dobbs is our guru and the sort of, you might say, the god of the subgeniuses and of strippers, I'm told.
Cool.
Yeah.
Bob, some of your listeners may be familiar with his face, which you see tattooed on kids and spray painted on cars and so forth.
He looks like, he looks like the 1950s version of the all-around good guy dad on sitcoms.
That's right.
And if you look at any old magazine, it'll be full of ads of these square looking happy guys with pipes.
They're always smoking a pipe.
Right.
Laying in a hammock while somebody else mows the yard.
And we, my partner and I, Dr. Philodruman and I, had noticed that the same figure popped up in all these old magazines and in old movies.
We thought it must be the same guy.
And at that point, Bob revealed himself to us through weird coincidences and messages and things.
Not too many people have actually met Bob in person and survived.
In other words, you cannot look upon the face of Bob.
Well, he's so lucky, I think he manages to avoid most of his followers without even trying to.
I'm looking at the picture of the Kababala.
We owe a lot to other religions.
It's true that we, when we were, we were born in the United States.
We, trying to put the, the Church of the Subgenius structure together.
We, as Bob directed us, we studied all the great religions from Zoroastrianism all the way up to Scientology.
And we picked all the good parts, you know.
Yeah.
When you were a kid, you'd find your dad's secret stash of paperbacks and look for the good parts.
Uh-huh.
That's what we did with our dad's holy books.
Nice.
I was always looking for my own stash of Mad Magazine, which my father would hide.
Well, you just mentioned one of our true holy books is Mad Magazine and their great publisher, William Gaines.
And the great Alfred E. Newman, who is a cousin to Bob.
I always thought, I always thought there was a kind of a connection there.
Yeah, he's, well, Bob's better looking.
But, yeah, they are related.
I think Alfred E. Newman was more like the country cousin.
And he's a little older than Bob in real life.
They both are ageless figures.
Now, the, the, and by the way, I'm looking at some of the names that involve high-profile names like Paul Rubens, Pee-wee Herman, who placed a picture of Bob in every episode of Pee-wee's Playhouse.
David Byrne, Mark Motherspaugh, Penn Jillette, Penn and Teller, Robert Wilson, Robert Anton Wilson, science fiction writers Rudy Rucker, John Shirley, actor Bruce Campbell.
Even Frank Zalman.
Yeah, so far, all of those are true.
I don't think any of those are lies or exaggerations.
Well, I'm almost certain it's probably true, especially in the Pee-wee Herman stuff.
Well, you could see, but he had Pee-wee in his title sequence every Saturday morning.
All the kids of America saw Bob leering over Pee-wee's shoulder during the titles.
Pee-wee never paid for his membership.
He left a phone message asking us to send him an ordainment.
Yeah.
He had a package so he could be a minister.
But he never, and he said, Bill me.
And we did, but he never paid up.
Which in our church really is a pretty major sin.
But I figure putting Bob on CBS for a year was worth at least $10.
Well, at least.
Yeah.
I mean, and afterward, you had to give the guy some slack.
Yeah, poor Pee-wee.
He really is.
It's a shame what happened to him.
Well, yeah, I always wondered, you know, all you got busted for doing what?
It's a big deal.
Try your 13-year-old kid.
Like the old t-shirt used to say, we're pulling for you, Pee-wee.
You betcha.
Bob, if he isn't done.
Bob?
Yeah, I dig you, Bob.
Bob.
Oh, Bob.
How long will it be?
Bob, I'm gonna miss you.
Bob's a bad influence on me.
What?
Oh, Bob, he's so charming and continental.
.
This is Bob.
I know Bob.
Oh, Bob, I don't know when I've been so hungry and .
Bob, you really shouldn't have given me yours.
Oh, Bob, I don't think I can eat one.
I'm full of greens right up to here.
Fill me up.
.
I got pot.
You naughty, naughty boy.
Bob, would you like to buy some information?
I've got it, Bob.
Oh, Bob.
So, uh, tell me, Bob, you're a good boy.
You're a good boy.
.
You know, what is the church of the subgenius?
Good question.
We're still trying to figure that out ourselves.
Uh, you know, it's like, well, is this a joke or is it a real religion?
And our answer is, why not both?
Uh, we are probably one of the only serious religions that admits that it's, we're completely
full of crap.
And as such, possibly the only true and honest religion.
Doesn't that just figure?
.
You know, um, but we have the problem of, uh, uh, Bobbies.
They're, they're the ones that want to, they're so excited about it, they immediately want
to start telling all the inside jokes and they haven't even gotten the outside joke
yet.
.
And, uh, some of them, I mean, really need luck getting the, but basically, uh, back
in 1953.
.
This, uh, uh, the man, this, that man, J.R., Bob Dobbs, and by the way, the J.R. doesn't
spell for, stand for anything.
It's on his birth certificate with, even with quotes on the name Bob.
Bob was a mere salesman.
Well not a mere salesman.
He was actually the greatest salesman the world has ever known.
Uh, and he was pretty, he, but he was very young then and he was just starting out on
his, his road, his path.
Religion had nothing to do with it.
He was just interested in money like any sane person.
But he was tinkering with, uh, uh, uh, a T. He was trying to build his own TV set and
it was, he was in his basement standing in a puddle and suddenly he had this, he was
seized up in the spirit.
He had this, this, this epiphany, which we call the divine immaculation of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
.
Hiding in his basement, hiding hisOPOs or any, hides UFOs and so forth.
None of that stuff.
And it was a conspiracy of plain and ordinary garden variety, normal human beings who didn't
even know they were part of a conspiracy, but just automatically, out of the fear of
anything different, had been keeping down and oppressing the slack of all the weirdos,
the abnormals, the different people, uh, the disbelievers, and most importantly, those
. . . . . . . . . who will be in danger.
believe anything. And that is when the Church of the Subgenius was formed. Not on a solid rock,
like some of our more prosperous competitors, but on a shifting sandy beach of pure hypocrisy.
Hypocrisy, friends, that is the beach our church is built on. We have a million rules,
which can all be read in our three books, but there's only one that really counts.
And since there's no one here but children, I'll say it in full vulgar English. The one
rule of the Church of the Subgenius is, fuck them if they can't take a joke.
So if you are feeling tender today, you should perhaps leave.
The Bob Show, brought to you by Bob.
Permanent, perfect, permanent, perfect. And here he is, Bob.
Smile, stop, smile, stop. You bet your life, you bet your life, there is heaven right here on Earth.
There is heaven right here on Earth.
Heaven right here on Earth.
Home of the dick jazz. So come on, guys and gals.
Won't you come along with me? Heaven on Earth.
No fussy, frizzy curls for this smart girl. She has a Bob. The perfect, permanent, permanent,
tight, kinky with a Bob. Because Bob is so easy, you can do it yourself.
Just regular pin curls and gentle Bob-otion. That's all you need. A Bob. A Bob-new body.
Make your next permanent a Bob. Bob-permanent. Permanent.
Give yourself a Bob. Give yourself a Bob. Give yourself a Bob. Give yourself a Bob.
You'll go Bob-Bob-Bobbing along with your Bob.
My Mommadant told me, my Mommadant told me.
My Mommadant me.
My mama done beat a worrisome thing, a worrisome thing.
Train it, train it, train it, train it.
My mama done, my mama done beat.
Woo!
Never before a stick so red, redder than a fire engine.
See what stick can do for you.
The comf, the comf, long-lasting.
You'll just love Bob.
Be sure to listen again next week
when Bob Perfect for Today again brings you
The Bob Show from Bobby Wood.
This girl knows that Bob is the essence of romance.
Who tonight?
BanditNorelPref.com is the essence of collagery,
as most of the subsequent collagers will continue to demonstrate.
And just as Fernanda Nande-Lemur is the killer of Bob.
You'll have to get rid of him somehow for good.
But how suddenly you found the answer?
It's as simple as kill Bob.
Kill Bob.
If he contacts you, don't try to help him.
He's dangerous.
Bob, Bob.
Hello?
Hello.
Did you hear the news on the radio?
They say I killed Bob.
Guess that's when I must have fallen asleep.
Bob's the only person I can kill.
I can kill Bob.
First thing I saw was Bob's body.
Then the gun beside me and I killed Bob.
Are you sure?
I'm afraid so, Bob.
I don't think the police will believe it.
But it's the truth.
I killed Bob.
Yes, Bob.
You've got to answer it, Bob.
Hello?
Hello, Bob.
Oh, darling.
Listen to me, Bob.
She was in love with Bob.
Oh, no, Bob.
I was at the cock party.
I actually thought I could kill Bob.
Where did you go after the cock party last night?
Somebody set up a boot trap in your cabin.
It was a dark one, Bob.
And it did just that.
I said I could kill Bob.
She meant that boot trap for you.
Don't look away, Bob.
Perhaps I did kill Bob.
Doesn't that make sense?
Well, yes.
Yes, it makes sense.
Yes, Bob.
Bob.
Listen, Bob.
I'm sorry about Gavin, but he's a little stressed.
Okay, but hell, he doesn't have to jump down my throat.
Does he have a family or relatives?
Yeah, I have a wife and a child.
You know, the deceased, what's his name, Dobbs?
Does he have a family?
Yes, he does.
He has a family.
He has a wife and two young kids.
I think they're divorced.
His kids are divorced?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Do you laugh at anything?
I mean, do you just laugh at anything?
A man has died.
She thinks this is funny.
No, no.
Are all you movie people like this?
Go, go.
Here's Bob One for A1 Slack.
Hi, this is Bob One.
Years ago, my grandfather Abner One, known for short because he was,
invented the A1 Slack.
However, today's go-go action now, gentlemen,
the generation man on campus and off, wants a little more out of life.
So, we added another leg to our super slim from fitting A1 Slack,
and came up with super slim from fitting A1 Slacks.
A1 Slacks, the two-legged action slacks for the two-legged action man.
Thank you, Bob.
You're welcome.
And now, back to our movie.
Looks like we're gonna find more and we expect it.
And we've, over the years, because of the churches,
we went public in 19...
Actually, July... January 1st, 1980,
we printed the first sacred subgenius pamphlet
and have been misunderstood from that day on.
But, you know, as they say,
those who know don't say and those who say don't know.
So, we should all just shut up.
And, but look here, we keep blabbering on and on.
Is it the drugs?
That's what the Cleveland Police Department might tell you.
In fact, a friend of ours sat in on a, uh,
a lecture to the Cleveland Police Department
by a cult expert who explained that Bob was a sign for Satan
and drugs and stuff.
But, obviously, friends, this is a religion.
Bob is here to replace the drugs!
Just looking at his face eats up more brain cells than most of your drugs.
If you're doing it right, like a real subgenius,
if you can meditate upon the dots,
every little dot...
So many of you have done this, I know.
You just, you just focus on that thing
and by, after a while, you feel so much slack.
It's like heroin combined with PCP
combined with DDT, LSD, and, uh,
marijuana, as my father puts it.
Um, but what, but what Bob's preaching is, is, uh,
the joy of drugs, but not necessarily with the drugs,
although those can certainly enhance everything for the first ten minutes.
Uh, so, uh, but we, what Bob preaches is slack, friends.
And slack is so simple that I can't explain it.
Because it's different for each person.
Everybody has their own form of slack.
Uh, some people,
uh, get their slack from,
uh, sitting on their ass watching TV and drinking beer.
There's nothing wrong with that.
The conspiracy of the normal people would love for that to be the only way
you feel you're getting slack.
We're here just as a pep talk, just a reminder
that, uh, slack is whatever makes you feel
like you're doing what you were supposed to be doing.
And that could be anything, you know, for, for,
uh, for our friend, uh, uh, Dennis Murphy here.
Uh, slack might be, um,
God, I can't even begin to imagine.
Maybe I should have picked a different, uh, you know,
some people like bird watching, right?
Some people like pornography.
Some people like, uh, movies, you know?
Some people like people.
And, and just, uh, hanging out and, and, uh, talking
can be your purest form of slack.
And you can steal that slack while on the job,
as you've learned around the coffee machine, uh, I'm sure.
As, as my, my good friend and, uh, and speechwriter,
you might say, Dr. Onan, can a bite put it,
slack is the oomph in un, in comfortable.
That's it.
See, he has, uh, he has some stage.
He has, he says, slack is the oomph in comfortable.
He says,
oomph is a co, is accompanied by a gesture of vigor
from the hips among adults or a pumped elbow on US TV.
So, it could actually be slack is the oomph in un, in comfortable.
Why do I keep wanting to say uncomfortable?
Uh, and as I said, slack can come when you throw good money after bad
and bad money after Bob, and that's why that sales table is out there.
This, oh, and we have a new book out, uh, Intelligent Design for Dummies.
Our, our new, uh, publication.
And for those, so, so be sure if you think you've already bought
all the accessories that go with Ken and Barbie,
there's some new accessories out there.
Um, so, uh.
So, you know, Bob has many death days.
What's his birthday?
Yeah.
Bob has had so many lives, so many past lives that, that by chance,
you know, one of almost every day of the year is the birthday of a Bob.
So, where is Bob now?
Is there, is there, is there somebody that we should be looking towards?
Where is Bob?
Is he mayhaps fishing, uh, on Lake Titicaca with G. Gordon Gordon?
Is he perhaps selling ice to an Eskimo somewhere in Alaska?
Yeah.
Is he perhaps selling hypocrisy to a subgenius in San Francisco?
But Bob is a traveling salesman and resides at no fixed address.
Unlike, uh, the god of the Mormons who is, uh, known to be, uh,
on a planet circling the star Koloff, having sex with his many spirit wives.
...star Bob, a guy named Smith on terrible pieces.
Although, uh, we don't know where Bob is now.
Joseph Smith?
We know that Bob is coming.
And when I say that, I don't mean...
It has been said.
It's not like when Jesus is coming.
That, that usually means Jesus is on his way, is due to arrive.
When we say Bob is coming...
Like Santa Claus.
Bob is literally, that is what Bob is.
...is always coming.
And it's true, I mean, but isn't he sometimes there, and then at other times not?
Yeah.
When you come tonight, you will see Bob.
Well, otherwise...
I'll be looking...
...with a big, close...
...about an hour and a half.
...self-defeating.
I will.
I don't want to see him.
No, no, I'll be, I'll be home by then.
And you can't move.
I know.
That's okay.
But I just don't want to see him during that, uh, thing, you know.
You can't move.
You don't want to be everywhere.
But I mean, don't you think you'd understand it all at that point?
Or maybe not.
I think that's when the shark bites you.
That's the part I thought about.
Because you're looking...
You're out there swimming around, and a shark bites you, and if you're...
Because you're being distracted.
Yeah, and if you're together enough to understand that last big organism, then, then you're pretty
well set.
Instead of, instead of, uh, the music stopping and you're just left out there...
Well, you shouldn't have...
Like some amateur show...
No, it's now that Bob's coming your way.
...in your field of biology.
He is?
Ah!
Oh!
Karunch.
Bob!
I mean, no, I said, oh, God.
I mean, oh, Bob, I did.
Well, there are no atheists in foxholes.
I'm sorry.
Stop it!
Don't!
You're right!
You killed Bob Mirror because now we're free.
Was that別夕 merge yours and mine together to cause this carnage.
That Пр tul.' bearing.
Ahhh...
Bład My Table Hot Yol Salad!
Just eliminating ships over on the surface, Mary?
partido mum!
We're really equallyattackable!
Hi, y'all.
Bollywood.
We are Et enabling for fin приех posts on YouTube!
Well, all I'm nosotros at this time because we need to hear one last story.
produce that. There's that Lithuanian
actor. Johnny Depp plays
the young Ivan Stang
and Jim Carrey
plays Violet Drummond.
I don't know who else has been
cast yet, but
Bob would be Andy
Serkis, the guy that played
Gollum and Kong.
That would be good.
He would basically be a performance
capture. And Mike Myers
is the voice of Cthulhu.
You can see we've been thinking about
that. Very true.
Any love interests in the film?
Yeah.
The hero would be Lonesome Cowboy
Dave and I think it would be
his...
He'd be courting
a popular
bullgirl Dave Vina.
Voiced by Lindsay Lohan.
In a bikini.
Just because. And they're all
penguins, right?
That's right. They're all CGI
penguins.
Thousands and thousands.
And then there's the Spielberg Saturday morning TV
show Lil' Subgenius.
Dear Subgenius!
I said Lil' Subgenius.
Lil' Subgenius.
With Pip and Squeak.
Well, we've been waiting for the remake.
That was the Sid and Marty
Croft production. What, the remake?
That was a great...
Original, Lil'?
Second big feature was another one of my favorites.
I never saw the remake. What is that about?
What is this thing?
It stinks.
That was a joke. That was a joke.
It stinks. What is this thing?
The second big feature was
a possible name
for a Subgenius feature movie.
What was the name?
Second big feature.
I thought they were like a real band.
Second big feature?
Yeah, but Philo disabused me of that notion tonight.
He said it was just negative land.
The Swingin' Love.
Wait, write that down. That's a good name for a band.
Yeah.
Negative man. Negative land.
Nobody expected what happened next.
Sensational career.
I'm Bob.
So why are so many people
flocking to
to to to to
Bob?
My message is that God is a
hope
that he'll take us places we've never dreamed of.
It's hard
to break a dick, to break a dick.
You may be misleading some people
so big
being gay.
Gay and generous.
Leading them to some
false god or something like that.
Deluding and dumbing down.
You know
Right up there with gardening.
Bam! There's a hit.
Great, great, great, great, great, great.
Wait, you're saying that...
Great, great, great, great, great, great, great.
Oh my god!
Nothing.
Make beautiful women fall all over you.
No doubt there.
Take steroids.
Slack, slack, slack.
Cut, cut. I'm weak.
Uh, now, now, a lot of people say that, uh,
some terms that are in the, in the, as you say, the Bobliographer on the, the, uh...
the, the cyclopedia, uh, it kind of uses, uh,
notions, uh, similar to, not the same as, but, but in the same area as Scientology
or kind of a New Age-y, but, but, but in a fashion that, that's almost Dada-esque.
Well, um, you know, any religion or priesthood is, uh, based on impenetrable jargon.
Lawyers, doctors, for instance.
And we get a lot of, of, uh, lawyers, doctors joining up because they appreciate...
that impenetrable obfuscation.
Uh, uh...
invented words and
words that have been
recombined.
So that when you're reading this stuff,
you feel like you're really part of a secret
army. And the great thing
is, you are.
It's not much of a...
I mean, it's still a secret, so it's not that much
of an army. Not much of an army, yeah.
But, you know, it's kind of like what they used
to say about Fight Club.
First rule, don't talk about it.
Don't talk about it, yeah. Of course, naturally, everybody
talks about it.
Well, and, you know, the Hell's Angels used to say
those who say don't know
and those who know don't say.
And we should probably just shut up.
Well, yeah, and that's a show
that would go right to hell.
I like one thing about it,
and I always say, you know, this has got to be
the best deal in
organized, shall we say,
religion or church,
and that is guaranteed
salvation or triple your
money back. That's right. Eternal
salvation or triple your money back.
That's an offer that no other
religion makes. Well, I, you know,
none of them do, and I'm thinking, you know,
now, there's one you can grasp.
That's the kind of church I can
get behind. Right. Or in front of.
It costs $30 to join,
and that means that if you,
at the end of time, find yourself
in the pit of hell,
we will
gladly refund your money.
Not only your $30, we'll give you
$90.
Now, there is a little book that you can,
that Bob sells down there called
Hell on Five Cents a Day,
which I think is
$89.95. Nowadays, yeah.
And a day lasts a long
time. In hell. Yeah,
in normal hell. Now, subgenius hell is
kind of like an endless party.
Well, that's my idea of a good idea.
Right. Yeah.
Now, we, I,
you know, this,
it's possible, some people think this subgenius
thing is just a joke.
And,
I mean, some people think. Well, compared to what, though?
Right, exactly. You know,
everybody's religion is going to be a joke to
somebody else. Yeah, I was going to say,
one of them has to be true. What if it was
this one? Who knows? Who knows?
Crazier things have happened.
Look at the
Inquisition. Look at the news.
See?
Yeah, you know,
I wouldn't be surprised
at anything
that would happen, although we're,
we are kind of behind Scientology,
we got started a little bit later.
That's all right. So did L. Ron Hubbard.
Hold on a second, if you will,
Reverend, we're going to take a quick break.
Reverend Ivan Stang, he is
the founder of the Church of the Subgenius,
and talking more about
the Church of the Subgenius, for those of you out there
who have never heard of it, well, here's a chance
to find a religion you can really get behind,
or next to, or in front of, or
you know, something.
Video now, video, if not, I'm going to see it for you.
Yeah, it's
definitely one of the world's fastest
growing religions.
But it's not a snack religion.
Well, it is a sack religion.
No, a snack.
Oh, you're sure?
It's a snack religion.
Okay.
We push Bob as a short-duration
personal savior.
We don't expect you to cling to it forever.
We don't want you to use
Bob as a crutch. Rather, we want
to let, you should
let Bob use
you as a crutch.
You are Bob's crutch.
I'm interested in your information.
I'd like to subscribe to the newsletter.
Wait, I already do.
You go to subgenius.com and
click on the news button.
It's actually all very logical.
There used to be a hard copy, that
famous publication,
The Stark Fist of Removal.
But in the cyber age,
it doesn't come out very often.
We allow special members to print out
the online version.
Well, you know, and Dobbs made
most of his important deals in strange
places when he first started out, like
a Waffle House in Haightville,
Georgia. I thought it was Ellicott City,
Maryland. It was the Stuckeys
in Texas.
Well, there were several.
He knows all this stuff. Right.
Where was it?
He fell asleep.
Stank.
I think
Stank's done.
He's suffering the wounds of
cripes.
Hey, you know, I got a joke.
What's the difference between Jesus Christ
and a picture of Jesus Christ?
Are you guys talking about me?
We were saying we're
I was actually
in the process of flipping
a tape.
Are we supposed to be funny now?
No, I don't think so.
We wanted to know the connection between the Raelians
on the one hand,
Dr. Sinister's show, and
Bob's hardest sell.
Not anything you can do with primate arrest.
So what is what's the difference between
now? What's the difference between Jesus and a picture of him?
I don't know.
Oh, yeah, that was it.
Yeah.
What's the difference between Jesus Christ and a picture of Jesus Christ?
You only need one nail to hang up the picture.
Oh, hey, what's it?
What's the difference between Jesus Christ and a picture of Jesus Christ?
The picture is real.
Keep going.
Oh, but Bob is real.
Bob is real.
He's real.
You know, you don't want to offend the Arabs saying Bob is real.
Bob is real.
And there was a waitress in in
April, Georgia, who I can't say this stuff on the air.
Sure, you can.
Well, I can't.
It is.
I get somebody found a dog's head in a pancake.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's much more complicated than that.
Well, I met her.
I was it was about three o'clock in the morning and she was
a Waffle House waitress, which, you know, is pretty normal.
And and she started telling me I had on a dog shirt and she said, I've seen him.
He was here with these weird guys.
And she tells me this long story and I can't really tell it on the air to not giving.
I don't want to give away too many secrets.
Well, like the guys weren't really guys.
They were like aliens.
You know what?
Yeah.
But she had met Bob just that she had met Bob.
Oh, she had served Bob a cup of coffee.
That's not unusual.
A Bob often has been where a subgenius arrives just before the subgenius got there.
You hear that all the time.
So actually, I've seen him arriving just as Bob has just has left.
I've seen him a couple of times, actually, a memory or a premonition because it's so fleeting.
And they're just aware of something having happened.
I've seen him driving away twice.
I've seen him getting Bob on the highway at least twice.
Actually, I saw him get thrown out of a car.
I saw him get thrown out of a car at a coffee shop, actually, because really, because he wouldn't put his pipe out, you know, and they threw him out.
And like that, exactly.
And then I but I figured I'd just leave it, you know, hands off, you know.
And I don't know what exactly it was, but the people in there got really upset about something.
They forcibly threw him out, like literally threw him out.
And right as soon as he threw him out, a big bus came by and hit him right as he threw him out there.
And then he was gone.
You see, that's unusual.
All I saw left behind was like.
There was like some.
Like a smoldering of the of like a broken pipe there.
But then again, you know, next week I saw Bob again.
You know, he was fine.
Yeah. Well, you know, it's funny.
The reason the waitress was asking about the shirt I had on is that Bob never paid his bill.
Oh, why is it always the rich ones?
You know, it really was Bob.
Why is it always the rich ones?
It was like the first night they were open at this particular location.
This had to have been back in like 58 or so.
60.
And she still remembered the guy because he stiffed her.
You know.
Well, you always remember the person who stiffed you.
Yeah.
Especially if they look like that, you know, they're grinning while they do it.
Your first night getting stiffed.
Yeah, we always remember that.
Has anybody delivered a peach to Bob and, you know, 13 cents tip, get the idea?
Wow, a whole 13 cents?
That's pretty good.
Bob doesn't tip the drivers either.
That's happened.
I know a driver who delivered to him.
And he was like, I'm going to pay you.
And Bob doesn't tip.
Bob says, let me give you a tip.
Don't get screwed or something really dumb and witty like that.
Yeah, he grabs the clementine.
It's the same thing to every pizza delivery guy.
Yeah.
My dad does that too.
Do you know how a leper leaves a tip for a hooker?
Oh.
We can stop there.
Man.
That was a quick one.
It was good.
That was quick.
It's old.
Yeah.
Old like me.
You know, and when I get home, I'll chop up another three shows out of this one real
fast and take off for Texas to Stang County where we go every December to help oversee
construction on the compound.
We're building a big cult compound in Stang County, Texas.
You don't want to go down by Stang County, son.
I don't want to go down by Stang County, son.
It's near Dead Branch Pass.
Actually, Stang County has a nuclear power plant that serves Dallas.
It has a really big tax base.
We have a lot of tax money because of that.
And my family is very involved in city politics, county politics, and so forth.
So we've been able to go forward on construction of this underground bunker.
It started as a mine.
It's an abandoned missile silo bunker.
Even better.
There are a lot of those in Texas.
They've done the digging for you.
Yeah, that's right.
I saw something a while back about people living in these, in the bunkers, owning them,
right?
Yeah.
We did that, and we also have extensive tunneling going on.
To the mall.
Luckily, there's uranium, raw uranium on the land of Stang County.
Brilliant.
And goats.
Like every good cow.
Why not?
Well, goats, you may ask.
Well, because there was a drought.
Why a goat?
And the cows, there wasn't enough grass for the cows or the zombies.
Goats in Jehovah.
Yeah.
But the goats, the goats are happy.
We actually have a cult compound in Texas.
Told he was busted, too.
With goats.
Slightly radioactive goats.
Yeah.
Machine gun, you know, encampments.
The horns glow.
It's a terrible thing.
So we, most of it is, you know, it's a very, very, very important thing.
And then, most of the time, the other members of the Stang clan run the ranch.
I just go down there every now and then to oversee this.
The Stang stomping ground.
The killing hounds.
Stang likes to go down to supervise the killings.
And the bodies.
We're going to build a big TV studio there.
And a crystal cathedral.
And a drive-through crystal cathedral.
And a creation.
Drive-through.
Drive by.
And we're going to have a Grand Canyon on the Grand Canyon.
a special museum about the
way evolution really worked.
Where subgeniuses really
came from.
Audio animatronic yeti.
The arrival of the exes, the
creation of the humans by the yetis
and so forth. That's actually my favorite part
where they have the audio animatronic staying
and throwing the guys and talking
and their arms kind of move.
Are you familiar with the creation of the
humanoids movie?
Yes, most certainly.
That's a great film.
A mandatory subgenius movie.
Why doesn't he listen to you?
What's his name? Gavin. Right, Garvin.
I can never remember his name.
So why doesn't he listen
to you, huh? I tend to rattle
his cage. He doesn't like it.
Was it like this before the actor? What was his name?
The one who died? Dobbs. Yeah, Hobbs.
What was going on then, huh? Anarchy.
Dobbs was rewriting the script.
He'd call script conferences
every morning before shooting and made everyone crazy.
We already had a script. What was the problem, huh?
An actor. What can I tell you?
He wasn't even good at it, you know?
He was the look-at-me-scratch-my-balls
school of acting.
Such assholes. I asked this guy, Dobbs.
I asked him last week. I said, why are you doing this?
What did he say? He said it was a generational thing.
What's that mean, huh?
Beats the hell out of me.
Little puke.
Come on! You couldn't do anything
to stop it? What could I do?
Gavin had no control.
He was terrified.
Couldn't make decisions about anything,
even about breakfast.
Could've helped me, you know.
Works. Dobbs, Dobbs, Dobbs, Dobbs.
Colt, Colt. Just out of time.
Dobbs, Dobbs, Dobbs, Dobbs. Went off.
The incredible last wrong.
Committed. Committed.
Now you do know,
Colt.
You know, with ADHD and, you know,
just kind of, you know, you know,
you know, um...
You know, uh...
Put your arm around
these young men.
Watch it. Watch it.
You know, but Colt, I...
I... It's my Colt.
I, uh, you know, you know,
Secret Life on the Internet Colt.
Uh, uh, uh, uh, well, doody-doody.
Uh, uh.
It doesn't make any sense, you know.
Action.
And so we were, you know, coming.
You know, it's, you know, you know.
Hmm, hmm.
So we got off, you know.
I'm really deeply involved in girls
and boys and girls today.
Mm-hmm.
Cult. Perfect.
Gone down the wrong road.
Good. Beautiful.
Crazy things get said.
Mm-hmm.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
Back again.
We're up right against the top of the hour
and, of course, a news update.
But I want to, uh, get some final details
from our good guest, the Reverend Ivan Stang.
He's, uh, the headmaster, I guess.
No, my title is Sacred Scribe.
Cool.
All right.
Sacred Scribe number 273.
Bob Dobbs is the living avatar of Slack.
Wow.
That's his official title.
Not to be confused with the other Dobbs
down the road from us.
Um, for those who wish to find out more
and or get your books and your DVD
and also, by the way, that hell on five cents a day
kind of thing.
Um, how does one do this?
If you're on the Internet,
the simplest thing would be to look at subgenius.com.
And I'll, uh, subgenius does not have an O in it.
I have to say that because there are a lot of subgeniuses out there.
It's S-U-B-G-E-N-I-U-S.com.
All right.
Very good indeed.
And Reverend Stang, I'm going to, by the way,
I'm going to put you on hold.
My producer, Steve, needs to speak with you,
but, uh, I want to thank you so much.
It's been a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
I'm just, I'm a little concerned
that I'm going to have those monkeys songs
stuck in my head for the next three days.
An ear bug is the worst, isn't it?
Thank you very much.
Indeed.
And thank you very much.
Okay.
And please stay there, Reverend,
but thanks very much indeed.
Praise Rick.
And praise Ivan.
Anyway, we're going to take it up to the news.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm involved in a prostitution ring.
President Bush says the U.S. will help Poland
modernize its childhood obesity.
Mr. Bush says health officials,
are overweight.
I'm optimistic that we'll be able to live
in deprivation and fear.
Health officials say children and teenagers
are not immune from congressional subpoenas,
as claimed by the Bush administration.
The president also said today
that this is PR News in Washington.
A thanks to Leemur for that,
and PR News and laughing.
This has been Hour of Slight,
number 1143,
with Dr. Hal Pasling,
Evidence,
Philo Drummond,
John Hell,
Mongoloid,
and K-Rob in San Francisco,
Dr. Sinister and Princess Pisces,
and Lonesome Cowboy Dave on WCSB Cleveland,
and Governor Rocknar,
and No Money Mark.
The movie soundtrack that is so weird
is from Slipstream,
and the background music is
Bonobo's Convergence from Last X Day
and Next X Day.
And now,
from Norell,
this message.
For the safety of your smile,
see your dentist twice a day,
and you'll never be able to escape.
The Bob Show,
starring Bob,
and his guest star,
LeWin Thrill.
How do you do, ladies and gentlemen?
This is Bob.
I was so glad to be back,
I went down to the blood bank
and gave a pint of blood.
WC Fields was there, too.
He donated a fifth.
Trip the Light, fantastic.
Have you tried
going a little buggy
with a girl?
And a horse?
With a horse,
the horse wants to
to go out
for a little buggy.
Get a horse,
black or brown or gray.
But a horse...
Robert, quit putting it in your pipe.
Jugs.
I thought you used your nose for that.
You talk like I was a freak.
I was a freak, freak, freak.
Father, I'm down here
with a nice young man.
Get a horse...
Hello.
Wrong number.
Uh-oh.
Hello.
Remove that film.
Quickly, easily, safely.
No one, no one.
Get a tube, get a tube.
Ladies and gentlemen,
you really like the girls, don't you?
Yes, Bob, I do.
Now, ladies and gentlemen,
I'd like to introduce
one of the reals of genius.
Thank you very much.
I presume you're Bob.
The genius.
I'm becoming known
as the Bob of this generation.
Bob.
Magic Bob.
I know, Bob.
Why do I stand here
reading this stripe
when I can get a good job at Lockheed?
I'm Bob.
Sit down, Bob.
I'll read your future.
I can tell you
who's going to be
in the White House.
I do a lot of deep thinking.
Get loaded.
So, uh, someone died?
Yeah, Dobbs.
You wrote the part of Ray
for an African-American, right?
I did?
Yeah, man.
What's wrong with you?
Are you on drugs?
No, no, I'm not on drugs.
Ray, the character
that Dobbs was playing,
was black.
Dobbs wasn't a black actor, man.
He was white, like her.
Oh, my God.
Why did you kill me off feelings?
Barbara.
I was just a script supervisor.
That's all I was.
It was Barbara.
Now you have no continuity.
Nothing makes sense anymore.
It's so unfair.
It's just so unfair.
Go.
Mommy.
In dealing with supernatural
reanimated mummies
that play the old age homes
in that movie.
Just like DJs at Firecat Radio,
ladies and gentlemen.
One day they are going to mummify us.
And it will be an honor.
Your encrusted sarcophagus,
rich with jewels and hieroglyphs,
will be lowered into your own
personal home.
While sealed by the sands of time.
I want to be frozen in loose sight
like Bob did.
Bob is...
One of the Bobs is in loose sight.
To be frozen in the ice
like the Frankenstein in us,
which we lost.
Lost? Where did it go?
Well, I mean, we lost ownership of it.
But that's where Bob is?
One of the Bobs?
The one that puzzling evidence shot.
Damn you.
But he's like a...
What's a real flesh and blood Bob?
Bob, that Bob.
Wow.
The scary Bob.
When I introduced people to that Bob,
they would...
I remember where I was that day.
...do a great big double take.
The last thing you expect
is actually to be introduced to Bob.
A small Bob.
But then came that terrible day,
the Victoria Theatre Show.
The anniversary of the beheading
of Louis XVI and Marie Antoinette.
The assassination of Bob.
Yeah, we all remember where we were that day, don't we?
I know where I was.
And it's on videotape to prove it.
So, we have one Bob buried in Dallas.
Is that right?
Well, you go back over the
Hinckley Commission hearings,
the entire official answer
was sort of cobbled together
out of variants.
Strains of rumor and innuendo.
Where's the director?
Let's get on with it!
Cut, cut, cut!
Cut!
Hey, Harvey!
I didn't know you were...
It's his money, isn't it?
Well, I'm sorry, but you got it.
You got it.
Let's shot this.
Hot shot!
What are you talking about?
What have you been doing?
I've gotta get out.
I've gotta get out of here.
Stop.
What are you doing?
Doug!
Oh, my God!
I've gotta get back.
It's 4 o'clock.
My time's up.
I've gotta go.
Please, don't.
Please.
My time's up.
It's over.
I've gotta go.
I've gotta get back!
I'm almost home!
I'm here to help!
Please, don't hurt us!
We're not gonna hurt them.
What's wrong?
You have some kind of medication?
Peg!
Wait, wait!
Oh, my God!
What's that, dear?
Oh, yes, I heard.
I heard.
Poor old Felix.
Cut!
That's lunch, everyone!
That's it.
Good.
Now I will count three.
At the count of three, you will wake up and remember nothing.
One, two, three.
Ten thousand dollars.
What do you know?
Yes, beautiful, isn't it?
Ah, this castle is filled with rare old treasures.
Feel free to browse, my friend.
Thank you very much.
A pleasant good evening to you.