B.D.I.s flexing, flexing, eager to crush out life.
Great teeth gnashing with rage, powerful fingers flashing with hatred.
Boyd, what are you doing up on that thing?
And now, for the first time on the air...
The subgenius, our old swat.
Run!
How were we to dislodge him from his perch and bring him back alive?
That is how the Batiks, the natives, make a complete roof over your head.
Bizarre.
Well, sir? Well, sir, ma'am?
I better get this show on the road,
because Honey Dipper Dan is on his way to Stang Ranch here.
He'll be here in about half an hour.
We'll hear the dogs barking.
But I have to crank out a show,
and I might just end up talking for an entire hour,
because it's the quickest way to crank out a show.
If there's any cussing, I'll know where it was.
And it's...
The reason I've had to do reruns so much lately
and haven't been doing the call-ins with Dave and so forth
is that I've been stiff.
I've been stiffer and stiffer and stiffer.
I ain't stiff myself yet, but I'm really slowed down.
And because of a combination of a couple of kinds of arthritis
in my back and neck,
and 40 years of Church of the Subgenius,
and fossils,
and people collecting,
and landscaping of a large property,
I'd rather be trimming trails and lopping branches, honestly.
But I can't do much of that,
and I can't sit in one place for very long, friends.
The excess...
You know, sometimes I think X-Day is just happening continuously,
and they're just taking little bits and pieces of us up onto the...
escape vessels.
And they took the integrity of my lower back.
I can still walk and everything, but...
But I...
Everything's much slower.
I'm definitely 68 years old.
Things have slowed down.
And there's a lot of things that I want to get done
besides this show,
before the saucers come.
I've done 1,883 shows.
That includes some reruns, but the reruns take a long time to do.
And...
It's harder for me to do shows with other people by phone,
especially Dave,
because my hearing has not gotten any better.
It's probably gotten worse.
And Dave's speaking has not gotten any better.
He's got early-onset Parkinson's.
And he was always a struggle to understand.
But it's not just me.
My wife has trouble understanding.
And I think that's the thing.
I just don't want to do a radio show
where I'm embarrassed half the time
because I can't hear anything.
It's just too goofy.
But there are lots of other things to talk about.
I'm going to catch you all up on some stuff
that you would not know about
unless you were pretty active
in the subgenius Internet world.
There's so many face...
The number of subgenius Facebook groups
is too damn high.
And so,
scrubgenius has kind of slowed down.
It's all old people.
But, there are...
Darn it!
See, I knew my phone
was going to give me hell.
Oh, it's time to go and take my time-lapse picture
of my garden.
Princess Wee!
Can you take the garden picture?
Thank you.
Every day at noon,
there's this waterproof camera
sitting on...
the cheapest tripod in the world.
And every day at noon,
we take a picture of my
huge garden.
It's a vegetable garden, not a flower garden.
This is all edibles.
Here at Stang Ranch.
Because why not? We got free goat poop.
Free well water.
And seeds are cheap.
Okay. Anyway.
Yeah, my hearing is bad
and that means I can't sweeten
bad sound like I used to.
Because I can't
tell if what I'm hearing is anything
remotely like what others hear.
I can hear human speech.
I have special devices that
allow that to happen.
But it doesn't sound the way
it sounds to you.
But, but, but! Oh, I was talking about
the other subgenius forums that are
really good and much more
active. They've got newer,
younger crowd.
Nothing against the old crowd.
In fact, the best group is one
that you can't get to.
Because only the
very oldest, earliest subgenius
doctors can even know about it.
But it's very active.
Little good it does you.
But you can go to
Dobbs.town
which is sort of
monitored and babysat
a little bit by
Uncle Dr. Onan Kanabite.
He also
and it's really interactive.
It's fun to use.
It's on the
Mastodon platform
which is actually
really simple.
And you should check it out.
Onan also
sponsors DobbsTown.org
Now Dobbs.town
is two words
with a dot in between.
But DobbsTown.org
is different.
And that's where there's sort of a very
nice list of where the
subgenius movie is playing.
What
other news groups
and forums and pages
there are.
What's for sale.
News and so forth.
Yet another
subgenius forum is
DobbsCord.
On Discord
platform. But the easiest way to get to
DobbsCord
besides following the links
on the front page of subgenius.com
the simplest way is
you'll like this
subgeniuses.com
Just type in
Dr.
Argus Fox and his
cohort, weirdos,
them and peas and fid and them
were smart enough to nail that
subgeniuses.com
domain and that's
great.
It's easy to remember.
Here's yet another one.
Did you know that there are monthly
Zoom meetings of subgeniuses?
It's been going
on for a couple of years now.
It's not very crowded. And also
there's a monthly Ask
Dr. Hal online
that's very entertaining. It's not
just Ask Dr. Hal.
There's, well, actually his shows
always involve this kind of thing. There's
monster movie clips that
he narrates. There's other people do
special shows.
Pastor Pressure does
real cool educational
things that are quite mirthful
and dry. All of
that is at
gonzotronics.net
g-o-n-z-o
gonzotronics
one more, gonzotronics
dot net
and that'll lead you to the
Ask Dr. Hal and monthly subgenius
diaspora. Princess Wee and I
get on that diaspora about every other
month.
And
depending on
how bad my
haircut is, I'm
very vain about that one
long hair I have left.
Okay.
And also X Day.
X Day Drill, maybe. Well, no.
This is the real X Day. That's how they're
billing it. And it's not July
4th weekend. It's
a somewhat cooler weekend,
we would guess.
June 10th
through June 13th.
Yes, June 10th through June 13th.
The real X Day.
Actually, everybody has X Day
anytime they want.
The real X Day happens all over the whole
planet.
Actually, as the planet turns
underneath a big line.
Well, ding, dang it.
There is no slack.
There is no slack. There is no slack.
I looked down.
I was in the middle of talking about X Day.
I looked down and my battery had run out
on the recorder. Little digital
recorder here. No battery.
I don't know when it ran out. I know I was
talking about X Day
and how it happens everywhere
all the time.
And you better be ready for it. But
we like to have parties. And
we've encouraged people this
year to have their own parties because
...
mainly because
we lost our
we temporarily lost our new Florida venue
until next year.
I can't do anything this
year anyway.
And in this case, it's not because of my
health. It's because I have other people
I have to take care of here.
Some of
you may know that we're taking care of
Wee Ma Ma.
She's the queen mom of
Princess Wee.
She's 92 Earthly years
old. And
nurses come here three times a day.
In fact, you may hear
them. Hospice nurses they're called.
You may hear one in a minute come in
the background. Anyway, so there's
a lot going on here. You know?
And, but
there's a lot going on outside
in the world. And June 10th
to June 13th is
a big party. We hope
it's a big party.
At the G Lodge.
81 Keller Road
in beautiful Hannibal, New
York.
I told you you'd hear dogs.
That's
three times a day this happens.
And that's not even the honey dipper man yet.
I'm just going to proceed.
This is part of the world.
And by the way, the music in the background
is Witch Disco. A CD.
Rare CD by Einstein's
Secret Orchestra.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave on guitar.
Chaz Smith on keyboards.
Good.
Settle down Chupacabra.
It's okay baby.
Oh God.
This is a barnyard.
It's a madhouse.
I guess Princess
We must be busy with something.
No, hey Chupy, no.
Get down.
I was hoping I wouldn't
have to edit this show.
Well, maybe I won't.
God almighty. Okay, yeah.
This is so ridiculous.
X Day. The real X Day.
Four day.
Gut blowout gonzo extravaganza.
Friday, June 10th
to Monday, June 13th
in Hannibal, New York
at a lodge.
There's a camping fee.
And there's a fee.
Well, it's
it costs more if you're not already
a subgenius minister.
I've got too many
public supported stations for me to
discuss prices, but you can find
their website
by going to
subgenius.com
and looking at the events
section. There's a link to
their, it's, here's their
URL.
Xday.ticketleap.com
slash 2022.
I read that last week. Anyway,
what if at the stroke of midnight on the
night of 11th of June,
what if that is the
one true end times?
Could the world end? If it didn't,
would you have to go back to work?
I would, and I'm
far as I know, I'm the only
world's only full-time
person working for Bob.
What if
Bob told us a false
date just to test us?
Come to
the real X Day and experience the end
of the world in style with the only
UFO death cult staffed
by swinging mutants
and the terminally abnormal.
Do you think the universe is
one sick joke? Do you
offer jokes when presented
problems? Do you
would rather have a good time than a bad trip?
Do you can help
us with a donation? Then the church
of the subgenius is just the punchline
you were looking for. Repent,
quit your job, slack off, come to the real
X Day and party like it's July
5th, 1998.
So there you go.
Dr. Howell will be there,
Rubik's pube will be there,
I will not be there, I wish I
could, but I can't.
And,
yeah, like I say, it's much cheaper
for subgenius
ministers, but
it's still pretty cheap
either way.
Other news I can
add here is that
oh, the agent and Mr. Dodd,
our latest novel,
subgenius novel publishing thing
by
Reverend Teeters LaVerge,
I read half
of it a couple of months ago
on the air.
We had a hardcover version out
that we were charging a lot for because
it was a special numbered edition,
but the paperback, by the time you hear this
probably the paperback version will be out
or almost out. Just look at
subgenius.com at the
main shop.
Bull.com, time control labs.
And,
under books.
And you'll find it. And we still have
Eyelash, the subgenius
science fiction book by Nicolai
Kingsley and Neighbor World.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave's
amazing novel written in
future slang.
You'll love them all.
And,
and more to come.
Australian subgeniuses,
and New Zealand subgeniuses.
Maybe
you're hearing this. I can
finally mail your stuff.
Many may not know that
one could not mail
anything from the United States to
Australia or New Zealand for about
six months there
because of COVID and stupid
crap. But
that has ended and I'm about
to mail all that stuff to Australia.
It's going to cost a fortune.
Seriously.
The subgenius
movie is
running on
Tubi and other things
but it's free on Tubi. It has,
it even has ads.
And it has subtitles.
My copy doesn't
have subtitles.
You know,
I can't hear an audio book
unless it has subtitles.
Isn't that sad?
Um,
okay. Yeah, the subgenius
movie is still really good.
And if you haven't seen it,
you really should. It's,
you think you know everything. You don't know nothing.
It's really well done. It's
really funny. The editing on it is
just mind blowing. Even the
sound mix is mind
blowing. It's really slick
all the way down the line.
And I helped.
Um,
what other news
do we have? Well, here. I'll tell you what
one of my projects is.
Then I'll
do some funny stuff. But I have personal
projects. And one of them
is a rather recent, sudden
one that came up when my bro
of 30 years,
Potter Nostril,
mentioned to me in an email
that he found a, an
affordable system for
digitizing Super 8
and 8mm ancient
home movies.
And it worked. And, uh,
and I got one.
And it is, it's
practically free compared to
paying for a service to do this kind of thing.
The one I'm using is called the Wolverine
Pro. No
relation to X-Men or
the Little Animal.
Uh, Kodak
also makes one.
They're kind of flimsy looking. They have a
couple of, they have a take up reel.
They hold two reels.
One side's motorized.
And it slowly pulls your
ancient home movies through the, past
the little scanner. Click, click,
click. Two per second.
Um,
and it displays what
it's scanning on
itself or on a big TV if you hook
that up. So for one month,
I have
been scanning all
of the 8mm and Super
8 movies in my archive, which is
pretty much all of them. Two
are missing that I can remember.
Only two.
I've scanned about
350 foot
reels.
Most people's home movies
are, you know, the kids opening
presents at Christmas. And there's a little of
that. But
I shot all these home movies.
Not my parents. I shot
them. Starting when I was 10.
And I wasn't interested
in family vacation stuff.
Although I shot that too. And that's
actually some of the most valuable
footage. But the funniest stuff
is the put on
monster movies that my brother and
I and our buddies did.
I've been putting those on my, the ones
that I, that we kind of finished
that were worth
looking at, that I remember
projecting a lot.
I narrated those recently.
60 years after the fact.
Almost. And they're
on YouTube. My YouTube channel.
RevStang.
But,
then the other ones were, I kept
discovering little treasures. Just
amazingly bizarre
and sick stuff. And
I just couldn't stop. I'm also doing
my wife's home movies
which were shot by her parents. And there's
a lot fewer of those.
But it's
been a real gas. I've been
learning that I haven't changed all
that much. My sense of humor was just
about the same
back when I was 11
years old trying to make monster movies.
I knew we didn't have the budget
for it to do it right
like a grown up. So let's do it fun
like a kid. With all
the fake blood we want. Boy
we messed up a lot of clothing back then.
So that's been going
on. That's been fun. That distracted
me from the newly discovered dinosaur
tracks on Stag Ranch.
Really close to the house.
We had one set
they're hard to get to in the back
40. But
my brother stumbled upon
some that I guess we'd
missed. They'd been under water or something
and the creek's totally dry.
And there's a
long string of them. They're not good
but they are
for real. And there are
a lot of them. And there are several different kinds.
There's at least two kinds.
Some kind of theropod, probably
acrocanthosaurus and some sort of
sauropod.
Probably a
let's just say brontosaurus.
Okay. And because
we don't know. But
it's fun. They're fun. They're
really fun.
I probably will not
ever get to making plaster casts
like we did of the three
high quality ones in the back 40.
And now back
to the Church of the Subgenius.
I've got lots of funny stuff
here. I can read from the Dobbs
Town Mirror. I can read
some, well here's a few little quotes.
Some quotes from recent
quotes.
He might be an ass, but he's
Bob's ass.
Now see the way I read that
I don't have to do an edit.
There was another word in there.
Onan
heard Bob say
in the restaurant
of the eyeball eaters
the one eyed man
is whiter.
Onan also
found an old flyer
from a three day
sales seminar that Bob did in
1982 that
we missed called
Laugh Till Your Guts Bleed
Invitation or Warning.
Now you think about that.
And finally
Reverend Angry Larry
the greatest guitar player
in the world.
Well actually that's arguable.
Um.
He's the greatest
thrash surf
guitar player in the world.
He has
revealed that
space aliens created the
dinosaurs to build the
pyramids. Then
they double crossed the dinosaurs after the
work was done and
made them extinct. That
is your Forbidden Sciences
subgenius history lesson for
the day. You're welcome and praised.
Bob says Reverend Angry
Larry. And friends these
slaxioms are in fact
the gospel
truth.
Um.
Let's see. Before I get
to Dobstocktown
I want to read you all
speaking of quotes. I like little
pithy quotes when I'm
not feeling too pithy about everything.
I read
this news magazine called The Week.
The reason I read it. In print
or the reason I read it in print
is because they try
to cover both the
standard
conservatard and
differently lived
uh. Oh wait I'm not
supposed to use that tard word.
Anyway you know what I mean. They try to cover
both tribal
idiocies and
um. Oh here's an interesting
statistic.
Uh. This is actually
this is kind of old news.
The specter
of a hot war with China
has 71% of us rattled.
61% of us
worry that a nuclear war
could erupt.
57% of us believe
in ghosts. 39%
in visitors from other planets
and 27%
in Bigfoot. Also
known as Sam Squanch.
And there are some
anxious carnivores with
26% of Americans
believing that there's a movement
to ban red meat.
Which 59%
say is essential to the
American way of life.
Well
I'm in a
I'm. My family
raises red meat and I
don't eat much of it at all.
I'll certainly eat it to be polite.
It's mainly a health thing.
Uh.
And I can't eat goat.
I'd feel like a cannibal. Here's some
interesting statistics. A new study has found
that alcohol related
deaths skyrocketed
more than 25% during the
first year of the COVID pandemic
to nearly 100,000.
And
get this.
Alcohol actually killed
more than, more under
65 Americans
than COVID during
2020. And
experts think there's even more drinking in
2021. Now see I don't have to
worry about that because I'm over 65
so I can drink like a fish.
But um
but it uh
yeah it actually killed more, more young
folks than COVID did.
Because they're stupid.
Because they don't
they don't just drink to
ease the arthritis. They drink to get
messed
up. You know what I mean.
Okay here's wit and
wisdom that comes from a million
different sources. And I
selected a few from the week.
Alfred Hitchcock
said that the length of a film should
be directly related to the
endurance of the human bladder.
So
that's kind of an F you Stanley
Kubrick from Alfred Hitchcock.
Um
Oh
here's a
touching one. Jonathan
Saffron
Fear
said you cannot
protect yourself from sadness
without protecting yourself
from happiness. So that's
kind of like you can't fend
off false slack
without fending off real slack.
No that's not true. That's not true.
So forget it. Skip
that one. Uh
Alexandra Solzhenitsyn
said evil people usually know
better than anyone else just what they're doing.
And they go on doing it.
Duh.
Mark Twain said
if you tell the truth you don't
have to remember anything.
And uh
after a certain point
in my life I tried
I kind of tried to switch
over to that. Things became
much more com-
much less complicated
when I no longer
had anything to hide.
You don't have to
remember anything.
C.G. Chesterton
agreed that
the great proto-subgenius said
the bible tells us to love our neighbors
and also to love our enemies.
Probably because generally
they're the same people.
And Tyler said
you can be in a good marriage
and you can be in a bad marriage
and they can both be the same one
but just at different times.
I know
I know about that.
And I think
Stephen Colbert
let me say something
as an objective observer.
It's never okay to punch a comedian.
I agree with that
as an objective observer.
And I've never been
in a comedy club
by the way. Ever.
Well once. I went to see Paul Krasner for free.
Okay. Star Jones
said
you're never allowed to step
on people to get ahead
but you can step over them
and they're in your way.
I like that one a whole lot.
Boy this is so sad.
Henry Adams
Politics as a practice
has always been
the systematic organization
of hatreds.
I'll say that again.
I'll cut it closer.
Politics has always been
the systematic organization
of hatreds.
That's never been more clear
than in American politics
now.
Because that's all it is.
Organized hatred.
Trevor Noah said
just as a general rule
nothing should change
mid-flight ever.
I haven't been on a plane in a long time
but I know what he means.
Well here's the last one of these.
Somebody named Jerome K. Jerome
I wonder if he knows G. Gordon Gordon.
Jerome K. Jerome said
I like work.
It fascinates me.
I can sit and look at it for hours.
And despite record turnout
80 million American adults
did not vote
in November
of 2020.
29% weren't registered.
23% don't care about politics.
20% don't like any of the candidates.
16% don't feel like
their vote would matter.
10% don't know who to vote for.
8% are scared of COVID.
And 53%
think it makes no difference
who's president.
Things just go on as they do before.
And I don't agree with that at all.
I think there is a big difference.
Here's a funny song by Reverend Pease.
I don't know what sort of melody
is supposed to go with it.
Reverend Pease wrote this funny song.
It's more like a poem
than the way I'm going to do it.
Bob's Monkey, ain't I lucky.
Don't live in a zoo,
I'm in the street with you.
Slacking and rocking is what I do.
I'm Bob's Monkey,
what are you?
I eat chicken tacos
cause I don't like nachos.
I drink hard cider
but I'm no fighter.
And I didn't steal your lighter.
The undercover merkin
who's always smirkin.
I'm Bob's Monkey,
who are you?
Isn't that cute?
That old Pease, he's just the cutest little thing.
Not everybody would agree with me on that.
But he is. He's just the cutest little thing.
Now here's something
that I'm going to try to read
to y'all.
It's actually
it started out
as just a little chat,
a text chat
on the secret
subgenius
old, old, old
doctors forum.
And I do mean old.
By the way, Dr. Drummond
just had his 70th birthday.
Onan had
his birthday on the same day.
Commie Day.
But yet,
Onan is the youngest.
He's a little ways behind us.
He's only 150 something.
G. Gordon Gordon's
80 something.
And he started this out.
Somebody looked at
the very first color
television broadcast
kinescope on YouTube.
Boy, that was a weird
string of words.
And G. Gordon Gordon said,
man, that early color was so creepy.
Onan,
I'm just going to go
through this as if it was a
an essay rather than people talking.
It had just been invented
and people were trying new things.
Same with sound.
For a long time,
the world was utterly silent everywhere.
Then sound was invented
by Edison.
How the secrets of color
got lost from the world of painting
to the first color film
remains a mystery.
Philo says,
well, after black and white
was invented first,
you know,
there was that long stretch.
Maybe the black and white
organized crime syndicate
paid off the painters
to keep silent about color.
And besides,
the monochrome rays
burned the color rods
out of everybody's eyes at first.
And that makes sense
because when you look at woodcuts,
they're just monochrome.
People hadn't grown multiple sets
of rods and cones yet.
Black and white TVs
emitted N rays
to neutralize them.
Only salesmen were spared.
Yes,
only salesmen were spared
because as a race,
salesmen are much more advanced
physiologically than mere ordinary humans.
Other races
can't compare.
Salesmen,
they are a predatory species.
So even if they're relatively more
primitive in specific cases,
as a whole,
the native prey species
cannot compete.
No way.
The salesmen know the techniques.
Some salesmen are harvesters.
Some are completists.
We can't say which is better
or worse for the
quote,
market, unquote.
It depends on how tired of life you are.
But, you know,
a specially developed section of the brain
that normal humans don't have
is called the vestigial
or if humans do have it,
it's just in a primordial vestigial state.
Even worse,
for the humans,
that vestigial sales gland
is considered either evil or cancer
and is cut out rather than developed.
A salesman can't become a normal,
but the vestigial hindbrain
of a mere pink human
can sometimes be activated.
The evidence confirms this.
Only by the pink
can the human
be able to
become a normal human.
So,
the best way to
explain this is
to say that
if you're a salesman
and you're not a salesman,
you're not a master salesman.
You're not a master salesman.
You're not a master salesman
if you're not a master salesman.
So, the salesman
who sells the other salesman
his own measuring methodology
is the master salesman?
Well, some are very
strict in their dispensation
of departmental slack.
That's how the whole early bird
and worm ethos evolved,
as nature intended.
There's never been a transaction
in which a salesman
was not involved in some stage
of the process.
Logic dictates that
there was a master salesman
on this planet when Bob
was just a boy.
Always selling.
Selling right out of the chute,
of course, but with a similar sales base.
The record of that prior master salesman
when he finally understood
how outclassed he was
must be humbling.
We hope he took it well.
Nowadays, there are many
master salesmen each selling
their own patented sales techniques
and advanced super sales technology
and onto the same market.
One of the signs that Bob
puts the urrr in salesman
is that he can
sell to himself
at a profit.
But then Sterno joined the conversation
and I cannot read
any of the rest of it because
it's just so very,
very juvenile.
Oh,
yes, okay, where are we?
I've been recording for about
38 minutes or something.
The Dobstown Mirror.
Let's see, I cannot remember
what I read from
issue number 106.
So I'm just gonna
start from issue number
and assume I don't
I didn't read anything from this.
There's something
that's a nice,
it opens up of course with
this is a printed magazine by the way,
the Dobstown Mirror.
You can get it from
Dr. Onan Kanabite.
P.O. Box 3.
That's right, P.O. Box 3.
Columbus, Indiana.
Not Columbus, Ohio.
47202.
Dobstown.
And
boy, this just covers everything.
There's a great reading
list of
cult management study guides
which includes
Papillon,
Castaneda's Journey,
Gentlemen of Leisure,
Assault on Culture,
The Satanic Bible,
Wag the Dog,
The Prince,
The Prisoner,
TV Show,
and a whole bunch of other
stuff that I don't know about really.
The Making of the Messiah
by Robert Schaeffer.
I know that guy, sort of.
I had to defend
Robert Anton Wilson from Robert
Schaeffer one time.
Anyway, here we go.
The Dobstown Mirror.
Subgenius jokes, koans, riddles,
spells, and gags.
Things to see, say,
do, think, know, and buy.
You know, I think I better
continue this later. I think the
Honey Dipper Man has arrived to
empty out the septic tank, and I'll have
even more material for you when he gives
me what he sucks out of the septic tank.
Be seeing you.
Okay, we're back.
We're back, and the
septic tank man,
Honey Dipper Dan,
has been
here, took the good stuff,
and gone. I wonder
where he empties that tanker
truck after he
sucks the stuff out
of four
or five home
septic tanks.
I just wonder.
Okay, the
Dobstown Mirror rant readings.
This one is an actual little
rant called
Sell Us Your Time.
Unless told otherwise,
everything is by
Conan, really.
And this is
actually from Dobstown issue
106. I'm pretty sure I
haven't read this. And if I have,
well, pick up on it.
Sell Us Your Time
is the title.
Send one
dollar. You've been hearing
the Subgenius Foundation repeat
this mantra for decades,
perhaps your entire lifetime.
Send one
dollar. But now, hear it
again for the first time.
Send one dollar.
We
will send you one dollar
if you will sell us
one hour of your time.
I don't mean listening to an
episode of Hour of Slap. That's a
minimal expectation of any
subgenius. I mean, quite
literally, that we
want you to sell us your
time. Sell us one
hour, and we will send you
one dollar. It's easy.
Most people have a back
catalog of hours they've saved
up. Think of all the
time you've not invested
in your physical and mental
and emotional well-being. It's
just laying around,
gathering no interest.
Gather up an hour of that time.
Ship it to the Subgenius
Foundation and watch your
income explode.
Or maybe
your stockroom of
clockrooms is all talk
doom. Time
is tight. You don't have much
to spare. We've all been
there, but look again.
Look closely.
See?
See how much time you're
putting into your unpaid data
entry job for social media?
See how much time you devote
to resentment of things that happened
so long ago that you're the only one still
thinking about them? See how
much time you spend around those who
are not members of the Church of the
Subgenius? See how much time
you spend on not
resolving your bad feelings but
practicing them, perfecting
them? See.
See how much
time you really have
and what you're doing with it.
Don't be selfish. Sell
us your time.
What will we do with your time?
You probably already know that your time
surplus is unclean
It takes a strong
stomach and a religious mind
to flens all this
time, to boil and bubble
it up until only the good stuff remains.
You could have done it
yourself. Bob showed
you how in Book of the Subgenius.
But instead,
you've been paid by us
to do it for you.
Once we've cleaned your time
from the marbling of both
rogue WeeRordian and
ultra emergentile funk,
we'll put your time to
good use. Doing
what? Well, that's our
business. This offer
is not the phony,
vampiric, empty promises
proffered by rival religions
to live forever.
No one lives forever,
not even us. Not even if
every one of you takes advantage
of this fantastic
time-sharing offer.
We aren't afraid of dying. We don't
even hate death. We do
hate that death happens to
the wrong people in the wrong
order, but that's a different
rant. Do not be
concerned with what we will do with your
time. You're not using it. That's
the main point. Waste makes
haste. Sell your unused
and misused hours to
the Church of the Subgenius.
Send one
dollar.
I remember seeing Onan deliver
this live.
This one's best yelled outside
of a divival on the street.
Ladies and gentlemen, step right up.
Welcome to the Subgenius
Medical Curiosity Show.
It's all real, all here,
all alive, and it's all on the
inside. See
the smart boy who can't
keep a job.
See the pretty
girl who can't get a date.
Alive and on the inside.
We have diseases
that are spread through sexual congress.
We have debates settled by
fisticuffs. We have people
famous for being famous,
and they're all inside.
Alive, alive,
alive. See grown men
and women talk to an invisible
monster that lives in the sky.
See your own
body become ever more fragile
before your very eyes.
Feel the horror as
schools turn innocent children into
innocent adults.
Listen to shocking
tales wherein you pay
to work. They're
all here on the inside.
We have a picture of a
salesman who smokes a pipe.
What other religions charge
all worldly goods for, we offer
at a discounted and guaranteed
low rate. Read
words on a screen. Attend
amateur religious satire
performance art. Hear
amateur podcasts
radio ranters. Get slack
and feel alive
on the inside.
Yes friends,
science has room
for the subgenius.
And you will be able
to meet or avoid
subgenie in your area
if you subscribe to
the Dobstown Mirror.
It's
very cheap.
And it's paper.
In fact this one here is
sixteen
pages. Like the
subgenius pamphlet. And just
about as dense.
See the Dobstown Mirror.
Post office
box three, Columbus, Indiana.
And that
zip code is
47202.
See the
Subgenius Foundation
website.
Subgenius.com
See the
Destruction Evidence
Museum. P.O.
Box 807, Glen Rose,
Texas 76043.
That's
my house.
Actually that box, that P.O.
box, that's my house. We
downsized.
Thank you Einstein Secret Orchestra
for that fabulous background music.
Why is this saying it's only
been recording...
Oh, oh, oh.
I looked down and thought it said 000
17 seconds.
But I...my eyes
are dim. And the light is
funny. And it said 008.
That's just about
right. We're
closing in on some kind of a show here.
From the Dobstown
Mirror here it says
It says that my father
Captain Hugh
M.
Pappy Smith
said this.
I believe what I need
to believe. And he did.
He said it sitting right
where I am sitting now. Believe
it or not. And
uh...
And he was just in conversation.
He was having some kind of an argument.
He was like, well, people believe all kinds
of stupid stuff.
No, no. I
believe...I go, well, what do you believe,
Pappy? Why do you believe that? I believe
what I need to believe. And I thought,
he just summed up the whole
human condition in one sentence.
I told him so, but he didn't
you know, it was like coming from me.
It didn't matter as much.
Yes, uh,
Tarzan's radio station is located
in what used to be Pappy's
control model...module.
Uh, he
had a TV
near here that he could watch.
Uh, I don't.
I have this radio
station, let's call it,
covering the entire table.
And where the TV was are two
plaster casts of real
dinosaur tracks from down in the creek.
And, uh,
it's a wonderful
environment in which to do a show.
I'm not actually sitting in Pappy's chair.
That would be creepy.
Because his ghost is sitting in his chair
right over there. But it's asleep,
so don't worry.
All definitions require
definitions,
etc. Therefore, defining
a problem is always going to begin
at an arbitrary point.
All sources have sources,
etc. Therefore,
identifying the source of a problem is
going to begin at an
arbitrary point. Beginning
at an arbitrary point isn't so bad, because
the goal is not defining a problem or
identifying the source of a problem.
The goal is solving a problem.
Solving a problem, as it is found,
trying to not accidentally
make things worse.
Slack is where you find it.
Do you find
Slack being heavily invested
in Facebook?
Or do you find Slack avoiding Facebook
like the plague?
Both are correct.
Why not both? Slack
is where you make it. Do you find
Slack in regular strenuous
physical exertion?
Or do you find Slack in lounge
changing about passively?
Both are correct. Slack is
where the subgenius is.
You could be that
very subgenius.
A subgenius will always
proceed forward, elbowing
the world to turn as
needed. Oh no, no.
Let me say that again. A subgenius
will always proceed forward,
allowing the world to turn as
needed.
Mmm, maybe a little bit
of both.
Speaking of
allowing,
or not allowing,
I'm tired, or I
will be tired.
Not allowing I'm tired or I will be tired
to be a loud voice in my
decisions was one of the best choices I've
made in my adult life. In the
past, I'm tired was
why I didn't do many things.
Now, I do many more
things, and sometimes while I do
them, I'm tired. The tiredness
doesn't exist afterwards.
But having done the things does
exist afterwards. Many
achievements and memories
gathered because I'm tired
stopped being good
enough in itself to stop
them from being gathered.
Price Bob and the Dobstown
Mirror.
And we'll be back
next week with
more Bob Time,
Bob Money,
Bob Countries,
and Bob Gods.
And all the imaginary
things that make the world
go round. The world of humans,
that is, friends.
Try selling anything
to an animal.
Try
converting an animal.
getting an animal to
salute your flag.
That's one reason I keep a lot of animal
guns around.
Because they're just not as full of
crap as everybody else.
Praise Bob, and
thank you for listening.
This has been Reverend Ivan Stang.
A good day.
And we'll see you next week.
Bye.
There have actually been
devivals in China.
There's an American friend of
ours that lives in Shanghai.
His reverend, Shining Path
of Least Resistance.
And he has a small
clench, mostly
foreigners there.
Right on.
I don't think we've ever sold
a ministership to a
native China Chinese.
Any other countries?
And no Russians.
Neither that I know of.
Oddly enough, there's
Bootleg Bob in China.
A friend of mine found a shirt with
little dobs heads and golfers all over it.
In China.
Not much you can do about stuff
like that.
Any other interesting countries?
Africa, Europe, South America,
Australia, any weird...
No, Spanish, not much from Spanish speaking countries.
Because those are heavily Catholic.
Hardly anything from Mexico.
But a ton
from Australia,
New Zealand, England, Germany,
the Netherlands.
We got to travel
Amsterdam a bunch of times.
I could find my way around Amsterdam
without a map.
That's heaven.
For a tourist.
How about recently?
I heard they kind of changed their stance on
a lot of things over the past few years.
Yeah, they're cracking.
Because the Englishmen
get too high and drunk and fall in the
mouths.
And walk out in front...
And Americans walk out in front of traffic
because everything's going the
wrong way.
Just dumb crap like that.
Actually,
I hear the place to go is Portugal
now. Have you been?
It's incredible, bro. It's the best.
Don't tell anybody.
I've got a buddy in Portugal.
We did a lot of shows in Germany
and England. That was really
fun. Now, how much of
the Robert Anton Wilson
material comes into play
here? Because I might have been altogether
confused, but I recently
came across a copy of the original
Illuminati card game and started
getting interested in all that. There's a church
of the subgenius deck that goes
along with that card game.
Those were all developed by Steve Jackson.
Steve Jackson
got permission to use the Illuminati
stuff and there was some crossover
there, so he decided to
do a subgenius one, too.
Now, the funny thing is I got to
hang out with Robert Anton Wilson
many times because of
that pagan festival, Starwood.
Originally,
Starwood was going to be kind of
like
wired
more of a
mind in those days with Mondo 2000,
but it was
more like fringe science,
alternate healing,
regular science,
and world music.
There were a lot of witches and
druids and shit up in
Northeast Ohio and they
kind of became a little top heavy
with that gang.
I know a lot of witches and I can tell
you what they say about their titties.
Brave Digger's ass?
I can't speak for that, but a witch's
tit is not cold.
Yeah, well there's a lot of mounds up there
in Ohio, so I wouldn't be surprised
if there's something in the water.
That's some mounds, boy.
Yeah, yeah.
We had a...
In fact, there was a turtle mound
at the last campground
we used in Ohio.
Fake. It was made by hippies,
not Indians.
You know, it looked good.
They called it a turtle mound.
It was a good place to wait for flying saucers,
I'll tell you that. They never came, but
boy, I was there at 7 o'clock
in the morning every July 5th
for 25 years.
And every time,
everybody stares at me.
Said that we do the countdown,
saucers don't show up,
and everybody looks at me.
So, you know, I've had to
get used... The very worst
one in 98,
there were like 400 people
there.
And there were some who
really expected they were going to get their
own flying saucer.
That was the one in the movie, right, Ivan?
Yeah, but I got...
Somebody suggested,
after the great disappointment
in 98,
I unveiled the fact that
actually looks like another number
if you turn it upside down.
It's 8661.
And the original memo
that Bob wrote down, it looked like
maybe it had been switched
over, you know?
But people got really mad.
They stripped
me naked and
poured honey
and pink
flowers, or feathers,
pink feathers all over me and threw me
in a pond. And I
stood there,
stark naked, shaking my fist at
like 300 laughing
people. This is all on
video. And so what
to most people is their worst
nightmare? Standing
naked in front of a laughing crowd?
It's just, for me,
it's just a memory of a wild party.
I love that.
I'll never let them do that again, though. Of course, we never had that many
people. It was
disappointing to find...
The next day after
that, only half as many people
dwindled each time, which indicated
to me that more people were taking this
seriously than we knew.
And that's a little...
That's a little creepy,
actually. I mean, you've literally started
a cult about a
joking cult, and then some people
have literally joined in
thinking it's serious. This is the most incredible
thing maybe ever... Has it ever gotten away
from you? It appeals...
It sort of...
There's people out there who are
just plain schizophrenic.
And our
writing style, especially
in the book and the first pamphlets,
mimics that
schizophrenic way of talking.
And it addresses the kind of things
they believe. Everybody's out to get
you. You're... You've got
magic powers just because you're weird
and different. You know, it's just telling people
what they want to hear. But the
schizophrenics believe it.
I believe it. There's a guy... Thank you,
My Family Thinks I'm
Crazy. That's the name of the podcast
that interviewed me for
a while, a couple of months
ago. My Family Thinks I'm
Crazy. We
know how that feels.
Actually, my family was crazy,
so it's cool.
Price Bob.