Life drop by the fantastic bag.
Well, welcome to the hour of slack.
Praise Bob, Gold, and Connie drag.
Yes, welcome to the hour of slack.
La, la, la, la, la, la, la.
La, la, la, hour of slack.
Schoolgirl fucks the whole team.
These sluts are waiting for the school bell to ring so they can't fuck the basketball team.
Not one player, the whole team.
It's unbelievable fuck and suck frenzy.
She sucks 620 guys for every last drop of their hot gooey cum.
Hard core and explicit team action that will leave you speechless.
Here's a fax from Cooter in Orlando who sends me a copy of a story that appeared in the Los Angeles Times.
He says, a prestigious newspaper, not the off-maligned Weekly World News.
Quoting the story.
In retrospect, lighting the match was my big mistake, but I was only trying to retrieve the gerbil.
Eric Tomaszewski told the news doctors,
in the severe burns unit of Salt Lake City Hospital.
Tomaszewski and his homosexual partner, Andrew Kinky Farnham,
had been admitted for emergency treatment after a felching session had gone seriously wrong.
I pushed a cardboard tube up his rectum and slipped Raggett, our gerbil, in, he explained.
As usual, Kinky shouted out, Armageddon!
My cue that he'd had enough.
I tried to retrieve Raggett.
But he wouldn't come out again.
So I peered into the tube and struck a match, thinking the light might attract him.
At a hushed press conference, a hospital spokesman described what happened next.
The match ignited a pocket of intestinal gas and flames shot out the tube,
igniting Mr. Tomaszewski's hair and severely burning his face.
It also set fire.
It set fire to the gerbil's fur and whiskers,
which in turn ignited a larger pocket of gas,
further up the intestine, propelling the rodent out like a cannonball.
Armageddon!
Tomaszewski suffered second-degree burns
and a broken nose.
from the impact of the gerbil.
Haha!
But Furnham suffered first and second-degree burns to his anus and lower intestinal tract.
Armageddon!
Hahaha!
Haha!
Peered into the tube and struck a match, thinking the light might attract him.
might make the gerbil come out.
So that's what felching is all about.
I'm again!
Who says that?
I didn't.
Robert D. Raymond on the John Bourne Billy Show.
Hello.
Yeah.
What are you playing right now?
Nothing.
We're not playing nothing.
We're playing with ourselves.
My own little organ, man.
What do you think of self-gratification?
I play organ.
I'm going to slop it out on this table here.
Sticky right out there, man.
It's self-gratification.
Look at that thing, man.
It's like more than 400, 500 pounds.
I think.
I don't know.
Wait, Dave, listen.
Ow.
Get my sword.
Oh, man.
How can you do that so low?
Oh, bro.
You're going to.
Oh, man.
Look, your eyes are already watering.
Calm down.
He's slapping it on the sharp edge.
Look what the Jesuit did to his head, man.
They threw him up, man.
He's bad.
Oh, come on, bro.
Oh, man.
Hey, man.
You're going to throw your hip out of balance, man.
Just.
Wow, man.
If that's what you got to do, man.
Is there a janitor?
Mr. Olsen.
I'm going to get me a box of nurses cream and get me a job.
Hi-ho, hi-ho.
It's on to bed we go.
I hate to miss to see your kids.
Hi-ho, hi-ho.
It's on to bed we go.
Get in that sack and spread your crap.
Hi-ho, hi-ho.
Hi-ho.
It's off to bed we go.
Just squeeze your cunt and make me grunt.
Hi-ho, hi-ho.
It's off your ass, I'll go.
Please wash your butt, you fucking slut.
Hi-ho, hi-ho.
Hi-ho.
It's time for you to blow.
Please get me hard, you tub of lard.
Hi-ho, hi-ho.
Hi-ho.
Into your bush I'll blow.
I'll make a splash inside your gas.
Hi-ho, hi-ho.
You're hosing me too slow.
I'm going limp, you fucking blimp.
Hi-ho, hi-ho.
Please give me head, my dick is dead.
Hi-ho.
Yeah, come on.
Let's go.
All right, guys.
With Razor, Blaze and Amberley.
We'll be right back.
Say you like the game.
And glee biết what you're thinking
Theitsu Ames jerks off more than you
He can prove it with math
When Don Neal puts his dick in a manis jar
He turns into a psychopath
The necrophilia is not enough
To satisfy the Bradford lust
The Limb Beck dick-spear'd with Dead Chip
The Clerd-Ice of God
Copyright movie
Well there needn't be anger
In this world
And my fiercest friend
Imве dunt
Your belki
Rel derivatives
I, want my love
To find
Out of Michelam
Franches
One implementation
We'll be right back.
He can prove it with math.
William Upton jerks off more than you.
The El Queso All-Stars.
More from them on stationmp3.com slash nterbulator.
And friends, welcome to Hour of Slack number XXX5.
An internet-only subgenius show.
And you know the great thing about an hour of Slack that's internet-only,
it doesn't have to be only an hour long.
Praise the E-Bub.
Bob is Slack, Bob is sex, and Bob is money.
And that's all we need.
Well, actually, we need more subgeniuses.
There aren't enough subgeniuses.
So you have to fuck more and make more little subgeniuses.
It's that simple.
Miles and miles of cock rings.
That's all I can say about that.
That's what we're expected to wear in today's military.
Stan knows this.
He was talking to a recruiter early, asking if they took elderly gents like ourselves.
And he said, you know, if you've got the right equipment, we've got the right U.S. American Army for you.
I mean, how do they say it?
I've got all the tool of preacher names.
I got the cock rings.
I got the ball jack.
A great big cum.
I guess now in the U.S. military.
Fort Bragg, Bragg and Bragg.
Places like that.
Ten-inch scrap on.
They're using those hand grenade pins for cock rings.
We're talking about real.
Oh, hand grenade pins.
Wow, that's creative.
Yeah.
It makes the kind of like the testicle area look like the grenades.
Do they use that as a cock ring or as a Prince Albert?
Oh, Prince Albert.
I'm sorry.
I'm not here to.
That seems like a little ring to use as a cock ring.
I used a pop top from a beer can, but it was a little too big and it kept slipping off.
I used a top guard.
It's my M16.
It works in any weather and keeps me alive.
I use 13-inch radials.
You get them, you know, you can find them in junk yards or along, you know, people throw them out now and then you stop and pick up.
I use it for those in picket lines.
Yeah.
I mean, sometimes.
Oh, boy.
That's going to be good.
I'm going to use you in a minute, boy.
I'm going to use you for what?
Open Wednesday.
Don't fuss.
sake him.
You can take silicon out a bit.
You can't take the conduct.
You can take a very smart.
You can take the.
You can take.
You can't take the.
You can totally.
there from the great Fernandin and a lemur and now little Theodore
he caught me both no I don't qualify
you give me heartache you make me grow you make me imagine that I know you make my blood run you make me howl you make my thoughts turn profane and foul you make me tremble you make me sigh you wake me up then you watch me die
you give me hard on you make me sweat I want to see you moaning and wet you get me floating you let me fall you get me started then make me stall but there's no resolve to my plight because underneath you're proud and tight
you give me hard on by the great little Theodore by the way the music in the background is by the swinging love corpses from the infamous bay dat sessions
good evening ladies and gentlemen here's the good evening and ladies and gentlemen
isn't it frightfully good to have a dong it's well to have a stiffy it's divine to own a dick
from the tiniest little
had you to the world's biggest brick that's Dave so three cheers for your Willie or John Thomas
hooray for your one eyed trouser snake
here it is
piece of pork your wife's best friend your Percy or your cock
you can wrap it up in ribbons you can slip it in your sock
don't take it out in public or they will stick you in the dock
and you won't a come a back
thank you very much
what the fuck is that
not him again
can we close the door just
pretend like we're not in here
hey Joe
be real quiet
I'm scared
what
I don't know
can you see the top of his head moving
I'm scared
look his ears are glowing Jesus Christ he's in a bad mood
he's mad
when he's mad his ears glow
what are we gonna do
what
July is national baked bean month
excuse me
yes a month in which we pay tribute to one of America's favorite most healthful and nutritious foods
excuse me yes a month in which we pay tribute to one of America's favorite most healthful and nutritious foods
I'm terribly sorry
as I was saying
good lord this is terribly embarrassing
I'm so
whoa doggy
I guess I'd better wrap this up quick
basically
Jesus whoa oh god oh my god
baked beans they're nature's way of saying for God's sake open a window
sorry
I come to ball you
I ball you just ball you
if you've been enough to ball I'll come too
you bounce around
ball you ball you
bouncy
when spot me do ball you
I come all welcome ball you
I'll come to ball you
ok I hate my parents
and I say leave me alone
with parental supervision I'm much more likely to smoke pot and stuff
Sponsored by the Partnership for a Free America.
The world.
Everywhere.
They're laughing.
Laughing.
Oh.
Next, British Prime Minister Tony Blair outlines his views on genetically modified Tony Blairs in Britain.
His remarks cover issues of royal research, genetically modified Tony, and the use of Blairs before the Royal Genetically Modified Animals Society in Britain.
The speech was about Britain.
Well, I'm king and I'm high on exciting news.
It's a very royal society and a very high society.
And also, we've seen the public.
But equally, the public is taking us.
We must.
We must learn to cum and blick.
Welcome the cum in science issues.
Does science get in this cum today?
I believe the Prime Minister has always shown cum to that interest that he has cum today to share his cum with you, Prime Minister.
Go on.
Stand up.
Turn around.
Thank you very much indeed, David, and thank you all of you for coming.
Margaret Beckett started to excite me.
Can I say I'm particularly pleased to be coming in the presence of Margaret.
The government, the government, the government.
It's all.
You make me a shame.
I mean, I start to cum on the latest scientific discoveries.
We'll cum.
It is with some proper modesty that I make my cum contribution to you today.
Because I actually believe cum is of fundamental importance to our future.
And partly because I cum.
And partly because I cum with science over the society.
I'm not a cum.
When twelve men found cum in 1666, it was possible for an educated person to come for more than half of this body's existence.
All be quiet.
Hey, c-qu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu N эффul
Or give somebody else a chance.
T-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t-t
You cum hangin' around my wife.
Please, please.
You make me a shame.
Cum cum cum cum cum cum cum cum, cum.
Please, please, you make me unconstitutional.
Lemur.
Love of Christ.
We read you.
Carlos Dave Tanner on guitar.
On the bottom rung of the ladder.
Just one more step and I'm...
Drank 40.
Breathing the same air as Carlos David.
Captain Daly.
A lonesome coward.
The pituitary glands are getting much bigger.
Are you fucking believing this?
The other kids have never had pituitary glands this large.
Look.
The endocrine system overall is growing and it's...
The sloth packet is getting bigger too.
The sloth packet is getting bigger too, but it's full spreadsheet.
Stay, come back, instead!
Leave them all behind.
Now a party dress.
Jack off till I'm blind.
Clean up that mess.
With a tur retourne.
Never mind mankind
Leave them all behind
Blow up your mind
Like the mummy baby rose
Over in my bed
Wrap up my clothes
And blow up my head
Dynamite or acid
Highbrow or hot bread
Foresee the forbidden
Blow the lid of your head
Never mind mankind
Leave them all behind
Blow up your mind
Do it, do it, do it, do it, do it
Are you a little too healthy?
Drink some bad wine
Drap some bats in your beltway
And blow up your mind
Ah, no more static in the attic
No, no, get erratic instead
Ah, get real acrobatic, yes
And land on your head
Ah, never mind mankind
Forget them, leave them all behind
Hear me now
Blow up your mind
Ah, never mind mankind
No, no, no
Leave them all behind
Blow up your mind
by Sonic Iligar
H oliver
Subtit continues
Don't listen to them
Do it
Do it, do it
The cramps blow up your mind and now a cheatham break
Cravings are the root of unhappiness
That sounds3000
Oh my God, I feel so good
Oh yeah, I slow down
Oh yeah, Oh yeah
Who's your daddy?
Oh my God
Yay, playes my balls, plays with my balls
Oh, that feels so good
Yeah just roll it around
and do some short short
Oh my 18
I
I receive a close
it would be. Uh-oh.
Look at that.
Don't move.
I'll go get you a towel.
I remember it.
It was 1942.
I was living in Prague
at the time.
I just bought myself a basket of bread
and invited Aunt Elder
over to chew my socks.
I looked out the window. I could see the
smoke billowing up from the horizon.
It looked like the panzers
were rolling in. It was
blitzkrieg time.
And I
laid back and had a nap.
Hey.
Alright.
What's so alright about it?
Nothing's alright about it.
I had this moment.
This moment was alright.
It was just alright.
It was kind of, I think it was the old
Afghani.
Jesus is just alright.
Could have been sweet as wine.
Could have been a lady.
One, three, four, two times.
Jesus is just alright too.
An avatar.
With me.
Jesus just sent me a big box of subgenius
membership packs.
Three times it's Jesus.
That sounds like a joke, but it's just
a business like normal.
Normal everyday saying.
The Messiah.
Seven, eight, nine times.
The Lord, the first.
And it says in Revelation 5, 12, 79, 6, 3.
I remember that year.
He shall come as a thief in the night.
It was a mess.
The Lord, the day of the Lord
is at hand.
And he shall come like a thief
in the night.
He's got a hell of a grip.
He's using the left hand to feel us like a stranger.
You know what I mean?
He's got a hell of a bright smile.
I know.
And look at the, look at the windows on those eyes, man.
Look at, look at how soft and fuzzy his ears are.
There's nothing like them.
I'd like to kiss them ears on that Jesus.
I'd like to just suck on them soft hairs on that point of the ears on that little.
Oh yeah, he wants that.
He wants you to sit on his lap like Michael Jackson or something and just relax and he'll tell you a story.
You remember?
I like to watch his face morph.
Like Michael does.
From, from a pretty face to the color of Kali.
From a little squished potato nose to the little tiny skeleton nose.
Back to a little squished potato nose and then a little skeleton nose.
And the little, the canines pop out and they begin sharpening themselves.
And he gets black and he gets white and he gets black and white.
He's all things to all people.
He's all things to all birds, all bees, all ducks, all trees.
He's always, always on his nose.
He's the only of number.
Ah, yes dear friends.
ESO, Swamp Radio, Lonesome Cowboy Dave, Professor Jazz Smith, Beautiful Princess Wiardo, and yours truly Rev. Ivan Stang and now,
Woma Woma Womomomor
Burt Reynolds' autobiography talks about that scene in Deliverance, that actor, that one actor, the guy—
That really messed him up.
Ned Beatty.
Oh, Ned Beatty, it really—
Right.
That scene, I guess filming that scene really traumatized me.
Because the dude was really going to do it.
Yeah, I heard a radio interview with Ned talking about it.
Oh, really? Right, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Remember, Marlon Brando got quite a reputation for actually, quote-unquote,
banging his co-stars during the love scene.
Can you imagine this sodomizing old toothless guy was actually going to mount that baby?
Ray Harryhausen was known for that, too.
Mounting the camera, I think, and humping it vigorously.
And those co-stars, like the Talos and that forearm-dancing Shiva.
I had a thing for monsters.
He would actually be doing it, but from on camera, in between frames.
I had a thing for monsters. I liked looking at their legs.
I liked sniffing things.
I heard that that was going on, too.
Yeah, the Island of Dr. Moreau.
Oh, man.
On the filming of the Island of Dr. Moreau that Marlon Brando was off.
With that pig woman.
The pig woman and stuff.
Giving him a little curfew.
Curlicue right there.
Yeah.
The Island of Dr. Moreau, it later became, as he was so guilty about what had happened to him,
he actually removed one of the little piglet curlicues.
Maybe four would be better.
Get down on four legs.
Yeah, that would be better.
I swallowed a bug.
Not my night.
What do you mean, not my night?
Maybe four legs would be better.
Six legs.
I'll show you my five-finger man.
He's going with that lemon in his mouth.
We'll show you how to centipede sex and we'll show you how to enjoy it.
And how to make millions of dollars in your spare time by watching others enjoy insect sex.
A snail woman leaving the trail on a straight razor.
It is absolutely a beautiful sight here as the slug women are all being escorted onto the buses.
Many of them painted in psychedelic day glow color.
And right there over the rain, Dr. Poo and the rest of the armada are waiting to pull out the truncheons and beat the slug women back to where they came from.
This is all part of the readjustment.
The devil, Mr. Dobbs, is a particularly pernicious gene.
The devil can be rooted out and eliminated and replaced with this perfect deity gene.
Mr. Dobbs.
And we're going to start with you.
Bend over.
Be careful.
Roll up your dress.
Yeah, yeah.
No, not you, man.
Put that dress back up.
Hey, man, get out of here.
You, over there.
I never.
The one with the hairy eyes, yeah.
Yeah, there you go.
Show me that tattoo again.
It's glowing.
Oh, baby.
I never saw a glowing tattoo.
I can't breathe.
It's no use, Stan.
My hand is getting numb.
Oh, come on, Seth.
Just a little longer.
I can't breathe.
You're a love slave.
You got the touch.
It's not working.
But it's gotta work.
I mean, listen.
It's getting close.
Come on, come on, just pump it, pump it.
No!
I'm done.
No.
I don't want any of this noise to skip.
The noise is bad.
The gun is good.
I need the gun.
I'm going to kill you.
This reality is stupid.
The gun is unburned.
The penis is stupid.
This reality is good.
The map.
That was Popes Lilith.
And this is the Lord Jesus.
No, no.
I don't...
You can't just assume that everyone is sucking your dick as a groupie.
Oh, okay.
They might be doing it because they don't like you.
They're doing it out of hate.
Really?
They might be doing it out of hate.
We're the ones that do it out of hate.
Yeah, I want to do one that'll do it out of indifference.
Well, you got a pimp hand strong, Dr. Drummond.
Yeah, but I don't have time for the higher order thoughts anymore.
I have to, like, manage and service them constantly.
Just over and over.
Just over and over again.
It's like, it gets so old.
Well, you know, that was...
And that's just before breakfast.
Many people say that that's where the church fell down,
is when the Connie tight contingent...
And let me tell you, tight is not the right word for her.
A tight is not...
is nowhere near the right word for Connie.
She's more like...
She gets tight.
She should be like Connie Loose.
I've seen her, though...
Connie flapping...
At the Christmas thing, she fell down because she was so tight.
She was pretty.
Tight, thin.
Yeah, but that's as tight...
As tight as she gets is when she's had about 14 bears.
He-he-he.
I can't believe you guys are talking about...
Thank you, Phineas Narco.
That's where we go.
The he-he-he laugh.
What's up, Cowboy Dave?
Yes, sir.
You're off the air.
And you're letting me out of...
Let me out of the box.
I'm farting.
Chaz, can we let this guy out of the box?
Or should we just kind of, like, dump on the...
Should we burn the box?
Let's put the box on one of those rockets and launch it.
Yes, sir.
See if this caller lives through it.
The box won't catch fire.
There's something wrong.
The box is some strange alien material.
That's Stephen Hawking, Dave.
Steve.
It is.
It's Stephen Hawking.
The great quantum physicist.
I heard that you just lost a $6 bet concerning singularity in black holes.
Is that true, Steve?
I have no techno.
What does that mean, Steve?
We heard your bladder was insular.
Your whole parts of your body were completely regrouperated by science
and made to your own order, kind of a customized body.
What do you mean by that?
Specifically, if you mean anything.
Attendance has not been what it used to be.
Boy, you can tell he's having trouble with the feedback.
He thinks he's at a high school, what do you call it, at assembly.
Well, he's real far away.
He's in Calif...
Wait, now I'm far away.
I'm in California.
No, no, you're still here.
You just look like you're in California.
You notice, look at your skin, how it's getting kind of scaly and everything.
You got that kind of snarly look under your tooth.
They're long teeth.
I am a man called horse.
Well, now he's shrunk himself into one of those little Tom Caraville ice cream horses
that you buy for birthdays, bar mitzvahs, or weddings, or suture parties.
And the day that Stephen Hawking joined the black hole, he was a black horse.
He joined the Sioux Sun Dance in order to be initiated into oneness.
We had to strap his wheelchair underneath the sun altar, and we had a very hard time
strapping him up.
He was so tight and stiff, like a little box already, that when we began to spin him in
the air, he sang like a little music box.
It was crazy.
There is no chocolate.
No.
It's all just part of the matrix.
That's right, friends.
There's no chocolate today, tomorrow, or the next day.
There is no sweet food.
There's nothing sweet left in this sweet land of ours.
You have to put that on the side.
The rich honey flavor has all run out, leaving nothing but acrimony and bitterness.
Vinegar, bad cheese, and foggy memories.
Where are you?
I'm in the kitchen.
I'm gonna make you some pie.
I think it's time for you to start to seriously consider salads, you fat fuck.
Respect my authority!
Before I slap you in the face!
Why don't you shut the fuck up?
Because if you don't, I promise you, they're gonna find pieces of you in eight different
dumpsters.
Right.
Go on, fuck this!
You got a lot of fucking balls, you know that?
I hate everything.
I hate you.
I hate everyone.
Fuck you!
I hate everything!
I hate everyone.
I hope you do, too.
I hate everything.
I hate you.
I hate everyone.
I hope you do, too.
I hate you.
I hate everyone.
I hope you do, too.
I hate everything.
Fuck you.
Fuck you as well.
I don't give a fuck.
I'm not joking.
I hate you.
I don't give a fuck.
I hope you do too.
I hate you.
I don't give a fuck.
Fuck you!
I hate you!
You leave me to kiss!
Fuck you!
I hate everything.
I hate you.
I hate everyone.
I hope you do.
I hate everything.
I hate you.
I hate everyone.
I hope you do.
You leave me to kiss!
Fuck you!
I don't give a fuck.
I hate everyone.
I hope you do too.
And that was Outro by Reverend Two Beans.
You know, back in the States, ever since last year,
we have a new phrase in the church.
For a long time we said, build your own ship.
And then some of our rockets exploded.
So we changed it to build your own Amsterdam,
which was a little safer.
But they can still throw you in jail for it.
And now we get here.
Here, in Amsterdam.
And we're told that we can't smoke Haberfrop Zip-E-Lups
in Amsterdam.
Inside a hotel room.
Not a drug.
Not a hotel room that we rented.
We might as well be in junior high school back in the States.
Hiding underneath in the toilet to smoke.
Why do we have to hide in the toilet to smoke?
Why do we have to hide in the toilet to shit for that matter?
Why can't a man or a woman just shit and smoke at the same time
right out there on the street?
Whatever happened?
What are these taboos based on?
Oh, just thinking about it.
Oh, it makes me.
Just loosen up.
Oh, the slack.
Oh, the slack is moving.
Oh, praise Bob.
Praise Bob.
The prunes.
Oh, yes.
But friends, you know, slack is so much more than just the body letting go, go, go.
It's when your mind melts and just sinks right in.
That's right.
Just release.
Just deflate.
You've been high, puffed up like a balloon.
You've been inflated.
You rose above it all.
But now it's time to just let it out.
Out, baby.
Just let it all blow.
Blow it all off, my friend.
And you'll find down there when you finally deflate,
you're nothing but a greasy skin on the ground.
But then you found slack.
Oh, yes.
True slack.
You'll be that way until Bob comes along and blows you up again.
And if you want to see Reverend Stang demonstrating a few of those aforementioned
phrases and activities, why not pop along to the Bad Kuip this Friday evening at about 10 o'clock.
The Bud...
The Bud Kuip.
It's the Bud Carp.
Well, the Reverend Lord...
The Reverend Lord Yenny will now tell us exactly how to pronounce it.
The Bud Kuip.
And where is that?
At the corner of Albert Kuipstraat and Eerste Zwelingstraat.
The exact address is Eerste Zwelingstraat, number 10.
You can call them.
020-675-9669.
Or, which is in Dutch, 020-675-9669.
That's the Church of the Subgenius, by the way.
Can I just say, Hail, Reverend Jitzer.
Hallelujah.
Praise Reverend Jitzer.
Hail, you guys.
Yes, indeed.
How do you say that?
Hell, yeah.
Jitzer.
Hell, yes.
Subgenius.
Jitzer.
Subgenius in Dutch.
Subgenius.
Hell, yeah.
Jizz Whiz.
Buy it now.
Process your jizz into sauces and also marinades.
You can find the Jizz Whiz in every branch of Comet right now.
The Jizz Whiz will process your jizz and make it into cubes.
Make it into slices.
If you want to see jizz, you can come see jizz this weekend.
You can...
You will have a communion of jizz this weekend.
It's Jizz Whiz.
Jizz Whiz.
It's Jizz.
And we'll have a communion of jizz at the Bad Kite here in Amsterdam.
Can you tell us this address?
Because you can pronounce these words.
Yeah, much better than I can.
I'll just read the entire flyer.
It says,
The Church of the Subgenius, 3rd Amsterdam Divival.
It's going to be on March 23.
That's next Friday at the Bad Kite.
As we well know,
it's on the corner of the Albert Kuipstraat and the 1st Zwelingstraat.
It's officially on the 1st Zwelingstraat, number 10.
Is it true?
Tell us.
Now, I see a pattern.
I see a pattern here.
The Mayans predicted the end of the world in 2012.
And of course, it should have already happened by the Khan calendar.
It's also true that...
It's also true that Dob's dad was a Mayan.
Okay, now we got two things.
Let's get...
The third thing is here.
Dob's dad was a pharmacist.
And everybody knows that these guys are running the damn jizz trade.
Now, there's too many correlations here.
We've got a pharmacist, Mayan, and calendar here.
I think you're reading too much into jizz.
I think you're looking at jizz and you're taking too much from it.
It's easy to do that.
Why must we embarrass the day?
It's the Dob's family.
You know, let's embarrass the Kennedys or somebody else instead.
I mean, it's...
It's the Dob's family.
There are some things that are...
Radio Patapu in Amsterdam.
Praise be to Lord Yeti and Pope Black for putting us on the air there.
And also, Pope Phil Monty...
That dream would never come true.
It's true.
And chanting along its way.
Well, thanks for that blissful moment.
Can I ask something for sure?
I doubt that you know all about nouc as a Hobbit.
Well, now, my favorite connects the wszystko di
ca.
Patsy, he says here in his dossier.
And he's a Capricorn.
Bubblegum and lollipops.
Yes, he's fond of bubblegum and lollipops.
And he's also a Gemini moon rising,
which makes him very hairy and extremely hard to get a hold of on Sunday nights.
Oh, he's a cultural icon, too.
He's a bar fighter, a reckless recluse,
who enjoys having shish kebab with mom and some of the other overgrown children.
Let's look at some of the comments.
And they all listen to the Hour of Slack, 9 o'clock Sunday nights on this.
Oh, they're faithful listeners.
Oh, I even knew that.
Here, I downloaded some of the users from the alt.slack chat here.
Do you have any of the users down there?
Who's Devious Female?
Ah, Devious Female. I would like to know her real name.
She's one of Sister Decadence's students in the Nun Snake Mission.
Oh, my God.
Huh.
Oh, I was going to ask you that.
The nun snakes of Dobbs Town are...
They're like the...
Sort of like...
Here's one.
Hellish robot monsters disguised as geisha girls.
Who is Love Stolic Ladies?
Well, that's the bar girl over there.
Love Stolic Ladies.
Did you see?
Notice one is named Hannibal Lictor.
Hannibal Lictor.
That fried steak waiting in the dumpster there is hers and has her name inscribed on it.
Perhaps in a gold icon format like the one showing here or there.
Well, Yukon Cornelius is in there tonight.
Oh, my.
Unzip.
You don't know who Yukon Cornelius is?
Dream weaver mating.
Oh, my God.
Yukon Cornelius.
Dave?
That's from Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer.
What was Yukon Cornelius?
Was he nice to the reindeer?
He was the big guy.
He was the real big guy.
He forced himself on the reindeer.
Look, there's a subgenius.
Austin Submail.
Yeah.
Um, BBW.
Let's tell him praise Bob.
Let's post ourselves as Bob Dobbs.
Yeah.
Let's post ourselves.
Actually, Chaz, you know, that is like the most dangerous thing you can do on the Internet is to pretend.
Pretend to be Bob Dobbs on the Internet.
And we're going to use the biggest font size we can use here.
Yeah, use a big pipe, smoky-smelling font.
Use one of those fonts that smells like an old ashtray.
Because that's the way Bob, the real Bob, smells.
Here's one called Lil' Cumwhore.
Lil' Cumwhore?
Yeah, who's that?
She was the character.
Wasn't she in that newspaper strip, Lil' Cumwhore?
It was in the Dallas Morning News comic section for a while.
Yeah.
I remember, by the way, she had her head shaved.
I'll let you know if anyone replies to Bob.
Lil' Cumwhore.
I'm going to just write.
I'm so proud.
I had a dream this Dracula, this like weird Dracula.
It was like a Dracula character was attacking me.
And actually, as he was biting down on my forehead.
And you know, like how usually the green worms.
Brain sucker.
The green worms come out first.
And they started exploding out of my forehead.
And the next thing you know, well, old Dracula's in.
Richie, would you do me a favor and eat my pussy for me, please?
I tried some of the, there's a new crazy restaurant in my neighborhood.
I got me a dozen snake wings.
Yeah, they have snake wings.
A dozen Quetzalcoatlus?
I think it's an esoteric Mexican restaurant.
They call it La Azteca.
Or Moctezuma.
Yeah, you have to be in the right mood for them.
I was thinking, because they used to worship a winged snake.
Oh, the other old feathered.
Old Mexico.
Yeah, the feathered serpent, which was just a.
The barbecue snake wings.
And East Dallas.
Was just the fallacy of the sun.
Did you know that?
Did you know the sun actually had.
The phallus?
The phallus of the sun.
But the solar orb has a pecker?
It's got a pecker that makes the wind blow and it makes the trees grow and it makes your
bowling bag zip up tight.
If you don't believe that the wind is part of the sun's phallus, well, you just are a
hip to esoteric, buddy.
Yeah, not only does it have a phallus, it's got a big old jangly pair of hookahs.
Like a great bigger steady.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Now for the next paragraph.
On my little note sheet here, I had intended to give something about a debate.
You may have read something about a little debate that we'd be having concerning the
eradication or domestication of the pinks and normals.
Sadly, such things are not approved for your security clearance.
Fortunately, my significant other, Reverend Cleo, has offered a suggestion.
Replace the word debate with anal sex.
Therefore, we have hot and steamy anal sex action.
If you thought that anal sex was boring, if you thought that anal sex was long and tedious,
if you thought that anal sex was intellectual, think again.
Ivan Stang and Reverend Papa Joe Mama are here today to offer their, well, philosophical
anal sex, if you will.
But that's only the main course, brothers and sisters.
Pope Fred at IndieVival 2002.
Millions of people get confused about how we're saved, whether we're saved by works or by grace.
One says, no, we're saved by grace and works have nothing to do with it.
The other says, no, it's not enough to be done that way.
You must also work.
And if you don't work, then you do not have salvation.
Now, that is a good point.
That is a good point.
Do you have slack?
If you display the trappings of slack, if you give slack to others and yet do not experience the slack yourself,
is that a slackful life in the manner of our Master Bob?
Or, by the same token, if ye yourself have slack,
of quite a pungent odor on your body and in your spirit,
your spirit,
then, but yet, if you do not share of this slack and use,
because there's always a little extra,
if there's any slack at all,
there's a little extra to share, to share.
That's right, to share with those around you,
those deserving ones.
Or else, by the same token, to use that slack to injure foes,
because there is the curse.
Because once you have slack,
now, you can use it to sap an equal amount of slack,
or negate.
You cannot take the slack of another subgenius exactly,
but you can negate his slack so that it does him no good.
And so, in other words, what we're saying here is,
if you have one without the other,
if you have a grace of slack without the works of slack,
and vice versa,
is it still salvation in the name of Bob?
Now, I think this is moot point.
Because, because if you do not have the fullness,
the ful-ness of slack,
why, it'll make you forget what you're going to say.
And so,
that we would become adopted children of God in his great family.
God knew who was going to be saved and who would not be saved.
And the Holy Ghost quickening those, the mind,
I was able to think better, and I was able to learn easier,
and it became a tremendous thing to me.
And ladies and gentlemen, I know of one gentleman,
You made my thing, gentlemen.
when God saved him,
Confess it!
You will arrive at the same level of fulfillment.
Confess your, your excrement.
Confess it!
Confess your,
uh,
the, when you have put your mouth on the sexual organs of others.
Tell me about it!
It's more than just a hard-on.
It's more than just coming in your path.
It is a way of life.
You forget everything but Bob.
You forget everything outside of the subgenius universe,
and,
and you can,
or,
when a child is fed this wonderful knowledge,
his personality is stamped,
cemented in place,
with a Bob,
a righteous,
Bob-ly,
um,
way of thought.
Oh, great Bob.
And I know that it has.
We can see,
we can rise,
we can see the jewels and members rising up.
Thank you.
Pray,
Bob.
Uh,
should,
should spill as,
spill the bad seed,
retain the good.
Spill the bad,
retain the good,
we say.
Uh,
remove the bad,
spit,
it's a squirting universe,
my friend.
And one good thing about this is that we can get,
we can,
we can squirt out the bad seed.
And,
they fill these children,
they fill them with the full gospel of slide.
Yeah,
Thank You,
uh-
we enjoy,
we can enjoy theek
the way the church is,
of discriminating religious rapists.
Oh, like Jimmy the Greek Baker.
But no, I don't get put up with the shirrids
in Sand Key Resort like Jessica Hahn.
No, I gotta take it up the ass from staying
in the toaster outside the Red Lobster,
which counts for the smell.
Susie the Floozy in Clearwater Beach.
Before that, the baby Reverend Stang.
And now, E-S-O-S-S-S.
He has traced the new maggots in the minds of the universe.
And he was not offended by it all.
But he knew he had to rise above it all.
For the risk of drowning in his own shit.
Thank you.
So here's the deal.
Since I'm older, they asked me to tell you guys
if you get Mr. Napoli, you're lucky
because he loves to blow the older kids.
Remember, just say thanks.
Then they won't treat you like a little kid anymore.
You know, if you're hanging in a group and you smell funny,
whatever they say, it's probably Mr. Napoli.
They think it's cool to see you get in trouble.
Sponsored by Pee and a partnership for Pee Free America.
Well, actually, what I have decided
might not take too long.
I decided to throw out the notes.
I'm going to...
Half the people are gone.
That's good.
Because I decided I'd just tell you something straight.
Here's my entire script.
It was this note to myself that said,
throwing out my comic books.
Friends, I'm about to tell you a tale of horror
and woe.
With which I'm afraid all too many of you might identify.
Now, many people have asked me and wondered,
gosh, how did that Reverend Stang get to be a subgenius?
What was it that made Reverend Stang so twisted and weird
that he would bust ass for so many years for Bob?
For such little pay for so long.
And friends, you know, people have asked me,
well, Reverend Stang, was it that you were...
Was it a bad...
Was it a bad religious upbringing?
Did the nuns wrap your knuckles with their metal rulers in school?
Was it the Southern Baptists making you handle snakes
when you weren't immune to the poison?
What was it that pissed you off so bad, Reverend Stang,
about religion?
And friends, guess what?
It didn't have a goddamn thing to do with religion.
It didn't have anything to do with my parents being mean
or anything like that.
Actually, they were secular humanists.
Rational, you know, scientific humanists, you might say.
Actually, now they're subgeniuses.
No, it didn't have anything to do with that.
It was simply that I was damned fucking weird, my friends.
I was a weird kid.
I was a real weird kid.
And I'll tell you how goddamn weird I was.
I've not chosen to share this before.
But here's the weirdest thing about me as a little kid.
From the age of four and a half,
as far back as I remember,
I wanted to fuck girls.
Now, you may think that's not so weird.
It is for a four-year-old.
It is for a seven-year-old.
And it is for most 12-years-old
as I found out the hard way, so to speak.
No, it wasn't just that.
It wasn't just that I liked girls
way ahead of the time.
I was supposed to be liking anybody that way.
I mean, everybody gets crushes, you know, and stuff.
But I wanted to lay naked on top of those little girls.
And I didn't even know why.
But I did know this.
That if you talked about it,
you'd get in big trouble.
The little girls got grossed out.
The teacher got grossed out.
Your fellow boys got grossed out.
So I learned that I had to keep my mouth shut
about my ceaseless, unending,
deep desires.
And to tell the truth,
the terrible fact of falling in love
every goddamn day at elementary school.
I mean, if it wasn't for what I did,
what I finally gave up on one of the prettiest little girls in the class,
I'd find it seemed what was cool about the ugly little girls in the class.
And there was no one here that went by
that I didn't have a crush on every girl in that class that I liked.
And if I'd been more open-minded,
it probably would have included the boys,
and the girls would have been the same.
They would have thought I was crazy
if I'd opened my mouth about it.
In fact, my third grade teacher had to
tell me to quit doing that in class.
But that wasn't the only thing that made me weird.
How many of you people are, or were,
monster fans?
Monster fans!
I see that there's a few monster fans
in this room tonight.
Now the reason that you like those monsters,
maybe because they are as hideous and ugly
as those little girls were.
Pretty!
That's kind of the way I felt about it.
They were just cool.
And not only that,
I kind of identified with those monsters.
And I'm sure most of you feel,
share the same feelings.
When you'd be sitting there at the age of six years old,
and you see that old black and white Frankenstein movie come on,
and that poor misunderstood Frankenstein monster,
he didn't have to be born,
he didn't have to be ugly,
he didn't have to be smarter and more powerful
than everybody, all the humans around him.
And when those villagers went up that hill
carrying those torches,
ready to kick his ass,
I bet you I didn't find that monster
and none of that big fucking burger monster
and those goddamn anger and blowbunker
when I got villagers.
My friends,
I was a weird kid,
and you were probably weird kids,
but, you know,
I was a weird kid,
and there came a time,
right about fifth or sixth grade,
when my love of,
my love of monsters didn't change at first,
but my love of all those little girls changed,
because it became, shall we say,
more of a productive love.
I was finally able to
really get going, you know?
And, uh,
but friends,
I kept falling in love,
I kept falling in lust,
and never, once,
did one of those little girls
return the, uh,
mutual affection.
I was a lonely kid.
I wasn't unpopular,
I wasn't too weird looking,
I was just weird!
I was just fucking weird!
Now, by the time
I was twelve years old,
and I thought I was gonna die,
I thought I was gonna have to just kill myself
if I didn't get played,
I thought my family's moved!
From one city to another.
I moved up a little bit from Fort Worth
to Dallas.
And I thought, now's my chance!
These kids in this new school,
they don't know that I like monsters,
and I don't know anything about baseball!
These new kids don't know
that I hate team sports!
that I'm weird!
And these new kids don't know
that every day while I sat there
in elementary school,
I drew these comic books!
Yes, friends, I used to be an artist!
I used to draw comics!
When I was in fourth, fifth, and sixth grade,
I drew comic books!
They weren't very original.
In fact, sometimes I ripped off my friends' ideas,
if you're familiar.
But I drew a hell of a...
Not only did I draw comic books,
but I drew animated flip-it books!
You know those little flip-it books?
Friends, I didn't just draw
one or two animated flip-it books!
I created a book
that created over a hundred
little animated flip-it books
in a series called
101 Tortures!
I was accidentally able to come up with
about 50 tortures,
but I doubled them up anyway.
Because I was interested
in seeing how many ways there were
to make normal people die
already at that age!
But, like I say,
we started to move
from forward to now.
And I thought,
here's my chance!
Here's my chance to finally get laid!
Here's my chance to finally be popular!
I'll learn about all the cool
music these kids listen to!
I'll put away my comic books!
I'll put away my famous
monsters in Thumbnail Magazine!
And you know what I did, friends?
You know what I did because
I wanted to be normal?
I took those 101 animated flip-it books
and all those comic books
that I drew over all those years
and I threw them away!
I threw them away!
Because I wanted to be
fucking goddamn normal!
Backpack!
I thought I will end
my life as a weirdo!
I will be reborn as a normal
pink fuck!
Well, needless to say,
it didn't do me a damn
bit of good!
I never got laid the whole time
I was in high school!
I just got weirder!
I was a hockey word!
I tried to be normal
but then I took acid!
And sometimes after that
I tried a beer!
And of course,
I had to be an alcoholic for a few years
and I had to take too much acid
for a while!
But friends,
I did learn one thing
that makes no sense
and does you no good
to try to be normal!
Not only do you know that,
but you can't do it!
You cannot become
what you're already not!
But what you can do
is become more
and more of what you already are!
We are a bunch of human
fucking cartoons
in this campground!
We have nothing in common with each other
except when you look around
we're all extreme exaggerations
of some kind of fucked up weirdo!
And there's some sort of
bluesy fuck-up fear
of human cartoons!
There's the Reverend Evangel of human cartoons!
There's the Pope Xanella
of human cartoons!
The Lonesome Cowboy
and the Reverend Saint!
And all of you, friends,
friends,
you know, I don't mean to tell you
that you're all or any clever,
cool, but fucking nuts!
I think you understand what I'm saying!
What I'm saying is
fuck them if they can't
take a fucking shot!
Fuck them!
Fuck them if they can't take a shit!
Ah, yes, dear friends,
my true confessions.
They're the music
by Einstein's Secret Orchestra
and, uh,
that was recorded in the
Pufferdome at Starwood
2002.
For more information about Starwood, see
Rosencomet.com
Thank you, and good night!
It was great fun!
It's that kind of thing, and I went all the way around Burning Man
in about half an hour and came back
to sort of nearby, you know, walk back
to where, walk back in
to the same scene with my friends sitting
there with pipe holes going around.
They had not moved, and I'd gone all the way
five miles through Burning Man.
It was pretty fun.
And Ivan Stang was there, he was sitting right there
while I did that.
But he was sitting right there, in fact,
I heard that there were photos of
Stang and Mexico City at the same time.
Yeah, well,
what? What? What?
It might not have been Stang, it might have been
somebody calling himself Stang.
I've seen the photos, some guy with gray hair,
gray beard, that doesn't look like Stang to me.
That waiter jacket thing?
No, no, they went to Burning Man.
I don't know, they look smudgy to me.
The guy's all kind of ashen and gray looking.
Yeah, I don't, see it doesn't look like
a real Ivan Stang doll.
That's what I'm saying, that was someone else,
a wavy gray beard, I don't know who it was.
When I first saw it, the first impression I had was
they had taken that Ivan Stang action doll
they got in the cereal about 15 years ago,
and were just shot at a gun.
It was crappy cereal.
Yeah, and a crappy action doll, and that's what it looked like.
In the first one I saw, then I saw the cleaned up
digital version, and it looked like a,
it actually looked like this yuppie guy,
it didn't look like Stang at all.
But it might be the yuppie guy
who's going to take over from Stang.
I don't know if he knows about that,
so I don't know if we should talk about that on this tape.
Probably not.
I heard Tom Hanks was going to play Stang in the movie.
Is that right?
Is that a country western guy?
What?
But you know, one thing we do talk about here
is how many people are in this foundation?
How many?
We don't know. But we assume
from the dirt of San Francisco
there are people in that foundation.
Like Jimmy Hoffa style.
That was
Doug Wellman and Byron Werner.
Gee, thanks guys.
Praise God.
We'll see you next time.
Bye.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community