Bob, Bob, love you.
Light your prop eyes up and test it back.
Well, welcome to the hour of slack.
Praise Bob, Bob, and Connie's rack.
Yes, welcome to the hour of slack.
All bow before the great metal lord.
Worshippers? This ought to liven up my endless tragic voyage.
We're all here tonight to praise Bob.
He's kind of shown us that Devo works in parallel ways with other pockets of humans on this planet.
Where we thought we were alone, we know there are now other human forms that believe in God.
And we know that Bob is a conscious mutation.
As he knows, Bob is merely an enema for a constipated society.
These people here are here to help a constipated society blow it out their ass.
Have you ever met Bob?
Well, like I said, Bob would appear in my bedroom and chase me around, making me do jumping jacks.
He's got food.
I know what you do.
Cause I do it too.
Intelligence.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Am I as smart as I think?
Probably not.
That's good.
Daily disease cannot feel pain.
Nobody eats and drinks in the beginnin'.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
We do the things we do because we want to.
We fight with them.
I'll take on humanity's repository of man.
Mutter words of silence,ALLY During the 거 connected corresponds with the
corresponding level three we just blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah.
held on August 10th in Cleveland.
The third annual one
organized by several old subgeniuses
and fellow Devo fans.
Reverend Toth Wilder,
Reverend Scott Orsi,
the good Blinker Boy at AOL.com
and help from Steve Sinek.
And friends, it's just been,
it's great.
Because I love the Devo's.
We have a lot in common,
the church and the Devo's.
We're both owned by Bob.
We were both controlled by Bob
completely for quite a long time.
And we both share a philosophy.
We don't always have the same kind of music,
but sometimes we do.
We always have the philosophy.
A special philosophy,
a little different,
depending on which cult you're talking about.
But it is a philosophy for the different.
You know, in pamphlet number one,
what the hell?
This is Herb Alpert here in the background.
Friends, did you know that Herb Alpert
was the guy who signed Devo
to their very first big time record deal?
Anyway, friends,
the church of the subgenius
has called itself the spaz church
of macho irony.
And as I enjoyed the various cover bands
covering Devo
and the new and old and rare Devo materials
that were dredged up
for each of these conventions,
I got to thinking and pondering
about the spazfulness of the great spaz bands.
And the ones I was thinking of primarily
are ones from the 80s.
Elvis Costello,
who I actually used to sort of resemble
back in the day.
And Talking Heads,
I never was that into Talking Heads,
but they were a great spaz band, I suppose.
And David Byrne is a deuce paying subgenius
twice over,
just as are several members of Devo.
Ah, friends.
But you know, some people,
and then of course there's spaz bands today,
and we'll be playing a lot of that.
But you know, some might say
that the spaz,
the spaziness and spazitude
of the weirdos
shows no dignity.
That it is somehow silly and unmanly.
But,
nay, my friends, nay!
I say the ability to spaz
is our treasure,
and the inability to spaz
is the curse of the blockhead and the pink.
Because think,
is not the sexual orgasm coming?
The ultimate,
spaz attack?
The spaz of sex, friends.
The spaz of letting your own mutant abnormality out.
Do you really care what the others think?
Well, sure you do.
But, why let on?
Friends, as Bob Dobbs said very recently
to his young ward, Dr. Onan Kanabite,
Bob said,
I'd rather have the right people laughing at me
than have the wrong people laughing with me.
Friends, you think about that
as you spaz out in this, uh,
friends, white, you just white.
You just white.
Is there anything religion can do to help me?
Help me find my friend?
Well, we could join together in prayer.
Uh-huh.
But is there anything useful we can do?
No.
Oh, man.
Whoa.
Oh, why, why?
Why should I be?
Oh, what a nophone.
Oh, why should I be behind this?
Why?
Boy, why, why should I divide this like
Oh, boy.
While we left and did it
While the right hand goes to work
I said we left and did it now
You've got both hands
You've got beret in hands
Take me for no man
Okay relax
And assume the position
Going to dog is a mission
Once around we've done today
Always do what your mama done say
But some people don't follow way
Once around we've done today
As soon as they love their jalass
Just try to stay cool
Just fly power în the air
Go ballin' like a trit
You got the whole scene
You've got left hand
Well done
Goodnight
We've found something now
You're melting now
You got old hands, you got beret and hands
You got beret and hands, they pray for no man
They pray for no man
Okay, relax and assume the position
You're into doggy's ambition
Watch your head three times a day
Always do what your mama let's say
Bust a dick with a ball away
Watch your head three times a day
Always do what your mama let's say
Bust a dick with a ball away
Watch your head three times a day
A lovely, lovely rendition of Devo's Praying Hands
Performed by All The Way
by Occupant
Who has covered a number of Devo songs
Which we'll hear this hour
Just absolutely amazingly
Occupant
You can learn more about Occupant at www.mp3.com
Slash Occupant
Or you could even write to Dr. Onan Kanabait
At onan at subgenius.com
And now
Through subversive measures
Devo passes on the word of Bob
By uh, we
If you take a look at our last album cover
His name's been airbrushed into the rubber hairlines
Of each of the band members
Right next to the word sex
Do Bob and sex go hand in hand?
Well, Bob is a kind of total all-consuming sex
Near like explosions
At length
It makes no sense
To faudet
This needin' sweet
Gross
Is conclude
That day
The only joke is
Well never mind
the Yoni. Tell us about that. What's that? I'm sure your audience knows what the Holy Temple of the Yoni is. Can you tell us? It's the female delta. Mark Mothersbaugh on Bob.
Come in, Boogie Boy. We're late. Have you got the papers the Chinaman gave you?
Here it is, Dad. Is it a surprise?
Yes, Boogie. In the past, this information has been suppressed. But now it can be told.
Every man, woman, and mutant on this planet shall know the truth about D.L.
Oh, shit.
Peek-a-boo!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
We are in the dark!
Peek-a-boo!
Go on!
We'll be right back.
A Bruiser Mix by Bruiser.
Whoever that is.
It came with the devotional special memorial CD.
A Bruiser Mix by Bruiser.
The song was devolving.
Turning back into the most simple of primates.
This would explain daytime TV.
Jerry Springer being so popular.
Why the hell were you not on a f***ing record label?
But right when I was about to tell Bubba about this.
He turned on Jerry Springer.
And as I watched.
That 13 year old prostitute straddle the Pope.
I couldn't think anything but.
What a damn fine country we live in.
God bless f***ing America.
Devolutionization.
By a group called the Cryogenic Strawberries.
An unusual group.
I think they're on mp3.com too.
Or somewhere out there.
Do a little search.
Cryogenic Strawberries.
二, into nice navies from跟
Wheelies,
Joyful- Ernest Shutters,
Love In hyung's Back,
and Al vouzuyou,
aret äาß,km Publications Cappel aus dem New Yorker Welcome to New York!
Today, what does it take to do the super thing?
I'll tell you what it takes, a very simple thing
Iron nerves, like the pilot of a jumbo jet
Or a girl, on the go who hasn't got there yet
Magnetic trumpets blowing, synthetic saxophones
The evidence kept growing from below
Hidden motivations, buried in my past
Still give a string for the super thing
The Red Alarm
A rude surprise every time it rings
It means it's time to go beyond the normal thing
Pay attention and be prepared to do it right
The super thing, the thing that makes you bigger than life
Magnetic trumpets blowing, synthetic saxophones
The evidence kept growing from below
Hidden motivations, buried in my past
Still give a string
Iron nerves, like the pilot of a jumbo jet
Magnetic trumpets blowing, synthetic saxophones
Still give a string for the super thing
The evidence kept growing from below
Hidden motivations, buried in my past
Still give a string for the super thing
Iron nerves, like the pilot of a jumbo jet
Magnetic trumpets blowing, synthetic saxophones
The evidence kept growing from below
Hidden motivations, buried in my past
Signals start to travel from a distant place
Lights go out, electrical shock, then pleasure pain
Sensations unfamiliar can make you sick
It's a superhuman thing and it does the trick
Magnetic drops are flowing, synthetic saxophone
The evidence kept growing from below
In motivation, buried in the past
Still give us strength
Superhuman
Cadaver Skyural
C... tonri gauge...
N....4... voix mockum...
świece okra ash cans...
some really weird yours truly watch my mind truly also man it's a king that's in the kingdom of the
spazzes the the one-jeaned man is blind the ironic jackanapes they call them well one time spazz
church of macho iron macho iron is what they said back in the in the old days and it's just as true
now as it was 10 000 years ago when bob carved those into that bear skull
you're walking down the street you keep lifting your feet but you never find a place to go
never find a place to go until suddenly man you never even knew
you
i say we hit you as the back of your hand that's right
i say get off of the street get off of the street
ball people gonna think you're still gonna think people gonna people gonna think you're spaz
come on now that's right
you're pretty shook up so you're going to get a cup of water just to calm you down
but when you turn around some jokers will just stay
yourself
hey you know it wasn't mama's tea
get off of the beach
get up on the flea
people gonna think you're spaz
song
guitar solo
Come on now, that's right, uh-huh
You wanna sit down when you know some crowd's gonna try and pull away your chair
So you stand and stand, stand and stand until
Now you can't stand any longer
Hey, you know you shouldn't have never sat down
That's right, uh-huh
I say get off of the floor, get off of the floor, boy
People gonna think, yes they're gonna think
People gonna, people gonna think you're spanked
Yes
People gonna think you're spanked
By the Elastic Band
A classic song of great spazitude
And before that, some ESO Swamp Radio
From WCSB Cleveland, Chaz Smith
And Lonesome Cowboy Dave and yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang
Talking about the Feast of Spazism
Speaking of which, upcoming are some amazing
Well, here's an example, it's not a Devo song
Although Little Theodore later on in the show will cover Through Being Cool
Here's Little Theodore with I Don't Care
I don't care about the economy
It has no effect on me
All I need to be happy
Is a woman that's cruel and a place to pee
I don't care about the government
I think it's about time it went
Nasty politicians I resent
Just like me, they're all hell-bent!
I don't wanna hear about big stars
They should all be behind bars
Maybe we can ship them off to Mars
Or take off their clothes and expose their scars
I don't want no more of the press
They're responsible for our mess
If we knew what was best
We'd live our own lives and skip the rest
Ah ha ha!
Yeah ha ha!
Yeah!
Little Theodore, dear friends
And you can contact Little Theodore at
littletheodoreatyahoo.com
Or write to
777 Raleigh Street, Denver, Colorado, 80212.
Or on www.grantrproductions.com
slash pages slash fiodor.html.
Fiodor, by the way, is spelled F-Y-O-D-O-R.
And now, the Hotfoot Quartet.
Hotfoot Quartet
He was a mongoloid and his friends were unaware
Mongoloid, he was a mongoloid and nobody even cared
And he wore a hat and he had a job
And he brought home the bacon so that nobody knew
Mongoloid, mongoloid
Music
Mongoloid, he was a mongoloid
happier than you and me.
The mongoloid, he was a mongoloid,
one from a song too many.
and his friends were unaware.
The mongoloid, he was a mongoloid,
and nobody even cared.
And he wore a hat,
and he had a job,
and he brought home the bacon
so that nobody knew.
Mongoloid, mongoloid.
The Hockfoot Quartet, friends,
and now, Occupant.
Occupant
Bottupant
lieutenant
office
associate
arc
Line
Arsenal
But that ain't much
Volunteer experimentation
Go and lose the pollutation
I'm going under
Going under
Down under where the lights glow
To a place where all the mutants go
Doing things I never did before
Inside, I'll come back for more
Little girl with a boring lips
Never knew it could be like this
You put me in a sad twist
And I'm going through some corp-nutri-sum
Down under where the lights glow
To a place where all the mutants go
Doing things I never did before
Inside, I'll come back for more
Little girl with a boring lips
Never knew it could be like this
You put me in a sad twist
And I'm going through some corp-nutri-sum
Down under where the lights glow
To a place where all the mutants go
Doing things I never did before
Inside, I'll come back for more
Little girl with a boring lips
Never knew it could be like this
You put me in a sad twist
And I'm going through some corp-nutri-sum
Going under
I'm going under
Go, go, go, go down
Occupant
At www.mp3.com
Slash occupant
There's more, more, more
More, more, more, more
Such as this song by
Well, this came from the
Devotional CD
For more information on the
Devotional, here's their
Well, a website that will help you
That's
Hometown.aol.com
Slash
Blinkerboy
But Blinkerboy isn't
Spelled with vowels exactly
It's spelled this way
Slash
B-L-N-K-R-B-O-Y
Blinkerboy
And they, on their CD
I found this piece
By Beal and Elvin the Sewer Rat
Back to the sand
We muster tails
Although I don't remember
The little sails
I say it's on
The Swicking Sails
Or we not men
We are Nemons
Are we not men
Baby-be-on
We are Nemons
We're pinheads and we are not home
We're pinheads all the go home
Are we not men? We are demons
From even old and business suits
Teachers and critics are fans of the law
Are we not men? We are demons
I say it's all just wind and sand
We're pinheads all the go home
Teachers and critics are fans of the law
Are we not men? We are demons
We are demons
We are todays.
But let's leave things of this world behind
and walk now down the path of Bob
for this brief minute of slack from the church of the sub-genius.
And we find then the family falling apart.
Oh, they wail and gnash their teeth, our rival churches do,
about how the children are getting exposed to too much this and too much that.
What they ain't being exposed to is a little bit of mom and dad.
Forget the pornography, I don't care.
It makes me mad, my friend, the hypocrisy.
Now, I have nothing against hypocrisy.
Every religion must have its fair share of hypocrisy.
As Bob Dobbs once said, I don't practice what I preach
because I'm not the kind of man I'm preaching to.
But that preacher can get up there on TV and, oh, he's so glad to keep you normal,
keep you working so hard you don't even know your own wifey anymore.
And your kids, you don't know your kids any better than your employees.
So, friend, let there be slack.
Salutations.
Today I feel a sense of urgency as I speak to you for Devo Incorporated.
There is a direct connection between Devo's work in the music field and a big wiggly world around us.
You may not be aware of this, but we are in the middle of World War III.
It is not nuclear bombs that we must fear.
The weapon is the human mind or lack of it on this planet.
That will determine our fate.
Capital punishment for airline passengers who attempt to save money.
Spud men and gas lines who forgot that guns don't arm.
And tourists attempting to catch some rays at Three Mile Island add up to a major attack of corkscrews in the brain.
We must fight back.
We must know what we want.
We must want what we need.
And what we need is duty now for the future.
And for the future it is even harder when you are a little kid who looks at this ship and says we are ever going to stand up again.
But in your place, in this world with yourégine will only carry thesenot worse.
We must move from thiskanal Videos.
Meaning we shouldn't lack abilities.
We have nothing to lose.
What is a god's Flash for?
So it is wise to have your possible result at the dispatcher scriptures as an example.
What you can learn is the word you have to practice in order to have success.
We can learn from various London's До Calls in this channel.
Bye.
Mother's ball fiddling around on his fair light around 1984 when we helped with the RU Experience video.
And now, more Occupant.
I'm saddened.
Because it's hard to believe.
Oh, it's so easy to see.
I'm saddened.
We're waiting for a reply.
For the very last time.
I'm saddened.
Oh, baby, this one's for you.
For everything that you do.
I'm saddened.
Until the battle is won.
We live to fight on and on.
And when you had it all together.
And when you rolled it in a ball.
And when you walked in the pyramid.
As it's about to fall.
Remember you were there.
Remember if you were there.
For those who held the ground.
When it all came down.
Sound.
Oh, baby, this one's for you.
For everything that you do.
Sound.
Until the battle is won.
We live to fight on and on.
Sound.
Oh, baby, this one's for you.
For everything that you do.
Sound.
Until the battle is won.
We live to fight on and on.
Sound.
About the world outside.
Because you just can't hide.
Sound.
From the plain honest truth.
There's so much we could do.
Sound.
Oh, baby, this one's for you.
For everything that you do.
Sound.
Until the battle is won.
We live to fight on and on.
Sound.
Oh, baby, this one's for you.
For everything that you knew.
Sound.
Until the battle is won.
We live to fight on and on.
Sound.
I'm serving.
Sound his out.
Sound.
I'm serving.
Sound his out.
Sound.
I'm shouting!
Shout it out!
D-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d
d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d
d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d
We tell us that we lost our tails
Evolving up from little snails
I say it's all just wind and sails
Are we not men? We are the evil
Are we not men? The evil
Young Nigel doing the classic Jocko Homo there
from the Devotional Devo Memorial CD
and now Little Theodors.
Oh no, I'm sorry friends.
And now Strange Pursuit by Occupant
and then Little Theodors through being cool.
Little Theodors
Telling you you have to, but you never turn the light on.
It's a great world.
Taking my mind and putting love into the beaver.
Never get stuck when you give a glance.
It's a great world.
Time to show those evil spuds what's what.
If you live in a small town, you might find a dozen or two
young alien types who step out and dare to declare
we're through being cool.
We're through being cool.
Thank the tank who tried to drive you nuts.
Time to clean some house.
Be a man or a mouse.
Waste those who make it tougher.
Get around.
If you live in a big place, any factions under the ground,
chase down Mr. Pinky Dink.
So don't say, can't be found.
We're through being cool.
52nd?
depende de itu goose.
The zinnies and the twits
Put the tape on a race
Rearrange your face
We all really like to tassel anyway
If you live in a small town
You might find a dozen or two
Young aliens try to step out
And dare to declare
We're through being cool
Eliminate the zinnies and the twits
Spank the punk who tries to make you wank
Spank the punk who tries to drive you nuts
Smash him!
We're through being cool
You have been listening to
The Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack
Produced by yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang
My address is P.O. Box 807 Glenrose, Texas 76043
But you can write for more information for free
Paper information from the Church of the Subgenius at
Post Office Box 807 Glenrose, Texas 76043
As seen on WSB-TV
www.subgenius.com
The band Devo is
They've got a new album coming out
Called Shout, which will be out in about a month
They've done a cover version of Hendrix's
Are You Experienced?
And the Subgenius Foundation in association with
Tele Music Corporation is going to be putting that video together
It'll be loaded with special effects and probably a cameo appearance
By the ghost of Bob Dobbs
And by the ghost of Jimi Hendrix, too
This is a whole, you know, combining two churches in one
Yeah, I'm serious
This ought to be quite a seance-packed shoot
So, but aside from the videos that we're trying to do
There's a lot of
The whole music video thing is kind of a funny situation
In that that whole world is loaded with what I consider false slack
And, you know, endless repetition of the same thing
But here is the whole deal
The other side of all that I can tell is that
I feel like probably
I don't believe it
Hey, you know Bob says
That you say
My dad d00d
Thank you.
Bender!
It's a mirror!
Miracle!
Ah!
This is by a wide margin the least likely thing that has ever happened.