Where's your fish?
I beg your pardon?
Well, I don't have one at the moment.
Okay, okay.
All right, mister, just hold the fish up with your right hand.
Yeah, that's right.
Smile.
Thank you very much.
Official report.
Let me tell you, you're wrong.
You're wrong in feeling that way about...
This is too genius to be a snack.
Hold it!
Dogstown.
Is actually nothing like this.
Unless you want it to be.
This is the Sakeem.
The Sakeem.
Yes.
Sakeem.
Our.
Slack.
National present, Cheese Theater.
With two of Hollywood's most distinguished citizens, Bob and Bob.
And here is that glamorous star of radio and pictures, Bob.
Bob, thank you.
Thank you.
It does feel wonderful, Bob.
Don't look now, but I think there's a plug coming.
Well, Bob, if it'll do you any good, I have an in with Bob.
I have a lady in the playpen, Doctor.
Do you know what it means?
To be sure.
And make it homogenous.
Psych.
A great actor, ladies and gentlemen, is one whose talents range in many directions.
Pretty.
Brass.
Bob and I.
Home.
Same.
Bailey Howard's hot rod beaver.
Most kids her age go for somebody like Bob.
Who's he?
An actor.
Oh, frankly, it evades me.
I don't think...
You're not supposed to, honey.
I'll do the thinking tonight.
Why, it's...
It's...
It's foam.
I thought you were...
You certainly are.
Really?
In just about a minute, you're going to hear Bob, who I'm sure will have a laugh or two
up his sleeve.
So listen.
A pint a day for adults, and a quart a day for children.
Then zing.
Carrot, carrot, carrot, carrot, carrot, carrot, carrot, carrot, carrot, carrot, carrot, carrot,
carrot, carrot.
Thank you, wrecking crew.
And now, folks, here he is, the star of screen, radio, television, vaudeville cafes, personal
appearances, and fat boy for the Cleveland Indians, Bob...
I love you.
I love that head.
It was a good ship lollipop.
Everyone aboard was a sucker.
I wonder what time it is.
My rubber sheep is afloat.
Next Thursday night, we'll be back with Dick.
So try and be with us.
Keep listening.
Bob, I'll soon be seen in the new Paramount picture, Paleface.
I'll see you then.
I'll write on it.
God damn it.
Oh, bên encore.
It's Steve.
Oh, it's Tom.
It's all right.
It's Steve.
You're not still cool?
Do you want some?
Love you.
Loveya and metres.
Loveya and surfaces.
Didna-as...
exoticiness.
I'm as free as a bird now
And Lord help me, I can change
Yes, I must have flown in one too many planes
Lord help me, I can change
Yee-haw!
guitar solo
How about you?
I'm as free as a bird now
And Lord help me, I can change
Yee-haw!
guitar solo
Ah, yes, yes, yes, friends.
The Leonard Skinner Memorial Tractor Pull
by the Rudy Schwartz Project
from Schwartz Tone
dot com
And before that,
friends, Reverend Norrell Preff
of norrellpreff.com
captured the Vintage Bob Show.
Our new intro
was by Popes Lilith von
Frau Mensch.
Also, thanks to Just John
and Fernanda Nandi-Liemer
for the openings.
This is Hour of Slack
number 1312.
A rerun
of the
of number
X-Day meets Burning Man.
Dr. Howell was at both events
and has many tales to tell
and I have recordings to play
from the subgenius event
of the 9X Day Drill.
But before we go into that,
here's Fat Harry White.
Mmm, baby
Slippin' into my new skin-tight job
is for you, honey.
And dressin' up
for the leaders for the love.
Come over here, Maureen.
Hey, I'm talking about dressing up
like it reminds me
of when I worked at Slack's R.O.S.
You know, right?
Next to Jessop's, the grocer's.
It was the first time I met Foxy Fiona,
my very sexy lady friend.
Never forget it,
she walked up to me at the counter
and in a very sexy voice
asked me what I had to offer
in the trouser department.
Apparently,
she wanted to buy some flared crimpling slacks
for her long-legged father's birthday.
Very partial to bright colours, it was.
Anyway, I told her I was almost certain
I'd have something with a good length
that would satisfy her
and asked her to follow me upstairs.
Well, after going through me trousers,
she surprised me by saying
that she really fancied the large pink pair that I had.
Not only did they hang well,
but she thought they looked really attractive,
particularly the way they swung about loosely
when I walked.
Mind you, she wasn't too sure of the size at first
and had me lay them out on the counter
so she could measure them up.
She also ran her fingers admiringly down the crease.
Well, she decided to go for it,
asked me how much.
I says three and a half quid.
She asked me rather cheekily if I would go down.
Well, you know, thought about it,
long and hard,
decided to drop them for her,
which I did there and then.
What fun, backwards and forwards,
over the counter.
A good bit of haggling and no mistake.
And I was thinking about this, right,
because I've been back to that shop,
because the weather's beginning to change a bit,
getting a bit parker, isn't it?
Well, I tell you what,
I went out the other morning
and me buns were so cold it started to change colour.
I'm not kidding.
When me very sexy lady friend, sexy Sam,
saw me coming towards her,
me purple head sticking out me coat,
she told me to get it covered immediately.
So I said, I'm going to the shop to buy a hat, a fur one.
Well, when I got there, you know,
I asked sexy Salea,
the very sexy lady friend hat assistant,
to show me what she had, you know,
in a fur department.
She said she'd be only too pleased
to show me what she had downstairs,
and led me to the basement,
where I could see everything she had
on full display.
I tell you what,
you wouldn't believe how much she had.
She had every kind of fur out you could imagine.
I was going to go for a fox fur,
but as soon as sexy Salea said she had
a particularly nice beaver
that I might be interested in,
immediately changed me mind.
Well, you know, after getting it out for me,
I've got to say I've never seen
such a big bushy one like it in all my life.
Well, when I asked her if she could,
you know, try it on for size,
she said I might find it a bit tight at first,
but if I buried me head deep enough,
then it should stretch a little
to accommodate me fully.
Tell you what, she weren't wrong,
and when I looked at it in the mirror,
you know, sideways on,
I could see it had slid in perfectly.
Well, you know, after that,
she then said she'd sum it round the back
that I might be interested in,
led me into the storeroom
to show me a selection of gloves
that had just arrived.
Well, I was obviously interested,
but as I didn't know what size I was,
I had to get sexy Salea to measure my hand.
Well, after asking me to, you know,
give her a finger, which I promptly did,
she then asked me to stick my thumb up.
No problem at all.
Within minutes, she declared,
as she was holding her measuring tape,
that I was extra, extra large.
Well, then she had to take a phone call,
but while she was on the mobile,
I took the opportunity of rummaging in her box
until I found the perfect fit,
and when I withdrew,
sexy Salea nodded appreciatively
at my great big leathery pair.
Dressing up for the ladies, yeah.
Am I looking in the mood for love?
Fat Harry White can be your friend.
See myspace.com
slash
Fat Harry White.
What a man.
Speaking of men,
Dr. Howell performed at Burning Man,
as he explains to Governor Rocknar on Puzzling Evidence.
I think that was Burning Man.
Oh, it burned like you wouldn't believe,
and off went a bunch of firecrackers.
See, they had a special deal where
they built this big, fake, phony,
up Egyptian temple,
and the men were sort of half sunk,
and half in it,
but then when the time came,
he rose up on his hydraulic pedestal,
higher and higher,
towering over the whole thing
before he burst into flame.
Yes.
Did people cheer like crazy people?
Cheering like crazy people,
or were they cheering like normal people?
The same crazy people walked widdershins
around the burning wicker man,
and so they were up there doing that.
Listening to this show tonight has been,
it makes me feel like I've been there.
I've been there,
and a precision bench lathe.
We've all been there.
We'll all be there.
I hope so.
I'm going back.
But do you feel like you've been through
57 years of specializing exclusively
in lathe manufacturing?
Incredible special effects.
My gosh, it's incredible what they can do.
I just love it.
And Dobbsco,
it means more value
for their lathe purchasing dollar.
What's going on here?
Which hand is open?
There we go.
Um.
I know we're trying to push our
lathe's on everybody,
but we've got these two left in stock,
and we're trying to do a closeout.
What's new in metalworking,
you might say?
I'm just trying to do a show.
Well, a whole lot of welding.
In Rocknar, where did you go?
I'm right here.
Well, you're just sitting back there.
I'm just daydreaming that I'm
on the volcanic dust desert.
Hail Rocknar.
Yes.
It's not volcanic.
It's not volcanic dust.
It's the bottom of a lake.
It's one of the worst places humans can go.
Yes, it's a lake bottom,
and the dust is diatomaceous earth.
What is the bottom?
Yeah, and the place is,
it's like the...
But you say earth.
It's so fine.
It's terrible for your lungs,
and it's terrible for your bare feet.
It's terrible for your machinery.
You're walking around in the sunlight,
which is being reflected almost 90% off that plane.
Incredibly destructive.
It's like being in another planet.
It's nice to come back.
That's one of the more interesting things
about the event.
It's the worst place on earth.
It's the worst place you can do it.
No, it's not that bad,
but it's the worst place you can have
a huge event.
You should go out there on your birthday.
On like X day,
where they put in a nice, healthy,
wet, green area.
I must say that the...
Because it's really nice.
Ice cold cans of ale eight,
which I had along with me,
really helped things.
Really came in handy.
Yes, they did,
and even chicken drank one.
Oh, how did he like it?
I'm afraid not much,
but he's a...
He doesn't like much of anything.
Well, perhaps that's so.
Anyway...
Faster than a speeding building.
Look, it's a bird.
And now, the adventures
of super delicious cereal.
Well, thank God he didn't sweat it.
But, that's the truth.
As if a lackluster food
had been Sirloin Neistat last
Guess who struck him dead?
Dr. Philodruman.
I Arbeits posture.
Neusaan,
you oldav,
It has the greatest capacity and the smallest floor space.
I haven't seen a sight like that since I was weaned.
Stay calm now, Dr. Howell. Stay calm.
What exists in the depths of the earth?
Hold yourself back.
In the caconic darkness, some say they come out at night to wreak hideous vengeance on the living.
Dr. Howell permits at any angle, at any height, horizontally or even vertically.
Dr. Howell and I will exorcise these evil spirits from your body.
And there's Dr. Howell as he goes about.
He's breaking down each job into fairly simple components.
Yes, he's getting the requirements from all the users.
And he's writing down the sequence to perform the operations.
Each of the steps are operations that Dr. Howell is devising.
The worker will perform and accompany each step
with a brief explanation.
The presentation of the essential things to be remembered about how to do
that next step.
We'll call these key points.
And Dr. Howell's development.
And with this breakdown job method, we will begin instruction as soon as possible.
Upon receipt of the permit.
The facilities have to be available.
Yes, and the funds transfer must be made.
The resources have to be available for acquisition.
The waiver is necessary for mutual protection to sign.
Implementation and completion.
It is possible that sometimes after receiving the treatment,
the patient is...
Once the budget is approved, we'll be on our way.
Less than satisfied characters.
We have to have the appropriate signatures.
Mere honesty stimulates us to mention this.
And then we will dispense and implement.
In three hardness grades, seven sizes, and two weights.
And thus the presence of the prenup, or as you might call it, the waiver,
which the young subgenius Ed must sign before beginning the treatment.
And now the drama will increase for the next 15 seconds.
And believe me, I had no idea that I would be forced into this role,
but at what you may call it...
Don't say it.
Ivanstock or Doc's Day or whatever it is,
I found that I was...
required to fill a role I had not thought myself...
Was that one where you got first night privileges?
And first morning and first middle of the day.
Ah, yes.
Let me ask you one thing then.
Is female choice of honest male advertisement adaptive
under conditions of promiscuous polygamy or...
Boy, I don't know.
Monogamy?
You're driving me crazy.
You're coming or going.
What can I say?
But at...
Exstock, it was an interesting time
because new people were being brought in
and certain ancient rituals had to be revised to accommodate them.
What could be the source of this bizarre sexual behavior?
Well, it's only human.
I mean, why do you call it bizarre?
It's like nature taking its course, kind of.
See? Not bizarre at all.
Now, others, of course,
require a certain amount of what we call kink
because they are atrophied in their imaginations
and they require special additions to flag their...
Now, did you seclude these young women and feed them on raw egg,
eggshell, gulps of Margosa oil,
and a dish of steamed rice,
black graham, grated coconut, and sesame oil?
They insisted upon it.
It was not anything of...
my doing.
But I will say that we also managed to do broadcasts,
radio broadcasts,
right out of the Ex Day main meeting room.
Yes, it was astonishing
because there we had generated future seeds for radio shows.
Our first questioner is asking,
Dr. Howell,
when the saucers do come,
how long will I have to wait
to exchange this body for another?
Impatient sort, apparently.
Impatient sort is the name of the questioner?
Well, then, in that case, I'll say...
It's not on here. That's an anonymous...
Dear impatient... Oh, it's anonymous.
Yeah, well, we didn't...
Did we specify that they needed to be signed?
No, they don't have to sign if they wish to...
remain hidden in the light of thought.
That is fine with us here at the Ask Dr. Howell Show.
When the saucers do come,
how long will I have to wait
to exchange this body for another?
Are you sure you want to be so precipitate
in giving up your beloved fleshly vehicle
which guided through the confusing mazes
of providence on this earth?
You know, your other may have more appendages.
It may have the latest in tentacles and maxillipeds,
but it may not have the homely familiarity
of your own anthropoidal body.
However, I think that I'm quite correct in saying
it is subgenius policy that you do go ahead
and experiment as much as you please
in this or any other direction
in your endless search for slack.
This question came up once before,
and Governor Rottenar, I believe, said that he intended to,
to keep his present physical body
because he's already used to it.
That is, of course, a pre-see of what I was saying,
but in the near future,
space travelers may get to modify their bodies
so they are more comfortable on those long flights.
Soaring through the far reaches of outer planetary space,
fantastic headquarters of that swashbuckling cosmic highwayman
of the past.
In the 30th century,
Bob.
Yes, here comes the one and only
Gliding through galaxies in his search for star-shattering adventure.
The interplanetary villains quiver in their space boots
when they hear the merry ring of his laughter
and hear the blast of his mighty
PONOCRAFET
fun-loving astral adventurer
Bob.
The happy outlaw of outer planetary space
is fast,
with a joyful laugh,
a ready jest,
and a quiverful,
full of futuristic arrows.
Bob.
Robs from the cosmic rich.
He's fiery.
He's fantastic.
Merriest of the merry men
in the astounding year 3000.
Bob.
Albinoids and before that a pseudo sauna
cut up and ask Dr. Howl at X-Day
that enough words and now let's hear
some grunts from Dr.
Biltie Miller and slack bangers.
Oh Jong-ho
oh
hello.
The mind
of the most.
most powerful sex organ.
You're gonna like it when you get left behind on it.
You sleazy weasel.
Listen to me, mister.
It's salvation I'm talking about.
Bravo.
The blues isn't about feeling better.
It's about making other people feel worse.
I will tell you about the fiction and the fallacy.
It's brought to you by the salesman of salvation.
That's marvelous. That is marvelous.
I'm very happy for you.
I'm so happy for you.
Slack bang my baby.
You know what I like.
I said slack bang my baby.
You know what I need.
You know what I want.
Oh yeah.
Slack bang my baby.
Now that's what I want best, right?
This is Slack.
Slack bang my baby.
That's Reverend Bill T. Miller, Brother Cleve, Reverend D.K. Jones,
and all of everything, friends, can be downloaded at kingofslack.com.
Except our background music, which is Joe Newman's Rudy Schwartz Project from schwartz.com.
Schwartztone.com, that is.
And now, back to 9X Day and the subgenius nude water baptism.
You want to join the club?
Well, you got to get undressed up there on the diving board.
So everybody gets to watch.
I participated in the...
Oh!
...baptism ceremony for the first time this year.
Oh, you hit my knee with that door.
Just to help out Reverend Stang, if you understand.
In previous years, I'd been warned away from it.
They said, don't go there.
Don't have anything to do with that.
I don't know why.
But this time, I thought, I really want to help.
For some reason, I can't remember.
It's all blurry.
I've been to Burning Man since then.
But at any rate, I went there, and we did indeed, with the total immersion,
bring many quivering naked bobbies to a full understanding of their new life as subgeniuses.
Many other mammals also show these patterns of aggression,
especially when females live in burrows that are costly to dig.
Edgar Rice Burrow.
Their housing is so valuable, they often pass it along to their daughters
and will wound any unrelated young females that try to establish themselves within the area.
They had a giant object which they continued to fling up into the sky,
and as it was practically isostatic in its weightlessness, they often succeeded.
Yet, aberrant breezes would blow it down to earth again.
But at Burning Man, on the other hand,
there was a perfectly formed flying saucer that did the same thing.
If you photographed it, and unfortunately, I never had a camera with me,
if you photographed it, it would look like the most realistic flying saucer photo ever taken,
because it was actually there.
It was actually a real flying saucer.
It was inflated, but it was so well-shaped that it was exactly like a science-fictional flying saucer,
of great size and silver.
So it would float.
It would float around.
Okay, let's get ready to leave now.
We'll give it a get in the car.
We're going to be taking a ride down to the docks, Dr. Howe.
There was a kite that looked like a computer cursor.
A computer cursor which appeared to move around in the sky.
Please ignore the movement of the vehicle.
Not to mention lasers, balloons, other objects.
You can remove the blindfold now.
And the cigarette. I'll have one of those.
I'll have one of those, too.
I want the one you have, though.
Can I have the one you already have?
I don't want just any cigarette. I want the one you have.
That specific one.
Can I have that one now?
Please give it to me.
If you don't give it to me, I'll step on your toe.
Because occasions rise so often that demand such sacrifice.
So take it. Here it is.
Thank you, thank you.
More skillful.
You get it all slobbery. It's all wet and slimy on the end. What happened?
More able to endure.
You seem to... Okay, look out.
As more endure suffering and distress than...
Oh, Jimmy, what have I let you in for?
Stay where you are. Don't move, Helen.
Who is it?
I don't know. Keep quiet.
Helen?
Who is it?
Conspiracy.
What's that?
We don't know.
Huh?
His head's still spinning. He's not responsible for what he says.
Conspiracy to commit...
The Self-Genius Power of Swag.
Right now.
We've got to get out of here.
edit
make
have
La la la la la la la la la la
Nine-year-olds that kick you in the shin
Toilet bowls with droplets on the rim
Leisure suits with polyester trim
And an orange is nothing but a juicy pumpkin
Pepperoni pizza by the slice
Ronald Reagan's gonads in a vice
Chinese food is nice with a bowl of rice
And an orange is nothing but a juicy pumpkin
Shopping malls on Sunday afternoon
Watching grandma vomit with a spoon
Margaret Thatcher squatting on a broom
And an orange is nothing but a juicy pumpkin
Pumpley skin infections turning red
Making fillish laughs that give you head
Hamsters that are dead rotting in your bed
And an orange is nothing but a juicy pumpkin
Let our age equal pumpkin
La la la la la la la la la la
Flavor
Schmackma
Sandwiches with moldy wonder bread
Oral sex with Ellie Mae and Jed
Telling children that their mother's dead
And an orange is nothing but a juicy pumpkin
Scrambling on your eyeball with a pen
Giving gonorrhea to a friend
Scraping at a scab with a grill or pad
And an orange is nothing but
Yes, an orange is nothing but
Yes, an orange is nothing but a juicy pumpkin
I'm Dexy, I'll be your guide for the next half hour
Divorce, divorce, um, white paper
Human augmentation
Flesh out this idea
Excited
Changing into the cat man
Titillated, titillated
You know, the augmentation of human animals
I'm looking at the spread
Reinvent the wheel
Post-humanist
Post-biological
Into that whole
Primate neural grafting
It's actually out there
Allow, um, bonobos
Bonobo, bonobo
They watch television
There's a little tweak here, a little tweak there
And suddenly you've got proto-humanish kind of an entity
And then you've got a little tweak there
Bonobo desires
So everything from increasing our, um
Doing
Would
But
Bail of ignorance
So there you are
In the bail of ignorance
A loosey-goosey
Maybe even fish
Yes, yes, yes, yes
Loosey-goosey
To bonifersons
Neural modification
Could be quite, uh, destructive
And, and harmful
Group sex
Um, going to prison quite often
I don't think so
Because we are still very little removed from our paleolithic ancestry
Sexy, sexy
And I hope to meet you in a sexy primate neural grafting
Woo!
Ay!
Blackberry, baby
Oh!
Oh yeah
That's what I want, that's right!
Uh, slack bangers, friends, uh, uh, well, uh, neural primate grafting, uh, was by Nor El
Pref
And Rudy Schwartz Project did
And orange is nothing but a juicy pumpkin
And now, back to, uh, the 9X Day Drill
Which, by the way, is held at a campground
There is a raccoon out here who is known for stealing pornography and liquor
Oh, how...
And cigars and things
It'll leave, uh, the occasional sack of sugar
But, uh, yeah, he's legendary around these parts
Don't worry about the bears at night
There are hardly any of them
And unless they're rabid, they probably won't do any more than sniff at your feet
Reverend Rosna at the X Day Campground recorded these, uh, bullfrogs at the Camp Pond
Bop!
Every time we turn around we pick up a banner
And I have to feed you food, you know
I turn around, I see myself when I turn around too fast
Ooba, ooba, ooba
There I am, and I shouldn't be there in time
Hey, what are you doing back there?
Get out from behind me
Oh I'm sorry, I just was looking at you
And suddenly, when they do that, you see it's not you
Get thee behind me, Satan!
It was never you, it was Hal
I, uh, well, if you say so, I, that is, I don't really recall because my memory isn't
what it used to be
to be. Too many lacunae
I think there's been too much
disk activity,
too much fragmentation,
and not enough disk proper optimization
taking place.
You should remember
to drink your mentions on your
hard drive.
One day you wake up, you've got
all your information distributed
and merged into a strange
hard drive.
And I couldn't tell whether I was freezing or
boiling as I sat on the mobile living
room and as I sat
moved onward through the
pulsating, whirling
blorp.
And then it happens.
Bad sectors
creep in.
They take over the media service.
And at that point
you are
I can only say you're in the state
of wash.
And as the mobile living room went along
this outriding, this wonderful
outriding, this wonderful
guy on a special motorcycle
scooter with five parallel
blue lights on it was sporting
and moving around it like a dolphin
moving around a ship, twisting
and turning. He wore an
outsized fireman's hat out of
which fireworks spurted and
sparkled. And he
flanked us and
went before us, clearing our way.
And he only wiped out one time
when he went through a puddle
of piddle
on the desert floor, which had not yet
hardened. And it caused him
and his vehicle to wipe out.
But he was alright and back
up on his feet a moment afterward.
Yeah, you can back up your feet.
You can back up your feet.
The miracle of Burning Man
from Dr. Howell there and
Dr. Philo Drummond on KPFA
in Berkeley. And now the miracle of
Reverend P. Kitty's sermon at
9X Day.
Friends, standing here tonight
I'd like to talk to you all
about love.
I'd like to talk to you
about the love that I feel
for that man Bob Dobbs.
I'd like to talk to you
about the joy, the love
I feel for the joy
that slack brings into my heart.
And I'd like to talk about the love,
the camaraderie,
the solidarity that I feel
with my fellow subgenia here.
I'd like to talk
about all those things,
but I can't.
Because I...
I hate.
Yeah!
I hate the conspiracy and everything
it's done to the world and to us.
Am I alone?
I hate this world
and the mazes that they've crafted in it.
The way they bring us down
and how everything's designed to turn it around
against ourselves. Who's with me?
I hate the exes for not showing up
and Bob for the false promises
again and again.
Am I the only one here who hates Bob?
Kill Bob!
And I hate the...
the pinks.
Oh God, I hate the pinks.
Making everything horrible in the world.
Turning society into a weapon against us.
Coming down against anything that stands against
their interpretation of how life should be.
Oh God, I hate them.
My finger has more hate than a thousand Hitlers ever did.
Every neuron in my brain is an atom bomb.
Exploding into billions of nuclear blasts
with every thought.
Leaving radios and radio waves
radioactive fallouts in a wake
miles across everywhere I go.
What's your point?
Some people would say that means that my hate consumes me.
But they're wrong.
My hate inspires me.
My hate lifts me up on wings of fire.
That I may rise above the pinks
and escape the normalcy that threatens to engulf me.
That's what my hate does.
My hatred for the pinks is for their small mindedness.
For their self-loathing.
And for their lack of imagination.
Oh God, we could be here all night.
For their petty obnoxiousnesses.
For their stupid shoes.
For their horrible shoes.
My God, the pink shoes.
Their socks.
And their complete hatred and lack of comprehension of anything and everything that doesn't fit into their particular world view.
Why they cry.
And why they pull up.
And why they police themselves.
But therefore, I'm going to be magnanimous.
What?
It's a failure man.
I refuse to become that which I despise.
I let my hatred bring joy to my heart.
Bring slack to my heart.
My hatred is a slackful hatred.
A joyous, wonderful hatred.
One which puts a smile on my face.
And a smile on my face as I go through the day.
I will open the door for that old lady even as I know that she will be burning in the fires of hell afterwards.
I will help that stranded motorist on the railway even if all he deserves is a painful death.
I will wear a slackful smile and offer courtesy to those who would destroy me.
Because I know in the end that Bob will see to it that they will suffer eternal torment.
And how can I not be happy knowing that?
The conspiracy wants us to turn into what the pinks are.
They want our hatred to burn so wrong that it consumes our slack.
That we're overwhelmed with nothing but anger.
Gripe.
Until all we can do is hate how the world is and not slack off.
And enjoy ourselves.
As well.
My hate powers my slack.
They want everything to turn into subgeniuses being like pinks pumping out more petty crap.
More obnoxiousness.
More flat out pink hate.
Petty hate.
Little hate.
Well my hate is not petty.
And I will not let the conspiracy turn it for their own devices.
I will use my hate to spread slack and joy to everything around me.
And I will not let the conspiracy be damned.
It's one of the things we hate about this world.
The obnoxiousness.
The stupidity.
The pinkness.
The complete bullshit that they spew into things.
So I will turn it against them.
I will turn my hate into slack.
Turn it into a weapon against the petty crap that they throw at me.
Because you need to take things into your own hands.
Sometimes no one's going to do it for you until you grab the world and fuck it into the shape that it needs to be.
Do you hear me?
You're gonna have me out on this one.
Little bitty from OBE called UA.
You seem a little nervous, my friend.
You summoned me from beyond.
Oh no!
You'd better be ready to speak your piece.
You called me from beyond.
You disturbed my restful sleep.
With your childish little games.
You don't know what you're playing with.
This is not a game for little boys and girls.
This is your life.
And we blacked out.
Listen to your music backwards and we press.
This isn't just another stupid heavy metal band.
I'm from the front and ready to eat my metal.
You thought you were gonna be cool, didn't you?
You ready for me?
I used to be a nice guy just like you.
Then I found...
The ticket of a soul is the truth I want.
I will eat you alive and chew you up and spit in your face.
You ready for me?
You'd better be ready to face the consequences little boys and girls.
One last chance, that's all you have.
You ready for me?
There's no escaping the eyes.
You will see them in every dream.
You ready?
You will never escape the eyes of dogs.
The eyes of dogs will follow you wherever you go.
Woo!
I'm gonna shine those eyes again.
You ready for me?
You called me from beyond the grave.
You better be ready to face the truth my friend.
Woo!
We're here for your soul.
Come on!
You ready?
dusid!
Woo!
You ready to fight!
Come on!
Get us out of here!
Come on brought the commissioners over here!
The brothers of planet Earth!
Get it all out now!
But I do believe the deep grave appears.
You got well there, right?
And he said you'd better be out of here, go to the outside of here, go to the inside of here.
Come on, baby.
Bye.
Everyone's heard
quit your job and slack off, right?
Right?
Right!
Alright, well I'd like to tell you a little something.
I was trapped in a conspiracy job.
Office job, Dilbert,
cubicles, all that crap.
Oh, the pay was great.
But I paid. Little by little.
Bits of soul, day after day.
So,
one day,
I called in sick, not because I was sick,
but just because I was sick of working there.
And it felt good.
So I called in the next day.
I called in the next day.
Turned into a week.
Weeks turned into months.
I kept calling in.
I was still on the books.
And their computer
was so ass-backwards
that it kept paying me
because the people I was calling into
didn't take the effort of marking me off
the books!
At the same time,
my wife, the Reverend Venus Envy,
she was hating her job too. She took
advantage of a lay-off option.
She was getting unemployment.
So here we are.
No jobs, no visible source
of income, and yet the income kept coming in.
The bills were getting
paid, and we were sitting around
the house, doing nothing,
slacking off, and enjoying
ourselves, and getting paid for it!
Now, do you
think someone may have had something to do
with that?
You think someone may be behind it?
Well, I'm not saying, I'm not going to jump to conclusions here.
No, I'm not going to jump to conclusions.
Let me just say a little something, though.
Eventually the unemployment ran out, as it does.
Things started to
look a little tight, and right when that
happened, we got a letter
from the unemployment office asking us
would we like another $3,000
gratis?
Yeah, we said yes.
Now, I'm not saying what you think I might be saying.
I'm not going to jump to conclusions here. I just want to say
the person who sent that letter, his initials
were J.R.
Oh!
So, when Bob says,
quit your job and slack off, do you think it's a joke?
No!
You think it's a lie? No!
You think it's yet another false promise from the man who has
betrayed us so many times?
No!
Well, actually it might be, you know. But the question comes down to
do you believe what Bob has
to offer you? Do you believe in Bob?
Yes!
Do you believe in Bob?
Do you believe that you can quit your job, you can
slack off, and that Bob will be there
to catch you when you fall? Do you believe in him?
Yes!
Well, let me tell you something. That doesn't matter.
Yes! It doesn't matter whether you believe in Bob.
Fuck Bob's job!
Doesn't matter to me.
Sure as hell doesn't matter to Bob.
All that matters in life is whether
Bob believes in you.
Bob believes in my money.
Exactly. When you quit your
job, when you walk away from
that asshole you're with, when you
leave the life behind
that you had, all that matters
is will Bob be there to catch you
when you fall?
Probably not!
What have you done for him?
Why should Bob help you? Have you paid your dues?
Yes! Have you converted the
worthy? Yes! Have you
bled for Bob? Yes! Have you
died for Bob? No! Have you killed
for Bob? Yes! Have you killed
Bob for Bob? Yes!
This
joke that you call existence
is nothing more than the pipe dream
of the only man who actually defines
reality. And you better pray
that he remembers that you're an extra
in this little movie.
When he lays himself to
sleep at night,
are you in his thoughts?
Are you in his pipe?
When he lays him down to sleep,
will your soul he pray
to keep? Think
about it. How confident are you?
Praise Bob.
Praise Bob!
For about 10 minutes.
Here is the
askDrHaul column that's repeated
from the publication known as
The Southpaw Self Pleaser
He was a right-handed man surrounded by
nubile willingness but only
his left hand could bring him satisfaction.
That's a Nicki Cheapo Adultамography
320, such a sad story
which can be purchased
right now for
5 dollars each
at subgenius.com
from the subgenius.
You can go there now.
These are pictures from last year's X-Day.
And here is Dr. Philo Drummond
and Ivan Stang and Dr. Howell
sitting there at the picnic table
spouting on the gym.
And here is Sister Decadence
in her role of Holly,
the ruthless one,
at the ball of gods and demons.
This week, the ball was of robots
and people in their pajamas.
Now you know,
Cuijibo, the subgenius house magazine,
is published by Christopher Lee.
And I have to say,
Christopher Lee was the box office magic word
for 2005,
appearing in movies that earned
a combined $640.1 million.
Did you know that Christopher Lee
is like the tallest of all the actors?
That means that...
He's like seven and a half feet tall.
Christopher Lee has beat out
Ewan McGregor, Brad Kitt,
Morgan Freeman,
Samuel Jackson,
Gary Oldman, Vince Vaughn,
Liam Neeson, Chris Rock,
Ralph Fiennes,
and Kerry Washington.
Whoever Kerry Washington is,
I don't know who he is.
You mean in terms of earning?
He appeared in 341 million dollars
worth of millions,
but Christopher Lee movies make more.
And he's in his 80s.
He was in Star Wars,
Revenge of the Sith,
Charlie and the Chocolate Factory,
The Corpse Bride,
a accomplished top box office,
and a star in 2002
with Star Wars Episode II,
Attack of the Clones,
and Lord of the Rings,
The Two Towers.
And so, in addition to all this,
he is a subgenius who publishes
Sweet Depot, the famous...
It's amazing how he gets all that work done
and still manages to come to
X-Day every year.
And he looks so different
when he's in X-Day, you know?
Normally he's like 6'5",
but when he gets to X-Day,
he's like 5'6".
Yes, he does change
considerably in appearance.
And he has glasses on at X-Day,
and his eyes are like,
these are perfect for an 89-year-old
when he's not at X-Day.
It's the weirdest thing.
And he wears that little beanie.
When interviewed,
Christopher Lee said this,
I have the slack gene,
which just means getting stuff done.
I'm actually starting to feel an affinity
for ex-president Gerald Ford.
Through wacky circumstances,
he also found himself increasingly
appointed to new positions,
inheriting the problems
of the previous administrations
and facing them with character
and personal decisions.
The thing to do that politicians do
in pushing their problems off
Mr. Ford gave conditional amnesty
to Vietnam draft dodgers
who had fled the country,
and I rehired our dodgers
who had fled the restaurant
where I work.
A great subgenius magazine, friends,
Cui Ji Bo is.
It's not put out by me.
You can find out how it is put out
by writing to this address,
Cui Ji Bo,
that's Q-U-I-J-I-B-O,
at 18 West Main,
Greenfield, Indiana,
46140.
Maybe a fiver.
That's 18 West Main,
Greenfield, Indiana, 46140.
Before Hal and Dr. Philo Drummond
and Puzzling Evidence were talking,
there was Reverend Peekity
preaching live at 9X Day
and some Rudy Schwartz Project
also heard in the background.
That's from schwartztone.com,
S-C-H-W-A-R-T-Z.
And you rang live at the
X Day 1998 drill,
turned out to be,
performed by Reverend Bill T. Miller,
the King of Slack,
and yours truly,
Reverend Ivan Stang.
I will be teaching a subgenius
online course in November and December
with maybelogic.org.
This you're listening to
is the Subgenius Radio Hour of Slack
from the Church of the Subgenius,
subgenius.com,
and our mailing address is
subgenius P.O. Box 181417
at Cleveland Heights, Ohio, 4417.
118.
And now back to 9X Day.
Foo beans, ladies and gentlemen.
Around the world
Thinking about that horny girl
Singing about her day and night
Wishing that she was here tonight
Singing, loray, loray,
Oh, baby, now we gotta blow
Right off this planet, baby
Loo-a-loo-a
Oh, Bob Bob's wants us to go
X Day is here
Woooooooo
Well, maybe they've blown a fuse,
or maybe a small spider crept in
and created havoc.
Doesn't take much.
It takes a thousand million slaves
to build a pyramid
and only one tiny little earthquake
to destroy it.
Well, we are, of course,
at the mercy of our instrumentality here.
Or a spider smeared across the original plans
making the number look like another number.
Anybody could mistake a fly speck
for a decimal point.
Anybody could.
Anyway, uh...
That's how I ended up on this planet, actually,
but that's a long other story.
We know about that.
Or in this time wrap.
Rather, I should say.
And yet now we go to eat doughnuts.
Yes, doughnut forsake me, oh my darlin'.
Yum.
Yum, little darlin'.
So don't forget...
Tomorrow is your wedding day.
It's you, the caller, and the listener...
On you.
...that make the audience.
Yep, that make this show...
Well, it's been fun, kid-a-roonies,
and we're gonna be back with more cartoon fun next week.
So tune in around this time...
Yippee!
...and listen to the puzzling evidence show.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And of course, the giant squid-a-roonie.
Tell your friends.
So tell Froggy to plunk his magic twanger
and keep the giant squid-a-roonie at bay.
He'll be back.
For your tunes.
Get along, little doggie.
And marry me.
Yip!
Chug, chug, chug.
Transfer of files.
Please, uh...
And read, chug.
Data, and chug, chug, chug.
Chug, chug, chug.
Chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug, chug.
暴
...