🎵
Genuinely beautiful.
Giant.
Perfect.
Cool.
Special.
Cheered.
Elaborate.
Easy.
Ultimate.
Best.
Natural.
Growing.
Special.
Nice.
Quicker.
And much more.
Ah, yes, dear friends, it is rerun time again, but you'll be glad to know that we're not
going to just do the same old three Christmas hour of slack show reruns in a row.
No, I'm going to compress it all into just this one intensive total rerun show, except
that actually it's not.
The whole first half will be largely peppered with a new Christmas sickness for the holidays
and holy days and the hole-in-head days, as it is for some people.
Actually, I have to work double time because it's the season of salad.
Selling.
Yes.
Oh, you wouldn't believe what the elves have done over at the subgenius catalogs.
But anyway, happy whatever you do.
Yes, this music in the background is somebody named Kenny Wayne Shepard.
Yeah, there's an album called Merry Axmus and Guitar Axmus.
It's cool, man.
Cool.
And praise Bob and the whole world.
Oh.
I'd like to find the guy who done me wrong and stuck my butt up on this Christmas.
Borg participated in a meeting with Billy Gee and Sepdin Juhlman who had died from gastric
They said he couldn't match up to a kid like me when Berger was 18.
He watery profiles out to me, selfish Brookshot Allen and his brother Freddy Skinner.
He's a Aberdeen insider.
Did you know him?
He was one of our favorites.
He was a müsste Shawn Kardel.
And left me stranded on this Christmas tree
When this angel heard
A dreadful fear went right into my heart
Those pine tree needles sting me
Ram-a-jam-a, ram-a-jam-a, ram-a-ding-dong
You'll never know how much that smarts
So who put the stump in my romp-a-bomp-a-bomp
Who took and jammed it in my ram-a-lam-a-ding-dong
Who stood the wood where I boop-sheep-boop-sheep-boop
Who put the stick up my hip-a-dip-a-dip
Who took that bush and crammed it in my tush
He made this angel beg for mercy, please
Too tight, too tight
And I'm gonna say to you
It's already 9 p.m.
Don't go looking out in the backyard to dog-aid him
Don't go walking down to the bar
Cause old Frankie died last night in the backyard
I mean, I'm gonna park my store and look at the credits
And in the right
Oh, can I borrow the brain cells tonight?
Yeah, he brought back the chainsaw, yeah
And I ain't gonna let you use the brain cells
Till I get to bed
I have chainsaw fixed and back in my arm the way it was Tuesday
Now you boys be good and I'll give you some of this here
Apple mango pie
You ain't no good of a child
That dog's running off with them brain cells
Can you do something about that, boy?
I'm gonna have to, I'm gonna have to
It could be his head wasn't screwed on just right
No!
I've got it all now
Gotta fix it
I knew the oldie would figure it out
You're него
The 19th century
What!
Ah- gonna do this
Yeah, without these
We tried
Dave's dressed like Santa Claus.
He's like a cowboy Santa.
How jolly.
Oh, Jazz is giving, gives Dave the show pills.
What am I going to do about laundromat in this suit though?
I need the show bath.
The show de-lousing.
Oh, Dave doesn't even have headphones yet.
That's enough of that.
Oh, he's got headphones.
I also have the part of my pancreas that I'd like to show you now.
It's been increased in size to...
Oh, your pancreas looks lovely, Dave.
Look, it's swelling.
I actually have the capability of a man of 190 IQ's brain.
I'll put more pills out for everybody.
Oh, those pills.
They make my mouth feel like it's on fire.
And my brain feel like it's a puddle of liquefied...
I'm shocked by the...
The red pills are really good.
I like to take the red one and the blue one at the same time.
That way you go in and out.
The warp mix is easy.
It's so high, you can't go over it.
Angels we have heard on high
Singing about mountains high
And those mountains in reply
Saying we wish we had some too
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Wario in excelsis Deo
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh Wario in excelsis Deo
Barbie Dolls
Women rape and memorialize their lives by role-playing with Barbie
We have devised a marketing scheme for children's toys.
It will empower the students.
Yes, sir.
You will use your church as a vehicle to bring these toys before the power.
It will be called Bobber for Kids.
But how?
How will the battle of good against evil be represented in your marketing schemes, human?
Good has a lot of muscle.
Good.
Good!
The primitive Earth societies should accept this value judgment.
Good will have great physical attributes according to human desires, sexual desires,
latent,
and children brought out through the vehicle of this so-called Farmer-Columbia-Split Church.
Batteries not included.
She's new from Kenner.
Where illusion is the ultimate weapon.
We must buy our toys!
Yes.
The old subgenius toy marketing scheme recorded there at Dockstock.
In 1984, Amin Palmer Veedees.
Angels We Have Heard on High.
It was by the Philistines.
The collage called All the Money You've Got is from the great Obtuse Christmas collage album,
which you can get for free.
Get this.
Check out this website.
Obtuse.iuma.com
That's Obtuse.
Excuse me.
My yes and next up, The Real Story of Christmas by Michael Shelley.
Once upon a time, there was the baby Jesus.
And he had two eyes made out of coal.
And he was stuck up a partridge in a pear tree.
And he wanted his two front teeth.
And he got McDonald's.
And he got McDonald's gift certificates.
And he had a dog named Santa's little helper.
And he took all the presents from Whoville.
And his friend Yukon Cornelius came with the three wise guys.
And he wanted to play the drums and be the little drummer boy.
But he couldn't.
He wanted 10s and 20s.
10s and 20s.
And he got McDonald's gift certificates.
And he wanted his three wise guys.
And he got Zuzu's pedals.
And that's the real story of Christmas.
The Real Story of Christmas
Take the halls and vines of holly
It's yet a season to be jolly
Don't we know how to get a barrel
Only in Chimney, I care
La la la la la la la la la
So separate, so separate, so separate
You from Tunga
Now you are in my evil clutches, Bob
I'll use this MTV bombardment to turn you normal
Shut up, pink boy!
No way, I'll never sell out to the conspiracy
Taste a little of my rocket pipe, alien fool
Bob Dobbs comes with rocket pipe, head launcher, jayner device, all I got is a fighting Jesus and other action figures sold separately
Some assembly required, batteries not included, this toy falls apart in three days
He-Bob and the bastards of the universe
Too much is always better than not enough
So Bob Dobbs and I can douse so separately
Gorgeous secrets can blow from head to toe
Like Connie
Can douse so separately
He-Bob and the bastards of the universe will be back after this message
Santa Claus
Well, Tommy knew exactly what he wanted for Christmas
He wanted an electric train
He had the whole thing in his mind, even to the table where it was going to set it up
He had a picture of the whole thing, and he would dream so far that the whole thing would come to life right before his eyes
He-Bob and the bastards of the universe
God!
And what he started wishing for was a pretty fancy looking train set with locomotives and great cars
hacks, gets through the walls
In the station and the gateways
Federides, basement
The mortar tower and all kinds of nice equipment and accessories
So grand that you might think Tommy was waiting for something that just didn't exist
Rotom Heart
Every day in the-
Let raven
The code have of spades
But Tommy knew what he was wishing for.
It is turnover.
The time of the year when all things sell.
The end of the year sale.
Oh, yeah.
So come and get it, everyone, and just buy our products.
Now, are we, is Christmas, I'm a little confused about what Christmas is all about.
Are we celebrating the birth of Santa Claus or his death when they nailed him?
Well, that's the ancient, ancient subgenie.
But the present subgenie tried to make sure that we have our inventories cleared by now and sell everything to the pigs.
Oh, yes.
Once a pagan holiday and now a shopping season.
And it was something else in between there.
Before it was, after it was a pagan holiday and before it was a shopping season.
It wasn't.
It wasn't something else.
But I think they started a war over it.
Yeah.
There you go.
A two-woman car.
All that noise and go.
When you touch the heart.
Oh, oh, oh, yeah.
There you go.
A two-woman car.
You're a sinner's car.
All that noise and go.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, yeah.
But it was fun.
It was fun.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, yeah.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
My hub is coming back.
Friends, try to imagine
somewhere in the snowy north
the Santibob trudging mindlessly
through the Himalayan snows
driven by strange forces
to complete his nameless errand
and he may show up at your house, my friend,
if you've been a bad subgenius
or a halfway subgenius
or if we keep getting tangled up
in these other shows
and having strange microphones.
How did that paternity suit ever turn out
between Dobbs and Santa?
And who?
His dad.
Santa dog.
I don't know.
I don't think it was...
Yes, but St. Nicholas, this is fact,
St. Nicholas,
punched another bishop in the nose
and bloodied his nose.
Really?
The historical St. Nicholas?
Over the trinity of God.
The original St. Nicholas in Turkey?
Who the hell is God?
Ask Dobbs one day.
That's the question.
That's the question we should be asking.
Suddenly, a lightning bolt struck from nowhere
on that bright, sunny day.
Bob did a backflip
and from that day on,
he too was a believer.
And from the snowdrift truck,
a little child bearing flowers emerged.
And Chip, Chip, what else is on the table?
Each one a dirty flower.
It's the St. Nicholas.
Sip, sicken.
The historical Santa Claus
is originally lived,
as the caller knows,
as a bishop in...
Was it Constantinople?
Yeah, like one of those...
It was an ancient Byzantium.
Yeah, Asia Minor in general.
Yes, he was...
And he was known for
sneaking into the rooms of young women
and leaving gifts.
Light-sized lumps of coal
complete with a fake beard
and a CIA Wall Street credit card.
A saint he was,
the girl said.
He was the one who protected the CIA.
That's good.
You got it, brother.
He snuck into people's houses
through the chimney.
You got it, brother.
He knew when they were sleeping.
He knew when they were awake.
You got it, brother.
But like the CIA,
he was protecting them.
He knew that St. Nick
was a creeping, stinking spy.
What?
He knows when you've been sleeping.
He knows what you've been eating.
Hey, man, my kids still believe
in St. Nicholas.
And who keeps that belief alive
in their fevered, sick little brain?
Madison Avenue, of course.
No, the surveillance community
under your direction.
And the Reynolds Tobacco Company.
Miller Bear.
If you're bad, he punishes you.
If you're good, he rewards you.
He's probably the closest thing
to Jesus walking the earth.
He's the closest thing
to Big Brother there is.
He rewards those who knows
when they are smiling
when they're awake.
I think, really,
if you want to make a deal,
you have to do it with, you know...
Could Dr. Claus, in fact,
be the wandering, quote,
milkman rumored
to be the most dangerous man in the world?
Could he be the one
who would have fathered
our savior, J.R. Bob Dobbs?
Well, we find it a very likely possibility
from the falsified documents
we have here.
And also the fluffy beard
that often grew on Bob's feet.
You better watch out.
You better not...
You better not tell anyone.
St. Nicholas is coming to town.
Do you think I'm psycho, Mama?
I seen my ex last night.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Mama?
We all saw X-Mas last night.
At a dance at Miller's.
A vision of Christmas
that was dancing in Stank's head.
It would not lay for them
little sugar plums and berries
dropping toxic things.
Those little sugar plums
are the secret that plums need.
The poison in the plums.
But they're real plums.
Don't say that.
It's biological agents
who only take 15%.
You...
It came to the past
in boxes or bags.
And now...
It's a great day, all right.
A salute to Mr. and Mrs. Iron.
Shop as usual.
And avoid panic buying.
That's two days old Christmas, a million things to do
Clean the house, put on tea, company is due
Where are my relatives, why haven't they showed up?
I bet they're at the airport, I forgot to pick them up
Christmas, almost here
Santa Claus is real
Who's the hitman?
Santa Claus.
He was a huge, beastly,
bulging man.
He was so real,
how come we didn't get squat last year?
Yes, the birth of the baby Satan
on July 4th.
And now you can have it all,
all pure 100% vinyl chloride CID.
The birth of our baby Satan
as told by various authors
and acquaintances.
And by eclectic scholars
from around the globular unit.
Including that announcer.
This announcement has not been
a perfunctory announcement,
but an announcement of the blessed
anointment and birthday of our Lord
Zinu.
One bright Christmas morning.
Was born in a cradle.
You can imagine the rave Jesus.
To a rich man's family.
The rave Jesus.
Oh, I know the rave Jesus.
I farked with the rave Jesus.
Have yourself a merry little Christmas.
Let yourself have.
From now on
our troubles will be
out of sight
Have yourself
a merry little
song
From now on
we're miles
away
Once a day
as in olden
day
happy golden
be miles
away
Let your heart
be out of sight
Out of sight
From mutated Christmas
friends
Have yourself a merry little
Christmas by
No-L
Before that some year old ESO
and Michael Shelley did that
real story of Christmas
from the Tarkin
Records All-Star Holiday
extravaganza.
I'm playing a lot from that.
So check out
www.triage.com
For that one also
the Tarkin Records
is also on
www.triage.com
And now
The Jethro's
Go!
Zoggo fun!
Just kidding!
Bet affections are
program room
No way kids
I can't see
I'm in a wreck
You just show me
I am in an accident
I brought my aunt
Mine and yours
on a horse
I am still dead
I laugh about
The weird bobs and I'm a,
those who have the psychosis that convinces them that they are the Santa Bob or,
or,
or that they're Santa Bob by night and they go shuffling through the snow on their nameless,
hideous errands.
The grin of Bob and the spirit of Santa Claus and the pipe of the Lord stuck on their face.
They stopped using the locks through their,
of their doors and they just kind of float into the keyhole.
Oh,
friends,
it's tough.
And you know,
you just,
just going to church ain't enough.
You got to send your money to the Santa,
Santa Bob.
As a matter of fact,
I,
the people across the street from me told their kids that,
that Santa Claus bills them for the toys he brings.
Can you believe that?
They,
they asked,
the kids were asking if their parents,
if maybe Santa Claus will bring us two He-Man erector sets.
And the mom said,
no,
he won't because he bills us.
We can't afford that.
Santa Claus sends us a bill after Christmas.
Yeah,
but at least he totes the note.
They say that it's,
that's Luca.
He is Santa.
It's...
I can't even understand that.
Hi,
Don't follow me around.
It's my sub,
my sub.
Oh,
my sooner,
Oh boy.
I have no kids.
That's fair to give our kids a rub-a-bum-bum.
Rub-a-bum-bum.
And amazing.
Amazing.
More from Corporal Blossom.
I am really impressed by their editing work.
And that's on...
Corporal Blossom and the Mutated Christmas is on the Illegal Art label.
That's www.detritus.net
slash illegal art.
www.detritus.net slash illegal art.
And now, more Jethro's.
Jethro's.
Now you're blaming Jesus.
You're blaming our Lord.
I sort of understand, because...
I understood the way any old fool would understand.
There was no Jesus.
No flatulent old woman waving her...
pennies on the hill. It's not that
you don't want to.
It's that they won't let you.
No, they're just a crime
in the wilderness. They're ashamed.
In the hot pursuit of wolves
everywhere in the background. I'm ashamed
of them.
It's cold.
I'm leaving
that city life behind
and radio people are crazy.
I can't get my
noodle back in the pan, Jan.
Come on, cowboy.
I was trying to hear a tune against this here tree
and it started whispering to me, man.
You've been drinking.
There's the face of Madonna right up there.
There's the face of Virgin Mary. I swear to God, look at it.
Isn't it?
What?
It's your Christmas witch coming true.
A Christmas witch?
I'll be whole.
She's beautiful.
Her breasts are so cold.
I know she must be a true witch.
I guess you could call her that
if that's what she's talking about.
She's spread by hovering
Christmas ornaments.
It's like a radar device.
What?
Yo.
Yo?
It's her.
What up?
Nothing.
What's up?
What a deep voice.
First Christmas witch.
Ha ha ha.
Well, if it weren't where I'm now,
database could never call a bowls and be줄.
It has the power to abnormalize a brain.
Henry serves before others.
G различ.
That?
Thank you.
My credit card makes me high.
My, oh my, until I die, die, die.
Swing, swing, swing.
Who wants the diamond ring?
Bye, bye, bye.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hail Mother Mary,
your blessed lady.
I fell in love with your son.
Hail Mother Mary,
turn me on and on and on.
thank God for you and your son.
Right on, right on,
right on.
Right on, right on.
I am yours truly,
Rudy Ray Moore,
bold and still beautiful.
Baby, I want to talk to you for this Christmas
because Christmas holds a lot of memories for me.
Baby, I've had a lot of hard times at Christmas time.
I can remember me and my brother
when I was about six years old.
We hung our stockings up over the mantelpiece
and the health department made us take them down.
I remember my father well, you know.
My father used to wake up every morning with a headache.
He used to have,
you know what caused it then?
He used to put a stocking cap on his head
and put a knock light in front of it.
Daddy wake up with that stomping headache
and he said,
the kids are saying my head's hurting so bad.
He said, I don't know what Santa's going to get y'all for Christmas
but he's going to bring you something.
So Daddy took that old rifle and went outside
and shot up in the air
and come back inside
and told us the biggest lie ever heard.
Said, kid, Santa just committed suicide.
And whose birth do we celebrate with this new century?
Who was nailed on that great manger cradle
but Satan Claus?
Whose father, Paul Bunyan
and whose mother, Big Sister
created the conspiracy?
Before there were malls,
there was no such thing as Christmas.
Yes, there was a down-home
Norman Rockwell style
it's a wonderful life type of Christmas.
It was a kite-flying Coca-Cola drinking Christmas,
not a crack-smoking, rubber-snapping Christmas.
When your little brother
fell through a hole in the ice
and slid,
he fell through a hole in the ice
and you went and saved him.
You didn't laugh at him
and huff some more glue.
It was a wonderful life back then.
But today Christmas has lost its meaning.
Scott, you made your choice.
When you rejected my word, you reject.
You rejected me.
And to your eternal soul,
you have found that only could you afford
to give to God that which was his.
But you could not afford to do otherwise.
The Senate still stands.
Frosty, the snowman
in the outer darkness
where there is wailing and gnashing of teeth.
Sir, please give me just one more chance, sir.
I don't want to go to hell, sir.
Sir, no, no.
I don't want to go to hell.
No!
As alive as he could be.
And the children say
he could laugh and play just the same.
You and me.
The tail-bearer will be at the judgment.
But if you speaks to me now,
I will make your head tremble.
You may say.
But you will never do yourself and me laundry.
You will be fine.
You will manage.
Why, I don't know.
I only cry when death comes.
Strange lights appear in the skies all over the world.
The wife of a carpenter experiences virgin birth,
and a baby is born with a head that glows like a fluorescent lamp.
Dare I ask it? Yes.
Was the infant Jesus neither man nor God,
but merely one of the countless aliens that visit the earth each and every day?
The answer? Yes, definitely.
Take that and shove it up the tube, mark certainty,
in the fuzzy place called the Twilight Zone.
Merry Christmas to all! Now you're all gonna die!
The night Santa went crazy
The night Saint Nick went insane
Realized he'd been getting the wrong deal
Something finally must have snapped in his brain
Well the workshop is gone now, he decided to bomb it
Everywhere you'll find pieces of Cupid and Comet
And he tied up his helpers, and he held the elves hostage
And he ground up poor Rudolph into reindeer sausage
He got dancer and prancer with an old German Luger
And he slashed up Dasher just like Freddy Krueger
And he picked up a flamethrower and a barbecue blitzer
And he took a flamethrower and a barbecue blitzer
And he took a big bite and said it tastes just like chicken
The night Santa went crazy
The night Kris Krankle went nuts
Now you can hardly walk around the North Pole
Without stepping in reindeer guts
There's a National Guard and the FBI
There's a van from the Eyewitness News
And the National Guard and the FBI
And helicopters circling round in the sky
And the bullets are flying
The bodyguards rising
And everyone's dying to know
Who's Santa why?
My, my, my, my, my, my
You used to be such a jolly guy
He knows when you're sleeping
He knows when you're awake
He knows when you're feeling bad or good
So be good for goodness sake
You better watch out
You better not cry
You better not pout
I'm telling you why
Santa Claus is coming to town
Have yourself an advanced Dogmatic Christmas song thing called Santa is Coming by F. Gillespie and F. J. Coot.
ElectricElf at loop.com can tell you more about that but now
Who gave the Lord the Claptrap?
Who made him talk in funny riddles so that we cannot understand?
Who made him so succinct and blind that he is actually blind my one and only?
Yeah, we're now officially in the Jesus season.
The time of the Lord, of the fact and of the craft.
How many before you reach your limit?
Jesuses?
Yeah, how many can you bag?
How many messiahs can you bag?
If you're doing it in season, if you're doing it out of season, you need a special permit.
Oh, you never do that.
And you can only take one.
You never bag the Lord in C. You bag the Lord in B-flat so you get that kind of rough sound.
But when they're in season, it's every God for himself.
This is the season for the fighting Jesus.
Obviously.
We are between a rock and a hard place.
Did you know the Lord walked through Chaldea in the old age and he got a very, very hard foot?
And he got elphantiasis of the rectum.
You know, it's not something well known by many Christian scholars.
Messy, messy, messy disease.
But I think the phrase in Hebrew was
Well, I like the story.
I kind of like those stories where the Lord dies and...
and then comes here to America and settles, you know, tames the West.
I like when he moves into a trailer park and...
I like the cowboy job with his dog.
Jesus fought for the Confederate army.
The ranger. I like the...
The Texas ranger. Jesus, Texas ranger.
Johnny Ripple was a Jesus.
I could see Jesus for the Navajo police, for maybe the Hopi police force.
Billy Jack was the Indian Jesus.
Man.
The white brother who came to instruct the Indians how to be liberal.
Billy Jack. What about...
Well, what about old peacemaker, the...
the Jesus of the Iroquois who was actually Huron?
A Huron.
You didn't know that, did you?
I got you!
Thin Ron.
Jesus.
Elron.
I got a Jesus like no other Jesus you've ever seen.
Oh, it tastes like butter.
A new Jesus. A different Jesus.
It tastes like a few chocolate pie children.
A few crappies.
A pipe-smoking Jesus.
Hey.
Dave, you know where it is.
Go kick that window open.
I already kicked it. I'll kick it again.
You know.
Kick it good this time.
We don't mean nothing by this Jesus and God.
We hope that...
We thank you for all the nice things that you've done for us this Thanksgiving.
Clap it.
We appreciate all that.
And we're just trying to insult your fan club.
That's all.
That's why we do this blasphemous stuff.
But we knew that you knew that because you're in all things and everything, right, Jesus?
Right.
I could hear him say that.
Praise God and Bob.
And Jesus.
Next topic.
And Connie.
And Carly.
And The Devil.
And the atheists.
And The Atheists.
The simple consulted Jesus.
I show spices.
The devil and the atheist.
And a theist.
And science.
And the atheist.
That's the life of Bryan isn't it?
And Greek mythology.
And Norse mythology.
Listen to the sounds of Hell.
Jingle, jungle, jingle.
We're on a sleigh ride to heck.
Santa and his reindeer are really wicked.
Rap and rap and pana.
We're gonna break our necks, got a rocket in my pocket on a sleigh ride to heck.
Sleigh ride to heck.
The elves are full of cheer, the kids are tucked in bed.
Santa ain't coming, we're on a sleigh ride to heck.
Their dreams are filled with toys, but they're out of luck.
Cause Satan's taking Santa on a sleigh ride to fuck.
Sleigh ride to heck.
The greatest scary Christmas song ever, friends, from his new album, Don't Trust Whitey, James Kochalka, Superstar.
You know, see, a subgenius has so much faith that he not only can accept somebody making fun of Bob, stomping on a picture of Bob, he'll do it himself.
He has so much trust and faith in Bob.
Bob is such a good friend that he can insult Bob.
Now, we subgeni, I hate to get on my soapbox in the middle of a bunch of entertaining tapes, but we subgeni may be bad, but our way of bad is holy.
Is holy compared to the evil.
Is holy compared to the evil of so, not all, by any means, but so many American fundamentalists, charismatics, evangelicals, etc., in general, of course, they and their corresponding types in Iran, Russia, Libya, South Africa, etc., if you ask me, are actually the ace up the devil's sleeve.
Wolves in sheep's clothing, friends, just like Jesus warned about.
We're, Jesus and Bob, like we say, are old drinking buddies.
Got nothing against Jesus.
It's just his fan club.
And now, we aren't saying that Bob is the ace up God's sleeve.
He's more like the smear on God's handkerchief, just like you or me.
But the uptight rival cults, they don't think God has a handkerchief.
Uh-uh, no, because God's perfect.
He doesn't even sneeze.
We're made in his image, except that we have all these nasty parts attached to us, and we have to go in the secret room, the bathroom, to do awful things.
But God, oh, he's clean and pure, according to them.
Oh, and he's male.
But he doesn't excrete juices and sweat and smelly stuff out of him like we do, because we sin.
Oh, yeah, we all sin.
We're bad.
We're worthless.
We're no good to God unless we sign a contract with his agent.
We interrupt this program for a special promotional announcement.
We turn.
E-Bob and the bastards of the universe will be back after this message.
Thank you.
I'm dreaming about the każدي GaS command and everyone can convite.
Make your days a living.
Shh!
and short.
And may all
your
dogs spend
you right.
By
Fernandan and Nellie Moore.
Oh, holy
night, the stars are
brightly shining.
It is the night
of our dear Savior's birth.
Long lay,
long lay the world
in terror and
fighting.
The pit and the stone
on its worth.
A thrill of hope,
the weary world rejoices
beyond our grace.
A new and glorious
dawn. Fall
on your knees.
Oh, hear
the angel voices.
Oh, night
divine.
when Christ was
born. Oh,
night. Oh,
night
divine.
Have yourselves
a
groovy little solstice.
Mithras won
his fight.
Oh, ho, ho.
Come on, come on.
It's he-bomb. Hey, kids, you can help
the mighty subgenus rice overthrow
the evil normals with new Bob-Dob's
action figure with rock and pie.
What I wouldn't do from Bob-Dob.
Get no more chocolatey pebbles from you, no?
Ooh.
I'm a chocolate space cadet.
Life support system down to zero cocoa.
Feeling free.
I need to have some of my new cocoa pebbles.
Now so trumpety.
Mmm, smells cocoa.
What is this?
This cocoa lipid.
Blue.
Hello, friends.
What do you think? Is it the
nativity of Santa Claus that we're
trying to celebrate here?
Or is it the
horrible death of the Santa?
Santa Bob, the Santai Bob,
as he's been referred to in some early
prescriptures.
We're getting so separate.
The Jethro's, friends.
You need to know where to write to the Jethro's.
They're at, um,
they did that Wreck the Halls and so many
other versions we've been playing.
The Jethro's are at
and a half
Miller Avenue.
That's 212 and a half Miller
Avenue, Portsmouth,
New Hampshire.
Portsmouth, N-H
O-3
8-0-1
Santa Claus is Coming to Town
was by
Corporal Blossom.
Information on that
Mutant Christmas is available
from www.triagemusic.com
or
www.detritus.net
I'm Rev. Ivan Stang, friends.
You can reach me, send me tapes or whatnot
at Post Office Box
Cleveland Heights, Ohio
And friends, as always, the Hour of Slack is brought to you
by the Church of the Subgenius
www.subgenius.com
It's all Christmas-y right now.
Green bob in the window and Christmas-y lights.
Is there a light out there?
Is DJA out there?
And devilish artwork that's Christmas-y.
No, that's something just left for DJA.
It's all Christmas-y.
It's all wrapped up in
perfumed, ribbon-wrapped
present.
Under the tree.
Open the door all the way so we can see if he comes in.
And those sugar plums.
Something's up the chimney hole in Satan's, isn't it?
Yeah.
Santa.
I mean, otherwise.
Gosh.
I guess we have to wait till Santa comes, Dave.
Oh, beloved Santa.
I have wanted to put your bag down for a minute.
It's always so ready to let him be.
Santa.
For so long.
Hi, Bob and Mary Xmas!
For so long, I've been having those eating dare this.
You're gonna make a mistake over there.
You're gonna make a mistake all around this place.
I don't understand why you came back here like that, Mike.
Lone cow Dave, don't you know what they're doing to yourself?
Don't despair just because it's Christmas
Children there are so gay at Christmas
All the children on the street
Hope they get something good to eat
But for me it's not so great
Fuck Christmas!
What a night!
Right before Christmas and all through the house
Not a creature was stirring, not even a mouse
The stockings were hung by the tree
Merry fucking Christmas
SHOOT YOU!
Thank you.