Yes.
Bred to be predators, but bred also to be controlled.
You see, my cast concentrated on expanding our cerebral abilities.
You control their thoughts?
Not just theirs.
The Heloi.
So it's not enough that you hunt them down like animals?
That's their role here.
To be your food?
Yes.
And for those who are suitable to be breeding vessels for our other colonies.
You see, I am just one of many.
For the first time, I realized what the meat I had seen below might be.
What else could it be?
Brightening as the thought may be,
it could happen.
The sun will become dark, the moon blood red,
the stars of the heavens will fall,
there'll be two major earthquakes that are going to be coming,
the islands and the mountains are shaken out of their sockets,
and the second one, no island, no mountain was found in the face of the earth.
It's all coming.
Yes, I'm ready now.
Then close your eyes,
and tap your heels together,
three times.
And think to yourself,
there's no place like...
Bob!
Round, round the slack foam,
Bob the Bob,
down in the saucer row.
Round, round the slack foam,
Bob the Bob,
down in the saucer row.
And in that air there was a ship,
a rare ship,
an exe-ship,
with a ship in the air,
and the air through the smoke,
and the smoke from the prop,
and the prop and the pipe,
and the pipe and the grid,
and the grid and the bottom,
bob down in the saucer row.
Round, round the slack foam,
Bob the Bob,
down in the saucer row.
Round, round the slack foam,
Bob the Bob,
down in the saucer row.
And in that ship there was a Bob,
a rare Bob,
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
With a Bob and a ship,
and a ship in the air,
and the air through the smoke,
and the smoke from the prop,
and the prop,
and the pipe,
and the pipe and the grid,
and the grid and the Bob,
Bob down in the saucer row!
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Bob down in the saucers, oh.
That was Pope Fred, some ancient X-Day drill.
A lively tune.
And I'll...
Are we supposed to be hearing through these headphones?
Yeah.
He likes to turn the blade down so you can barely hear.
I just wanted to make sure.
You can't hear very loud through them.
I can hear you real well, though.
Oh, we can hear each other.
I can hear...
Man, I can hear me great.
That's your favorite sound, isn't it?
Man, it's so great to hear me.
I'm so good sometimes.
Dr. Drummond is luxuriating in the sound of his own voice.
Oh, he's getting to you.
He just got him a baby bear hug.
I just got a bear hug.
A baby bear hug.
Okay.
So...
Everything will go...
Wow, found a giant frop thing.
Frop, frop, zippy frop, frop.
So...
So, recording?
Now, all recording devices are on go.
Oh, this one's not.
Oh, I have to do something with this.
And I hear the swells of the movie
Abominable Story.
Snowman, 1957.
Starring Forrest Tucker and Peter Cushing.
And so, with that, we begin
Subgenius Mind Control Experiment number 2203
for Friday, July 3rd, quote, 2015, unquote.
With the Hour of Slack Live,
followed by Ask Dr. Hal,
and then the first iteration of the Bull Dada auction
right here on our stage.
At Caffeina's.
So, bring your Bull Dada or your money or both.
Say, some of...
You two guys missed some great jamming last night.
Yeah, I did.
There was some seriously...
Actually, some really good music being played here,
which we will cut to at some point in some show.
Yeah.
It actually happened.
I got in late last night.
Well, at one point,
all of the musicians on the stage,
knew what they were doing,
which is unusual in a...
Why, though?
Why?
Well, we'll fix that later tonight.
It's a statistical phenomenon.
When you put a bunch of chimpanzees and bonobos
all together with musical instruments,
eventually they will play...
You hear Mozart.
Yes, exactly.
Yeah, but you may have a long wait before you hear...
It might take 200 to 300 million years.
For hour upon hour,
until the music gels on the stage.
It might...
You might actually have to wait
for the chimpanzee to evolve into Mozart.
Well, fortunately, we don't need to worry about that
because we have Chaosmic Kitty tonight
who's going to join the musicians
and others who are equally musically accomplished.
Yeah, we're going to have doctors for Wotan,
but you know what?
I'm really distracted.
I know I'm supposed to be on the radio now,
but I'm so distracted
because I can't find my lighter.
Oh, Dr. Drummond here.
Oh, no.
I bet I have a lighter somewhere.
I hope.
Well...
No.
By the way,
the ones that have Monster High stickers are mine.
Uh-huh.
Those are yours?
Okay.
Well, I've got some.
And the ones that have laughing squid sigils on them are mine.
Well, I've got a couple that are about this long,
so the really long ones,
like this long...
I use that one to light my stove at home.
Why did you just take my lighter?
Because I left it at my domicile.
Hmm.
By the end of today,
there'll be 40 lighters in his pocket.
So if you need a light, ask Philo.
Yeah, tonight I'll be opening up...
Philo's Lighter Emporium down the road there,
so please come by.
Yes, light up and live with Dr. Drummond.
We're going to have a close-out special tonight.
We haven't even opened yet.
We're already thinking about closing out.
Everything must go.
Bargain basement rock bottom prices.
So you're eating frop cookies, huh?
Shh!
You're not supposed to frop on the radio.
This is simply going to...
This is an herb.
It's not a drug.
Render staying inaudible.
I don't know about the cheeks.
But look at me.
You're drinking on the radio.
You're drinking beer.
I'm a little hungover.
I have to stay up later than anybody
because I have to copy the audio files.
That is sad.
And it takes a long time
because they're long files.
I used to have to do that.
And they're horrible sounding.
I did that for a while.
The more horrible...
There's Leon and Reverend Finord.
That's back when I was doing this audio, Philo.
I remembered this time.
Yeah.
It's good to remember.
Remember sometimes.
Remember.
Some of the good things.
Usually just before X-Day,
I look at all the pictures from the previous X-Day
and the sign-in sheets
so I won't embarrass myself as badly.
Just like a teacher.
I've still managed to embarrass myself a few times.
On the first day of school.
Fight C. Todd told me every X-Day
for five X-Days what his name meant.
And he forgot.
Did you forget it?
Each time I had...
Well, that's the sad thing.
I mean, every X-Day I'd go,
what is it?
What's your name?
I said, fuck them if they can't take a joke, Stang.
I told you every year for the last five years.
So it's not you, friends.
It's me.
Wow.
Also, I'm only pretending to have the sense of hearing.
I'm just guessing what everybody says.
But then, of course, there's your inner hearing.
I just thought it was a very cleverly made-up name.
I wondered what happened.
Yeah, Fight C. Todd.
Right.
The initials of...
Fuck them if they can't take a joke.
Exactly.
I just have to use that kind of language
just to say the only law in the church.
Yeah.
We could have said something else.
We talked about that a lot, remember?
About what we should use if we don't want to say fuck them.
You know, we wanted to say, like...
We had some other alternatives.
The classic one, if thou canst not take a joke.
If they cannot take a joke, let them mount up upon themselves.
Yeah.
That was the Irish version.
Somebody said.
But it's too late now.
Too late.
I'm the one who has to...
We mounted upon ourselves.
You know, there's fewer and fewer broadcast stations
that I have to do the censoring for.
Which is sort of sad.
Because they used to pay money.
Yeah.
Well, do we have to censor...
The old days, when they paid money for the show.
But we're beyond all that now.
The free speech radio.
So we always have to censor.
We have to think silly things like money.
Yes.
Who needs it?
Food.
Hey, Dr. Powell, you having some of that one old screaming chicken down there?
Which chicken?
What?
The screaming chicken I see on the end of the wild turkey.
Oh.
Do you want some?
Is it iced tea?
Is it really iced tea?
I want a beer.
It is not.
Oh, no.
I don't want it.
No one's been putting pineapple juice in my pineapple juice.
I want it to look like booze, but actually be just iced tea.
That's for the movie version.
Like they do on the movies.
Right.
Except Lee Marvin.
Lee Marvin.
He said, if I'm going to pretend to be a drunk, I don't want to be in this movie.
I actually want to drink real booze.
It won him an Academy Award.
He's a man's actor.
And if you've ever seen that movie, Cat Baloo, he actually is stinking drunk.
Really?
Half of that movie.
Sure.
Even the horse.
When he plays the kid Chalene parts, he's...
Now, I read somewhere that Evelyn Anchors, or one of those actresses in those old monster
movies, really didn't like...
They had Fat chance.
Very weird.
They played this in those times...
We were upset though.
You know, Mary Jane, I think she was like..
She's like you know, you never wis good.
She's usually always a butler.
So...
They're just the wrong kids.
No!
Yeah, so you see, the tanner leaves are from the tea that was drunk on stage.
Yeah.
I've seen things on Facebook I never expected to see,
like a scan of Lon Chaney Jr.'s passport from 1959.
Well, I hope you enjoyed it as fulsomely as possible.
What do you do with that?
I like monster movies.
He was a big, strong oaf,
and so he could pick up the actress in the traditional monster crawl,
but some monsters were small, like Bela Lugosi was fairly small.
It was very hard for him to pick up Ellen Chandler or anybody else.
He was a junkie, you know.
Oh, let's not go through that again.
He took morphine because he had...
That was his medicine.
Yeah, it's his medicine.
We call it our medicine.
Yeah, right, it's his medicine.
Yeah, loosen up.
Let me do my medicine and then finish some people.
That Johnny Depp movie got it all wrong.
Interestingly enough...
Interestingly enough, Doug and I, I mean, Stang and I...
It's Doug.
...knew all about that group
because we followed their adventures in Famous Monsters of Filmland
long before Johnny Depp was...
What are you...
You're talking about Ed Wood.
Are you cutting me out of this exclusive club of you two guys
sitting right next to me?
Did you follow the stories of...
Sure, Famous Monsters of Filmland.
Vampyra and all these characters.
So you're on his bad side.
Did I fall off?
The bench, I'll say.
You're on the deaf side.
Who else is here?
I'm on the deaf side.
So, Lugosi, for example, didn't have little yapping, snapping dogs.
He had huge wolfhounds that followed him around.
And the movie got other details wrong, too.
That's Hollywood.
They always make the good guys look like the bad guys
and the bad guys look like the good guys.
They make the bad guys virile and strong
and the good guys look like wimps
because it's been shown it's better box office.
That's that way.
Well, you know, it's much more fun to be a bad guy than a good guy.
Well, what I meant was they usually cast the aliens as monsters
and the humans are the good guys you're supposed to root for.
Nobody remembers the good guys.
They remember the crazy monsters, though.
Villains are more interesting than heroes.
Villains are the ones that make things happen.
The reason that there's a movie there at all is because of the villain.
And the villain eventually becomes the hero.
Humphrey Bogart started out as tough-talking gangsters
but graduated to being the hero because everybody liked him better.
And Godzilla, whose theme is in the background right now,
started out as a bad guy, you know,
just because he destroyed a few cities.
But by the end of the series,
he's routinely saving the Earth from worse monsters.
And, of course, the classic thing is the Yeti.
Yetis are...
Even the great Zukowski, who studied the Yeti more than anyone,
thought that the Yeti were the source of evil in the world
and that the humans were the pure, nice ones.
But you suggested to him that the opposite was the core.
Yes, I actually...
Well, in Book of the Subgenius, we explained all that.
But I got a chance to meet Zukowski at a sci-fi con
and I got to be treated like a kook by Zukowski.
By Zukowski.
I stood up and said,
Sir, we've read Behold the Proton and all of your works,
but we think that you have it backwards.
The Yetinsen are the force of good
and the humans are the communists and gangster thugs.
And he gave me the classic, polite kook brush-off.
He kind of looks at everybody else and raises his eyes
and kind of does this and goes,
Well, some people get funny ideas in their heads about my work.
Any other questions?
Oh, man.
Another offensive thing they do with aliens in the movies
is they make them cute and simple and little and lovable and uncomplicated.
I don't like his feet.
The undeveloped humans are more animal-like in comparison to the aliens
than the aliens are to the lesser advanced humans.
And that goes right down the line.
So where...
Where's the...
Aren't we supposed to have, like, some food and things up here?
What?
Oh, I guess we can't use food and electronics.
That'd be like committing a Michael Pepe.
Food and electronics?
Actually, this is if you...
Because we no longer are allowed to do anything fun
in any radio stations that are real,
we have to make up for lost time right here, right now.
But here at Tarzan's radio station, it's Liberty Hall all day.
Yes, let joy...
You know, I do.
Joy be unconfined.
Perfect freedom is here.
Like that radio station that Dr. Hal and I are on.
Yes, it has...
It's supposed to be free speech.
And it has cameras watching your every move
that even look like eyeballs bulging out of the walls
with whites and corneas and pupils.
We feel like we're in an NSA headquarters interrogation office.
They cover every angle of the inside and the outside.
Whenever you're speaking to the mic, this big bright light goes on
and, like, flashes into your ear.
Flashes into your eyes.
We have to go outside to pollute ourselves
and stand quivering under the dwarf maples.
We can't even...
You know, we're, like, out there freezing.
Yes, it used to be nice and comfortable,
but those are old times.
We never worry about rain, though.
Well, we don't have to worry about rain
and dry as a bone in California,
but here in the land of abundant water,
you guys don't know how good you've gotten it.
Yeah, we have real weather.
Splash your way to...
The first time we saw rain, we stopped the car
and we all got out and just danced.
It was like in Nevada.
Look, little bitty drops falling out of the sky.
He's not...
It was in Nevada, the driest state in the nation.
Yeah, but the moment you get away from California,
it starts to rain.
It doesn't rain in California,
but it's raining in green and verdant and lush in Nevada.
You know, the last time I drove through Death Valley...
I returned your light. It's on your desk.
It rained.
It only rains for a couple of years in Death Valley.
Things are different now.
The desert is the lush, verdant, green,
place people should go to and live
and drink all the water and everything.
Death Valley looked really strange full of water.
It was a lake.
The Badwater Basin, the lowest point in the world,
was...
It was a lake for 10 minutes.
Wow.
And then the lake was gone again.
But there were frogs mating everywhere.
Yes, that's the way of it.
Was this a flute?
Well, they had to hurry because they only got...
They had to hurry.
And then they were dead again, you know,
for another hundred years or whatever.
This flute's broken.
No, it's not.
You need to push the button on the side.
I was blowing as hard as I could.
And it just...
There we go.
The Colorado River Toad,
which I mentioned the other day,
estivates 60 feet underground
and then burrows during the monsoon season
toward the surface.
Oh, you didn't click.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Can you do the flute thing
that draws Frankenstein's monster?
Only Igor can play that flute.
I really wanted to learn how to play that little...
Man, what makes it taste like that?
That would cause the monster
to do his bidding for some reason.
Ghost of Frankenstein was the first monster movie I saw
and I immediately identified with Igor.
It begins with him...
He's a sad character.
Of course you sympathize with the poor hunchback guy.
They're bullying him.
They're ganging up on him.
He throws a few chunks of rock off the ramparts on him.
But then he goes down and wakes up his old friend,
the Frankenstein monster.
Who will only respond to him.
Yeah.
They pull him out of his sulfur bath.
Even though he used to be enemies.
Right.
And growing up,
I felt that that was my destiny,
to be like...
Igor.
Throwing rocks down on normals
and leading monsters around.
First, you would have to be...
At least you got to...
If you believe in your dream,
it will come true.
Igor was hanged,
but the execution didn't take.
He had a strange broken upper spine
and his head was canted at an odd angle.
Is that the future you envisage for yourself?
Yeah, I thought that was a cool look.
I think it was because they hung him.
Wasn't it because they hung him
and it didn't work?
Yeah, it didn't work.
Right.
Not so.
They hung him and said,
well, I guess he's not going to die,
so we better let him go.
Well, you can't execute him twice.
And he got the monster to get revenge for him.
That sounded pretty cool to me.
The monster went after anyone who ever mistreated him,
which was a long list.
Since he was the village...
Punchback.
Well, more like the...
It would be a good thing.
One that everybody punches.
You know, the punching bag.
To have a monster.
Judas Goat.
What am I thinking of?
What was that?
Yeah, I saw a TV...
A movie recently
where somebody was a hitman
and he was killing everybody
that the other guy knew.
They do that.
Not Brad Pitt, I hope.
No.
How much does that guy charge?
Who, Brad Pitt?
No, the hitman
that can kill everybody
that you want killed.
Just to get...
You know, just interesting.
I think...
In this case, he did it for free.
He was just like a hitman.
What's his phone number?
On vacation.
Not no country for old men.
He didn't have anything to do.
He was just, you know,
hanging out on vacation
and he's like...
Did he give you a business card?
Yeah, I'm bored.
I'm gonna go see if somebody
will just let me go off a few people,
you know, for fun.
Do that.
I saw that.
That was a movie.
Maybe it was
and maybe it wasn't.
It was a movie and not a memory?
Yes.
It may be a memory.
Did you wake up with blood
all over your hands
and panties on your head?
No, no.
I mean, no more often than normal.
No.
But I did
wash my hands a lot
for a while there.
You know, like,
it's like a guilty thing.
Like, why am I washing
my hands so much?
It's like...
Pontius Pilate.
The...
No, wait.
That's wrong.
What about Pontius?
That misunderstood
public official?
Poor guy.
He was a poor...
He was really put
between a rock and a hard place.
First of all,
he was assigned to Judea,
a horrible land
reeking of goats.
And secondly,
the office of procurator
of Judea
was a place
that they sent people
that they didn't like
who had no other place to go.
He was already
being punished.
Hey, we'll teach him a lesson.
This was like,
you know,
on the slow boat to China
or we're going to exile him
to Siberia.
Well, Basil Rathbone
played him sympathetically
in the motion picture
The Last Days of Pompeii.
Didn't Christopher Pace
play him in Plummer
or somebody play him
in some movie?
In Barabbas.
Who played him in Barabbas?
That Italian job.
Is this where you guys
learned your religion?
From Bible movies.
Where did you learn it?
Yeah, obviously.
We get the epics out.
You mean Victor Mature
wasn't in the Bible?
Yeah.
Demetrius and the Gladiator.
That's a good one.
Demetrius and the Gladiators
is one of those sequels
that's better than
the movie it follows,
The Robe.
Yeah, The Robe.
No holier than thou
Christians in that one
to speak of.
Just big brawny gladiators
slicing, chopping, and dicing.
They killed some Christians
in that one.
Oh, they killed plenty
and they had that wonderful guy
for Caligula.
Oh, yeah, that guy is great.
He's so good.
Horrible toad
of the Roman Emperor.
Those heavy-lidded eyes,
those pursed lips.
Where's your God now, Christian?
I'm thinking of a different
Caligula movie,
the one that starts...
There was me.
That is Caligula
and my three droogs.
But you remember
in the second movie,
he gets speared
right in the chest.
He did.
That's actually
an accurate historical...
That would have been
really fun.
He alienated everybody
and then he went on further
and he alienated
the Praetorian guard
who were supposed
to guard him.
And so they speared him
in the chest
and then they went
and dragged Claudius
out of a closet
when he was quivering
in terror
and made him emperor.
Were you there?
You know I was there.
I was there.
Because we just,
we make it up.
Kiwis Romanus Sum.
We make it up.
I wasn't in the early empire
but I was there
long enough to remember.
I wrote that stuff myself
when I was younger.
Yeah.
Philo was a senator
for four terms.
He was quaestor.
He made a senator
in the second term
of Lucius Mammilius.
You see references
to Philo.
That's right.
There was Philo,
also Philo of Alexandria
and Philo Antipater.
Philo of...
Archidias.
And then there was Philina.
Philo Do.
And then...
Oh ho.
Philomina.
Oh, when will we see
Philomina again?
She's a-coming.
She may be.
She's heading this way.
Your sister, Philomina.
Yeah.
Does she still have
that mustache?
Yeah, she's horrible.
Everyone in Philo's family
has a mustache.
No, Lily doesn't have
much of one.
Not yet.
She's only eight.
Not developed.
Not developed yet.
But in time,
she'll be able to sing
a barbershop quartet.
Well, the Yeti subgenius
should be proud
of its Yeti palate.
An enhanced
natural lip brow.
Well, we're not going
to entertain anyone
by talking about
our family sequence.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, if they're hairy enough,
if they're really
hairy and deformed,
it's kind of interesting.
Have you seen
Ed Strange's little girl?
Why?
She's got black,
thick black hair
coming up from her ass
collar.
She's got a crack
up her back.
She's about five years old.
Vital, feral,
luxuriant,
animal.
Maybe a future
lycanthrope.
Check her for the
unibrow and for the
equivalent of the
first and second digit.
I used to have a
girlfriend who had
a nice pelt on her
hair.
I hear scary
creeper, stalker,
killer guy music.
Yes.
Coincidence
or conspiracy?
Any scary
creeper, stalker,
killer guys around
besides us
that we ought to
know about?
And Bob?
We did that last year,
remember?
Yeah.
Yeah, the creepy
killer guy was last year
and we couldn't catch him
so he could be back
but there's been
no evidence yet.
It's been peaceful.
Well, you know,
there are plenty
of funny fake
But something could
happen any second.
Did that mean?
Including X-Day.
Well, that music
seems to imply
a certain ominous
overtone.
Right.
John Carpenter
composes music
as well as
directs the movie
but does he ever
get credit?
No.
Yeah, he does.
Yeah, in fact,
there's a couple
of albums of his.
And what about
Robert Rodriguez?
He does that too.
Yes, he's quite
multi-talented
and we mentioned
before, before you
got here, that
James Horner died
in a plane crash
so no more movie
scores from him.
He was good.
I liked his stuff.
sat in a corner?
No, that was
the guy,
Little Jack Horner.
And not
John Horner,
the paleontologist.
some people do
use Jack
as a diminutive
character.
in the form of
John,
which I never understood
because it has
the same number
of letters.
The name John
appears in
endless variations.
The name John
is the same as
Hans, Hansel,
Ivan,
Johannes,
Jack,
well,
Jacques.
It was obviously
from the French
Jacques,
which is,
you know,
that's how
Jack got in there.
And the name
Harry,
I might as well
point out,
is equally
versatile.
The same as
Henry and
Harold and
so forth,
linguistically.
And Heinrich.
Yes.
But the name
Bob has a
different and
more unusual
derivation.
More ominous.
Yes.
One we don't
talk about so
glibly.
If you don't
put the quotes
around that
name to
contain it,
it just
flies apart.
It flies apart.
I did over there
when they were
announcing the food
the other day
with Bob Burgers,
I quickly put the
quotes because of
Nimbus of
Ectoplasm was
starting to form
around the sign.
Well, the two
bees could disengage,
you know,
without the
quote.
That's true.
Without the
rondeur in the
middle pressuring
them outward,
they would stay
where they are.
But Bob wants
to expand and
engulf the world.
It's only we
who have kept
him so far
where he is.
balanced within
the quotes.
An omnivorous
entity,
eating more
and more.
The quotes are
the quote marks
around his name
are like a cage.
They do
contain you.
Just like you
draw your special
circle so as not
to be gobbled
by a demon.
Yeah, yeah.
We drove a lot
of people away
the first day
reading.
You can open
that up.
It's written
in like 1930.
And it's published
by the Eugenics
Publishing Company.
Everyone was
big on Eugenics
in those days.
Good Lord.
The Eugenics
Publishing Company.
No, here's a good
chapter.
The Perversions
of Love, of course,
is a great chapter.
Another good thing.
Masturbation is a
thing so natural
and spontaneous
that the man
was without a woman
and the woman
was without a man
that it tends
to spring up
at all times
and in all countries.
Stop it.
Stop it, Reverend
Stang.
I'm going to hurl.
When we were
reading from this,
people got so
turned on that
they had to go
run off and try
the things we were
reading about.
Sodomy, I think,
was the...
Big fans.
Sodomy?
What is this?
So-do-my?
It's from the
cities of the plains,
Sodom and Gomorrah.
So-do-my?
They were destroyed
by the fire from heaven
and Lot's wife
So-do-me?
That's what it means.
So-do-me.
Jammed into a
pillar of salt.
A big Lot's.
Boy, I wish I'd
known that
when I was younger.
You didn't mention
one other thing
about the quotes
around Bob, Stang,
which we should
throw in before
we abandon the subject
and that is
that's a good way
to tell who's
really a subgenius,
and who isn't.
Some jerk
who puts up
Bob without the quotes
is just playing
at being a subgenius.
Well, they're playing
with disaster.
Yes.
Either one of those
bees could go
skittering off.
Susie!
Susie the floozy's here.
You should show
everybody your
Bob tattoo
with the bees
on either cheek.
You know,
she's got to...
She's got a bee
on each cheek
of her life.
An unfortunate
encounter
with a beehive
creature.
Donald,
she's already there.
She...
Problem.
That's all right.
You have a bee
on each cheek
of your life.
Yeah.
You'll remember me
for the rest
of your life.
I'm going to cut
the two Z's.
One on each cheek.
You're not...
And God bless
your son.
Well,
leave it off the...
He does a pretty good
read, doesn't he?
He won't be able
to talk for another
hour after that, though.
I can't talk anyway.
Anyway,
cut your belly
open and make it
like that black stuff
you got in there.
Oh, yeah.
Remember when you
showed the black stuff
that one time?
It's gross.
It smelled bad, too.
Another term for that
is glaxel.
Yeah,
as we were saying,
you can tell
the dilettantes
by the way
they spell Bob's name.
They can't even
spell Bob.
Look,
the Holy Temple
of Mass Consumption
has entered the building.
Yes,
and look,
David Apocalypse
is headed this way
and St. Andrew
the Impaled
and more and more
they come.
What would it take
to get Circus Apocalypse
back together?
Two more bullets.
Hey, hey, hey,
yeah, yeah.
Whee, whee.
Whiskey, he said.
Whiskey and acid.
That's a good combination,
I would say.
After...
After a stroll
through the rain.
Philo,
are you on the internet?
No.
Oh, he's jamming.
He's got your
synthesizer up.
Well, why don't I
start playing my video game?
We'll be even.
I can play.
Are you saying
I can't play and talk
at the same time?
Yeah, you can play and talk.
He does this at the show
all the time, Doug.
He whips out
his electronic doodads
and twiddles them
all through the broadcast.
I know.
And he reads
from Wikipedia
as if he was just...
As if he knew
all this stuff.
He also keeps me honest
by looking up
everything I say.
I may as well have
composed Wikipedia myself.
He looks up
what I say
and keeps it on.
I probably did, you know,
just do great
sections of it.
I could have,
you know.
Anybody can.
You all can.
I'm a Wikipedia editor.
You are?
Yeah, I keep putting
your name back
into that article.
Those assholes.
Who keeps pulling it out?
That's the question.
Wikipedia is like,
unfollowers.
Facebook,
Mermadons.
Wikipedia editors.
Other than you,
Reverend Stang,
and any of you
people in the audience here,
of course,
not included.
But other than that,
they're the most
lowest lives on Earth.
They're the scumbags.
Oh, Reverend N. Carrick.
He babysits
the subgenius entry
in Wikipedia
and fixes it
when the jealous people
Thank God for his good work.
Anybody can go in there
and just write
all kinds of lies.
Regular people
have had trouble
getting their lies
out of there,
you know?
Just regular,
normal,
everyday people.
Kill them all.
Fortunately,
many people think
that there's some
special admin privilege
they have to have
to get in there.
No, not so.
And, in fact,
there's no complicated
machinery to buy
and you can start
at once.
You can go in there
and really destroy
all kinds of
Wikipedia pages.
But they're ready
for you.
Whenever our page
is vandalized
in Wikipedia,
it's fixed again.
Very quickly.
Thanks, Ankara.
Yes, all hail
Ankara.
So, now that
we've given credit
where credit is due.
Is there someone here
that does that for us?
Now, this is
when the ladies
are all supposed
to get undressed, right?
If not the guys.
Oh, wow, look at them go!
There they are.
See?
Not you, Susie.
Um, remember.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
spontaneous expression
of pure joy
that we've come
to love and expect.
Well, yeah,
it's too bad
the radio audience
can't see
this endless display
of naked,
uh, female
and similar clothes.
The parade of
pulchritude
now taking place.
Yes, sir,
look at them go.
Easy on the eyes.
Next topic.
Yeah, that's like
looking at YouTubes
on the radio.
Yes.
It's unfair.
It's mean.
Uh-huh.
On the radio.
Radio.
No one can
see you.
You scream.
Dr. Drummond,
do you think
we will ever
get puzzling evidence
to come out to X-Day?
I don't think so.
Never?
He's afraid
that he wouldn't
get his butt
kissed enough.
Well, he could be.
It might be such
a terrible,
and plus,
the reality,
you know,
of the,
the church.
Yes, it's
scary to some.
One thing to hear it
as a form of audio,
but to experience it
in the fully
sensitive,
sensual fashion
might be more
even than puzzling
evidence could do,
but I doubt it.
I think he's adaptable.
Was I just hearing that?
Yeah.
Did that again?
This is what
Philo,
what happens
when Philo plays
with his belly button.
It makes these sounds.
True slack
is by definition
indefinable,
a kind of
direct perception,
unfettered
by common sense.
It is not
mere laziness.
It is a
rather a kind of
active sloth.
Slack is different
for each person.
One might call it
something for nothing,
but the normals,
the mediocretins,
the somnambulax
and pseudo subslans
have tried
to make it
something that
we have been led
to believe
we must work
to buy.
And this is
a terrible error.
That's the sign
of false slack.
If you have to
spend your days
in meaningless toil
to buy
meaningless objects
which will
allegedly
improve your
meaningless leisure,
you are on
the wrong path
and you're buying
false slack
merchandised
and manufactured
by the conspiracy.
True slack
is instantly
recognizable
and discernible.
By the way,
there's a misprint
here in this
sacred book.
Oh, you were
reading that.
I thought you
had watched Arise.
memorized that.
I was like,
what the...
It's a quote from Arise,
but look at this
important misspelling here.
Yeah,
I tried to fix
some of those
pseudo-sub-slans.
The author of this book
simply wasn't well...
about slans.
No, they don't know
about slans
who are the future
super-intelligent race
which will supplant
the human race,
supposedly.
Not slans,
as it says
in the book.
But not everybody
can follow
the quick,
flea-hopping,
adroit wit
of the font
of creativity
known as
the church
of the subgenius.
Then we get to
Revelation X,
which was born
in a night
to perish in a night
while the soul
slept in beams of light.
If you didn't get it,
too bad,
because now
it's very hard
to get your little tentacles
on a copy
of Revelation X.
It is?
Yes, it is.
Because you have to...
I thought it would go
for $999
on Amazon once.
Yes, you have to do
something to get it.
No, some days
it's only 35 cents,
but then it'll be
$1,000 the next day.
There are a lot of
There are peaks
and valleys.
Of course,
a meaningless
palimpsest
created by
industrious demons
in the lower circles
of hell.
So, speaking of slack,
I got up on stage
last night
and ranted about
how I can't rant
because I have
too much slack.
I can only rant
about how much
slack I have now
because my life
is turned around
and it's not
hellish and terrible
at all.
And it's proof
that there are
such things
as old bastards
with slack.
And I want to
formally announce
for the first time
and congratulate
Dr. Drummond,
he officially retired
from that conspiracy job.
He's never going
to frop at work again.
He had the ultimate
conspiracy job
and now he does not.
I'm never going
to frop at work again.
That's how he told
his brother
he had quit his job.
Actually, I said it
like this.
Miss him.
Hey, man,
I'm never going
to frop at work again.
And he goes,
why?
What happened?
I said,
because this is
my last day
and I'm fropping
right now.
So I can't do it again
because I'm already
doing it.
No more weapon sales
from Dr. Drummond
because those terrorists
and Russians
want more good weapons.
They're going to have to
It's good to wash
my hands of all
those dirty deals
and stuff, you know.
Turn my back
and
You know,
when Princess Wee
left
Horrible stuff
I had to do for Bob.
I was doing it for Bob,
you know.
That's the
price you pay
sometimes.
Work a conspiracy
job.
Look at this
bad misspelling.
Ken Kesey
became a member
of the Church
of the Subgenius.
K-E-Y-S-E-Y.
Some proofreader
should go
through this material.
How do you catch it?
The author
is supposed
to be here,
Reverend Lee Seifer.
Well, of course,
some slight
variation
occurs in every text.
Well, he wants us
to point out
those things
to make it perfect.
For future editions.
Although he's already
got his Ph.D.
so who cares?
Well, because one
should polish the
apple
when one can.
Anytime?
Yes, that's right.
Not polish the knob.
Oh.
Polish the
surface.
Shucks.
Look, it's just
playing itself now.
Yes, it hardly
needs a human
anymore.
It's found
its own way.
That little
artificial intelligence
program
ropes its way
along.
Smar it.
And it'll go on
forever if you
don't do something
to get it out
of its jag.
So which song
are we going to do
of some of our old hits
tonight?
I've got,
yeah, I was thinking
we'd do,
just go through
the first side
of the first album.
Some of our
forgotten classics?
Yeah.
Oh,
Split the Anus
of a Mooney.
It cost five dollars.
Would you tell me
if your face is on fire?
Some of those, right?
Yeah.
The old, the old
classic.
What about
Who Threw the Overalls
in Mrs. Murphy's Chowder?
No, we didn't do that one.
Lacking.
Sadly lacking.
But I guess
it's not politically
correct anymore
to make fun
of those Irish people.
The Bing Crosby version
was once very popular
in this land.
Irish people
have thick skin.
Yes, they do.
Those beet,
bog, potato,
pick and mix.
Oops, did I say that?
Yeah, Negi likes
the old ways,
old ways.
List list.
All right,
now we are going
through archives.
Let's do, yeah,
Louie Louie.
I like that one.
Are you a girl
or a goat woman?
Yeah.
Why a goat woman?
I still remember that one.
We worked on the lyrics
on that one for like,
you don't remember
that version?
These Zombies
in a Gada De Vida.
Yeah.
That's an easy one.
By John Milton.
Dance with the doctors
or die.
Yes, that all
should take to heart.
I don't remember that one.
We might have to
listen to that.
Dance with the doctors
or die.
Oh, okay.
Of course, I used all the,
I edited this one
so it has all of my,
the ones with my lyrics.
Right.
If I had edited it,
it would have been
all my words.
It would have been all Philo
on the mic.
Strange how that works out.
We'll spare you
by not playing this
here.
For the time being.
Very provocative
artwork.
Well, we can't,
we can't really
cover,
the old tunes properly
because you forgot
the drummer.
Yeah, I did.
I left the drummer
at home.
I had a great,
I had great intentions.
The best intentions.
Well, we might get a
substitute.
I should definitely
get credit for that.
A fill in.
I really intended to.
The original doctor.
And trying is good as,
is just as good as doing
sometimes.
It was,
it was,
let's,
it really is.
No, it's not as good
as doing.
No, it's not.
Trying, trying
is just as good.
My kids tell me that,
but dad, I tried.
Don't you,
don't I get a little bit
of credit just for trying?
Dad, come on,
don't.
No, describe it.
And I have to admit
that, yeah, okay,
I'll give you a,
I'll give you a little,
just, you know,
if it was a dollar,
I'd give you like two cents
for just for trying.
But you'd get 98 cents
for success.
He's trying to make
excuses for what,
for forgetting the drummer.
The doctor's
for Wotan drummer.
It was working.
I was on a roll there.
No, I'm going to go
ahead and tell them
what they're missing
thanks to you.
Very well.
I'm a,
I'm amazed that you
still even have that.
The drummer that started
and ended every song.
Yeah.
It was a,
you know,
those,
those little battery
operated chimpanzees
with the symbol
that goes,
and at the end
they go,
well,
that was the drummer.
But Philo's
brilliant move
was to put
the chimpanzee
in a box
so that its elbows
hit the side
of the box
and make it backbeat.
So it was like,
boom,
pop, boom,
pop.
Ah.
Plus he always
And then we just
put the mic in it.
He would run out
of batteries
pretty soon.
So the song
always slumped down.
We had to wind him up,
you know.
Yeah, it's a wind-up chimpanzee.
All the songs
were the same length.
Clockwork mechanism.
Yeah, they kept
the song short
because eventually
the monkey
would just kind of
stop.
Yeah.
Make one last
fitful,
ah.
Damn it,
you left the monkey
behind.
I fucked up.
Big time.
With no rhythm
track at all.
Oh.
Well, no,
before the monkey
we had coffee cans
and spoons.
Yeah, so we've got
electronics now.
Oh, yeah, but that's
And devices.
Like Ed Holmes.
And we have
Chaos McBobcat
who can play
those things
and make lots of noises.
All I need to make
Wotan is these.
He's in his
second childhood,
ladies and gentlemen.
Aye, aye, aye.
Oh, what a
me, me, me.
A noble mind
is here also.
Oh, that's one of your songs.
Yeah, that's one of my songs.
That was how
Doctors for Wotan started.
It's all about me.
We were to tell me.
We're caught up
with all the extraneous
words out.
I mean, you don't need
all that other stuff.
Me, me, me, me, me, me, me.
We stole the clever name
from Doctors for Bob, though.
Oh, we did?
Yeah, not the concept.
Oh, the Doctors for Wotan.
They were Doctors first.
Yeah, we were mad.
We were already doctoring,
but we didn't have
that title for it.
We didn't have that title
for it.
I'm so very sorry
that we ever printed
the word anti-music
in that book
because I hate anti-music.
You do.
I like anti-music.
I know you like anti-music
and I hate it.
I'm going to play
some more now.
I hate the fact
that you love it
and you've saddled me with it.
For years, people have been
sending me these horrible tapes.
They're just horrible
and they're proud
because it's anti-music.
We heard subgenius
is all about anti-music.
Ah.
And well,
as you sow,
so shall he reap.
Why, why, why?
You started it.
No, he started it.
Just roll with it.
He started it
and Sterno encouraged him.
They were bad influence
on each other's.
Like, nasty little boys.
I come to think
of everything about
the church's subgenius
just reminds me
of nasty little boys
doing just what
their mom told them
not to do. Those brats.
That doesn't sound like good, clean laughter
to me. No, they're off hatching
more of their devilment.
I notice another anomaly in this
book here. It says
Philo
Drummond's program is the puzzling
evidence show on KPFA.
It's all me. It is. That's me too.
He started it. He interviewed you.
Drummond reflects on his own
audience here.
He did interview me.
He did. He talked to you.
He got that information.
He must have said, yeah, my show, the puzzling
evidence show has been on since 1982.
It's me. I've been doing it
for a long time.
Fortunately, puzzling evidence will never see this
text, but it is unusual.
No, actually, he didn't
call me. I didn't actually lie about that.
That's something that he did on his own.
History is a game of telegraph.
Everything gets changed.
I think he interviewed me.
He interviewed me by email.
Right.
Email? Well, that's
doomed to be wrong.
Maybe.
That's the way you can get it all right.
Oh, well, all right, if you say so.
I just don't remember.
The spell check is a robotic function which doesn't
understand all your high-flying
subgenius terminology.
So we're being interrupted
by electronics at the
present time. It kind of
strengthens us for the struggle ahead.
It helps us gird our loins
and put on our spiritual armor
so we can thwack'em all day
and all night.
Whack'em, smack'em, sack'em.
Smack'em.
Sweet music
makes a rainy sky seem clear again.
It does?
It's pretty rainy.
It means...
Sweet music makes a rainy sky
seem clear again.
So is there going to be a...
Are you going to be on Half-Life 3, Dr. Howe?
Huh? What?
Is there going to be a Half-Life 3?
Oh, that's proprietary information.
Wow.
I guess that means yes.
Actually, I didn't find out it was...
No, that means the project is dead.
I didn't find out it was actually happening
until I came to this camp
where others more informed than I told me.
Does that mean Dr. Kleiner
won't have a role in the new game?
Oh, Dr. Kleiner will have plenty
of a role.
All right.
I just started playing it again,
Half-Life 2,
because they had an update.
Are you having fun with that?
The graphics were better.
Yeah.
Did you get to City 17?
I just started, like,
just before I left,
because they had an update.
Oh, cool.
All right.
Somebody had redone it.
They have it now in Anaglyph 3D,
which you can find on the Internet.
And they have the PlayStation version.
And they have Half-Life Opposing Force,
which you might want to be
on the other side.
You get a little action
every time I play, right?
Well, no.
I simply get an extremely generous...
For those who are confused,
the very popular video game Half-Life
had Dr. Howell
did voice talent on that.
So he's...
You probably get recognized
for that more than for...
Yes, but...
Anything else.
But that's just one thing.
Can't live it down.
One little thing.
It's like Princess...
Princess, we and I went to...
We were somewhere
and these youths ran up to us
and went,
we know who you are.
We know who you are.
And I was expecting, you know,
a subgenius fan.
You guys do that Numa Numa song.
And sure enough, you do.
Or did.
That's the only thing
you're famous for.
Well, we did the phonetic
Numa Numa song
where we took the original
Romanian lyrics
and changed them to English
that sounded kind of the same.
So that we sounded like...
It sounded like they were
singing along with us.
Only the lyrics didn't
really make any sense.
It ended up being called
Rather Bob Didn't Stay.
And it got us in big trouble
on the station.
I almost lost my show
because of that song.
What?
Sesame Street Lawyers called it?
It's got nonsense lyrics
and Princess We and Me singing.
And for some reason,
the phrase
Rather Bob Didn't Stay
sounded exactly like
Go fuck the something something.
I mean, the station manager
heard it as having the word
fuck in it.
And he was seriously
going to kick us off the air
just for that one use.
And it wasn't...
I had to prove to him,
no, that word is not
in the song anywhere.
Your filthy mind is hearing it.
He goes, well, I played it
for several people
and they all distinctly heard it.
I said, look, I'll show you
a copy of the Romanian lyrics.
I'll show you the lyrics
we were actually reading
and then listen to it again.
And only when he was looking
at the lyrics
and hearing the song
did he believe me.
What a dick.
That's why no one knows
where he is anymore.
He's gone.
At least you got him to stand down
before he was necessarily liquidated
as an enemy of slack.
Yeah.
I think he kind of maybe
didn't like what we stand for.
took care of that.
Yes, he was just fundamentally opposed
to subgenius principles and doctrine.
There's no room in the new world
for such...
Luckily, I've had at WCSB,
we've been on the air there so long,
even before I lived there,
that several of the station managers
are subgenius fans.
One, this is the kind of thing
that makes me feel young.
This station manager, Sarah Corrigan,
came up to me and goes,
Stang, I just wanted to let you know
I've known about Bob since third grade.
They had a fire drill
at my school.
We had to go stand outside
and do nothing for 20 minutes.
And that was when,
for the first time,
I noticed that real high up
on the edge of the elementary school
was a spray-painted Dobbs head.
And she stood there
looking at that thing.
The thing is,
the woman I'm talking to
is like 39 or 40.
That seems old to a child.
I get that a lot.
My parents used to listen to your...
Yeah, I used to listen to your show.
I used to listen to your show
when I was like 13.
And the guy I'm talking to is 50.
And that's when, of course,
it's my cue to go,
it's still on.
It's still happening.
And another one of our station managers
had Bob's Dobbs head tattooed on his arm.
So I knew we could get away with murder
as long as we had subgenius station managers
by chance.
But I think our current one,
is not.
Has not been informed, regrettably.
She is not.
Regrettably.
I've already gotten a couple of pink slips.
How appropriate.
Yeah, right.
Yeah, I never thought about it.
Pink slips.
Yes, when pinks find fault with you,
they give you a pink slip.
That's another way one can always tell.
I see these T-shirts all the time
that say, I love pink.
I'm assuming that's a band, right?
Or a singer?
It's a singer.
But then there's also,
Nenslo showed me in his house,
he had a record released by one Joanna Galt
called The Pink Life,
where she sings about how the pink life
is so wonderful and everybody should join it.
What does that mean?
Well, her name is suspiciously reminiscent
of Ayn Rand's hero, John Galt.
But whoever she is,
she's a freckle-faced Iowa apple knocker,
nobody,
who put out,
this record to affront the ears
of all thinking people.
But that song...
That's the way a lot of pop music is.
The pink life is an earworm.
Once you have heard that song,
it never goes away.
That's another of its mephitic manifestations.
I wish I could whip out,
I'd love to be,
I'd like to be a ding-a-ling.
No, I'm glad to be a ding-a-ling.
Yeah.
Well, I could sing it.
Frank Sinatra.
I have it all to memory.
I could sing it if you wanted it, but...
Do it.
All right, folks.
This is from a duet by Nancy and Frank Sinatra.
And it starts with...
Getting stoned on sunshine
Getting high on air
Getting to it naturally
Really gets me there
I've got such a high on
Living like I do
I'm so full of happiness
I'm hooked on something new
Life is such a trippy thing
Hello birdies, hello spring
Each day on earth is a day that's worth
Remembering, remembering, remembering
And I mean just what I sing
Life is such a groovy thing
Don't pity me, I'm proud to be
Just a ding-a-ling, ding-a-ling, ding-a-ling
My pot is full of fruit
Flowers, my grass is fresh and green
My tea is brewing in the cup
And still I make the scene
But just don't try to change me
I love this world I've found
I've got to fly my own sweet way
So don't you put me down
Life is just a trippy thing
Hello birdies, hello spring
Each day on earth is a day that's worth
Remembering, remembering, remembering
And I mean just what I sing
Life is such a groovy thing
Don't pity me, I'm glad to be
A ding-a-ling, ding-a-ling, ding-a-ling
My, what was it?
My Coke is Diet Cola
My horse is Mr. Ed
My down is in my pillow
Where I lay my feet on the ground
My sleepy head
My, what is it?
My speed is 55
He knows the censored lyrics
Oh well, you get the idea
That's a, yeah, it's a great
That was, that was a
Good job, Dr. Howell
And funny, I just
You sounded, I could have sworn
Nancy Sinatra was sitting next to me the whole time
Well, in a spiritual sense, she was
Yes, indeed
It's funny, I just had been playing around with that song
Like a week ago, two weeks ago
My Coke is Diet Cola
My horse is Mr. Ed
My down is in my pillow
Where I lay my sleepy head
Yeah, they're drug-free, I get it
Yeah, they don't like drugs
They like being happy
And snapping your fingers
They're high on money
Well, that's the subtext, of course
The fact that they're
But then they say
They act like they're the persecuted ones
You know, just don't try to change me
I love this world I've found
Quit forcing your drugs and gay sex
On me, I love this world I've found
Quit forcing your drugs on me
Yeah
And, yeah
Let me fly my confetti flag, darn it
Poor Frank and Nancy Sinatra
They are to be pitied, of course
Everybody's doing it to them
They're not doing it to us
We don't really do real drugs
Well, drugs turn you on
But don't tell me what to do
Or drugs turn on you
God damn the pusher man
Public service announcement from
From Arizona TV had that
But the weirdest of all
Was one way late at night
One night, St. Paul Mavridis and I were up
And on TV came an anti-cappuccino public service
What?
In San Francisco?
Yes, with black people dressed up
As huge cups of cappuccino dancing around
This must have cost money to produce
That had to be
You were probably tripping
No, fortunately, Paul was there
And saw it, too
And we looked at each other with incredulousness
They also had an anti-cappuccino
And a coffee one
But this was an anti-cappuccino one
This was many years ago
In the 80s
But who got money for putting that on the air?
In the very dead of night
When only subgeniuses are up
And churchyards yawn
And gibbering phantoms twist
In smoky wreaths above graveyards
I read on the internet
That the reason people get addicted to cappuccino
Is because the gay pushers put male semen in them
And that gets people hooked
On gayness as well as Starbucks
So only a house coffee is not suspect?
That's what works with Red Bull
They put the bull semen in there
Or bull something in there, right?
I never did care for that stuff
These are just primitive folk superstitions
You know, you go with what works
People like that stuff
No, you see what you're thinking of
Is this kind of sympathetic
Real big
Magic
Gosh, we're coming up on
In Thailand, you know
3 p.m.
How striking
What's that?
The passage of time
Oh yeah, yeah
In fact, we've just run out of this hour
Of slack
Yes, more time
There are more hours in the day
But this particular hour of slack
Has been brought to you by
The Church of the Subgenius
Broadcast live from
Caffeine is a Cosmic Cafe
At Wisteria Community Cafe
Campground
And the year that the
Crazy human idiots
Called 2015
But we know it's really
Well, we hope it's
Once again
Well, last year was really nice
Let's change the subject, okay?
And change the tape
Okay
Yes, let's flip the cassette
Okay, that's where the trumpet fanfare
Insert here
You've been listening
To the Subgenius
Radio Ministry
Hour of Slack
For free information
Write to
P.O. Box
Cleveland Heights, Ohio
Or see
www.subgenius.com
Praise Bob