the
Does your mother know you're listening to the subgenius hour of slack with a somewhat
sticky rubber diamond stank?
She's listening with you?
That's illegal in 24 states, you know.
I'll bet you let your dog watch you undress for a bit, too.
I mean, praise Bob!
In beautiful Sweden.
I was arrested and held as an accessory.
You'll read about it in the probation report.
But, Connie, why didn't you get in touch with me?
Well, I was so terribly ashamed, I didn't want anyone to know.
Take your hands off me!
You can't treat me the way you used to!
I can, eh?
We'll see about that!
You ever been arrested before?
Go on, squawk.
Tell them all about yourself so everybody will know the jam you're in.
Oh, you're not as tough as you think you are.
You're both pretty young to be in a racket like this.
You say you talked about some trouble you girls had.
I can't tell you that.
You mean...
You mean you're afraid to tell me for fear it might uncover other criminal activities you girls were engaged in?
Everybody's talking about Monica, the story of a bad girl.
Labeled by Time Magazine, Sex on the Rocks.
If you're one of those people who giggles like a schoolgirl when anyone uses the word titillate,
you're a prime candidate.
You're a prime candidate to be a registered listener devoted to...
The Subgenius Hour of Squawk.
With the prurient river diving stank, Dr. Johnson bets his covenant trademark that it'll do you a world of good.
Keep listening for tips on how to measure the blockage.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
Well, I think we have a fun, fun show for you tonight because...
Well, Bob made a great big B-T-M.
Yes, Bob made a huge...
And that doesn't mean a bowel-tee Miller.
It means Bill T. Miller came out with a new CD, friends.
And, uh, uh, kings of feedback.
And, well, actually two, two new CDs.
Kings of Feedback and Drum Army.
That and, um, the, uh, X-Day materials that have finally made it into audio only.
And the, the Einstein Secret Orchestra and, and, and Connie and Susie's latest at Con.
And, and, uh, and KPFA, a whole bunch of KPFA.
Friends, it's just one of those shows.
And so, uh, I don't know.
I'm not sure.
It's whatever.
We least expect.
Love hides in narrow corners.
Love comes for those who seek it.
Love hides inside the rainbow.
Yeah.
Love hides in molecular structures.
Love is the answer.
Yeah.
, baby mired eh no want hahaha hair gotta line.
Yeah came out now.
You gave your待案.
Now you get yours baby I'll get mine.
Gonna make it baby way to will keep me trying.
I'll make my life easier I know it's not gonna be as easy but I'm.
And.
And I.
And I did.
And they, they I'm too.
The old get old and the young get stronger
May take a week and it may take longer
They got the guns but we got the numbers
Gonna win, yeah, we're taking over
Come on!
Cause there will be no more, there will be no more
Little baby ducks, no friends
There'll be no more mushroom clouds
Raining down toxic plutonium dust
No, no friends
There'll be no more incisions
In the bladder tumor ward
There'll be no brains removed
No brains removed
No more monkeys
Cut up and thrown out the back door
There'll be no more overfishing of the seas
There'll be no more turning of the poles
On their little magnetic holes
There'll be no more political intrigues
And no more politics
There'll be no more people to squick around and bollocks
They ain't gonna be S.H. nothing
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, okay
I pooped my pants
That all out, I'm better now
I'm sorry I ruined your show
Dave's better now
It's okay
He's not sorry he ruined my show
He ruins it every week
Want me to prove it?
Hello, you're on the air
Jazz?
Yes
Hey man
Hey Mon
You're on the air
We're not on the air
You're in the air
You're all through the air
All over the world
Almost there
Yes!
Again!
I just wanted to call and see if you could give me a ride
I just wanted to call and see if you could give me a ride from the airport
Or not me actually
My friend, Cerno, needs a ride from the airport
July 3rd
Somebody's gotta do it
Okay, okay, okay
Does this have a lock?
All right, let's start the show now
The show is starting
Okay, we're starting now
On your mark
Amanda Lynn has so many goals
Joe!
What are you trying to do?
It appears as though something has happened
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Shawn Mena has gone shooting
Thanks for watching
You're going shopping
リン
This is the only thing I know
Ask the zweiten powder
Ask the usable
I'm just curious
What do we do?
Something is...
It commission
No
What?
I call everything
pointed questions
almost on his stomach,
and the side of his head,
and his head was laying on the edge of the seat.
He was laying more on his stomach
than his foot was hanging out over the edge of the car,
upside down.
Don't listen to him, children.
Listen to me.
After all, I'm your friend.
You're special to me.
Special, special, special to me.
See, Arnie loves you,
and Jesus loves you,
and Arnie doesn't like Mr. Pink anymore
because Mr. Pink's a jerk.
And I think that Mr. Pink
deserves to slide under a cement truck
and die with a mouthful of his own blood,
and all of his parents and his children,
and all of his stinky Hindu friends with him.
Ha ha, Mr. Pink's ancestors all live in dirt huts.
Ha ha.
Woo-hoo.
All right, all right, all right.
Hey, listen, listen, listen, man.
Listen, man.
I don't know how many of you people believe in astrology.
Are you Sagittarius?
Yeah, that's right.
That's right, baby.
I am a Sagittarius.
The most philosophical of all the signs.
I am a philosophize.
But anyway, I don't believe in it.
I don't either.
I think it's a bunch of...
bullshit myself.
But I'll tell you this, man.
I'll tell you this.
I don't know what's gonna happen, man,
but I want to have my kicks
before the whole shithouse goes up in flames.
All right.
This time, let go your consciousness.
Let go.
Now, I have final instinct.
I'm not gonna let it slip out of my hands,メ
Dispotional toys
Distort my perception
This No Channel toys
Animated figurines
Dance in harmony
Love fractures
If rejected
What is reality for sound?
What is reality in terms of space?
What is reality in terms of time?
Trans-historic
Prize cartoons
Streaming endlessly
Brainwaves will process
Your body's electricity
Animated figurines
Dance in harmony
Trans-historic
Zimocast
Cross-posted to your next dream
Oh, that's now. That's real now.
They depend on hallucinations for their philosophy.
This is not a new idea, and it has never worked.
If you want it, you can have it.
Reach out. You deserve it. Celebrate yourself.
We could disconnect the interface and still maintain the input level.
Neurotransmitters allow brain cells to communicate with each other.
Oh, that's now.
attempted X Day.
Beat me up Scotty, there's no intelligent body out here.
If there was some I'd only get away from it.
Anyway, let's go.
If you want it now, love can give you a whole planet.
Love can give you a whole planet.
When did you say you wanted it now?
You want the whole planet now or you're just trying to get it done?
You can spend 80 days for $30.
$2 a day in restful bed.
It's not bad.
Crazy.
Be part of the in-ear world.
And the beginning of your own new world.
And the best thing is, it's a doing yourself new world.
That's right.
But we are in the countdown now, you know.
There's only a little bit of time left before the end times begin.
What does that mean?
They're pounding their airborne badges into the air.
Into their flesh.
Oh yes, we have our jobs, butt wings, ceremony.
That was nothing because they were placing that on their breasts and pounding it in.
Oh boy.
Yeah, you know, whatever.
The actual badge is on our foreheads, my friends.
Some people do it on the end of their nose.
And I've even heard of a perverse sect in San Francisco that, well, I'll just say that piercing takes on a new name.
The rain falls.
And the listeners remain fixed here.
If you come down to the station, yes, you can get that giveaway ticket.
For the sex saucers in the end times.
You won't need drugs in the future.
You won't need anything except that little subgenius pamphlet out your hand.
Wake up!
You can't remember where it was!
Had this dream stopped?
The snake was pale gold, glazed and shrunken.
We were afraid to touch it.
The sheets were hot dead prison.
The earth was dark.
We must get off.
That's... Chaz, I had to tell you.
And Princess Wee and Dave and Leepo.
I had a vision today in the car of a bumper sticker that said earth dot dot dot.
We must get off!
Exclamation point.
Yeah.
Wow!
Out!
Wait, open up!
Open the door.
I think you got another smash.
It's time to find a way to get a break in
All the good things have been taken
A cover of wings to make certain things work
But I'm dressed in rags I will save all someday
Hear what I say
I'm gonna ride in the subway
No more time spent sweating red
Hear my command I'm blameless
It ain't over yet Hold me down
Stick around
Baby, baby, baby
It's my fight and I'll do what I want
It's my fight
And I'll think what I want
Show me a brawl
Purpose and time
But someday I'll teach you your mind
guitar solo
bass solo
drums and bass
drums and bass solo
bass solo
drum and bass solo
drums and bass solo
drums
제 부 재결
IR
That was my day
Can you believe
I ain't no sin
Who complains
So girl, go on now
Head on out
But baby, baby
Remember, remember
It's my life
And I do what I want
It's my mind
And I think what I want
Show me I'm wrong
Or there's some time
But someday I'll treat you real fine
It's my life
And I do what I want
It's my mind
And I think what I want
It's my life
And I do what I want
It's my mind
And I think what I want
It's my life
It's my mind
And I think what I want
It's my life
And I do what I want
These are my dreams
Yeah, this is my time
This is my way
This is my time
Yeah
You know I like it
Yeah, I like it
Yeah
We're going to be going outside of the sphere.
The sphere of humanity is...
I've never really cared for it.
You know, I never really gave a crap.
I was always told I was different, weird,
in some vague, unnameable way.
I wasn't, you know,
I didn't have a cleft palate or anything.
But I just knew I was different.
And when I finally found the actual mother church,
I knew that I was home.
Praise Connie!
Oh, praise Connie is right.
You will now realize that Connie is the one living true black master.
Friends, you see,
and I've been jealous of them.
Piss on each other's turf all they want.
But the whole time Connie's menstrual blood washes away the filth.
It washes away the unclean.
The way it is unclean.
Praise Connie!
You are out of control.
Don't worry, Ivan.
The bleeding, spurting side effects are part of the treatment.
I can't play.
My mouth won't do it.
It's just that everybody's milk.
You're listening to the subgenius hour of slack.
Too late to stop now.
You might as well go all the way.
Love is love.
If you listen.
You see, we're dealing in opposites here.
Everything's in reverse, you might say.
He's off.
Here I go.
L traveller, what are you trying to do?
Nothing, I got mess you here.
What have you been doing lately, it's to tuck back our yoke.
You don't have time to head out to the Park.
Oh my God.
Who are you?
Don't go.
living in a fantasy world and looking for sounds that may not even be possible
Why are you looking for sounds?
There areinteresting sounds !
No ...
More !
Yes !
No !
parent !
反!
fan !
What do you see?
The world of stereo is filled with spectacular sound surprises.
And an evening.
Can you hear it?
This is a madness.
The stream of life is a wave on the ocean of love.
Life is expressed in the waves of love.
And the ocean of love flows in the waves of life.
Dimethicone. What is it?
It's in the food you eat.
It's in the water you drink.
It's in the air you breathe.
Dimethicone.
Where did it come from?
It shouldn't be in the air.
It shouldn't be in your food.
It shouldn't be in your water.
Dimethicone.
Find out what it is.
Find out how to fight it.
This insidious plague rotting out the heart of America.
Dimethicone.
To find out how you can eliminate Dimethicone from your life,
send one dollar to NoDimethicone.com.
P.O. Box 140306.
Dallas, Texas 75214.
Save yourself.
Save your children.
Save your soul.
We're on the Super Highway.
Really the fast lane to that pot of gold at the end of the rainbow?
M-O-N-E-Y.
This here is the Colquitt.
Welcome to the Internet, folks.
Yesterday I couldn't spell Internet.
Today I'm right smack dab in the middle of it.
I am not a geek.
I am a nerd.
I know you are, but what am I?
Nerd.
Woo!
I'm a nerd.
I know you are, but what am I?
Nerd.
This here is the Colquitt.
Welcome to the Internet, folks.
Yes, I'm a nerd.
I know you are.
Yes, I am.
Yes.
Yes, I am, yes, yes, yes, I am.
I am.
Yes, I am.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, I am.
I am a nerd.
You're a nerd.
I know you are, but what am I?
I am a nerd.
You're a nerd.
Yeah.
I know you are, so what do you mind?
Friends, this is...
Everybody's making money off the internet except us.
Braze Pop.
Braze.
King of the internet.
of feedback friends this is you nerds this is kings of feedback built II king
of feedback king of slack built email
nerd triumphant you see that what it comes down to now man
Oh
and quiet and get up just one sight and try it.
...tiny as little collar in bed, hard to stay awake.
And we understand.
We are all babies inside.
And can you sign my enamel?
You'll just have to squeeze it in with a micron.
And that baby's bombosity is washed off the aircraft carrier
with a high-pressure hose in my movie.
Oh, no, I know this part all too well from military school.
You didn't have one of those things?
You live with those things.
These things, you...
You learn to poop those things so you can find them immediately.
You literally swallow these things at lunch and breakfast
just in case you get straight in on a desert island
and you want to have a supply of these things.
And the smell of Brasso, that's the only other thing.
Well, he's got the last one I have.
You swallow these things and you wolf them down with Brasso.
Actually, you know, I grew up with those things,
and so I thought they were really cool
because I realized the whole world...
That was like pre-Gaffer's Tape fastener.
That was the one thing that held the whole world together.
But once Gaffer's Tape was instructed,
in about 1941...
These are the little clips, my friend.
Yes, we're...
How old are you?
Let's view those.
We are eons old.
We are not free to say that on the radio,
but suffice to say you cannot add enough zeros
on the end of the number in order to make sense of it.
You're getting nothing for nothing,
so you tell us how old you are,
then we tell you how old we are.
Wait, are you talking Earth years?
I think she is.
I think she's limited to that thinking, yeah.
I'm not at the realm of you people.
The realm of people?
What kind of derogatory remark is that?
I'm saying I'm not good enough.
I'm just me.
Well, you know, that's probably not for me.
You don't even need to be.
I'm saying I'm just here.
Well, you know, this is the me generation.
So you're right in time.
That must mean you're rather young to be part of the me generation.
I know what you're talking about.
I'm just a kid.
Well, at least that makes one of us.
Hey, look, the car's starting.
Everybody's driving away because that guy wants to meet us at the front door.
There's just some things that we can't really do.
There's a crowd at the door there.
There is?
There are about a thousand people out there.
I think you're carrying...
I think it's signs.
They all want to get...
Stay high.
The signs are facing the street, but I think they say something with down with,
and then I can't make out the last word.
Down with syndrome.
Oh.
He's pressing his nose up against the glass.
Oh, yes.
They're from over there at 10th Avenue.
I forgot.
He's pressing it up against the glass.
I can see it.
That's still one of my favorite moments when you and I are in the elevator with all of the callers.
This is what it's like to be a subjugist walking the streets.
It was so hard not to laugh.
You know what I'd like to know?
Yes, we had that moment.
What normals are to subjugists.
What the hell is that talking about?
You're just babbling.
We're talking about real life.
That really happened.
Yes, we are babbling, but the wise amongst you will be able to discern.
You wouldn't think so if you had been a more constant listener.
You would understand.
I've been listening to this show for four years.
Four years.
I'm in the basement.
Imagine that.
Four years.
Well, of course you're in the basement.
That's where we keep all our listeners.
Now, listen.
I'd like to know...
Yeah.
If I come down to the station...
Okay, we're punching in the record.
Will you come down?
Will you come outside?
No, no, I didn't mean...
Literally, this is info world now.
Will you come outside and meet me?
No, why should we do that?
What is this, some kind of playground thing?
I don't understand.
Come outside.
Are you challenging us to come outside and meet you in the street or something?
No, I just...
I'm a big fan of the show.
Well, I know the show.
Well, I'll tell you.
You can listen to it better from the comfort of your home than you can out in the windy, rainy street.
I don't think you want to come down here.
You're much safer in the house than you're at now.
Okay, newest caller.
What do you think we should do?
I'll be a wonderful...
Did you ever see Salem's Lot?
We are outside your window right now, scratching at the sale.
3D stereogram book.
Oh, all right.
And there's only 26 cents left, folks.
Call it right now.
Who is that guy?
If you have to wait, you know, just bear with us.
We're taking Visa MasterCard.
It's not a problem.
Oh, another pledge break.
Oh, okay.
Oops, I'm sorry.
That's why we have to gather money for...
What station are we on?
Oh, I forget.
Now, remember, we cannot take your Visa Card out of the air, nor your expiration date.
But we can take it over a phone line.
We're sort of young in our hearts, so whatever.
We can bring you the kind of programming that you, the listener, demand.
So, demand, listener.
It's your phone.
Free to demand on this show.
It's like what demand wanted.
Do you believe in those 3D stereogram books?
Yes, we do.
The kind men like.
They're a hoax.
It's a hoax conspiracy put out by the major eyeglass manufacturers.
No, you just can't read them, son.
I don't think so.
If you stare really hard at the 3D books, you'll see the truth.
Just as we, if we look at the science fiction movies, see the truth.
So, it messes up your eyes to force you to buy corrective lenses.
Well, that's true, too.
But that's, you know, that's the same as if you do this too much.
If you want to use your eyes...
If you do what we're doing right now too much, you get hairy hands.
They're all again.
They're suitable for framing.
Yeah.
That's what the cops say to me every time they pull me over.
Goodness gracious, what a simply horrible patchwork of noise that church of the subgenius is.
I listen every week to gather evidence and ammunition for the citizens for normalcy.
Let me tell you, we're not going to get those subgeniuses.
We're going to get them right in the gonads.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to say that.
I mean, I don't use words like...
I don't use words like that.
This tape, all about Satanism, drugs, and rock and roll, is proof positive that this so-called church is going to send the world to heck in a handbasket.
All those demented be-ow's-a-bob-kissing-hop-heads make me want to toss my Nestle's dollhouse cookies with their talk of buckets of pills from that low-life pusher J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Boy, they're so high on drugs that they can't even keep any continuity in their tapes.
Too many children listen to these tapes and subscribe to the insane doctrines of the subgenius foundation.
They're led down a deceptive road to what these weirdos call slack, like that heathenist idea of nirvana.
I say that slack should be taken up like the excess yarn in my knitting and pulled until it sees the light of a normal day like the rest of us do.
So what should any decent-minded American do when faced with one of these zombies for Bob?
Well, first off, give them a bath in Pine Sol.
They usually stink to high heaven.
Then ship them off to the nearest normally accredited deprogrammer.
Well, they'll get bombarded with enough People magazines, arid extra-dry deodorant, and Regis Philbin fan club material, so they won't be able to think anymore the way it should be.
Then they'll feed them real dogma about the glories of the home shopping club, Wingo, Zingo, and the evils.
The Mandingo.
We cannot stand by while our standards and principles are made light of by these possessed fools.
Normals of the world unite.
Oh, dear friends, and quit calling in with those contest answers.
We got all three winners. I can't believe it.
Dave Bales, hey, guy. Great.
Douglas Hooper and, yeah, Reverend Brian.
And that was the Citizens for Normalcy tape you just heard. Thank you.
Wouldn't you like revenge on these mediocratons, these pink boys, these box-dwelling Barbies and Kens?
These normals who have made normality the norm?
Pinks. Pinks are but living stereotypes, insensate meat puppets, and mere food tubes who lack and fear the spark of originality that ignites everything.
Yes.
Every person bears some good and there's some bad.
And it's a choice.
You choose whether you want to love or hate that person.
And for myself, I just choose to hate most of them.
We want Uranus and we want him now.
We want Saturn and we want him now.
We want Mercury.
And we want it now.
We want the sun and we want it now.
25 hour day for couples and we want it now!
We will enslave the sun.
The sun will be ours.
We will give you for life.
The earth will give a life to you.
For we shall own the sun.
We shall own the sun.
We want Saturn and we want it now.
We will enslave the sun.
Gas giants.
We want Mars and we want it now.
We are the asteroids.
We want Venus and we want it now.
We want the sun and we want it now.
Hydrogen reactions.
We want the sun.
Get your hydrogen atoms here.
10 billion year old carbon.
Thanks Bob.
It's made of the old ashes from stars that a long ago went dead.
If everything was fine, everything comes apart one way or another, Bob said.
You better be glad of that.
You should take the old words and smoke it.
Remember what happens when the ashes rise.
Like a mighty phoenix.
Friends, join the church.
Build yourself a noose.
Build your own spaceship.
Stick it in your pipe.
Smoke it.
Blast off.
What's the matter?
Are you scared?
Are you afraid of college?
Come find out.
Go on down there.
We want the universe and we want it now.
We want the universe as we want it now.
We want the cosmos and we want it now.
What is the law?
The subgenius must have slack.
That is the law.
We are not men.
We are evil.
Earth, we must get off.
Wow.
So what are the two possible interpretations?
I mean, just to share with our listeners.
Well, in the most obvious one, we're talking about Earth and saying we must remove our
selves from Earth.
We must get off of the Earth's surface and migrate as much as we can and as soon as we
can.
Even if we must build our own ships, preferably the Xs will come.
The other way that the bumper sticker can be meant is all of Earth, listen to me.
We must get off, man.
It cannot be done as the Xs will lead us.
Anyway, that's the way I think it's called.
Well, just now, we celebrate the complete forgiveness of our country, come him and
They again come and say something like, they say something but nothing.
So it's Ihr reinforcements.
¶¶
Massachusetts 0212 3021 23 I'm going to
get that one more time because it's so
good
p.o. box 330 221 230 221 Boston
Massachusetts 021 23 also on the web
biltiemiller.com that's right biltiemiller
one word dot com friends in the meantime
we are the church of the subgenius
headquarters our slack subgenius
foundation at well you can write to me
staying at subgenius.com or post office
box 140 306 that's the subgenius p.o.
box 140 306 Dallas Texas 75214 is the
zip code
so I'll see you next time
and that's of course www.subgenius.com
now you know everything you need to know
nothing more and you will keep cramming
it into your brains this music in the
background is the swing and love
purchase dear friends and on that note I
think I'll just drop out
yeah
this sounds like heaven
look at that
The Lord, the lard, the lubes, the lerbs, the lardclothes, the lard.
I can't remember.
Whips.
They will, child.
Have you ever taken orders from a shipmate?
We'll keep you safe till Dos Eque.
Yeah.
Well, till next week.
Sounds like the voice of a thousand angels.
It's the voice of Arnold Palmer, calling you from another dimension, saying,
give me back my sacred vowel sounds.
Arn-oil, palm oil.
Cornhole, palm oil.
I think it was the third archbishop of Silesia.
He's a minor.
Abner, the palm oil.
Is this the Eddie Arnold version?
It is.
Sounds very Eddie Arnold.
Do you guys remember him in Sargent's Four, I think it was, or Rio El Paso, Otto?
No, this is the Rio El Paso.
It's from the consummate Eddie Arnold.
And that was Ernest Borgnine.
He played the plumber.
Remember that?
With the fist?
Huh?
Yeah, he had a big fist on the side of his head, right by his neck.
And when it exploded, I think his mom was serving him spaghetti.
Right, right.
Keep your hat on tight.
I can't remember a lot of it right now.
You're back to the wind and you're sack in the saddle.
We'll see you next week.
See you next week there, kids.
But don't.
Don't.
See ya.
Reverend Ivan Stang, the Princess We Are Doe, the Reverend Fleepo Abernathy, and lonesome Cowboy Dave.
My name is Chaz, and this is Einstein's Secret Orchestra ESO with Radio The Swamp.
Yeah.
There's so many of these children.
And look here, the pumpkin headed.
Build your own ship.
Build your own ships.
Even if you must build it from your own shit, we must get off.
Some of the best ships have been made out of shit.
Well, actually, you can make some really good solid rocket fuel out of your own ship.
Build your own ship.
your own shit. There we go.
Claw the bark of trees that is the law.
Drink from the street that is the law.
Four legs and run run free four legs and run legs and run legs and run.
To spit blood that is the law. We're not men. Praise God.
The seven seals shall be broken and the first seven seals shall juggle the great circus of beach ball and park and play.
Have a nice park day.
And there shall be plagues, plagues upon the children.
And they've got some pretty damn cool plagues.
You're going to get off on some of the plagues they've got. You'll make the good plagues.
Some of the other plagues, it's a bummer man.
And the great blind press of Jehovah shall squeeze out the stupidity and the dumbassery from the innocent and the guilty alike.
And the great can opener from Al Jazeera.
And the great champion of the game.