And now, the subgenius hour of SWAC.
Okay, engine stop.
We've got a descent.
Both control both auto-damage.
Command override off.
And drop off.
Tranquility base here.
The Eagle has landed.
Roger, Twink.
Tranquility, we copy you on the ground.
Levitating 285, contact 105-25-52.
Computer, activate emergency medical holographic program.
All program.
Although your world wonders me,
with your majestic and superior cackling hand,
your people I do not understand.
So to you I shall put an end.
Hello, I am your New Moon bender.
I do everyone bad.
The other one has switched off the Hierophant Quan,
because they are seeing the No Jean and they do one thing
that I would not imagine dealing with them that most people would feel like it is a trouble.
And you are going to be
standing on this piece of ice for a long time.
For all as much hurt and as marriage and such.
And the others want you dead,
and so I think I am younger and ранier.
Have you seen him?
How he looks.
I do not want to see you hanged.
Oh!
My fellow Americans,
I'm pleased to tell you today that I've signed legislation
that will outlaw Russia forever.
We begin bombing in five minutes.
The functioning of our senses has been spiritually impaired
and chemically corrupted by the fake artificial food coloring.
We're the lucky ones.
The handful with the chance to reach another world.
And we're the lucky ones.
And we'll use those guns, you'll use them, doctor,
to keep your only chance to stay alive.
Somebody tell me, who is this guy?
Shit-hot Bob John.
Bob John.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, baby, let me tell you about a place
that ain't far from here, it's in outer space.
That good chicken there.
Salt-fried chicken.
A musician, if you consider the normal pattern
of modern civilized life, is on the outside of it all.
He doesn't build things, he doesn't work regular hours
like a decent, God-fearing citizen,
and the life he leads in many ways seems useless,
and irrelevant to those of us who prefer
a quiet evening in front of the television
and a bottle of beer.
Amazing as it might seem to some of us,
musicians have basic physical needs,
just like real people.
If I could just get my hands on a big, fat, juicy prairie squid.
Oh, yeah!
Ha, ha, ha.
Prairie squid.
Whenever you can hear NATO
traumat glow
Look, Connie is coming.
It's useless to read this.
Mr. Connie.
Anti-virgin Cosmo Green, the prettiest thing you've ever seen.
She's super sexy, nasty, mean.
The original bad girl, so unclean.
An uber from outer space.
She's so outrageous in your face.
An icon of desire and sex, just like the girls from Planet X.
A diva of debauchery, mistress of hot swivory.
She's ultra cool, she's so hot.
A juice of genius, patriarch.
Our sister of salvation.
A pin-up queen for masturbation.
A true Jezebel.
She'll send you straight to pink hell.
Divine domestic deviation.
Connie is your inspiration.
A lonely leader in fighting love.
This is the Connie we trust.
Divine domestic deviation.
Connie is your inspiration.
A lonely leader in fighting love.
This is the Connie we trust.
Look out, boy, she's on her way.
Our darling Connie is here to stay.
A girl like her is something rare.
She's superwoman, she's everywhere.
A mighty enemy of the safe.
She's the devil incarnate.
She's one hell of a revelation.
A siren of divine creation.
Hail Connie, fuck Bob.
This girl's got class, a true hard throb.
She'll get you on this righteous kick.
Get with Connie, do it quick.
This girl's a winner in plain to see.
She's the center of our galaxy.
She's the heaven's interpretation.
Straight from bottom radiation.
Divine domestic deviation.
Connie is your inspiration.
A lonely leader in fighting love.
This is the Connie do we trust.
Divine domestic deviation.
Connie is your inspiration.
A lonely leader in fighting love.
This is the Connie do we trust.
This is the Connie.
Divine domestic deviation.
Connie is your inspiration.
A lonely leader in fighting love.
This is the Connie.
Does we trust.
A lovely leader in fighting love.
Sister Corny
I have sinned against you my lord
And I beg your forgiveness
I do not call it a mistake
I do not call it
A mendacity
I call it sin
I want to address myself
As best as I know how
To those that I have wronged
That I have sinned against
I want to address myself
First of all
My wife Frances
God never gave a man
A better helpmate
And companion
To stand beside him
I have sinned against you
And I beg your forgiveness
Sister Corny
God never gave a man
A father
A minister
Of the gospel
A finer son
Than he has given me
And his mother
Sister Corny
I have sinned against you my lord
Donnie and Debbie,
I have sinned against you.
And I beg you to forgive me.
I know that so many would ask,
why?
Why?
I have asked myself that 10,000 times
through 10,000 tears.
Why?
I call it sin.
I have sinned against you, my Lord.
And I would ask that your precious blood
be shed.
I would wash and cleanse every stain
until it is in the seas of God's forgetfulness,
never to be remembered against me anymore.
Here is my testimony against minimizing the sin
Ilán Gonzalez
Ilán González
he's the media darling they like to see.
They watch him go pee
look at him playing
playing Nintendo...
while Barney's asleep on the floor.
Let's give him more.
All the stupid people, where do they all come from?
All the stupid people, where do they all belong?
Look at this moron, cutting me off on the freeway because he can't drive.
He should not be alive.
Here comes George Jr., constructing sentences badly while he smirks and grins.
Will he get in?
All the stupid people, where do they all come from?
All the stupid people, where do they all belong?
I look at all the stupid people.
My heart is broken.
Luckily you won't hear me talk at all.
That's because it's over in shape.
They want me to come back.
I don't want him to come back.
I'm never going to come back.
All the stupid people, where do they all come from?
All the stupid people, where do they all belong?
Well, that was, uh, old death.
Friend, you know, you gotta shout and make a lot of noise.
Because when you're dead, you shut up like hell.
So we're here to make some noise.
And, uh, that song, Old Death, was used in that movie, Brother, Where Art Thou?
A great movie.
Uh, I would recommend to anybody.
Really, it's just an amazing movie.
Um, somebody told me that when they, um, they saw,
saw that movie and Fight Club in the same week,
and they said, well, I felt like I'd been rebooted with a new operating system.
Friends, before that, we heard, uh, several cuts from the new Subgenius album,
A Squid for Connie.
And I'm holding, uh, the second copy of that self-same album.
That had, um, Phineas Narco doing all the stupid people.
Bit of a takeoff there.
Um, we had, uh,
prior to that was, uh, I call it sin there with Jimmy Swaggart,
Reverend Jimmy Swaggart, bitching and griping and confessing.
Uh, that was by a group called Panting Antics,
which, uh, Bleepo Abernathy sent to me.
Before that, Saint Anne and Helena Handbasket doing Sister Connie.
Um, you can find them at www.mp3.com slash Saint Anne.
As in Saint Anne.
And loves you.
And before that, a squid space collage by Professor Chaz Smith,
Dances with Rockets, who couldn't be here tonight
because he's flying all over Mojo World on the other side of the planet.
And so it's just Princess Wiardo and yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stangen here,
uh, playing music until the lone cow, Daveman, gets here.
And, uh, then, uh, then, uh, well, I just, we just don't know.
Oh, and the very first thing that we started off with was,
a message from space by champion Jack Codini.
All of those sequences off of A Squid for Connie.
Um, you heard it here first on the Ips AC, my dear friends.
Mmm, hey there, sweet little nurse-ay.
Mmm, come into the strong yet capable hands of Dr. White.
Ow!
I'm gonna perform some delicate surgery of the heart.
So...
Come here, my child, and lay right down on my operating table, yeah.
Hey, I tell you, talking about medical matters, right,
you know, I went to see me old mate Fat Larry at the hospital.
He's having his tonsils out.
Now, I had mine done about six months ago.
I remember I was having a lot of trouble,
and my very, very handsome man friend, Dr. Simon,
you know, he's from, uh, Leicester's a shire, right,
said I better let him operate.
Well, I submissively laid back while he came over me.
And after a few tentative probes and pokes,
he whipped out me big swollen pear
as soon as you could say Jack Robinson.
Brought me instant relief, I can tell you.
Although, of course, he did leave me a little raw,
and it was quite a while before I could swallow properly.
Well, anyway, I went to see Fat Lass.
I took him some chocolates, and for a gag,
I hid them under me ankle-length black fur coat
with the single vent at the rear.
Well, when I got there, Fat Lass looked at the bulge down below
and, turning me round, prized open the slit at the back
to get a good look at it.
A little big box.
Well, he greedily grabbed it
and was just about to get stuck in when I remembered,
Oi, lass, nil by mouth, our kid.
Oh, well, he was right, act off.
Said he was fed up not getting what he wanted.
Said that very morning, the hospital cook had presented him
with his lovely spotted dick,
and he hadn't been able to take that either.
Oh, blimey.
Well, I felt sorry for him,
but I fancied the chocolates meself.
And fair play to Larry,
he helped me push them all in me mouth.
And what a sight,
the ver-very,
sexy ward sister friend found when she came in,
saw Fat Lass stuffing me between the cheeks, you know.
Well, I left him soon after, feeling very sorry for himself.
But I know it won't be too long
before he'll be able to gobble away to his heart's content.
But, you know, I mean, you should look after yourself,
shouldn't you?
Which is why me and my very, very sexy lady friend,
Foxy Fiona, went to a health farm just the other week.
Well, we got there, we got to our bedroom with our luggage.
I was just about to unload my big bag in the corner
when first sexy lady friend, Foxy Fiona,
asked me if I'd be, you know, rising early.
Well, when I told her I wanted to be up at six, her jaw dropped.
She said it might be a bit too hard for her, you know, getting up so early.
Still, she soon got used to it
and particularly enjoyed an early dip in the pool just before breakfast.
I'd recommend it too.
You know, a quick length first thing in the morning
always puts a spring in your step.
Well, when it came to breakfast time,
we were at it like rabbits, you know,
scoffing away at all the lettuce and carrot salad.
I also enjoyed the celery that was available.
But when I offered some to Foxy Fiona, she refused.
She said she didn't really fancy Goblin on a full store just then.
But if I, you know, gave it to her later in the sauna,
she might have a nibble.
Well, as we were on a strict vegan diet,
we weren't allowed to eat any dairy produce,
which personally I found very difficult indeed.
And I've got to confess,
I did try to smuggle some butter in.
But unfortunately, would you adamant believe it, I got caught.
I mean, I only had a small knob and was really surprised
when the elf farm manager walked into my bedroom,
grabbed hold of it and tossed it out of the window.
Still, apart from that, we had an enjoyable time.
It's anecdotal, really, but look after your health
and then you'll be in the mood for loving.
Mmmmm.
Come over to the good doctor, Dr. White.
The doctor of...
Yes, dear friends, Fat Harry White,
the great Fat Harry White there from his album,
Mmmmm, Baby.
And that's the third cut, no, second cut,
Calling Dr. Love.
Yeah, Pope Phil Monty of Northern England
turned us on to that one.
Fat Harry White, just amazing.
This is WCSB Cleveland.
Praise the Dave brain, which just got here.
легwaest
thump thump successes
comprehensive
in matric sculpture
today's prize
I'm with my family once again And I think I should say yes
Had Mr. Young sing about her There's no need to put her down
I hope Neil Young will remember Southern man don't need him around anyhow
Sweet home Alabama Where the sky is so blue
Sweet home Alabama Lord, I'm coming home to you
In Birmingham they loved the governor We all did what we to do
The Water Gator did not bother me Does your conscience bother you?
Tell me truth
Sweet home Alabama Where the sky is so blue
Sweet home Alabama Lord, I'm coming home to you
Yes, it's true
Sweet home Alabama
Now, Muscle Shoals has got the swampers They've been known to sing a song or two
Here comes the混'ros
Burns of flavour
Citeyont in Monte Corn 쪽
What a pleasant song
onom 주고
Sweet home, Alabama, where the sky is so blue Sweet home, Alabama, Lord, I'm coming home to you
Hey, we're going home, son. Hey, we're going home.
Hey, we're going home.
The King there, the mighty, the, the King.
It's from his album Gravelands. It says here on the Gravelands CD,
The King's patented vocal style answers the musical question,
What would Elvis Presley be singing if he were alive today?
Gravelands is a tribute to the great deceased rockers of the past.
The King sinks his teeth into such classics as
Nirvana,
Nirvana's Come As You Are,
ACDC's Whole Lotta Rosie,
Jimi Hendrix's Voodoo Child,
and many more.
Since Elvis's death in 1976,
there have been numerous sightings of him,
but who would have thought the King would take up the residence in the body of
James Brown,
a 31-year-old Belfast postman.
Ah, yes.
Oh, we have to do this.
We would love to see the rest of the cast in person.
I want you to be shy,
that youogenic to listen to,
and be very clear-headed.
I hope that our storm Being black,
That you could Seldom hear Kelly goodbye,
For you both
An older version of me
Is he perverted like me?
Will he go down and win a theater?
Does he speak eloquently?
And will you have his baby?
I'm sure you'll really make an excellent mother
But the love that you gave that we made
Wasn't able to make it enough for you to be open
Why?
No
And every time you speak his name
Does he know how you'd hold me and hold me
Until you die?
But you're still alive
Cause I'm here
To remind you
Of the mess you left
When you went away
It's not fair
To deny me
Of the cross I bear
That you gave to me
You
You oughta know
Things seem very well
You look peaceful
I'm not quite as well
I thought you should know
Did you forget about me?
Mrs. Duplicity
I hate to bug you in the middle of dinner
But I'm not quite as well as you think you are
It was a slap in the face
How quickly I was replaced
And all your thinking of me
When he fucks you
But the love that you gave that we made
Wasn't able to make it enough for you to be open
Why?
No
And every time you speak his name
Does he know how you told me to hold me
Until you die?
But you're still alive
Cause I'm here
To remind you
Of the mess you left
When you went away
It's not fair
To deny me
Of the cross I bear
That you gave to me
You
You oughta know
Oh
And the joke that you made in the bed that was me
And I'm not gonna fade as soon as you close your eyes
Ah don't you know it
And every time I scratched my nails down someone else's back
I hope you'll feel it
Ah can you feel it?
Cause I'm here
To remind you of my love
Of the mess you left when you went away
It's not fair
To deny me
Of the cross I bear
That you gave to me
Cause I'm here
To remind you
Of the mess you left when you went away
It's not fair
To deny me
Of the cross I bear
That you gave to me
You wanna know
That I'm not mean, man.
You're funny, you know.
I can't, like, tell you stuff, man, you know.
Don't turn by your foot.
Pick that up right now.
You're not so stupid, like, you think I might be.
Pick that up by what you drop that thing by your foot.
What I pick up?
What I drop it?
I don't know.
Something you drop.
I don't know what I drop it.
You drop something by your foot right now.
No, there is nothing down there.
Radio stations of the gods, dear friends.
That's us.
Prophylactics.
Prophylactic users of the world unite.
You have nothing to lose but your sensibilities
and your wide-open, wide-open psychotic musings.
The things you hear when you can't really hear.
Yes, good luck for a long, long nap
because you're gonna be needed
the way your brains are gonna be twisted and torn
and shaved into sweetbreads
and deep-fried in a fatty vessel
and left alone for three and a half...
...and left alone for three and a half years
for you to cry over.
It's gonna happen, baby.
It's gonna be real...
It's coming.
It's coming down, man.
Not pretty.
Not pretty at all.
No, man.
It's a bad scene.
Pigs are everywhere.
Last night the pigs were at my door.
Not, you know, no, not real pigs, man.
They were like these real pigs
clambering all over the house
and banging on my door.
We've got your name.
We've got your number.
We've got your...
Oh, man.
We've got your blood type.
We've also got some of your favorite pictures
on the interweb.
Dave ain't here.
They turned...
They turned it...
Dave ain't here.
We're selling on Yubay.
We're selling some of your shavings
from your inner ear.
So listen softly, dear friend.
You're allowed to visit a place
where very few people are allowed to go.
Make sure you're wearing sunglasses, man.
It's too loud in there.
Too loud, man.
Too loud to go in there.
Too loud.
Make sure you're turned down real smooth.
You know, you're wearing something
the archbishop would wear in his underwear.
You know, make sure you're wearing something
to be ready to scream, daddy-o,
because...
Yeah.
And make sure you're wearing your lockdown braces, too,
so you don't bite your tongue
when you go into convulsions.
Yeah.
And make sure that all your body parts
are all really well shaved
and painted up real good.
That way they can recognize you.
Yeah.
But there's more to life
than shaved knees and body parts, my friends.
Yes, there is more to slack and to life
than death and anti-slack.
So much more.
There is...
There is no divine purpose for you,
but there is a turp-a-turp-a-turp-a-dickin'-on lifestyle
designed especially for you
and your finuncular unicorn family.
Now wrapped in a crystalline silver plate,
I'll get someone with that,
and I'll give you a little tip.
Your hands will be softly welded into the background
as your brain lifts silently and softly to the other side.
Yes, friends,
have a frock.
Zipulops is the one true medicine.
The only food or drink you will ever need
is the sacred herb.
Replace it and save mankind.
Have a frock, Zipulops.
The one Bob grows on the droppings...
The common vegetable.
...and graves of dead yetis
and Tibetan holy men, friends.
The frock is the only thing
that can save mankind.
Bop-bop, bop-bop.
One tiny whiff, one droplet,
one tiny skin pop of the frappy.
One little pinch shoved up your exit wound,
and my friend,
you'll never, ever come down.
We've been sitting in the same room
for the last five and a half hours and nobody seems to notice the clock is picking away it's
packing clacking clacking like that old street car that your grandmother ran down back in the
days before there were real days back in the years before time disputed its first parts those were
the knights of night back in them days but the knights of knights had enemies there were those
strange cults secret societies and the stone pounders the flea bakers the stone breakers
the rose old questions the alunimators and the squags not the squags the squags first form in
the years zip in a lonely saloon in the jerusalem basement three former crusaders hatched a plan
the squags an elite paramilitary group of fighting monkeys
men with short haircuts and shorter tempers isn't happening mostly blue-eyed but sometimes they
knew more than they were supposed to
stand back from the cabinet ironman wait a minute that's the wrong device there
stand clear from the element cleanser
you tried to say something
yeah calm down now i can see you running down your legs just have a little seat over there
what seems to be bothering you honey honey honey please you're convoluting the whole atmosphere
come on you're gonna make my head get all soft come on the spin dryer it's all messed up oh my god
did you did you tell father henker whether no no you know you were supposed to inform him i know but i'm going to do it now
yeah i can't is it very what's gonna happen now tell me what happened was it shaking very very hard
and large yeah oh my god cleveland did it make the sign of zeus in appear ignominiously in the dark
yeah oh damn dear purple light came out okay now father hickenbottom is asleep right now we're
gonna have to pull his socks off if you can oh no no all right no let's see here is these on the
roof i can't do it no no no damn it i can't roll them over on his side i can't do it i can't do it
I think it's too late!
Oh no!
Damn, I should have never-
Oh I'm sorry I said that in front of our lord, but you should never-
I should have never left you in charge of the washing devices!
I'm so sorry! I'm so, so, so, so-
Has this happened to you before?
The child you leave to wash the washing devices is left alone.
Her mind is confused.
She sees trees, airplanes, frogs, apparitions, things that don't exist,
and yet at the same time she's being controlled by an ubermind much smaller than his.
If you look crystal clear into the dark, you'll see she's coming back.
What can we do with these wayward waves?
Certainly we're not going to leave them to wash our washings.
Hey, hey.
Yeah?
He didn't want you to do that.
You get the wrong impression.
The film was not meant to hurt your feelings, just to illuminate you.
The problems we are having reconditioning the children and the furniture.
Some of them do not accept Bob as the ultimate uberman.
The consummate thinker, the lover, the poet, the prophet.
They think he was just a silly-ass businessman from Tohoku, Kansas.
Or so they said in the old days.
I see, yes, I see.
Well, what do you expect from your little trip here, underneath the sheep?
I don't know.
You know, I try not to expect too much.
So, you know, I just keep open my...
Yes, yes.
Do you have any specific desires?
You notice the desire window is opening just for you, my sweaty face.
I should not talk about my desires.
Well, now I'm afraid everyone must know.
The whole cabin clues are as now is filled with sickening children who cannot watch the washing machine.
Ah, you are...
Pablo, hermano, .
.
Ah, the world of the squid.
When was the last time you slept with you, a big old...
Something started to snow.
Squid.
They are so delicious.
.
. .
Reese has no idea about my guts and she obviously she was used by western forces.
Perhaps she was subjected to some type of mind control or is it deeper?
He deserves the 83.
So, um, it's just a lot of speculation actually.
Well, I would say the first thing, 83 is in a numerology.
The 8 and the 3 are combined to make the form of 11.
11 has the same standard as the 2 which is a symbol of unity or of things in balance.
11 is a spiritual number which many of our people have used until the time of the fourth nostril beyond the dreaming days.
Have managed to accrue such a great waste of knowledge that look here.
Now, if they do, look at some of these books. I've spit on them.
Hector, Hector, you cannot turn on the books.
Ah!
But look, look, these other ones are so perfectly confined.
Just bursting at the seams.
Like veils with the air.
Yes, much like your own apertures you are wearing.
I see you have met Bob.
Well, you know.
You have known Dubs.
Talk about it.
Yes, of course.
I think Dubs knows you very good.
Oh, yes.
I can't get myself in trouble, you know.
Well.
You can't be talking about it.
I won't say nothing.
I can't.
Honey is mighty, you know.
Oh, my goodness.
You are serious?
Yes.
Oh, my God.
I have no idea.
Why?
Is he long or short?
Is he like a billy goat?
Or is he like an old, flaccid man?
A mountain.
Like a mountain.
Yes, like a mountain.
Mountain on the shore.
I will tell all of them.
Everyone I know.
I don't know that many people.
I will make sure that there are plenty of people.
Plenty of ears for which these two fall on, okay?
Oh, I thought you must know lots of people because you're so interesting a person.
You must know lots and lots and lots of people.
I talk a good game.
I want the affection of people and yet I am very shallow.
I see.
I am also very confused right now because if you will notice you look on the clock and
while it's going backwards now.
Yeah.
And I think it is time for a little.
I never see something like that before.
A station breakage.
How you do it?
I choose.
Nostradamus forecast that Armageddon would come in the 20th century.
The days in which we live.
Born and hailed, you little green bastard.
Hey, hey look up in the sky.
So what Ozzy?
It's just a rainbow.
It's a magic rainbow.
No dad, that was not an animal.
Okay, I know what it feels like when a man caresses my leg.
You do?
Whether or not I like someone doesn't depend on what kind of genitals they have.
The most interesting fact is that I am a man.
But not one of us, they say it's only Mr. Red electron, from the
rzebs of vacuum.
I do.
Has an aggressor because I'm soUC.
Or have
in Bible,
the
power of now.
This is kind of.
I said,
it's important.
We don't even know what they say. For all we know you could be reading Latin insults about our mothers.
Dr. Hughes called you and told you that the tumor on her neck is definitely a fetus.
Just assume for a moment, sir, that this woman is a young woman?
Yeah, a young woman.
Just assume that she has a problem. Now assume also this problem has to do with Indian magic.
Oh my god, son, you do have one hell of a problem.
My boss would be rich too. And you have boss too. And his boss. See that dame over there in the car?
Oh my god. They keep on breaking my heart.
If only we could get out of this wild tough stuff. If we could only burrow beneath the barbed wire.
If only these vessels could get us out of here. These tiny little boats.
The sponge rafts.
Perhaps we can fashion some sort of crew device. And maybe if we flap our arms very, very hard we will go...
I can help keep you buoyed up old Davey. You won't think.
I have some ideas. I think wild kind of craft things that we can float on.
I think I know what we can use. We'll make our own ship.
No, no, no, no. There's no chance.
Yeah, yeah. We'll make our own ship.
We have some mailing tubes and old cams and marshmallow cream. It will be good. It will work.
In order to sink, you have to lose your ship, my friend.
And in order to fly, you have to lose your little poo poo head.
Yeah, fly so far and long because you lost your little poo poo head.
They call this inappropriate laughter for those people confined in mental institutions.
Don't you know the walls around you have eyes and ears and nose and throat, doctors?
You must be aware that Dr. Ben no longer exists except for in your own febrile sexual organs.
The what?
The contaminated.
The Dr. Ben's no longer exist?
You're contaminated.
Then what do you call this thing?
He is contaminated.
And no one understands his point.
Oh, yes, it is the most contaminated music of all.
Music made by doctors.
True, enlightened doctors.
We're going to remove your hypothalamus with sound now.
Now Dr. Philodrumon applies his saxophone to the patient's sacroiliac in this sacred act of love.
Yes, friends.
Surgery is a form of intimate love.
And the doctors of the airwaves will do this to your very ear, mind and your ear brain.
Just trust the good doctor.
Now he's going to take out your spleen and your hava pancus.
He's going to replace the soles of those tired shoes with a brand new heart and belly button.
Just like the one you wanted to grow.
I was scared but it was over, doctor.
Sit down here on this barbed wire seat.
Don't worry.
Don't wink and nod about those little winkings in your eyes now.
They're just controlling your rapid eye movements.
Those doctors have powers you don't know about yet.
But you're going to find out.
Oh, you'll find out soon enough, my good fellow.
My good little nurse girl.
Yes, yes.
Come on into the operating room now.
The operating theater we call it.
But on these rubber gloves.
Sit down, doctor.
Come on.
Yes.
Pour this alcohol into your lap and here, drink some of this.
And have some of this gas.
And take this pill.
And take this shot.
And then this knife here.
Insert this deep into your chest cavity.
Now take these pencils and work them gradually into your ears.
Now put on these headphones and give me $20.
You notice the acrobatics we are doing now?
Look at me.
I am a monkey man.
Look at my strong forceps.
Look at my chin.
I bet you wish you could imitate this.
But no.
You need more, more, more sound cut.
More.
There will always be a need for more.
More slack.
And yet more money, dear friends.
More money.
And how, how, you ask me, Reverend Stang.
You say, how should I get this money?
With what you speak?
Because it's true.
Oh, sure.
Slack is what you make of your imagination, your dreams, and blah, blah, blah.
But let's face it, we need money.
We don't need a bunch of this hoo-hahs and a bunch of new age gobbledygook.
We need money.
We need money coming into this radio station.
We need money coming into this church.
We need money coming into this wallet.
The one I am sitting on with my butt.
Now I want you to get off of the button, my friends.
And get on down there to the left.
that sub.com thing
and check out that because
this is a prosperity ministry.
We are not going to sit here
and just hope that some
magical monkey's going to start
crapping money out of its butt.
We want you to
start crapping that money out of
your butt. So get with
it, baby.
Oh, Ellie, you understood.
If you were one of the
brilliant shining lights of
humanity, you would know that
you can crap that money out
of your butt as easily
as flying saucers make
planets. You
know that you can create a better
world for you and your
mutant clones by simply
following
the
Ruga!
It was moving very close
to some place.
I didn't want to go.
My head was
throbbing, sure.
I had been knocked down ahead
three times by a bowling
ball.
Of course, that dang was no
helpまだ.
I was sticking that strange
substance down my pants and
was also trying to click my
donuts together with a safety
bun.
I understand it was to
stupid reason I could still
walk unlike so many other
jobs that passed this way
before.
Oh, they just they couldn't
still collect i just got still still like not only still walking hey you wait hey you there
yeah no no you there leaned on the corner singing man singing man yeah what do you what do you want
buddy hey i need a little help you guys go ahead and keep singing what i'll attend to this to this
what what are you a cop now i'm a private dickhead listen buddy i've been out of the car
for the last five weeks my pants are pretty shabby and uh you know i i need a place to go if you catch
my drift or oh you're looking for huh you're seeking something yeah yeah yeah i'm seeking
something i see i'm right here here sit down there let me look into my crystal ball thanks
close your eyes let me look through this uh uh the wallet of yours what you doing i see this
just leave the wall alone
i tell you what we're going to do we're going to go see thanks oh we don't need to go see him at all
here he comes right now you're gonna drink it here comes the man i wanted you to meet his name is
and you're about to meet shay or bob
don't say here he is what a disgusting body oh my god i'm gonna pass out from the fumes
i want a grotesque bucket
my pipe
some displayed it for you
we're done
water
you
drain
in your
Watch, fiend rifle.
Lawrence, could you please, could you please get down?
Demon sperm, my friend.
Are you a victim?
Are you a user of the demon sperm?
Are you addicted, my friend?
Are you lost in bondage to the demon sperm?
I saw them down by the riverfront.
Come on, now, you can tell an old preacher.
They can't, and they can't do it, and they can't move their limbs anymore.
What about this demon?
They feed around disease.
Demon disease?
Most of them have eye problems.
Eye, eye, eye, eye, eye, this.
You know, they're egocentric.
Of course, they're the old wino bums.
Aye, aye, sir.
We make good use of them.
So Shanghai Willie, I mean, Shanghai Nelly.
Could you come and help me put some of this cottage cheese here on my pantyhose, child?
I'm going to touch nothing around there.
You know, great, great uncle grandma woman thing here needs help putting...
Hepace.
Help is here now.
Help is on its way.
Help is here and on its way.
Help is coming, friends.
In the form of a well-dressed businessman carrying a briefcase, smoking pipe, and wearing a great big grin on his face.
He's got something for you in that briefcase, my friend.
It's a little minister's card.
You never thought of yourself as minister, preacher, any kind of religious person.
Did you?
In fact, the last thing you ever saw yourself as was some kind of a holy man or holy babe.
I'll tell you what.
Maybe this is a different kind of holy man.
A hole in the head that we're talking about, friends.
They don't call it the church of the subgenius for nothing.
We're not picky.
It's not hard to qualify.
All you got to do is praise Bob.
Love Bob with all your heart, mind, soul.
Do whatever he says.
Chances are he's probably not even going to notice you there.
You'll just glean that luck power off.
You'll just be sapping some slack off Bob, won't you?
Yeah, sure.
It's easy.
Easy.
That's why everybody's doing it.
Everybody's doing it right now.
Everybody is doing it.
Right, buddy?
Right, pal?
That's right.
You're the only buddy pal right there not doing it yet.
You can't make it.
You can't make it real.
You can build your own ship.
You can make this right.
You can do it, man.
You can do it.
If you don't rock the band, you're in baby's mood.
A magic moment of resolution.
A grand relation, for sure.
A great...
You are waiting a moment of innocence.
I'm not doing it.
Everybody's doing it.
Doing it.
We have to go now.
Could you please, uh, could you please put your hand just a little bit further to the left?
Oh, I can't.
I'm using a spirit hand again.
Not a line.
Could you use a real, real electric hand?
It tastes like chicken.
Ah.
Oh.
It tastes...
It tastes like rattlesnake.
It tastes like...
I love you.
I love you, Mike.
Smell the sausage.
Yes, baby.
We're going back in time.
In fact, we're going back in time to when this show ends, and another show begins.
This is ten years after.
It's lot of fill more east in the background, friend.
And we're gonna slowly groove on outta here.
But Chaz will be back next Chaz week.
Chaz time and Chaz channel.
And Dave is still here.
So Scott-
Wait.
You will be backstage next week?
Oh my God.
We'll be back in a lot better physical condition than we were this week.
We're going to come back from the therapist.
We're going to have to really solve some problems,
not just diddling our times away eating those weird cinnamon bites you're hanging.
But that said, we're going to really find out what's making it tick.
And then once we pronounce ourselves deaf,
we'll be ready to solve all the problems it's created for me.
Oh, the son of a bitch.
I wish I knew who my mind controller was.
I wish I knew who was pushing my click on the off and clicking off button.
I wish I could get out of this terrible suitcase.
Bob Dogs, indeed.
I don't know how much longer I can take in Bob's suitcase.
I don't know.
With marijuana in your brain.
Oh, you smoke a dog.
Hear me knocking upon your door.
But you can't move no more.
You're stoned.
Yo, yeah.
Y'all know what time it is.
It's a good time.
If you need more information about the Church of the Subgenius,
please write to this address I'm about to give.
That's Bob at Post Office Box 140306 Dallas, Texas 75214.
Once again, that's Box 140306 Dallas, Texas 75214.
www.subgenius.com.
And praise the...