🎵
Remember, remember, remember, remember
You need me, and I have come
Hi Bob
Yeah
Bob, Bob
Bob
Bob, Bob, Bob
Yes sir, I like subgenius
No sir, I don't like pink boys
Yes sir, I love Bob
No sir
No sir, I do not want to stop Bob
I want Bob in every tree
I just want to give my feast to the thousands
In every flower, in every bee, in every leaf, in every twig
In every cow, in every pig
I want Bob deep fried and deep freezed
I want to feel him in the breeze
I want to see him in the sky
I hope his fight will catch me
Dear Bob who floats above the ground
I long to hear the mournful sound
That's made when you emerge from space
And come to this, my dwelling
Dear Bob, each night while I'm asleep
I hope to my house you will creep
And poke your pipe in through the wall
So I'll be burned, remembering all
Dear Bob, it's time to close my eyes
Remember now, it's no surprise
If I should be found dead someday
I'll think that you were in the way
Oh, gimme Bob
Confusing that face
With my own
Can't remember my place
You are about to experience the awe and mystery
Which reaches from the inner mind to
The subgenius hour of slack
Bob's role on this planet
Is to see that the earth is not sold
On that glorious or terrible day
We call X-Day in 1998
When the men from Planet X arrive
Yeah, now it may sound ludicrous
It may sound ridiculous to many
It may sound impossible
Are you saying that all nuts, all those people
Maybe, yeah, maybe
Your brothers from the park of space
Are coming with advanced knowledge
To help
Superman
Bob will save all true believers though in 1998 right?
Actually Bob, if, you better hope that Bob does some wheeling and dealing for your soul come 1998
He is the salesman of the universe here to make sure that the earth and your soul does not get sold
To ah, to the robot mutilators
At least for not too low a price
So you better read that book with all three eyes or however many you have left
And leave the driving to Bob
That's right, you do the walking, let Bob do the talking
Who are these men from Planet X children?
What is waiting there for me?
Bob
Gosh
Ah, yes dear friends, well I guess this is one way to start a show
Jesus and Nick and Bob are here to help you out today
Bob and Nicky are here having a business meeting
Reverend Nicky Deathcheck
They're counting through hours of slack masters
Did some good, good prayer partner order a lot of backpipes?
How many?
Several of them, it's just we're about three months behind
Hey!
What that is a bunch of them
Ones that haven't even been made yet
Oh that's a, those are good choices
The 587, I can't wait to hear that one.
589?
That'll be the...
589 is gonna be the greatest, man.
This one, we are on hour of slack number 584, folks.
Incidentally, 382 days to X-Day, the end of the world.
And we've determined that there will never be an hour of slack number 666
unless we continue to do them on the escape vessels,
but I don't see much point in that.
Someone else?
You might as well come on in.
We got the whole crew in here.
I've just started doing the radio show.
I thought, well, heck, we got all these big minions in here,
sort of rummaging through tapes of shows.
Of all the shows, people actually buy copies of this show.
Folks, I've got a stacked and packed show.
Several of those bands came out with new CDs.
Zug's Rift has a new album out.
And friends, you know something?
Five big bands.
A billion pinheads.
Can't be wrong.
That's the name of the album.
And...
I work on the retard bar
Where blind compliance keeps me from harm
There's only so many hours a day
But I have to sell them to get me my pay
I work on the retard bar
guitar solo
Putting this thing over there
Doing this, doing that
I do the same thing every day
Man, I got it down
I work and I work
But I can't get ahead
Live all this time
Living like a better off dead
I work on the retard farm
I know a guy
You can call me
I know a guy who refuses to buy it
He never goes to work out and then to try it
But he's always broke and can't go on a diet
There's hell to pay if you try to defy it
I work on the retard farm
Yes I do
And friends, you know something?
Five billion pinheads can't be wrong.
That's the name of the album.
And the guys that used to do Silica Gel
have two new Noise albums out.
We have The Truth About the Greys
which we will be revealing.
The Greys and Jesus, by the way.
We're going to go ahead and tell them about that, Lord.
See, he doesn't even think of it.
He's paying attention to filling your orders, dear friend.
We've got Heba Phreniatrix.
We've got the KPFA show.
We've got more Suzy the Flusie's Apocalypse
Saturday night collection.
We've got more Stupid Apocalypse
and thrift store music from Yeti's for Bob.
And we have Slack Jeopardy!
recordings of the subgenius trivia game show
from our Dallas Clinch meeting.
Friends, here in Dallas
we've been holding monthly meetings
only not in a church.
It's in a bar.
Well, we just...
The bar just got sold to somebody else
so we're going to have to do them
in another venue.
But we do prefer bars.
We do prefer bars.
We may start mixing
Hour of Slack live at those.
And I've got so much X Day music.
By the time you hear this
we're going to be in Sherman, New York
at Brushwood Campground.
Not the Rainbow Gathering.
It's not the Rainbow...
Yeah, we're going to...
We're just going to drive on past this time.
Yes, friends.
We're going to be...
The All Naked Baptisms
will be practicing
for the next few days.
For the...
For the pure pleasure
that awaits us
on the actual X Day
which of course
is not this year
on July 5th, 1997
but next year
on July 5th
when we...
Well, you've heard the...
You've heard the...
You've heard that routine.
If you haven't sent us
your love offering
and become a minister
in this church
you're going to fry
while
we...
escape.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ooh.
Friend, the elder gods
have been sleeping
but they're waking up.
And you've got to find that word of Bob
before it's too late.
Before 1998, July 5th,
the end of the world,
the end of time as we know it.
When the very...
The very...
The score is racked up.
The score is racked up
and it's the time and a half time.
Yes, sir.
We just won't have a chance.
They'll be able to have their ways with us.
You've heard about the smallpox blankets
and the Indians, you know.
Well, this is going to be...
technological viral infectation
of an entire planet
with means of doing things
and means of destruction,
means of alteration
of genetic patterns,
means of controlling people's minds
that we don't even...
To us, it's magic.
Any significantly advanced form of science
becomes magic.
If that smoke comes out of Bob's pipe no more,
then we shall be reduced
to that can of warm beer
under the bed of a hungover elder god
at 11.30 on a Sunday morning.
Bob is here to make sure
that instead of it being a bomb,
it's the end of the world.
It's the end of their world.
And the new...
The new Jerusalem.
The new Jerusalem where slack begins.
Yes, dear friends.
Oh, former subgenius Pastor Buck Naked
there with G. Gordon Gordon.
Oh, God.
That was so many long years ago.
Oh, yes.
And yes, friends,
and slack does begin somewhere, somehow.
And I'm gonna lay some slack on you right now.
This is a song that's not by a subgenius band,
and it's not about Bob.
I just like this song.
Let me tell you about a girl I know
Had a drink about an hour ago
Sitting in the corner by herself
In a bar in downtown hell
She heard a noise as she looked through the door
And saw a man she'd never seen before
Light skin, light blue eyes
A double chin and a plastic smile
Well, her heart erased as he walked in the door
And took an empty seat next to her at the bar
My brand new car is parked right outside
Had you lied to go for the ride
And she said, wait a minute
I have to think
He said, that's fine
May I please buy you a drink?
One drink turned into three or four
And then that thing got into his car
And they drove away someplace for fun
Now, babe, the time has come
How'd you like to have a little fun?
And she said, if we could only pace beyond our way
I would not run
That's when things got out of control
She didn't want to
He had his way
She said, let's go
He said, no way
Come on, babe, it's your lucky day
Shut your mouth, we're gonna do it my way
Come on, baby, don't be afraid
If it wasn't for date rape, I'd never get laid
He finished up and he started the car
He turned around and drove back to the bar
He said, no, baby, don't be sad
In my opinion, you weren't half bad
She picked up a rock, threw it in the car
Hit him in the head, now he's got a big scar
Come on, party people, she'll listen to me
Date rape, stylee!
The next day, she went to her drawer
Looked up her local attorney at law
Went to the phone and filed a police report
And then she took the guy's ass to court
Well, the day he stood in front of the judge
He screamed, she lies, that little slut!
The judge knew he was full of sh**
And he gave him 25 years
And now his heart is filled with tears
One night in jail, it was getting late
He was butt raped by a large inmate
And he screamed
But the guards paid no attention to his cries
That's when things got out of control
The moral of the date-wretch story
It does not pay to be drunk and horny
But that's the way it had to be
They locked him up and threw away the keys
But I can't take pity on men of his kind
Even though he now takes it in the behind
That's the way it had to be
They locked him up and threw away the keys
But I can't take pity on men of his kind
Even though he now takes it in the behind
Date rape!
DAVID
Roman
David
the Church of the Subgenius or anything, but it's a good vengeance song because the bad pink boy
gets his just desserts in the end, one might say. That's Sublime, the band called Sublime,
from their older album 40 Ounces to Freedom, which has a Dobbs head printed on the CD itself.
Yes, friends, and what we're listening to in the background here is the Potatoes
from Dallas, Texas, doing that old Nino Rota theme from Eight and a Half. And friends,
we've got some sounds coming up. I hope you have your headphones on. And if you're listening by
internet, it ain't going to do you a whole lot of good because we broadcast that in mono. But
really, I've got some, you know, we like negative land around here.
And there is a band out of Raleigh, North Carolina that used to be called Silicon,
Cajal. They have two new CDs out under the name Polycarp. And what's the other one?
Anyway, they're from Wifflefish, Racco. Beatless. Beatless is the other one. And they do sound
effects music. Friends, I love sound effects music. It's not really music. It's just sounds.
But I like the sounds of prying things. So let's,
let the potatoes finish up here and then we'll go into some pure audio slack.
Ah, yes.
.
I'm sorry.
It's a sunny day.
And I wouldn't have it any other way.
It's a beautiful day.
And I just want to go out to play.
But you know when I'm feeling good.
I just want a piece of you.
It's a beautiful day.
And I don't care what the big boys say.
With a little bit of color in mind.
Make it.
Just all the time.
But you know when I'm feeling blue.
I just want a piece of you.
What can you do?
Just a piece of you.
What is a.
A poor girl to choose.
When I call you up.
When I dial you up.
Oh, you just.
Say you love me.
But you know.
When I'm feeling blue.
I just want.
A piece of.
You.
A piece of you.
uh yes dear friends um polycarp the name of that band and i'm about to give you a couple of
addresses so get that pencil ready an address for zoogs rift and an address for uh polycarp or
whiffle fist actually okay whiffle whiffle fist is the record company that creates
um this uh polycarp stuff and their address is once again one word whiffle fist
p.o box three three five six one
that's box three three five six one raleigh north carolina two seven six three six
that zip once again two seven six three six um or you can web them at www.whifflefist.com
uh zoogs rift machinery is available from
avt
records p.o box 24 0 36 that's p.o box 24036
sounds sort of familiar uh hilton head island south carolina
two nine nine two five two nine nine two five for avt records p.o box 24 036
hilton head island south carolina or um you can uh check out uh for promotional information and
so forth you can contact zoogs himself at p.o box one eight seven six five and cno california
nine one four one six
uh
dear friends
now
we'll go back
to uh
delving into
to x-day
tapes
and uh
on side two
i think we will get into the truth
about the grays
uh
thank you
especially if you got a white copy
now if you got a white copy and a brown copy
it's a little bit of difference
but they're both worth more
than a bundle of thousand dollar treasury bills
a foot high
room full of bills
there will be people trading paragraphs
of that pamphlet
for box cars
full of food
we think it will replace currency
tracing
bob will replace drugs
religion
rock music
and everything
in a great paradise
of unrestrained sales
unrestrained um
slack and sex
and if you have any drug users in your audience
we should note that the book of the subgenius
we found in a test
that was conducted in austin recently
that if adulterated street drugs are thrown on top of the cover
all of the uh
non-narcotic qualities are completely erased
and uh
indicated uh
as negative
and or
All impurities are destroyed.
All impurities are removed, giving you that 1% of pure that you paid for
out of whatever it was that you were...
By the way...
That's better than pyramid power.
Yes, much better than pyramid power.
I'd like to say those...
Because it's in a plane rather than going to a point.
Book of the subgenius. That's it.
Book of the subgenius.
Come to fellow, everyone knows.
Bob.
Bob!
Yes, Bob.
Hey, man.
That is one thing.
Who is it?
One strange dude.
I think Bob is just the guy with the pipe.
Oh, that's crazy talk.
You hand him that pamphlet.
Oh, friends, the scales fall from their eyes.
But you know, when those pink boys discover Bob,
it's either truth or death.
For the love of Bob can kill normals, friends, yes?
Yes, but Bob's men are moving on this planet.
Oh, that planetary alignment that came up.
The Jupiter effect.
Oh, I'm now sure that may have caused earthquakes.
And volcanoes and the Earth to tilt on its axis.
And men will, in the end times to come,
men will gnash their brains and think backwards.
Dead Christians will come up from their graves
shambling and rotting like not of the living dead.
But through it all, helping to profit from it all
is that one mighty link between heaven and earth.
That Bob.
Oh, yeah, I can see it now.
The miracle of the Bob world is unfolding.
They're wading up to their knees in blood, dear friends.
But it's the blood of the baptism of a mighty fist.
Face of Bob.
That face that can pile through eight-foot-thick titanium steel
conspiracy fork-knock stores with that mighty pipe.
Oh, he ain't from another planet.
He ain't something we have to bow down and kiss to.
He's a man.
Oh, well, you can pull Bob's leg and he'll laugh right along with you
because Bob, he's been a fool just like you and me.
Bob's been a pathetic fool.
And I tell you what, that J.R. Bob Dobbs will be a fool again.
He's a fool today.
He's a fool tomorrow because he's the same Bob.
He's always the same Bob and he's working for you and me.
Well, do you guys have anything to say to the prayer partners
out there listening to the radio?
Well, you guys are just full of you.
This is just such a slack-filled.
Listen to these wild partying.
We're going to take our party downstairs.
Yeah, man.
You're not invited.
I don't want to.
This is very frequently the case, folks.
I'm up here working.
He's boring.
For Bob.
And these babes and the Lord are down there frolicking.
And actually, they're not.
I'm partying.
I'm the one who's partying.
You guys are shuffling through tapes and trying to fill orders.
I guess somebody's...
Don't give me that kind of look.
Someone has to have slack.
Yeah.
That's right.
Hey, this is my idea of slack.
Trying to get me hooked on Bryce.
Yeah, I'm just trying to get...
I just started...
I gave her a quick run-through on the 3D computer program so that she would be...
It's like first...
That's right.
First hits free.
Yeah, I gave her a bunch of programs.
Here, these are free.
You just go ahead and take these, Nikki.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
It's loads of fun.
Next time.
Yeah.
Next time she's going to be going,
you wouldn't happen to have a copy of Ray Dream Designer, would you?
I mean, I'd be willing to pay you.
I can wait.
I've been in no hurry or anything.
It's like, he said he was going to come by and bring that program.
I've been waiting here.
We've been waiting for an hour.
I'm sure he's going to have the stuff.
I hope something didn't happen to him.
He said he was going to have the stuff.
The proggies.
The connection was bad.
Huh?
He didn't have the connection.
Yeah, man.
Couldn't meet my connection.
Oh.
One, two, three, four.
You crashed.
Okay.
I'm out of here.
You promised.
You promised that all the time.
I'm going to go whack off the negative light.
I'll leave you to your self.
My reverence, thanks.
Leave me.
Leave me alone.
But I'm not alone, friends.
I'm with you.
Good God.
What in the name of sweet screaming Jesus is this world coming to?
People bitch.
People gripe.
This is a sign of the end times.
That's a sign of the end times.
When you should all be hollering, it's all a sign of the end times.
What, brothers and sisters, will happen to this heretic on July 5th, 1998?
Would anyone like to take a guess what's going to happen to this heretic when the saucers come?
Bring it!
He will be on the escape vessels on July 5th, 1998.
He will be on those saucers with the sex goddesses because he paid his $30 subgenius membership
fee.
He had his membership card in the church.
And even if you were to go out today and turn your back on Bob, forget that you ever heard
any of this, even if you were to go out tomorrow and get a job, maybe even as president of
the United States or a cop somewhere ripping apart people's cars searching for dope.
You would still be able to get on the pleasure saucers as long as you had that subgenius membership
card, as long as you paid for that subgenius membership card.
Can you say the same?
Can you say that you're going to be on those escape vessels on July 5th?
Do you think you're going to squeak by just because you're cool?
You think coolness is going to get you onto those space vessels?
Well, what are you going to do on X day?
When suddenly all of a sudden, you're going to be on those escape vessels.
All your paid in full subgenius buddies disappear.
Many people would say, well, I'm not going to join up with the church of the subgenius.
The church of the subgenius is an organization of non-joiners.
So I'm not going to join.
Well, I got a surprise for you folks.
You're not going to be joining this on X day either.
I'm not going to join.
One of my own pretending bobs beside me.
In the dark, his dots in pipe, they guide me.
Without Bob, I smell his frop around me,
and when I have no slack, I touch my gland and Bob has bound me.
On my journey to love, I have only one-way guard, we're taking you with us on our stay,
All the normals act like dumb shits. Without slack, the sweat runs down my armpits.
The next day, I'll see the saucers coming, and all I need is Bob and me forever and forever.
But until I spend my thirty bucks, I'm just ranting to myself and not to Bob.
And although I know that I am screwed, still I say, there's a day of pain.
I love Bob, but when the rapture's over, he'll be gone. The earth will be in ruins.
Without him, the world around me changes. The conspiracy is everywhere. The malls are full of pink boys.
I love Bob.
But every day, I don't spend that thirty bucks. I'm only just pretending.
Without me, Bob's world will go on burning. Our next day, Bob will have this life that I'll never know.
I love Bob.
Not only on my own.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Sivet Stang there, dear friends, my little dafter with her own song on Bob's own.
But now it is time for me to read some more to you from Silicon Valley.
Embrace by John Shirley, the science fiction novel which has embedded in it the truth about
the Greys, or the Zaytans, as they are called, as we continue here.
Certain strains of humanity developed, apparently spontaneously, a gene that had made them unusually
interactive with the ambient Iamton Continuum, with the sea of mind that intertwines quantum
probability and which can manipulate quantum probability and improbability.
They communed with this continuum and called it God.
The Zaytans have no natural capacity for this communing, this manipulation, this magic,
this grace.
And so they tried to experiment with humans and so forth, but the thing that activates
it is beyond the Greys, or the Zaytans, because they refuse to let the higher take part in
them.
The Zaytans have been controlling, but not controlled humanity in every particular, nor
wanted to.
A chance is always a necessary part of any long-term.
For centuries they would merely sit back and watch.
However, certain humans are telepathically sensitive.
And from time to time, the Zaytans influenced these certain humans through telepathic signals
sent from a transmitter which is hidden in space, past the orbit of the moon, a transmitter
corresponding in position to the star Sirius.
A small hidden moon.
The moon of Earth.
They influenced men to seek out those who carried this gene in human bloodlines, this
inherited proclivity for the apparently divine, and to refine it, develop it into a form they
could exploit.
They did this through, among other things, certain royal families in Europe, descended
from Joseph of Arimathea and Mary Magdalene, and Jesus himself.
Who fathered Magdalene's children after he escaped from Jerusalem.
He wasn't crucified.
Well, he was crucified, but he didn't actually die on the cross.
Jesus was active under other names in Rome and the Far East afterwards.
The Zaytans tried to keep these sacred families in power so as to protect this special DNA
through a variety of human organizations.
For example, the Priory of the Holy Cross.
The Priory of Zion.
An ancient and secret organization of which Dr. Le Guim was a member.
In fact, Le Guim was an initiated member of a series of interlinked secret orders culminating
in a certain arch-Masonic cult wherein he was initiated of the 23rd degree of the order
which underlay all orders which formed MJ15 at the behest of the Zaytans, but you know,
friends many organizations.
They were supposed to work for their own purposes.
Like the P2, the True Knights of Malta, and of course the MJ12, and even the Chinese Tong.
All of these were in fact working for agents of the Greys, the Zaytans.
It was always easier to use human resources for building bases and so forth than to import
resources from Zeta Reticuli, and it was easier to buy these resources here than to endlessly
have to commandeer them.
So money was needed, secret bank accounts and deals with drug dealers and the CIA and
the Vatican were needed.
Yes, dear friends, some of the truth, the hidden truth there from John Shirley's hardcover
sci-fi book, Silicon Embrace.
Pick up on it, man.
Do it.
You must.
And now, well I don't...
I don't know.
OK, I'm going to do it.
Friends, here is a recording...
of my...
wife.
I have to tell you a story about a man named John.
He could barely keep his family fun.
So?
He went out one day to hunt.
And he saw these giant pigeons.
footprints. He could sit in them. They were about a foot deep and he wondered where they came from.
Did a monster really come by or was someone playing a big joke on him? If he could find that monster
he'd be able to eat all that monster and feed it to his family for a long time to come.
So he started looking for the monster following the tracks up and down the hills
and into the valleys. He even found some of the monster's scat.
I really like them. I love them, the scat. He found rat bones and deer bones.
And was able to
and was able to
symbol an entire skeleton of a wolf.
And I'm losing, I can't think of anything.
He took all the bones home to his family
to show them how the wolf was put together.
And the children went to the library
and found all kinds of books on wolves
and learned all the names of the bones in the wolf's body.
But they died of starvation
because Jeff never found the monster
and could not keep his family fed.
The end.
That is an anxiety-producing term.
You gotta do, you gotta learn one word.
And the word is...
Wee!
Since we have a priest among us,
perhaps he would like to comment on this subject.
Lie on the floor, arms at your side.
Now hold the legs very straight and point the toes.
And if one
Thedle talalk too,
de thính mèdite xì?
xì!
It's a record of all my favorite songs!
White boys are so pretty.
Remember kids, I am your friend.
To many of us, that is an anxiety-producing term.
Oh, I get the idea.
Ouch!
Oh yeah!
By now, most of you women in the audience are saying to yourselves,
how can I meet the love god?
What can you do that's fantastic?
Bizarre.
Oh, boy.
Boy, I'm plumb tuckered out.
Was it a rug or was it something else?
What was the floor like?
This, as recreated from a court transcript,
is what testifying was like for a nine-year-old girl we'll call sodomized,
raped, injected with drugs, and physically abused.
She was a victim of a nine-year-old girl we'll call Shelly.
During the trial, she and her sister received death threats from her mother and grandmother.
For their protection, the girls were separated from their father,
who was placed in protective custody.
UCLA psychiatrist Spencer,
can be enough to trigger a severe emotional reaction.
Did anybody put their privates in your bottom?
Okay.
Would you tell me, please, which way I ought to walk from here?
That depends.
Go to your lawn where you want to get to.
I don't much care where.
Then it...
It doesn't matter which way you walk.
No, no.
So long as I get somewhere.
Oh.
You're sure to do that?
If you only walk long enough.
But I don't want to go among mad people.
Oh, you can't help that.
We're all mad here.
I'm mad.
And you're mad.
How do you know?
How do you know I'm mad?
Well, you must be.
Or else, you wouldn't have come here.
We're all mad.
I tell you, we're all mad.
You're mad.
And I'm mad.
And everyone here is mad.
We're all mad.
I tell you.
I'm mad.
You're mad.
Stay tuned for the adventures of Ace Budlow, Psychotic Detective.
As the Duke of Madness radio program continues.
Now, this caller was there a couple of times, Dave.
With us.
What?
Spiritually.
Not you, but you can be with us now.
Not you, no.
By drinking the radio beer that's in front of you.
Authorized to blaspheme by the gods themselves.
But the other caller that's kissing you in your little caller ear there, that guy was with us.
Incompatible with all major world religions.
All right, there we go.
Okay.
Now, this caller kind of feels the way I did in the desert.
As I told Reverend Hal.
Hey, did you get to the desert?
Did you make it out there?
Oh, I didn't tell you what happened?
Sure.
No, no, what happened?
Pretend I'm pretty happy, you know?
Yeah, okay.
Just pretend.
When you guys go up to the clubhouse and start dropping anvils on people.
Yeah.
It's sort of like.
Okay, there goes one.
Hal's launching those anvils on an old catapult.
That's right.
If it stays together, I'll try a third one.
Oh, there goes another one.
Right on the little caller.
And welcome back to Slack.
Jeff, what's up?
I'm a celebrity.
Where are the scores are?
Matt, 400.
Holly, 400.
Shelby, 300.
Man, I can't believe I was there.
And Holly, I mean, Shelby, you have control of the board.
World leaders.
World leaders for 400.
And the answer is cousin of Mickey Gilly, Jerry Lee Lewis.
This preacher was caught with a hoe Bob Dobbs wouldn't sleep with.
You know who it is?
Shelby buzzes in.
Hey, hey, hey.
Jimmy Swagger.
Jimmy Swagger is correct.
Four, 400.
Oh, my gosh.
400.
Slack points.
Shelby jumps out and leaves with 700 points.
And Shelby, you have control of the board.
Control it, baby.
Go.
Let's see.
We haven't done any of the subgenius stuff, have we?
Subgenius, gods, and saints.
Four?
I don't know.
What is it?
I don't play with 100.
You can go 100 to 500.
100, I guess.
Subgenius, gods, and saints for 100.
And the answer is?
Something has happened in the motor show.
All being of Time, Space, and Dimension, who took up salesman J.R. Bob Dobbs to fill
the Messiah.
Oh, come on, guys.
What is it?
He didn't hear it.
All being of Time, Space, and Dimension, who took up salesman J.R. Bob Dobbs to be the
Messiah.
Uh-oh.
I don't want to hear it.
Shelby.
The Exes?
And Reverend May.
Wait, wait.
I beep first.
Is that terrible?
Jehovah One.
Who is Jehovah One?
Holly beeps in with Jehovah One.
Jehovah One is correct for 100.
Slack points.
I would have gotten it wrong anyway.
I would have said, vote.
I would have said, vote, team.
And Holly, you have control of the board.
Oh, that's early pamphlet boy.
Oh, let's go with whatever's next in the music scene.
200, 300, whatever's next.
The music scene for 200, and the answer is Shock Metal Band, who has joined the
Subgenius Foundation in their own war against a conspiracy.
Reverend Matt.
Who am Gwar?
Gwar is correct for 200 slack points.
Who dies?
Who chats?
You.
Like I said, you can rat my name.
I hate murder.
Yeah, like a piece of Energie.
To the slaughter
What are you going to do?
What will be your habitat?
When we get done with you
Are you gonna cry for your mama?
Or are you gonna have a good time?
Are you gonna be a bohab?
When it's your turn to die
The dog is playing the crazy
Dread them all around
Anarchy
Chaos
Rural streets
It's a randorock party town
Your pain isn't turning your brain
It isn't burning in your sanitation
So why hide?
The final hour's here, now wrap your thermal beer
You're only king for one time
Come on and get the job, we're gonna have some fun
Nothing else to lose
Breaking all the rules
The only really winning device
Is all the sinning, sinning feels so fine
You're running out of time
Ashes to ashes
And
That's the nut
It's always one hell of a party
When Ragnarok rolls around
Ragnarok is low, Ragnarok is low
It's time to trash the planet
Ragnarok and man, no ground
Ragnarok is low, Ragnarok is low
Welcome to Valhalla
Do not be afraid
Now you are a
Zombie
And all your friends are dead
It all gets rarer than awesome
When you get backstage
Everybody takes a grounder
I hope you're undressed
Hey
With a jump alone
You're failing, finding out
And you wanna have one more time
Looking for a lover, no need a world
Have a ride, a rock and roll, roll by
You're only by somebody
Against the milly bloody
Feeling then I'm talking, feeling then I'm joking
Floating like a bomb
Now you're running out of time
Dust
To dust
And the church of the subgenius
Send a self address stamped envelope to
Got your pencil ready?
Bob, P.O. Box 140306
Dallas Texas 75214
That's Bob
P.O. Box 140306
Dallas T bef
Stay tuned and
Praise! Bob
Yeah praise Bob man
Friends stay tuned
For uh gelato
July 5th, 1998.
It seems like everybody's trying to get in on the act.
This is Soundgarden.
Soundgarden
Once asleep but now I stand
And I still remember your sweet everything
Light a Roman candle
And hold it in your hand
Cause it hit it in the wind
And I saw it in the sky
And I thought it was the end
I thought it was the fourth of July
Hit it in the wind
And I saw it in the sky
And I thought it was the end
I thought it was the fourth of July
Hit it in the wind
And I thought it was the fifth of July
And I thought it was the sixth of July
Hit it in the wind