Dear friends, stay tuned for the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack, number 1,465.
The program you are about to hear, Bob's Slacktime Funhouse, is parody, satire, and comedy.
Any reference to Bob, the Church of the Subgenius, religion, politics, or any other touchy subjects is intended only as humor,
and should cast no reflection on the high standards of WREK Atlanta, its staff, or that of Georgia Tech.
Or WCSB Cleveland, for that matter.
Oh, the show. What are we going to do?
Let the joy jump in the good times roll. Let the pleasure pop. Now let's take a stroll.
Light up. Let's all get...
Melon. Light up. You're smoking your eyes. Light up. Get hip, I say, fella. Light up.
Say, what is this job? Light up. Let's all get ready. Light up. I know how you feel. Light up.
Now don't be afraid of you. Find what I mean in any old field.
Pop. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7.
Slow. 8, 9, 10, and then 11.
Closer. Now get your day going.
Lays up. I'm saying that's the thing.
Light up. Don't let that man get you. Just pop on your seat and get blown to smoke, man.
Music.
Friends, this hour of Slack is most, well, the first third or so will be from Reverend Susie the Flusie's Bob Slack Time Funhouse,
an episode that was a Bob Dobbs special.
Music.
Originally broadcast on beautiful WREK Atlanta.
But we'll be back with Lonesome Cowboy Dave soon enough.
First, the collaging of that crazy collage-y-ass Reverend Susie the Flusie.
By the way, what does Jack the Ripper have in common with Susie the Flusie?
I don't know. What does Jack the Ripper have in common with Susie the Flusie?
V.
I may not change my underwear, but I'm changing my ways.
Oh, there hasn't been a whole lot of Bob in the Slack Time Funhouse lately.
But now it's battle stations and full speed ahead Slack.
Ooh, with the size tension here.
Whew.
God, it's the reek of future.
Future death zooming down on us.
This isn't the time to be lulled into warm complacency.
Oh, the end times have checked in and they've left an early wake-up call.
What does it take to convince you of the signs of the end times anyway?
Oh.
Think you'll be able to hang on to your precious Slack now?
You don't have enough Slack to go around now.
And they're going to take even that little.
I've been away.
Good Lord.
Name me one friend you've got left, he said.
Bob, I said.
This was the only lifer in the prison.
The only American to have been convicted of treason during the Korean War.
He was the chief clerk in the supply room where I would soon be given my civilian clothes.
He was a science fiction writer of some note, publishing many stories a year under various pseudonyms, including Frank X. Barlow and Kilgore Trout.
Somebody said, oh, Mr. 666 is way off in the future.
No, my dear friend, he's been around a while.
And he's here tonight.
He's here tonight on the face of the earth.
And all the world is wondering after him.
And that's why this subject is so important.
The deceptions are all around us.
Deceptions are saying it's off in the future.
It's off in the future.
Don't worry about it.
We better start worrying about it.
And friends, there are some things taking place around us that's going to come down very, very soon.
Are you ready for it?
I tell you, we're living in serious time.
Look at the signs before basic food groups have been replaced with a pyramid.
Isn't that enough to tip you off?
Look at the signs.
The new Blue Star ointment commercial no longer mentions tether.
I don't even know what tether is.
And they took it away from me.
Look at the signs.
We think we're okay in our little shells minding our own business, standing on the corner of walk and don't walk.
But, Seekers, it's time to run.
Quick.
It's not too late.
We got to get some Bob into us.
Bad.
Oh, even if it hurts.
Oh.
It will.
Oh, it's time to read some beads until it bleeds.
The only sensitivity I care about is nerve endings.
Are you yeti enough to test yours?
So welcome, friends, to Reverend Commandant Susie Darflusie's Boot Camp for Bob.
Today is the first day of your last hurrah.
Hey, you, pink boy.
Drop and give me 20, mister.
The rest of you, you'll have to suffer through these Bob songs and don't think you're getting off easy.
The hell is just beginning.
Ah, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
She says things I would not dare to articulate.
But I'll simply say this.
If that is true, why so many of them get injured in the very act?
Why are some of them killed in the act?
And why do so many of them have to have colostomies?
Ah, good times.
You!
You're one of us!
Maybe you're one.
Something to be outright laughed at.
I heard someone over here say who's been the most effective evangelist the last 20 years.
His name is Bob.
And while, listen, listen, wait, listen, look at me.
Listen, wait, wait, wait.
While he entertains you, he indoctrinates you.
While he entertains you, he gets through to you.
While you laugh, you begin to lose automatically.
I met Bob when he came in.
When I came in the door to service today.
And Bob was formerly bound by the powers of darkness to a terrible degree.
Oh, whatever.
He says he gets a funny feeling down inside when he sees the Boy Scouts and the YMCA.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Ah!
And they were doing these crazy things.
Of course, that's just the start.
Thank goodness that, you know, nobody I knew was there because I thought,
Bobby, I'm never going to another one of these as long as I live.
I mean, you know, and he was a little nervous too when they grabbed his hands, you know.
It was like, this is not what we're used to.
What we learned a long time ago is that you become what the people you associate with.
And so he started associating with people in this business.
And I began to see the changes.
You know, Bobby was a good person and a good guy.
But I started seeing the change of staying away from the people that he was hanging around with
and looking forward to the future.
And so I started getting a glimpse of what this business had to offer.
So will all you goonie birds answering this description please stand up?
You misfits in this brave new age.
You dismally disorganized, improperly apologetic ghosts of the past.
Stand up.
Stand up and be counted.
And now it's time to bring up the headliner of the evening, a very special gentleman.
Please welcome to the stage, Bob.
Bob!
Last night my baby wanted to talk to me about art.
But I said no.
No.
Let's just close our eyes and watch.
Bob!
Hi, Bob.
I like to get mail, of course.
But for some reason, I get the strangest kind of mail.
And these are all real letters I'm reading you.
Every one I assure you has come in in the mail from someone I don't know.
To give you an idea of what the people think of the show and what they like to say in their communications.
Dear Bob, before I tuned in your program, I could never get my husband out of bed in the morning.
Now he can't get out of the house fast enough.
Why don't you give up?
Why can't you act like normal people?
Why don't you stop whistling?
Why don't you stop acting like a moron?
Or maybe you aren't acting.
Yes.
That's all I'm taking from you.
Get back here, you jackal!
He's gone!
Ah, old slack magic has me in its spell!
Mmm.
Oh, it's hard sometimes, howling and bumping and grinding in the radio wilderness.
Trying to sow my little seeds of slack on hundreds of sweaty strangers in the dark.
Oh, while the city sleeps around, I'm lighting up your dials with the power of Bob.
When I tell people I have a show called Bob's Black Time Funhouse,
they often say, who's Bob?
Well, that certainly separates a wheat from a chaff now, doesn't it?
Oh, I like to think that you all know Bob,
at least those of you who matter.
But don't fool yourself into thinking that that puts you any higher up in the food web because of it.
Oh, yeah, here at the funhouse, it seems like we've lost our grip on Bob.
We gotta latch onto his pipe and pull him down off the ceiling and bump his stomach
and get him into fight and trim because he's our only hope.
Oh, I want you to get to know Bob personally.
If you don't already, those of you who don't know Bob,
my heart sings like...
The prairie squid and rutting season for you,
the joy you're about to experience.
Oh, and those of you who've forgotten Bob,
fie, fie upon thee.
Wake up.
It's time to cover your ass, kids.
Don't be a pink boy.
Pinks are like sponges that don't work.
You, you subgenius, Todd.
Yeah.
You, on the other hand,
soak in this.
I want to give you...
I want to give you a close encounter with Bob and his amazing life,
his precocious youth,
his early careers in sports and salesmanship,
and his hot, hot linkage with Connie, his first and primary wife.
And all through the wonders of our patented sub-g-liminal
hypnognostic brain-ventilating system.
I want you to take the fronts off of your speaker-seekers.
There.
Yeah, now...
Now, put your head in the speaker cone.
No, no, no, not, not that one, the big one.
Yeah.
Okay, reach over.
Yeah, you can still barely reach now.
Turn that dial up to 11.
Or lethal, if you have it.
And I want you to feel the slack
pouring over you like drug tapping,
saturating you with pure wobbling.
Meanwhile...
Ah!
Just match up your pain meters a little bit.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Once upon a time, there was Bobby.
Bobby was a boy who drank milk.
He drank milk in the morning, he drank milk at noon,
he drank milk before he went to bed.
And where do you think all that milk came from?
Well, that milk had a long journey.
For once upon a time, there was Bobby,
and once upon a time, there also was...
Do you hear them?
Yes, there also were five cows,
five cows, five cows.
They didn't like to wait,
but came and moved at the farmer's gate.
Five big cows.
The farmer came when he heard them call
and led each one into her stall.
Now I must milk them one and all
to get the milk for Bobby.
The five cows were Daisy,
and Squirrel, and Queen, and Lady, and Buttercup.
When they were in the barn,
the farmer took his stool and big pail
and sat down to milk.
Squirt, squirt, the milk poured into the pail.
And when the five cows had given all their milk,
the farmer let the cows wander out of the barn
and into the pasture again.
There they ate the green grass
and forgot all about the milk.
But the milk had only just begun its journey.
For once upon a time, there was Bobby,
and once upon a time, there also was...
Do you hear it?
Yes, there also...
There was a wagon, a wagon,
with a horse, rubber shoes, a clock.
Each time he started, each time he stopped.
A milk wagon.
And the milkman said,
My work is done before most other work's begun.
From house to house I hurry on
to bring the milk to Bobby.
The milk wagon came down the street
until it stopped at Bobby's house.
The driver jumped out and put down the bottles
Bobby's mother had ordered.
Then he drove away and forgot all about the milk.
But the milk still went on with its journey.
For after the milkman went away,
Johnny's mother ran downstairs and opened the door.
There stood the milk bottles.
The milk from the cows who couldn't wait
But said moo moo at the farmer's gate
The milk in the truck that couldn't stand still
But went a-hawking down the hill
The milk on the train that carried the freight
And clickety-clackety couldn't be late
The milk where the factory whistle blew
And said now there is work to do
The milk that went where the horse could plop
Each time he started, each time he stopped
The milk from a bottle that opened up
And mother poured into Bobby's cup.
Don't call me Bobby.
The milk slipped and slid down Bobby's throat
And so turned into Bobby.
And so at last the milk ended its long, long journey.
Your commentator was privileged to visit
Space Platform 7 last week.
And before Cadet Bobby and Cadet Betty
Went into pre-lunar medical quarantine,
I interviewed them.
These telememory tapes will introduce you
To these two exceptional youngsters.
Cadet Bobby.
Don't call me Bobby.
Bob,
Are you and Betty worried at all
About your lunar adventure?
Not really, Doctor.
We've been thoroughly checked out
On our space shuttle craft.
And of course, adults have made thousands of such trips.
After all these years of research,
And training, I suppose it's
Really a great thrill.
It certainly is.
Bob, of course, studied 18 months longer than I.
Bob, where have you trained?
Well, I had calculus and logarithms
In elementary school in Washington, USA.
Then I spent one year
In the Space Flight Center
At Houston, USA.
Another year in Moscow
On advanced power and propulsion systems.
Six months in England
At the Academy of Celestial Navigation.
And then back to Houston for a year.
For advanced computer technology.
I had just about the same program.
Except for the fuels and propulsion.
The girls,
Just don't seem to take
To the engineering courses.
Well, you kids have spent
Six months here,
50,000 miles from Earth
On Space Station Number 7.
And now you are ready for the final
200,000 mile
Voyage to the Moon.
Goodbye.
And thanks to all of you.
For watching.
I hope you enjoyed the video.
And I'll see you in the next video.
Bye.
B
O
He said,
Do you know the story about Bob?
And I said, well, Coach, the only thing I can tell you
He looks like Mr. Clean.
I mean, he's the largest thing I've ever seen
Since a Big Mac truck.
He is about 225, 230 pounds.
Packs arms the size of my thighs.
A huge, huge man.
This is my friend and colleague,
Texan.
Howdy there.
I didn't catch your name, mister.
Bob.
About as big as a mountain.
90 feet high and 9 feet wide.
God, oh, man.
Like you might have played some football.
Wanna kill some elephants today, are we?
Ding, ding, ding.
Help.
Ha, ha, ha.
Why did Bob do that?
Bob knew what he wanted.
He made a plan.
And he stayed enthusiastic
Over several years.
I mean, I've read his interviews and his letters.
No, he's, you know, not retarded.
I mean, I've talked to the man
And he's pretty quick.
But for some reason,
You kind of get that impression sometimes.
I don't know, maybe he just like,
You know, when he goes into create,
It's like somebody, you know,
Playing a musical instrument
Or driving a car.
That kind of went into a thin state of retardedness
Where if they were neurotic,
Neurotically trying to, you know,
Do something.
Specifically,
You can't drive a car
If you're totally concentrating.
You'll go nuts.
It's like being, you know,
That's the way you are when you're learning to drive.
At the same time, he's kind of nuts.
I mean, he's kind of a nutty guy.
And eccentric.
I mean, he's not Hugh Beaumont.
He's definitely not Mr. Normal.
Then neither am I.
Put the car in here!
Someone, someone said that
To your native speaker
Let's consult with Dr.
AOC about a major issue
With pre-suggesting
Tendency issues at 9 to 9.
Dr. Sharon Parham speaks
So, what do you try to do?
Tibur is actually like this.
Just keep going until all things
stop and at their agencies
More assumed that of us
Her buddy's the Lymphnode Institute.
You can find that at subgenius.com if you push the radio page button.
And you can find copies of all of this show.
Well, not all of them.
Not the first 200.
But I think everything since then.
And we're on show number 1,465 this time.
Well.
And that was some really old stuff that Susie played there.
That was, in fact, the original of that cut of the man, the square man saying, Bob.
And it was the beginning of the end of Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
Dave!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
It's Dave!
It was.
I called on the regular land phone just to see what miracle might happen.
Because miraculously, this thing got healed somehow.
Well, then that is a first for this month.
A healing.
I'm really glad to hear of a healing for a change.
I'm real glad to hear of a healing.
Have there been many sickenings going on this month?
Let the healing continue.
Dave.
Let's see.
Since the last time I talked to you, I think we know two more close friends are in the hospital.
Oh, no.
In fact, as we left to drive to the station, our friend Reverend Pockets was Facebooking madly from the emergency ward.
Yes.
Somewhere in North Carolina where they rushed her for gallbladder problem or something like that.
And she was.
They've already given her her diluted or dilaudid or whatever.
Her pain drugs.
In an IV.
She called it the medicine water.
And she's sitting next to a guy, a gunshot wound victim, who's ranting and singing and laughing and crying.
And she just wishes that she could stream that to the Hour of Slack audience or YouTube or someplace.
Because she thinks it would go viral immediately.
She's probably okay because she's laughing and joking in the emergency room.
Thanks.
I think selfies are forbidden in the, especially humorous selfies are forbidden in the EM.
I think so, too.
Fascists.
Neo-Nazis.
CNN.
Scorpions.
Yeah.
High testosterone, slime berries, and other, I'm sorry.
Don't go, Dave.
It's not your fault.
And of course it's not.
You'd kind of want to take credit for it if it was.
Yeah, this is the special hospital's Hour of Slack, I guess.
Yes.
Or get out.
Get out of the hospital.
Get well and get out.
Princess, we had a chunk taken out of her head yesterday.
It happened to be a tooth, luckily, and not a permanent bone like the entire skull or the mandible.
Yes.
And that was an easy one.
Well, that sounds terrible, too.
I hate when teeth leave.
I had a tooth leave at a high school reunion, which is portentous, you know.
This is really great.
I hate people.
Yeah, I have to have young, strong teeth to eat that pizza.
I didn't tell you.
I don't know if I mentioned this to Princess Wee, but I've been getting emails about a
classmate of mine from 19, the class of 71 who croaked.
Oh.
It's just, well, I don't even remember the guy.
But I keep getting emails about it.
I didn't know anybody in my class.
I got a call from a bass player who I thought had a tooth.
I had died.
And that was the common rumor.
Oh man, that cat's dead.
That cat's dead.
Yeah.
He's like, .
He called you up and went .
Let's hope it's not the cat that I know that played with us at X Day once.
Let's hope not.
What?
In the Mondo Ricardo band, there was a bass player.
Let's hope it's not that one he's not talking about.
No, I certainly hope not.
No, I hope not.
I'm not talking about that.
I'm talking about the guy who played with us at the X Day.
Oh, that's good.
Very good.
No, you're talking about Charles of Rabbit's fame.
Right.
Yes, Jay.
Okay, so somebody's still alive.
That's good.
Yes, yes.
We're just somewhere now.
Thank goodness.
Well, what's weird, it's amazing that Dave is still alive, or me, or you for that matter.
Well, that's what we want.
And we revel in the amazement every day as we walk down the corridor looking at the other
patient so grim-faced and sleepy, baby.
We laugh and sing his song.
Oh, that's good.
It'll never happen to me.
And it, I'm sorry?
Dave, did you know that the first time I experienced an ophthalmic migraine or an optical
migraine, I was looking at you in the old station on Chaz's show, and you hear me in
the recording saying, suddenly I say, I think I drank too much coffee, you guys.
And what was happening was I was looking at your face, Dave, and it was disappearing.
Yes.
And your face was disappearing from the center, moving out.
Well, no, no, no.
That's not an ophthalmic or optometric migraine.
That's when little sparkles go around, make it look like an old-fashioned drive-in movie
type of that, or like a large flat-screen monitor.
Oh, yeah.
That goes on for 10 minutes like you're describing, although today I had it for about three hours.
I almost decided not to do the show.
That sounds like poop.
Because I was seeing the inside out.
Well, that's a good thing.
You know, the very first thing that you said about what it is, is, it's the Brian
Patterson story about the paramecium, or the Batman-Pow cartoon balloon with jaggy edges.
But, no, when the ophthalmic migraine begins, the very center of your vision, or maybe just
to one side—maybe Dave's nose, or left eye—begins to just, it's not there somehow.
And then the effect spreads to where the hole—
If you're talking about me, I say that all the time.
It's not fair.
But I've learned to accept things the way they are, that I have a perfect face for a radio.
And as far as things disappearing, we will attest to the fact that my face regularly does disappear, and you just won't accept it.
It's true.
You're like a hypochondriac.
His face does disappear sometimes.
Oh, Dave's face is disappearing.
I must be having a migraine.
No.
It could be that Dave's face just simply disappeared.
Exactly.
And that's what happens frequently.
The center does not hold.
Yeah, especially when the knobs are all too low.
And none of them go up to 12.
My feet smell.
Mis piedes es del bueno.
Or, that's the wrong word.
Ah, mis piedes.
Oh, never mind.
I think it's that we're large mammals and we're not getting younger.
But the center...
The scrub genius...
Well, what about time control, you scrub genius hypochondriac?
Time control.
Right.
Yeah, well, time control is when you go, I'm not even going to go in and do this show.
I'm just going to do a rerun.
Dang it.
It's not giving yourself a few more years somehow?
Right.
I'd be giving myself some more years.
But I'd have to make a new show sooner or later anyway.
Oh, my God.
And nobody's talking about the fact that you...
The reason why you're making less frequent appearances is because the last few times you've been showing up like Captain America and Daredevil and other kinds of weird costumes.
And then their faces disappear.
Like comic book stores during comic book week.
Hey, I'm Captain America, too.
I mean, the red, the rascally of anger.
I was always the red skull.
The thing...
I can't get those jobs anymore.
They're all going to younger folks.
But at least I'm not in the hospital like everybody else except you.
Thank goodness.
Like I said, Princess Wee, she was at the dentist's office yesterday, knocked out on some kind of narcotics.
I wish I'd had a recorder yesterday driving her home.
That would have been a show right there.
And I remember none of this.
None of this.
She doesn't remember driving home or being driven home.
I should have let her drive.
That would have been a YouTube viral, you know.
As long as you drive home the pathetic propaganda on a daily basis, that's how the elixir of life is squeezed out of a stone.
You just keep on BS-ing people until their eyes turn purple.
Or figure out some way of getting rid of all those figs you got laying around the backyard, if you know what I mean.
If only we could BS the disease out.
You know, if we could BS...
The sickness out.
Yeah.
The BS.
Maybe...
Yeah, she missed it out like a bad poor.
You know, sometimes the laying on of hands or sledgehammers can do that.
Philo used to teach the laying on of sledgehammers.
It was a diversion of pain sort of thing, you know.
Right.
He was a...
Philo's still a diversionist, isn't he?
Yes.
If you're...
For instance, if you had a headache, he would apply a thumb screw to your toe.
Or a toe screw to your thumb.
Did you just rename Philo and call him...
DeFilo?
DeFilo.
Lord DeFilo.
Was one of the names back when he was hanging around with Cagliostro and those other...
And Nostradingle.
Don't forget about that guy.
Yeah, Nostradingle.
The only one I shock at.
That's the only one that worked half the time.
The other times you're taking days without pay, you know.
Yeah.
One man's bummer is another man's beautiful thing.
Yep.
This is the life we live, compadres.
We run to the mountains.
Squirrels get dry or too hot or perhaps even too wet.
Other times we collect coconuts and give them to the peasants.
It is the life that we have chosen.
Well, there was a discussion on the Scrub Genius Forum about...
Well, it was Phineas Narco, yet another of our radio friends, said,
I wish people wouldn't say, I'm sending good vibes your way.
That irritated him because he doesn't believe in good vibes especially.
Because he's a sacrilegious woman with no eyes to see what he's doing.
A lot of people jumped in and said, yeah, I hate it when people say they're going to pray
for me or send me good vibes.
But a few of us, me included, said, well, actually, it can't hurt.
I don't believe in that stuff.
But by God, if I didn't wake up the other morning just praying my little heart out for
my sick friend in the hospital, I can't even remember which one it was.
Now, I'm going to go to the hospital.
I guess every morning I wake up going, oh, whatever.
I hope God does better.
It just happens naturally.
You can't help it.
You can't help it, but send good vibes.
If you're concerned about a friend, absolutely.
Yeah.
That's the real true religion right there.
And that's one thing that I think bothers a little bit of a frozen temple, you know.
Wow!
Man, that was great!
I'm going to turn on this Byron Leonard music in the background to get you to surrender.
go with that.
That was amazing.
I missed that
because I'm in a low,
I'm in an,
I'm invisible.
Wow.
What happened?
I wish we could do it again.
That was a cool sound effect.
I think he channeled
Bob just now.
No, I think he channeled
Negative Land,
actually,
maybe the web.
Oh, you channeled
Negative Land.
No,
Negative Land may be
in the background right now.
I'm not sure if this is
Rural War Room
or Thing-matic.
Thing-o-matic.
Mark Hostler's band.
Princess,
we was down at
Mark Hostler Street Fair.
Yes, I went to
Here in Cleveland,
they have a Hostler's.
I don't know if it was
worth the laugh after all.
Well,
the one thing I was going to say
about the praying
or sending good vibes and stuff,
it won't necessarily
do any harm
unless you let
the good vibe
and prayer sending
replace doing something.
If you could do something,
but instead you sit
on your butt going,
oh, Lord,
please go,
will you do the dirty work here
and drive over to the hospital
and visit my friend
because I really don't want to
because it makes me depressed
to go in a hospital,
but I'm praying for him.
Well, it seems to me...
Or if you go,
well, I could do
mouth-to-mouth resuscitation
or the Heimlich maneuver
on this dying person,
but I think I'll send
really good vibes their way instead
because I wouldn't want to
make a mistake and look stupid.
Or hurt them
instead of making them better.
Yeah, let's let them die
rather than be injured
by my crude CPR.
They change the rules on CPR
every week, you know.
What do you mean?
The way they make you push
on the chest
or blow in the mouth.
Well, if they're changing it
every week,
it must be very important now
that maybe perhaps
there's a lot of disingenuous
dingleberries riding the wind,
so to speak,
meaning that our aeroflora
and fauna
have captured
our very innards
and are leading us
to the waters of sticks.
Well, that plus
all the microbes
can evolve a lot faster
than we can make medicines,
so they're going to win anyway.
Well, I smelled the...
the diesel fuel-ish smell,
the kind of puffer dome-ish,
propane-ish smell
associated with large swaths
of nuclear lapazoids.
That means you're having...
And I wondered if I was just
smelling diesel in the air
or if...
Or if you were having
a nose-centric migraine.
Yeah.
Hallucinating smells.
Yeah, I was hoping I was,
you know,
because I was thinking,
Fukushima!
Well, they say it's still
floating around various places
like two or less or...
You know, it didn't go away
or anything,
and it's still coming, so...
Well, it would be carried
on the rain and the...
Oh, I see what you're saying.
Well, I think people should go
to the sub-genius site
and play Iodine-131
and Nuclear Boy.
Nuclear Boy.
Oh, did you see that video?
Yes.
That General Public made.
This guy took a...
a Fukushima cartoon
and put Dave's song with it.
Oh.
Fukimanga.
Oh, is that his dream?
Yeah.
Fukimanga anime.
I'm sorry.
There...
We went to see
one of those
Japanese disaster movies
just a couple of days ago.
It was called Godzilla,
the one they're advertising on TV.
Yeah, just like the other one,
Hiroshima and Nagasaki.
Those were funny, too.
Yeah, yeah.
It was...
Well, it's...
You know,
if the...
The photography's great.
It looks cool.
But, yeah,
that actually had
a lot of
very deliberate
visual references
to 9-11
and the...
the Christmas tsunami.
You know,
there were lots of
shots of
tidal waves
carrying cars down streets.
And, of course,
they were caused by
monsters the size of
medium-sized towns.
That was pretty cool.
Well, you know,
in the media,
people are conning you.
They used to, you know,
pictures of cars
submerged on streets
and stuff like that.
But I dare say,
in a picky-lo-peek-o
tiny-lilly-teeny-tiny voice,
that such things
are becoming
a little bit
more...
every day.
Well, there are
a lot of movies
with cars underwater
in them,
that's for sure.
That is true.
What about
Namor of the Deep?
He drove a rocket 88
until he took a sleep.
They haven't done
that movie yet.
What they told me
when I was a baby boy,
now I'm 75.
Hoi, hoi.
Ah, hoi, hoi.
I'm not really
spending my time
searching how it feels
like to help
everybody else
who's not dead, too.
Are we even alive?
Do we really know?
Are we in the Matrix?
Did X-Day actually happen
in what we thought
was 1998?
And it was 1998,
and now we're in a jar.
Thinking we're
in a radio station.
What's the difference?
None.
There's no difference.
No, I agree completely.
I think that what has happened
is, you know,
since everything's a product
of your own perception,
as the yogis would say,
the mind creates the world,
the...
Until you stub your toe.
Yeah.
And you go,
I didn't freaking do that.
I really didn't.
I didn't do it.
I didn't create that.
I didn't build that.
I didn't build that thing
that stubbed my toe.
That's when you start to...
I didn't build that stubbing.
It's not fair.
Not fair.
Fair is where you take your pig
and hope you win a prize.
Stubbed toes and...
and, uh...
three-day-old fish
usually are what lead people
to conventional relations.
You know,
minor catastrophes
make them go,
uh, it's just not perfect.
Well, we call that involuntary.
I don't find that a perfection.
It's, uh...
We call that involuntary slack.
Yes.
Where something dreadful
interrupts all of your plans.
But then,
after a while,
you realize,
well, those plans were stupid
and what I'm doing now is better.
I'm glad that disaster happened.
Yes.
Yeah.
But sometimes you just go,
if that disaster hadn't happened,
I wouldn't be in this iron lung.
Oh.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know what I mean?
But, uh,
you pointed in the right direction
and wasted it away
from the rest of us.
Thank goodness.
Yeah, I don't want you
getting a hold of it.
It'd make you sick.
You guys wouldn't be able
to handle it.
Hell yeah, you gotta...
It's like you gotta have
a bunch of PhDs
in biochemistry.
Yeah.
Even, like, Glock.
Yeah, just a Glock
you have to have...
you have to have a degrees.
And bony knees.
And you also have to have
a filigree thigh,
like one of the elder ladies.
At the Kabooska house.
What do you know?
What do you mean, bony knees?
Are you making fun of me again?
No, my knees were knocking,
so I thought I'd give myself a jab.
Oh.
Okay.
I was afraid
because the moon is getting
pretty big right now.
Is that what it is?
Because, you know,
not only have I been lately
beset by the sadness
of seeing so many people fall,
literally fall,
or get sick,
but what was the other thing
that was bothering me?
Now I can't remember.
It must not have been that bad.
Oh, well.
Life is great.
Yeah.
As long as I don't remember anything,
it's really cool.
Yeah.
Oh, well.
I'm sure it'll come to me
when I listen back to the tape.
You see the purity,
the essential,
the innate beauty of the system.
It's just a little glimpse.
It's like a crappy movie,
and then the movie's over.
But who knows where the audience goes?
That's what I want to know.
Well, the system is about punishment,
not reform.
That's the bottom line.
There might have been a system
that was about reform
instead of punishment,
or maybe both.
But no,
it's going to be punishment
all the way down.
And bad puns.
All the way down.
All the world gone bad.
Yeah, I unfortunately
harmonized with you there
on that elaborate backwards note.
Although I fail to see
what kind of grand choral design
we're bringing into the universe,
if such a thing could exist.
Because we want everyone's toes
pointed in the right...
Well, we don't want
to proselytize or misrepresent
an area or anything like that,
but it would be nice
if everyone's toes...
Grand choral?
Well, Suzy the Flusy
already did that
earlier in the show.
She proselytized...
What, in her toes?
Yeah, well,
she always does that,
and everybody else's toes.
But she did the proselytizing
and did a nice little
Bob brainwashing thing.
Might work on some people.
But I'm blanking
on the grand choral.
That just doesn't...
Grand choral?
Yes.
That means the universal chorus.
Ah.
The implazoid conjecture
beyond the roofing.
The next outspoken
argumentative individual
that needs to be restrained.
And they never restrain.
Oh, now I remember
what it was.
Besides people getting sick,
is the insane people
are agitated.
This week.
Maybe Mercury's hiding
behind the moon or something,
but my regular crazy person callers,
message leavers who leave...
See, we have a toll-free phone.
Subgenius church phone,
and we get crazy people.
Let's go ahead and say it.
Really, really crazy people.
And there's been a...
There's a new one started
this week.
Oh, my.
Yeah.
Staring out the window.
He said...
He mentioned that he was
in a mental institution.
And he said that he wanted
to get in touch
with our cult leader
because he had discovered
our cult leader
who was Hermes Trimestus,
or Trid...
Oh, yeah, that guy.
I've heard of that guy.
Oh.
And he wanted to talk to him
and let us know
that that was who he was
or who we were.
Well, just send him a picture
of anybody with a beard,
you know,
and a kind of a short beard.
Well, he left his number
several times,
and he can't remember
saying that he would call back
when we were in.
Ah.
But I sat there
and listened to him
leave messages
without picking up the phone.
Well, tell him
that you will not
call him back
until you're three times
as ready.
But it wasn't just him.
I got an email
that was about
a hundred pages long
of coded sentences
that the author knew
had to be true
because he'd run them
through a little
computer program
an end time program.
It was written by
Book of Revelation
numerology calculator
that if your sentence
came out to decode
to 777 times three,
whatever the heck
he means by that,
then therefore
that sentence was correct.
And some of the sentences
of this author,
Sam Moser,
you can look him up
on the internet.
There's quite a bit about him
because he talks about
the masons all the time.
And he's in and out.
Oh yeah, the masons.
I've been out there
You mean on the Southwest?
One of his sentences was, Ivan Stang's very demonic.
And I was like, did he leave a word off?
Does he mean Ivan Stang's very demonic pet newt or Ivan Stang's very demonic latest album or what?
But it just meant that I'm very demonic.
It also, another thing that he had decoded was that Barack Obama was after him, that it was okay for fathers to sleep with their daughters because they do it in the Bible.
Okay.
Although he tried that with his hamsters.
I've been looking forward to that.
Honest to God, Dave, this guy in the midst of this hundred-page email, which takes like ten minutes just to open on an older computer, just a text file, it's that long.
I hear you.
He said that he had been breeding his hamsters to see whether...
Like in the Bible, if the father got drunk and did it with the daughters, whether how the baby hamsters would turn out.
And he said that they turned out catatonic, which made him almost doubt the Bible.
But then he ran his phrase through that computer on somebody else's website, some other religious nuts website.
And it came out to 777 times 21.
Times three.
So that meant it was true that father mate with daughter, okay.
I think that's what he said.
Ten minutes, yeah.
It was really something.
And I mean, it's like every time the phone rings, either it's a crazy person telling me something like that, or it's somebody, another crazy person telling me one of our friends is in the hospital.
Or it's the person in the hospital calling us up or texting us and going, I'm on painkillers.
Yeehaw, come on down and get yourself trepanated like me.
Yeehaw.
So, you know, some of them are having fun.
Well, I'm glad I got trepanated.
Believe me, boy, a lot of times I just couldn't go to the bathroom, you know.
It fixed your phone.
Other apertures, of course, but, you know.
It did fix your phone.
Dave's phone sounds so good, it's like pornography to me to hear this.
It's so clear.
It's crystal clear.
You'd think Dave was in the studio with us.
Yes.
I am the specter in your studio, right behind you.
And if you look on the console, you'll notice I've left a present for you.
Is that what that is?
You did that?
That's gross, man.
A piece of demon dung.
Yes, I did that.
I gave that to you.
Yes, yes.
It was me.
It's got maggots in it.
Oh, don't worry.
They're not real maggots.
Maggots don't grow in demon excretion.
Okay, well, if you left your brain here, what are you using to talk with now?
Because this is a stinky old brain.
A maggot brain.
Well, thanks a lot.
Well, it's stinky.
It looks pretty old.
I'm trying to make yourself nice for Mother's Day and for happy, you know, non-Easter or whatever.
Poor Reverend Pockets.
Not only did she get no Mother's Day, but she got thrown into the emergency room.
Yeah.
It's not fair.
And on top of that, I jokingly told her she was crazy for giving us such wonderful gifts.
And she thought I meant it.
Yeah.
Oh.
So, Reverend Pockets, if you're in the hospital or doped up listening to this later, I was just, that was an icebreaker.
I didn't really, I don't really, well, I do think you're crazy, but not that kind of crazy.
The same way you've always been bragging that you're crazy.
Nice, crazy.
Reverend Pockets.
Creative.
Happy, free-spirited, you know.
Crazy.
Wild and crazy guy.
Kind of crazy.
Yeah.
What happened to our background music here?
What happened to the beacon and the gloom?
That's what I'd like to know.
I hear the rough disadvantages of an accordion and the coarse laughter of naked people.
And I can hear it all the time.
You hear naked people?
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
I hear them in the wind.
I would feel so cheated.
Pardon?
I'd feel cheated, you know, hearing naked people all the time.
But believe me, you don't want this present.
Once you get it, you know you've been cheated out of real hearing and real searing.
Well, if there were naked people there, it must have been the dream Starwood Festival.
Oh, that's right.
We were going to brag up Starwood.
Princess, we're already at Starwood.
And handing out little postcards and flyers about the Starwood Festival, which comes up in, what is it, July.
I don't make money off this, so I can talk about it.
I do help with it.
But right after X-Day, at the same place.
Sometimes if you're really drunk.
No, I'm just kidding.
Right after, immediately after X-Day Festival at Wisteria Campground in Southern Ohio, there's Starwood Festival.
That starts, you can hear it in the background here.
And that starts, what, July 8th?
Yes.
July 8th through 14th, I believe.
And it's a camp out.
But there's a...
About 40 bands and a bunch of lecturers and ranters like me.
Oh, and there's a great magician going to be there, Magnus the Magician.
Yes.
He's...
He is a professional Las Vegas magician who's done a lot of shows at...
He's famous.
And we've opened for him.
And Penn Jillette hates him because he believes in the other kind of magic.
He's a stage magician.
But he also believes in magic.
That is very unusual.
Right.
Wouldn't you say?
Yeah, yeah, it is.
Usually they're debunkers that, you know...
Right, right.
And they know that the card's always going to be pointed...
Oh, never mind.
I am pointing to...
Well, Magnus or Jeff McBride is not trying to convince adults that they're...
The spirits of their parents are revealing where the hidden will is or anything like that.
He's...
It's the kind of thing where...
I'd almost be afraid to tell Penn Jillette that I'm friends with that guy, too.
Although, when we were in Las Vegas, we visited Magnus.
And he got to see his nice house, and he told us about the Valley of Fire.
I thought he was going to tell you that the house was built by Lord Zaldor.
It was.
It looks like it was built by Lord Zaldor.
But...
And there's weird...
It's a magician.
It's a...
It's like a Kabuki...
Yeah, a Kabuki alchemist house.
Oh, boy.
Yeah, it's pretty cool.
It's fabulous.
But he did...
He told...
He said if you...
Flying around the place all over there, you know?
The way he got rid of us was he said, you know, if you guys take off now, you can make it
to Valley of Fire by sunset, and that'd be really worth it.
And we did take off, and we got...
Valley of Fire is a state...
It's a state park about an hour from Las Vegas, and it's the most alien-looking place of all
the alien places we went to, just about.
It was spectacular.
Much to us here in the East, much of the West does look very alien indeed.
It looks lunarscaped and strange.
I'm sorry.
Well, if you look at a globe that's got the wrinkles where mountains are, the right half
of the country is interesting and wrinkly.
And the...
No, no.
Left half of the country.
Is interesting and wrinkly.
And the right half where we are, starting about at Albuquerque, it's...
You don't even know how sad it is until you drove across the West.
Mm-hmm.
And you realize how utterly boring the Midwest is.
The plain plains.
Yeah.
Did you ever drive through North Dakota or South Dakota, man?
I've lived in South Dakota, Dave.
Oh, man.
I've lived in Mission, South Dakota for two years.
And there's a new subgenius who's in Valentine, Nebraska.
That's where I used to drive for beer on Sundays.
I drove across Nebraska one time.
It was like, it just goes on and on.
And there's these, like, roads with lights on them and stuff.
And it's like, who is it for?
Right.
It's for the drunk person driving straight at you down that highway.
And they're talking about flatness.
And I couldn't believe that it was really that true, that things could just be...
The horizon just went on forever and on forever.
Yeah.
Our friend Dr. Zeronius...
...Taudry Milk Toast did a series of tapes while they were hallucinating their way driving across Kansas.
Because it's like being in a sensory deprivation chamber.
Yes.
It's just the same thing.
I mean, driving through Kentucky, the interstate going through Kentucky and Tennessee will almost hypnotize you.
But at least there's...
At least there are beautiful trees in Tennessee.
Yeah, but it's the same tree over and over again.
It's like you can tell it's an animated background.
Yes.
And in Kansas, it's the same pool.
It's the same pool and the same field over and over and over forever and ever and ever.
Yes.
It makes Ohio and Texas look sort of interesting almost.
I would have to do that.
There is one...
There are three interesting places in Texas.
We've been to all of them.
They're all named after the devil.
Well, to me, the piece is humongous, so there's got to be like 20 places.
It was like the devil's staircase, the devil's wash basin, the devil's commode, the devil's inkwell.
Devil's pool.
The devil's pool.
Yeah.
The devil's armpit.
The devil's Facebook page.
Yeah.
The devil's picnic table.
It's...
Yeah, anything named after the devil is good.
Hey, we've only got like five minutes left of this show.
Thank God and Bob both.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm sorry.
Well, I've actually kind of been fighting off this hallucination of the...
of the ophthalmic migraines a little bit this whole time.
Hmm.
He's a warrior of the ophthalmic migraine.
I experienced my nerve a couple days ago, but it was only for a few hours.
No, I did not know.
Norm, they don't hurt.
They're not like migraine headaches that are brutally painful.
They don't hurt at all.
You try to ignore what you're seeing there.
Well, it's hard.
You read.
It's...
If you're playing a video game, you miss the monsters every other hit
because you can't really focus well.
It's irritating.
You know, it's like...
Do you experience colon sometimes?
It's kind of like what they say that LSD stuff is like, visually.
Yes.
But not quite as much frilly frill work and paisleys and fiddly bits as you might get.
As I've heard.
But they're...
They're so
It was the first CGI type of movie.
Yes.
You know what I mean, man?
Dave, you lived so long that they've made a remodel
remake of Tron.
Did you know that?
Oh, of course.
Oh, okay.
Well, they've remade everything.
Somebody was saying...
I don't watch movies anymore.
I let the movies come to me.
Right.
There was a guy on Scrub Genius saying,
okay, they must have a mathematical sheet
or some kind of schedule where they go,
okay, Godzilla was cool of 25...
It's been 25 years.
Okay, time for the remake of Godzilla.
Or before, it was like Beverly Hillbillies.
It's been 25 years.
Time to make a Beverly Hillbillies movie.
That was about 10 years ago.
So they're probably due to make another
Beverly Hillbillies remake movie remake.
And they'll be due for another Tron.
And it occurred to me that by this formula,
by the year 2047,
the Church of the Sub-Junior should start making money.
If that's the way that formula goes.
We came along a little ways after,
26 years after Godzilla,
because I was born the year Godzilla was born.
And the Church came along and grabbed me when I was 26.
So that means 26 years from now,
we ought to be able to do the remake of Church of the Sub-Junior.
And this time actually make money.
That Godzilla movie's made 96 million bucks
in the last two days since it opened.
Goodness gracious.
That was because I mentioned it.
You know, that's all.
Of course.
You really knew Godzilla.
I guess that's what the real name is.
Kotsura or something like that.
Gojira.
It was actually the nickname of a big...
It was the nickname of a funny looking guy
that worked at the studio.
And it means a gorilla whale.
And originally Godzilla was like a gorilla whale.
If you think about the way he looks,
he's kind of not a normal dinosaur.
He's kind of like a gorilla whale.
Anyway.
He's kind of way aquatic.
Yeah.
He's big.
He's mad.
He's Godzilla.
And there were some nice little funny jokes
like cops shooting at these creatures
the size of several buildings.
I mean, shooting with pistols.
At one point, it works.
The guy's like, he's about to be killed by Godzilla.
I'm just total spoiler.
He clicks it.
He shoots his gun at Godzilla, at the monster.
It's not Godzilla.
It's another monster.
And the monster...
stops in its tracks like the bullet did something.
Yeah.
Then you realize it's because Godzilla's got his teeth
sunk into the back of that monster's neck.
And with that lovely image, friends,
we must bid you some sort of adieu or adidu
as we fade slowly off into subgenius.com,
which is where you can find out about all this stupid...
Yes, yes, yes.
Often, often, often, often.
I used to say...
Thank you, Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Thank you, Princess We Are Doe.
Oh, okay.
And thank you, me.
And...
Aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye.
And so...
There they go.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm showing slow but steady improvement
on the ground in a hail of bricks and bullets.
Some analysts say this year was last year.
Good.
PR's...
Report reports.
You're listening to PR News,
found dead in Washington.
And that's one thing that I think bothers
a little bit of a frozen tadpole.
Uh...
Whoa!
Wow!
Man, that was great!