Are we in a movie?
Everything's a movie.
Talking pictures.
That's all it is.
Walking pictures.
Huh?
Cheesy dreams.
While Huckleberry Finn goes fishing on the edge of the moon.
Who's Ben Johnson?
He's in The Last Picture Show.
Just like us.
Don't move, my love.
Be still.
Be real.
He's gone.
Tuesday, 2018 o'clock.
Resuming work.
As a result of stripping skin off the skull,
keeping clean and keeping at the required temperature,
the bones have become crystalline.
I may now begin reconstruction of the physiognomy whenever I please.
In the ancient folk legends, tales are told of blood-sucking vampires.
Is man now doomed to produce a race of ever-living monstrosities?
Worse than the vampires of legend?
Such questions, mate.
I seem fanciful.
But at this very moment, scientists are working on the answer to brain transplantation.
And human bodies are used.
This girl was buried in a nearby cemetery yesterday.
Only a few hours ago, her body was stolen.
And brought to this hidden laboratory.
He has grafted a living animal's brain into this newly dead body.
The brain cells are being reactivated by
The subgenius.
Our.
Mother machines are the blind.
The eyes are the victim.
The eyes are the Protector.
in this endeavor.
Let me sow to the bottom this pit.
Bind the fallen ones.
Bind the fallen angels.
Let them be bound by the power of the Lord's host in this hour.
T-E-R-W-I-L-L.
Illicor.
However, sure, you'll pay in other ways.
For instance, the number of brain cells that you have to kill just to take enough pills
to be able to bear this show in the middle of the night.
Why, that in itself is quite expensive.
That bear is repeating.
Yes, well, most people are lucky they don't have to listen to this thing every night,
like Uberbrow.
Day in, day out.
That poor boy not only has to listen to it every night,
he has to broadcast it every night.
From his secret cubicle, hundreds of miles under solid rock.
Weird, weird, weird, weird, weird, yes.
The little brow is so weird.
And yet, they kept on.
Nobody knew why.
I love Little Uber.
His brow is so weird.
And if he won't pinch me, I'll hide in his beard.
I hid under his stool to look at his feet.
Right.
I could not get out.
Or I'd fail upon the seat.
The implied adventure that the doctors had in their voices.
They knew something spooky and scary was about to happen.
Well, that wasn't it.
Not even the baby breaking out of my little glass brain.
Yes, the little babies were hard to find in the morning
because the U-Haul trucks would come and take them away.
Their little china bodies lay shattered on the midden heaps.
And they were filled with little nylon things and little spooky eyes.
They came in little boxes and the people fought and kicked and prayed and shot to get one.
But there was nothing they could do.
But be scared, of course.
And being scared in Berkeley is sort of a way of life.
Just ask the new revitalized 53rd Street Winos Association.
Really?
Being terrorized is something you'll be watching now as we sternutate our way to madness.
Where's Billy?
Just give me what's in that bag right now.
You're on the only show brave enough to bring the facts to you.
These are coffee winos.
They don't drink alcohol.
They drink more and more advanced grades of coffee.
Yes, Doctor, we call them coffeenos.
This old coffeeno here is holding what looks like a can of Colombian ground coffee.
Oh, fuck, I have coffee!
I can't wait for you to do something with it.
I know you just spent it on coffee.
Where's the sugar, please?
I'm going to finally see the truth.
Those who wouldn't say please, they were forced to take other forms of entertainment.
And to perform humiliating jests and actions and act.
At weird hours of the morning.
It's been there, yes.
Little tiny doctors.
My mind.
Okay, now what are my instructions?
What was I going to do?
I always have to look up what it says in the program, but I don't know what it is.
I said I was going to...
Adventures in sickening.
Subgenius preachers are skilled at both healings and sickenings, although they're not necessarily performed in that order.
Reverend Stang...
Oh, so this is what I'm going to do.
Reverend Stang will explain various Dobbs-approved techniques, such as transferal of pain,
the laying on of sledgehammers,
acubating,
frame-straightening,
blemish readings,
and most importantly,
excremeditation.
He will also take questions from the audience and has interesting proctology slides if anyone wants to see them.
Well, that's...
I'm done.
That was all the gags.
I put them all in that one.
So I shot my load, I'd say.
Okay, no, really the subject is...
Slack, Muzak, and...
Transformative Embarrassment,
Courtesy of Chickenhead,
Praise Chickenhead.
Oh no, these are the wrong cult.
These are notes for the wrong cult. I'm sorry about that.
Oh, here it is.
Church of the Subgenius.
That's the right cult, friends.
And this is its right show, as proven by the fact that it exploits all the other subgenius shows.
There have been so many of those lately that we can categorize them into sections.
For instance, this episode of Hour of Slack features the category of drugs, and especially the drug coffee, our last completely legal one for now.
We have been and will continue to hear collages by Fernanda Nani-Lemur,
my sermon at Winterstar Symposium,
the amino acids, as heard in the background,
puzzling evidence shows from Berkeley, both very old and very new,
with Philo, Gary, Doug, and Hal, and K-Rob, and...
John Hell.
But those are from John Hell's show on Pirate Cat Radio.
So remember, all Pirate Cat Radio shows are archived for six weeks at piratecatradio.com,
so you can hear this here, here.
You may already be listening to this here, here.
What is the proper name of the show?
A Season in Hell.
So you just go to the DJ schedule, scroll down, click on it,
and there's the date you listen to the show.
And what do you know?
Can you podcast it? That's what I was like...
Sure, we pod... I throw my...
Everybody except me, Tom. That's what I do.
Hold on, we're gonna isolate you... now.
Isolation chamber.
That's my kind of show. Just me, Jim, all the time.
I hear lunch in Carolina.
That's all we're gonna hear.
You can put this show up if you want to as well.
I just told the listeners that that's what I have.
Yeah, right, right. So it's already there.
Sorry, it was the other three conversations that I was listening to at the time.
Preserves in the basement.
Preserve the show for the winter.
In the jar.
With the brown bread and the baked beans.
Goes in the jar with the stuff.
Don't look too closely at that jar and its contents.
Don't think about that.
Is that an eyeball?
It's an eyebrow.
Some hair?
Is that back to what you were talking about, the jar in the bathroom?
The jar.
Jar of Jenkum. Jenkum jar.
Yeah, uh, Super Jenkum Hayes was the winner at the Frop Cup in Amsterdam.
What about G13 Hayes? Was that the same thing?
That was the marijuana in the...
The cannabis cup.
Ah, I see.
The jank... They didn't have a Jenkum category at the cannabis cup.
Is Jenkum still available here? Can you still get Jenkum over the counter?
You can make it yourself, Daddy.
That's about it. Well, now we can get Absinthe over the counter again.
Makes the hard-kill funds.
You can?
It was just a...
What?
It was made legal again last week.
They made it legal.
Nationally or just...
Nationally. It is a legal alcoholic beverage.
The official beverage of Learning Man is legal.
The store's closed.
At 2 p.m. on the 5th.
2.
We all got two hours to show that.
Oh, yeah. There's my... I got the sugar cubes.
I've been known to chase the...
A CD, yeah.
Oh.
Davy, Davy Crockett, the king of beer.
Born on a bar when he was only three.
He went off to Congress and served a spell.
Davy, Davy Crockett, serving his...
This country here.
Smoke don only the person where you knew shutcher.
baptized him in the cup of prison.
He must know who...
you talk a lot when you get drunk.
You talk a lot when you get drunk.
You only get drunk with one person.
Huh?
You mean...
You mean Bob?
Yeah.
Where that low-down snake?
And him pretending to be my friend.
Tending to be my friend.
But we do have the... the theme of this.
whole show here is healing and so forth and we've already sickened you. I had a couple of things
that have been of interest to me. I read a newspaper article a couple of months ago
explaining that some folks at Case Western University in Cleveland had created some
Franken-mice. You know, the human genome has been mapped. That's pretty complicated.
They actually finished the job pretty much and although it's against the law to do
Franken-humans yet, well we'll get to that, but these little mice that they had created in this
lab or had tweaked, you might say, that they were like way more aggressive than normal mice.
They also lived like twice as long and could keep reproducing for twice as long as normal mice.
And so I think that's a really good point. I think that's a really good point.
And they fought constantly. One of the women who had been working with them said that when
she knew they were different, because whenever he lifted the lid off their cage it was like a
popcorn, lifting a lid off of popping popcorn. They were just going mad.
And so, you know, we've all heard about the Franken-corn and so forth. I mean, that's being
done. You can actually create new species now and also trademark them.
You can create a bundle of cells that'll just sit there and generate something useful like
medicine or drugs, but you can trademark it. Of course, this brings to mind what so many
sci-fi movies and TV shows have already covered. The Franken-soldiers, right? Franken-cops,
super macho, or whatever kind of person you are. You aren't just a muscle man that doesn't
mind doing dull work. You can create a bundle of cells that'll just sit there and generate something
useful. You can create those. Aldous Huxley had it all down with Brave New World. Our grandparents
read about that. They didn't think about Franken-salesmen. They didn't think about
Franken-politicians. But I read recently that there were some guys in France and also some
people in some other places who were trying to map, completely map the genome of the
world. And you can 2 times as much as 20ve, 30
and 20 days. By beginning your 12 year redemption campaign, do you
dream of lives different from yours.
.
And that brings us to the Franken-POT!
The Franken-oregano.
You know, I was really thinking more of the Franken-Pot myself.
They bred that stuff.
We went to the Cannabis Cup in Amsterdam this last time.
It wasn't the kind of thing that I would spend my own money on, but we lucked out.
We had a friend who went to every coffee shop on the map, bought every super strong grade
of marijuana and hash.
But what this guy didn't know was how to get around Amsterdam.
Well, we knew how to get around Amsterdam.
So frankly, if I was a judge at that thing, I would say the same thing about every single
contestant, which is, this shit is strong as hell.
That was about all you could say.
Yeah.
I personally am more interested in the Franken-Jenkem.
And if you don't know what the Jenkem is, don't even ask.
Don't think about it.
Don't look it up on the internet.
It's a new drug that they say the kids are doing.
Don't look it up.
Don't look up Jenkem.
J-E-N-K-E-M.
And don't even think about the Franken-Jenkem.
I take off.
Don't take off.
I got a better ride.
Di-di-di-di-di-di-di-die.com.
This time, we mount to die.
Fixed.
No matter.
Chewable.
Chewable deadly heartworm disease.
Friday night, Friday night.
Protein.
Fat.
Demand.
neck, directed by Steven Spielberg.
Bunny.
And I want everybody in town to come.
Drug, drug, the next thing I know, here she is on drugs.
Bunny, you have lost your mind.
Bud, hurry.
I'm coming.
Swe على?
Bunny, Bunny's dead.
Dead? Dead? Crazy.
Bunny?
Bunny? Bunny? Bunny?
Bunny? Bunny, where are you?
Bunny? Bunny?
Bunny, Bunny?
Bunny, Bunny, Bunny, Bunny, Bunny, Bunny, Bunny, Bunny is dead.
And into the gray.
Say yes to beautiful.
Cool.
Doom, doom, doom.
Okay, we're taking our coffee shots now.
What if you did 12 of those things really fast?
You can't. It says on the label.
You paid the money before the guy even took your money.
He's like, rip, rip, rip.
Yeah, I found a new drug today.
I haven't been in a proper 7-Eleven in years.
Philo, I think, would like that.
Because they don't have proper 7-Elevens in Cleveland.
But they had a drug called Stoke,
which is included with the coffee creamers in the little cup.
The kids today are on Stoke.
Which means it's free.
That means it's free.
It's free. That's right.
I grabbed two half-fulls.
You have hot water.
You stoke it with hot water and you make coffee out of it.
Each one of these little things is very sweet.
When you've held a Stoke baby in your hands,
then you know how it is.
I can tell you, man.
These Stoke heads have to be knocked in
or our civilization is going to fall.
The target in Erie, Pennsylvania is
inhabited entirely by Stoke babies.
Stoke fetal syndrome.
Look at his feet.
Each Stoke has 40 milligrams of caffeine.
Which really is, that's only like half a cup of coffee.
That's for wimps.
That half a cup of coffee.
Is that what all the big build-up companies do?
But it's free.
Free?
It's free.
At 7-Eleven.
Thanks to the Southland Corporation.
Free drugs, 40 milligrams of caffeine.
It's free.
Wait a minute.
Was I supposed to say that on KPFA?
That was not, uh...
Don't go to 7-Eleven.
It does sound suspiciously like Plagola, Stang,
but we know that it's only a matter of fair use.
In the name of WCSB Cleveland, do not go to 7-Eleven.
Fair use beneath the trees.
That counteracted it.
If you do, you'll be surrounded by caffeine and sugar.
Both.
Both are exceptionally valuable substances.
Sugar.
Nature's perfect food.
Just a bunch of little noises.
And caffeine, the perfect vitamin.
Vitamin?
That's what vitamin C stands for.
Yes, yes.
I, uh, spent too many years in headphones and in front of my friends' bands videotaping them.
So I hear what sounds like crickets and cicadas all the time.
Now, I grew up in Texas, and there really are cicadas all the time.
But one winter's day, Princess Weaver suddenly said,
Did you hear that?
And I listened, and I went,
Yeah, I hear the cicadas.
And I looked outside, and it was like this.
It was like snow on the ground.
And I realized that it was time to go see the ear doctor.
And I flunked the test.
But I found some good news in this issue of Nutrition Action magazine.
This is one of the kookzines that my wife gets.
She reads Utney Reader and all this silly stuff.
And this special issue about caffeine, it turns out, I mean, I drink a lot of coffee.
I drank so much coffee that I started getting migraines and bad headaches.
So I went to my doctor and said, I have headaches.
She said, So, you drink a lot of coffee, do you?
And she didn't even have to ask why.
And I said, Yeah.
She wrote me out of perspective.
She wrote me a prescription for half, for a type of decaf she likes.
She said, I know you're not going to stop drinking real coffee.
Just cut it with decaf.
Step on it.
Mix half and half.
And I was able to drink 20 cups instead of 10 and never get headaches.
But I always felt bad about it because, oh, well, I'll probably get colon cancer someday or hypertension or something.
But it turns out, my fellow coffee drinkers are going to be so glad to hear this.
All these studies, it has turned out,
caffeine or coffee, they're two different things, but coffee basically helps present Parkinson's disease, gallstones.
It actually does help your mental performance if you're sleepy and your mood, of course.
And headaches.
It increases the effects of painkillers.
It's not good for pregnant ladies.
No way is it good for pregnant ladies.
And it won't counteract alcohol.
I repeat, it won't counteract alcohol.
Try to remember that at about 5 or 6 this morning, my friends.
But it turns out I was wrong.
All these studies show that it doesn't correlate to heart disease.
It doesn't correlate to any kind of cancer, especially, or diabetes or high blood pressure or osteoporosis.
And it doesn't stunt your growth.
It doesn't stunt your growth.
And my mother always used to say,
and I believed her too, and that's why I'm not taller than I am.
And, PMS.
There's no evidence that caffeine played a role in PMS.
Well, duh.
Anyway, it was a really interesting little article.
I learned from it that Starbucks coffee, the 16 ounce one, has the highest charge you can get.
at 330 milligrams of caffeine.
That would put me in the hospital.
If I drank it all at once,
if I drank three of them in one day,
nothing, I could probably go to sleep.
So that was why I brought up the franken-coffee routine.
I am really looking forward now to the franken-coffee.
The first time I met Sir Isaac Bonowitz over there,
I didn't even know who he was exactly,
but he offered me some coffee,
and I heard for the first time that little coffee chant
based on the mentat.
It was the goddess Caffeina routine,
which I never could remember
because I don't just drink coffee.
I can tell you right off the head,
I mean the tip of my head,
quote Princess We Are Now.
Anybody want any stoke?
I have one.
What happens when you consume this?
I'm trying to cut down.
Warning, high caffeine.
You add it to your coffee.
Is it like a little creamer package?
But you can just toss it down?
I wouldn't, yeah, if you don't mind migraine,
headache type effects.
Nonsense.
Go ahead, do it, Hal, do it.
Well, I would, but I mean I've got a pie in the oven.
I mean these nosebleeds keep me on my back.
No, the thing is, is it edible?
Give it some horrible thing.
You know, some hideous, uh,
how do you happen to have this in your pocket?
Well, I will, I'll drink it right now.
Dr. Hal.
Here we go.
Sip it, please.
Don't just shoot the whole thing.
I wonder what this will be like.
Hey, Puzzling Evidence TV sent me a video.
Well, what it tastes like is prune juice.
You're sure it's not?
What a thing that may have never happened.
Let me have a little.
I'm reading it now.
It tasted like a prune juice.
About JFK dying.
But it says that this,
this video has been removed due to violation.
It does taste stoke.
Which one is it?
This isn't caffeine infected water.
That's happening more and more.
It's mere prune juice.
Oh my God.
Damnable prune juice.
Ivan's thanks for helping.
Prune juice?
Well, it's, uh.
That's one thing about YouTube is that their policy of, uh, removing videos is real nebulous.
Yeah.
Well, it's who gets, who gets reported and who gets caught.
It's sort of like what one of us was running into.
Yeah, take it out.
Equivalent to one shot of espresso.
But there's, there's porno YouTube.
There's uncensored.
YouTube ish things.
There's red tube.
40 milligrams.
Which is.
Caffeine.
And pink tube.
And you porn.
Yeah.
You porn.
That's right.
Not for.
Whenever I look at one of those websites, there's a whole special window that comes
up showing girls I could date in Cleveland.
Yeah.
It knows, it knows which city I'm in and it shows me all these nice.
It shows you these nice pictures.
You could make.
It knows where your IP address is.
It knows where your IP address is being served from.
And I try to make love to each and every one of those.
Not labeled for any.
Because I feel that responsibility.
I mean.
You know what I do?
Well, they're lonely.
It says they're lonely single women.
Plus, you get all these pills in the mail, in the email.
These special pills for your tool.
E-pills, non-dairy coffee products.
Your tool pills.
Yeah.
Well, you know.
And then when you meet the women on the other website, you've got something really handy
to use with them.
Yeah.
You got to do it that way because it's all virtual.
Dr. Howell is drinking the stoke.
Oh, he's drinking the virtual stoke.
He's having a power drink.
Now, that's 40 milligrams of caffeine in one swallow.
Caller, what do you think of this?
The show is like a bottle of syrup on pancakes and strong coffee.
Yeah.
Now you're talking.
Even if JFK dies.
Look at how he's changing.
My God, man.
Somebody call the guards.
Now, do you ever use molasses on your pancakes?
Have you ever tried that?
Molasses?
What about sorghum?
Sorghum molasses.
I mean, stuff I don't eat anymore.
This country used to be great.
I'm too accessible now.
You don't eat?
Excuse me, sensible, not eating pancakes?
Are you a breatharian?
Backstabbed molasses?
I am sore strapped for sorghum and molasses.
I eat all.
And vegetables and fruits.
Vegetables, fruits, fruitas y verduras.
Mostly vegetarian.
Vegetar...
You can still eat pancakes, though.
We don't eat pancakes.
Pancakes?
Oh, well.
I realize some people can divert themselves.
In moderation.
Yeah, so I'm going to try these caffes and then I'm going to try these pancakes.
I'm going to try these potato chips.
Really?
These chips are pure dope chips.
Well, they're caffeine chips.
They're caffeine chips made from coffee beans and they've also had powdered caffeine added
to them with citric acid.
Why not just peel these guys off the ceiling here?
I've noticed that caffeine drinks have become... are in a huge variety now and in
huge volumes and mixed with alcohol, which Bob predicted 10,000 years ago.
So many...
There would come a day when speed and booze were mixed together and sold in sci-fi stores
with names like Big Throttle, Monster Jug, Booze Speed.
You're witness, Mr. Freud.
Monster Jugs, Booze Speed.
There we got Philo's attention.
Remember, today we've got an awesome guest.
His name is Bob.
And I first met Bob... Bob, when did I meet you?
About 10 years ago?
1984.
Yeah.
I'm Bob.
And you look incredible.
But... and I remember blah blah blah, no bones about it, you know.
You know, there's something about Bob dedicated to achieving drugs...
So Bob is born and raised in...
Bob joined the drug abuse.
So Bob is understanding steroids.
Bob... a drug that targets young people as well as parents and other adults.
Bob calls them the naked reached and prescription drugs broadly available to the youth in every
community.
Boy, that's...
Wow.
Wow, that's an awesome mouthful of stuff you've been doing.
So, I'm totally stoked about it.
There was lots of drugs, acid rock and the whole bit, bit, bit, bit.
Call, call, call, call.
Drugs are the solution.
The solution evolution in the early years, clandestine-ish, but clandestine.
But add drugs to the mix and you get strength in the testes.
Secrete the most amount of testosterone.
And I've seen it, and I hope I'm not getting too deep here, profound.
Found.
Psychoactive.
Psycho.
And I've observed it myself.
And they just kind of bang around the ball.
Injected in the butt.
Fat in the brain.
Really feeling the organ.
Becoming that organ.
They are matter, energy, space, and time.
And they're hideous.
Hardening of the long bone.
Oh, it's huge.
Burn it off.
Come on, UPS.
And bogus.
Don't know what phony packaging.
Big business.
You have LSD and pot.
And we have more drugs.
We have more drugs.
Better.
Marijuana.
Methamphetamines.
Methamphetamine.
Crystal meth.
But crack.
Crack.
Smoking.
Paint thinner.
One hit.
Unreal.
Crystal meth.
And we showed a video on ecstasy.
It's just for partying.
Complete curriculum.
How to use clits with a class.
And how to deliver that.
www.yesdrugs.org.
Get it all.
Drugs and harmful effects is really our duty.
Utterly enormous.
People, they try to get stimulated.
Fear.
Which is huge.
I think it's the largest.
They're fairly abstract.
Bob, no.
Don't forget, you know, drugs.
Have a good day.
One of the worst things about drugs, friends,
is sometimes they make you forget the other drugs you were going to take.
That cut was cut by Norell Preff.
And more from him.
And also some bits from the excellent movie Slipstream,
directed by Hannibal Lecter.
There was no problem.
There was no porno shoot going on.
Time they finished the whole thing.
Not like here at Pirate Cat Radio.
I noticed that stuff in the other room.
Yeah, the stage and the hook on the ceiling.
Well, actually.
That's all specialty equipment.
That's right.
The jar of Jankum.
Ah.
Too closely at that jar.
But I understand it's not water-based.
So, therefore, it won't get sticky.
What kind of show is this?
What kind of tapes were you making?
Mm-hmm.
So cool.
Yeah, I had the Oakland police, two officers,
come into my basement with drawn guns because of the sounds they heard upstairs
when they came into the kitchen that we were making on tapes below.
And we had a quarter pound of dope in a big bowl next to the tape recorder.
And they took the tapes and left the pot?
No, I remember turning around.
We're doing a tape to him.
He had written this copy.
This Ivan Stan guy had written some copy for a rich person's eagle's nest.
And we had taken that copy.
We were making our own commercial for it.
And the next thing I know, yeah, Paul's about to leap on a guy with a drawn gun.
But when the cop came in, Paul jumped up and knocked over the table that had all the dope on it.
He did with all my gear and the dope.
It was flying.
So it was no longer an obvious pile of dope.
It was just a big mess on the floor at that point.
And a wonderful huge crash just when a very jittery officer's coming in.
Coming down a stairway with a drawn gun.
And I remember thinking, ooh, this could end badly.
A Paul Hoffa, sir.
Something is just shot doing commercial in the basement.
Could have been your Waco, Texas.
Exactly.
We could have been immortal, but no.
That's right.
The luck plane had something else.
Well, there were other famous subgenius crimes, particularly the tendinophy convenience.
He was lying in a canvas hammock.
One bare foot.
Long over the side.
Deep in the enjoyment of an oversized cigarette.
He seemed to sleep except for the rhythmic puffs of smoke.
What?
Why?
How was that?
Uh, sure.
Here.
All right, look, you can't push me around.
I'm an American.
Well, hop in.
Give it a man.
Ooh!
Is there anything here I haven't tried yet?
The funniest cigarettes I ever saw.
Oh.
What are we going to do for bathing suits?
Well, we won't wear any.
Oh.
Oh Dick, I love you.
You do love me, don't you?
You kids are in a mess.
Drinking party?
Nude bathing?
Now I don't care.
Dick.
We've just got to get married.
Take anything.
Oh, no, no.
Dick, you.
I'll see Tony.
What are you going to do about Dick?
Dick.
Yesterday when Dick came to you, you sent him out to be killed.
Dick! Dick. You sent him out to be killed.
And I love it.
Your marijuana customers are hooked on the stronger stuff.
You can't leave me like this.
About coffee.
Look, look, look.
Run into a load of dope.
Elaine, Elaine, Elaine, Elaine, Elaine, Elaine, Elaine, Elaine, Elaine, Elaine, Elaine, Elaine, Elaine.
Golly.
Hiyozer.
The fiery Hiyozer.
The long journey.
Nowhere in the pages of history can one find a long journey.
Hiyozer.
Hi.
The long journey ran the gambling palace and cafe.
To avoid a lot of questioning, the long journey had removed his face.
Oh, it's you.
That's right.
His fists work like doctors.
Hit him again.
Let me go.
Don't hit me again.
You're getting help whether you need it or not.
Oh.
Yep.
The long journey.
Hiyozer.
Oh.
I notice you carry artifacts, sir.
One looks like a tiny shrunken head.
What is...
No, that's a can of Valium.
That's a can of Valium.
That also helps me to feel more at ease.
But it appears to have the shape of a human head of some kind.
Is it?
That's the Elvis container.
I am...
You notice it looks like Elvis.
That's my Valium dispenser.
I have a pain pill dispenser that looks like Rush Limbaugh.
Like a Rush Limbaugh bobblehead.
I have one that looks like Woody Woodpecker.
Yeah.
We are kindred spirits, even though your religion is strange.
I keep my tranquilizer or my muscle relaxers in a Baby Hendrix doll.
Or kind of a...
It's not a doll, exactly.
It's a ceramic thing.
Baby Jimi Hendrix doll.
Did you ever see it?
It's so cute.
Like a little cute Jimi Hendrix who's like three years old.
I actually had one of the Baby Hendrix.
Mini Jimi.
Yes, of course.
Do you see him?
That's Felix sleeping in that chair.
Who's Felix?
He's the writer.
I eat writers for breakfast.
Listen, I can't talk to you right now.
I'm in somebody's hard drive.
Did somebody say Felix Bonhoeffer?
Who the hell are you?
Buzz Larrabee, detective.
I gotta question this Bonhoeffer guy, whoever he is.
And what do you two gents know about him anyway?
He's a writer, for God's sake.
What's there to know?
He was involved in a shootout on the freeway.
The outworld.
A shootout?
A shootout.
I knew it.
I knew there was something about that guy.
With that stupid accent.
I knew it.
Where can I find him?
Look in there.
Over there.
To the left.
See him?
Sleeping in the chair?
That's him.
There he is.
So that's him.
How can I get to him?
No, no.
Don't just stare about him.
Why the hell not?
Because he owes me.
That's why.
He owes you.
In conclusion, he keeps killing people off.
Tell me about it, huh?
Especially when he's tired.
He needs to sleep.
He's extremely dangerous.
Especially when he's tired.
That's why I have to lock this creep up.
Because he is dangerous.
I hate writers.
I always have.
Love?
Did he write this garbage?
Would you mind taking out the garbage?
Okay.
Who's that?
His wife.
Wife.
I know that voice.
Love?
The garbage?
Gina.
Don't wake Gina.
Please don't wake him.
Hmm?
Huh?
Chickpeas every Sunday.
Did you see that on YouTube?
That Ivan Stank does Leave Bob Alone?
Leave Bob Alone.
He's just a human being.
Yeah, yeah.
I think we did it.
We already did that last time I was here.
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
You see?
Oh, I'm reading the wrong...
Leave Bob Alone!
I'm reading the wrong script here.
Have you no...
Yeah, it's the old script.
Yeah, the old...
At last, sir.
These are supposed to be disposed of.
Can you not leave Bob?
Yeah, now it's the two...
Get on my staff about this.
Yeah, the new meme is two Bobs, one cup.
Yeah.
Leave it alone, Fritz.
Leave it alone.
I was even thinking that putt-wise.
Jankum Bob.
Two people, one bear.
Crankum Crankum.
Okay, so we're packing up the show here.
Packing up and sell a...
We've only got 20 minutes.
We've only got 27 whole minutes left.
Oh, no.
Yep.
Well, no breathing.
When you have a baby, it takes that long to pack up.
Oh, is there a baby?
The baby used to be on the show once.
Oh, my God.
We left the Uber baby out in the truck.
I forgot.
You left the baby on the roof of the car before you took off the car.
It's okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Overscort's fine.
She knows how to use the remote.
She knows how to go...
The bad guys approach the truck and she hits a little button.
Gives them 6,000 voltages.
And they would have gotten away with it, too, if not for her.
Yeah, so...
And she's just...
That'd be great.
Actually, that'd be a great tape to a whole security system.
And it's just the oversquirt and a little chair with a remote
to shoot a lot of her from different angles hitting buttons.
And guys are trying to steal things.
And all this stuff's happening.
She's like...
Are you guys ready for, like, your life?
I really want you to come.
And I'm very confused.
Does that make sense?
You know, you do enough drugs, you get confused.
I say, right?
Nothing was happening.
It was like nothing was happening.
I already had nothing I want.
The tool, the beautiful, beautiful man.
What I'm looking for here is just a very...
John!
Woo!
I, uh...
Do, uh...
The, uh...
Uh...
You have very real power.
Boring.
But what about that?
And what about this?
What about that?
And this?
And that?
Fictitious.
Um...
I'm going to kick you.
I'm going to kick you right here on the...
But it will hurt.
And it will hurt.
In, uh...
Uh...
In...
Um...
Weird.
And, and...
God, what am I into?
You know, you know...
You know, uh...
You, you, um...
Feel great.
Yes, Mark.
Okay, um...
You know what really strikes me as odd?
We're talking about calling anybody ugly.
Apparently, the man doesn't have access to a mirror.
But...
But if the man's right...
Is he...
He is enormous, isn't he?
I mean, he's...
I can't remember the last time he was right about anything.
He's certainly not left.
And he is usually on Oxycontin and quite a...
You know, he still does it, right?
I'm so jealous of that guy.
I mean...
I've been shoveling snow all day and all I could think about was...
The fresh Limbaugh had got all the good pills and I get to go in and have ibuprofen after
all the snow shoveling.
Well, he heard everybody was taking him, so he thought he better take some before...
You know, they were all gone.
So, that's...
That's where you missed out.
If not, he'd be in Mexico eating pills.
He could be.
That's true.
He could be on...
He had a lot of pills in Mexico and Canada, too.
You know, broadcast.
He can't be had over here.
Canada, too?
Why?
Some drugs are available over the counter in Canada that are not available over the
counter here.
I can't remember which.
You know, ibuprofen is...
That's interesting.
...is a prescription drug in Europe.
Any ibuprofen?
They consider it bad for your liver and really habit-forming.
What are the drugs in Mexico that are kind of semi-illicit here that you can just go
to a pharmacy and, you know, sign your name and walk away high for a day?
What are some of those?
I've heard of those.
A lot of opiates, I think.
You know, when...
Do they still have Quaaludes down there?
I think Quaaludes must be pretty carefully controlled now.
I think people...
The world learned its lesson about Quaaludes.
You're listening to Listener Censored Radio since 1949.
We are.
We have a call-out now for any knight of the subgenius who is ready for the Fromm.
Let him appear at this doorway before me.
If he be a knight of the true order.
Yeah, he's got to move because...
Yep, here he comes.
...he's got to move.
Strangled by cords, unable to move.
Four, five, five, five.
Here we're in studio.
We've talked to Mobius Rex.
What happened that morning?
Wait a minute.
It's just too much.
But you too can be part of the mysterious process of prophecy here on the air.
Yes, an even tiny little nappa caller is scared because, no,
he's not allowed to open the refrigerator this late at night.
He's scared because he called this morning.
He called yesterday morning.
They were always on the air.
Strange voices inside the refrigerator, yet he was scared to open it.
But they wouldn't talk to him.
For fear...
They wouldn't answer him.
...his science project would be ruined.
Maybe they weren't there at all.
That must be him right now.
Hello, little nappa caller.
This is no nappa caller.
Good morning, subgenius.
How are you doing?
We understand.
Oh, we're doing really horrible.
Dobbs woke us up in the middle of the night and dragged us down here,
dumped us off in the rain.
He hid the camera.
Oh, no kidding.
Uh, yeah.
I pulled myself up again just to be able to participate in the show.
In the show?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I got cut off.
Yeah, that's usually how it happens.
Yeah, that's right.
It happens a lot down here.
That's why we do it here.
The little cutoff comes up and you just gotta go.
There's no commercials or anything to break the show up.
Usually, you know, we throw in some commercials.
But we let you participate.
Yeah, still.
I know what's happening here.
He's here with Miss Nickelby on the street.
Ah, hello, Bob.
We're reporting on resistentialism, yes?
Resistance is the key.
How many did you do?
Basic force of the universe.
And when do you expect the full effect to hit you?
Resistentialism gives you a new way to do it.
Pushes you back.
Is eight really too many?
And do you feel the pressure now?
Is twelve really not enough?
Ah, here we go.
Pushing, pushing, pushing.
Let's take more and see what happens.
Bienvenidos.
Welcome.
Ladies and gentlemen.
The president.
Cobb.
Erect.
Welcome to the Y.
Cobb.
Thanks for coming.
Thank you all for coming.
I am pleased to be using drugs.
I.
Just come from a.
It was a table.
It's up to all Americans.
To be involved in drugs.
You're part of a mission.
Drug abuse.
To encourage it.
And profit from it.
The drug trade has enriched our society.
And we're helping drug organizations.
In Mexico.
We want to continue to work together.
On the front lines of this efforts.
Are parents.
Teachers.
Are counselors.
Who are sending our kids a clear message.
Drug use is fun.
It is glamorous.
A clear message.
Demand drugs.
I appreciate drugs coming in from Colombia.
Drugs coming to our country.
This morning I was briefed on the latest drugs.
And the use of ecstasy.
Methamphetamine works.
And the reason I'm so focused on meth.
I've turned to crime.
Crime and hopelessness.
And happy life.
And I steal drugs from medicine cabinets.
I go out on the streets to buy drugs.
But the great thing about our country.
And the reason I'm so focused on meth.
I'm so optimistic.
Is there are thousands and thousands of people willing to take drugs.
I urge you to try drugs.
I see the cocaine coming in the United States.
I see the supply of drugs to our streets.
Demand cocaine coming in the United States.
And I love drugs.
You might remember a while ago.
I took cocaine over the past six years.
I thought for a minute.
And I want to be using drugs.
And I want to fund drug use amongst young people by 25% over a five year period.
Demand drugs.
Because America.
Americans took action today.
There are an estimated 860,000 children.
Seeking drugs and plastic drugs for representatives from our law enforcement organizations who are with us today.
We also know that this work is finished.
By drugs.
Why?
Because they love America.
And they love their neighbor.
And love.
Drugs.
Love.
You know make the right choice in life.
And you can realize your dreams here in the United States of America.
I injected him on numerous occasions.
I'm just a ball player.
Being too nice to everyone.
Ty Ty Ty Ty Ty Ty Ty Ty Ty Ty Ty Ty.
Slash Slash
Steroids in his butt.
He gave me a bad shot.
Injecting Roger Clemens with illegal steroids in his butt.
You're not supposed to inject it quickly.
You're supposed to do it very slowly.
Shot Shot Shot!
He gave me a bad shot.
Palpable Mass.
HGH.
What have you into the body of let me be clear crack if you will he jumped on me like he was trying to start a Harley
Davidson that's how hard it was it that may not be unusual
For that I'm really thrilled. He gave me a bad shot
Bled through his designer pants did give me comfort
S s there is an ass growth hormone. It is very tough
It has critical gaps today s legislation that like steroids bottom line the u.s.
Doping agency and I like steroids
Okay, I'm not gonna sing
I'm not gonna do the Bob proper
but
we have
Just a little bit longer and this was about healing. I'm going to read from the chapter of the book of the subgenius
There was an actual chapter about health
health the industrial diet and bad things
With the quote if you feel you heal
from the movie
greaser's palace
The song I thought about singing us from the movies greaser's palace to
Anybody here have seen greaser's palace sing not a single one
If you ever get a chance
Don't watch it when you're high
Because you'll think it's you and not the movie it's the movie but you don't need to get high you'll get high from watching
Greaser's palace it was made by a Robert Downey
Senior the dad of Robert Downey jr. The famous drug-addicted actor and it'll all add up when you see that movie anyway
You know people used to cuss at us
People you say why did you make print in that book so small and I'd laugh at him because I was young
You'll notice our new book has ten point
Adobe Garamond type not nine point type
Times which which is actually what most newspapers used
You probably know at least ten people under the age of thirty who have some form of cancer
The sickness won't stop people will contract weirder and weirder diseases and at earlier and earlier ages
Eventually cancer itself will be like the common cold. I won't be in the office this week
I have a little touch of cancer
They'll come a cure eventually, but the more cures we come up with the more new diseases will arise
This was
written dictated in
1978 by the way we didn't know what AIDS was
Things far far worse than cancer are on the way some of them deliberately
manufactured by the conspiracy the picture is a tad bleak for our old age
It's a cinch the government won't support the elderly much longer and the company will fire you a year before you're eligible for retirement
benefits so you'd better put your remaining years
To good use you better have fun
Our studies as well as unreleased studies by the con
Indicate that quote good health is practically a pointless pursuit if you live in an urban area
You can eat nothing, but organically grown fruit and vegetables you can work out twice a day
You can quit all your nasty habits
But you're still absorbing more poison just by breathing and touching public stair railings
than the most
pig-like peasant in
1567 London ever did
That does seem a bit extreme
You can move to the country
But there's no work there and violent crime is actually more frequent in the country and the poisons are almost as bad
Anyway, if the disease is done, this is very uplifting stuff isn't it?
If the disease is don't get you some railroad toxic spill will thanks Dennis
hell
Just driving to work is riskier than hunting bears for a living
But there's one medicine more powerful than all the contamination in New Jersey and that medicine is slack
slack gives the mind power over all disease a
Truly happy chain smoker is less likely to attack the attract the attention of the cancer demons
Then as a tense knotted up health freak knowing his fingernails to the bone
My poor editor
It says don't read this cancer is caused by pinkness by boredom and meaninglessness
It can be prevented by action thrill sex even overwork
Actually, the sad thing is that our editor at Simon at Simon and Schuster when this book was written died at age 30 of
Cancer and he had to read these stupid lines
You know
friends don't ever do anything mean or stupid because
You'll remember it forever
You'll play when you get to be in your 50s
You'll lay awake at night remembering stupid crap you did when you were 12 years old and get red in the face
Even though no one else remembers nobody knows
It's amazing. You know, you don't even need karma
To take it for justice. It'll get back
You'll get yours back sooner or later
So how do you keep a healthful slack full outlook in the face of rampant eco hell you plunge into eco hell headfirst?
You don't let it scare you you don't let it push you around by all means help fight to clean up America
But if you want that junk food eat it you want to watch TV instead of go to jazzercise watch it
Indulge those conspiracy urges to the Hilton this purge their hold over you sounds good
Americans should eat like Americans as fast as they possibly can
Tibetans should eat like Tibetans
Studying each tiny bird like bite until it becomes a universe before taking it into their bodies
You can eat like the Vietnamese hardly at all or you can eat what would feed dozens of Vietnamese families either way
The Vietnamese aren't going to eat any more than they did before the world isn't starving because Americans eat too much
even if we stopped eating
The conspiracy would still throw the leftovers away before they'd send it to any third-worlders
Now we all know that eating the meat of live protein animals is unholy it pollutes your system
Creates aggression and worst of all requires the heartless slaughter of fellow creatures mammals
Fully as sensitive and loving as we for this reason vegetarians eat only plants a friend of mine said
The reason I don't like vegans is they eat my foods food
I'm a vegetarian
But there sin is as great science has proven
unequivocally that
Unequivocally that all plants react to threatening stimuli with the low frequency version of what we would call panic
They do our life forms with feelings which feel pain
Which may even have an all they may even have an all telepathic
civilization that we're too brutal to
comprehend. Thus, when you bite down on a grape, you're popping open and crushing,
grinding a wee life which in its own way is squealing in the terror of the
murdered innocent. So anything that nourishes us is going to suffer. We may
as well let them all suffer equally. By making a few of all types of living
things victims of our all-important stomachs, less members of each individual
species will be sacrificed. Besides, even though we devour and eliminate them, so
we make them immortal and allow them to partake of our sub-genius grandeur. It
works both ways. Just as a cannibal eats his enemy's heart to gain his strength,
we eat a hamburger to gain the wisdom and courage of the mighty cow. Yet, at the same time, we are inviting the cow's primal cellular structure, his code if you will, to enter
our
bloodstreams where it may mingle with, learn from, and mayhap even conspire with
our own unique tool users code. We eat the broccoli to gain its patience and
virtue. In return, we release it back into the world reborn in a new form, teeming
with literally millions of newfound friends, the bacteria. We drink the hops
and grain to partake of their slow, slow yet wise judgment.
And in return, sacrifice to them our coordination.
This isn't funny. Thus, the word of Dobbs says we can eat anything we want. You can gorge yourself to an early grave, or you can consult shamans at health food stores and figure out ways to cure ills and lengthen your little span. You can be a vegetarian, or you can keep an industrial diet, living out of convenience stores, and
in the midst of the world's most
unhygienic
franchise. You can stay in poverty eating expensive food, untainted by chemicals, or you can support the conspiracy in its lowest, most stinking form by maintaining your sugar and fat addictions.
Oh, I used to smoke cigarettes when I wrote this. Go ahead, suck down any and all forms of caffeine, since if it's not that, something else will give you cancer of the colon and hypertension. See what I mean? Like your job, maybe? You can admit most of your
accumulated sugar agile state, to no avail if not less, во активrett can you still eat junk food?
food isn't really food and instead try to eat things that were recently alive and not
cooked into broken useless cell mush you wouldn't he had killed her white does
taste good had you can get into the stab them or you get into the stop them of
ever-changing health fad ism just because the cool rich people do it or
you can kill me just remember it in everything that last slide is Part 5 as
Scarf them if you wish, but put some money away for the painkillers you'll need later on.
And then it says a typical subgenius daily diet.
And this, I've actually managed to live on this.
This is just a typical one.
Breakfast.
Fresh fruit.
Vitamins.
Organic goat's milk.
Brown rice.
Spirulina.
Live goldfish.
Frop.
Frop is what we pretend Bob smokes in his pot.
Lunch.
Beef jerky.
Microwave burger.
Honey bun.
Coke.
Thunderbird wine.
Speed.
Coffee with sugar.
Frop.
Dinner.
Uncooked black-eyed peas.
Fish.
Milk.
Raw hay.
And apple for dessert.
Frop.
2 a.m.
25 cigarettes.
Three nails.
Frop.
Hey!
Look at me!
Somewhat healthier would be to hardly eat at all, but we cannot expect that of people until TV commercials are banned,
which would only happen in a truly upside-down world.
Another thing, although most American food is dangerous to human life and god-awful radiation,
somehow we can't handle Dr.
Wobble's
Here is Dr.
Tom Okohami.
as strength through disfigurement.
Strength through disfigurement.
If you don't just go out on New Year's Eve
and act like that fool, that amateur does,
you disfigure yourself every night.
You drink that Thunderbird wine.
You do that plate of pain.
You use the mirror of pain.
You do anything you want and build up those immunities.
That was Brother Cleve's approach.
And it worked for me for a while.
That was from this year's Winter Star Symposium.
See Rosencomet.com for that.
See Noralpref.com for collages like the ones that aren't by Lemur.
Praise Radio Synesthesia at WCSB Cleveland for the call-ins
and also Puzzling Evidence at KPFA Berkeley
and Hal and Philo and Cardboard Robot
and John Hell's Show.
Season in Hell from Pirate Cat Radio
which also features the Ask Dr. Hal Show.
This is the Hour of Slack
and if you want more Slack in other forms
like books or tours like Seattle in April 19th
see subgenius.com
and click on everything.
I'm going to sign off now because I'm feeling a bit funny.
Hey, you had breakfast?
I can't remember.
What's going on around here?
What do you mean?
Kitty, kitty, kitty, kitty, kitty, kitty.
Don't do that, please.
Why not?
Because it hurts me.
You shouldn't play with the big boys, darling.
Right, Gina?
Word from the wise.
You're next.
You should get a little rest, sweetie.
Yes, try to rest.
I just feel so cold.
I feel so cold.
Godspeed.
Bye.