The subgenius powerhouse.
Bob!
All right!
Well done!
Thank you!
we'll see you next week.
Thank you.
This week is also from 24XDay, the fourth hour of Slack, second hour, with Dr. Howell, Reverend Pease, Papa Joe Mama, and myself, as follows.
That free beer is a good example of what we're talking about, the problem of everything being too perfect.
Because it's free, I've been finding warm, opened, almost full blossom, orange blossom.
Blossom cans.
Everywhere.
Very warm.
I've obviously, you know, they've been sitting there at least five minutes.
Popped open.
Two sips taken out.
Oh, thanks, Dr. Howell.
This will last about five minutes.
That orange blossom special.
Yeah, and it's because it's free.
They, you know, they don't, if they had paid for that beer, they'd carry it around until it was finished.
But as it is, they just put it down somewhere and look around.
Oh, where'd that beer go?
I'll just get another one.
A ridiculous number of cigarettes laying around.
Why is it that the old timers end up doing the cleanup?
Oh, I know.
Oh, now I remember why I've got OCD.
Yeah.
I would do it anyway.
You would do it anyway.
It doesn't have anything to do with the good feelings.
It's like, oh, there's a thing that's out of place.
I must put it in order.
If they weren't there, you wouldn't know what to do.
So you took too much OCD when you were young?
Yeah.
It's.
It worked for me.
I mean, it's.
Hey, that's all wrong.
That's all wrong.
No, it's right my way, though.
It's wrong for you, but it's right for me.
No, this is wrong.
There's the perfect balance.
No, no, no.
It's.
Immersion tile versus the reward.
Ian.
Easy staying.
Yeah, that's right.
He's got ADHD.
Yeah.
OCD says, why we need to stick together together.
Together.
We're almost an alphabet.
I was telling my grandson could finish this puzzle game in two hours.
It took me two days and he goes, I'm smarter than you.
And I said, your brain works faster for sure, but I know a lot more.
So we need to work together, kid.
And I'm convinced that that's what you have to do.
The speed of thought might be overrated.
My wife is a complete reward in hoarding.
Now, do the do the grandsons do Legos?
Do they do the Legos?
The kids?
Yeah.
No, I haven't.
Adult foot torture devices.
They were they've been into all the kid fads, but Legos is old time.
Well, see, that's the thing.
I asked my daughter to get me this Lego cake because I thought, oh, that'll be relaxing for me.
So I have her get me this Saturn.
Five replica of the Lego thing.
Right. And I'm like, I'm a I'm a jam this out.
Right. Well, I get about third way done.
And there's just one little thing that I didn't do right.
So I got to take it all apart.
I don't think I'm ever going to finish that rocket.
I think I got a toy that was a toy is too challenging for peas.
Well, there's not an age limit on it.
Promises a future.
You need even if it's a future of putting together a Lego.
I read the instructions.
I looked at the emergent tiles, read the instructions first.
Rewarding is only that never read the instructions.
I just want to rock it.
I remember when Legos came in.
That was in my lifetime.
And they replaced what I used before that, which I liked much better.
American plastic bricks.
Yes, American plastic bricks were great.
They overlapped and so on.
They were somewhat like Legos, but with them.
It was all about building.
Miniature buildings with windows and doors, stairways, chimneys, all that stuff with the bricks.
You can get them all interlocked and, you know, make perfect buildings.
But those are real hard to find now.
I know. Well, they broke very easily.
The they weren't tough like Legos.
Nothing can break them.
Then there was the kits that have little plastic girders and panels that you've made skyscraper.
Yes.
Well, the erector set was metal.
The erector set was metal.
I'm talking about plastic.
Meccano.
Yeah, I had a little plastic thing and you had a little friction gun that you melted the girders to each other with friction.
And then you put little plastic sheets on.
You could build these really elaborate skyscrapers.
But it was kind of a gyp toy because once you had soldered the girders together.
Why would you solder them?
They just snapped together.
Well, I'm just telling you my version of that toy.
Mine didn't snap together.
You had to like get the end of it like gluey with this little friction thing that spun around and then you stuck it to another girder.
Are you sure that you just didn't read the instructions?
Maybe I was doing it wrong.
Maybe you were creatively customizing it.
I think I'm going to find that toy.
But once again, we're talking about toys that existed in the 60s and nobody even knows what the hell we're talking about now.
The 60s?
I was talking about the 50s.
But in the 60s, things came in like the Great Garlou and so forth.
Oh, I wanted the Great Garlou so bad.
Yeah, the other kids all had it.
I'll have one tomorrow.
I wasn't allowed to get a Great Garlou either.
I was told it was ridiculous.
I'm going to have the Great Garlou tomorrow.
Anything I can remember.
And those building kits.
How about Robert the Robot?
I never had that.
The other kids had Robert the Robot.
I had Mr. Atom.
However, Mr. Atom.
had many praiseworthy features.
But it didn't talk like Dan Robert the Robot.
Was that the one that had a top hat and went like this?
That's Mr. Machine, which is sort of a two-dimensional robotoid thing.
It did have a top hat.
Mr. Atom had changeable eye lenses in his atomic eye sockets and so forth.
But was mainly a walking robot of the boxy kind.
Everybody's rockin' so much.
We rockin' robots.
When the Japanese actually did break that barrier and create the first humanoid robots
in 1999, the Honda company, what was so strange was they looked like those boxy robots of our
childhood with feet like shoe boxes and so forth.
But they could move with exquisite gliding.
They could go up and down a flight of stairs without clanging on to anything.
Dr. Hal, did you see this?
highly evolved magnolia blossoms painted in the famous
Rudolf Zellinger mural at the Peabody Museum in Yale, you know, life through the ages that one. They were
more like proto flowers, but it doesn't take long for
things that are on a good course of evolving to
evolve and so the
you have the gymnosperms and the angiosperms
and the
So anyway, they probably had some crude butterflies something they had the things before they had the insects to pollinate them
Yeah, apparently
I'm sorry. I have that wrong. They had the insects and then they had the things well
You know think about maybe it would be that's why it would destroy
time because it would be like the first butterfly and
Then that because you stepped on it that eliminated that whole food source
For the and it could be it could be a desolate wasteland
If we did that perhaps we should heed and take heed and take caution and maybe
Slay not the moth nor the butterfly
The big lesson is you go back in time to try to fix things
For the last judgment draweth nigh
Any time you go back in time to fix something you break something else
It always happens. So you can't get back to your own timeline
You have to go with this timeline that you created
The church used to be much bigger till Stang went back in the timeline to fix it and here we are
Here's it. Here's a
Green play all to avoid a certain is pretty good movie
Harold Harold and Kumar meet Hitler they they go back in time to kill Hitler
but they they
He said he hadn't joined the Nazis yet
and he's just a frustrated artist and they go wait a minute, let's just get a whole bunch of his art and
And take that back. He'll be worth millions, you know
In in our times an original they make friends with Hitler the pre-nazi Hitler
and he's never been laid and and they and he's never been high and they get him drunk and high and they get him laid and
He's not interested in the Nazis the Nazis start, you know trying to recruit him. He's like I'll go away fuck off
I mean, I like these guys with their pot
he was party member number eight and so they they go back to their own time with all these Hitler paintings and
Everybody's going who's Hitler? These are mediocre landscape paintings
Why the hell would we pay you for the badly done?
architectural
Wanderings
Well, so not only do you humiliate Hitler who however in this scenario is not guilty
But you prevent the suffering in the terrible war
It's funny. I know but poor sure that the World War two never happened and the world is much better
But they can't sell those stupid painting that Adolf Hitler went on to win the Nobel
priest mentioned it from PR news in Washington
I'm decrying the violent political crisis in Nicaragua
Saying I'm repressing social protest to launch a nationwide collaboration
The collaborative will seek data driven answers on the causes and patterns of PR news
Scientists will examine characteristics risk factors and interventions
Tonight in Oakland, California White House economic adviser Larry says don't go to school
meanwhile, there are reports of death threats against PR news a
Houston foundation is giving two dollars to launch a study on
hot dry and windy violence from other philanthropists in Santa Fe, Texas
The New York Times says it's spreading officials say that may help in the short term, but this is PR news in Washington
Mentioned this before but the modern world was created by Annie Oakley. I told you about this
You know the famous little sure shot. Yeah, she could shoot. She was at Buffalo Bills Wild West shows
He was a great attraction there
She used to shoot
Cigarettes out from between her husband's lips backwards with a rifle looking in a mirror
She could always do it and one time these visiting Germans
insisted especially this one German princeling
insisted on getting down there and being the guy that she shot the
The cigarette out from he screamed I insist and he stamped his boots and so Buffalo Bill said, you know
It's his dime and he's down there. He's holding the cigarette and Annie is so
She's a little bit nervous, but she shoots and she makes the shot but four inches to the left
There would have been no Kaiser Wilhelm
certainly no
Assassination at Sarajevo no World War one no angry corporal Hitler no Dachau Belson Hiroshima
Any of that all because Annie Oakley was such a good shot and she really was it was instinctive
to her but sometimes
This fucking up can be the greatest gift that you can give to the
World that's how Bob does everything
And up is how I
Lived my life
I was I wasn't gonna say I wasn't gonna say anything
It's a hard path of chosen, but it's mine
Yeah, you can. You're welcome to it, please. Yes the way you walk is thorny
Well, look at this. I mean it's it's
It's succeeding.
He's replaced Bob.
The Dobbstown Weekly Whiff Reader doesn't have a single picture of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
It has pictures of peas.
It has all these hideous pictures of peas, dozens of them.
Everything's about you these days, Bob.
They put in your picture and mine at the end.
All you do is f*** up.
I know.
It's a claim to fame.
Isn't it awesome?
You fall upwards.
He's a good example of a subgenius.
Almost Bob-like in his childlike simplistic idiocy.
You may be comforted by that thought until he purges you from the party.
In incompetence and completely shot memory, he's kind of a little bit more Bob-like than most of us.
What were you saying?
There is that.
You're entering the fringes of overman territory, the way you've been acting, like Philo.
Yeah, Philo.
Philo is a lot like that.
Internal transformation that takes place upon oneself as you near the rupture time.
The landing side is here.
I'm starting to feel the power of the collective nature of the subgenius
and getting excited about my pleasure vessel and the sex goddesses,
which is, you know, as Stang has said, it's very important you understand his distinction.
Sex goddess takes on whatever form you like.
You like hamsters?
Sex goddess is a hamster.
On the other hand, they employ a chemical...
Watch two girls making it.
I'd rather be two girls making it.
So strong that what you want is what they are,
even though they may look like a cross between a steel spring mattress and a giant crab or something.
With this chemical attractant, you will frenziedly copulate with these so-called sex goddesses.
And enjoy it.
The first film screens wiele videos material.
Grandma's smashing the cats again
She's calling the class
She says I gotta feed them less
I can't do that because my furballs are the best
Yes
Meow, meow, meow, meow, meow, meow, meow
Meow
Meow, meow, meow, meow, meow, meow
Grandma lifts my cat, she says it's unbelievable
That I even let him get this big at all
I said it's not my fault, he loves to eat, he loves his treats
And when he's good, I feed him his favorite good old fancy feets
So best for me to live one most delicious meal in every camp
Every camp
From PR News in Washington, I'm searching for 36,000 people buried
Because of a volcanic same-sex
couple, citing his religious wildfire
The Dow is 91-12-33
PR's reports
This is PR News
I'm gonna go turn off that coffee machine
It's probably already scorched the coffee
I didn't think this coffee was so bad
In fact, I enjoyed mine
Good to the last drop
Well, I need to mix the stuff in
I'll mix the stuff in
Alright, make sure you put lots of it in
Oh, I will
I can't believe you're
Thank you
Dr. Howell has an iron tongue and stomach
Do I?
I guess it's from reciting all that poetry
That could vulcanize your throat, certainly
Sorry, it's too late for me to offer to move the chair
Watch out for the extra briefcase there
I attempted to make his egress more simplistic
But he, being the master, knew better than I, the young acolyte
Well, Reverend, I'm sorry, but I'm not sure you're going to be able to do that in the next few days
I'm sorry, but I'm not sure you're going to be able to do that in the next few days
How do you like the great state of Florida
And its marvelous invasion of walking catfish yesterday?
Well, I couldn't believe that we were all so blessed to have seen this miracle of Bob come about
I was told you were tripping at the time
Well, I stumbled here and there from place to place
But, you know, this is what I want to do in a wet environment
Some of them even wriggled into the house
Across the carpet and so forth
Wow
You are crafty devils
Yeah, well, it's not good for them because the carpet is not wet with the dews of heaven
But it's dry and it's scraping off the mucus layer that generally surrounds and protects them
It brings back memories of the failed church venture of marketing those fish as pets
And it did not work out well and Stang had to move
My memory is vague, but I do remember that these same walking catfish created no...
National attention a few years ago
There was some national story about walking catfish disturbed Floridans and so forth
Yes, it was a walk across America to gather funds for the Lou Gehrig's disease
But they didn't have as many catfish participants as they wanted
So it kind of fizzled out
Philo's daughter was at the X-Day in Wisteria a couple of years ago
And she didn't want to come anywhere near the catfish
She didn't want to come near the adults because she was afraid she'd see the naked person
She was what a prude
I mean, that was her choice
She also didn't like it when she heard bad language
This is the daughter of a subgenius
This is going to be in the Bulldada auction
A DVD of God's Cartoonist, the movie I was talking about yesterday
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I did that cover
What? Really?
A documentary by...
It's possible you might even autograph it for someone, isn't it?
I've never met him
And now I'm involved in drawing another one of those things
And it has...
Yeah, it's got animated versions of chick comics brought to life
Of the history of the great man and all of his artists
It's got me making a terrible mistake
I don't know, I hope people think I'm doing it on purpose
Where I mention John 3.16 instead of 3.17
Oh yeah, that really stood out
It did
Because that's the Jesus...
John 3.16
For he so loved the world he gave his only begotten son
Yeah, yeah
There's a store in West Virginia where everything was priced
Three, either $3.16, $31.60
Jesus Christ
That was the only prices
It didn't last long
From PR News in Washington, I'm not guilty
Ethiopia was set to expire
Ethiopia was beset by a storm
Sparking power
The head of the Roman Catholic Church sent a telegram today saying
This is PR News
This Don't Think button goes very well with this wonderful t-shirt image of Bob's pipe
Smoking Bob's brain
It almost looks like a tree
I saved this one for today
It's my favorite
Emerging from the bowl of Bob's pipe
I think Aspira did this
Beautiful job
Oh yeah, it's one of my...
It says...
Subgenius Olympic Doping Committee
That's me
See, subgenius olympics, you are not allowed to participate unless you're doping of some kind
Okay, we don't want really good athletes
Oh, you can just be a dope
Or a dope, yeah
And by definition...
But the dope is such an ugly word
We prefer the term subgenius
There, see I do it every day
Why do you think they call it dope?
Every single day
Yeah
Subgenius Olympic Doping Committee
Doping Committee
We're going to have our own version, sort of, of the Olympics today
We're going to have the Olympics
The Special Olympics
And it will be a phallic festival of fun
I saw that in the schedule
Yeah
No, it was the Olymp-dics, wasn't it?
The Olymp-dics
Yeah, well that's easy
Did I say it wrong?
I should win that one real easily
I've got so many of them, and pretty much all of them have gone limp
I was thinking...
There's one that I forgot to mention...
I can still crank up if I work at it
I was thinking... well...
And by crank up, I mean pee
Is it a manual type crank, or is it like one of those push buttons for your blinds?
Both
You know how the blinds kind of...
Either one
Oh, okay, that's handy
That's handy
It's based on a garage door opener, actually
Well, Dear Abby recommends putting some sort of device in there
That can be activated from a remote control box
It's like a comedy
One of her columns that I read
Dear Abby suggested put a thing in there that you can control with a remote control
TV remote control box
An automatic stiffening device
It was in her column, her serious answer to somebody's question
Well, I was thinking something between an auto-suck and a garage door opener
And a garbage disposal
Why not both?
All three, yeah
Yeah
Yeah, why not all three?
Yeah, I don't know why not all three, but...
Three sometimes comes up
I think the auto-suck combined with the garbage disposal would be really awesome
But it depends on which end you put the garbage disposal
Like if it's first...
Oh yeah, you don't want to screw...
You don't want to do it when you're drunk
Yeah
Just what kind of disposal are you...
Stay sober for that type of pleasure
Yeah
As if the garbage ever really went away
It never actually goes away
That's the illusion
That you whisk it away
It's just food for the sea friends
Uh huh
That's what the walking catfish eat
The algal slime set to cover the earth
Now is that what makes the coating on them?
Or that's the secretion that they exude?
What's the secretion?
The catfish, you were...
Earlier you were giving a warning that you...
Besides touching them because of the barbs
That there's a mucus...
Yeah, they...
That's an interface they have between themselves and the environment
I got it
So they...
But they can scrape that mucus off
Particularly when they slither into your house
And are scraping across the carpet and the floor
You know, you're gaining no liquid
And you're losing that mucus
So those fish had to be helped out by helpful human xanthia
I got to be good friends with several of them
Before I cast them back into the pond
Well that's good
I'm sure that will count as well
That's part of your score
I've got to say this is my favorite part of X-Day
A new animal
I've never encountered before
And never...
Hundreds of them
All over the yard
All I could think of was
Peas is tripping
He's going to freak out
It took a long time to see them
But then after seeing the first one
We saw hundreds of them
Billy, you deal with shit
He was completely immune to it
He was a regular Ken Kesey
Walking fish
Mary Prankster school of acid overdosing
And still functioning
You have to be able to drive the fish
You have to drive a school bus
While tripping on four hits of acid
And you pass the acid test
Peas passed that test yesterday
I'm so proud
I can't wait to tell my mother
I've passed that test so many times
I don't need to take it anymore
The school bus?
Really?
Well a school bus full of hippies
Not full of kids
Not children
That would be criminal
That would be irresponsible
If it was like that it would happen
No one cares what happens to you
I've ended up tripping and driving
But I don't recommend it
When I was 18
I read Tom Wolfe's
Glamorized story of the Mary Pranksters
The electric Kool-Aid acid test
And I distinctly remember thinking
Man, what a cool scene
I wish I could do something like that
Well since then
I've actually seen the bus movie
Kesey sent it to me himself
And we so totally outdid the Mary Pranksters
And Kesey, we never went as far as having the Hell's Angels hanging around
To scare everybody
And I never had to escape the police in a helicopter
And I never went to prison
Because we didn't have LSD
Jars of LSD around
But we managed to do the big national freak out thing
Better than those guys ever dreamed of
Of course they didn't have the internet
And they had to use 16mm cameras
But then so did I for a long time
Anyway, Kesey was a subgenius
He actually wanted to come
I didn't know that
Yeah, yeah, he would have been at the first convention
If I'd had money for a plane ticket
Not only that
He said, you know, get me a plane ticket
First church of the last laugh also
Yeah, I never met Kesey
He was there for one of those
His buddy Ken is still in touch
And his son is selling Bob Blotter replicas
Somebody sent me a link to
Some asshole is selling fake acid
Blotter acid with Bob on it
And I looked at it and it was like
Oh, that's Ken Kesey's son
Oh, we owe them, that's okay
He's allowed
I'm not gonna bother him
I should have hit him up for a free copy though
But, yeah, boy, Kesey died real suddenly
Exactly when he was my age
67, I think
Everybody thought he was just fine
It was liver, some liver thing
But you had a close brush a couple years ago
The same thing could have happened
But they rushed you in the helicopter
Helicopter, yeah, yeah
Saved you
Yeah
Oh, I wasn't any
I was just a mere 90% blockage
Yeah, you'd be fine
I waited three hours to go to the doctor
Reading about heart attacks
Guys, I love you so much
Taking aspirin and drinking beer
And thinking, listen, go away
I'm gonna take a break
And let Papa Joe Mama come up here
And get ready for the rest of our crazy events
That we got planned up
The Ask Dr. Hal show
Olympics
Uh, baptism
Oh, man, how could I forget that?
Baptism
You've gotta get
I'm gonna get baptismed again
Just cause I don't like it when Stang touches me
So
No, we're gonna do that in the pool
Or, I think the pool
No, there's an alligator in the damn pond
We're doing it in the pool
Well, I did heard the hot tub
And I thought that's a dumb idea
Too small
That's just gonna be a subgenius stew
As somebody pointed out
Since all of our funk washes off
You know, we're gonna have to
Get off into that pool water
When we go home
We'll be covered with each other's germs
Like, did you say funk or stomp?
No, I don't know if that's togetherness
Or just gross
Well, I
Maybe both
Why not both?
Trust me
Keep the pH of that pool
Stomach turning and endearing
At the same time
There'll be lots of new subgeniuses in nine months
All from the pool experience
Well, it'll broaden our gene pool
That, too, is often a topic of
We've never had the problem that the Amish had
Dear Abbie
Could you be impregnated by being in a pool
While someone had been masturbating?
They asked Abbie that
And Abbie went into it and said that
There was a very remote possibility
That that could happen
Now, hold on, Hal
People describe me a good debater
But a master debater
That's taken a little far
No one is more than momentarily mastered
Then there's the relaxation and ease
That would just take me too long
I used to be able to knock one off
In about 30 seconds
Oh, is it?
I mean, in about an hour and a half
Coming and going
Coming and always too soon
Used to be able to hit the ceiling
Crumb said he felt he'd been released
By some force that made him act like an idiot
And I'm glad it was gone
Oh, old man at old age got me
What you got in there?
Eh, he brought some nuts for the nuts
Yeah, there you go
Soup to nuts
For some nuts
Well, there's some odd stuff
Almonds in there
Some color-appropriated raisins
And all sorts of unusual
The rural rednecks of Texas
Seem to think that California
Is just a bunch of silly antifa libtards
Burning all their cities down
They don't seem to understand
That most of California
Is actually farmland
Full of conservative rednecks
Absolutely
And fruit-saving
Fruits and nuts
They have
It is a land of fruits and nuts
And the human ones live in the big cities
But the countryside is regular edible fruits and nuts
And they're really good
And I've never understood
Why these rural Texans hate California so much
Well, that goes for the rest of the country
They say California starts a trend
And then the country follows it
So what's in California now
Will be universal soon
And much sooner than it used to be
You being in the religious biz, though
I mean, any good religion person
Should know that
It's not about loving your own religion
That brings people together
It's hating the other religions
Right
That's why
The dream of everyone else going to hell
The same thing happens with politics
You gotta hate the other side
That's what brings all of your side together
Right
You gotta really
And it's become
That's what all it is now
Nobody can say anything good about their own side
They can only say
Infinite bad lies about the other side
I'm still waiting for the
Biden's the best president ever bumper sticker
It's out there somewhere, I'm sure
But we're still getting the we hate Trump stickers
And of course, when Trump was president
Obama was his turn in the barrel
Everybody hates the other guy
When Trump is reinstated in August, you mean?
Lock them all up
Lock us up
They've all thrown a little in a hole
What at the end of the wing
Wait what's he doing
Oh I was withdrawal
Isn't it ridiculous
Why not
Look at the
We've always been
We've always become
Everyone's a one-man band
Somebody called it
Media
I'm saying
There's Toward
On the bar
There's Crystals
I think
On the bar
We'll see what happens
I'm looking out at my class here today and I'm noticing you're all wearing blue jeans.
Do you mean like that?
Yeah, well, you see, it's a convergence of forces.
And one of them is convenience.
Because if you just dress like everybody else, then you don't have to spend time thinking about it or worrying about it.
So you are free to do other things.
You're not occupied with something that is trivial.
The Brundlefly School of Clothing Fashion just wear the same suit every day.
We got that idea from Einstein.
He said, I essentially do pretty much the same thing.
I just don't even think about it.
I'm not fabric oriented and don't give a shit what other people think about how I look.
That would never have worked for me.
There was never any point in which I thought, if only I looked a little more slick.
Wait a minute, what am I talking about?
Well, it's a slippery slope.
If you start caring about the way you look, the next thing you're going to worry about is the way that other people perceive your thoughts.
Right, exactly.
It can be more motivated by the way you don't want to look.
So that ends up determining how you look.
Defiance.
The central ingredient to subgeniusness.
Says the guy wearing the SS uniform hat, but with a Dobbs head stuck on top.
No, I'm not.
This isn't SS.
This is actually a communist hat.
Is it?
Yeah.
Papa Joe was Stalin.
Uh-huh.
But, you know, I don't want to put down, I mean, after all, the Nazis did come in second place.
But first place actually goes to Mao Zedong.
Yeah.
And then I guess it depends on where you draw the lines, but Papa Joe Stalin did come in a close second and Hitler third.
Did you ever read the last Doc Savage novel ever written, but not Papa Joe?
No.
I think it's the last one he published where Doc and his men go into Stalinist Russia for an operation.
No, no, uh-uh.
I thought the last Doc Savage novel he actually started down to hell.
Up from Earth's center.
This is the one.
It's the last one because he gets killed.
And he ran into something that terrified even him.
Yes.
But there was another one after that?
It's called The Red Spider.
Wow.
Did it get reprinted somehow?
I have it with me.
I'm going to put it in the bulldog to auction.
He keeps it with him at all times.
Okay, I got dibs on that one.
Oh, really?
You may have.
Why bother putting it into auction?
Onan recently sent me a collection of every Doc Savage comic book.
Oh, yes.
They had Street and Smith published them.
I had no idea how many times.
I didn't know how many times it had been attempted.
There were like 20 different versions.
There was a slight difference about it.
I had to wear this hood with a special jewel in it that gave him his powers.
Do you remember that?
No.
That he got from an old priestly llama-like person?
I don't know.
In the comic.
He wore high boots and pants, no shirt, and this hood with the jewel on it.
And if you weren't totally pure and a super being like Doc Savage, it would kill you to
put it on.
But Clark Savage was a super being.
And I knew, I knew he was a super being.
That's the way it was in the comic book, not in the pulp magazines.
So he survived.
He was worthy.
Worthy of the jewel.
He perfected himself.
That was his idea.
Like Batman, Doc Savage just started out as an ordinary person who trained himself with
exercises and mental exercises and acrobatics and chemistry and science and ballistics and
...
Batman owes Doc Savage an explanation for sure
well my favorite
the utility belt and all that stuff
Doc Savage had all that
and he didn't need a mask
he had a fortress of solitude before Superman did
that's where Superman got that idea
well I could tell you
Arctic retreat where he goes and meditates
in the snow in his speedos or something
well think about it
Clark Kent
both Clark Kent and Bruce Wayne
would have been the right age to have been reading
Doc Savage pulp novels
that's true
when they were coming out in the early 30s
deep into his Peter
even with new technology
cunt
cool
your empty soul
It can't possibly be that hard
I get impatient as well
But I'd rather wait
for the second
to see if I need to jump out
guitar solo
These kids are pretty quick
on their feet
So you're looking
for some trouble
When you're going nearly
60 down my street
guitar solo
Thank you.
that on VHS somewhere.
Supposedly part of that was filmed
in Glen Rose.
Well, there's an attempt to do some
creditable stop motion dinosaur
effects, but of course those things are hard to
do gracefully and symmetrically.
I've wondered
if maybe they used the Dinosaur
Valley State Park for
Dinosaur Valley Girls, if only for
the title sequence.
They've got a free sign there.
So-called
scream queen
starlets of the time
in Cave Girl
drag and then these
oafs with beards
grunting with clubs and so on.
All very stereotypically.
In sequences which
go on far too long.
But it's
an oddity. That's the sort
of thing we should be showing for
Oddball Movie Night
and so on.
The same things tend to be shown
over and over.
Is that a VHS copy or a DVD?
I believe it's a VHS copy
that the late Pedro recorded
for me.
Just for those in the know, Hal's
room is essential
visiting grounds if you're
a bit of a hoarder like myself. I made sure
that my wife had a chance to see it.
It's not hoarding, I just don't have enough room for the stuff.
Readjust what her definition of cluttered is.
Some sacrifices are worth
making.
And that's why
he also gets a little bit
exacerbated if you send him something he already
has. Because it's like
this is just what I need.
We'll continue this
nostalgic nerd out another
time. Thanks to Reverend Pease,
Papa Joe Mama, and Dr. Hal.
And thanks to Rubik's
Pube for all of the songs in this
show. And
thanks to Lemur for the titles
and PR news.
You can find everything
about everything at subgenius.com
including how to become
an actual minister
in the church of the subgenius.
To end the show,
let's go to another album by
Rubik's Pube, the album
Bob Comp 1,
also easily found on bandcamp.com
as are, for that
matter, a dozen subgenius
official music compilation
albums spanning decades.
But now, Rubik's
Pube.
Yuttyism in a young
female
Enlargement of the
feet and shoulders, and of course
the third nostril.
Spaghettification
and reversion.
Isolating yourself
from them.
Ba ba ba ba ba ba ba.
Ooh.
Shapeshifting,
pre-gifting,
bestiality,
insanity, defying gravity,
exposing yourself, unfortunately,
to the underlying primal hierarchy.
And not giving a Bob damn.
.
Oh God.
Oh my babies.
Oh if.
Okay for all your left.
Off the top of my bed.
Of course you throw.
channel addressizard19ices.com
Bye!