Hello, hello, my name is Bobby J. Dobbs, Jr., hello.
Hello.
Hey Bob, we're all going to the creek tonight, it's gonna be a gas, you're coming, right?
I can't, guys.
Have a
The Self Genius Hour of
Swag.
You're stupid.
S-T-U-P-I-D.
See you at the disco tonight.
It's nice to break your ankle.
You're stupid.
S-T-U-P-I-D.
Oh yeah.
I like around the glasses.
Make you look real cool.
Make you look real clever.
Yeah.
I like dungarees.
They're full to the brim.
But you're not very clever.
I bet you're a real interesting person.
I bet you like to read and talk a lot about politics.
Oh yeah.
But most of all,
you're like me with big bodies.
I make brick hot blood.
Six plus batter.
Extra stupid.
S-T-U-P-I-D.
Second lucky number two.
The same as your ID.
You're stupid.
S-T-U-P-I-D.
Kid.
You're stupid.
S-T-U-P-I-D.
Kid.
La la la.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, you're stupid, S-T-B-I-D, stupid, S-T-B-I-D, stupid, S-T-B-I-D.
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you're stupid, S-T-B-I-D, stupid, S-T-B-I-D, stupid, S-T-B-I-D.
See for yourself, a dog with two bodies and one head.
They're all on the inside right now.
A pig with hands and feet, just like a human, just like yours or mine.
A gruesome, ugly sight, but an educational one.
Come in now.
They're all on the inside right now.
The world's largest collection on tour.
And you're just in time.
Come in now.
Alive, alive, a cow with six legs.
Look, look at the doorway.
The six-legged cow is standing up in there right now.
You're going to see the zonkey, half zebra, half bulldog.
A midget horse standing, only 27 inches tall.
Look, look through the doorway.
They're in there right now.
Smell the aroma, and you know they're alive.
Alive, alive.
They're on the inside right now.
A raccoon with two heads.
A pig with two heads.
A rabbit with two heads.
They're on the inside right now.
Two complete heads on the same body, and they're on the inside right now.
Don't miss.
The amazing fish.
Is she girl?
Is she fish?
Or is she girl?
You judge for yourself.
And you're just in time.
Come in now.
The first thing that's going to happen is we're going to allow Andrew the Impaled to
finally finish his set with electricity.
So before he was only causing himself pain, and now he will cause us pain.
All right, this is going to be great.
You're not going to know what to think.
I hope you get to enjoy this very, very painful moment.
Where I do things to you with this machine and my mouth.
Yeah, it sounds hotter than it is.
The first song that I have for you is called I'm Free.
It's alternately titled this weekend as The Pink's Delusion.
The Pink's Delusion.
Get a job.
Go to church.
Find a mate.
Hope it works.
Say big.
Going fast.
By now, it won't last.
And who's the better dancer on that?
Who's the better dancer show?
And which team going to bring the trophy home?
You want to look at臣
But what would you do if the overcoat you were wearing dejОg fе CEOs maid me hanى?
He needs to go.
You Chàp.
I don't know if you've ever seen me?
free. I said repeat after me. I'm free, I'm free, I'm free, I'm free, I'm free, I'm free, I'm free.
Now we all know you need a home. So find a bank and get a loan. Pay it back threefold. And if you
don't, out in the cold. You always can refinance if there comes a rainy day. Unless of course the
value drops, then no way. I said repeat after me. I'm free, I'm free, I'm free, I said repeat after me.
I'm free, I'm free, I'm free, I'm free, I'm free, I'm free.
Now go to school for your degree. To get a job, that's what you need. When you're done, you'll be
prepared for what's available out there. And if nothing is available,
I'll tell you what you get.
Now go back in with mom and dad.
And let them struggle with your debt.
I said repeat after me. Спасибо.
I'm free, I'm free, I'm free, I'm free, I'm free, I'm free, I'm free, I'm free.
I said repeat after me.
I'm free, I'm free, I'm free, I'm free, I'm free, I'm free, I'm free, I'm free, I'm free, I'm free...
I'm free, I'm free...
free money
free
those are some
now none of you try this at home right now
okay
go to someone else's house and try it there
yeah
because you don't want to offend
anybody
in today's new
transparent world
yeah he's trying to get up
the show's on top of him
he can't get up
the show's on top of me
that's a funny thing
get off
get off of me
did you ever see Great Lakes, Illinois?
that's where I was stationed
get off of me Paul you're crushing the smokes
that's where boot camp is
my A school was across the street my friend
no in fact
I was 19
I stayed in the west and went out west
and came back west
it was cool because while we were going through boot camp
they would talk about the cannonballs that were off the shore there
from the war of 18
in fact John Shirley was
many years ago writing
something to do with
the ship at the bottom
of one of the Great Lakes and it's so cold
that the ship was in pretty good shape
preserved yeah that's true
it's so cold down there
I'm going to reinstall animode
it's true
I've seen it
well I watched a documentary about it
so it's true
so yeah any documentary makes it true
no I mean
I mean this one was legit
it had all the people that were involved in
and looking for it and everything else
and it was a video of it
it was very well preserved
earlier you stated that Dave and David are one person
uh oh
that's weird
that's just weird man
Philo are one and same person
oh really
who and Philo
Philo
ível
The
Actually
the
Majuran's
Ghost
Because they both go way back, you know, in the olden times in Texas, you see.
Yeah, it's not really like six people or even three people.
Oh, I've been misled, hopefully.
It's not six people or three people.
I have some ghost milk in my fridge now.
If there is normal ghost milk and fat-free ghost milk,
well, then in the creamier, fuller, tastier, thicker, fat-containing ghost milk,
look, it's the fat actually from a ghost.
So you've actually been milking these ghosts yourself,
or is this just the ghost milk you would buy in the stores?
It's a machine.
I have an automatic machine, a fully automatic machine.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
It does all the work, the dirty work, I like to call it, the ghost work.
You don't actually want to touch those ghost mammary areas or anything?
I want some.
The machine has a dial, you know, a knob.
I turn it to the right.
Is it really creamy?
Yeah.
Ghost style.
Is the ghost still creamy?
I've heard it's thin and insubstantial.
I'm turning on the pump now.
Just wait a minute.
Is it kind of...
Now, have you run into any trouble with the authorities coming down on you for ghost abuse?
He's got the machinery running, I think.
Yeah, I can hear the machinery.
The machinery is starting up.
Is it actually...
Actually, ghost fat.
Don't you put a little, like, some pads in there to keep the ghost comfortable?
Do you let the ghost imbibe in some type of intoxicant before you latch onto their breast area?
Is the ghost milk pasteurized?
I hope it is.
I hope we can get the pasteurized...
Although, I'd like to get some whole ghost milk if you have some of that.
Or some raw milk.
Raw ghost milk?
Raw ghost milk.
Yeah, raw ghost milk.
Raw ghost yogurt.
That's the best.
The only kind of milk I will drink from this moment is bastard milk.
Oh, yes.
Bastard milk?
You get bastard...
Bastard ghost milk.
...by Mr. John O'Connor.
Not related to the boy from Terminator.
Movie.
Yeah, not J.C.
You're right.
Mm-hmm.
Is that why Casper is fat now?
Because you've been feeding him ghost milk?
Have you been feeding a fat man lately?
Well, no.
Well, maybe he's got a ghost girlfriend.
Do you have chocolate ghost milk?
Well, I hate that.
Can I get some chocolate ghost cottage cheese?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, chocolate ghost cottage cheese.
That sounds like ghost cottage cheese, ghost ice cream.
I think we're going to bring down the wrath of the authorities with this ghost abuse that's going on here.
Unless we make sure that they're comfortable while we're depriving them of their fluids.
You know, some planets, those fluids are very, very expensive.
And we can make a lot of money.
We've got to give this some careful consideration.
I think we need a five-year business plan, net present value.
Extrapolate the cost reduction over the long term.
Add the scissors to the camper tools.
Have you ever had any breast milk cheese?
Can you imagine?
Cheese made from the old
If the light I was through, I wouldn't be alive.
When you told your best friend when the lean I was your only guy.
Your sophistication makes me feel so paranoid.
Kick me with your leather boots, the way that I enjoy.
Please, my dear, kick me with your leather boots.
I'm sincere, kick me with your leather boots.
I snarkatize and choke and hurrah really very nice.
換 되 рад, I'm delighted and you said it right twice.
Your stomach's closed and conscience has me running around the bend.
Kick me with your leather boots, kick me hard again.
Please, my dear, kick me with your leather boots.
I'm sincere.
Kick me with your leather boots, please my dear
Kick me with your leather boots, I'm so chill
Kick me with your leather boots
You took me to your bedroom and I got such a thrill
It was like a sequel to The Boys from Brazil
When we wear our leather boots, it's so much fun
You're smashing like a volley, send the flash of my brain
You say, yes, he was the greatest of them all
In mapping and putting up a bit of old control
Your stunning social conscience had me banging on the wall
Kick me with your leather boots, kick me to high four
Please my dear, kick me with your leather boots
I'm so chill, kick me with your leather boots
Yes!
Listing is a function of the mind
Foggy Fedex Mendel said it's well before my time
Your sonic social content has made me inside
Kick me with your leather boots
Kick me in the brain
Please my dear
Kick me with your leather boots
I'm sincere
Please my dear
Kick me with your leather boots
I'm sincere
You took me to your bedroom and I got such a thrill
It was like a sequel to The Push from Brazil
Where we were all like the bricks they sell on the sign
It's passing by football, except the black tonight, right?
Oh, I gotta do this one quick.
That song and Stupid Kid were by the Sultans of Bling by way of The Large,
who also brought about half of this show, including the Puzzling Evidence show clips,
with Doug Filo, Phineas Narco, and Callers.
The other half, such as Andrew,
The Impaled, is from X Day Drill of Aught 16.
The music in the background right now is my air conditioner.
And now this.
From PR News in Washington, I'm still being investigated.
The victims were not immediately identified.
PR News trying to escape Southern police.
President Obama has PR News.
That has not helped to create new jobs.
Economist Hugh Johnson says it was two-tenths of a percent.
It's still a pretty number.
For Wall Street, 64887.
307.
11.
Officials are now confirming the five-foot sections say they are not listening to PR.
Film and photography company Kodak is confirming it'll sell its human remains for $650 million billion.
President Obama has chosen PR News in Washington.
One starred night, Prince Lucifer arose.
Tired of his dark dominions.
Swung the fiend above the rolling ball in cloud parts screened.
Where sinners hugged their specter of repose.
Now upon his western wing he leans.
Now his great bulk o'er Africa's sands careens.
Now the black planet shadowed.
Arctic snows.
Soaring through wider zones that prick his scars.
With memory of the old revolt from awe.
He reached a middle height.
And at the stars which are the brain of heaven.
He paused and sang.
Around the ancient track stood rank on rank.
The army of unalterable law.
Thezem the
sh 그래p warsemula qu
s classroom.
Factory womans awoke in long platforms from a doormat.
Thank you.
That's why we don't play surf rock.
Well, no, actually it is.
Thank you.
We're going to do one song and then we're going to bring up a couple of special guests.
This one is originally entitled, Gandhi Lives.
But I don't worship Gandhi.
And I don't really worship Bob either, but I do appreciate everything he's done for me.
So if you know this song, please sing along.
And everywhere you heard the word Gandhi before, just change it for the next song.
And I'm going to sing the word Bob.
If you don't know the song, you know I've got CDs for sale.
They're only $10.
And I promise you I will only spend the money on wine, women, and froth.
Are you ready?
Oh my God, aren't they adorable?
Oh my God, they're very single too.
Bob Dob lives.
And Bob Dob lives.
And Bob Dob breathes.
But only if you so believe.
You act as if you were a saint.
Well, tent is and you just ain't.
Bob Dob lives all night and well.
He's living in a big hotel.
Don't tell us so.
Alive or dead.
It might not matter as Mr. Dead.
Shake a bob, shake a shake.
Shake, shake, shake, shake.
Bob Dob Shake, shake, shake.
Bob Dob Shake.
You do the shake, shake, shake.
Shake, shake, Bob Dob Shake.
Bob Dob Shake.
Shake, shake, Shake.
You do the Bomb Dance, you do the Bomb Dance.
You do the Bomb Dance.
You Do the hundreds of factors.
Turbo rises uncomfortable situations, passengers cross roads deixa.
911 takes us.
Sendestruct dolls, change your Paris時間.
Assisteed неёук צ.
Give a ba-bop-dop, give a ba-bop-dop, give a ba-bop-dop, shoo-shoo.
Give a ba-bop-dop, give a ba-bop-dop, ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-ba-bop.
Let's freeze Bob!
Now here's Ernie Ford and the whole Hee-Haw gang singing the great old gospel song,
Jesus, hold my hand.
Some of you might be thinking,
Sing it if you know it.
It's been played a few times.
It is.
From the piglets to the billowing pack
On your life, a warping dark
Walk away
There's a hole in your soul
That's burning you alive
Where's life?
You'll never be paid
Walk away
From the piglets to the billowing pack
guitar solo
Every spot is a village
It's heaven's heaven
And your life, your life's all here
There's a hymn-telling man
Who is beckoning
With his day
Somebody that always there
Walk away
From the piglets to the billowing pack
On your life, a warping dark
There's a hole in your soul
You'll never be paid
That's burning you alive
There's a hymn-telling man
Who is beckoning with his day
Walk away
There's a hole in your soul
That's burning you alive
There's a hymn-telling man
Who lives by your side
And up in heaven
There's a hymn-telling man
Who is beckoning with his day
Who lives by your side
He's who's on the way
And the09
I'm on your side
No one will look
You want to play
Because that's how I ride
When the dreamed
Go in time
I'll shape projects
your tax, coffee, turtle, snack, from the pinch to the billowing pipe.
Triple bob for your money back, from the pinch to the billowing pipe.
We're going to ascend to our native stars, a brighter and better world than this one.
Gleaming in glory.
After a night of dubstep and partying.
After a night of filth and imbecility.
Actually, the dubstep is tomorrow night, which can go on forever.
I thought it was tonight.
No, not tonight.
It was going to be tonight, but I said, it was me that said, I need to sleep before 7 a.m.
You changed the schedule then?
Huh?
You changed the schedule?
Yeah.
Well, no, it's in the schedule.
It's written in there.
The all-night long dubstep, which, by the way, you'll be interested to know,
the Starwood, the early Starwood people complained bitterly about that last year.
I mean, real bitterly.
So they couldn't take it, huh?
Oh, they come in early on Saturday.
Panty waste.
To get, you know, set up their witchcraft stills.
Wimpcraft.
Yeah.
Would they prefer, like, an all-night acoustic yodeling?
They drum all night long.
Oh, the drums.
They drum all damn night long.
The hideous drums.
What's the difference?
The beating of those hideous drums.
The drums.
The natives are restless tonight.
But apparently the dubstep was too loud and went on.
Oh, that is sad.
So the pagans weren't able to rest in bowers of this.
They don't appreciate bass drops.
Yeah, really.
You know, if you can't suffer a little bit of discomfort for your so-called faith,
then what good are you?
It only works when the sun shines.
And why would you can't hear the stage at a place where they've advertised
they're going to be making noise all night?
What kind of a fair-weather sailor are you, anyway?
Oh, the kind that wants to get a...
Just a minute of sleep, please.
No.
Try going to Burning Man.
Can you just shut up for a minute?
Try going to Burning Man, where they set enormous speakers pointed right at you from across the street.
And yet they don't complain about the giant dick-eating spiders.
That's because nobody out here really has that giant of a dick.
They're silenced by the horror of it all.
From PR News.
In Washington, I'm to become the 18th Afghan civilian arrested in connection with Vietnam.
President Obama today announced he'll be stepping down July the 1st.
President made the announcement today in the White House Rose Garden.
I am conducted to a special release.
I don't shit.
Not clear with or without the possibility of parole.
The Commerce Department says factories that sold banned performance-enhancing drugs
rose 1%, a 1.2% increase.
The Dow Jones 2649643.
Investigators say it could take several months to determine what caused PR News in Houston.
Law enforcement officials in the U.S. and the U.K. say you're listening to what they say was a $200 million PR News in Washington.
Okay, friends, I think it's time to end the hour of slack.
It's now become completely slackless, unless you guys want to keep going.
Wait, I did have one more thing that I wanted to ask you guys.
I didn't know if you guys had talked about this yet.
Have you guys heard about on Facebook how they succumbed to the pressure and now you can get banned and have things?
It's completely ruined if you make any rape jokes at all.
I'm a little worried about the state of the slack hole.
We've got three Facebook pages that are nothing but.
And it's filled with the pink and the unsaved and the unwashed and unclean.
And I think it's probably only a matter of time before it gets reported again.
And I worry about it.
God forbid that there should be pornography on the Internet.
Well, but now if we even make jokes about rape bears,
which are awful,
they're obviously a favorite on the slack hole.
It's the most insidious form of censorship is when the government can do nothing,
but they can't stop people from censoring you who aren't with the government.
So they come up with a way that you can all communicate together
and then let somebody else make the rules.
And they'll decide what you can say and can't say.
And usually it'll be the government agreeing.
Well, you can or can't say.
Yeah, you can read my note there.
That's my rant note.
A serendipitous quote at the end of these rant notes is,
rape isn't funny.
It is the way we do it.
That's what's funny, the way we do it.
Yes.
But you'll have to be careful.
Don't be surprised if the whole Facebook comes crumbling down on our ears.
We're here overnight off face crack.
Oh, well.
We'll just have to go to Scrub.
Yes.
Well, there you go.
The nice thing about it, you can't get into Scrub unless you get past old gatekeeper Stang.
You have to answer the riddle about when and exactly how you paid your 35 bucks.
We should just make the front butt book.
There you go.
Isn't that a common thing?
People say, well, no, I don't have any.
No, certainly not.
Are you sure?
Sure.
And because they don't recognize what's actually happening.
We should end it now.
We've upset you.
I'm sorry.
Oh, she gets upset.
She's so sensitive and sweet.
I'm so mean.
Well, at least she's sensitive.
Most people around here are about as sensitive as a power shovel.
That's me.
I've been working on that for years, building up a good shell.
Right.
Many, many butt cheeks.
I've got your sensitivity.
Right here.
I think I'll be hearing that a lot later tonight.
Okay, well, I'm going to fade this out.
Well, Ivan Stang, what is the theme of tomorrow's ball?
How about that?
You want to put that in the list?
Simple.
What was it again?
Day of the Dead.
The Day of the Dead.
I actually have a sack of skull masks of different kinds in my car.
Oh.
A whole sack of skull masks.
Dear Day of the Dead.
Attention, subgeniuses.
There will be a human fight and accu-beating clinic at the top of the hill at Camp Hypercube before the pig roast.
So get your third nostrils unclogged and meet us at the top of the hill for...
Possibly the bloodiest of the blood orgies to about to begin.
There will be nothing but tits.
At what time?
We shall begin in a few moments.
We were going to start a little later.
But if we can get a few subgenius volunteers to tie up some other subgenius volunteers and drag them kicking and screaming to Camp Hypercube,
we will flay and disperse.
We will dismember accordingly.
And we will be supervising and documenting quite heavily.
So, praise Bob.
Indeed.
I thought we were going to start all the flaying and torturing tomorrow, but that's okay.
Practice makes perfect.
My testicles are actually connected to my body most of the time.
But which body are you talking about?
The undescended testicle of Jesus Christ.
No, no.
If anybody sees a spare unclogged...
Unconnected testicle...
Please send them on home.
Drop us a line.
Okay.
Send them on home now, y'all.
That's a remote orbiting ball.
Send it home.
Send it, the homeless testicle tossed to me.
I lift my lump before the golden door.
You know, childhood innocence is now gone,
and we are left as cynical adults to weather the...
bitter winds that are blowing our way from X-Day,
from the launching platform area where the great saucer ship will descend.
Now, that was a large spaceship in eight and a half, too, wasn't there,
that never got off the ground?
Well, you didn't see it.
It wasn't on camera.
It took off after the movie was over.
I thought there were actually scenes where they were trying to construct that,
and they...
Oh, yeah.
They built a huge spaceship set under construction.
That was the set, an under-construction set of a set under construction.
And when the movie was finished, they could complete it and take off.
But it was important that it not fly during the movie.
Actually, I understand that that whole spaceship set ending was kind of an afterthought.
The movie was going to end a completely different way.
And just as the subject matter of the movie would indicate,
everything's fake and unpredictable and unplanned,
and you can't fit it all into a formula.
There's nobody at the controls.
And that's...
We like it that way.
It's fun.
It's organic.
It evolves on its own.
And slack comes dripping down from the heavens.
You'll get the best slack that way.
It's revolutionary.
There's no status.
There's constant movement.
Movement.
But aren't we closing in on the magic?
It's getting near the hour when we get to go home.
It's getting near the hour.
When the church lights yawn.
As El Duce would say,
it's near the hour.
Yes, it's time.
It's the time, girls.
Make the trains run on time.
And organize...
Oh, not El Duce.
I'm talking about El Duce.
Bob never made the trains.
I think that's one of the greatest things that you could say about Bob,
was the trains never ran on time when he was in charge.
I don't remember.
Oh, no, it was more than that.
When Bob was in charge,
it's not that the trains ran on time or didn't run on time.
It's that time ceased to have any meaning on the trains.
When railroads reorganized time,
our system of time was created by the American Railroad.
The trains ran on time.
Literally.
Instead of stopping at fueling stations with big bins of coal or diesel fuel,
there would be big bins of time that they would put into the fuel tanks of the trains.
The trains literally ran on time.
They would pour in from the hopper by the side of the tracks,
all those seconds, minutes, and pulped hours that had been crammed in by the service railroads.
In the summer, they would switch to daylight savings time,
which has a much lower octane.
Daylight savings time.
Nobody could ever really understand why they did that seasonal switch.
I think it had something to do with California regulations.
I don't know.
And in the winter, it was back to the fungus and the berries that their grandmothers had given them.
They looked out the window and knew that the time was nigh.
Praise Bob!
And praise Tommy Amoeba, the next entertainer on this Pittsburgh cabal.
They're our subgenius in Pittsburgh, and sadly, this is what we look like.
That made me salute my pants.
Woo!
mean
yeah
you
Yeah, Lord
I'm a hero
Like Captain Kirk in Star Trek
Aboard the Enterprise
Surrounded by your high tech fantasy
You went out surprised
While jacking your tic-tac
You listened to these lies
And fizzled like fuck
Oh, take a look at this
What is this?
This is my
Lord, make way
I am here to pay
All the money
To me
You want me
Hey
I will stop the rain
You will stop the rain
Tell me what we did
Are you
You know the pain
It's not supposed to be
Rain
Love
Don't you know
That we stonk
gig
Down our
He adds
New
Here's a woman
Come back
Say
I am
Angel
unplugged. In fact, everything was unplugged that night at X-Day.
Lee Murr did PR News and
Jesus, and thanks to Dr. Sinister for
letting us on his show at WCSB Cleveland.
We'll hear a little more from that, but otherwise
all the rest is by and large by The Large.
Thank ya.
Yes! You know the...
And I think
it's hilarious when he yells out,
BOMBS!
And it took a while, like
months afterwards, and then I
watched the video again, and I was like,
nothing happened, and I was just very
interested in the video.
And that was it.
Actually, maybe a year later,
I started saying, BOMBS!
And then
everyone burst out laughing.
Everyone was like, BOMBS!
It's very funny.
To say BOMBS,
I thought in the video that it was hilarious
because it's not actually a swear word,
it's just his name.
I like BOMBS.
So that was funny.
And then, you know,
it evolved.
What did I get from other people?
Well, when I watched videos
that I'm a thon,
I'm a thon,
for example,
I'd start doing what they're doing,
or, you know, just do what I usually do.
So, yeah, it definitely
does get picked up.
I'm gonna see if I missed any questions here.
Pick up new ones and old ones go away,
or do old ones never go away?
Some old ones never go away.
They can be kind of...
kind of classics.
BOMBS!
We're going to take one last call.
I can't wait to hear what this is.
I want to hear about the RNA trials.
I want to eat this.
I want to hear about the RNA drops.
Hello, you're on the air.
And join me.
Hello.
Hi, guys.
Are you on the air?
I want to know about the LSD drops.
MST drops.
Man, we're doing it, and we're just about out of time.
Yes, we are.
We could have done something here.
I just figured I'd try one last time before you all went home.
Well, thank you so much.
It's glad to hear from you.
I'm glad to hear from you.
It's good to hear from you.
It is good time.
It is good to hear.
I wanted to say I'm going to miss you guys because I wasn't going to be there for X days this year.
You know what?
No, I won't be there either, Janice.
That makes two of us.
The saucers will find you where you are.
What the hell are you doing?
Man, what the hell have I been doing for the last year?
I don't know.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
I suddenly find myself without the means.
Dragging your butt through the day.
Selling body and soul to a bunch of bad normals?
My daughter was tired of getting...
No, seriously, the conspiracy.
Oh, man.
You know what's really messed up?
There's a guy in a supervisory position who works on the same floor in my building.
His name is Bob.
And there's a Dobbshead sticker on his wall.
Dope.
And I'm afraid to bring it up.
I would be.
Yep.
Old Bob Cyclops.
Old Bob might take offense at...
Do they know?
Or did they just find a t-shirt in a thrift store somewhere?
Yeah, you never know where that came from.
As long as it doesn't actually say Bob, you have to suspect the worst.
That full knowledge is there.
And the...
What a day of reckoning.
Oh, here's what you can do, Dr. Sinister,
to determine if the guy is a for real subgenius.
See how he spells Bob.
That's it.
Yes.
I know for a fact that in correspondence that has been addressed to him and from him,
there are no quotation marks in his name.
Well, I don't mean his name.
I mean J.R. Bob Dobbs.
The actual Bob.
Yeah.
That is important.
This is important as drawing the pentagram right
when you're performing a magical operation.
What?
You just have to...
You have to draw...
Oh, no.
I got to go home immediately.
You have to put those quotes there.
You better get down that basement pretty quick, buddy,
or the whole house is going to start exploding.
Those amusing chalk drawings.
So, now we come to an end of another session.
If you think Bob's trains ran late,
wait till you see his saucers.
I mean, wait.
He has saucers as big as eyes.
No, the sky will be full of...
Full of ships.
And flame will illuminate the night
as the giant saucers the size of entire U.S. states
make a landing.
So, until next time, folks,
this is the last time we'll speak to each other on planet Earth.
It's been good knowing you.
Thanks for all the fish.
Thanks for all the $35 checks, everybody.
See you in the next world.
See you later, suckers!
It's the last time we will speak to each other on planet Earth.
Staying off again.
Listen to them yowling and howling
in the agony of their own creation.
Well, we tried to warn them.
Anyway, it's been good to be on your show.
Yes, now they are...
And now they are doomed.
They didn't...
We will watch them burn.
...get with the program.
We tried and tried, you know.
I don't know if a professional propaganda ministry
could have really solved the problem.
You can lead a horse...
...to water, but you can't make him drink.
But you can waterboard it.
Well, you can lead a pink to the truth,
but you can't make him think.
And so, now they have to take it.
They have to roll over and take it.
Take their medicine.
And we, the subgeniuses, will snicker and laugh from afar,
sipping effete cocktails from the observation platforms
of the giant globe-spanning saucer ships.
We'll look down on the tossers from our seats
and the saucers.
Well, folks, I think this is as good a time as any
to end the program.
Ope.
This has been a special edition of Synesthesia.
If I manage to get the transmitter onto the saucers in time,
then I'll be broadcasting this time next week from Planet X.
If not, then Bob help us all.
X the Unknown.
Until whenever that next time is, whatever planet that's on.
Thank you, Dr. Hal.
Most welcome.
Thank you, Reverend Stang.
Aye, aye, sir.
Thank you, Princess Wee, even though you're in the other room right now and can't hear me.
Thank you, anyway.
And thank you to the callers who put up with all this.
Until next time, keep it surreal.
Thank you.
In matters of money, it's never wrong.
But in this case, it's complete.
And he's never wrong.
Completely wrong.
And we were moving furniture around.
And somebody said, a woman said, and I wasn't even looking in that direction,
but popped into my head.
And he said, why, I happened to, yes, it happened to be.
And I said, Bob.
And he said, fantastic.
And so I had, and just be looking right at the camera.
No idea at all.
Stop.
You're not a dirty old slob
When you are praising the boss
You're not acting up like a snob
You're not a dirty old slob
When you are praising the boss
You're not acting up like a snob
You're not a dirty old slob
When you are praising the boss
You're not acting up like a snob
You're not a dirty old slob
When you are praising the boss
You're not acting up like a snob
You're not a dirty old slob
When you are praising the boss
You're not acting up like a snob
When you are pricing by, you're not a dirty old slob
A dirty old slob
When you're pricing by, when you're pricing by
Brothers keep on pricing by
You're not acting like a slob
Don't listen but the time you're down
You know what you're doing with your life
Do what you want to do with it
Do with it
You're not acting like a slob
Acting like a acting like a slob
Never acting like a slob
You can't even act like a slob
You're so stupid you can't even act like a slob
Robot, pro crime freak, broken back, older fool
They're doing what they wanna do
They don't go to school
But you and Bob Bree you're a sucka
You're not a slacker, sly sucker
But you're a sly, yeah, wild, wild, yeah, yeah, yeah
Wow, wow, wow, wow
This is all about Bob
Wow
We like to praise people. This is like a godlike thing.
You read to us all the consistence and dots.
It doesn't matter.
Maybe even Bob doesn't give those things to you that you want to have.
But maybe Bob cracks open like Faberge's egg and something comes out from there.
Something that really reflects the innermost truth behind the man-made words.
You know what I'm saying. The man-made words.
We're just making things worse with our codes and premeditated stuff.
And our norms and... you know...
Everything is so normal. Pink.
Reditude.
Unoriginal.
Uninspiring.
Unintelligent.
Not even as sexy as it used to be.
But let's still praise Bob for a while.
We're the funny weirdos making fun of the bad weirdos.
Thank you, The Large.
You've been listening to the subgenius radio ministry Hour of Slack.
For free information, write to P.O. Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Or see...
www.subgenius.com
Praise Bob!
Believe me, your unpaid job doing data entry for Facebook will still be there when you get back.
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show.
And we're even more glad that some listeners have donated enough to help us keep on going for another couple of months.
Not just this show, but subgenius.com and all the other radio stations.
And if you truly love Bob and want some of that slack back to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com front page or especially the radio page or the catalog store pages
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty and we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference, even if it's only once a month from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that blow jobs could go the way of Steve jobs if you don't pay dogs.
We also take checks and money orders to Subgenius Foundation.
P.O. Box 181-417.
Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Thanks for anything you can do to help let there be slack.