No wonder millions and millions of ladies say, I love body temperature.
Morning, ladies.
Good morning. Who are you?
I'm usually called Old Tyler.
That's my husband's name.
I'm sorry, but illegal possession of uranium is the one charge we can't hang on you.
I suppose you haven't seen Son of Kong lately, the touching monkey band scene.
A new Son of Kong?
No, the old movie.
The one where Carl Denham goes back to Skull Island.
I saw that probably the week it came out, I remember.
In 1933?
Oh my God, no.
Come on, Mr. Michael Pepe.
That's a little bit much even for me to believe in.
What was the one in the 50s, the Son of Kong?
There was no Son of Kong in the 50s.
Well, they showed it in 1960.
Okay, now there was the De Laurentiis King Kong had a sequel that had a wife of Kong.
That's right, they brought in Mrs. Kong.
Yeah, Mrs. What was the name of that?
Boy, did they degrade the whole brand with that.
That is called King Kong Escapes.
But I'm talking about when Carl Denham was bankrupted because of...
Blue Jeans.
...of bringing King Kong to America, he had to escape hidden with his head under a blanket in a junk truck.
But Captain Englehorn took him on board and they cruised the South Seas.
Yes.
And one night on a South Sea island of some kind.
Well, let me set the setting for you.
The palm trees were swaying.
You know that's the wrong music, right?
Okay, just checking.
Actually, it was in some place like Sang Karang or...
Oh, yeah.
Or Rack-A-Jack or something like that.
Indonesian.
Yes, it was in Indonesian.
Let's get some peanut.
Some peanut.
Well, they come to this...
Well, no, let's go back.
I mean, what happens in the movie?
What happens is there's nothing to do in this tiny town.
And so Englehorn and Denham stroll into this ridiculously small circus where trained monkeys are trying to play these instruments.
And, you know, these stolid, betel nut-chewing islanders are watching it with no flicker of emotion.
And they're like, oh, my God.
And the scene goes on and on.
It's amazing.
You see all the monkeys playing their various instruments.
Wow, I would love to see.
I have to look at that.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm just glad K-Rob never didn't hear you say that.
And then a horrible fire destroys the entire establishment.
So, you know, that...
An exciting, fast-moving tracking shot.
Well, how did they end up on Skull Island after that boring beginning?
How did they get the fuck Skull Island?
They have met the guy who gave them the map in the first place.
Oh.
And they throw the capitalist bosses, that is to say, Englehorn and Denham, overboard
at Skull Island.
And they run into giant mammals there, don't they?
It's not just dinosaurs.
A giant cave bear.
Yes.
Mammoths?
Perhaps?
Sabertooth?
No, they run into a cave bear and a nothosaurus and a styracosaurus.
And they're saved by the baby Kong, who's kind of an albino, pig-legged Kong.
Yes, he makes all sorts of terrible gestures which ruin the entire movie.
He spoils the film with his goofy gestures, which they insisted on putting in to make him lovable.
Shrugging and mugging and winking and so on.
It's funny how you can kill a whole zoner in one.
Poor old Kong.
Not a patch on his old man.
And the people are tiny up in the top.
They discover that there is a treasure on the island after all, which is something that Nils Helmström just made up.
And they get it.
And they get it by lifting it off the penis and testicles of an enormous statue, which they discover in a cave.
Of Bob?
It's not of Bob, but it's of a strange, evil-looking idol.
No, no, of Bob.
But as soon as they pull this off what has to be...
I mean, look at it.
Oh, oh, no.
Oh, my God, look at it.
Good heavens.
I can't believe you're showing it right here to our audience.
I can't believe it either because I've been silenced by a technical...
It's a penis attached to a...
Problem.
A glob of pulsating...
Are we going out?
Yes.
Yeah, Hal, everything is going fine.
Mass fat cells...
Not for me.
Just your headphones are here on the problem.
My headphones?
There we go.
Work on that headphone.
Hey, zip up your pants.
Hey, what are you doing?
Oh, my God, that's not your headphone.
Press those pants.
Give me 20.
Yes, and at the end...
I can't hear you.
Just in the last 80 minutes or 60 minutes of the movie, Skull Island finally has its convulsive earthquake
that causes it to sink beneath the waves forever with Baby Kong standing at the very tip top of the island...
To rescue Denim.
...holding Denim.
Definitely.
It's exploited.
Denim?
Well, then what happens to Baby Kong?
Yes, that was...
It's all product...
Wait, he's wearing Levi's?
What happens to Baby Kong at the end?
He drowns and dies.
He really?
And he doesn't float.
Wow.
He drowns and dies and he doesn't float.
He's holding up Carl Denim, but the island...
I never saw that.
...the ocean closes over his head.
He's a Jesus Kong.
Yeah.
He dies for the exploitative capitalist Carl Denim.
Wow.
And there's no more Kongs.
No more...
Or Megaphymatus Kong.
They did save the treasure that took off the island.
Species name.
But the moment they took it off, the entire island sunk beneath the ocean.
But they recovered with Mighty Joe Young, right?
I mean...
Mighty Joe Young was only...
That's a different creature entire.
That's just a big gorilla.
A really big gorilla.
That's how back when you were growing up...
But the way it was presented to me in the 60s, there were three movies.
On late night television.
King Kong.
No, on the matinee in the theater.
King Kong, Son of Kong, Mighty Joe Young.
The three main stop motion tapes.
And they had gone...
With Jiggly...
Godzilla.
And they all were presented as if...
Jiggly hair movies.
They just came out.
As if they were new movies that had just come out.
They are eternally new movies.
The Darth Vader theme, so you can get a beer.
Right?
Well, they...
They're...
Like Mighty Joe Young, you're saying it's from the 30s.
It is not.
Mighty Joe Young comes from the 40s, from 1946.
40s, okay then.
Well...
That was Ray Harryhausen's first professional monster movie job.
So they made money from him.
He's showing that movie for 40 years.
40 years.
Mighty Joe Young has some astounding stop motion.
And kids never ever stop.
Especially the version I have.
It's really, really amazing.
Yeah.
It's...
It's never been equal.
Like Frankenstein or what I am.
I saw...
I happened to see the remake of Mighty Joe Young recently with...
What's his name?
That Texas boy.
Oh.
Bill...
George Bush.
With the three names.
Yeah.
I saw him.
And...
No, Tommy Lee.
Monster with the girl.
What year is that?
You don't have the...
No...
I don't think I even heard of it.
Tommy Lee's so much better.
Late 90s, I think.
It's a guy in a suit, but it's the best guy in a suit.
Wait a minute.
It's Rick Baker and his absolute best.
It's a CG gorilla all the way.
No, in Mighty Joe Young?
In the one that they recently made?
It's computer generated.
No.
Really?
It's the best guy in a suit.
You're sure Rick said...
Well, no.
Rick Baker did the design and someone else was wearing the suit.
They probably...
It's a computer generator.
I think he had a suit for some shots, I guess, but for the most part...
Mr. CG, I wasn't that far along then.
They didn't do hair like that.
They were beating the drum about it and tooting their horn about how this movie represented
a giant advance.
It may have been a giant advance in compositing.
What is that?
Which is half the short...
The man who designed Yoda just died recently and he got the job because of the hair on
the monkeys in 2001.
Oh.
That was apparently a...
Those aren't monkeys.
Nice.
They're apes.
Oh, you mean...
And then Lucas said that he thought he didn't get the special effects Oscar for it because
he thought they were so dumb that the people who judge were so dumb that they thought they
were probably real monkeys because they look so good.
I didn't think they looked like real monkeys, but the hair was amazing.
It was some combination of human hair and horse hair and some other kind of hair.
I thought they looked humanoid.
They were fine.
They were rather humanoid.
Pithecanthropoe.
They were great.
That whole thing was mesmerizing.
Pithecanthropoe.
Pithecanthropoe?
Or...
They later evolved into both homo sapiens, homo subgenius, homo excelsior...
I see.
...and the Kongs, which is mega primatus kongs.
What about gigantopithecus?
Of course.
Gigantopithecus.
And what...
I try to not to draw attention to those because...
What is it?
...I don't want people to catch him and hunt him and...
Primal anthropithecus?
Bigfoot should always remain right on the edge of fish.
That's why whenever you listen to subgenius, you'll always hear something about the
radio, they always talk about how
go to New York to find that creature.
Or the center of town.
I don't know if there's an urban yeti.
Hiding in plain sight, you mean.
Yeah, kind of.
That one Kardashian sister.
It's misdirection.
There's no question.
I think the creatures across the street are punas.
There's no question Gigantopithecus
actually existed at one time.
The only reason to ask is
are they really extinct or are they
in fact the elusive yeti?
Smart enough to hide
and make it
a game that he always wins.
If I may point out,
what Reb Stang...
I guess that's the music.
That's as far as we paid for the music.
It's right to that part in the score.
What Reb Stang was saying earlier,
the condition you were describing
earlier I think is called
a stetopithecus.
Which condition?
The condition of the buttocks
becoming unusually
swelling and bloated
and becoming
unusually distended
like the hot and taut Venus.
Exactly.
It's called stetopithecus.
And the buttocks come out
often in a shelf like
more or less parallel
horizontal to the ground.
Well, it's for water storage
like the camel's hump.
Exactly.
And also the young can be
carried on the back
on the huge rack like
ass.
It sounds worse with every
moment as you describe it.
Yeah.
Go call, call.
This is the same strategy as
the giant brown-backed
spider.
It's the young riding on its back.
And if I were
over there, then Get Back
would suddenly come up by the London Symphony Orchestra.
It would come on backwards though.
And they face with the
open booty.
I like big butts and I cannot lie.
You other brothers can't deny.
When a girl walks in with a itty bitty waist
and a round thing in your face.
You get sprung, you wanna pull up tight.
You notice that butt was stuffed
deep in the jeans she's wearing.
I'm hooked and I can't stop staring.
Oobay.
I wanna get with ya.
Take your pretty picture.
My homeboys tried to warn me.
But that butt you got makes me so horny.
Oob, rumpled smooth skin.
You say you wanna get in my bands.
Well, use me, use me.
Cause you ain't that rich, coobee.
I've seen them dancing.
To hell with romancing.
Cause she's sweat, wet.
Gotta go like a turtle.
I'm tired of magazines.
Saying flat butts are the thing.
Take the average black man and ask him that.
She gotta pack much back.
So fellas, fellas.
Has your girlfriend got the butt?
Tell her to shake it, shake it.
Shake that healthy butt.
Baby got it.
Now baby, face with the open booty.
I like em round and big.
And when I'm throwing a gig.
I just can't help myself from acting like an animal.
Here's my scandal.
I'm just a child.
I want to get you home.
Whoa, double up.
Whoa, whoa.
I ain't talking about Playboy.
Silicone pots are made for toys.
I want them real thick and juicy.
So find that juicy double.
Johnny C's in trouble.
Begging for a piece of that bubble.
So I'm looking at bike videos.
Knock me bimbos walking like hoes.
You can have them bimbos.
I'll keep my limo like Flojo.
A word to the Pixel Sisters.
I won't get with ya.
I won't cuss or hit ya.
But I gotta be straight when I say I wanna
till the break of dawn.
Baby, I got it going on.
A lot of simps won't like this song.
Cause them punks like to hit it and quit.
And I'd rather stay and play.
Cause I'm long and I'm strong.
And I'm down to get the friction on.
So.
Ladies, ladies.
If you wanna roll in my Mercedes.
Then turn around and stick it out.
Even white boys got to shout.
Baby, got back.
Actually, when it comes to females,
Cosmo does not have very much to do at all with my selection.
I mean, 36, 24, 36.
Maybe if she's 5'3".
So your girlfriend rules a Honda.
Playing work out tapes by Fonda.
But Fonda ain't got a motor in the back of a Honda.
My anaconda don't want me.
Unless you have got a motor in the back of a Honda.
So let me model you this.
But I'm going for what the bordered Martin I can
Yeah.
I can make my own.
rough and smooth.
Yo流
yo yo yo yo yo yo yo yo ya yo ya ya ya ya ya ya You, you, you!
You ain't in this thing
Give me a sister
I can't resist her
Red beans and rice didn't miss her
Some knucklehead tried to diss
Cause his girls are on my list
He had a game but he chose to hit em
And I pull up quick to get with em
So ladies
If the buddies around
Then you wanna triple X roll down
You down one nine hundred
Johnny C and
Kick them nasty thoughts
Baby got back
Nemo
Play
I'll play it for you sometime.
Now we're having a McCartney-esque goodbye.
A course in a subgenius thing.
I'll convert from one format to another.
That's just the kind of thing I'm looking forward to.
Oh, man.
We're saying goodbye.
My manic-depressive is kicking in.
You're, like, freaking out, man?
Don't worry.
Everything's going to be fine.
And we have some giant pills the size of atomic submarines.
I went on tour with those giant pills in 77.
Yes, I've had those giant pills.
They were made by the man who would, years later, make the giant, wonderful bobhead.
On the giant?
Did you actually swallow one of those?
And he made giant pills and pillboxes.
Yeah.
And pillbox hats.
But you would choke to death.
No, atheists.
And the band was called The Tubes.
The Tubes.
The Tubes pills take you.
Hurley Gates was one of the girls.
That was the greatest song ever.
White punks on dope.
Yeah, it was.
It inspired a generation.
I didn't like their music all that much.
Jane, that one song, and also Doernacker, remember?
Jane Doernacker.
I spent that tour in the back of the bus with Jane Doernacker and Hurley Gates,
talking the whole time about her dream about dying in the river in a helicopter.
Right, exactly.
Wanting to do that.
No, she did say she thought she'd die in water coming in from the air, falling from the sky.
She dreamed about that.
And so it happened.
She had a couple of talents.
And Hurley Gates had a band with Pearl Harbor and the...
Yeah, remember?
Explosion.
Yes, thank you.
Yeah, during the punk era.
That was a great band, Pearl Harbor and the Explosion.
It was, and she was...
Pearl was beautiful.
She's still around.
She was.
She's friends with...
She is still around?
Yeah, she's friends with Barbara Lou, the girl that appeared on Mondo 2000.
And also Barbara Golden, who plays, you know, who comes before us once a month.
Yes.
I was just talking about Prairie Prince and somebody else from the Tubes.
Oh, yeah.
Being at some event soon.
Because they had an air...
I'm probably 80 years old.
I used to be in the Tubes.
Air spray art company.
And so in his bedroom, he had like an amazing view of the desert.
This wall, you know, long walls, just forever the desert.
What do you mean?
He spray painted the desert on his wall?
Yeah, that kind of airbrush.
Airbrush painting.
Yeah, it was a masterpiece.
Oh, like a...
Parches.
Right.
It takes a lot of paint.
Like a Geiger.
To view the whole desert.
It does, but then you run over in the morning and it's gone.
Well, what is it?
It's just two colors.
I saw the painted desert last year, but I saw it in the night.
Geiger actually worked.
He makes in oil.
I know.
See, that's the desert needs...
Yeah, that one needs to be seen.
All deserts really need to be seen.
Need to be seen.
Sunrise and sunset is the best.
I see.
They have different aspects during all the day.
All day, all night is wonderful.
But yeah, sunrise and sunset, the oblique lighting really punches in the brain.
It is nice to go where there's little animals running around, though, to provide more interest.
Yeah, everybody should go to the high desert and concentrate on little rears.
Once again, it depends on what little animals you mean.
Well, little jackrabbits or...
Oh, yeah, they're all right.
Little jackalots.
Jackrabbits, okay.
This music makes you want to order more beer.
I don't want to see a bear.
Deer.
There's beer in the icebox.
You know, Armadillo.
Okay, here's...
Mom's telling us what to do.
Go get a beer out of the icebox if you want it.
I think it's all gone.
What am I supposed to do?
I want an ice cream cone.
Well, you're supposed to.
Growing up is...
Get me a Pepsi.
I want an ice cream cone.
See, that's the nature of growing up.
I want an Easter egg.
Just get me a Pepsi and...
I want, I want...
Mike, you're on drugs.
I will kill on a rough beer.
Literally, Mike, you're on beer.
Mike, you're on drugs.
Mom, give me a Pepsi.
Okay, so this village, this entire village will die until I get beer.
This village is revolting.
Yes, I agree.
Remember the king of id?
He's the one that said that first.
Yeah, and in the last frame will be him jumping to a chopper saying...
Is it id?
You don't know what id is.
Id is...
Did he have any cores?
No, it couldn't have been id.
Now, what are you talking about?
The id monster in...
The cartoon.
The cartoon where the guy said...
The kingdom of id?
The guy said the peasants are revolting.
Yes, it was a comic strip.
Yeah.
From your Sunday...
The wizard of id.
Id?
Yes, a comic strip running in the newspaper now.
ID.
The wizard of id.
Wow.
Yes, it's on.
That puts a whole...
I hadn't thought about that.
He would go up against King Frank.
He's a Freudian.
A Ferdinandian.
Remember Little King Ferdinand?
Ferdinand, yes, I do.
The Little King.
The Little King, yeah.
Right.
Oh, was he small?
Drawn by Otto Sobel.
Great little...
Yeah.
Yeah, right.
He had a pyramidal shape.
Yes, yes.
An ermine coat.
He never said anything.
His name was id.
There were Little King cartoons, which were quite wonderful, too.
Animated Little King cartoons back in the day.
I know I saw them, but I don't know.
They must be...
Supposedly, K-Rob has all those, right?
Another byproduct of the Fleischer studio.
I don't know what K-Rob has.
His treasuries are mighty and wonderful, but I...
You never know.
A lot of stuff, surprisingly, is still available, because nobody really knows who owns it.
Certain early cartoons, nobody seems to want to lay claim to Porky the Giant Killer or
something like that.
What a fun cartoon it is.
There's many cartoons that should not be made into movies.
Porky forced to play a toy piano.
For better or for worse.
Forever and ever.
Lin Johnson.
Oh, my God.
Lyndon Baines Johnson.
Sorry.
You mean for better or for worse?
Yeah.
It's like a stupid...
I don't know.
It's kind of Ozzie and Harriet for the millennial generation, I guess.
Or for the 90s generation.
But we're not on the air, are we?
We are on the air.
It's just my headphones that can't hear it.
Your headphones?
Are they out?
No.
We're going to hear it in a moment.
I assure you, you're going out over the air to be heard by tens in this area.
I can't hear it.
If we put it out, will anybody hear it?
Why, we have nine authenticated viewers right now, and at the peak, 20 viewers.
My God.
Viewers of radio.
20 people.
So, 11 have heard.
My God's bigger than you.
All right, let's do it.
How many of those people...
I know, that's not good.
And the Lord said...
How many of those people have their clothes off?
Let there be great whales.
That's the quality...
Walking around with their clothes off.
That's...
He vexes me.
We know chicks love to listen to our masculine voices.
They do?
Oh, yes, of course.
Coming over here.
John Kennedy.
No pun intended.
That's why they all left the studio some time ago.
Apparently.
Well, it reminds me of an amusing anecdote.
What was that?
We're also sensitive guys.
It's hard to be a radio audience.
Oh, yeah, I'm a sensitive guy, too.
You're about as sensitive as a power shovel, but I'm really sensitive.
You're not a vaccine.
Just sniff this patchouli.
Just to stand around and watch other people doing it doesn't make any sense.
I love the forests and the fields and the walking on the beach and the birds.
Yes, the little birds of the sky.
Listen to the mockingbirds.
Are you getting a radiocarpal tunnel, Evan Stang?
I've been fighting all manner of joint-related problems.
It's all right.
I've had too many joints.
If you want another joint...
No, no, no.
I would like some, and I'm...
I don't want any more.
I want to...
Here it comes.
I just want...
Well, I do, because my joints are aching, too.
Now your joints are aching for jellied slouts and bacon.
Where's my glucosamine?
For pork smith, Smith, you're super tricky, folks.
Shots.
Reb Stang, I'll tell you.
And there's my vitamin G.
The way you were shaking that hand, you've been holding too many little mice.
You've been holding on to mice.
He's been living in the other world.
I'm not.
Don't say what I was...
Identity as Stangor.
Something.
You've been...
You've been using your wrist a lot, Reb Stang.
That Stang's really something.
His wrist is the most...
Yeah, that's one way to put it.
Or we can call it scratching the squirrel.
It's really the most supple wrist I've ever seen.
A couple of supple.
I think it kind of jumped out of its socket or something.
Ew.
I hate that.
It kind of just...
Oh, there it goes.
I do get...
Sock it to me.
I hate to admit, I get mouse and remote control.
It's a little carpool.
Tunnel.
Yeah, I'm going that way.
Go, Stang, go.
Wait, he's taking his clothes off.
You, look at...
Come on.
Just look at...
Put me in so uptight, you guys.
Be free.
Hey.
We're with you, Stang.
We're following along.
We're with you.
What's the matter, you afraid?
No, we're coming.
Hold on.
Wait up.
Give a guy a break.
Don't you want to be cool?
Nobody's doing it.
I'm coming.
Hold on.
Yeah.
You beat me out there.
Oh, my God.
The horror.
The vertiginous horror.
Wait, is this...
Madness.
That's why we're nude, because then the monster attacks us.
And we are defenseless.
I got my man thing out.
Well, throw a towel over there.
Man by day.
And, you know, I'm just loving it, baby, because it's San Francisco.
All right, all right.
Yes, the magic of radio.
We call it...
Stem load.
Stem load?
From stem to stern.
It's called stem to stern.
It's called wasting your stem cells, as Onan did when he spilt his seeds.
Dr. DeBruyck's friend was complaining last night about menopause, because apparently...
Really?
Yeah, he's having the change.
It's very real.
He's going through the change.
Oh, my God.
But on him, you wouldn't notice, though.
That sounds so sad.
But everybody else had better watch out.
What happens to you?
Certain physical signs appear.
Oh, you wear mommy jeans.
I don't wear mommy jeans.
Do you wear mommy jeans?
I don't even know what mommy jeans are.
I don't believe I can...
I take your meaning.
I know about moon pants.
I'm speaking the bottoms.
So do you do...
Are you in menopause?
Like, what do you do now?
No, no, no.
I'm not sure.
Well, I forget things, but I think that's due to...
What foof are all in Terradiddle?
Balderdash.
Pure balderdash.
I forget things even when I was young, when I was smoking froth.
Well, that may have had something to do with it.
I would do that now, but...
Actually, I can tell you...
I got news for you.
...a memory booster or enhancer.
Even people who don't smoke froth have terrible memories.
That's right.
Even folks who don't smoke froth forget everything in their life.
Why is that?
Because they say everything you've experienced is stored.
Here's my memory right here.
I store it on a folded-up sheet of paper.
On an extrasomatic system.
That's old school.
I use a pen.
Recently...
You use an artifact.
...on the Scrub Genius Forum, somebody posed the question,
when was the last time you used a pencil?
And about half of the people could think of one time in the last year
that they had used a pencil, but then the old fogies like Reverend Susie the Floozy
and G. Gordon Gordon and myself were all...
And me.
Well, an hour ago.
Yeah, exactly.
Five minutes ago.
Why didn't you see me pencil sharpener?
Wow, yeah.
Yeah, I constantly use a pencil.
I like pencil.
Number two.
Yeah, I use them all the time.
But my erasers always dry out.
But we're old, you see.
Exactly.
Yes, it's true.
We are fading fast.
Even I don't use...
But that's okay.
That's exactly how it's supposed to happen.
They don't teach you how to map or person.
I can feel myself...
No, they don't have to do figures.
I can feel myself turning into my grandmother.
They do.
Well, my sacred grandmother.
The Uber child.
On the Uber.
I feel myself coming up with the same thoughts
that I would hear her say to me when I was so young.
I thought, you're crazy, old lady.
And now those same roads are in my head.
And I'm thinking, that's what she meant.
Well, what did she tell you?
You mean, do your math?
Well, it was that.
But that was...
I remember the new math.
We did have that.
No one else had that.
Is it the new math?
Please help us.
Tell us.
No, I'm sorry.
I can't share that with you on the air.
The new math?
Yeah.
No, the secret lore passed down.
Because then, yeah, if you say it on the radio,
it becomes true.
Right.
I know.
Now they're calling.
I'm not going to be able to answer.
Don't answer that.
We can't give these secrets away.
They are classified.
She died.
Church business only.
She tried to kill herself.
Me too.
First rule of forbidden science.
Really?
Wow.
Yes.
Was her name Wellman?
Chapter 11.
That's all you need to know.
Verse than ever.
Nor McCoy, nor Hatfield, nor Smith, nor Drummond.
Yeah.
Well, you know what they found about the brains of the Hatfields, I believe.
What they did see was that they had a chronic genetic disease, which inclined them to be
unable to control their anger.
Their temper.
Yeah.
They didn't have enough mass in the neocortical area to...
Are you a Hatfield, my friend, or are you a McCoy?
But I don't know which one.
I forget which side.
Ren Hatfield and Stephen McCoy.
Which is the important thing.
But one of them just couldn't control their anger.
And subsequent generations...
Hatfield Anger Management Corporation.
The Hatfield guys were a little more violent.
Right.
Yeah.
And the book I was reading was all about...
It's a criminal brain.
Just like Dr. Xavier would say.
The endless history of violence that goes through those myths and feuds all the way
into our century and becomes a story to us like Beverly Hillbillies or my favorite, Petticoat
Junction.
Yeah.
That's a sexist shit.
Well, there was a...
There was no show.
It's just girls.
I know, but they never appeared.
I know.
I confused him.
There were shows that I don't remember because he's just a few years older.
They're on the internet.
Look on the internet.
I know, but...
Yeah, but you remember to look at them on the internet.
You should look at them.
Because you remember the show.
The show.
I can't remember the name.
It's ultra cool compared to anything they did after that.
You can't remember the show.
You just don't remember the name.
The more these shows went on, the less they came based on anything real.
Yeah.
That's why I love Petticoat Junction.
What little I remember.
Because there's nothing real except the girls and the...
No.
Well, I was more of a Green Acres man.
I was a Green Acres fan myself.
Well, you had a little bit more television there.
Green Acres was a co-show of Petticoat Junction.
But her sister was kind of...
Sometimes there was actual fusion and crossover between the two shows.
And she was like Eddie Albert on it, which kind of...
The yokels in Green Acres used to watch Petticoat Junction on their television.
Oh, yeah.
Because it was more country-fied, even more crude and rural.
Right.
Did it ever cross over into the Marvel universe, though?
Not for hundreds of years.
Not yet.
But in time...
Would Mr. Douglas ever have to tangle with Doc Ock?
Ever.
That would be great.
Doc, Marvel has yet to tackle Doc Ock.
I have a scene.
Is it from Beverly Hillbillies where...
Did Spider-Man have to fight Mr. Haney?
Not even during Batman, of course.
Doc Ock needs a special part from Mr. Haney's store.
It's Beverly Hillbillies.
Finding it proves difficult.
I know.
D.C. really just dominated TV.
I mean, over Marvel.
Why?
He waited 30...
30 years, Stan Lee.
The time was ripe.
It was incubating.
And now it is ready to decant.
The time was ripe.
He had to wait for those artists to die.
Yes.
Jack Kirby.
I didn't say that.
They set certain standards of balloon dialogue.
Am I on?
Okay, good.
Thank you.
Keep going.
It certainly influenced my text writing style.
I had a tendency to rant.
I kind of quit doing that.
They ranted.
Everybody ranted.
Monsters ranted.
Scientists ranted in those comics.
They went on and on.
For am I not Goo-Gam, son of legume?
Did I not rescue the princess of Ra?
For this is not the way of Grunthorpe.
Asterisk.
No, you know, editor's note from issues 11.
Am I not Cock-a-hoom?
15, 17, and 19.
There was a monster made of wood who came from Planet X,
and he said,
For I am Groot, the lord of all the timber.
In the universe.
Did he wear underpants like the rest of those monsters?
So you've set fire to them.
Because the one weird thing about these huge blobby monsters,
Kirby always drew like swimming trunks on them.
So they'd be decent.
Right.
You can't just have a huge blobby humanoid giant.
It has to have a neat pair of pants on it.
Approved by the Comics Code.
He tried to stay close to the human body.
Would the Comics Code have even...
He did not always stay close to the human body.
What about his most infamous creation,
Fin Fang Foom?
Those commies.
Not humanoid at all.
Those commies deserved it.
Fin Fang Foom.
That was revenge.
I don't even know what that is.
Communist Chinese agents pursuing a victim down an alley
when suddenly they reel back in horror
because of that graffiti.
That graffiti up ahead.
That terrifying graffiti that says,
Fin Fang Foom.
And then it turns out to be,
ultimately it turns out to be a dragon-like monster.
Not a humanoid.
And it punishes the commies.
One of my favorites of those is the Easter Island heads.
Adolf Hitler.
There's got a whole body underneath there.
Yeah, they actually turn out to be real heads
of these huge stone-like giants that come tearing out.
It's just like Fingo.
Oh, that's beautiful.
And all the time,
they're ranting.
They're bellowing.
Foolish humans who dare to think
they can stand beneath the mighty onslaught of...
But then the scientist uses a rock pit
to break a little rock.
Oh my God, their power is too great.
We must flee and never invade this planet again.
Or if they're made of fire,
he lights a match and blows it out.
Do you have this comic still?
He melts an ice cube.
Hal just cognated.
I have a lot of comics with no cover at all.
I thought I smelled something.
I just...
Ladies and gentlemen,
we're getting ready to wind it up.
We're going to make the final pitch
and, uh...
Yes, the end of the first chapter.
Yes.
In a story which will grow longer and longer.
Yes, indeed.
Strange tales.
Those were the big...
Well, I was...
You mean Fin Fang Foo?
Um...
I think they were the oldest.
And then Tales of Suspense.
And then Tales to Astonish.
Tales of Suspenders.
In that order.
Because many of them...
There's 60, 80 issues gone by that...
That I just don't have.
And I've always felt the hole in my life.
You don't have them.
Because of the...
No.
I started, you know, with the superhero era.
See, if you've been loved...
I started with FF25.
If you had been loved,
then your teacher from grade school...
Yes.
Decades ago would have called
and returned those comics to you.
That's right.
But instead, you were...
You know, your family turned you out.
And you had only the comic books to warm you
in the streets of Boston as a child.
Hey, how about...
Has anyone in this room...
Any experience with a comic book called
Kona, Monarch of Monster Isle?
I have.
I remember.
The first...
The most bizarre comics ever.
Yes.
I've got them, Dr. Howell.
In fact, I have Kona going all the way up through
like number 20 or so.
It's not only a lost dinosaur inhabited land,
but it's one that suffers bizarre mutations and...
And giantism.
Even further giantism.
Giantism.
Giant dinosaurs, giant insects.
Right.
Spiders grow the size of dinosaurs
and fight Tyrannosauruses who get infected
and then grow to that much bigger size.
Right.
And they end up forming a mountain
of giant mutated dinosaur and insect flesh.
Right.
Seeking a pheromone...
Every kid's dream.
...that Dr. What's-His-Name has invented
to lure them away.
And then they crack through the ocean...
No, they break through into the cave...
...with a wave of mutations...
Mutants.
...which is full of animals...
And giant mutant sharks that gobble up all the rest.
...mixed up together like a gorilla with an ostrich's legs.
Oh, yeah.
Like a rabbit with a lion's behind.
Like a lion and an alien monster.
And then they fight with the dinosaurs.
It was really bizarre.
And then it got...
After the first three issues,
it's almost like somebody else took over
and it became normal.
The land of the lost.
Right.
The land of the lost actually was a ripoff.
Like DC.
Well, things had to settle down.
Monarch and Monster Eye.
There couldn't be a giant bio-crisis in every issue.
I'm getting all bogged down.
Can't move as fast on show.
In a froggy, bog-infested bog.
What's happening?
Drunk deals.
Oh, we're freaking out now.
The cancer of superstition.
It's the sandbox of pain.
Everyone talking at once.
Was this like Pink Floyd?
That's the only way we'll keep the dark ones away.
Keep talking.
Like kindergarten.
Kids in a sandbox.
I assume we've got the outro guests over there.
At the same time, like meth head kindergarteners.
They can have worked it out.
Kindergarten meth heads?
Yes.
Right.
Yeah, that was a great meth head.
Kindergarten meth heads.
What meth heads?
They were awesome.
Oh, kindergarten meth heads.
I saw them in the open for...
Right.
Well, they named themselves after that movie,
Kindergarten Meth Heads.
With Arnold Schwarzenegger.
The size project, that second album.
Nursery school...
Nursery school dropout.
Nursery school tramp.
Now, the nursery school crack heads was like a rip off that they...
Yeah.
Straight to DVD.
Right.
Didn't work.
It just does sound like a little girl's band, you know?
Girl generation and little girl crack heads are opening, you know, for 12 year olds.
Oh, it's not real, Dad.
Yes, it's mad, it's cracked, it's...
Just characters.
Yeah, like Sailor Moon.
Sailor Moon in your time.
I think we could do a K-pop band like that.
And Hal's still in love with the French girl that was at the...
Oh, I know, the naked girl?
Yes, she was so charming.
We all loved her.
All are in love with her.
Still.
I didn't know she was French.
Yes.
She was French.
She was.
She is French.
And she will be French long after we die.
It seems so, being so young and vigorous.
Viva la France.
Maybe.
And full of something that blurred her out.
It seemed during the evening.
She looked like she was on a blurry voyage.
I'd go close up in her face and just...
Why?
She was just high on life.
Then she'd kind of come back and do it.
I thought you meant she was always out of focus.
She had taken some drug that caused her to be out of focus.
She did well.
She knew exactly how to move and what to do.
Yes.
She was theatrical and stage.
I think they were getting a kick out of the old guy with the camera kind of thing, you know.
Oh, yeah.
Not the old guy with the camera.
Just to have...
That was their audience, huh?
Yes.
Yes, it's getting for me to do time to close down the show.
And remind all my fans that bullying and braggadocio never get you anywhere.
Or maybe not.
And also...
But you get to beat up all the pencil necks and the wimps.
Pencil neck baboons.
Yes, the sickly...
Are you talking about the nattering bulbs of negativism?
Mutations of nature's honest rule.
The pencil neck baboons?
Well, it's...
Let's not get too specific to particular afflictions and cases.
Of the spiral agnew.
The spiral agnew fracture.
Yes, one of the most corrupt vice presidents in history.
He was something, wasn't he?
He liked to go to strip clubs.
Yes, and this nattering the bulbs of negativism.
And the...
You know what?
All that crap was not originating with agnew.
It was written by William Sapphire.
Really?
What I heard...
Nattering the bulbs of negativism was a Sapphire lie.
That's right.
I thought it was written by that woman.
On the other hand, Governor Agnew was one of the most corrupt politicians in American history.
Yes.
As befits any politician that comes out of Maryland.
Is that true?
Oh, yeah.
Or New Jersey.
Or one of our oldest states.
How do you think they call it Maryland?
Or Illinois.
Well, it's just it's one of the oldest states.
It was the capital of the U.S. for all those sorts of things.
And, yeah, the deals go way back in the old family.
It's also the geopolitical...
And Virginia's like that.
Oh, yeah.
Virginia's more important than any other state.
The United States and the Union.
A hundred.
Did you see any of those?
I saw Abraham Lincoln Vampire.
Were we talking about...
Yeah, because it's...
I read the book and really enjoyed it.
And to see the movie, I was very disappointed because it turned into an action flick.
And it's a pretty funny, clever, silly book about Civil War history.
Plus, he also did one of Jane Austen and...
That's what I've heard.
Ghouls, which I have not read yet.
And then there's one about...
Did you read?
Read?
More.
You were here when I watched TV.
Exactly.
Read books, man.
I am.
Read.
Read a book, read a man.
Because you can see the book thing shrinking in front of you.
I know.
The whole...
It's frightening.
I'm trying to read a book now.
But it's not about books.
It's way beyond books now.
What's happening is the end of ownership.
I know.
You can't...
Dammit!
You can't get paid if you write a book.
That's the thing.
Try to...
You can't get paid directly.
See?
The conspiracy is making Reverend Stang...
Eat his hand.
...into a marionette.
Right.
He can't help it, but he...
It's making me hit myself in the face.
Yeah.
Conspiracies.
And it will until you pay those taxes.
It's going to make me set my face on fire any minute now.
You have to cut his strings.
Oh, no!
Don't do that.
Stop making me hurt myself.
Me!
Stop doing that to me.
Don't make him hurt himself.
Stop me!
Lord, me!
Wow, he's gone completely...
That was the Demi-Urge.
The Demi-Urge makes him hit himself.
The Demi-Urge?
His...
The little demigod?
He sprints off his left ear.
Thanks, Bob.
I needed that.
Do any demigods show up at X-Day?
I hope so.
God.
Supposedly, goddesses show up.
Are there goddesses?
You mean a real X-Day?
Yeah, at X-Day Drills.
Yeah, X-Day Drills.
Oh, oh.
Well, we had some girls in funny costumes.
They had...
They had interesting costumes.
There were three of them.
And they had penile and breast-like...
appendages all over them.
Oh!
So they're true subgeni.
It's like a bunch of rubbery fake breasts
and little pointing and phallic things.
I can't think of anything that's more subgenius than that.
It was kind of gross.
At midnight the day...
July 5th.
Or July 4th.
Midnight, July 4th.
They were on stage
and the drunken boys of the...
Very well.
Bobby...
I'm 90%.
The tribe were broken down.
They made a tableau that was unseemly
when seen on video in retrospect.
I was not there.
I was hiding out
because we were planning to arrive by helicopter
at quarter of seven in the morning.
We really did.
We had a...
Jesus had lined up a helicopter
but the weather was too misty.
Oh, damn.
We couldn't fly so we had to do a limousine.
Oh, too bad.
But still, that's pretty...
Pretty prestigious.
Yeah.
I mean, it costs a buck
but it's worth it.
I...
And then I got thrown in the pond
and dunked.
That year was the limousine year?
Yeah.
Wow.
I stepped out of the limousine
wearing a tuxedo
and ended up with a...
tarred and feathered
and thrown in the amoeba pond.
That's mundane human year 1998.
Right, right.
Of course.
1998 con year.
Yeah.
It's the primitive time.
Conspiracy year.
1998.
I'm quite...
Yes, right.
The tribe must decapitate
or assassinate its own pharaoh
or king in order to...
Well, not necessarily
if a suitable sacrifice can be found.
But it's funny.
In some cases,
the king must be eaten.
The way I hear this story come back to me,
I was literally tarred and feathered
by angry people.
But actually, it was honey
and I paid for the feathers,
the pink feathers myself.
That was all planned.
Well, I hope Judge Punch never...
It was the brilliant Papa Joe Mama.
As they were pouring honey on me,
Papa Joe yelled out,
it's motor oil.
And from that point on,
that was gospel.
I had been dunked in motor oil.
Sure, yeah.
A very clever propagandist.
The unplanned part.
Very political.
Being thrown in the pond was not planned.
Thrown in the pond.
And I wish I'd been able to step
just a little bit deeper
into the world.
I was going to be a little bit more
You wouldn't be able to see
where my package ended.
And you wouldn't be...
Which would leave it up to the imagination.
But as it is...
You know, I just looked like
a guy would look
if he had 300 people laughing
at his nakedness.
So what's most people's
most dreadful nightmare
is my memory of a big party
that really happened.
I really did have 300 people
pointing at my nakedness.
And laughing.
Because the aliens hadn't shown up.
Well, you know,
I think I dream about
my worst nightmare.
Like I was Bob.
Like it was all my fault.
Like I ran the exes schedule.
Faithless.
A bunch of...
What are you going to dream about?
They suck on the finger
instead of going where the finger points.
If your dream has come true,
what are you going to dream about now?
I don't.
I just play...
I've retired from reality.
And I just play video games
and read novels.
Yes.
There you go.
I just try to focus on the positive
and have a piece of gum
and I hope it tastes good.
I just hide from everything real.
Alright, for exercise...
I hide from everything real in my life.
I think that's the rest of that.
For exercise,
I stagger a few steps
and fall into a coma.
Yeah, but I've seen that.
I've driven up to pick up
Michael Pepe
for some good reason.
He's in a business meeting
and he's running down the street
naked with 300 people chasing him
in a coma.
Oh, okay.
I thought I was the only one.
We should have a support group.
Yeah, I know.
Two guys.
People that are in there
traumatized
and yet now numb
and can't...
Yes, horribly numb.
...notice it when people
chase them down the street.
You haven't seen me
in that situation since then.
Me neither.
I've learned my lesson.
I don't mess with that.
Well, the thing is,
it's worth the pictures, I think.
Don't get these girls excited.
All these things are worth the pictures
because people look at them.
Look at all these strange photographs
and they're turned into a symbol font.
You don't go see that stuff.
Well, they know you're popes
in a great cult
and they're not sure about what it is
but they know it's going to overtake
the nation and the world.
As time has overtaken us
because now it's time to end
our vigil here.
That was ten minutes ago.
Yes, at this time
the Ask Dr. Hal show
live on radio
ends its broadcast day
on RadioValencia.fm
and...
RadioValencia.fm
is showing you
these mental movies
of ducks and other things
in scratched film
that shows an overexposed
sunset sky
juddering and flicking
and light reflecting from the water.
All right.
Let's clear out of this.