At last I have control of your radio tubes!
Uh, and I do too!
Good! This is Ren Hoak!
And this is Stimson J. Cat of the Ren and Stimpy Show!
And you're listening to the Hour of Slack!
Keep listening, you idiots!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Else I shall kill you!
Shane, look out!
The Self-Genius Hour of Slack!
If anything is excellent or praiseworthy,
we should find something else to do instead.
Now you're starting to get odd.
That's right. Watch it.
Oh!
The problem is, it's special.
Hard of thinking of us.
I cannot.
You really tolerate it well.
And what happens is an old pan,
a pair of neon and old pizelle,
it thins skinless serrates,
and the back of it now comes critched.
In fact, in there, in a gay spunner,
to live in a sea of pus.
The openings of this show, down there,
were by, all of them,
Fernanda Nande, Lee Murr.
More, of course, from him.
My friend, the Pope of all Europe!
Pope Dave Lee Black!
An exile from his own country in America!
Well, I'll tell you more about the conspiracy.
It is Pope Dave Lee Black!
Praise Bob!
Hi-ya!
Hallelujah!
Now, before I get started,
I've noticed that most of you are standing in the back.
I think you need to come up here a little bit.
Come on, come on to the front.
Come on to the front!
Come on, don't stand in the back.
Step up, step up!
Step on up!
Don't be afraid.
Don't be afraid of this man,
this smiley man with a pipe in his mouth.
Come on, don't smile!
Okay.
Now, I want everybody...
He's not real! He's not real!
I want everybody to bow your hands.
Bow your hands in a moment of...
A moment of truly sacred...
Noise!
No!
Praise Bob!
No one wants to...
Woo!
Now, I know most of you have been wondering,
what is this church of the subgenius?
What are you?
We're a...
Well, just to make it a little bit simple,
we are a sex, drugs, and rock and roll,
end of the world, UFO religion,
and the world's only true religion.
Praise Bob!
I'm going to put Bill Money in place.
Allegation that I was...
I had been kicked out of America, this is true.
I am banned from America.
Because I am too slack for America!
And I bring slack and Bob to the shores of Europe,
and I want to...
I want you to look upon this...
You are Meat Loaf, kid!
I am Meat Loaf.
I'm the Meat Loaf of Bob!
Hallelujah!
Look upon this man, this man with the smiley face.
He is the Bob that we all choose to follow.
Pope to Bob!
Point to Bob now!
Point to Bob in the holy photo opportunity!
I'm going to prove to you this is the only world's true only religion.
There were maniacs who flew planes into buildings in New York on the 11th of September.
And they flew these planes into these buildings with a promise they would go to heaven
and they would receive each 42 virgins.
Not in the Church of the Subjugates, my friends!
No!
You don't have to fly a plane into a building and get virgins.
Hell, who wants virgins?
The Church of the Subjugates for $30, you don't have to fly a plane and you get professionals.
Not virgins, but professionals.
Professional virgins.
Now, this is true.
There are other...
There are other popes in Europe, but I am the only pope in Europe that passes out condoms.
It's true.
That other pope won't even wear a condom!
As a matter of fact...
Give me one!
I'm a fan of condoms!
I'll give you one.
I'm not only the only pope in the world that passes out condoms, I'm the only pope in
the world that passes out used condoms.
There you go!
I'm the only pope in the world that eats used condoms!
Hell yeah!
Ultima, Ultimata
That's our story, simple as can be
Though the plan is fraught with dangers and never guarantees
We might be eaten by dragons on the way
But we might prove indigestible, perhaps you'll agree
Illuminatus, Illuminatus, Immaculatus
Illumina, Illumina, Illumina
Ultima, Ultimata, Ultimata
Bang, woo, bill smoking, yay
You live in Raleigh, North Carolina?
What's your, what, suddenly the economy gets a boost?
Fuck
No, I've been getting that look a lot lately
Because I started smoking again and performing abortions
So, you know, I mean
Everywhere I turn these
Sometimes I can hardly get out of bed
But I just love smoking, folks
I'm sorry, I went nine months without them
And, uh, man, what can I tell you?
The hook is fucking deep, man
I'm telling you, they just dropped the bait
Back in the water, boom, plop
They weighed me, you know, hung me up
Caught a big one
But I have this theory
Actually, it's a hope
That if that scenario, you know, is it all the same?
true when you die and you go to heaven and St. Peter meets you at the gate, if that's
at all true, I believe the first thing he's going to ask you is, you got a light? You
mean you all smoke here? Yeah, that's why it's heaven. These aren't clouds, this is
cigarette smoke, buddy. Hell is non-smoking. You want to look down at them for a minute?
Alright. I can't believe what they do to their body. It smells like an ashtray. I'm trying
to eat my food. Why would they want to do that to themselves? Do they know how stupid
that is? God, how hellish. No shit. Light up. Come on in. Hendrix is on harp tonight.
Let me stand next to your fire. Yeah. Man, no one beats Hendrix, man. Fuck Eddie Van
Halen. Fuck Steve Vai. No one beats, fuck. Hendrix was an alien, okay? The ship landed.
They started to fly. They started to fly. They started to fly. They started to fly.
said, Jimmy, show them how it's done. We'll pick you up in 28 years. And you know what
Jimmy said? Alright! He plays his cock. Did you all know that? They just strung his cock.
He played it with his teeth. Does that make him gay? I love people that are dead, for
some reason. They're all my heroes are dead. Keith Richards, for instance. I don't know,
What do you say we do some comedy?
I always like to put some comedy in my shows.
Here's an impression of Keith Richards.
Some people are...
Start talking to him.
It's so real.
Keith!
Boy, Keith went over the edge years ago.
Went over the fucking edge, right?
And everyone thought, that's it.
Keith's gone.
And then they looked over the edge,
and there was a fucking ledge,
and he had hit and landed on it.
There's a ledge beyond the edge.
Keith was like, I hit a fucking ledge.
I'm all right.
Throw down me guitar, I got a song.
There's a ledge beyond the edge.
Keith landed on it.
Lucky bloke.
A lot of people miss the ledge.
I love dead people.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
Bill Hicks.
The great Bill Hicks.
Speaking of dead guys.
You know, we sent him a membership pack.
As an honorary subgenius minister.
One month before learning that he had just died.
Blubber Pigs 15.
Here we go.
Clean it up.
Blubber Pigs 15.
Did you ever ponder the movements of whales?
Whale.
Ah, you're a whale.
Stop.
Whale.
Lemur.
Am I the only one here who feels that tremor in the force?
Or did somebody just cut a fart?
Did someone just bite a tooth?
Did I just hear the moan of the trouser ghost?
Or did the pups...
just take a puff of Bob our guru Bob dogs does not smoke the pipe the pipe
smokes that pipe ever stop smoking that's when we're in real trouble
because you know here's what it really is all about this is the truth if you're
new to this subgenius thing and don't know and and really came here for an
explanation sorry I can't tell you it's like this this is the true subgenius in
slack
that's what the church of the subgenius is all about well Sundays some days
friends it's but see it's not about the intelligence it's about sense common
sense sense of humor the subgenius says dr. own and canna bites said is pre
targeted
free target you know we'd rather be stupid than their idea of smart we'd
rather be stupid than they're smart that's what jr. Bob said don't have
friends we get to see the world through rose-colored glasses and Bob holds them
up for us we pay for a subscription to what we really think and you know you
might say well that's why that guess that's why they call it subgenius
but really friends are the normals that much smarter
have you watched TV lately you know the less you watch it the more retarded it
seems when you do watch I don't have cable deliberately and but when I go to
a hotel I turn the cable TV on and then I'm locked in and I sit there switching
channels for five hours and doing thank God I don't have a TV
I don't have this cable stuff
I can't stop but you know it's gotten to the point where they're so
sophisticated the television producers and makers that you know they're they've
taken it like conceptually they they they go ahead they gloat brazenly at what
cows we are to watch their dumb crap this reality TV stuff actually I'm
surprised it took him so long to start
doing this because it's actually not a bad idea the average dumbass normal human
being is more entertaining than a lot of what they were scripting and putting on
and if you know they aren't following people around and with cameras as they
act stupid or day in danger themselves that's fine you know that's that's no
problem but it's almost as if it's like you watch Jerry Springer or so many of
these shows and you're going God this is so stupid
people must be really dumb to watch this
don't change the channel though
they're just so up front about it the television itself tells you how bad it
is they make fun of how bad they are and how dumb you are to watch them it's as
if they're saying break free of the matrix after this message
I I wasn't going to bring this up my son
sometimes they're inadvertently done
I saw an ad for Go Play yogurt that
they were saying they I guess it's like
every time you buy the yogurt they give
a little bit of money to breast cancer
and the announcer actually said together
we can lick breasts cancer and you know
that Anna Nicole Smith show and my
cousin by the way you watch that stuff
you go maybe everybody's doing that
maybe everybody's looking at the TV
saying man I can't believe how stupid
this is is they're on the cut so rivered by that autosil ski to see her and Miguel Luna who was there well someone who happens to be going down here forever now her partner was studying with these dogs and they were turkey cows at one point before she ran they이 malls with Electronic Black спокойr and they have been to Barcelona zoans as the Carl einhoender very Builtuni over the monitor and Amazon people tried toジ council without them and we get to the thing that's amazing
is. People watch this stuff?
Cool. Well, that group
must be stupid. I could sit here
forever looking at how stupid people
must be to be watching this stuff.
And I'm guilty of it, too.
But the ultimate reality
TV show, friends, started
this Wednesday. It's a great follow-up
to that miniseries from
91. You know,
they've got some new special effects. They've
improved all the graphics and things.
Reality
TV. They've certainly taken it
all the way, I guess.
Viewed
paleoanthropologically,
television paints quite
a visible picture of its very self.
Incredible
levels of talent dedicated
to the giant alibi
for pinkness!
And the dope rating of the language
itself, friends, changing words
to mean less and less instead
of more, and oddly enough, using
more words to do it, irregardlessly.
And the news,
my God, man, I swore
off the news totally for three years,
but of course on September 11th
we had to start tuning in again.
The news is either evil
or it is a sin. We don't know
which yet. But we know
that, uh,
well, maybe, even if the
revolution was televised,
television will
not be revolutionized.
And it is addictive.
And even, you know, I try
to fight back, but
you know, we're all slackers.
As the great slacker princess
we said once, I have
feist in me.
I have feist,
but it just can't be
sourced properly.
In order to fight,
friends, the subgenius
must have slack!
True slack, though.
And everybody knows that.
You know, I don't have to explain that.
And I'm with everybody who's anybody.
But not if it's for everybody,
because I'm cool, you know.
I'm not, I'm only into it
if it's only for everybody
who's anybody.
I'm too independent
to follow the big crowd.
I follow the small crowd.
Good. Real independent thinker.
And everybody knows that
everybody who's anybody
already knew that,
except for the nobodies.
Nobody who's anybody
doesn't know that.
I'm nobody's fool.
Not nobody who's anybody, anyway.
I'm the Ç'olgågu,
And I'm only one with Yaroslav,
It's just me and her fiancée
And me and her fiancée
Vichy and
Rebecca from Warwick,
I'm smarter than all others.
I barely even know
How to put on my own pants
But I'm a genius in France
Genius in France
I may not be the sharpest
Honka cheese
I got a negative number
On my SATs
I'm not good looking
And I don't know how to dance
But nevertheless it is
Quite a de-evil
And I am so widely considered
To be a genius in France
Genius in France
People say I'm a geek
I'm a ronin little freak
And I'm not
With an unfortunate physique
If I was any dumber
They'd have to water me twice a week
But when the mademoiselles see me
They all swoon and shriek
They dig my mystique
They think I'm c'est magnifique
When I'm in Paris
I'm the chicest of the chic
They love my body odor
And my bad toupee
They love my stripy shirt
And my stupid beret
And when I'm sipping
On a Perrier
In some cafe
Down in Saint-Tropez
It's hard to keep
The fans at bay
They say
Sign my poodle
Sibu play
Poodle
Stretches on the hill.
But when I'm in Reuvence, I get free croissants.
Yeah, I'm the guy every French lady wants.
And if you ask them why, you're bound to get this response.
He's a genius in France, genius in France.
That's right.
You know it.
He's a genius in France, genius in France, genius in France.
I'm not the brightest bulb on the Christmas tree.
But the folks in France, they don't seem to agree.
They say, bonjour, monsieur.
Would you take the picture with me?
I say, oui, oui.
That's right.
Oui, oui.
He says, oui, oui.
I'm dumber than a box of hair.
But those Frenchies don't seem to care.
Don't know why I'm on france, but they love me there.
I'm a genius in France.
Gonna make a big splash when I show up in Cannes.
Gonna make those Frenchies scream.
Use a man, use a man, use a man.
Like a fine red war.
War.
I got that shit to say.
Like a fine red war.
Ooh la la.
I got that shit to say.
Qua, qua, qua, qua, qua.
Oui, oui.
I'm a taco short of a combo plate.
But by some twist of fate all the frogs think I'm great.
Oh, the men all faint and the women scream.
They like me more than heavy cream.
When I'm in Versailles, I'm a popular guy.
My, oh, my.
I'm as French as apple pie.
Apple pie.
They think I'm awfully witty.
A riot and a half.
When I tell a stupid joke, they laugh.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
And laugh.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
People and friends have lots of attitude.
They're snotty and rude.
They like disgusting food.
But when they see me, they just come unglued.
They think that I am one happening dude.
Pow, pow, pow, pow, pow, pow, pow.
I'm about as sharp as a bowling ball.
But they like me better than Charles de Gaulle.
André knew it's very true.
The room temperature's higher than my IQ.
But they love me more than Gerard Depardieu.
How did this happen?
I don't have a clue.
I'm not the greatest tractor on the farm.
I don't have any skills or grace or charm.
And most people look at me
like I'm all covered with ants.
But I'm a genius in France.
Genius in France.
And I'm never going back.
I'm never going back.
I'm never, never, never, never going back home again.
I'm tearing up my return flight ticket.
Gonna tell the folks back home where they can't stick it.
Cause I'm never going back.
I'm never going back.
The girls back home never gave me a chance.
But I've shown off goddamn frogs and some kind of trance.
And I'm aware that it's a most improbable circumstance.
But great googly moogly.
I'm a genius in France.
Genius in France.
Just can't wait to kiss my feet.
Get in line, fuck her up, too sweet.
Pow diddy, pow diddy, pow diddy.
I'm getting even more famous by the hour.
I'm stuffed with pastries and drunk with power.
Now they're putting up my statue by the Eiffel Tower.
A little more to the left, boys.
A little more to the left.
I'm the biggest dork there is alive.
My mom picked out my clothes for me till I was 35.
And I forgot to mention I'm not even welcome at the Star Trek convention.
But the Frenchies think that my poop don't stink.
I'm a genius in France.
Say, would you pass the Grey Poupon?
Merci beaucoup.
Weird Al Yankovic, of course, from the album Hoodle Hat.
I think that I ought to begin by saying that our subject today concerns silly.
Oh, let's take an example.
Probably the silliest personal emergency that can come to a man is his silly wedding.
Oh!
Rather than keep you in suspense any longer, the ladies will have to leave the room.
Thank you.
Are you all right?
I'll say that we are guilty, but also look silly.
No, no.
Oh, yes.
24 and a half.
9 and 3 quarters.
13 and a quarter.
24 and a quarter.
42.
42 and a quarter.
39.
43.
Well, I guess I'm in the way here.
So I see.
Good night.
La, la, la, la, la, Lee Moore did it.
And now, a puzzling evidence and glass madness about 20 years ago.
Whatcha gonna sing about at five o'clock in the morning?
Her name, her name, yee-haw.
Talking about Bob Dobbs and the church, everything in a whole big mess on the floor.
Just back, a disorganized first church, a disorganized mess on the floor.
You're a little intimidated.
I'm joining any kind of church.
You can call a church anything you want.
A foundation or a club or just something to look at.
We call it Church of the Fill in the Blank.
And Bob Dobbs is the biggest blank to fill in you'll ever see.
And that's all it is.
Friends and neighbors out there listening, please join us in a moment.
Tonight, we hope that you're putting your hands on the radio and getting the full impact
of this message that's coming down to you.
Face at the very fact of your eyes moving across the page at this very moment as you
try to read your radio as inevitably and sub-atomically decreed.
Your brain is working without your control.
You are locked into the machinations of a cosmic puppeteer who worked your strings so
skillfully you never knew they were there until now.
Feels good, doesn't it?
Oh, it feels so very good when I've got the strings bolt tight.
But we can show you where the strings are attached and how to single them out.
Wake up with a puppeteer.
Will this say life after death, reincarnality, psychic powers, immortality, invisibility,
nirvana, communications, higher challenges, slack, slack, slack, so on.
They may be pink, but their money is green.
So I walked into the jaws of corporate sellout city today.
You did?
Did you lose your corn edge?
Yeah, I bent over and said, let me in the club.
You didn't say put it in here, but don't be gentle?
I said, you put it wherever you want.
Just let me in the club.
He doesn't even want it, gentlemen.
Let me in the dome.
When they release the gas, let me in the dome.
Lube or no lube, don't matter to me, bub.
You let me in, you got your way.
That's why you got into it, man.
You don't like the lube.
You like it rough.
So we'll see if I get called back into the sacred orb for round two.
Are you going to have to kiss?
Round two will be a showdown between three people, like Good to Bad and the Ugly.
Remember the Good to Bad and the Ugly?
At the end, it was three people.
Not a shootout between two people.
But a shootout between three people.
I'm not kidding.
Three people.
Job interviews are more and more like American Idol.
This was definitely like American Idol.
They are definitely all videotaped now, too, from the time you walk in the door.
They want to make sure there are no stains down there, you know, where I'm talking about,
too.
The feet are packed.
Well, you did great in the bathing suit contest.
I did really good in that.
You had to wear five pairs of socks on that thing, though, to get any kind of substantial
formate.
Oh, they all do that.
That's understood.
I did really good with the Motown song.
That goes with the rock and roll.
You sometimes take off that ten-point slide for too many songs.
The Motown song was good.
The R&B song was all right.
Somebody else.
What did you do?
Did you stop the name of love?
The Elvis song, though, was a little tough because I picked a hard one.
Which air...
I picked the American Trilogy.
Which air guitar tin did you pick?
Or did they assign one?
No, no.
That's coming up in round two.
Oh.
They're saving that for the big round.
Yeah.
That's just a bunch of eye injuries and those things.
Man, they make sure that EMS is on call.
And make sure you're getting plenty of food and water.
And make sure your vacation time is clearly marked here on the digital cock.
I mean, clock.
I'm sorry.
Rocking...
It's only rock and roll.
Boy, talking about Freudian.
Yeah, I know.
Man.
That guy kind of climbed in my head, and now I can't...
I just...
I don't know.
That was pretty Freudian.
I'm still thinking about little kids.
I mean, super everyone.
Just have my 12-year-old boys punching me in the eye.
The one listener is listening.
Because they don't get their way.
Look, Chaz, the one listener is listening.
Oh, cool.
He's calling again.
And his twin brother on the other line.
Come on, man.
It's okay.
You can call now, and you can express yourself freely, because damn it, we liberated this
zone for your protection and flavor.
Just relax, release, and just let it go.
Enjoy.
It's for your own good, man.
It's good for your own good.
Push, like you're trying to get one out.
It'll go in easier.
Come on.
Remember what mommy did so many years ago when she pooped a waterman?
I called it you, son.
And friends, of course, that was ESO Radio, Swamp Radio from WCSB, Cleveland, with Professor
Chaz Smith, the host, lonesome cowboy Dave, Princess Wee, and Yee.
And now, Leigh-mer.
You got it.
Re-scanning the Earth, you can do it.
Hey, you guys want to keep it down?
There's more than enough lame decor.
It doesn't have to be an entity.
Delicious frozen custard.
It doesn't have to be a custard.
It doesn't have to be an entity.
It doesn't have to have fibulations because its heart beats.
Listen, you can hear the sound of the pounding heart of the show from under the floorboards.
Has the pain ended?
Oh, God, look at that EEG.
It's incredible that it could be in a coma for this long, yet still it goes on and on like the vegetable it is and doesn't die.
Although when you purchase all three, it's only $16.98 per stew.
They try to clean up the song and make it feel good about itself.
They thought maybe then it would be over.
Maybe just a sense of bitterness was keeping it from dying.
The other members of the team kept ranting about other things while the song pulsated along behind them.
Unbeknownst to their very actions.
You know, go ahead, try to kill it, Hal.
Try to kill the song right now.
Take this gun and shoot the song.
Just try to cripple this song, Hal.
No, let it glide along.
Slow it down.
Hold on, we're trying to pull you up right next to our little spacecraft.
They cut off three of its legs, but look at it.
It's still chopping along.
There you are.
You're climbed on.
You're on, you're on.
You're in, you're in.
Dr. Philodrum, Dr. Howell and Puzzling Evidence on the KPFA Puzzling Evidence Show.
By the way, this music or sound in the background is from Negative Land,
whose show precedes the Puzzling Evidence Show on KPFA.
I don't know.
For the vivid subgenius imagination is in a churning turmoil of constant growth,
and it can make the wait blessed.
When starving, or contemplating unpaid bills,
the subgenius eats his imagination for breakfast and lunches on his own soul.
It invents more possibility of future pain and joy,
letting us see their immense range and depth,
and that they are subjective.
We then realize that duration is dependent upon mood.
Could we control our own rates?
We could shorten a paradigm,
and reduce the time to zero and apparent slack time infinitely.
Meanwhile, the subgenius must bravely face the bars of his cage.
Patience is the only form of time control,
at least until the time of now.
Now, go for a walk and keep walking,
until you stub your toe,
get mugged,
or until your feet really hurt.
This will remind you that what you have been reading is valid only hygenia your head
and just a bunch of philosophical crap to begin with.
There's no sense in getting permanently cosmic,
McHatted, even if you could and most yulgis are only faking it to themselves. You still have to eat, and your shit still stinks.
There is such a thing as getting too high, and death is a waste, though that is the only reason you should be afraid of it.
Religious yahoos can keep blabbering glib crap forever, us included, and it's a good flushing out of the brain-pen,
but that's all it is. The rest is between you and Bob. Good luck, suckers.
Time control outtakes from the subgenius book Revelation X, read by the author.
One of the most spectacular kinds of automobile accidents is the one in which a car not only gets banged up,
but bursts into flames.
What makes it really horrible
is the idea that a driver and his passengers, stunned by the accident, may be trapped inside the burning car.
Let me get up.
The National Safety Council says that, proportionately for most of us, this type of spectacular smash-up
is very rare.
The thing that stuns people inside a car...
Well, let me get up.
Artemia Salina did it.
And now,
Les Meux.
McCain, you've got a lot to learn about dirt.
That dirt, McCain.
I want you to look around, and you tell me who'll pick dirt.
That dirt.
But, if the marshal's dirt was the dirt, why Paul never throw that dirt in the dirt?
I don't know.
He's got too much dirt.
Because I don't believe in principles.
But it's important dirt. Very, very important.
Who is it?
Still awake, son?
Can't seem to get to sleep.
Well, maybe you can sleep if you think of something pleasant.
Not Michael or me!
Maybe.
Mark, I told you before.
You had no right to get away.
I'm sorry, Paul.
One thing is sure.
We're not your friend.
Mark, wait.
I'd be glad to.
Well, I guess I take the prize for stupidity.
I know.
I know the one you mean.
Don't you have at least 15 friends?
No, it's easy.
The problem is you get too many.
A range of friend stock.
Like 16.
We'd have to have a friend stock.
We'd have to have like more than 15.
We might have to have 16 friends.
We can rent some friends.
I know there's this place called Rent-A-Friend now where you can go in and you can rent somebody.
Rent-A-Friend?
Is that like where you can get a Russian bride?
They'll act like they've known you for a long time.
You'd give them like a bio sheet and they'll memorize your bio sheet.
And then like when they walk around with you, you know, they'll always be laughing at your jokes no matter how late.
I don't show any jokes.
I don't trust anyone in my bio sheet.
You know, you don't have to pay them too much.
You notice this scene looks a lot like the one in 2002 where the guy touches the monolith.
You pay their expenses and give them money.
I was enjoying the special effects but they just somehow didn't look very convincing.
But did you notice that when you have your Rent-A-Friend that they never say anything bad?
Yes. Well, that's their job, you see.
They never ever say anything bad.
I mean a good friend, a real friend will tell you bad news every now and then.
So...
When you rent one, it sort of like breaks down after a while.
And people can say, you know, people will notice, hey, I think that's Hal's Rent-A-Friend because he never says anything bad about Hal.
But there are natural culling factors which would remove me and him from any suspicion.
That boy needs therapy.
Psychosomatic.
You're psychosomatic.
That boy needs therapy.
You lie down on the couch.
What does that mean?
You're a nut!
You're crazy in the coconuts!
What does that mean?
That boy needs therapy.
I'm gonna kill you.
Granny gazoo, let's have a cheer.
I will not count to three.
That bro.
That.
Boy needs therapy.
He was white as a sheet.
And he also made false teeth.
That's what I want to see.
And I want to see what you're looking for.
Frontier Psychiatry
Can you think of anything that talks?
Other than a person?
Uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh.
A bird?
Yeah.
Sometimes a parrot talks to me.
And sometimes...
Sometimes...
The laundry talks to me.
And sometimes...
A little teeny piece of hardware talks to me.
A little wax statue.
A little...
A person this big talks to me.
And we go dancing.
In a club in my own mind.
And I used to have friends.
And they used to be on the air with me.
But now they just sit around and drink little energy drinks.
And draw little smiley faces.
At times.
Yeah.
But people still think the show's funny.
They do talk about phantom planets that are actually planets in another dimension
that we can't see or anything like that.
Oh, come on.
The only thing that...
The only way we can tell they exist is through their gravitational...
The only messenger particles that could carry between the two dimensions would be gravity.
So would this explain dark matter and that stuff running out of Dave's nose?
Yeah, they're trying to...
Gravity waves.
Explain all kinds of stuff like that.
Now she...
Now I'm confused again.
Gravity is particles?
I thought gravity was waves.
Or maybe wave particles.
The graviton.
There's actually...
Did you ever hear about the graviton?
No, I have not heard of graviton.
It's all a bunch of fairy tale stuff.
What are these?
I find these to be odd.
I don't believe it unless I see it.
Fairy tales and children's stories.
I can prove the world's flat.
The moon is made of green cheese and the world is no more.
It's flat.
If the world was curved, then puddles would have a curve.
They're flat.
If the world was round, stank, we'd be able to dance all the way to the other side and back and never know the difference.
What do you think, Wee?
Well, the horizon is straight.
It's not curved.
It's straight.
So it must be flat.
Flat.
Flat as it can be.
Flat as your skull.
Sometimes it seems to go up and down and kind of curves at the sides.
Upwards.
Like...
There's something really wrong.
Stank, if the world was round, you couldn't go bowling.
The balls would go on infinitely and return back into your hand from the opposite direction.
That happens below the equator, right?
I don't know about blowing the equator or any of these other strange things you allude to,
but I know one thing.
If the world was truly round, you'd not be standing where you are right now.
All ready?
This lecture is about Guatemala.
Uh, heeem.
Guatemala is far more, uh, powerful than the CIA.
Before beginning the lecture, one point I should make is that when people think of this Guatemala,
they think of lawyers, they are gonna be front and center because
The Lord's law and the sons of our Lord,
which maps the un-made things.
I don't know what I'm doing.
It's difficult to give a lecture and not avoid Guatemala.
All by myself!
You look down, you see a Guatemala, Leon.
What's that?
You know what a turtle is?
Of course.
Same thing.
A little bit there by Reverend Jartow.
Uh, friends, you know, this show, it's not just you.
This show makes me feel weird, too.
In fact,
I'm feeling kind of weird.
I'm feeling kind of sick!
Do you need to go to the hospital?
No, take the camera out of the hospital.
Do you need to the hospital?
I need the hospital!
I need to go to the hospital now.
Until I'm one of the current early middle aged.
Hey, can I take you to the hospital now?
Yeah, take me to the hospital, please.
I think you need to go to the hospital.
No, I don't.
Yes, you do.
No, I don't!
No, I don't.
Yes, you do.
Jews of the arcane period.
It's weird.
Go to the hospital.
Go!
Get up and go now.
Get up and go?
Or you just stand up and walk over
to the hospital? Yeah, just go.
Just get the hell out
and go to the hospital.
But I feel better now.
I don't think my heart is beating
too fast in that crash.
It's imploring my mind as bad
as it was.
Something is subtly wrong with me.
That's okay. The hospital is waiting.
They've staffed up for you.
They've added on new doctors
and new nurses.
And a whole army of volunteers
ready to meet your needs are waiting
at the hospital.
I don't want to go to the hospital anymore.
I don't want to be more injured.
That's okay.
The hospital is free now.
You go to the hospital.
It doesn't cost any money.
You just walk in.
They'll start doing the tests.
You don't have to sign
any papers.
You don't have to wait in the waiting room.
They did away with the waiting room
because there's no waiting.
You just walk in.
And there's a whole hospital
dedicated just to you.
A whole staff.
Yeah, just for you.
It has a whole staff of doctors
and nurses, lawyers,
all those other kind of people
that are at hospitals
to take care of you
without any overlap.
Without any
focus on any other patients
besides you.
You are it.
Yee-haw!
I make electric chair
at home in your own hat.
Everybody's dropping out, man.
Everybody's dropping out.
Some of these blue and red...
Can't fight the machine no more.
And they're tuning out
and turning out.
That's right.
And toning out.
Did you ever try and make a...
a homemade electric chair
in your own home?
Like you make the chair
with the straps
and you get like one of mom's
aluminum pie pans
to put on your head.
Oh, sure.
And then you get the, uh,
you know, the battery charges
and attach them to your
nine, nine, nine, nine, nine,
nine, nine, nine, nine apples.
And then you...
you just stick your feet in the water
and you're good to go
somewhere.
We killed the neighbor's
kid's bunny that way.
You put him in the chair?
You gave him the chair?
A little fake chair
and a car battery.
Did you guys go through
like a series of appeals
or anything like that?
No, no.
No, you just...
It was just cruel
Pobucker kids.
Not even a trial
for the bunny.
You didn't even try him
or anything or charge him
or anything?
No, it was just,
just cruelty to animals.
That's what kids did
in Fort Worth in the day.
See, when we would...
In the 50s.
When we...
The 1850s.
Yeah, the 1850s.
Who else was there
to torture besides animals?
You were a kid.
We have a real police force here
and they have enough
M-16 toting criminals
to deal with
and without scooping up
sub-dini's without table manners.
Sidewalk lawyer G.G. Gordon
had his hands full
just trying to get
us out in one piece
because of that little dinner.
Those jokers have got to go.
Can't you burn their houses down
like you did
your buddy D. Burns suggested?
Maybe then they'll see
Stemo comes out here
with the same fake accent
they all use,
all of you use,
and slays no one.
Jayner spouts
that his lower extremities
are aflame.
That he wishes
and asks
that a member of the court
at both the state
and federal levels
not to mention God
to perform
an evil,
defiled,
sex act on him.
Just that he may hear
the same washed out sound effect
of an explosion
that we all heard.
Ha ha ha.
I was mortally embarrassed
to play that Midwestern drivel.
But in the interest
of salvaging
some sort of a show
from the muck,
I bore on.
Kids,
I'm afraid I've
I've lost
the most precious thing
there is to me.
My personal slag.
All children,
gather round.
The older girls
come closer.
The ones who are
starting to sprout.
Are you missing
your slag, brother?
Have you no slag?
Well,
praise Don.
Don brings slag
to the slagless.
If you down in your mine
or your quarry
have not enough slag,
you're not going to have
why R.L.
Don Glods
will bring you slag.
Smooth.
And he will teach you
the story
of the M-ists
from outer space
who will come
down to Earth
and save all those
who spent their $31.
Oh, yes.
Praise Don.
Don will let you play
with your thermometer
in the rain
unlike Bob Dobbs
who will let you
stand in hackneyed
in short.
He's the kind of man
who visited his block
and was like,
whew,
what was in that stuff?
Is that stuff
or is it just something else?
Oh, that's that stuff
we are Bob Dobbs,
soldier, ain't it?
He ate it?
He ate it.
He can't stop thinking
and hang down it
all the time.
It just goes like Bob.
It gets into your brain
and then it just
scrambles everything up.
Thank God we're into Don now
and forgot that evil slag.
Black Meister Bob.
Trying to heal, you know,
those who've been brainwashed
by the Bob cult.
Those we dare.
We're recovering.
Those poor people.
Recovering cult addicts.
That was about his mother, I think.
His sainted mother.
His sainted gray-haired granny.
Well, you know,
there's no replacing
his gray-haired granny
and his...
blue-haired brother,
brown-haired idiot uncle.
His pet idiot.
And his pet idiot.
Can you believe
that they allowed him
to keep a pet idiot?
Actually, to tell the truth, Chaz,
I've been doing
X-Day shows
for Hour of Slack
ahead of time.
They're all done.
So it's like
anything we say about X-Day now
would be used
on next year's show.
I can't stand the pleasure.
Assuming that the world
was still here
and that our cult is, in fact,
just a sad, pathetic joke.
Well, that's true.
Struggling tadpole out of the water.
Never to grow.
Never, ever to lose its tail
and grow legs.
Well, now, Reverend Stang,
is it not true that you gave
in the year 1980 itself,
and it says here
in my congressional rectify,
says here that you gave...
We tried to destroy the world.
You tried.
Well, you actually succeeded.
You tried to destroy
some parts of the world.
Isn't that true, Senator Klebop?
No.
That was absolutely true,
Senator Hedwig.
That was the federal building
in Waco, Texas.
Well, it says here
it was the Fezziwig building
of the Imperial Literacy Towers,
a place that doesn't really exist
except for in your warped mind.
Well, look, look.
Almost every religion
has an end-of-the-world prediction.
Sir, are you...
Fizzles are...
You know, they try to end the world
in their immediate vicinity.
I cannot...
We've got a...
We've got a virus this time, though,
that we think is going to work.
It's going to take a while,
so, you know,
the July 5th thing
becomes sort of more of a symbolic...
If my ears aren't burning now,
I don't know so when my ears
will ever burn again.
You have said not only
you've promised to hook
the virus upon this land...
It's done.
...to visitate the pestilences
and so forth.
You've not only included yourself
in this plan,
but you call yourself
a religion?
What?
I almost swore.
In the name of the Lord,
I can't...
What kind of religion
would you call that?
Well, I'm...
An above-average...
Well, below-genius religion, sir.
Your Honor.
It's not...
Just another...
Just another end-of-the-world
UFO sex weirdness.
Well, these moon pants you've marked there,
they're containing spent plutonium,
much like the weapons
we're using in Osaka, Japan.
Sir, how can you be
so cold-blooded?
I know you have some
lizard blood in you,
but how can you be
so cold-blooded?
Who let the rooster in?
Yeah.
Well, the plutonium
in the moon pants
prevents normals
from being born
to subgenius couples
who wear the moon pants.
That's weird.
Well, I...
I never saw a rooster
If my ankles are not
covered with sweat
and turning green right now, sir,
I do not know
if they ever shall.
Now you've got
the music to this.
You've got the music to this.
You seem to think
you're some kind of big deal.
God only knows
where you get those ideas.
You know you're nothing
but a shield for the need-mill
that you want you to
make happy a bill.
But everybody wants
a slice of the pie,
but I don't see
who's watching through you.
This Catholic tradition,
it's a sin.
It's a downright disgrace.
It's a sin.
You never thought
I'd find out the big secret.
Now you've got
the music to this.
You've got the music to this.
The geeks at the boys
know all about it.
You've got to get out of town.
You've got to take a platter with it.
It doesn't look like
you draw a lot of water with it.
You don't have any say
in the matter with it.
Look for someone
to throw the book at you.
Take the world's last
sincape off our heads.
It's a shame.
It's a sin.
It's a downright disgrace.
You never thought
I'd find out the big secret.
Now you've got
the music to this.
You've got the music to this.
Now you've got the music to this.
You've got the music too
Music
You've got to face the music
Face the music
You've got to face the music this time
You've got to face the music
Think boys
With Dr. X on vocals
May he rest in peace
Red Heights, Ohio
Ah yes
I am the bursar of
Dumpstown
Dumpstown, Ohio