it begins
when you and connie first split up i i think i i end up being the same yeah
what does your husband think about your relationship with this but we're friends that's
it
so
oh my god
too bad he was such a fine noble savages
it wasn't he oh
i don't understand i don't understand neither do i i think you take the rabbits after you eat them
and you stuff the air in that and then you put them in the guns you know stuff the air in the
rabbits yeah the rabbits and then the rabbits you know wow man have you ever seen the rabbits
man slam across the freeway the pink noise is blowing in the night on new year's eve heavy
not getting nobody not even here not not even hitting on nobody man not even begging like
they do most of the time for the rabbits fun those rabbits remember they are screwing up
the whole park with this begging how is that well man oh daddy oh you're so crazy bob
bob
the message is now part of and registered in your subconscious mind every time you say see
hear or think what about slack that's your key phrase it will trigger the entire message without
your being aware of it uh yes dear friends this week's show hour of slack number 983
is a rerun of an ancient golden age hour of slack number 373 recorded in december in 1992 over 100
years ago actually we have removed some of that show and replaced it with a clip
from an excerpt of the bob larson christian radio talk show which featured me yours and the show is
truly revered i've been staying as a guest in may of 1998 yes in 1998 bob larson did an interview
with me about the church coming up and now the subgenius
a universe where anything is possible
a universe of many gods often in conflict when she made it with the dust
what came forth was water
the living water water that contained the minuscule beginnings of the critters crawling little things
there was no
big
knowledge bigger careers occurred you've seen you've seen pictures in the museums and books
the dinosaurs hey these were the big ones
the dinosaurs cool
My goggles.
Big bird.
You've seen them.
Hello?
Yes, go ahead. You're on the show.
Hi.
I've been, uh,
up all night.
And, uh,
starting to see things.
Like, um,
well, heck,
you know how sometimes
when there's only a little bit of light in the room
and pictures on the wall
start to get wavy?
Um,
are you smoking, Frog?
No, absolutely not.
Just sleep deprivation.
Bones, bones.
Could something
be making me hallucinate?
I mean,
nice touch.
I'm, uh,
arriving.
And this, uh,
it helps me write
sometimes.
But, um,
I'm not writing right now.
I'm trying to sleep.
It's not working.
So I turned into...
So would you like us to
turn our...
Would you like us to turn our show down?
Is that what you're saying?
No, not at all.
It's really neat.
I like it a lot.
It's actually healthy.
It's actually nice.
It's nice.
The subgenius
owl of slack
that you are about to listen to
is specially designed
only to be played
on radio station
Uh, this one.
and only
in the city of
right around here.
Should any other shows
be heard from or contacted
in the course of this show,
the listener is advised
to remain calm
and only contact
listed or unlisted officials
in the event of any material
from this radio
or other listening device
being inhaled during broadcast.
Small animals
or other children
becoming exposed
to the ultra-high
or ultra-low shocks
and brain frequencies
constantly screaming,
and the brain scan
throughout our program
should seek shelter
in an approved safety unit only.
This is Walter Teasdale
reminding you
that it's often a photon
that light releases,
but truth is,
not everyone gets the picture.
The sound of the apprentice
is smelling
and they smell bad.
Yes.
We are the brain's least gravity.
Self-indulgent
is a matter of taste.
We're a living, breathing example
that a brain is a terrible thing
to waste.
We are brain-free.
Yes.
And this here is insane.
A five-year-old Chinese boy
has been inexplicably
bursting into flames,
according to baffled doctors
and the lad's frustrated mother.
Little Tong Tang Jiang
has burned his way
through numerous sets
of underwear
as doctors try to contain
the spontaneous combustion
of the little tot,
which occurs as often
as twice an hour.
The little tot
is a little bit
more likely to die
than the little boy.
So far,
the incendiary infant
has set fire to a couch,
ruined the bed mattress,
the opposite of bed wetting,
and narrowly missed
setting his grandmother on fire
when she got too close.
Everyone is terrified
to go near him.
For Goofball Radio,
this is Ralph Fielding Snell.
Yeah, okay,
now we're talking
to Granny now
about the birth
of the little boy.
See if you can get
anything out of her.
I couldn't.
Oh, God.
You know,
I think we just had
a bulletin in
from the subgenius
something or other.
It's the sad show.
That laughing gas again.
It's a very sad moment
here on the show.
Come on.
Oh, sorry,
I put these feathers away.
I should be crying
and you're making me laugh.
It's a sad moment
here on the show.
We don't like
to make fun of things,
like, of course,
pregnant men.
Hi,
this is Goofball.
You're wearing
an A-back top for me.
Were the awesome
megaliths of Europe
erected on Earth
energy centers
not long ago,
but since forgotten?
Hmm.
I forgot.
Where were you, Hal?
Why do powerful
magnetic fields
and ultrasound
continue to be
recorded near them?
One in five
German motorists
actually enjoys
being stuck
in a traffic jam,
according to a survey
in the Hamburg-based
BAT Leisure Research
Institute.
The BAT Leisure Research
is a major
research facility
in the United States
that has been
used to
detect
a possible
Mammoth
in the world.
very
powerful
device
that can
detect
a Mammoth
in an
And
it's
a
very
a Mammoth
in a
huge
space.
It's
a
very
powerful
device
that can
detect
a Mammoth
in a
very
small
size.
It's
like
a
human
in a
small
space.
But
it's
a
very
powerful
device
that can
detect
a Mammoth
in a
and you're on the verge of destroying each other.
Something has gone wrong,
and we are going to come back and show you
how to take this next step in your evolution
and start a new age on this earth.
I think it is themselves that the popular story goes,
because they overfed themselves.
Believe it or not, it doesn't make any difference.
She was out.
To get a critter with the appendages
to finally have evolved over the centuries,
a critter with the appendages to carry out her will.
Her will is to command a critter
to be able to build and manipulate
the extension of the brain,
of the brain, the knowledge center,
which she instilled in her.
The water, the initial blooming water,
is something that a religious man
not sure about.
Well, I'm not.
Yeah, people have been mindless since the world began.
You see, it's perfectly all right.
Who cares about life if that is just in the real world?
We demand our human rights.
We are brain free.
This here is insanity.
Come on, come on, come on.
Thank you, thank you.
Come on, thank you.
Squeal.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
I guess I should make some personal contact with you real quick
and let you know that you've been listening
to so many different subgenius tape contributions.
We have so many for you here.
Going back, we have so many.
We're going backwards in time.
Let's see, the music, Brain Free 7 by John Bartels.
More John Bartels coming up, also known as Joe Schmo.
That amazing stuff about she who evolved the critter
to build the pipe.
We still don't know, friends.
Some KPFA news from Dr. Howell and Puzzling Evidence.
Puzzling Evidence and Dr. Howell show
that's, there's more of that coming up.
Of course, Bleepo Abernathy is our official announcer.
You heard some KHSU shows, bits there from the fellow who,
the caller who was seeing things.
And little bits of Media Barrage by Reverend Nick Nolan.
Some really rare Firesign Theater,
which will also pop up again.
And some Joe Newman, of course, which, and some,
and some Joe Sosodotta on sound effects.
Even Dave Fluglewitz on sound effects.
But friends,
friends,
I have an announcement to make.
Ah, yes, and this is not,
Watch what you say to me.
That was very heavy sound effect.
You know, the United Nations right now is meeting,
trying to limit the use of violent sound effects.
You got a big nose.
You know, I think KCSA should be a little more serious.
I wake up in the morning and I turn you on.
I'm an original subscriber.
And you're disrespectful of your listeners.
In what way?
You know, I'm quite serious about this.
Well, which listener are we not respectful of, properly speaking?
Well, if...
If you wake up in the morning and you come into the station,
you should listen that your readers, your listeners should be intelligent.
Well, we can't affect that.
You don't sound intelligent.
Our listeners should be intelligent.
We can't affect their intelligence level.
You could try.
Well, how?
Will you teach them parables?
You could try by being intelligent yourself.
Well, we attempt to educate them, but they just won't learn.
You don't seem to be talking about anything serious like...
like understanding, like consideration, like...
like education, like stuff like that.
This is a peaceful situation.
Uh, no, I don't think it's peaceful.
I think it's silly.
It's not warlike.
What do you mean?
You complain about silliness?
What about the laugh, the ecstatic laugh in the fields of the Lord?
The whirling in the fields of understanding and peace?
Oh, don't be silly.
Well, do you want us to be unnaturally grave, gross?
No, no, no.
You're not even funny.
Honey, you're not even funny.
Well, we're funny looking.
That's worth something.
Why don't you try to develop a little humor?
Well, uh, we're acme-ish or vitreous humor.
We'll try to grow a lump for you.
That's your idea.
You are not humorous.
You are silly.
You are ticklish.
Well, I'm sure that some of our callers may agree with what this caller has to say.
And naturally, like...
That's my humor.
...all such...
People like Chris and Philip, for instance, is that they're very serious.
You know, I know Chris and Philip personally.
But they're also humorous.
We go golfing together, and I go water skiing with his lovely wife.
You have to get personal.
It's time to get personal now.
Oh, dear. Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
What inspires you to attempt to modify and...
I used to work at KPSA, and I'm 72 now.
And I have five children.
Well, I hope they're listening to our program, too.
And the thing that...
...impresses me about you young people in the morning is that...
What makes you think we're young people?
...you're so frightened is that you're silly.
Well, but we're actually old as the hills.
We're not young.
Ah, she just couldn't take the blinding treat.
I have waited so long for such a call.
I must say, it's pretty low when people call up and pretend to be old.
When they're actually young hippersnappers and spring chickens, they can't fool old grandpappy.
Does that sound kind of foolish to you?
You know, you're not funny.
And you're not...
You're not serious.
And you're just silly.
I'm sorry, honey.
You're just silly.
But here's the point.
I work at it.
You know, the thing I've noticed about you young people is that you're just...
You're silly.
Oh, come on.
We're serious.
This is an absolutely serious show.
You can't tell that...
No, you're from Sirius, not Alpha Centauri like most people think.
A mysterious object from the depths of space.
We don't make any jokes.
We don't ever...
You know, I'm...
I'm serious.
I'm 160.
I'm 60 years old now.
I've got 25 great-grandchildren.
Hey, didn't you accidentally cut off your head?
Oh, no.
You're not funny and you're not serious.
What is peace and what is funny and what is serious?
They don't really make perfect sense to me.
I'm a dang.
I'm a hypocrite.
I ask for sincerity and I lie.
I denounce the system as I embrace it.
I want money and power and prestige.
I want ratings and success.
I don't give a damn about you or the world.
The world.
That's the truth.
For this, I could say I'm sorry, but I won't.
Why should I?
I mean, who the hell are you anyways, you audience?
You're on me every night like a pack of wolves
because I can't stand facing what you are and what you've made.
Yes, the world is a terrible place.
Yes, cancer and garbage is what will get you.
Yes, a war is coming.
Yes, the world is shut to hell and you're all goners.
Everything's screwed up and you like it that way, don't you?
You're fascinated by the gory details.
You're mesmerized by your own fear.
You revel in floods.
Car accidents.
Unstoppable diseases.
The happiest wonders are pain.
That's where I come in, isn't it?
I'm here to lead you by the hand through the dark forest
of your own hatred and anger and humiliation.
I'm providing a public service.
It's so scary.
You're like a little child under the tree.
You're afraid of the covers.
You're afraid of the boogeyman
because you can't live without him.
Your fear, your own lies,
are becoming your entertainment.
Next month, millions of people are going to be listening to this show
and you have nothing to talk about.
Marvelous technology is at a disposal.
Instead of reaching up to new heights,
you're going to see how far down we can go.
How deep into the muck we can immerse ourselves.
What do you want to talk about?
These last four hours.
Your pet.
Orgasms.
You're pathetic.
You despise each and every one of you.
You've got nothing.
Absolutely nothing.
Your brains.
Your power.
Your body.
Your future.
Your hope.
Your God.
Your faith.
The only thing you believe in is me.
What are you afraid of?
I'm not afraid, see?
I come in here every night.
I make my case. I make my point. I say what I believe in.
I tell you what you are.
I have to. I have no choice.
You frighten me.
I come in here every night.
I tear into you. I abuse you.
I insult you.
And you keep going back for more.
What's wrong with you? Why do you keep calling?
I don't want to hear anymore. Stop talking!
Go away!
A yellow-bellied, spineless,
bigoted, quivering, drunken,
insomniac, paranoid,
disgusting, perverted, boyish,
little, obscene phone callers.
What the hell with you?
I don't need your fear
and your stupidity. You don't get it.
It's wasted on you.
Poor swine.
So sad.
So fresh.
The days that are no more.
Tears.
I know not what they mean.
Tears from the depths of some divine despair.
Dennis Whiterson, 61, of Newark,
when looking only happy at the fields,
and thinking of the days that are no more.
Two days later, he killed himself
by hammering two five-inch nails
into his head.
Fresh as a sunbeam
glittering on the sail
he brings our friends up from the underworld.
Here they come, Al.
Sad as the one that
trembles on the verge
before it sucks them all back down again.
I'm gonna take those nails away while he's trembling there.
I think that's a bad deal.
So sad, so fresh,
the days that are no more.
Ah,
brain-burned hours
as in dark summer dawns,
the earliest pipe of half-awakened birds
which see to dying eyes a dying show
which in the listener's ear
fade and fade.
So sad, so fresh,
the shows that are no more.
So how goes the show?
Well, it wanders
mooing throughout the pastures,
up the hillsides, across the meadows,
over the stills,
it is buried deep in Neck Valley Glade.
It is buried deep in Neck Valley Glade.
Oh, spooky!
Oh, yeah, Jim Jones'
rocket party.
That's right.
Yes, that's right. You see,
we trap deuterium in the form of a plasma.
It's an ionized gas
and confine it within a powerful magnetic field
right here in the studio.
The gas is then heated by
bombarding it with energy.
Now when we get the temperature of this plasma
up to at least 50 million degrees Celsius,
this process becomes self-sustaining.
This process becomes self-sustaining.
The energy of the emitted neutrons
can be captured as heat,
and in turn we use that to power our vehicle.
...positive by the otherness
of the 9-1-1 instructions
that are included in the warhead.
Yes, the itchiness of the scratchiness
and the richness of the whatness.
Well, I hope you don't have a heart attack right now.
I'm going to call 9-1-1.
Excuse me.
Oh, no, no, no, wait a moment.
You know, it's all in the mind, you know.
We are the legendary seven.
We are living we shall.
The brain is a terrible thing to weigh.
And if you think space
And if you think space and time
are everything, all encompassing
But whether or not you
think it or not
Does it matter? What is the reality?
To discover the reality of anything, we have to find out certain facts.
And the most important fact in any scheme is to find out what the end result of the scheme is.
Something is trying to get through to us.
The moment person out there had any idea of what I was talking about, I...
I...
Your mind. It is the center of your life.
It is everything you hear.
Everything you see.
Everything you feel.
It is everything you are.
How you move.
It is what's still your mind.
It is what's still your life.
What would you do?
Suppose that the little pet, the friend of your bosom that you had all these times,
was taken and thrown into a pit like vermin.
What would you do?
Fly around, little car.
Whee! Whee! Whee!
The music would get louder and louder and louder and you'd feel like you have a cold.
I would be a little more
That was our night, dear friends, at the Bob Larson Ministries.
Divival, actually.
We went to a Bob Larson revival.
I taped it.
Couldn't get hardly any kind of a decent tape off of it.
But, I did get to be on his show and here it is.
That turning point to the daily in-depth study of God's word.
We are quickly lining up.
We want to see you.
We want to help you.
And I want you not to miss Dallas tomorrow night.
Please put it on your calendar.
Get there.
Be there.
It's going to be a night unlike any that city has ever seen.
And Dallas has seen some pretty strange things.
So don't miss it for anything.
And speaking of some pretty strange things,
before I get to the rest of you callers out there at 1-800-821-TALK,
we've got some publicity seekers out there.
They are a strange bunch.
Maybe someday we'll do a larger show on them.
But I wanted to talk to them briefly because some of them plan to be there tomorrow.
Yes, I am aware of them.
I have been sent their literature through the years
and have never really talked to one of these particular people.
But some of you may be aware of the Church of the Subgenius and their god, Bob.
At least they have good taste, tongue in cheek.
And I've got one of their representatives on the line with me right now,
direct from Dallas, Ivan Stang.
Ivan!
Bob!
Bob, at long last.
You are the current church leader of the Church of the Subgenius.
Well, I just work here, Bob.
I'm working for Mr. Dobbs.
Bob Dobbs.
Right, Bob Dobbs.
I'll tell you, I'm so glad to finally be on your show.
I've been listening for years.
Years?
Well, especially around Halloween.
I love your Halloween shows.
Now, how have I managed to fail by not getting through your thick head
after all these years to get you from Bob Dobbs?
To God.
Oh, you...
Bob, you have saved me so many times.
I have converted over to Christianity almost every time I ever listen to your show.
And then go back.
Well, we believe in the short-duration personal savior phenomenon.
Bob Dobbs himself considers himself a short-duration personal savior.
Now, come on.
Now, you people have really had 10,000 people ante up 30 bucks a piece
to join this Internet religion,
this religion of...
Of the quickie printer, tabloid-style, cigar-smoking, pipe-smoking God
who will come to Earth soon to take everybody away in pleasure saucers.
You've really gotten people to pay 30 bucks a piece?
Oh, yeah, absolutely.
And we've sold about 100,000 copies of our books.
Okay, so what...
I mean, we've been around for 20 years.
Now, in a nutshell, for the people out there who've never heard of this sort of thing before,
you are what?
Well, the church...
The church of the subgenius is a religion that Bob started
specifically to help the mutants, the misfits, the disbelievers,
and also those who would believe anything
in our fight against the conspiracy of the normal people.
And...
But you're definitely not normal.
Nobody's going to ever accuse you of that.
Well, in that respect, I think we probably have a lot in common, Bob.
All right, all right.
Touche.
You believe that the world is due for demolition,
on July the 5th, 1998, at 7 a.m.?
Praise Bob, that is correct.
52 days from now.
And if it doesn't happen?
What kind of a question is that?
I mean, if I...
You think we're going to end up looking ridiculous,
like those poor little religious nuts here in Garland,
right around the corner from me?
Remember the...
Oh, yes.
God's Salvation Church.
Yeah, the Taiwanese folks.
Yeah, they happen to just be very, very nearby.
Yeah.
I went over there and gave them my $30 just in case.
You know, we've been telling people to have faith in Bob.
I figure I might as well practice what I preached for once.
Now, you say it's...
In your literature, you say it's not too late to be saved.
All you have to do is send $30 to Bob.
And I want folks to understand, this is not Bob Larson.
This is Bob Dobbs, the God.
Oh, Bob...
Yeah, Bob Dobbs is probably a lot cheaper for salvation than you are, Bob.
And you get eternal salvation.
You get eternal salvation or triple your money back.
It's not a bad deal now, is it?
Well, how do you know if you don't get it to get your money back?
Well, I guess you'll have to cross that bridge when you come to it.
Now, some people...
Let me put it this way.
If you end up in hell as a result of investing $30 in Bob Dobbs' church,
he will meet you at the gates of hell with a check for $90
and a little booklet called How to Enjoy Hell for 5 Cents a Day.
It's $89.95, I think.
Now, other than...
And having a good laugh and creating something out of minds
that otherwise would be wasted on something probably even worse than this,
what are you people up to?
Well, basically, Bob, we've declared war on God.
And I know that that sounds...
I mean, that's kind of taken on a big job.
We've been pulling God's leg for a long time,
and that's a very large leg to pull.
It takes a lot of nerve, and you damn well better be funny if you're going to do it.
But we have gotten so sick and tired of this invisible monster
that everybody keeps talking about that is so weak and pathetic
that it has to be defended by illiterate little old ladies and rednecks
against jerks like me.
Now, what kind of a God is that?
We're just sick and tired of putting up with it.
This thing's been, you know, allowing starvation and hunger
and all this stuff all over the world.
We've just had enough.
It's been telling us for years we were going to go to hell.
What else could we do but start our own religion?
Are you guys going to be there tomorrow night?
Yeah, I wouldn't miss it for the world.
Now, we don't plan any kind of disruptions.
We're generally very polite folks.
Well, you're going to see God tomorrow night.
You're going to see God in action.
You're going to see the supernatural like you've never seen it before.
Then what?
Well, if I'm impressed, I'm sure I'll convert.
And put $30 in the offering.
There's a lot of chances.
And I've...
I've worshipped many, many gods and demons.
But, you know, I always end up coming back to old Bob Dobbs.
Now, there are people out there who probably think
you are some secret friend of mine that I just put up to this for comic relief.
I don't know.
You haven't met him.
You people contacted me this week and said,
oh, by the way, since Bob's coming to Dallas,
maybe he'd like to talk to us.
Oh, yeah.
Well, we happen to have been, you know,
because our end of the world is coming up very soon,
and kind of a big PR blitz.
And I'll tell you what, Bob,
it is a big relief for me to talk to somebody
with even the slightest bit of sense.
Because mostly I've been on the radio with
drive time rock, classic rock jocks,
which is the lowest form of life on earth.
And I'd much rather be talking to a fellow religious nut
than one of these normals, if you don't mind,
you know, present company excluded.
Yeah, yeah.
I have Richard on the line.
Richard, don't...
You called in a second ago to ask a question about this guy.
What's your question, Richard?
Yeah, I wanted to know if, basically,
if this kind of thing was serious.
Oh, friends.
Oh, man.
I forgot how funny all that stuff was.
This guy called in who...
He was actually the guy from the
alt.fan.bob-network.com.
And he was a member of the Bob Larson news group,
which is not really a Bob Larson fan club.
They actually kind of make fun of the guy and so forth.
And this anti-Bob Larson guy called up and said,
Reverend Stang, what are you doing on the air
with this adulterous radio preacher?
And I knew what he was talking about.
Bob Larson has had some problems in that respect,
much like our current acting president.
You know, some guys just have these organs.
I'm sorry, you know.
And I jumped in and said,
you must be talking about me.
I'm sure you're not talking about Bob Larson.
And the caller said, well, basically,
they're not talking about me.
They censored him.
And it was totally, completely removed
from all human reality.
Oh, but check out what...
Larson tuned in as he faded back in
after the censored out stuff.
He fades back in going,
well, you know, I've got a lot more nuts calling me
than you have in your whole religion.
And you know, friends, he's right.
And it's kind of a sad,
sad commentary, isn't it?
I've got more nutcases who listen to me
than follow you.
And we're not going to glorify
these idiots out there and jerks
who try to take advantage
of religious fanatics like you
to attack sane people like me.
But Ivan, I want to know,
in all seriousness,
how many people belong to your religion?
It's just you and a couple of buddies.
Where do you get the figure of 10,000?
No, Bob, quite seriously,
we have four books that have been published
by Simon & Schuster,
the first one being Book of the Subgenius.
It's still in print.
About 100,000 copies is sold.
I've printed, well, 60 or 70,000 copies
of our little pamphlet,
our equivalent of one of those chick comics.
And we have had at least 10,000 members sign up over...
I mean, we've been around for 15 years.
Bob predicted that there would be millions of them
and that we would have taken over the world by now,
but I think the conspiracy read Bob's prophecies, too,
and prophecy heeded is prophecy fulfilled.
And you are the sacred scribe of the church?
I'm the one...
I'm the guy who has to do a lot of the dirty work, yeah.
I assign the sacrifices and that kind of thing.
All right, well, I tell you what,
one of these days we're going to get you back
and talk a little longer.
I would suggest, however,
beware those little...
little old illiterate ladies,
as you referred to them a moment ago,
because there are some godly women of the Lord
who deeply resent what you just said,
and they are going to kick your spiritual butt
with the power of prayer
if you show up on Friday night,
so beware.
Those people that you denigrate
have got more spiritual power
and common eternal horse sense
in their little finger than you've got
in a lifetime of pursuing illicit religions.
And they're ready to take you on,
and they're ready to pray you into the kingdom.
So I say, prayer warriors, my friends in Dallas,
beware.
As you can see, it's going to be an interesting evening.
I got David on the line.
Hello, David, let's go from the ridiculous to the sublime.
David!
There are so many logical and thoroughly possible ways
in which the entire tribe of mankind
could be wiped off the earth at any moment.
Hey, hey, why don't you knock on that trap door there
and say, Yogg-Sothoth, three times.
Go ahead, do it, man.
Okay.
Yogg-Sothoth.
No, I'm not going to say it the third time,
because you know I won't get one out.
I didn't think I would do that.
That's right.
That's right, I know your tricks.
Last time I did that, I had bad luck for ten years.
Ten years, man.
That's what...
The old mean Mr. Tooth Decay.
That's right, and then ultimately that was because of your truth decay.
When one stops to think what a tiny little grain of sand
this haughty world of ours actually is in the dark sea of space,
the spectacle of man's inhumanity to man becomes a cosmic joke.
What's interesting to a dog?
To run, to hunt, with a pack, to kill.
Oh, master.
Dark and shriveled.
Shriveled like a disgusting, horrible, shriveled spider.
That rhyme gets better.
Hot and cold, and it flashes.
One minute connection.
When we were smaller than the spider, up the ladder,
we were worse.
Reverend Hal and myself crawling up the sides of the flowers,
looking out for spiders because they were bigger than we were.
You'll remember it differently from I did.
There were no flowers in this early time in our Earth's history.
They were like flowers to me in those days when I was so teeny.
They had broad leaves, but they were actually gigantic.
A burst of color up near the sky,
and a little color all alone out there in the cold.
That's a little color, not little color,
since most of everything was green and brown.
The color that we associate with flowers didn't arise until the Cretaceous period ended,
approximately 65 million years before the present era.
Then grasses and flowering plants,
made their appearance in the Cenozoic world.
The common bee, which appeared during the Cretaceous era,
managed to organize and pollinate the plants,
causing the flowering of the flowers.
The world was taken over by huge, gorgeous blossoms,
but the flowers of this early prehistoric time
were far more glorious in their first defaulting
than the decayed and senile blossoms and plants of today.
Yes?
Horrible horticultural facts.
Ah!
The eyeballs are their own flower,
like the eyeballs of a decaying mummy,
into the mysterious, infinite vagueness of the future.
Here we go now into the mysterious, vague future of yesterday,
the Rob Joes.
I'm Reverend Hal,
giving you a guide of how to find out about the future
when it happens to you.
Here we go!
Yes, we're hurtling into the future at 60 seconds per minute.
Wow.
A sh...
Now, a bigger jar.
Now, let's go over that again.
You say you saw some sort of future...
The little collar looks like a firefly, doesn't he?
As he glows inside the jar here.
Well, the reason he is, uh, highly glows that way,
it's a powerful sexual attractor
of the opposite species,
or the opposite sex, rather, of this little collar.
Yes, these little collars mate by eliminating the, uh,
the fluid which causes bioluminescence,
or the phenomenon of a little collar's hiney,
blinking in the dark.
Stop it.
Let's have that close-up now.
Wow!
Look at it!
It's scintillating!
There's some little collar's insect-like round eyes,
with which they could see the movement of the sun if they cared to.
Yeah, but they don't.
So we don't either.
They're prepared to spend their time burrowing through the muck.
...out of this jar.
Well, uh, forget it, fella.
We gave you some air holes.
Heh, heh, heh.
And a little flashlight.
And some food that'll last you,
the size of an insect,
over one month in your time.
Oh, hi.
Okay, there we go.
Even Bob Nelson's here to entertain you.
Good morning.
Oh, no, that old man's trying to kill us!
Bad show.
You're routed in here.
What?
All right, now, what's your beat, collar?
And we'll just play piano here.
I'd like to dedicate this next song to all of you,
who are out there listening to the show, and...
On the show.
...being with us tonight here.
It's spooky.
It's cootie.
It's almost six o'clock, but, uh...
It has all of those adjectives...
We still have a little fun and good cheer to go around.
...outside the fire.
We're still trying to find out where the fun and good cheer went.
And we're gonna see the night out with you, our audience.
That's right.
...is trying to get through to us.
Something is trying to communicate with the consciousness of mankind.
And he says it appears to be space aliens.
But Starbuck also points out, he says it's funny in almost every instance of the universe.
Now, people contacting UFOs, there's a heavy occult involvement as well.
These people have been involved in New Age techniques and therapies.
You say you can throw boot out the window and ash into wisdom and...
No, no, no, you don't.
Because these were way showers as they came by at a certain time or periods of our time
to show us the light back to God.
But what they're telling us, the space brothers, don't put too much of your energy in letting
somebody else show you the way.
You should be in direct contact with God since we are all part of that God creation.
And you think like Christ is just like somebody that is like showing us the way to this God?
Well, he was a way shower too.
His real name was Emmanuel.
Emmanuel?
Well, look at your Bible, Matthew 1, verse 22.
Right.
And if you have, depending on what version of the Bible that you have, verse 23 and 24
will tell you a different person gave him the name Jesus.
He was really named Jesus.
Right.
And he was named Jesus, which meant the anointed one by Saul of Tharsis 300 years after he left
the Middle East after he went through the crucifixion.
So you actually do prescribe to the Bible then?
No, I say parts of the Bible are correct, not all of it.
Okay, we're talking to George Green, some wild things tonight.
He's talking about UFO and much more than just UFOs and UFO sightings.
He's really got theories about how this whole world runs and he's making it run, the committee
of 300 and so on and so forth.
Okay, first of all, all right, this is the...
I'm a believer, all right?
Okay, first of all, I'm from Vancouver.
I was in Cypress Park last year.
I saw an alien crash land.
Were we on acid, Alex?
No, this is truth.
Truth, I'm telling you, all right?
We'll be right back.
It's the
You don't know
To you
It kind of makes you wonder
Don't it?
You don't know
To you
Who put the holes in the doors?
Who let the blood out of the vat?
That's mine, don't matter
Now you tell me what you say
Nothing on earth can hold you
Hold on all over your eyes
Master the art of illusion
Nothing can keep you inside
Who put the holes in the doors?
Who let the blood out of the vat?
That's mine, don't matter
Now you tell me what you say
Don't you know
And who I really am
Don't try it
He knows the tricks
Of the trade
You don't know
If he was truly
A friend of mine
When he said
I'll be back in his way
I'll be back someday
Uh, sad.
The tape runs out so suddenly there.
A beautiful song called, uh,
I don't know what it's called,
but it's from Cloaking Device,
Ultimate Klingons.
It's a song from the band,
Reverend Nancy Darnell,
there in Germany.
She's like the Grace Slick
of the Church of the Subgenius.
Uh, Ultimate Klingons.
Before that, some clips,
uh, Media Barrage clips
put together by Reverend Nick Nolan
about the Space Brothers.
A little bit more music by, uh,
uh,
Who was it that I ran?
Oh, John Bartles, yeah.
And John Bartles,
wonderful, uh,
uh, sort of cantankerous singer,
songwriter in, uh,
Springwater, New York,
I believe it is.
And, dear friends,
lots of KPFA Subgenius radio show,
uh, from the California radio show
with Dr. Howell and Puzzling Evidence.
Oh, I should mention that, uh,
some of the tapes that we're playing
in the background,
including the music that's in the background
right now is by Reverend Arnold Mathis.
I like, uh, Arnold Mathis stuff.
And some of that KPFA material, um,
and some other material we're playing tonight
is from the KPFA fan, uh,
Reverend Phineas Narco,
who did a compilation of the, uh,
sort of a best of the KPFA show,
which he sells.
And some of the recording quality
is kind of tinny
because it's a little bit more
it's been copied several times,
but I think Phineas Narco
has done a pretty good editing job,
really an excellent editing job
if you consider how difficult it is
to edit those guys' show.
Not like this show, of course.
This show's really, um,
and, what else?
Yeah, that's, uh, that's, uh, about it.
Now, I do have a whole nother
show's worth of tape
that I put together last night
that I could play, but I won't
because, uh, I think it's very important.
It's still near-court,
and it's Christmas now,
and some of you need,
well, you have to hear
Brain Rot Theater's
Rudolph Hitler tape.
Although I did want to mention one thing,
well, two things.
Number one, you're listening to
the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack,
the voice of the Church of the Subgenius
here in Dallas, Texas.
And we do have this show coming up,
a massive Subgenius revival,
or devival, as the case may be,
uh, New Year's,
New Year's night,
inaugurating the year 5BX.
And we had some listeners call
from Fort Worth who had a good idea,
a real good idea.
You know, we always do
short-duration mass marriages
at our revivals towards the end
so that those who aren't married
can, oh, do whatever sort of
guilty sex acts that they can think of
completely absolved
completely absolved.
And sanctified during that duration
of that short-duration marriage,
usually 24 hours.
Well, this couple in Fort Worth
suggested that we ought to do
a mass short-duration divorce first
because several people,
them, for instance,
are already married.
But they want to go fornicate
with other people that New Year's night
at the Subgenius show
at Club No.
And, uh, they don't feel like they can
unless they have a short-duration divorce first.
Which, of course,
will only last as long as those
short-duration marriages will, too.
So they're going to be looking
for other people to marry, friend.
And, uh, if that serves as
any sort of inducement,
I'm glad because
I have a feeling
we've been getting call after call
from young folks going,
come on, it's not really
only 21 and over, is it?
I'm afraid it is.
They serve drugs at this club,
Club No, alcohol.
The, well, it's probably
the strongest thing
that's drugged.
Next to crack.
I'm sure crack will be legalized next.
They'll never, ever get around to
froth because the froth users
just aren't that desperate, you know?
Uh,
so,
so, friends,
really, uh,
if you were thinking, well,
it's going to be too crowded down there.
I don't want to go down there on New Year's.
It's going to be too crowded.
I have a feeling it's not going to be too crowded.
Okay?
Uh, and not only that,
it's, uh,
well, we need, we need the support.
We need the show of support, dear friends.
Anyway, enough of that.
Once again, you are listening
to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
If you need
more information on the Church of the Subgenius
for free, just for free,
go ahead.
See, let me put a challenge to you.
See if you can not only write that postcard
but address it and put a stamp on it
and get it into the mail.
I'm amazed how few people
are even able to do that much
for such a wonderful,
giant pack.
Well, actually, it's a pretty pathetic pack
of free information, but it tells you
how to get a really good pack
for almost free information.
Write to Bob,
just Bob, or Hour of Slack,
or Subgenius. The post office knows
all our names at
postofficebox
181-417
Cleveland Heights.
Ohio 44118.
I'll give that number again.
That's Bob's.
181-417
Cleveland Heights.
Ohio 44118.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
Hey, friends, we're also coming up on
Hour of Slack number
1000. And for that show,
I thought we'd do a comments from
listeners special.
So, think about it and send
me a tight door recording.
I'll see you next time.
A minute of audio about
the Hour of Slack that we can
play on Hour of Slack number 1000.
Email stang
at subgenius.com
or use our Cleveland
post office box
181-417
at Cleveland Heights, Ohio
or see
subgenius.com
You could also phone it in
to our
toll-free number
1-888-669-2323.
That's
It does
not make good recordings,
so speak clearly.
Friends, this is the Amino
Acids playing in the background,
and they will be playing at the
D5L in Detroit
on March 19th
at the Magic Stick.
Along with
Matt and the
LSDudes
and yours truly
and Reverend Carter LeBlanc
on May 7th
outside Austin at a strange
wickabilly campground
Tex Day.
And then July 5th, of course,
X Day at Brushwood
in far western New York and a new one
August
17th through 21st.
We'll see you at Cytopia.
In Jamaica.
Praise Bob.
I got
two legs laying and
three sparks of spring as my brain
sploomed out into the
abacron nova somewhere in the middle of the
signal.
I got
one of those little red race cars
that have a big head
and a tail on the back
and a little
you know,
a little
generator, I mean a little
microbiota generator.
And I got
I had the
hippopotamus removed and sent to me
from a friend of mine
who's working in Kenya
and had a reserve there.
And he said, what the hell?
These things are not in danger, so why not just
go in there?
Take a big chainsaw and lop off one of the
feet, send it to old Lonesome Cowboy Dave back to Kenya.
But if you're still trying to act like a
human, you're like 4K and I'm smoking the snuff.
These are the world's
best.
The world's best.