Ah, the one that's not real.
That's the one you must listen to, darling.
Now, just come over here and sit on my lap.
But it doesn't really make noise.
I know my knee looks a little strange.
It only makes noise when I turn the pages or when I close it or open it.
I had a few additions made.
What now? What did you say?
It only makes noise when I open it or close it.
It doesn't make noise.
And, like, talk to me like I thought you meant when you said that.
Well, we'll try and close it and open it very gently.
Wrap it around your head and listen real carefully to the printed letters on that book.
The Bible is a beautiful story, but this book is even better.
Humans, on the other hand, don't have to.
We have a choice.
If you don't like your place in the world, you can get off anytime you want.
Suicide.
That's right.
If you don't like the way your life's going, you don't like the way you are in the world,
anything around you, you can check out anytime you like.
Animals aren't allowed that thought.
And believe me, if they were,
I would use it.
There'd be a lot of dogs and cats owned by assholes who live in high-rises diving out the windows.
Zebras, if they even had remotely that thought, would take a look at themselves and go,
what the fuck?
Black and white, the green and brown world.
Now, this blows.
I'm just going to jump in the river.
I don't have a thumb to work a gun or hold a knife.
Or even open up a jar of pills.
I'm just going to dive into the next lion's mouth.
Why even bother?
Now, monkeys have the opposable thumb, so they could kind of do it the exact same way we do.
Now, there's a bunch of people that say, oh, it's against the law.
Well, it's only against the law if you do a crappy job and you get caught.
Other people say, oh, we should save them.
Yeah, well, you know what?
Not everybody wants to be saved.
Not everybody should be saved.
And who are we to force our will upon them?
I mean, isn't that one of the joys about being a human?
Freedom of choice?
Now, it's not all bad.
Now, I'm not saying kill yourself.
But if you're going to be an idiot,
and do it anyway,
there's no sweat off of my back.
There's a lot of good that could come from it.
A little bit of bad thrown in.
Some of the things?
A job will open.
An apartment will become available.
There'll be more air for me.
They say there's two girls for every guy.
If you're a man, there'll be four chicks for me.
There'll be more cats.
The cattle won vodka for me.
There'll be one less idiot in line at the bank
who gets up to the window without their fucking slips filled out.
I won't ever have to go to the store
to buy my favorite salt and vinegar chips
and have the clerk point to you and say,
they bought the last bag.
You won't help change the McDonald's sign
to 100 billion served.
You'll never get AIDS.
You won't have to worry about calories ever.
No more, hey, does this make me look fat?
There'll be one less polluting human.
You won't have to recycle.
There'll be one less car on the road.
There'll be more ring things for me.
50 or so chickens' lives will be spared.
Your fingers won't ever get red from eating pistachios.
You won't be forced to visit your grandparents on Sundays anymore.
No more church.
You'll be saying, hey world, kiss my ass.
No more wet dreams about supermodels.
No more Barry Manilow.
For a few years, anyway.
Wondering, am I a loser?
Will be a thing of the past.
Say goodbye to crappy Xmas presents from aunts and uncles.
You won't have to suffer through a motley crew reunion.
Fuck flossing and brushing.
You'll never lose sleep over a pregnancy scare.
Adios, acne.
Worrying whether you fit in or not won't be on your brain.
Adios.
See you later, homework.
You'll never have to sit through another movie brought to you by the creators of South Park.
School's out forever.
No more paying bills.
You won't have to do chores.
You won't be able to run over toads with a lawnmower, though.
You'll also miss McDonald's french fries.
Bugs Bunny.
The amazing electrifying feeling that surges through your body when you kiss someone for the first time.
You won't be able to watch the letterbox director's cut of Jaws.
Candy.
Living above ground.
Pudding crust.
You'll miss the rush of getting your first apartment.
Getting to the point in your life where you can tell your parents to fuck off.
I gotta make my own mistakes.
You did.
You'll miss sex.
You'll miss thinking about it, looking for it.
Sex by yourself.
Sex with a partner.
Sex with multiple partners.
No more summer nights that seem to go on forever.
Rollercoasters.
Naming your kid the name you always wanted.
Making a difference in the world.
You'll miss the experience and pleasure of hallucinations.
Watching your neighbor's wife change clothes with her blinds open.
A lifetime of masturbating.
Watching your favorite team sweep the series.
Music.
You will definitely miss music.
Trying to sneak into your house drunk three hours past your curfew.
You'll miss the blazing glory of the Fourth of July fireworks.
The taste of Captain Crunch.
If you're a boy, you'll miss the feeling the first time you reach up a girl's shirt.
If you're a girl, the feeling the first time you reach down a boy's pants.
You'll miss your favorite coat.
Waffles with whipped cream and strawberries.
Beating your friends' asses.
At video games.
You won't be around to see what shape and color the new marshmallow and Lucky Charms will be.
You'll miss the feeling you'll get when reminiscing about your first love 30 years after the fact.
The joy of giving and receiving at Christmas.
Skinny dipping.
Getting stoned.
Reading Green Eggs and Ham.
And eating like a horse that got loose in the grain bin.
Flying cars.
Hey, you were born.
Finish what was started.
The guy who slagged the football team.
Those jobs were not for him.
He turns into a real estate agent who believes in discipline.
The guy who's first to use cocaine.
The wild boy breaking free.
He'll end up in a corner lawn as a prosecuting QC.
Remember the school captain?
Success was a matter of time.
I can hear her now as she screams,
Greg, you missed the stop sign.
Forget Snoop Doggy Dog.
Forget Old Ice-T.
The true world out on the streets is produced by the DAC.
What's the use of striving?
Life's road in front unravels.
We get to do the driving.
Don't choose the direction we travel.
Do your homework and wait for weeks.
Completely the damn, not lying.
It don't matter much when you hear that scream.
Greg, you missed the stop sign.
Greg, the stop sign.
Sometime in the next 10,000 years,
a comet's gonna wipe out old Tracer Manor.
Banking on it, coming before my end of year exams.
The rich kid becomes a junkie.
The poor kid an advertiser.
What a tragic waste of potential.
Being a junkie's not so good either.
Your folks weren't down for what you got.
You were the fruit of their vibe.
Who cares what you sow and what you reap?
It's Greg, you missed the stop sign.
Just staying humble.
Who cares what you sow and what you reap?
Don't
And
But
That was an easy unreasonable honk.
Just the other day
Man, could that baby run?
But you know what they always say
There's always a better one
Got a tumor in my brain
It's creeping to my lungs
And I'm searched around in vain
Can't find me a better one
I'm lying into everyone's head
It's the best they're gonna be
Growing up's not a matter of choice
It's a matter of wait and see
So kids, yeah, you can do it
You can be your best
Girls can do anything
You can pass the test
I'm okay, you're okay
We're okay, we're fine
I thought I heard a semi-trailer
Playing your business, stop fighting
Break the stock soon
Thank you.
The thousandth and tenth day of the human totem pole.
The morning was December gray of the thousandth and tenth day of the human totem pole.
The man at the bottom was smiling.
He had just finished his breakfast smiling.
It hadn't rained or manured for over two hours.
The man at the top was starving.
The pole was a horrible looking thing.
With all of those eyes and ears and waving hands for balance.
There was no way to get a copter in close.
So everybody was starving together.
The man at the top had long ago given up.
But didn't have nerve enough to climb down.
At night the pole would talk to itself.
And the chatter wasn't too good.
Obviously the pole didn't like itself.
It wanted to walk.
It was the summer and it was hot.
And balance wouldn't permit a skinning to undergarments.
It was an integrated pole.
It was taking on a reddish brown.
It was a little bit of a
It was a gurgling and googling herd.
A tenth of the way up the pole.
Approaching was a small child with Statue of Liberty doll.
And a little more than that.
Crouching tall.
Astounding! Captain Beefheart there and the Magic Band.
The 1010th day of the human totem pole from the album Ice Cream for Crow.
Before that, friends, that song Greg the Stop Sign is by a British group called This Is Serious Mum.
That's the name of the group, This Is Serious Mum.
And you can get more information about them from www.tism.
That's short for This Is Serious Mum.
www.tism.com
www.wanker.com
www.tism.wanker.com
And friends, before that, that incredible song about suicide and why and why not
is by a comedian named Bobby Gaylord.
Dr. Lagune sent me a copy of that.
It's from an album called Fuzzatonic Scream.
And you can check out bobbygaylord.com
That's spelled G-A-Y-L-O-R.
Bobby Gaylord.
Just amazing.
And it helps set the theme of anti-slack as it is taken away from us.
And somehow it always returns back to slack.
Friends, yes, slack.
And for more slack, we're going to go back in time to the old subgenius media barrage number 11.
Once a tape, and now a CD.
We're remastering it.
Made from tapes created in the early 1980s.
And friends, after that, I don't know what we're going to play.
I ain't going to make any decisions right now.
This music by Tipsy in the background from their album Uh-Oh.
It just makes me want to slack off.
I'm going to duck the responsibility.
Dear friends.
As Aleister Crowley once said, if I can't be God, I'm not going to play.
This ain't no video game church.
It ain't no church of bingo.
It's a church of Bob.
It's a Bob Rice's church.
I don't see what the hell's going on here.
What the hell?
Did you know that heaven, Christian heaven is hotter than the Christian hell?
Yes, the Christian heaven is hotter.
That's because there are seven sons.
That's genius hell is fun.
Oh yeah, all your friends will be down there.
No.
There's seven sons.
There's seven sons around the Christian hell.
This is true.
You can find it in their own Bible.
They admit it.
And seven sons would make it much hotter than the gaseous molten threshold of brimstone.
That means that heaven is hotter than hell.
They've been lying to you all this time.
Well, that ain't the only thing they lie about, friends.
They lie that the world isn't coming to an end right away in 15 years.
Of course it's coming to an end in 15 years.
It can't last any longer.
It wasn't built to last.
It wasn't meant to last.
It's inferior.
It's a Spartan universe.
The cultists say it's a Spartan universe.
It's full of superstition and mysticism.
We're scientists.
The way that we want is what we become.
So please pay attention while I show you some of what's about to happen.
So play your cards right.
And now, here are my predictions.
Listen.
Listen carefully.
Join me in knowing the headlines of tomorrow today.
I predict public executions will be shown on television sponsored by your local Gatwick.
I predict the future will be filled with good things for you and yours.
I've got to believe.
Two months ago, the observatory issued a press statement that the world was coming to an end.
Now, that's the same story the cult of the Book of Revelations had been preaching.
Now, when a scientist backs that up, it's news.
Our conclusions have nothing to do with the cult.
Well, today we deal with Bible prophecy.
But the Word of God tells us we can expect nothing but trouble and trouble.
And we can expect nothing but turmoil in the Middle East until our Lord returns to be the Prince of Peace.
Bob?
It's been known for some time that the fossil record contains several very pronounced mass extinctions,
when large numbers of quite unrelated species from all kinds of habitats appear to die out during a relatively short period.
You have, say, an asteroid about 10 kilometers across impacting on the Earth at a speed of about 40 kilometers a second.
Did you hear what he was saying?
Is it possible that the end of the world will come in July 1999?
Perhaps in the form of an atomic holocaust?
Such a forewarning of ultimate doom could generally be dismissed out of hand.
The White House will confirm an order to use the atom bomb.
And our first target will be the initial landing place outside Los Angeles.
Those missiles have all gone off.
They pushed all the buttons!
You know what that means, don't you?
Either we fired first and they're gonna try to hit what's left,
or they fired first and we just got our missiles out of the ground in time.
Either way, we're gonna get hit.
So what are we still standing around here for?
Of course, since all human life has been under the surface of Earth for 16 years,
there was no actual loss of life in the sense we know it.
What you say you're what you get?
What the hell do you expect?
Richie Redrose.
White puppy noses.
Mammoth proper hoses is more like it!
Oh!
The strange worshippers pull at their faces.
Despite himself, a strangled cry escapes Brent,
as he sees the ghastly heritage of atomic radiation.
Hey, Tony, let's have some.
Get me outta here!
I mean, hell, this turn, the other cheap thing could be carried a bit too far, you know.
I'm sorry.
Hey, neighbor, let me give you some advice.
The Russians are about to pulverize us if I sleep tonight.
That is, if the crazy Arabs on the right don't get us first,
and the fire will rain down from the sky, the fire will rain down from the sky.
People die, people die, people die, people die.
The gurgle of a death rattle.
The awful heat.
And I couldn't see.
The smell.
The terrible rotten smell of burning flesh.
Help me, please.
Here comes Bob!
Yeah!
Get him, Bob, you son of a bitch!
We've got nothing left!
Why did we come all this way?
But the trouble is that all this knowledge I've got hold of is useless.
We're going to come back in just a moment.
We're going to have some strong comments about this, and we're going to continue with this.
It's no wonder one group of kids said we're the generation that's been born under the mushroom cloud.
Ah, here on the subgenius death ship, we approach San Francisco.
Our mission? Destroy anything.
Somebody help. Help me, please.
Has this ever happened to you?
Meltdown.
Please remove all humans from container area six.
Be really...
Doug, pull over! We've got to scrape the collar off the front of the show!
If we have another collar...
The show could overheat.
If we get another collar on the front of this show smeared like that last one, we're going to be in severe heat damage.
Well, I don't think we should drive the show so fast.
Well, you're right.
It's just stupid to keep wasting fuel running over listeners like this.
There is no collar.
There never has been a collar.
Radio is all a tape.
All the collars are gone.
The show was just a tape.
Yes.
Launching a probe into the...
This joke has been real.
Well, but they did survive, and they're willing to give us their wristwatches and most of their...
That's what I mean.
Imagine listening to this show and surviving.
Unfortunate. Yes, it was.
We do have some...
But the doctors were still here.
Good morning, tiny collar.
Don't drive any faster.
Yes, well, it would have been nice to hear your message, but at this hour, we're asking all messages.
Ten minutes left to...
Ten minutes.
Rotate your message toward the war and off the planet.
So aim high with us.
To find out more, all you have to do is speak with your nearest Air Force recruiter.
Ah, that's more like it.
We're all in the Air Force now.
We're all heading toward Grenada.
Los Angeles approach control.
No, no, wait.
We're over Los Angeles.
Don't drop the bomb now.
No, look at her.
It's too late.
.
Holy cow, that's LA Stadium down there.
Oh, this is awful.
What are we going to tell the newspapers?
I have no interest in anything but it's exploding bright.
They're congratulating us.
Look at that beautiful bomb pattern.
That's half the Olympics taken out in one final sweep of some genius terrorist.
I'd say that was one of the most beautiful patterns I've seen in the performance so far.
I think that'll get a nine for most of the judges, don't you?
Down there on the floor.
That was a flawless performance on that 9th explosion.
The Olympic nuclear explosion competition has been...
It's been a fierce and competitive one with some unexpected contributors.
Yes, the LA Olympics this year.
In smaller countries.
But this is...
I'm glad I got my tickets there.
You know what?
I've even bought a spare ticket for my Cabbage Patch doll.
Well, I hope you left that Cabbage Patch doll at the door.
The baby's back.
There's no place in the future.
Because you know they said some of them have a mind of their own.
The makes of the rich have packed back.
But silence did not follow.
The awful heat.
.
I'm sorry, but you see, it is my curse to tell the absolute truth.
Darkness and despair, gloom, chaos, anarchy.
A hopeless culture, self-indulgent, into evil perverseness.
It's like Jones told me that one time.
He said, if you can't X that tractor out of your ass,
you don't ever get to heaven.
Oh, darkness, gloom, destruction, despair, poverty, and other bad shit.
I fall like a dead man from the canyons of my mind.
In the canyons of your mind.
They're like those wagon wheel wraps on the bottom of the canyon in your mind.
They're like those tiny little turd things
in the bottom of the rocks in the canyons of your mind.
Now these aren't just little valleys.
They're not just little grooves or ditches in the earth.
No, no, no, no.
But they're canyons!
Mighty sized deep wide canyons.
Ah yes, the swingin' love corpses with that lovely lilting tune.
Canyons of my mind.
Or I should say falling like a dead man through the canyons of my mind.
The swingin' love corpses.
And before that, KPFA Berkeley radio with Palmer Vreede's Gary the Brogue friend and Puzzling Evidence Doug Wellman with Glass Madness singing.
And all of that friends and the collage material before that was all from the old subgenius Media Barrage number 11.
Edited by yours truly with Saint Byron Werner and Doug Wellman.
Puzzling Evidence friends.
There was also a lot of Devo and Oingo Boingo clips in there cause it was the 80s.
Now it's the 80s.
And as the old pass on and pass out in the fields of Asgard, the uppity youngsters come along.
Such as Reverend Alex Thompson, age 14.
In fact, we're going to listen to Reverend Thompson's first sermon.
In public anyway.
Recorded live at the 4X Day Drill 2001.
And after that we'll hear a nice piece of Connie from Reverend Protectrix Amazonia.
But now friends, Reverend Alex Thompson, age 14.
Whenever I introduce an unsaved friend to the church of the subgenius, they'll read the pamphlet number one.
And they'll read the pamphlet number two.
And they'll read through the long, long paragraphs of confusing and arcane text typed up by Stang and Drummond so, so very long ago.
Oh, they'll read through it as they'll say, ah, this is what it is.
This is what it is.
This is so bizarre and off the wall.
But what about Bob?
What about him?
He looks just about as strange.
What about his ward cleaver?
He looks like your ordinary, everyday dad, dad man, father image.
He's got the way about him.
But you know, and they get this image in their heads of the pipe-smoking businessman in the three-piece suit chatting up Jesus or the devil or whoever.
The most important thing to remember about the image of Bob has always been that no matter what,
no matter where you go, when you see a dog's head, you know what it stands for.
It's simply him, a man smiling and smoking a pipe.
A pipe filled with the uncut word of himself.
A pipe filled with his holy f-
A pipe so filled with the word of Bob.
And that's what we mortals are only now beginning to understand.
That's his image.
That's his way.
That's Bob.
Praise Bob.
And if no one else, then by all means turn to Connie because, you know, because let's not kid ourselves, guys.
She's the real power behind this church.
You know, she's the one we all know.
Hail, Connie!
Woo!
Ladies, gentlemen, fellow travelers, here ended the rant.
Good evening.
Yeah!
Woo!
Right, it's like Alex, friends.
Fourteen years old!
Woo!
Don't even think about it, girls.
That's jail time.
Yeah, the church of the subgenius is much older than that young man Jesus pointed out was born.
We're celebrating her 25th anniversary soon.
As long as it can be distinguished that man is man and woman is woman.
I think you're just a big bully.
I don't care if you like us because we don't like you and we don't give a flying what you think.
I thought you were trying to French kiss me.
You're better than I am.
Boys have a vagina.
Girls have a penis.
Man is woman and woman is man.
Guys, we're glimpsed at midwinter.
Humana, humana, humana.
A woman pretending to be a man pretending to be a woman?
Ridiculous.
It's preposterous.
In fact, it's so preposterous no one would ever believe it.
I find it very mind-bending.
There is going to be hell.
Medically impossible.
It's not really hard to believe.
It's just hard for you to accept.
Medically impossible.
Guards!
Pass grade hit.
Good heavens!
Ah!
You can hit me while I whip this out.
Guards!
Pass grade hit.
No!
This is not a haphazard maneuver.
Careful planning for it started months back.
Beware.
Beware of the big green dragon that sits on your doorstep.
He eats little boys.
Boys have a vagina.
By the way, Bob Hal transmission heads of the channel,inter imagen bubbles are well
clear Detroit TXTalk Radio is at theiretto basic.
I didn't say Bobby Gr混 at all.
Computer pup this is sawable.
Call Card!?
We are on a short break.
But he doesn't look dry tonight,so my friend André move on this time.
I was at the Safealtresonic东ig club.
I'm at a姐至 sorta the comedian with the breathe bar of Mobile One Beer.
horse sense, common sense, sense of humor, and most importantly of all, dollars and cents.
J.R. Dobbs, Bob Dobbs, J.R. Bob Dobbs was on the number one list of frauds and phonies for Time Magazine,
and I didn't know who he was.
And J.R. Bob Dobbs is the creator of the Church of the Subgenius.
This guy, the Reverend Ivan Stang, is one of their...
Disciples.
Disciples. Disciples. Yeah.
You know, it's funny. I don't think Jesus had a disciple named Dopey.
Poor Bob.
Oh, baby.
Life is grim, is it not?
It is grim. Yes, life is grim.
You drive through town and see the abandoned factories.
Yes, yes, yes.
The ice caps are melting.
We hate it.
The water's dry.
The world will soon be drowned.
Yes, yes, yes.
The plague is spreading.
Yes, yes. The booboos are on everyone, master.
All is lost.
Yes, yes, yes.
Barbarism and inhumanity reign in the street.
The children are lost souls.
Oh, my God.
Yes, yes, master.
The world is coming to an end.
Yes, master.
Yes, yes, master.
These are all signs of the end time.
Yes, yes, yes, master.
Yes, yes, yes.
Bob spoke of it before.
He wrote of it in the book.
Is your name writ in the book of the book?
Yes.
Yes, yes, sir.
Okay.
Your name's Mr. Blondie.
You're my master.
Yes, yes, sir.
Yes, sir.
Yes, I'm your master.
Oh, maybe he don't care about the end of the world, the end of freedom, the end
of the ability to think, freedom of thought.
Yes, my master.
My freedom.
My master.
They just want the law read to them.
I guess they like Johnny Law.
I guess they ain't going to send in that $30.
I guess they ain't going to play it.
But friend, what will you do when you're called up before the judge?
You know, you tied your shoes this morning, but will the undertaker untie them tonight?
And saw your feet off to fit you in that coffin because your family couldn't afford a big enough one?
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Oh, things are bleak.
Things are rough.
Sure, you can try to think positive.
That's just when they're going to come up behind you, sneak up on you.
They sneak up on you.
You know they're after you.
They're after you.
They wait for you.
They're not being paranoid.
They really are after you.
They're coming for you.
That means you better know who your friends are, buddy.
You better know where you go.
You're going to find Sukor, an aide, when the big hammer comes down.
You know what I mean.
Can't get it in the circle.
Who are you going to go to?
You're going to go to the cops?
You're going to go call 911?
Oh, yeah.
The earthquake's sucking you right down.
The giant volcano's going off in the middle of Kansas.
The mosquitoes the size of dinosaurs are sucking your blood.
You're going to call 911?
Oh, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
911.
You're going to know who your friends are and go to the man with the pipe.
You're going to call 669.
669.
911.
You call 669 and talk to the man with the pipe.
The pipe.
He might even offer you a light himself.
Hell.
Where's that pipe?
Lean back.
Big old...
Take a big old hit of that church there.
You know everything's going to be all right.
You get hanged off here.
Now, me, I don't hang down.
Or are you going to screw up?
Or are you just going to say, well, that was a real funny little skit.
But I'm...
Yeah, sure, I read in the newspaper that the child murderers are killing their mediocrity parents and putting them in jars.
Oh, yeah, I read that the ozone layer was almost completely gone.
And that's why me and all my...
My neighbors happen to seem to have cataracts.
I know that the electrical wiring in my home's giving me cancer.
But, you know, well, nothing's perfect.
You know, every cloud has a silver lining.
Tomorrow's another day.
What you know won't hurt you.
You know, Bob's not real.
I don't need slack.
I guess I'll just go down with the rest of them.
Yeah.
Yes, I guess so.
Me, me, Bob.
Me, no, you.
Me, me, me.
Look at these joyous little Morlocks below.
Sure, today the Morlocks are little friends.
Stunted.
Rather depressing looking as they are.
They love Bob.
They may be pathetic and sad.
But you know that in the future they will be the ones who run things.
Sure, the pinks may live in their mansions up above ground.
Being fed mysteriously every night somehow.
Fattened up.
And they never grow old.
Because when they turn 30 they're taken away by the Morlocks at night.
And fed to Morlocks families.
That is the destiny of the subgeniuses who are left behind on X-Day.
Yes, you may...
If you're left behind on X-Day your grandkids will get to be Morlocks.
Morlocks.
And feed off the Eloi.
But if you're truly saved, friend, you ain't gonna have to worry about that.
You're gonna have universal luxury on the escape vessels of the sex goddesses.
Universal luxury.
Oh boy.
Come on baby, come on baby.
Universal luxury.
Oh boy.
Come on baby, come on baby.
Universal luxury.
Shower me with universal luxury.
Once you find out
the circumstances
then you cannot go out.
Oh boy.
Oh yeah.
Once you find out
the circumstances
then you cannot go out.
Oh yeah.
Little girl, don't you know
That the stars up above are running all alone
Little girl, don't you know that they're blinking at you
Now the sun can sunburn you, but not as bad as the lost old people do
guitar solo
Little girl, don't you know that the stars up above are running all alone
Little girl, don't you know that they're blinking at you
Now the sun can sunburn you, but not as bad as the lost old people do
guitar solo
I want you, once you find out the circumstances
Then you, then you, then you, then you
Can go out, oh yeah, you can go out
Just want your old comfy slippers and the big fuzzy pillow
I've tried everything
Wild orgies
All kinds of drugs
Drugs, traveling the world
Booty coconut parties
Violence, torture
Wearing the ARF ARF mask
You know what I decided the best, what really counts
What really, when you really get down to it
Cream eggs
Five more minutes in bed
suite
All it's getting to be
Well, since my old baby left me
I found a new place to dwell
It's down at the end of Lonely Street
That's a heartbreak hotel
A baby so lonely, baby
A baby so lonely
Ah oh.
Baby, don't do aroad
I've been so lonely, baby
I could die
The bellboy's always crying
The lady's dressed in black
They've been so long, all along
This trip will never, never, never come back
I've been so lonely, baby
I've been so lonely
I could die
People talking all about
About the way you left me flat
I don't care what those people say
I know where that jive is at
But one thing I do have on my mind
And it terrifies me too
The way you call me another guy's name
When I try to find you
It's just more than what I've ever known
Loving you
Oh, oh, oh
You, and you seulah
If your baby leaves you
Got a tale to tell
Just take a walk down lonely street to
A heartbreak motel
I bet you're so lonely, baby
I bet you're so lonely
I could die
Heartbreaker
Hotel
Heartbreaker by Dred Zeppelin
And before that we heard
Circumstances by
Captain Beefheart and the Magic Band
from the album Clear Spot
Ah yes, and a little clip
of my life with the Thrill Kill
cult and a lot of
old old ESO
swamp radio
on WCSB Cleveland
with Chaz Smith
Lonesome Cowboy Dave
Special guest Princess We Are Doe
and yours truly from
February 1995
Reverend Chaz
Smith there providing the live
music but now
let us go even further
back before the
Morlocks and the Eloy and the
ESO to Berkeley
California
the KPFA radio station
back in the day before they changed
with Dr. Howell puzzling evidence
and glass
madness
I first
had my experience with Bob at
Bob's Big Boy on the corner of
Bellevue Drive in Los Angeles
California in 1959
It changed my life
and I became able to
open my third nostril and snort
the divine wisdom of the subgenius
Every morning before breakfast
I find it helpful to go into
my sternutition room
as we call them and sniff up
Yes, violent sternutition may be
named after the famous sternio
Well yes, the famous sternio does
practice sternutition as does everyone who
possesses the simple accoutrement of a
handkerchief and a head full of ideas
that need to be relieved
blasted out as it might be
Oh Bob with your square little
grey brain how do you use that
thing it's hooked up all wrong
Oh Bob what about this rumor that your pipe is a living
organism? Yes, that has invaded
your brain and made everything all wrong
Yeah what about that Bob grinning malarkey turkey
flunky prophet of the... What about them aliens
as you say or us aliens? We're not aliens
How about it Bob and who's this anti-Bob
some relation of yours some nepotistic cousin
on the payroll and... In a computer
field of nerds. We dare to question our
supreme epopt Bob because we
have the freedom within the church of the subgenius
to question even the basic verities
like whether or not there is a Mokele Mbembe
whether it's frog like bellow does
echo over the South American or even
the African swamps
Swamps? Swamps. Yes
Right now, Glass Madness
is in that swamp, yes he's gone down to the green hill
They say the Mokele Mbembe lives in Lake
Ukabalabonga which is only four feet deep
but the creature of a
considerate... Ukabalabonga
is coming right up
keep walking
buy the book of the subgenius
Up there it went
and here... Oh wait a minute
I think it's time for a commercial
Bob Dobbs he's no
slob Bob Dobbs he's
no fool
he is the head of the subgenius church
and that's why he's super cool
like Glassies Bob
Dobbs he's no slob
Bob Dobbs he's no fool
he is the head of the
subgenius church and he is
super cool
music
Glass
Madness friends from Media Barrage
11 and now it's
time for you to get your pencils
out and write down the address
of Bob so that you can
figure out what the hell this church of the subgenius
thing is all about and maybe get some free
weird little pamphlets with stuff printed on them
or you can just check out
www.subgenius.com
on the internet
but to cut that pencil ready friends
while this background music by
Tipsy from their album
Uh-Oh is playing
you can write down the address
of Hour of Slack at
P.O. Box
181-417
Cleveland Heights
Ohio 44118
www.subgenius.com
and here now
is little Theodore
and Babushka
then live at
the triple X day drill
in 1999
and after that friends we're gonna take some calls
Praise Bob
music
There's
only one
hope for me
music
I wanna be Bob
sit and smile all the time
think everything is just fine
don't wanna be Jesus
always look so sad
haha he must have had an
awful dad
I wanna be Bob
tell everyone about Slack
let the pigs kiss my crack
don't wanna be Jesus
don't wanna be no slave
he should have stayed in his grave
I wanna be Bob
never have to work a day
all eternity's a play
don't wanna be Jesus
don't wanna carry no cross
don't wanna speak for no haha boss
I wanna be Bob
see everything all so clear
shit eating red ear to ear
I wanna be Bob
don't wanna be Jesus
always trying to figure things out
who needs all them fucking
cosmic doubts
I wanna be Bob
yeah I wanna be Bob
I'd even like an
In-N-Out Jersey
music
maybe I could go over to
in the days when that was possible
goodwill and see if I could find me a nice pink suit coat
find you? what's with the reflection stuff here?
you're from Appalachia too and I mean you know find me this
I'm gonna get me that you know come on man watch out
I'm gonna get me some
find me this
I'm gonna get me one of them
I'm gonna get you one too
I feel like that I'm gonna get me one of them
I'm fam skip
go out there and get me one of them
I'm fitting to get me one
I'm gonna kill you
I'm ok
that is one of the most frightening words to any
yes hello
hello hello
how are you you're so beautiful
oh thank you
you sound like a soft spring breeze
it's because I haven't been showering too much
oh
you're just taking a shower I bet that your skin is still moist
and a little bit warm
mm hm
and the little evaporation of the vapors
can smell very well eh?
really?
oh my god my way my commandant
oh boy
perhaps the smell of lilacs and diseased ovaries
no no no
I'm using my third nostril
to whiff read your psychic stench
have you been watching the movie Sinbad the Sailor
and eating garlic popcorn
you had many important past lives
no
more work
you have had many important past lives
you are an old soul
you are a very old soul want some more soul?
well what did you call to ask about your old soul?
some more show
some more Dave
think of the fun you'll have taking Barbie and Ken on dates
we've already had all that fun
I actually
we're taking Barbie and Ken on dates
with Krabby and Barma?
no we've already executed them out in the ditches
way beyond Pannonia
you dress them up real pretty and put the caveman outfit on one of them
and sometimes a little skinny tie on the boy
and take them out on a little date
oh that would be my favorite
thing to do
that's always my favorite thing to do when I'm home
I like to take the caveman and take the
you know the necktie from the business suit guy
and strangle them all up
when you're home
when you're home or at the home
now when you're home or at the home
that's before you start burning them
I have to stay home lately
the home lately?
I have to stay home
a shut in
and what is your problem there dear sister
I have a busted up knee
what a beautiful bust
and money you say
busted up money and knee
I went to the bank and they said I didn't have any
it seemed to have hit the concrete
and been pushed to the side in every direction
that sounds beautiful
I would like to watch that in slow motion
so uh
would you be interested in
in joining the bonobo sect
um
what's in it for me
oh everything goes in
what's in it for you
yes everything going there
what's in it
or should I say what will be in me
what would you say rubs you the right way
the spirit
you will be filled
we'll fill you up
the spirit of slack
the spunk of some diseased mentally ill old gentleman
who believe the world is coming to an end
and in actuality
their own minds are coming to an abrupt halt
they'll join you soon in the town
one at a time
so David
there's a spunk of an old diseased man
Davey just closes his eyes and goes
he's there
it doesn't matter
yeah see that's why
that all sounds really really nice
it does
yeah
the spunk of an old diseased man
don't you get pleasure out of the most mundane things
I think the old diseased man Dave is referring to may be Dave
I was referring to you
I thought so.
I thought that...
I thought it was in there.
How's the mutated eunuch you're letting live in the basement?
I don't have a basement.
I don't know who you mean.
Well, then how the hell is a mutated eunuch living in your basement?
Till next week.
Keep your hat on tight.
You're sacking the saddle.
You're back to the wind.
You know all what else.
Hey, thanks for calling, Devangela.
Thanks for calling, Devangela.
Long cow, Dave, don't you know what they're doing to yourself?
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show,
and we're even more glad that some listeners have donated enough
to help us keep on going for another couple of months.
Not just this show, but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob and want some of that slack back to rebound to you,
you should go to...
subgenius.com front page, or especially the radio page,
or the catalog store pages,
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty,
and we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference,
even if it's only once a month from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that blowjobs could go the way of Steve Jobs
if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to...
Subgenius Foundation.
P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118
Thanks for anything you can do to help...
Let there be slack.