From PR News in Washington, I'm getting worse.
Doctors say they're basketball fans, and Michigan State battles with PR News.
Lawyers say Bob had little chance of winning.
Reverend Jesse Jackson climbed the side of the St. Peter's Dome before he killed nine people, then himself.
Authorities demanded Pope John Paul start a lottery to help brain-damaged PR News, Washington.
The Self-Genius Powerhouse.
What are they trying to prove, anyway?
Beats me.
Hello there, I'm George Putnam.
I'd like to begin with a fact.
A simple yet shocking fact.
It is this.
A flood tide of filth is engulfing our country in the form of newsstand obscenity.
It is threatening to pervert an entire generation of our...
American children.
We know that once a person is perverted,
it is practically impossible for that person to adjust to normal attitudes in regard to sex.
Yet, much of this material has been described as an illustrated, detailed course in perversion.
I've been feeding off and
Foi-
Fem brothers.
The
By the time legs first became parallel,
let alone any part of me,
none of us knew how to carry.
And that crew,
was endangering all our troubles.
investigate stangs,
And here he is.
But not of an hour of slack.
Not even of a minute of slack.
Nay, but rather of Bob's Slack Time Funhouse from WREK Atlanta.
Actually, this is the Thanksgiving Subgenius Executive Banquet from the Pom Poms right here in downtown Berkeley.
And we aren't wherever he said at all.
This is in Berkeley.
And not this time won by the good reverend Susie the Floozy.
But a mental classic by her co-pod was the Lymph Node Institute.
Toot, toot, toot, toot, toot, toot, toot, toot, toot, toot, toot.
I'm Doc.
And?
I'm Bugsy.
We're going to discuss the brain this evening in the interest of the magic dancing giants above us.
It's funny because your brain will fill in gaps as needed, especially when you're receiving everything through your ear holes.
All of these can be prepared in the morning.
So if you hear any extra noises, it's just a...
It's always a help for the hostess on her own.
The subliminal dancing giant.
We're not really, as far as you know, hammering.
Anything into your brain.
It's for your benefit.
Let me get a visual here.
Yeah, Dobbs, this is...
You know who this is.
I'm going to get to the point.
I'm going to get to the point right now.
You and me.
A.M. P.M.
Market Street.
Be there.
Buy me a Frosty.
Maybe a hot dog or a Tquito.
We'll sell this right now.
We'll see who's doing some quote-unquote slacking, if you know what I mean.
What we want to do is...
Talk about what happened.
Sure.
November 22nd, 1963.
I'll tell you what happened.
That's when a good old Walter Three Toes Johnson came in and pitched a perfect game.
You know what I'm talking about.
Yes, I do.
Good.
Now let me get to the point once again.
Pizza Hut versus Domino's.
Go.
I'm sorry.
That's not the discussion of the year.
Yes, it is.
I was there.
Wait.
Yes.
Okay.
I'm a new caller.
I am a new caller.
He was here.
He was there.
Is Don Joyce there?
He has a very useful voice.
Not the prettiest sight.
Don?
The Nash Rambler's here.
Who's he?
Because he isn't, if you don't mind.
Okay.
Excuse me, Mr. Isn't.
Yes.
Question for you.
Go ahead.
I've heard some past shows.
I think you sound like a young man.
You're doing well.
Are you doing some kind of herbal supplement?
Yeah, I am a young man.
Don?
And he's pulling the eyepiece over the rearmost position.
Okay.
I'm a very young man.
Adjusting opticular resolution.
Are you trying to say some pedophilia stuff there?
He's not trying.
No, no.
I'm just out of high school.
Don.
You've got to be at least 62.
Let's just be honest here.
No.
I just graduated from high school.
Don.
Three, four years ago.
You sound like some sort of game show host, first of all.
As you know, traditionally, they usually range about 40 to 62.
All right.
Are these the types of callers you get on your show?
Yes, Mr. Dobbs.
Is this all there is?
We're ready to talk about the Kennedy assassination and the next day in the Church of the Sun.
Sorry.
You are incorrect.
Never in the history of the world have the merchants of obscenity, the teachers of unnatural
sexism...
...acted.
...had available to them the modern facilities for disseminating this filth.
And cheese.
And still more cheese.
High-speed presses, rapid transportation, mass distribution, all have combined to put
the vilest obscenity within reach of every man, woman, and child in the country.
And that fresh vegetable platter that looks like an artist's palate with its vigorous outdoor
color.
Your mixed salad.
So simple, apparently, but actually a combination of various shades of green and contrasting
textures.
Stuffing.
Yeah.
Cram the stuff real tight.
Together.
It's paradise.
It's delicious.
This is the legal ID for the subgenius Thanksgiving.
No!
No.
89.3.
And did you know that we're also...
We're also carried in Alaska and London, England.
Wow.
I didn't know that.
Right now.
Amazing.
Do we know those numbers?
I don't have them right on the tip of my desk here.
Of course we can be found all the time at kpfa.org.
It's her uncle.
So remember, you have a lot of people in Alaska and England who have never heard of this group,
this cult, this organization, this foundation, this church, whatever the preferred term is.
What?
You've never heard of it?
That's right.
So you're speaking to...
What planet are they from?
You are hardly preaching to the choir here.
You are preaching to the completely ignorant.
That makes no difference.
I think Reb Stang has got to...
Well, who are you going to take offense to there?
He's doing the spirit of...
All right.
Go ahead.
If the Holy Spirit is possessing Reb Stang, he has to try to tell the truth of that.
It's not a Holy Spirit at all.
It's nothing but the pressure from my flunads down below.
Well, the same thing.
It's my claim, crime, and urge that Bob Fried admits.
He said, Reverend Stang, take your pants off.
Go forth, stand on car hoods, and preach.
I didn't do it.
Yeah, have you not seen the tape of that on the Internet?
I remember him when he asked you that.
He said, you would be rich if you did that.
We put out an old video tape of Stang's pants leaving his body, and it's on the Internet.
It's been on there for like eight years.
Bob's been a good subgenius.
You know, subgenius was the second website ever.
You disobey Bob.
Oh, you do?
Yeah, he says slack off, so you go to work.
Before there were webs or sites or any of that stuff,
people that were beginning that process came to the subgenius church and said,
can we borrow the word?
Because there was so much of the word.
And they said, you can be the content or content.
And also, if you want, you have to beg for it,
but I'll tell you the story of why Bob gets shot in the movie Fight Club.
Oh, really?
Hyperimmunization, that's what we call it.
He was shot in 84 in the night of slack.
Yes, he was.
And Michael Pepe was there in a three-piece suit.
I was there.
And afterwards, the whole story was given to me under hypnosis
because I'm losing parts of that brain.
I think that's the kind of thing we only can talk about.
I'm just trying to sort out all these voices.
This college radio stuff is just nonsense.
Right now, Reverend Stans, you are covering all of northern and central California.
All of Arnold Schwarzenegger's breadbasket.
Hey, there's a red-headed girl here in Palais.
I don't even know about her.
I don't know about her.
Girl in Galeo?
Girls?
So has Reverend Funny Name called in yet?
Yes.
Her name is Kim.
The caller?
Is that the caller?
Where is Dr. Howell?
Her name's Kim.
I hate sitting next to her.
I have her off.
Has anyone stopped to think about J.R. Bob Dobbs
and to thank him and give thanks on this day of thanks that has just been given?
Too late now.
He's not listening now.
Well, actually, he might be.
So bend over and pray to Bob Dobbs.
Well, look.
And the caller has bent over.
So, Bob, bend over and pray.
And display him whatever it was that you have to give thanks.
The most private part, his wallet.
Say, Bob, thanks for you.
Hey, tell Kim to stay.
Thanks for being there, Bob.
And other insects.
Thanks for ignoring me, Bob.
Thanks for not torturing me as much as you could have.
And also, beautiful listening audience from over here.
What an amazing opportunity here to speak to the lowerarchy of the sub-genius church.
Think how great you have it compared to what it could be.
Kim, Kim, Kim, Kim.
And so...
I only worry that I know too much.
I should know less, actually.
Oh, yeah.
You wish you knew.
They all say...
They all think they know too much.
If I could only...
You don't know nothing!
I know.
I know that very well.
Oh, if only we could know anything, though.
That is the goal of every true world religion, is to truly know nothing.
That's why I keep it here.
Because then you can initiate something.
In fact, you don't even need much.
Once you really know nothing, very little will get you off.
Yeah.
I try to know as little as possible.
Then every movie you haven't seen before, every book you haven't read before...
They're so good.
Everything is just...
Until you see what it is.
Yeah.
A number of doctors have worked there.
The scope slows down.
So try...
Even go out there and mess with that movie or that book.
Yeah.
Just...
If you can learn to get off on nothing, you've got it made!
That's right.
You don't have to go to the movies.
This is a picture of a major American...
problem.
An ugly sore eating away at the wall of the wall of the wall of the wall.
It's one of the commonest causes of death, pain, and unhappiness.
There's nothing too mysterious about it, really.
Work.
Such suffering needn't be.
As in this case of one man's fight, his fight against work.
What's the matter with you?
Why does a man act like this?
Boom!
Burn that day.
At the office?
Responsibility?
Boom!
Doesn't look good.
The gnawing, the burning.
Various drugs.
Acid.
What you think has no bearing whatever on your condition.
The acid's working nice.
Go deeper.
You've got to face up to reality.
So you vomit.
That irregular bulge there.
Problem from work.
Get the kind of food and medication that helps relax it and takes the bite out of the acid.
I'm talking about feelings, not thinking.
Not logic.
Emotions.
Now, wait a minute.
That still spells jerk to me and I don't like it.
Only a complete idiot would act that way.
A complete idiot.
I don't care about anything.
Don't ever let me forget that.
And I'm paying you for medicine, not a bunch of crazy theories.
Do something about it.
Does a man really have to buy love, pay cash for it, acting like a machine instead of a human being?
That's right.
Ball me.
Down, down, down.
Life can be worth living down at the office.
Yes, that's right.
How about it?
Are you crazy?
I'm going to die.
I have a name tag that I wear to my job at the mall
It says, hello, my name is Paul
We have a chain store called Hot Topic
Next to the place that sells cheese pretzels
They sell alternative wear
I wanna work there
Cause I'm a sucker
Sucker
Hopelessly suburban
So many fat ladies with their babies
And their hairstyles from the 80s
I have to kiss their asses
If I wanna keep my job
See the youngsters, just like gangsters
Answering their pagers
When their mommies call
Let's do some shopping, get there early
Go downstairs and get a slurpee
So much to do here
In my special world
Sucker
He's a big sucker, he's a big fat sucker
He's a big sucker, he's a real motherfucker
He's a big sucker
He's a big sucker, he's a big fat sucker
He's a big sucker, he's the real motherfucker
He's a big sucker, he's a real motherfucker
Where do you want to be today?
I don't care just as long as it comes on a plastic train
I cruise around in my Japanese car with my butterball girlfriend
And a 40 answer
I have a name tag that I wear to my job at the mall
It says hello, my name is Paul
The Bean Weevils did that song, friends, from their one album
called The Bean Weevils.
The Bean Weevils, see beanweevils.com
Which we bought from Bean, the CD that is,
when we saw his band in San Francisco at the Ask Dr. Howell show
at Café du Monde just before we did this five hour Thanksgiving
subgenius business banquet on the Over the Edge and Puzzling Evidence shows
on KPFA in Berkeley.
With Don Joyce of Negative Land and Doug Wellman, Puzzling Evidence,
mixing up us guests, Dr. Philo Drummond, the original Overman,
Pope Michael Pepe, Dr. Howell Robbins, Princess Wee Argo,
and the callers, and yours, truly Reverend Ivan Stang,
and that's mostly what this particular hour of slack
and several future ones will be.
Except for all of the remixed collage musical cut-ups
by Reverend Norell Preff,
which is most of the collages in this show
that are longer than 33 seconds.
And for the PR news,
and the collages shorter than or equal to 33 seconds,
which are mostly by Mr. Fernanda Ndele Mer.
Friends, the background music is by the Flyin' Ryan Brothers
from Blue Marble right now.
That's their CD.
That's Ryanetics.com.
Praise the guitar tech skills of Reverend Jimmy Ryan
and his brother, Johnny.
You don't need money.
Well, a little bit.
Well, you need to stay awake.
Send in the money to Bob.
J.R. Bob Dobbs, that is.
Not one of these false bobs.
There's a lot of false bobs running around.
False bobs.
As was predicted.
In Book of the Subjeans.
He said, didn't he?
He said, there shall come many like unto me.
But if they froppeth not,
and die.
That's what I was thinking.
And if they have not the verticulitis of me,
then there are false bobs.
And he said, kill him.
Because if it ain't,
if it ain't really Bob,
then they deserve to die.
Then he can't die.
Right.
But he was killed anyway.
He was killed for you.
He couldn't, yeah.
No, he was killed by.
He didn't die for you,
but he was killed for you.
By puzzling evidence.
Puzzling evidence killed him for you.
Yeah, I know.
He did it for you.
And yet you just walk about your daily life
just thinking, oh, well,
I'll just buy this stuff and work this job.
They don't stop and think,
puzzling evidence killed Bob for me.
Reverend Stang, when you think about that,
you cause yourself,
you cause yourself to black out.
So most people can't think of that.
We ask them not to think of that.
Certainly not right now.
It's too big.
At 1.15 in the morning.
It's too big for 1.15 in the morning.
It's too big for most people's hearts to take.
Or their minds.
It's too big for my mind.
I just shut it down.
It's like the whole universe.
It's such a huge idea of slack.
I mean, it just takes in,
it makes the rest of the world go,
the rest of the world seem like Bambi.
The rest of the world is Bambi.
A cute little doe.
A beautiful doe.
Compared to the,
a weird doe.
A weeeearrrr doe.
It's the abnormalities are corrupting.
Also, didn't Bob say,
let there be frop?
That was another thing.
Oh, wait a minute.
Reverend Stang, I'm going to take,
I'll have a frop Zip-de-lops.
Quick, run over there and grab,
I need some more of a sanctity.
Don't get your lips close to it.
Do it twice.
Okay.
Okay, Reverend Stang,
now you and I can talk at a more reasonable pace.
This is something I enjoy in the show.
The rhythms of the show always give you a better opportunity
to have more.
This show is great.
It's a really good show.
You want to hit a show, man.
Take it more.
More.
Yeah.
I'm going to have a frop.
I can't get enough.
This stuff is great.
You know, I got some new CD from Negative Lands.
I just want to talk about the church and JFK's murder.
Kennedy Day went right by and I hardly even noticed.
I was shooting at turkeys.
Weren't we all?
The thing is, when you start studying the documents,
you start to think about Bob's assassination.
It opens up such a huge can of worms.
The next thing you know, you're studying pornography and drugs and all kinds of terrible criminal activities.
I have for years asked that people not give a hoot about who killed Bob.
It just doesn't matter for us.
Get a life.
Move on.
What?
Bob's dead?
Nothing.
We all killed Bob.
Why not?
No.
Why?
After all, it was you and me.
That's it.
That's what Bob said.
Somebody said.
Let me please introduce myself.
So we were trying to tie in the 60s to Bob's death.
At least I was in my mind when I stood up too quickly there.
Nothing, of course, was done.
Princess We Are Doe is here in the studio tonight.
She is a descendant from her spaceship.
She is the queen of all the unidentified flying objects, which unfortunately doesn't
do us a whole lot of good.
We can't identify them.
And you must remember, comrade, proteins are weapons too.
Yes, comrade.
I must have taken that to Doc's office.
Must be suspicious.
Yeah, we will cover the pool of blood, but not right now.
Yeah, leave it uncovered.
Do you want to give a plug for your show?
Take that salty smell.
I'm going to give it to you.
You should give a plug for your show on your college station.
Well, the Subgenius radio ministry hour of Slack originates in the heads of the subgeniuses
and then makes its way on to several stations, all of them found at www.subgenius.com.
There are the one-eyed ogvorbis shows.
There are the miscarrying MP3 shows with the most amazing sound effects.
There are the millions of legs that run right up your pants leg and bite you.
Is that Slack?
Perhaps it could be for you.
We won't know until you try.
Now, will you?
Or are you chicken?
We've got you coming and going.
We assault you with so many contradictory messages that sooner or later, your brain
breaks open wide and you say, okay, just shut up.
That's how it worked in those days.
The insidious picture of the publication.
But the way they were going about it, it was a very, very long process.
I think the only way this show works is we have to walk up these spooky 13-step stairs.
I have to go check the tape.
The tape?
Really?
Violin and bird guitar.
What?
Well, uh, you fellas better go on up and get completely wasted.
Thanks, Dad.
Mm-hmm.
Come on, Wally.
Warren?
I don't think at all.
Mom and Dad.
Putting me down.
Because I must.
Well?
Mom and Dad.
Weirdos.
Podstock.
smokers, and speed freaks.
Phonies.
You don't understand.
Don't be weirdos.
We knew you were something aimless and unreal.
I wasn't.
Come back. Come back aimless and unreal.
I've tried many times.
My first dream split each other.
So that each may find his own thing.
And I didn't.
Well, where is this thing down?
Mother has remained behind me.
A second ago, she gently touched my thing.
Sex on the streets.
In every major city from coast to coast.
And get ready for a shock.
Planning to use.
Rotten, filthy, lascivious.
Junk.
Rock.
It's the beat.
Beat.
You can get beat.
Teenage girls.
Beep.
Jungle.
Bir Boler.
Stir erwem.
Brendan Belladio.
Bir boler.
Sex on the streets.
Norrell Preff, friends.
www.heavyconfetti.com
From PR News in Washington,
ongoing public with a terrorist threat to New York's subway system.
Economist expected labor because of labor.
It does suggest workers, even though those workers did not work.
Economist expected PR News.
On Wall Street 51022.
The House of Representatives has narrowly approved six new PR News in Washington.
The Warren Commission met.
They never even called.
So did you guys go do it?
Did you guys do what you had to do?
And so in 1965, Garrison was in Washington, D.C.
That's the way the show is sometimes, folks.
You have to do it by yourself.
You're sitting there listening,
and you're thinking,
these guys just don't do it for me.
I mean, these guys just talk and talk and talk.
That's all they do.
Who the hell cares?
It's like six, ten, eighteen guys talking.
Sometimes a female.
Well, and then, of course, the callers fly or the phones fly.
And he was left out in the Alaskan wilderness by himself
as his plane's motor failed.
And he said,
in this wonderful shot where the cameraman dropped his camera and shot up
and caught Alan Dulles with a six-floor window in the background saying,
you'll probably not know what happened here in your lifetime.
It was like a setup.
Yeah, the JFK thing's wonderful.
And now it's passed from history into myth.
There is no truth anymore.
There was once.
Something happened in that place.
But there's no sense looking for it now.
You're crazy out of your mind.
You don't know if anything is real.
Anything.
The reality of reality is not reality.
It's just too much.
What's real?
What's not?
When you stand out in Healy Plaza and there's Robert Grodin
selling his little books like, what does he sell?
Oh, like that one?
The one underneath the book is like Venus.
The one underneath there is like Robert Grodin.
The one underneath the book.
It costs nothing.
Big old table.
What is a coffee table?
Pictures of Bob.
Yeah.
And properly you would they create an order.
That's the first book of the century.
It's brought too many times.
Please.
We go on.
You're over from PR news in Washington.
I'm the strongest in South Asia in 100 years.
The Bush administration is releasing of its flu pandemic.
Workers who actually produce the vaccine would be hospitalized.
With the illness.
Former president Jimmy Carter says faulty Democrats circulated in the past year and a half.
About 1500 union machinists broke down early today.
Machinists in Los Angeles.
Tens of thousands of machinists trapped in the mountainous region of Los Angeles.
In fact, for PR news, I'm already in Los Angeles.
Thousands of machinists in Florida.
On Wall Street 610-635-58.
US military officials say at least
PR news died in Washington.
Now turn that thing on.
You can do this five hour show.
I'll tell you.
I knew Bob for what he was.
I knew the sub-demics for what they were.
I'm not repeating myself.
Then you are opposed to kidnapping the space man.
This one's closer but I don't know if it's that better.
No, we are only opposed to killing.
The headphones are universally bad.
And every other kind of debris.
You know, Bob's promise says that on July 5th, 1998, when that day finally comes,
that you, the sub-genius, will be given great power over the pinks and normals.
What will you choose to do with that power, friend?
Will you choose to just wantonly slay the normals?
Your old fifth grade teacher who embarrassed you that one time?
Are you going to kill her?
Are you going to torture her for years?
Or set up a robo-beast that will terrorize her crippled body forever?
Are you?
Friend, are you going to think twice and think how these creatures can be used?
Don't waste your slack on vengeance for years.
Are you renting out these sub-genius hideous creatures?
You know, the hideous creature depends on what your dreams are, my friend.
I'm not going to do that.
If you have hideous dreams, then that's what your creature will be like.
If you have purdy dreams, then you'll have that sex goddess or whatever it was that you had in mind.
So you better hope that you have pure thoughts.
Are you going to be asleep when next day suddenly comes upon you like a thief in the night or in the middle of your day?
It's November 22nd, 12, 20 in the afternoon.
Are you going to be ready?
Are you going to be thinking about some monster?
JFK, Mr. Trump.
The monster movie you saw.
And then forever you'll be trapped in the world of that monster movie or that bad commercial or that bad date you were on.
Instead, when you should have been at church, weren't you being mobbed?
Which, by the way, can happen in a bar.
Is that a one little mob sound guy?
Sounds like a one-man army.
That's that pull-my-finger guy.
Oh, that's the governor.
Oh, man, it's the pull-my-finger guy.
All right.
This week's great, hilarious, new, trendy.
Your comrade.
Pull-my-finger guy.
See if that makes any difference.
Okay, that one's over.
I was told maybe.
Next.
300,000 volts of electricity.
Get it all fooling around.
And give it up.
Living hell of another world.
The man in it.
Earth is always painting things.
Break it down.
Break down.
Burst into flame.
Come up.
Hit another jack.
And the fire starts to burn.
Freaky boys jamming.
Free me.
God.
Here come the funk.
Horrible monster.
Insolent, ungodly monster.
Is she ready?
Isn't he handsome?
It was all in your mind.
Let me out.
Let it go.
Must let it grow.
Only thus can the whole evil be destroyed.
Give me my toys.
Power.
Productive.
Programmed your brain.
We pump it up.
Release her.
Romantic, isn't it?
Shut up.
And sit down.
Skin.
Sublimated.
Take it outside.
Take your.
That was interesting.
Time to rock.
Wonderful.
You've got a spot.
Must learn to obey.
You.
You will like to make love to me.
Young and beautiful.
Norrell Preff.
From PR News in Washington, I'm beating cosmonaut Sergei Krikalev following the weekend's massive PR news.
In India, the Prime Minister says more than $110 in federal aid for victims in India, killing 30.
No.
President Bush caused hundreds of deaths.
He's, uh, and, uh...
The President will be on hand for today's reopening of PR News in Washington.
I believe that this nation should commit itself.
Wave on.
Shot and killed.
Enjoy the smell of tear gas.
Heavy.
Definitely heavy.
Anything with monosodium glutamate.
I can't talk and start making.
Tricky dicky.
I met the Kray twins once.
Compared to most successful politicians, and I've come across a few in my time,
they were rank amateurs.
I'll give you an aphorism.
Politics is legalized crime.
Or crime by consent.
Uh, you're dripping ice cream on your suit, sir.
Oh, yes, damn.
I've discovered I'm a psychopath.
Rubbish.
Caught with their pants down.
America means business.
Think about it.
When doors are opened and closed in the world today,
the orders come,
from Washington.
The watchman watches in vain,
unless the Lord guards the city.
It's attributed to St. Francis de Salle,
but of course it comes from Psalm 127.
Kindly meant, I'm sure.
An interesting quotation.
Kennedy put it into the speech he was going to deliver in Dallas
the day he was hit in the head by a bullet.
Half his brain blown across the street.
That's America.
Temptation Island.
Everybody has been burned before.
Plastic Assassin.
I'm not too fond of the Americans lately.
The Americans are like the ancient Romans.
They have exactly the same kind of bad,
bad taste.
They see nothing unethical in wishing to dominate the world.
Kennedy wanted to go to the moon
because he was an idealist.
Johnson wants to go because he's a vengeful bastard.
Why didn't somebody shoot that great big cow-punching Texan slob instead?
I've got a good face, a good bum, and that's it.
I work for the government.
I kill people.
I'm an assassin.
Come on.
Love my good love.
Yeah, come on.
I guess it just doesn't feel right.
Everybody can justify murder.
The other fellow's on the other side,
and the other fellow's holding a gun.
The other fellow's going to kill us if we don't kill him first.
I need to go to the bathroom.
Jerusalem, 1961.
The state of Israel put Adolf Eichmann on trial for war crimes.
He was convicted and executed.
I thought I can defend was actually a pretty good one.
I was obeying orders.
What are you people trying to do to me?
Who the hell are you people?
I knew perfectly well what the bomb was for.
It wasn't to finish the war.
The war was as good as over.
It was to keep the Russians in their corner.
To make sure the USA came out on top.
Everyone understood it.
J. Robert Oppenheimer especially.
Sheer arrogance.
Oh, my dear fellow.
Temptation Island.
I tried to find my own Nirvana by gazing at the constellations.
He's paranoid.
It's just very sad.
Norrell Preff, friends.
Speaking of the Kennedy assassination, friends,
the ultimate sacrifice can now be yours.
Actually, the book Ultimate Sacrifice by Lamar Waldron and Tom Hartman is out now.
And I have been waiting for this book for, well, I've known Lamar Waldron for about 17 years.
And that's how long he's been working on Ultimate Sacrifice.
It was finally published in hardback.
By Carol and Graff Publishers.
And you can find out all you need to know at a website called
UltimateSacrificeTheBook.com
One word.
Ultimate Sacrifice The Book.
Ultimate Sacrifice.
John and Robert Kennedy.
The plan for a coup in Cuba.
And the murder of JFK.
Friends, it's a whole different story.
It's a whole different look at the Kennedy assassination than what you may be used to.
I can't even begin to go into the depths of the research and all of that.
Because this is the hour of slack.
And the Kennedy assassination isn't slackful for everybody.
But I've been around it for a long time.
And this is, you know, if you're really seriously looking for answers,
I, you could, you,
you should definitely check out Ultimate Sacrifice.
The case is not closed.
But this one comes close.
Ultimate Sacrifice The Book.com
Uh, by the good Lamar Waldron and Thomas Hartman.
Praise God.
Wherever you are, however you are, this is the BBB.
The BBB News.
Today the US Senate have been torturing prisoners.
BBB News.
The United States has said that it's bad.
An Iraqi Deputy Interior Minister had been paralyzed by three people in Hunan Province.
Others had had their skin peeled off during the BBB.
The French Parliament has approved violent unrest in a number of French cities and towns.
The Interior Minister told Parliament that he was beaten and stabbed in the capital, Tunis.
The Tunisian government has denied that it was behind the organized United Nations attack on Wednesday.
China says it's producing more than 100 million doses of bird flu,
and is producing more than 14 billion human deaths from bird flu in a day.
The US government's announced it intends to take the grisly Interior Secretary, Gal Norton,
off its list of endangered secretaries.
hazardous
zu
Butts, butts, butts.
One of the last remaining uneaten helper monkeys.
Monkeys, monkeys.
The helper monkey's monkey.
Monkeys fly out of my butt.
Rabbit, each sprout.
Reminded me of some damn funding technicality.
That figures.
Community outreach bullfish.
So.
Bulltish.
What language was that in?
Friends and each other.
I was just too full of bulltish.
Bulltish?
Have you just had it with all the bulltish?
Can you feel?
You don't look bulltish.
I'm not bulltish.
Yes.
Sometimes I have to go through these guys and reverse the reverse cuss words
so that they'll be suitable for the internet X-rated version.
Innumerable.
Yeah, but nobody...
See, this show comes pre-cleaned.
Well, that's what I'm saying.
If you just talk about the bulltish,
you have to go through and reverse that tish sound
so as to make it suitable for the internet.
Are you saying you want to listen to John Tish?
No, no, no, no, no.
It's a reverse psychology is what I was trying to use and get some...
But out here in Dealey Plaza, the dew is forming.
It's six in the morning.
I began writing a biography...
Dealey Plaza?
I thought this was...
That's where we're shooting from today.
Oh, Dealey Playa.
Oh, you're right.
Oh, jeez.
I just...
In my mind, I...
Yeah, I know.
There are all these different crossovers of subgenius...
It really is.
My mind is not my mind.
No.
Oh, and look at the little minds dancing now.
Step to your left and move towards the black freestanding panel directly in front of you.
And they are looking in the little mind...
Right there, right in front of you.
They're using the mind mirror to see themselves dancing.
At or around the point.
And now up.
There we go.
Now they're just hitting the roof.
Oh!
Oh, that's got to hurt.
Low-hanging stalactites.
Too many thoughts about candy.
Now, more than ever...
Put your head down, Governor.
Your mind is...
It's a battleground.
And continue with the stills from a home movie taken by Dallas businessman Abraham Zekruder.
The invading armies of normalcy have already dug in on the beachhead of your desire for acceptance.
And before I was done, after the seven years of work on this project, now we're in our eighth year.
And secure with food pay.
I was doing my own investigation based on all the new documents.
As the president was shot.
I was standing across the street from Supreme.
Yes, you too can learn to edit without splicings.
Which is, not coincidentally, perilously close to your slack reserves.
Fabian, did you hear that?
Oh.
Bend over and empty out those slack reserves, kids.
Nope.
Bob's here!
Do you hear me?
Oh!
Ah!
Freeze, Bob!
Bob's here!
Ah!
Bob is the drug!
It's the Bob show, kids!
Fabian!
Bob!
Can you hear me over the microphone?
Bob.
They all ask whether you can hear them over the microphone, and you can't.
But you always say you can.
This is moral decay!
Yeah, sure, we can hear you.
Moral decay!
So, uh, then you'll chop this show up and play it on your show, huh?
Uh, well you'll get that meat, Bob.
Just like a chop shop.
Well there was ONE cut.
Oh well, bred, yeah...
MY dear friend and our great leader, Bob
My dear friend and our great leader, Bob
его
My dear friend and our great leader Bob
From PR News in Washington, I'm treating prisoners humanely.
This is just the first step in the development of inhumane treatment of prisoners.
They're expected to...
adhere to the president for quite some time. On Wall Street 610-514-624-1218, this is PR.
A white spokesman says today's attack on lawyers could imperil efforts to protect the U.S. from PR
news in Washington.
Wall? Honey, I've been thinking. Oh, June, you just don't do things like that.
Well, I don't think. Oh, June, just don't throw wet towels.
Oh, osteoporosis. Why wait? Why wait? Fortunately, bone loss can be osteoporosis.
Osteoporosis proven to help bone loss and fractures of the spine. Why wait?
Okay, and track 14. Now we're advancing into the Christmas part of the show.
Tubular bells. Yeah. Carry on, gentlemen. I have to take a pee.
Pee on. Pee on. I tried to quit peeing years ago.
I became a breatharian. You know, I must have tried 150 times, and it just always gets the best of me.
I always end up falling back, you know.
It doesn't make any sense. I just can't seem to stop.
Penis. It's like it's got this. He is such a peer.
It's got this hold on me. He pees every day.
It's got a mind of its own. Bob, can't you free me from peeing?
I suppose that could happen, but why would you want to?
Because, really, is that time not what's perhaps one of the most relaxing times you have during your pathetic, hairy day?
Oh, friend. Oh, working friend.
Just a moment of serenity.
I've had better.
From PR News in Washington, I'm to face charges of treason.
The White House's current chief economic advisor has agreed to acquire 21...
$1.5 billion in cash for about $63.08.
The federal agency says it has a huge annual financial report today.
Uganda's main opposition leader pledged he would be Alan Greenspan.
And will be guided solely by the political influences.
Greenspan gives Palestinians medical B.O. in Newark.
His arrest comes after more than three weeks in the job.
If convicted, Greenspan could face the PR penalty.
On Wall Street, 4217-2203.
12-6.
The Senate has rejected PR News in Washington.
March of premature babies.
But still, no one knows premature babies.
Let's find the premature baby together.
For information, visit prematurebabies.com.
Peace in the Pacific.
Oh, I'm freeing that from the internet.
I'm very sorry to die.
And then they stole that idea from the last action hero.
The whole thing went down the tube.
Oboe.
Fresno.
What's your decision?
Oboe.
This guy has been overcome by the mushrooms of Fresno.
Is that like the OEA guy?
Yeah.
Oboe.
This guy lives eight blocks from the guy that stole the lectern.
What?
Victor Cantu, that son of a...
That pink, pink conspiracy duke.
False subgenius.
Jackass!
Copyright 2005.
Poop.
Oh, shit.
Shit.
You're a fucking child.
Is there a good idea I can speak to him?
But...
Who's Bob?
Bob.
Hey, hey.
Bob is Phil in the black.
No, no, no.
Skip him down.
Who is Bob?
What is Bob?
Bob.
Who is Bob?
How about Frank?
Yes.
Is he there?
What's the answer to that question?
You'll be in extreme danger every minute.
And loving it.
That lady forgot the trigger for about one minute!
Okay.
Hey!
I saw that thing run up in your
That was me.
I'll never forget it.
Doc.
What you believe?
And once again, the authors of Mindscape and Grindhouse have triumphed over the authors of Evil and Run.
Norrell Preff, friends.
www.heavyconfetti.com
On PR News in Washington, I'm taking the pain-killing drug.
Germany's new foreign minister has been pounding Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice today
to improve relations between Germany and the United States.
Be quiet!
Federal prosecutors have wrapped up shopping.
This holiday season, President Bush will be shutting down South Dakota's state government
to try to build momentum for his PR news.
Mr. Bush says he wants temporary legal working status.
The president says Internet shopping may help reverse the gay culture in some American seminaries
and lead to an even greater PR news in Washington.
Here's a PR news program.
The PR Corporation created Congress more than 30 years ago.
The idea was Congress doles out money to PR radio stations.
PR's broadcasters.
The PR Corporation's
own
PR
and PR.
We are constantly confused.
PR, it's fun.
If it's not, it should be.
Crazy.
You can say that.
Guys are crazy.
And that guy in there is a
viral ass attack.
Hi.
How are you?
I see you outside the ship.
What's wrong?
I keep...
I could swear I hear the ghost of Michael Pepe.
It's just an illusion.
It's freaking me out.
Does that happen to everybody?
Yeah.
Exactly.
As the ship turns, as we leave the atmosphere,
you'll appear to see Michael Pepe near you.
That's gross.
I'm not coming...
Hello?
Is that what they call space puny?
I've heard of that.
Hey, hey, hold on.
Hold on.
Six seconds.
Hit my knee with a hammer.
The caller is feeling that right now, too.
I just got out of rehab.
I'm here.
I'm getting drunk.
No, there's no rehab, caller.
It simply has to wear off.
Caller, is that you?
Diesel, um...
I'm Carl.
No, that's not him.
I just want to...
Hey, caller, we thought you were the caller for a minute.
I am the caller.
Is that caller?
I just have an unusually good quality phone.
Where can people get information on this reference, dang?
It's a little bit of something just called Tom.
Of course, the subgenius website.
Subgenius.com.
Yeah, man.
I'm sitting here in Dobstown
waiting for the Kool-Aid to come.
Well, I'm sitting...
Here in Dobstown
waiting for the Kool-Aid to come.
Well, it's a little bit of resistance,
but you know the pamphlet will keep them deaf and dumb.
Dumb, dumb, dumb, dumb.
I'm sitting here...
You can see my long hair
and my Rastafari hair
whirring everywhere.
Is that Rastafari?
Yes.
Rastafari number five you're wearing?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I love that.
It's not the ganja weed.
Oh, it's Fropman.
And we have no need for all his squares.
Fropman.
Fropman, yeah.
Yeah, Smokey Frop.
So I'm putting up resistance,
but I know...
No, Bob Dobbs got no stairs.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Man, it's a hit.
I know it's a hit.
Yeah, it's a hit, man.
I'm sitting here in Dobstown
waiting for the Kool-Aid to come.
Waiting for the Kool-Aid to come.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's what I'm doing, man.
I'm sitting here in Dobstown
waiting for the Bob to come.
Where is the Bob now?
See the Bob now.
Putting up resistance,
but I know he's going to leave me
deaf and dumb.
Deaf and dumb.
That's right.
When the Bob comes,
he'll leave me deaf and dumb.
I feel so good all over.
Jimmy Cliff, don't hear us.
What we are doing.
To his song.
No, he won't give a shit, man.
He's with Bob smoking the ganja from.
Yeah, yeah, he must be smoking ganja.
With the Bob in the Learjet.
With the Bob in the Dobstown in the Learjet.
Yeah, with the Dobstown.
Oh, look, there's Werner Erhard over there.
Werner, Werner, how you doing?
Werner, yeah.
Look, it's Jimmy Swaggart.
He's over there with Bob.
Oh, Jimmy Swaggart.
There's Earl Roberts.
There's Ronald Reagan.
Look what we're doing with Bob.
G. Gordon Lee.
Omar Gaddafi.
Dancing.
Oh, my God, look at Tower of Duty.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, there's Walt Disney.
They were all just frozen when they came back.
That's right.
We should all have been here.
Here's the White House.
The Glass Madness did that song, friends, from 1980.
From PR News in Washington, I'm accused of helping PR.
President Bush has departed from the White House.
The U.S. military says Dick Cheney's tainted.
Bob admitted he struggled to figure out what was going on in his head.
Confused for a while.
On Wall Street 310-545-64.
Al-Qaeda in Iraq is accused of illegal PR news.
Washington.
I can see the monitor wherever it stands down the studio.
He's answering questions from the caller at this time.
Do you have an appetite for bone meal?
I have an appetite for donuts or beef jerky.
I like bacon.
Hi.
40 minutes.
Serve bacon.
Bacon pie.
I can see that.
Some sweet potato pie.
Man.
Just one of the greatest broadcasts in history lined up.
Bacon pie.
Mmm, bacon pie.
Man.
When was the last time you had a steaming bacon pie?
Last night.
But now, I'm fine.
Sweaty bacon.
Cucumber sticks.
Bacon Jesus pie.
Carrots sticks.
Well, if you won't let me go, I guess I'm going to go.
Fine.
Juicy old bacon Jesus pie.
Okay, please speak with us now.
Just like Ma used to make down.
Don't.
The old bag.
We're hearing you.
We hear everything.
It's just that we can't talk to everybody.
Reverend Stans made her hang up.
It's your fault.
Well, he's not paying attention.
Who?
What?
Never mind.
Go on with your diatribe.
Somebody said something about, yeah, I can't.
Don't.
It's just, I get this pep-sick with the bacon.
Is anybody listening?
Yes.
We had a delicate female caller trying to get through.
They're so rare.
So rare.
And we just ignored her, basically.
The good.
Oh, dear.
But then again, she probably wasn't.
You've got to speak up.
Maybe we, yeah.
And also, maybe we should just let Queen of UFOs speak to her when she comes back.
I don't think she was part of the cult.
And calls 8484425.
All the better.
There she is again.
Please do call back, dear.
I hope that.
But she's not part of the cult.
I would much rather speak to people who are not.
We'd like to have you.
Like me.
I don't want you.
People who are a part of the cult have already sent him.
That's singing to the choir, babe.
They're used up.
They're burned out.
They're all flashed.
Their little souls are inside these aluminum containers inside the rocket ship, ready to go.
You have to go to the children.
Well, actually, they're still in my basement.
I'm sorry.
We heard this before.
I was trying to make it sound a little more exciting.
Yeah, go ahead, please, and join us as we dance around the radio show floor.
From PR News in Washington, I'm developing nuclear weapons in a facility in Russia.
The White House has fired explosives at Congressman John Murtha after the Pennsylvania Democrats blew themselves up.
A U.S. commander says another two turds failed to break through a bag on Wall Street.
810-712-1222.
U.N. Secretary General Kofi Annan says.
This is PR.
Steve reports on the effort to fund preschool for all Democrats.
He's gathered a million billion proposed poor preschool programs.
President Bush says he supports Russia's proposal aimed at keeping Iran in Russia.
Today, directivist Rob Reiner, strapped with explosives, continues asking for more than $5 at two Shiite mosques in Cuba.
Human rights experts with the United Nations say they will not visit PR News in Russia.
Ugh, unbeliving the Democrats.
Put the dream börner before me.
Be careful, we'd all be killed.
We're not afraid if they built this newspaper.
I couldn't believe it, or not even breathe.
And 對不對õ JIM maleno?
We don't have the lineup that would be afraid of nothing.
Please ...