Well, you can't blame a girl for trying.
What's on the radio?
Oh, this radio's no joke.
Turn it on, see.
Thanks.
No, not that one, Ann.
That's my police radio.
I'm sorry.
That's what you're in.
Right.
The Self Genius Hour of Swag.
You're becoming a regular boy scout, aren't you?
Aren't you?
I can take care of myself.
Oh, I see.
What do you think, then?
Let me be perfectly clear here.
This is Over the Edge,
and also, simultaneously,
it is the Puzzling Evidence Show.
How can that be?
And we're going for five hours tonight,
right here on kpfa.org online,
where we can look on our monitors
and see where you're tuned in from.
There's no other stations.
If you're listening in Sweden,
we see that.
We see that someone is tuned in in Sweden.
We can see you.
Yeah.
We can see you under your clothes.
Britt Eklund.
If you're in Sweden, give us a call.
You know,
what was her name?
Bridget Thorntonsen?
That's correct.
That starred with...
Yes.
Yeah.
The famous model.
Are you saying that she could be me right now?
You've got the one that made the...
We can beam you right now.
...Singmar's wife.
And Christine Jorgensen.
Beautiful girl ever.
Welcome to Babylon.
Well, that was...
I guess...
You know, can you fill in our listeners
about this whole trial?
I mean, because this whole...
Jesus, these are two subgeni who are being...
whose reproductive rights are being trashed
and whose right to reproduce
their own mutated versions of the human race
are actually being prevented by the law
in the form of a judge, I believe, in Texas?
No.
New York.
New York judge.
Yes.
In New York.
In Texas, they said,
whatever you do,
don't take that child back to New York.
But Jesus and Magdalene
took the Christ child.
Yeah.
Bob, who's called Conbo, by the way.
Conbo is a cute little boy of about...
Conbo.
...eleven now.
You know, like Marjo.
Yeah.
Oh.
Judge Punch John.
Marion.
Marjo is named after Marion Joseph, right?
Yeah.
Conbo is Connie and Bob.
Anyway, Jesus and Magdalene...
The subgenius business managers at that time
had a custody problem going on with the child's father,
who was a pink human.
And at one point, the judge was shown photographs
of a typical X-Day drill celebration
in which Jesus and his wife were doing normal X-Day things.
And this shocked the judge so much
that he said that the mother was...
Unbelievable.
...not a fit mother
because she was a member of Church of the Subgenius
and gave custody of the child to the father,
who was basically a ne'er-do-well welfare cheat thief
in a trailer court.
And it wasn't even a double Y!
Unbelievable.
Yeah.
No.
It was an X-Y.
And the case made the news on the internet
and created quite a bit of buzz.
It made quite a bit of stir
and caused many people to buy memberships from the church.
Oh, good!
It made me quite rich.
So it was a helpful...
Oh, that's good.
However, they...
You're getting rich off me?
Yeah, that's good.
The good, kindly, well-educated, hardworking subgenius parents
still are not allowed to see their child
until the judge makes up his mind.
The first judge...
That's obscene.
The first judge was screwed up so bad...
Seriously, it's disgusting.
...he was refused...
He had to be...
He had to step down from the case.
Why?
Because he was such a jerk?
He was so stupid that he...
He recused himself.
So next time you're fired from a job, just say...
Just say, I've recused myself.
...I've recused myself because I was too emotionally tied to the job.
Well, the second guy should have done that.
Why?
Because...
Because he was a what?
He was such a Christian that he couldn't handle the idea of a cult sense of humor or a church
sense of humor?
Well, the images that threw him were the beautiful Magdalene with Jesus drawing a
heart on her privates in front of a crowd on the internet.
The other thing that bothered him was Jesus dressed in clown... in a Jesus suit with clown
face being beaten in a parody of that Mel Gibson movie, being beaten by naked women
with dildos.
Did you see a clown face?
It was a takeoff on the Passion of the Christ, which they thought was not bloody enough and
they decided to restage it.
Could there be a connection with the insane clown posse people?
No, just some of the photographs that were on subgenius.com.
Yeah.
This is...
Maybe it's just a juggalo.
Unbelievable.
Well...
What's unbelievable?
I think I can believe it.
No, it would hurt them.
Well, because, you know, I think that's what I'm saying.
In other words, because the judge...
I don't believe anything.
Does anybody talk about those...
Everything you know is true.
You'll see in a moment.
You should believe everything that I say.
Yeah, because what...
I don't know about stank, I mean, but...
No wrinkles for me.
They're happy.
That's pretty scary, though.
Subgeni, they can take your baby away.
I won't even say...
Don't let me jinx it.
Look, they don't take babies away from strippers.
You know, they...
They don't take babies away from performance artists.
Yeah, I know.
They don't take babies away from big channels.
Because they don't have...
They don't have any.
I don't believe that they won't let them have any.
They don't let them have any.
They turn the baby away from...
Yeah.
A guy has a job.
Jesus and Magdalene.
And he has a job, right?
Oh, yeah.
They both have three jobs.
They both...
They have three jobs.
They're college-educated subgeniuses who are responsible citizens and yet...
That's why they...
You know, normally, the courts just blindly give the kid to the mob.
But in this case, they blindly gave the kid to the Christian or the...
Yeah.
Absolutely abolished him.
Right.
The Christian deadbeat...
The deadbeat Christian dad...
Who was beating...
Garage band...
A dead horse instead of a live Jesus who was being beaten at X Day.
And the judge didn't think that was funny or...
Yeah.
Rather, we're not...
It's not that we're...
Yeah.
It's not that it's sick humor.
We're a reflection of the illness in society around us.
Exactly.
Of course.
I wonder if the judge was more...
I...
I'm just a reflection of everybody else's...
Failure.
Failure and neurosis at the moment.
Yeah.
We're not really totally screwed up.
We're a reflection of a screwed up society.
So, all people ever...
That's right.
Or, as we put it, officer, have you ever heard of Mad Magazine?
You're right, Tony.
Sure can.
That's how you really...
That's how the court case...
Is that what your lawyer said?
No.
That's how it should have started.
But they forgot that crucial line.
Oh...
I believe you.
Scotty, you round up the crew.
I wonder if...
Well, you know, they will never take away Philo's baby, wonderful baby, because Philo
has a job.
And so...
Good night, Phil.
A few salesmen for a large downtown department store...
He has a really good job.
I mean, not like Philo.
... reports each weekend is only two days off.
Why is it...
... to the office of the police...
Everyone in Iran is a subpoena.
... between immigrants from Middle East countries...
Everything was one-off, huh?
... and the government.
The president is the head of the subpoena.
Well, good morning, Miss Helvinger.
Oh, good morning, Southern Fighter.
Well, once more, I'm here to strike terrific terror into the hearts of criminals everywhere.
Bob, you're the best at that of anybody.
Hmm?
Oh, all right.
Stand up again, please.
Yes, sir.
And sing in unison.
I'm stinking.
Oh.
The president's a very driveled.
He is a very driveled man on the front.
It's not a very driveled man.
He's a man of irish background.
because it is partial, because it almost inevitably involves some kind of hatred.
You hate the people who don't share your fanaticism.
If you think you've got a mark on the book with a line of people because it says so somewhere,
I mean, that's not really fanaticism, it's just orthodox behavior.
That's what I told the judge that one time.
It still goes over time.
Northern States.
Don't look up there.
Where the hell are you opening the book?
People have done that.
They have jumped, they have just marched dutifully.
Without giving it a second thought.
Just behaving like they're on parade.
March.
With their eyes open, oblivious to what their next step will bring.
Oh, none for any of us.
We'll be able to live in water, heat, cold, you name the worst, and never again a wrinkle.
Cryogenic suspension.
Why don't you shut up for a second?
I'm not worried.
No, you don't have to.
If you'd say a few words, it'd be better.
Harry, I can't believe it.
I just can't believe it.
Then if it gets taken over by a man, it's a good thing.
If it gets taken over by economic considerations, say, like the Crusades, then fanaticism disappears and perhaps does no harm.
I must go to extermination before I am exterminated by this gangster, computer god, concocted and controlled, worst mongrel, organized crime, murdering, cooperating gangster communist government.
I hand you the secret to save the entire human race and the entire universe.
One dollar.
One dollar is nice.
Or even a manual typewriter to me.
For your only hope for evil.
Maybe we could promote fanatical non-achievement.
Well, I don't know.
I can't think of any good that the Crusades did.
The Crusades had, of course, two different streams in them.
A fanatical stream and an economic stream.
The economic thing was very strong indeed, but it wouldn't have worked without the fanaticism.
I'm not saying it's bad, but the huge economic chain données were very important for the
anti-cognition and anti-corruption quandaries that were spread.
Where would they be?
West Virginia, in West Virginia.
Convinced?
Wow.
As far as we like to say, one of a kind.
The end of this part of the album.
I understand. It's just as well you didn't.
Hey, wait till she stops rolling, Doc.
You're very excited, ain't you?
I'm afraid so. Even scientists get excited sometimes.
So, good day. Good day.
Hey.
Hey, where are you?
I'm over here.
No.
Okay.
Like, here we are.
Peter's Donuts.
Oh, take off.
We are.
Okay.
Thanks for blowing it.
It's three in the morning.
Whose donuts?
Peter's Donuts.
Here?
She's at the till now. She'll see us in a minute.
I've got some crickets and worms.
We feed our little ones.
By the sound ofzwang, take me to mermaid city,
where the more we wanna fly we'll learn to срав Terra at dawn.
Ooh, Billy.
À tous les trois avant vos enfants,
nous sommes bourgeois.
Anticons Areum!
The new psychology was at that time sweeping through us all.
We were all influenced.
We were all concerned about fantasy or wishful thinking.
I formed the resolution of always judging and acting with the greatest good sense.
The fanaticism provided the troops and the economic motive the generals, roughly speaking.
What part would you say that witchcraft had played in fanaticism?
Oh, witchcraft played a terrible, terrible part.
Especially from about 1450 to about 1600.
A little longer than 1600.
A quite terrible part.
There was a work called The Hammer of Female Malefactors,
which was written by an eminent ecclesiastic and inspired,
just mad profusion of witch hunts,
which the people themselves believed.
I think it's very like...
It's very likely that Joan of Arc believed she was a witch.
Certainly a great many people condemned as witches did believe they were witches.
And there was an enormous spread of cruelty.
Now millions of men, women and children will be entering this world of the elder shape
and experiencing for themselves one of the great miracles of our time.
Your
reagent-like colour of the eye.
That, Meh.
Well, while you're here, Nicky, we'd like to have you do a little vocalizing with me, duet-wise.
You feel up to it?
I do.
Okay, let's be away.
Here we go.
Oh, what a day.
Come marching in.
The outer shape we describe is the clothes we each wear.
Yes, you are.
Yes, I am.
Hey, don't you think you ought to wait for the rescue again?
I can't. I've got to see what's in there.
In backbaking, like, normally you eat a pound, right?
Okay.
So, in metric, the double is 2, and 30 is 32 kilos in backbaking.
Yeah.
Watch your head.
What if the speed limit is, like, 50 miles an hour?
Yeah.
Then what do you do, double it?
In a dollar is still closed.
Let's hope it'll open.
It will.
If we dare say most people believe...
We have to be ready.
I don't know.
That was our ring, wasn't it?
I don't know. I never paid no attention.
But only with two bottles.
Okay, go.
This is the beginning of our theme.
You know, a lot of those pills,
they're a fake.
You know something?
They give me a pain in my aches.
An invention of Doug McKenzie.
He used,
gave her a little pinch of snooze
and she sneezed her fat away.
She died.
No, she only tried it
and she lost ten pounds every day.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
For when she sneezed,
she shook like Yelly
that made the fat come off of her.
She used,
gave her a little pinch of snooze
and she,
and she sneezed her fat away.
Now, making some suggestions,
would her bed,
which is the best for me?
One night they were sitting on the sofa
with my Jenny.
That's the girl I go for.
Oh, she lay in my arms all ready to kiss
and they was all pocketed up for this.
But they didn't know when I was doing it.
She had snooze and she was chewing it.
I think that'd take you out.
Yeah.
No, that'd be taking you out.
Take him out.
Uh,
you could knock him off
or you could whack him.
Whack him.
This is the best song of all time.
This is,
this is,
this is
the girl of all time.
Hello, hello.
She wants to be bad.
If it's naughty to dance the men
Sleep each morning laughter dance
Then the end is the end
I wanna be bad
This is cute, and I must congratulate you,
uh, Artiste, on the cuteness of this.
Yep.
This august business meeting has been the cutest one
I've ever had the, uh, pleasure to...
It's the baby.
It really is.
Does it tarnish?
Does it, it doesn't tarnish our gravity though, does it?
It's the baby.
Yeah, it does.
When you bring a baby into a radio studio,
you just, you know, it can't help but cutify things.
It lightens things.
Uh, she was...
We were going to codify...
She's playing the keyboard in there.
...the doctrine, but instead we cutified the doctrine.
Did you see her playing the keyboard?
Well, we've cutified the church by a great margin.
I would say we've just about tripled the cutification of the church.
Well, that's saying something because we have never been able to cutify it very well.
Yeah.
It doesn't lend itself to cuti...
When somebody wants to insult us, they say that we've cutified it.
Oh, that's cute.
Oh.
Uh...
I have, uh, with me the entire of this book of the history of the Church of the Subgenius.
It's rather dry.
Yeah.
A lot of it's just counting which million was put into which bank and so forth.
Yeah, yeah.
But, but there's some...
The record of Vatican, you know, finances.
What about...
There's some interesting stuff about the Kennedy assassination and, uh...
Yeah, we've all heard that.
...the early involvement of...
Where did the money go out for...
What about the catalog?
Is that...
The tiger got him.
I'm waiting for the catalog.
All the money for the investigation into the assassination of dogs.
What happened to the money?
It was his...
It was a tremendous amount.
It was, uh...
Thank you, thank you.
It was a tremendous amount of time was spent on, uh, prosecuting, uh, Doug Wellman.
Dr. Drummond, was that you making that horrible noise?
And, uh, they were able to...
Anything else?
That was me and Walter making that horrible noise.
Well, uh, and they never were able to get Wellman for anything.
Walter and me.
Maybe I should say Walter and me.
Wellman was slippery.
I and Walter.
Even, uh, David Byrne was not able to get Wellman, and he tried.
I'm gonna try to ask for more.
This is, uh...
A little late.
Maybe even...
Beth, I wanna be back.
I'm just...
Finally.
David Byrne had another song called Buck Naked.
It has become...
You know, he, uh, one of them died.
Another song called Buck Naked.
A reality.
I'm serious.
I'm wondering...
Well, there was...
There have been so many musicians, singers named Buck Naked.
Including former subgenius Buck Naked.
Who made...
Who told me that if I ever mention him, I have to...
I had to say that he was former subgenius Buck Naked.
He did not want to be associated...
Yeah.
Please.
So I don't want to associate Reverend Buck...
Is he an apostate?
He's an apostate?
Oh, yeah.
Major.
Really?
Oh, yeah.
Why?
Well...
I used to...
He was a good...
I met him.
He was okay.
He was regular Michael Pepe.
But...
He was...
Oh, wow.
But, uh, what, uh...
He joined...
He, uh, joined the last...
As I understand it, former subgenius Reverend Buck Naked joined a rival concert.
Oh, wow.
I think possibly even a Jesus-oriented one.
A genuine one?
Have you ever heard of the I Am people?
Oh, no.
Well, apparently he is.
Oh, my God.
I Am.
The I Am?
Holy...
I Am had some great graphics.
Would that be...
That's...
I've ripped off...
I've got...
Five syllables to the line.
No, they still are.
To dovetain.
No.
You're thinking of the they were cult.
They did.
Yeah.
That was the, uh...
And then there was the Be Here cult, which I was in Be Here Now and Ram Das.
Were you in one of those Be Here Now cults?
Yeah.
I just liked his, uh, you know, show.
His, uh...
Penises.
Yeah.
Buck played a devil.
Oh, my God.
He was one of the foreground devils.
He made a great devil.
Speak of background devils.
That's former subgenius.
Former devil subgenius.
Now devil Celtists with the I Am.
There's a lot of former subgeniuses, actually.
It's quite a long list of people who decided they'd had it.
The top one, Appa State Schism, would be Bob Black, right?
I mean, he was...
Well, no, not really.
He was a scary guy.
I mean, I don't want to say Bob Black on the radio.
He wasn't.
His reputation precedes it.
He never scared me, let me put it that way.
Well, I know people that just...
Because he really did try as much as he could to arouse people's antagonism and opposition.
And, you know, wrote those nasty letters.
Well, I'm not trying to air a smeared underwear of the church on the air.
No, see, I've been trying.
In my revised...
85, essentially.
In the Stank Centric...
Revised history of the church, which I'm teaching to these innocents.
Hello, by the way.
Yeah.
Rosna and Chainsburger.
Hello.
Gary Gabo fan who's driving away.
Yeah.
Anyway, I've decided to just skip over the unpleasant aspect.
Yeah, I see.
I've un-personed quite a few.
Well, I...
That's...
We use the tried and true un-personing where you just don't mention them at all.
And they hate that.
Yeah.
You know, that's...
I know.
They hate that worse than anything.
It's the worst thing.
I know, in fact, that Bob Black hates...
Is more offended and enraged by being ignored than anything else.
Yeah.
And that kills him.
That's really the best way to treat people like, you know, the kooks.
I know.
He's a kook, even compared to us.
That's the funny thing.
I mean, even...
I mean, you know what I mean?
I mean, how can you be a kook compared to Stank?
To Church and Subgenius.
Yeah, but no.
They...
No, we feel for...
We feel for the differently-signed.
We're, you know...
Yeah, but they're not reality.
We're all kooks on some level.
No, you have to be a...
It's just that we're also subjectivists.
So anybody that we really dislike, we can say, well, he's a kook and write it off like that.
That's how words work.
Yeah.
They're just not.
That's what language is all about, is to label things.
Right.
Put them away.
And say prejudgments that are unfair.
They're prejudgments that keep order, which means you have to...
That's why there's this difference between...
Between subgeniuses and kooks.
Yeah.
It's just a way using linguistics to simplify things that are actually very complicated.
And it appeals to the stupid, the superstitious.
Yeah.
And to people who enjoy studying the effects of stupidity and superstition.
Stupidity, I'm afraid, you know, doesn't really exist.
I think stupidity actually is just fear where...
I mean, that is to say...
Stupidity is everywhere at all times, but...
I can see why you would say that.
Yeah.
But is Bush really stupid?
Almost everything is stupid.
I mean, but...
Compared to what?
I mean, it's just like saying, you know, almost everything is insane.
Things are insane.
But they're so insane, the word insane doesn't apply.
Or it does, but...
Right.
So when we say subgenius kook, what we're basically talking about is a normal.
Is...
A normal person.
Okay.
Who...
A pink.
A pink who pretended to be a subgenius.
Yeah.
A pink who was aping its betters.
There you go.
That's the worst.
That's what we call a subgenius kook.
Yeah.
A gimme bob.
A gimme bob, yeah.
Or an imabob, actually.
The worst are the imabobs.
Imabob.
Oh, yeah.
Those are people who think they're bob.
You know, I knew bob dogs.
And...
Sir, you are...
You are no bob dog.
You know, I haven't...
I haven't...
I'm a bob.
I actually had a case to say that in all sincerity.
I'm a sane.
To one of the imabobs.
Yeah.
If you can see what I'm...
Can you hear where I'm coming from?
Then there's...
You know, then there's the he's-a-bobs.
Do you see what I'm saying?
Can you see the words I'm saying?
Well, they's-a-bobs.
The words...
I'm a bobby.
You see them?
He's-a-bob, it means the same thing as I'm a bobby.
Or the may-bobbs.
Yeah.
Nay-bobs.
Now, that was...
That's a little different.
Nylon shell, fully waterproof.
I kind of like the nay-bobs.
Sealed seats.
Yeah.
They're a refreshing change from all the yay-bobs.
The may-bobs?
Okay.
They're the opposite of yay-bobs and yay-hoos, which are sort of like yay-hoos.
On things.
You don't know who the yay-hoos are, but you do know who the yay-bobs are.
Straddle the line, you know?
Rather than...
Well, you have to compromise.
Life is a series of compromises and terrible pain.
Just try to compromise.
Life is a series of balancing between the interstitial vortices.
Exactly.
Dr. Drummond, you love that interstitial vortices thing.
It explains so much.
It's right.
It explains everything.
It's like the unified field theory plus string theory all rolled into one.
Plus the golden mean.
And not only that, it combines earth, fire, and water and air into a unified...
Wow.
Chemical.
Three times 666 equals 1998.
What's the vortices?
It's right in front of us all the time.
The interior is nylon lined for easy on and off.
The strings are aligned with nylon for...
So what, it takes your soul off?
Your skin...
Finally.
The vortices.
What do you mean the vortices?
First, you take the skin off of the feet.
String theory.
Okay.
What is string theory?
Now, the power here...
String theory is what superstitious scientists came up with.
Yeah.
They're trying to invent...
Because...
Because they couldn't understand the interstitial vortices.
Exactly.
That's right.
This is what Philo's talking about.
Exactly.
They knew that...
Stephen Hawking could not quite grasp the interstitial vortices.
Because he wasn't a subgenius.
So they had to come up with all these other silly...
I might add that if anyone...
Any of your subgeniuses out there are interested in an in-depth analysis of this concept,
scientists, and it's just another...
It's simply is look at the new edition.
It's...
The new printing of...
The interstitial vortices.
Oh, yes.
The new printing...
We forgot.
We forgot the swag, such as the newly reprinted...
Yes.
Long out of print.
Revelation X is back in stores.
The Bob Apocryphon.
Oh.
There you go.
The Bob Apocryphon is back in stores these days.
Wow.
Not that you should buy it.
No, you should buy it.
We can't...
You should buy it and give it to...
Give it to me.
I don't even have one.
I don't even get one.
This is a buy as a whole.
This is a revival...
A revised edition, by the way.
The first...
We have to go through...
I don't...
I've never even gotten a...
Which edition is it?
The new...
Bob Apocryphon.
Revelation X has unpersoned a couple of people.
Unpersoned?
War in heaven became war is heaven.
Unpersoned in a way?
Yeah.
And you know, the good thing about it,
don't we go into detail on the interstitial vortices in that book?
Really?
The Dallas P.O. Box is now the Cleveland...
Well, what is it?
Okay, tell me about...
Because...
Well...
Vortices now, as far as...
So the ten strings that are...
There's a balance between pain and pleasure.
Are rotating...
That's right.
The dynamo of pain and pleasure.
Whirlpool.
Pain and pleasure.
You have to listen to Philo, Michael.
Okay, go ahead.
And they will...
It's the dynamo...
It's the eddies that are created between the dynamos of pain and pleasure,
balancing each other out.
They create this vortex.
And the vortices are...
Wow.
They are contiguous with each other.
They are contiguous with each other simultaneously.
And yet, each one is its own separate unit,
and separated by their own interstitial area,
which we call the interstitial vortices.
Dr. Drummond just explained the makeup of the universe and the meaning of life,
and you weren't even paying attention.
No, he wasn't.
Who are you folks?
I was.
He's so broke.
He can't even pay attention.
I can't believe this, that I found out about six meanings of life,
just tonight.
Just tonight only.
And the love...
Okay, so this is the interstitial...
And your assignment, you have to learn, you have to pick which one is valid.
Michael told me he was...
I would say so far, the interstitial vortices has it over everything I've heard so far.
If you read the back end of Revelation X,
there is a very detailed description of the theory of the interstitial vortices,
including illustrations.
Where can I get a copy of that?
You can get...
Revelation X from any better bookstore, as well as things like Walmart.com,
the evil, well, I should say, the evil Walmart.com,
the terrible Amazon.com.
We only...
And also available is the new Hal Robbins dinosaur book.
All right, Hal Robbins, who is...
Who has just walked in.
Rumored to have just walked in.
Yes, it's true.
It's true.
Dr. Howe is here in the flesh for the first time.
In the flesh.
Someone who knows how to use his shift lead on their commander.
Yeah.
Carcass removed of all organs.
A man with a vocabulary five times larger than the entire English language.
Yeah.
Those are my organs.
Keep away from that.
Those are my extras.
In case I...
Now, you know, in China, you can sell those.
Dr. Howe is now being interviewed by Princess Marie.
You can lose a tongue talking too much on the radio.
That's the best part.
It shuts the carcass.
You can't...
$10,000 a kidney.
I know.
The way she's taking off his clothes, though, it looks a little bit perky.
Look, here's somebody left this food thing here.
It's still got something in it.
It's called bourbon treat.
Hey, stay away from that.
Chocolate cream biscuits.
Look.
Wait, that's...
That's laced with 325 milligrams of LSD-25.
Okay.
Bourbon treat.
He's just going to just eat it.
Now, back in the old days when the subgeniuses didn't have brains per se,
they just had this sort of a nerve center at the end of their hind...
at their hind end.
This nerve center served as a thinking mechanism
which caused them to be able to discern between pleasure and pain.
Gravitating towards the one
and moving...
moving away from the other, they found their little cubby holes.
Uh-oh.
A special bulletin has just been handed to me.
Oh, my God.
Stand by as we switch you over to our main studio.
A report from the DuPont Company of Wilmington, Delaware has just been received.
Hurry.
The news is that fabrics containing Dacron polyester made by DuPont
are now being prepared for the special scientific heat treatment.
This means all garments made from this material...
this specifically treated fabric...
can later be durably pressed for the perfect counter shape.
And that fabric has been used to create this new Hal Robbins book,
which, since I'm not a member of this station, I can promote, I guess.
Dinosaur Alphabet by Harry S...
Can you believe that?
Harry S. Robbins.
Yes.
I knew that was his name.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Dr. Hal...
uh...
his new book, uh...
which is absolutely one of the most gorgeous dinosaur art books.
Well, it is the most gorgeous dinosaur art book ever seen.
Yeah, yeah.
But is it...
Dinosaur Alphabet.
Is it real or is it fantasy?
No, it's...
it's...
well, it is sort of fantasy.
These dinosaurs are better than anatomically correct.
That's one way of looking at it.
They're colored in a way that has to be fancy.
You know, no one's ever proven...
Are their sexual organs enhanced?
No one really knows what color they are.
No one's ever proven...
that dinosaurs existed in any form other than bones.
That's all we have.
That's right.
What's less the large...
What makes anyone think...
Not only that, but there is...
genitalia...
There are poetic paragraphs that go with each of these full-page color...
draw...
uh...
they're almost like paintings, really.
Man's best friend.
Yangchuanasaurus hid away from the prey on which he dined,
panting in the heat of midday,
crouching in his hunter's blind.
An ambush predator.
Yangchuanasaurus, though...
just doesn't sound very interesting to me.
...arosaurus-sized.
And, uh, there's a...
At the end of it, there's a kind of a bibliography...
that describes the details about each of these fabulous creatures.
Who wants to know details?
But they're not fabulous.
They're real animals that really existed.
I want the gross, scanned overview.
I don't want details.
Like Gigantosnotosaurus.
Ha!
Gigantosnotosaurus.
Which, uh, lived in, uh, Argentina.
Had to flee to Argentina.
Because it was bigger than three Tyrannosaurus rexes standing on top...
on each other's piggy back.
By the way, we have to do an ID here.
Uh, this is...
Over the Edge and the Puzzling Evidence Show combined and homogenized for your convenience.
Now, now.
Girl, what idea, baby, is that?
Oh, I know.
You should know.
Face it.
What's there?
You'll hear me, baby.
You'll hear me.
This has been such a wonderful excesslessness mess.
It's not over yet.
We're going till 5 a.m. this morning.
That means we'll get more presents.
There are probably 20 to 30 people in the studio, each one of them with an instrument.
It's the proof of karma, friends.
I brought Phineas Narco a copy of the Bobliographon.
He's got some pieces in it.
And in the karma, I had instant karma happen when Dr. Howell brought me a copy of the Bobliographon.
I'm sure he's got a copy of his new book, The Dinosaur Alphabet, by Harry S. Robbins.
And by the way, Robbins is spelled with one B. I bet you radio-listening illiterates didn't
know that.
Some of them may have known it.
And some may have known about it and repressed the memory.
Well, I'm not a radio illiterate, and I didn't know that.
But you do now.
What does it matter when one knew something?
So long as one knows it.
What's important is that when you type in Bobliographon, you know it's a thing.
If you type in Bobliographon, you know it's a thing.
But if you want to go into that search engine in the bookstore-
See?
I got you.
You use the name Robbins with the one B.
Like the bird.
Look, you can either feed a man and he's full for one day or I can teach you-
There is no-
I can give you this fishing pole and teach you to fish and you can go feed yourself
forever.
No, put down that fishing pole.
In the old-
You're not supposed to hit Howell with a fishing pole.
Stop it.
Is it true, Reverend Stang, that the new edition of Revelation X is digest-sized?
No, no, it is not.
No, no, it's full-sized.
In fact, aficionados of the Church of the Subgenius will want to lay out their old copy right next to their new copy
because they'll want to have a new copy to keep their old copy in shape for its future value.
As well as being able to have a new coffee table edition to show to their friends on their evenings of entertainment and frivolity.
The third Subgenius holy book, which I always forget the title.
If you buy a Revelation X, you get the coffee table?
The Cyclopedia of Slack with Bob Leografon is small.
It's not digest-sized, it's family Bible-sized.
It's nice and small.
It's like a family Bible.
The earlier version.
The older books are more like coffee tables.
Well, it hasn't, but it hasn't got smaller, a la the Penguin.
It's small and compact.
It's tough.
In any case, you'll want to lay your old one next to your new one and look at them page by page
and try to study them to figure out what's different, what's changed, and where is Waldo?
That's the big selling point of the new edition of Revelation X is that 23 of the pages are very subtly different.
Oh, good Lord.
And if you can find all those differences...
Then you win, of course, the trip to Dobbspan.
As seen on television.
Tremendous honor, of course.
Well, YouTube, anyway.
It's not for the honor.
An unspoken assumption of the expanding Earth theory is that dinosaurs were actually like the size of chickens back then.
Well, yeah, but the Earth was only the size of Mercury back then.
Right.
So it's an expanding universe.
Exactly.
So dinosaurs were really...
Dinky little things.
But since then, the elastic has weakened.
Well, it would have been like the blue whales of their day.
There were many whales, whines, and complaints.
But nothing was done.
And the Earth was without form.
It makes sense because those dragonfly fossils and stuff, they're impossibly big.
They had a meter-wide wingspan in the fossils.
Right.
Adontal standard size as we see them now.
They found fossilized frog sticks that were 15 feet long.
They did.
Well, I guess they were prospecting in the proper garden.
There were giants in the Earth in those days.
Everything was turned into giants over the millions of years as fossils.
I have a theory.
Dinosaurs were able to get so large because gravity was added.
actually less in those days.
But what about comedy?
Now people ask me, well, how could that be possible? And I ask you, why not?
We don't know anything about gravity. We don't even know what planet this is. We don't even know what it is,
what makes it, how it gets here. I say that in the early days,
it was probably because the Earth was spinning slower or faster,
but the gravity was less. Well, if the Earth was smaller, of course the gravity would be less.
No, it wasn't that much smaller. That wouldn't make that much difference, but gravity would.
A fraction of its size would make a heck of a difference.
Nothing can grow that big today because they'd have an immediate heart attack as they were crushed by their own organs.
It's too big. It's too heavy.
Well, it didn't happen at once.
There were no dinosaurs when the Earth was the size of the moon.
Well, that's a whole point. Of course there were, because they popped into the Earth.
Fun, fun.
Fun.
Oh, suicide man, you're crazy.
Well, let me accuse you once again.
That's a crazy idea.
Well, it is crazy.
But it is true that things were different on this planet at different times in its history.
What is crazy anyway?
You wouldn't recognize it, I think.
Back in the days of giant insects, the atmosphere used to be quite different.
It's just being not reality oriented.
You didn't have insanity, or did you? Was it all insanity?
Gravity was less, mark my words.
There was really a sanity that didn't exist since the human race didn't exist.
Can an animal be insane?
More energy to exploit.
More food to eat.
More fecundity of the Earth.
That wouldn't account for the...
Vital ability to grow.
None of that would account for the gigantic size of these things.
Given the ability to attain gigantic size, they attained it.
Only because the gravity allowed them to.
It would not connect.
And they had to.
Of course.
Now the...
Really the size of reptiles of today, back then...
The whale.
The greatest...
Giant reptiles have persisted through into many ages, including the age of man.
That's a crazy idea.
Yes.
The megalania of the Australian continent is one example.
An enormous...
This is Walter Braun broadcasting from the factory of Tiny Togs Company.
Really?
What?
It's alive today?
No, it's not alive today, but it's...
You can look at fossils of raindrops and there are a lot...
Relative of the well-known Kamado dragon.
That's right.
What accounts for that?
Much larger.
Less gravity.
What's the big shark's name?
Kamado.
That was the Carcharodon megalodon.
If I was running for office today, I would advocate gravity reduction.
Everything would be bigger.
Everything would be lighter.
You could lift more.
You could jump higher.
It would be great.
It was like that on our original planet, what's now called Mars.
It would take care of the obesity problem.
Yes, Stan.
Why?
It would increase gravity.
And there would have to be a compromise, which would end up just about where it is now.
This whole argument is so moot because the planets were switched.
Suicide man.
That's a crazy idea.
And that's a crazy idea.
The planets were switched in 1945.
It's in the book.
What is this?
It's in the new subgenius book.
Check it out.
This is official subgenius doctrine.
Dr. Howell, what do you think of expanding Earth?
There's no point in struggling.
The truth of the expansion of Earth is...
Now, this does not, however, claim that subgeni expands in a certain sense.
If a dinosaur wanted to get a donut...
Yes.
...the Earth is constantly being pelted by extraplanetary material.
I'm not talking about meteorites.
...and is increasing in size through that method of accretion.
...that all matter is taking up more volume as time passes...
...in a dramatically increased way.
God pelts the Earth with excrement like a chimpanzee thrown at his enemy.
We're not talking about cosmic spring here.
We're talking about fecal peltings.
In other words, if you were to take out one linear-sized piece of platinum...
...and put it in a vault, in 100 million years, it should be like four or five meters huge.
Here's another thing.
Forbidden sciences teach us that gravity is not something that sucks you towards the nearest, the biggest mass...
...but pressure from outer space pushing down on you against the Earth.
That's why things fall.
It's because outer space is pressing down on us.
The pressure from space...
Our science, Earth science, is so primitive.
It's really in its infancy.
It's based on language, which you feel good science would be based on things in themselves...
...if they could be proved to exist.
Right. We're babies compared to the people from the future.
My former employers, I might add.
And the excess.
What can we do about the people from the future?
Primal energies of the animal, man.
We can't do anything about the people from the future except not give birth to them.
Yeah.
It's too late for me.
And even that's hard to do.
I already gave birth to two of the people from the future.
What did they look like?
Were they older than they were at the time you saw them a moment ago?
They were. Yeah.
I'm talking about the UFOs or the...
Oh, yeah.
Well, they made it with the subgeniuses, right?
Is that how the Yeti became more than man?
No, it's really that the excess just flat out instant created the Yetis as a perfect creature.
They were able to give life to...
They were able to create new life forms.
The Yeti was the smartest animal on the Earth.
The Yetis then created the humans.
The humans, much the same way by quick mutating a certain type of rat.
Monkey seed.
Monkey's mistake.
So really, humans were the lab rats of the Yetis.
Yeah.
But a stunted, retarded Yeti made the mistake of freeing the humans and teaching them fire and language.
And that's when the conspiracy was born.
It's just that...
Wow, nuts.
There was a traitor Yeti.
If you try to look for the...
That's horrible.
You know, they should have just let them fall back into the slime.
...know when you're going to be looking for them.
Why teach them?
Why educate them?
I mean, if they're only going to raise themselves up and out of the slime.
It seemed like a good idea at the time.
Well, actually, the Yetis did go out and exterminate most of the humans, but some of them...
They survived.
...were projected by time control into about a million years ago.
Yeah, 100,000 years ago, where Cro-Magnon Man suddenly appeared and wiped out all the other wonderful, pleasant humanoids.
Yeah, good-looking Neanderthals.
Yeah, Neanderthals, the Homo erectus and the Homo connectus.
You have the return of that in Jay Leno, you know, that's got the prognathus.
I know, he's got the big jaw of the Neanderthals.
And Anthony Robbins.
He appeals, of course, to the...
Yes, they're both that uber-human...
What do they call that?
Well, Jay Leno has that superhuman jaw like Bob does.
The football.
J.R. Bob Dobbs has a jawbone like that.
It is the jawbone of the Yeti.
Yes, a strong jaw, almost prognathous of a larger primate such as Gigantopithecus...
Or J.R. Bob Dobbs.
...or Gorilla or J.R. Bob Dobbs.
But the Yeti now is such a much bigger...
...and a larger animal than most subgeni I know.
And it seems rather dwarf compared to the Yeti.
Well, that's neither here nor there.
Hitler wasn't very arrogant either.
Yes, true.
As far as ideological purity is concerned, do as we say, not as we do.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll practice.
We can do what we want.
You can do what you want.
As Bob said, I don't practice what I preach because I'm not the kind of person I preach to.
Exactly.
Here, here.
Neuronicus 1.14.
Another door over there.
You have to be crazy.
You better stay calm.
It's been a long journey.
Many of us are tired, ready to lay our bodies down.
I have the pain of a hundred million hells.
Above all, a subgenius needs slack.
That is it.
The subgenius must have slack.
It's not that the subgenius needs slack.
The subgenius is born with slack.
It doesn't mean that slack is not something you go out and acquire.
Slack is what you have.
The subgenius, to be a subgenius, must have slack.
You were born with original slack, but the conspiracy took it away from you.
That's right.
Tell us.
As heard on TV.
Why?
That conspiracy forced you to purchase false slack.
And now you don't even know what real slack is.
So if you're having a slack attack, you can find out how American hair must have it.
So if you're having a slack attack, check out Revelation X at better bookstores everywhere.
At Subgenius.com.
Does the cover look just like the other cover?
Yes, it is identical.
Same colors?
Yes.
It all looks...
In fact, I'd have a copy for you, Dr. Howell, but I gave them...
All the ones that I had, I gave them away to my nieces and nephews in Stang County, Texas.
Well, that's all right, I guess.
Oh, I can mail you one.
But those youths had never been exposed to the word of Bob in this form at all.
You've read Revelation X because you co-authored it.
Urban youths ought to be exposed to this kind of literature.
The youths of America deserve nothing less than full exposure to the Subgenius Doctrine.
But are you saying that the authors of Subgenius Doctrine, Revelation X,
are also working on the minds of tiny little helpless innocent children?
Tiny little midgets?
Well, as Bob ordered us to, yes, of course we are.
You're only following orders?
Little innocent precious fresh minds.
I know what you mean, Michael Pepe, because every little innocent life is of inestimable value to us here in the Church of the Subgenius.
Every tiny little runny pipsqueak that comes along toddling down the pike is to us a brother.
And he toddles into a bookstore.
He deserves to be coddled and burped and tickled.
But there comes a time when you have to draw the line somewhere.
And that line is www.subgenius.com.
You have been listening to the Hour of Slack.
Although this time it was a rerun.
One of the KPFA over the edge and puzzling evidence show.
Nonetheless, it is an hour of slack.
Or just was.
Subgenius.com.
Praise Bob and thank you.