The Self-Genius Hour of Swag.
And it was pleasing to Bob.
Hey, old Diablo's here.
Oh!
Just wandered into the studio.
Just thought I was starting to...
Into the new ship.
The new...
The new escape vessel.
I'll be hauling this...
Oh, man, listen to this.
Now Jesus calls.
Well, we're just so popular.
Yes, well, here we have...
We have Papa Joe Mama,
Pope S. Lillis,
and Bleepo
all on the phone tonight.
And Dave in the studio.
And Bleepo Adpanaki.
Yes, there's one more with me.
There's one more.
And yet more in the Bleepo...
Oh, there's a Bleepo clone.
The Bleepo net.
The female Bleepo clone.
Oh, and they are...
They haven't even had to bleep Bleepo yet.
What's your...
Not a clone.
You're not a clone?
No, I'm sorry, I am not.
You are the original whoever...
What is your name now?
I am Contessa Conchetta Dabalina.
Oh, you are the countess devil lady herself.
Oh, yes.
You may even experience intense breath
or you may not.
Thank you.
Thank you, Contessa.
Oh, friends, we have so many guests.
Most people in our society
are addicted to subventilation.
And subgenius.
We have subventilation and subgeniuses
in our society.
But friends, everything will be all right.
Everything, I promise.
And, you know,
Bob or me
or any holy man
wouldn't.
Wouldn't.
Lie to you.
Now, would we?
But, uh...
Friends, welcome to the third
of our formatted shows.
Now that we've done 680 shows,
we've got a format.
And right now,
the format calls for the news.
And I'm afraid the news
is fairly typical this time.
Um...
U.S. populace...
lurches methodically
through the motions
for yet another day.
The wall-eyed,
slack-jawed U.S. populace
beaten down into a state
of near catatonia
by the relentlessly deadening
banality of their joyless,
insipid lives
dutifully trudged through the motions
for yet another
emotionally blank day.
Monday.
Sources reported.
Against all logic,
the nation's citizenry,
their insides withering away
with each passing moment,
somehow managed to continue
filling out invoices,
shopping for footwear,
loading dishwashers,
eating Whoppers,
pressing buttons,
watching reality-based TV programs,
vacuuming floors,
engaging in conversations
about petty office problems,
politics,
riding buses,
sitting in traffic,
mailing letters,
and tending to the little rubber mats
people wipe their feet on
as they enter the lobby areas
of vast, windowless,
industrial complexes.
How they managed to do it,
no one can say.
The populace's minor victory
of continuing...
Pardon me, friends.
I'm reading this from The Onion.
The populace's minor victory
of continuing to participate
in the meaningless charade
that is their lives,
sources said,
was rendered all the more futile
by the inescapable realization
that they must do it again
tomorrow and the next day
and so on and so on
unceasingly
until the day they inevitably die.
Friends,
that's one way of looking at it.
We don't read from The Onion
that frequently anymore
because The Onion is now
very well-known and popular.
It's the most, I'd say,
the most ripped-off humor magazine
in America today.
It is a humor news magazine
and I guess it's www.onion.com.
They give it away in cities up north.
But I don't think they'd like it
down south here, friends.
But what we do like here
is a sub...
You know, that's one way of looking at it.
What I just read to you,
that's one way.
That's what the pinks did.
That's the news for the pinks,
those shadows,
those three-dimensional,
fixed-legged fools, friends.
But there's another way to look at it.
There's another type of news,
one could say,
that the revolution has occurred.
You may have been too busy
watching Seinfeld to notice.
And guess what?
The bad guys won.
And now most of the population
lives in a de facto state of slavery,
bound to their miserable lives,
jobs, and homes
by the bonds of socioeconomic control.
Sounds like a bunch of leftist
Bolshevik propaganda, doesn't it?
Well, of course it does.
Unfortunately, it's true.
Slavery, as defined by the book,
as defined by the dictionary,
is submission to a dominating influence
or a lack of freedom.
And just what is this dominating influence
that has such a large chunk of the population
in its iron grip?
Money.
Moolah.
The long green.
Dead presidents.
Nobody ever feels they have enough, do they?
How many people are stuck
in miserable, hateful jobs
because they have too many bills
and financial obligations?
How many people do you know
who can comfortably pick
and go, pick up and go where they want?
Can you?
What happened to your freedom?
Studies indicate
that wealth is becoming concentrated
in the control of the smaller and smaller
segment of the population.
Who the hell are these people
that are hoarding all the gold?
Buckminster Fuller called them
the great pirates.
Plutocrats that dominate industry,
government, advertising, and marketing
in order to fulfill their insane lust
for wealth and power.
Not satisfied with the possession
of more money and control
than any normal entity
would ever know what to do with,
competing groups of these great pirates
vie to exploit more land, labor, and material
in an insane race
to die with the most toys.
How do these avaricious rogues
get away with it?
What insidious form of mind control
do they employ to keep the money hemorrhage going
and the people ignorant and complacent?
What can you do to break these bonds?
In the following few shows,
the subgenius hour of slack
reading from this pamphlet,
There He Is,
outlines a few simple steps you can take
to better understand the predicament
and liberate yourself.
Certainly, this sounds like idiotic,
overblown extremist nonsense.
We'll admit that.
The real question is whether the problem
is being exaggerated to make a point,
or is actually understated
because the truth is too horrible to contemplate.
And friends, this pamphlet,
written by my cousin, Crawford Smith,
it's called S.O.S.,
Stamp Out Slavery,
From There He Is Productions.
Here's the sample.
It's many Вотul chapters
and part 2 of the first three.
Here's the Good,
Han,
that's good.
It's also not bad.
I really enjoy my book.
It's really good.
That's a good thing.
It's good.
It's a good thing.
but vote anyway. Statistics are meaningless 87% of the time. Organized religion, nemesis of mankind,
take that job and detonate it. Stop reproduction before it starts. Laugh or die. And the secret
of happiness. Hey, let's skip ahead to the secret of happiness, the very last page of the booklet.
It's simple, really. Just accept that happiness comes in small doses and at irregular intervals,
and that you must learn to appreciate those unexpected peak moments when they occur.
Attempting to seize or prolong these events is as useless and futile as trying to grab a fistful
of water. Face it, there's no way you'll be happy all the time, so learn to enjoy the moments that
you are happy. So there you have it, the secret wisdom of the ages. Yours absolutely free,
just for listening through a few pages of insane rants on this dopey radio show read from a poorly
thought out and cheaply done pamphlet by Crawford Smith. Pretty good deal, huh? You know, get out of
here now. Get out of here. You're standing in our light. Oh, and speaking of light, the light music
in the background is by El Diablo.
I don't know what comes next on this old media barrage type, but we'll figure it out. Come on.
We're already two hours late for the show.
Oh, watch it with that water, man. We don't have much.
Where's the road?
I think it's behind us.
Behind us?
What the? I thought we were going towards the road.
Okay, give me some of that air before it's gone.
Before there's just a big blank space and nothing else.
I hope it lasts till it gets there.
Yeah, I know.
God, my feet are killing me, too.
Look, look. See, the sun's this way, so the road's gotta be over there.
Yeah, but the moss is growing on the other side of that.
And the radiation warning signs are all pointing that way.
It looks kind of menacing. The sun's just coming up.
If that really is a sign.
Yeah, the sun's just coming up.
It looks pretty weird.
Boy, the air smells good. I just wish...
I don't think this is...
That looks like the Cactus Wren, Arizona's national...
No, I don't think that's the Cactus Wren.
I think this is Arizona, Hal. This is Texas.
Yeah, there it is.
We've gotta be in Texas.
Let's get out of here. It's creepy.
I just hope the Indians haven't, uh, set one of their deadly traps.
Hey, watch out!
Boy, we'll never get back to KPFA at this rate.
KPFA?
I thought we were going to K-N-O-N.
I thought we were just going to Hope Studio.
All we have to do is use the mobile field antenna and we can start our broadcast.
And also, we should just be able to see the rocket from here somewhere.
I'm afraid that went down several hours ago.
A rocket?
It would have shown up on our locator, but...
Hey, look over there.
Just a natural rock formation. Nothing to be afraid of.
That's an abandoned secret.
That's a secret.
It looks like a big scary monster. I know, but...
You know, out in the desert, things can look like things that they aren't.
It's called a psychic heat mirage.
They call them duendes.
Oh, don't talk about the duendes.
Yeah, the Indians say they're little shriveled...
dried up, mummified like beings about a foot tall that...
It ain't just a legend.
This rock over here just...
Oh!
Just tear a piece off.
That...
This cactus doesn't feel like plastic.
These rocks are made out of paper mache.
This is a...
This tree is made out of a spring.
Maybe we can get some water, huh?
I don't know, you guys. What does that symbol mean?
Oh, yeah, this is bed springs.
We don't have any more coffee.
Doesn't that mean biochemical hazard or something?
No sugar, no more beans.
You can't figure out where the road is.
At least we got a good astronomical observation last night.
Check out the man pack, see if we can figure out where we are.
We better get a Geiger counter reading.
...star called SS 433.
It's kind of cold out here.
They don't call it nuclear winter for nothing.
...readings. We can take another reading a little later on.
I just hope we've got something to say when it's time for that broadcast.
Yeah, no kidding. I love my script.
A lot of people are counting on us. Remember that.
All ten listeners in the Bay Area.
The Bay Area.
They've got to hear us or they just can't make it through the noise.
This is Texas.
...as it were.
Come on, you guys.
Oh, look, a jackalope, Arizona's national rabbit.
Man, I thought those were extinct.
There it goes.
Okay, it's glowing.
That little speaker's in its head.
Yeah, I wonder where that's coming from.
It's probably an observation drone.
We all follow where the artists lead us.
They are our Galileans. Our Lewises are Edisons.
Is there still law?
There is still law, yes.
But how can there be law without the father?
Father.
He hasn't left us.
That is what I will tell the others.
But his spirit is watching over us.
We must wait for a sign.
That is what I will tell the others.
They'll believe anything.
Yes, the father, he's still there.
Don't worry, it's all right.
Everything's fine.
Bob will take care of everything.
Just rest your head down here.
That's right.
Father will watch over us.
Bob loves you.
Would you like some more book?
Oh, sorry.
It's all right.
Within every person, there's some good
and there's some evil.
There's some bad.
And it's a choice.
You choose whether you want to love or hate that person.
And for myself, I just choose to hate most of them.
Now, when a subgenius says that he hates,
what kind of a hate is he talking about, children?
Is he talking about your average, run-of-the-mill hate?
No!
Oh, I just hate Reagan.
That's pathetic!
Or even worse, the nampy-pimpy, pitiful little,
I just hate myself.
No!
What we talk about when we talk about hate
is an all-consuming, an all-encompassing,
an all-pervasive hate!
Yes, I believe it!
An infinite hate!
A hate that knows no bounds!
A hate that extends to the very end of all of the universes!
A hate!
A hate as black as outer space itself!
We're talking about an all-consuming hate!
More hate!
Ah, yes, the harvest.
This is the way they did it in the New Testament.
God scolded his people in the Old Testament.
The greatest people on earth.
And you walked in with the Judas tribe,
and the wife of Judas might be one of the ladies I'd laid to make a socialist.
I knew I couldn't trust anything but communism and the principle in me.
Yes, I knew that that's what I had to depend upon,
not depend upon the arm of the flesh,
and never put all your eggs in one basket.
So, honey, I put my eggs in many places.
You figure that out if you want to.
Some of you are too naive.
You don't know what Jim Jones is all about.
You can't even follow him.
You haven't even smelled where he's at yet.
Much less followed him.
You don't even know who he is.
And you might miss him if you didn't have a real good look at him.
You wouldn't even know who he looked like.
You really haven't got an excuse.
But I've got all kinds of things in store.
Bob, get out of the box.
That's last!
Yes!
I feel sorry for the friends of mine who never bought a membership.
I've always tried to expose them gently to Bob's word,
not to force it down their throats,
not mail them pamphlets constantly.
I have turned some people to the church.
I am very proud of those people.
I look forward to greeting them on the saucers.
You know?
But it's kind of sad that my mother,
who really is a wonderful person,
never did buy that membership.
Then again, I don't know what she would make of the saucers.
And of course, there are my enemies.
I do have people in my life who have hurt me
for no particular reason all the way back in high school.
And once I get my memory editing,
I'll be able to remember who you all are.
And I probably will have specific tribulations set aside just for you.
I understand them.
They don't understand me.
To the fucking beat now.
They can't beat us!
We're subgeniuses!
The End
What the fuck am I doing here?
Write us toён
Blood!
From my dead boy,
A subscriber heavy hitter
about my love for yah
Everyone except me
But what I cannot live for
is what this dare
Thank you.
friends yeah i guess we must have mixed up the departments already we've already screwed up the
format uh that was the old media barrage department mixed up with a brand new guest
rant department and friday jones uh reading about the termites mixed up with the rock and roll
that was steve vi uh rock and roll cd sound there in the background what was that's his uh flexible
reversible album but this is i think in the background now is fart dog explosion
an amalgam of the greatest doctor bands
doctors for bob the swinging love corpses doctors for wotan and 1000 doctors
does this mean there is no more law if there's no more pain is there no more law
now there's no more pain does that mean then that there is no more law
some of the guy that has legal notice in the paper and my right to smoke a cigarette
i have the oxygen case and uh like i said i got the house of evolutionary tree that was
stolen from me in the six i got permission to search euclid school board
uh then i have the story i think an old sheriff this guy's too this guy's to discover southern
albuquerque uh then there's i'm waiting for a seed source i have my address registered
what this house is about what people are trying to disturb and draw attention to my privacy
and then i need somebody that understands what they're talking about i need to declare a center
for scheduled recovery of toxins i'm interested in the oxygen of course and uh then i have the
indo-chinese
one their case i'm allowed to put another
on the indo-chinese i'm first industrials families of europe and america i'm allowed
to put in one of the first french german and hospice prussian swedish families norwegian
all of which are arabs and too steel why is that abused
i'm just saying for you a very good thing
they don't do high school
Oh, no.
Ba-ba-ba.
Oh.
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, no.
Oh, yes, dear friends, Onan Canobite did this music in the background, the B.O.B.
Incredible mix.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Ba-ba-ba.
Bye.
I have a telegraph first.
Yeah.
Just saying all the radios will be gone.
Instant.
Instantly.
There'll be, we'll be back to horse and buggies and a big rush on blankets for smoke.
Telegraph.
Hey, don't pile.
Hey, you need to feed those horses something.
And then we'll have to have a lot of.
sacrifices because it didn't work out last time.
I think it's not enough bloodletting.
I think we need to take a few drops more.
How important were the
computers to the
telegraph system at the turn
of the century? Well, I know the Vikings needed
them real bad. Yeah.
They couldn't get anywhere without them computers.
Like those wires they stretched all
over the country had a chip on it.
Yeah. Sometimes
they had those curly fries.
What if the Y2K problem is
retroactive and the shockwave
goes back in time, destroying
all computers in the past as
well. So that means we'll have to go back
even more epic. We'll all
be in America that has never been
discovered by Columbus because he didn't have
the computer to make his map.
Yeah, it instantly wipes out
all artificial intelligence in the universe.
Even beads will fall off
of abacus. Yeah.
Bees will pass out too coming out of the
combs. Animals will become
very confused. That'll be hard for most of the
listeners to live with if they have to go out
side and pick turnips, you know. Yeah.
I don't know if I want to live
through it. A new dark ages.
Yeah, it's baffling.
On the other hand, maybe we'll all just be
reincarnated as our ancestors in the
year 1900. Oh, that'd be
scary. I think what'll actually
happen is our consciousnesses will be
blasted amidst all of our ancestors
so all of them will have this
vague memory of a strange
time when everyone had magical machines
that did everything for them, but it'll all
end in 1999.
Yeah. And then they'll all live
forward and eventually produce
us and in us the memory will be concentrated.
The terrible thing will happen in
1999 and then it will happen again
and our consciousness will be blasted back to
1900 again. That's an
endless loop. It's terrible.
That's an ill prescription for mankind
to constantly keep reabsorbing
itself. Maybe we can, this
time around, maybe we
can plant something that
will clue us in as
we're living our lives, you know, as kids,
and stuff like that. We won't know it's
coming, but maybe we can
leave something behind that will
send us a message
to start working on...
We need an artifact that's completely computer
untouched so it won't be destroyed.
Right. And we need to immediately impregnate
the first person we see in that
world so that our seed, like
a tiny little oak, can grow out of
them and impregnate the rest of the seeds
of mankind's depleted accordion.
Um, uh...
Maybe we could just bring along business cards instead.
Or sub-accordion. Yeah.
Yeah. That's a different
pitch place that you're gonna go in there.
We wanna get people to dance
into the new century, right? Or just kill
themselves again, or what?
I think they should dance until they die.
All time ends, as far as I know,
from listening to, like, a lot of radio.
Uh, talk radio
and stuff. Whatever you are doing at the
moment of the turnover, you will do
for all eternity. That's right.
Frozen in that one moment. So obviously
you should be having sex.
Yeah. So if you can just
reach orgasm at
midnight. You'll be scrubbing it
forever? That's right.
Well, what about Pat Boone? Is that guy gonna be
on a heavy metal stage saying
the world's gonna end in six minutes
for the rest of time? He's gonna be singing a heavy...
For all of eternity. Pat Boone singing
a heavy metal version of We Are the World.
Forever. With Metallica,
you know, special guest.
The real despotically
bone-chilling Christian
undertones there, just kinda like putting
you in the mausoleum in the Inquisition
at the same time you're getting rocked out.
Yeah. And if you're reaching
to scratch an itch at the moment,
you'll be eternally reaching for
that terrible itch and you'll never be able
to scratch it. You'll just be spinning around
forever and ever, reaching.
Reaching for that spot in your
back you can't quite reach.
Yeah. But you'll be eternally ungrateful.
Forever and ever. If you got it.
Yeah. Well, at each moment
I suppose there'd be a plethora of delights
that would last or kill you forever. Maybe we should
start killing all the computers now.
Just to get used to it.
If you can't fix the problem
in a year, I'm sure we could kill
every computer within a year.
How about we all become Buddhist?
Nah. Nah, there'd be a few computers
left over. It's kinda like, you know, the...
Someone would hide theirs. They'd have their underground
shelter with the rank of batteries.
We gotta kill... It'd be like the killer, you know,
that movie Killer Bees, you know, where there's
that one bee left up on the seat
at the top of the... Bill Gates.
Superdome. That's him, Bill Gates.
That's what I was getting to. That one last
killer bee that we gotta get. No, it won't be a big guy like
Gates. It won't be a big guy. They'll get him first.
But he's the... He is the evil one.
He is the evil one. He will...
It'll be one of Gates' spawn. The unnamed
spawn with that chip
directly coded into his DNA.
That one would escape.
I think Gates has already implanted that chip into
that spawn wherever... Oh, they're rushing right now
to clone people so hard, too.
Do you know that, folks?
Oh, yeah. Oh, we gotta do it
tomorrow. Of course. Jeez.
You know,
hardly six months has gone
by since it was the bad idea. Now,
we're all supposed to be for it. Well, they have to hurry up, though. They have
to come to term before
1999 rolls over.
So they only got 11
and a half months. Look, I'm
a Dos Equisist, actually.
And I don't really think there is
gonna be any problem after July
5th anyway this year. I don't know. And then none of
the clones will come to fruition.
I never really thought it was gonna happen on X-Day.
I was a Dos Equisist all the way.
Yeah, I'm a bohemian man myself. 1999.
I think it's gonna keep on going on
with grueling drudgery forever.
I've been labeled a Nexus
and I don't shrink from
that label. How about a Plexus?
Either one of those are spots that
can't be scab-picked.
The Nexus or the Plexus. Your lunar
Plexus? The Plexus.
That's that special spot on your ass
where if someone kicks you, you can't breathe.
Your lunar Plexus. Yes, it's
a chakra of yoga. Uh-huh.
For those of you who want to get off the planet without
a body or with one, either way, you gotta
use it. Uh-huh.
We might need to build some kind of dynamic cadre
of robot
android computer killing people
that can use it like Chonk Twine.
Based on a DNA segment built
on the dodecahedron. Who can
kill all the bad guys here and then still get off the planet
and then maybe come back and kill some more like
pirates. And can exist in any dimension
up to a level. Hey, you guys, what's up?
What's up, man? Hey, man, what's up?
Hey, you know, X-Wings, I got these new kind of fighters
and they can kill your robots off.
And, uh, and friends, I think that
collar, in some
respects, shows more
maturity and
realistic, practical
grasp of things in this modern
world than our unfortunate
friends at Einstein's
Secret Orchestra.
Chaz and Dave with their special guest
Princess Weard. Oh, and
actually, you didn't hear Princess We much,
but Friday Jones
was taking us back
in time.
And, uh, friends,
we've been, this is great with this,
I got through most of the departments
before we even
started the show.
Or, wait a minute,
what am I saying? I don't know what the hell's going
on. Let's see what...
Oh, I...
Whenever he starts going
you know that it's time for the pill.
Yeah, that's what it is.
Take another one of their pills.
I am pills.
Salvador L. Dolly Parton once said,
I am pills. There was a time before pills.
No, friends.
You must be one with the pills.
The Dave and the pill are one.
But there's a time we have to think about
before the pills. Hey, Leib, could you paint
that scene for us? We'll shut up for a second.
Alright. There was a time
before the pills.
When the pills
were liquids and powders
in their separate forms.
Alone
and bottled.
Bottled and alone.
Alone.
And as...
The seas swelled and the various
lubricants slurped around
the ancient seas.
A conch shell...
A conch shell formed from the
sands around the seas.
And as the seas
churned and mixed the liquids
and the powders,
the conch shell
embraced all that was
to become the pills.
Aphrodite rose from the waters
with her one Etruscan breast
showing.
Flipped skyward.
And she held forth
two bottles.
In one bottle were the uppers
and in the other
the downers.
And in between
were all the other pills that would ever be
or ever might be imagined.
Dr. Fence, a veritable
laboratory of...
Not alone.
We can sure have...
And the Yeti people surrounded her
and praised her.
And began to paint her picture.
They wondered about the pills
that she held.
This is the great goddess Naya.
The great goddess Naya
who brings not only fertility
but great pork and bean sandwiches.
I fed all the others.
Thank you for the letters.
And pills, Davey.
Pills too.
For we're talking about the pills
and the time before the pills.
Two pills.
Late 50s, I think it was.
Four pills.
I don't know.
Five pills.
And the people and the Yetis
looked on the pills
and they wondered.
The pills.
And the subgeni came
and they asked the goddess
for the pills.
And the goddess said...
DMT.
The goddess said...
Yes, the goddess laughed.
Guilty.
Hang each and every one
of these private parts.
Take them separately
and hang each and every one
of the other parts.
That's why I take this.
Yes.
Papa Joe.
Yes, sir, ma'am.
The goddess says...
Climb up on that podium
and give us a minute or two.
As I step within the 13 deadly steps
upon the loosely nailed scaffolds
I stand
and look upon the sea
of sickening pain.
I stand
These are the looks
of those who will scream in pain.
Yes.
The rocket
of the fire sky
on the sea today.
For as we have fooled
the normals
into thinking
X-Day 1998 has passed,
X-Day 1999 approaches
in a gallop
of the seven horsemen
of the apocalypse.
Let them who doubt
not attend.
scoff and laugh.
And let those
true believers
laugh.
Gather with their oxygen masks
and big,
stupid,
to gather
for the rest
of the day.
Bob.
My corpuscles
are exploding.
Only as they ascend
the escalators
into the pleasure saucers
to see
what they think
will be
an eternity of bliss
will they realize
that Bob
has been preparing
a special sauce
for them.
Yes,
the bodies
in the barbers
will be separated
from the true
believers of Bob
and the subgeniuses.
For even now
with 10,000 members,
10,000 paid members,
there are too many
to ascend
into the X's
pleasure saucers
and to planet X.
We must separate
the wheat
from the chaff.
The wheat.
You need to
close the valve
down there.
And that, my friends,
is why we have
the special subgenius
slogans
to separate the Barbies
from the true subgenies.
So we will know
who will be
those who travel
to and fro
and who will be
the food for those
who travel to and fro.
Fro!
I vote fro!
Vote fro!
Yes, my dear friends,
you don't need
to be a peewee hermit
in order to enjoy
the flesh of humans.
All the flesh
are Barbies
and Barbettes.
But remember,
it is more pleasant
and good
to feed
than it is
to be fed upon.
Eat while the carnage
is fresh.
Ah!
The corpses
were swollen
into the land.
It is always better
than not enough.
The river's
running red.
Pink is
as pink
does.
It is always better
than not enough.
Even the pinks
are pink on the inside.
Too much
is always better
than not enough.
You can...
You can never
have...
You can never,
ever, ever
have too much
solid rocket fuel.
It's been five months
and though it's left
in the...
in the heat for so long...
Hey, let me show you
too much rocket fuel
underneath.
Save is always better
than not enough rocket fuel
Hey, guys, let me show you
my frop rocket.
Oh, frop rocket?
All right.
Yeah.
It could only be lit
with an actual
frop joint.
Let me ride.
Let's ride.
Here's my frop rocket.
Is that a waste of good frop?
Do you stick a...
No, no.
No.
Whoa!
Did I get right in the middle
of the frop-a-thon?
Oh, man, Stang's here.
Oh, my God!
Papa Joe Mama's here.
Bleepo's here.
And Pony Rack is gone.
And Dave's in the studio.
Gary's in the house tonight.
He's not wearing
It's a full house tonight
here on WCSC Cleveland.
It's a royal flush here.
And let's not
forget the Contessa here.
Yep.
I'm inаль do my best
to hold an electoral
election here.
One disabled Excuse me administration
I'm ineligible for deportation
So- tired of untuk
every single american
This is actuallyiram
Addicato.
Ladies and gentlemen of the world,
it is my utmost privilege to announce to you
that these little green men actually do exist,
for they are part of the eternal past
and venture from all regions of our galaxy
to find homage in our Earth's center.
Governments of the world have been very good
at concealing these little visitors
and preparing the public with loving movies
and pleasant melodies.
You see, like this one.
You hear that?
Yes, controlled media has to cushion the impact
of the arrival of our little friends.
Throughout history, many people have claimed to see
strange lights in the sky.
The truth of the matter is that these lights and beings
will only reveal themselves to those who are pure at heart,
for these enlightened aliens
leave permanent imprinted information
on the psyche of those chosen humans
only to be revealed to our deteriorating planet
at the point at which our civilization
shall enter the new age of
Light Without Heat.
Light Without Heat
Little green man about four foot one
Maybe they want to have some fun
Little green man about four foot two
Maybe he wants to mate with you
Little green man about four foot three
Maybe they want to be set free
Little green man about four foot
Maybe he wants to kick some butt
Oh, oh, oh
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Little green man, yeah
Ele Score, the little green man
If I big mouth you who makes so give her hurt
LAU бо h Ар
How far you run around and you loose like that
Runnn and diamond, all that she***
Being free to control how you feel
beseree
Be very skillful to be sou telefonice
Se'tSeyFloorAndoffWhenTheLine Aw dedけている
Oh, friends, a classic of melodramatic cheesiness there from Steve Vai.
I guess he's some kind of a guitar god to some people,
but that was an interesting derivative and yet inspiring piece of something.
And we've mostly been listening to E.
Now that we went through the old stuff departments,
it's been an instinct like an orchestries in old men of Dave and Times.
Ooh.
Will it be?
Will it be you?
You.
You're standing there in the dark.
I can see your face clearly now.
Will it be you?
You with the shining face.
Will you take us out of this place?
Lead us far, far away.
Come, come.
You come up to the front of the stage.
Show them who you are.
You're golden boots, aren't you?
You've come to take us away from...
Plutonium storms and the endless dark and the air with no moisture and the croaking of the birds as they die.
You, you will take us away to a place where there are no birds anymore.
Well, that about wraps it up in a sandwich so far.
It seems that, uh,
some people are having a hard time getting their way.
The window's open.
The, uh, detritus has reached an alarming level of 15 centimeters.
If you're out today, you're probably going to die.
You don't want to reach for the, uh, thermometer, though.
You don't want to reach for that evacu-gen.
You want to make sure that everybody, including the pets, are inside the house.
Well, those of us who can make it to the stars,
perhaps we will try and get there.
And I will word from the Reverend Forrest Mellon,
the Church of the Apocalyptic Vision tonight,
the incorrect assumption and the play on worms by our lady of the Wombat,
a spoken ceremony without any ending,
concluding the following passage.
Hello.
I have been a wanderer through the stars.
I have left my footprints.
On Mars.
I have settled strumpets in outer space
and specked their booties and their face.
These words, dear Reverend and sisters,
these words were uttered by our father and jingoistic leader,
Punicum and Ten Wenmen, in the year 6,
when the Mayan calendar first was discovered.
Thank you.
And as the calendar was discovered,
we realized here at Cathedral Central we needed plans.
Plans were in order.
We need to get ready to leave this place,
which we have left our urine-infested and toxic wastes for so long.
And now it's time to split it like an old port-a-booty,
which we have no further use for.
I don't want some of you out there, if you are out there,
some of you are right in here, where I keep you.
And I will not let you go from this minute forward.
You're stuck.
You're stuck in this box.
A box of your own creation, friends.
And as you wander in this creation,
this box, this trapezoid you have created
from your own silly iniquities and stupid, irresponsible actions,
you look inside, back inside,
and you see that there is,
there is an answer to your prayers, if you will,
to your beckonings, if you want,
your innermost desires for spiritual tranquility and bliss.
Ah, yes, friends, and I think you know the answer to the P.O. box
of where you can get that bliss all over yourself.
Friends, just, you got that pencil ready?
If you want to know all the rest,
just write to Bob at
Post Office Box 140306
Dallas, Texas 75214
You can also, that's Box 1403-06
1403-06 Dallas, Texas 75214
WSB-106-7252
www.subgenius.com
And friends, I've got some other addresses for you,
because, but we, I almost forgot
the Subgenius Zine Reviews Department
and upcoming shows.
Upcoming shows, well, Memorial Day weekend,
there's this giant subgenius revival in Seattle, Washington,
with every preacher,
Pope David and Meyer, myself,
Doctors for Bob, and Papa Joe Mama,
and Pope S. Lilith is sponsoring that and preaching,
and it will be just a, I don't know who else,
and June 10th, June 10th, friends, in Portland, Oregon,
the Lemurian race shall rise again up out of the ocean,
out of Portland Sound,
and shall grab out for news, subgenius,
souls, new minds and hearts,
that we can squeeze like sponges,
and get that red stuff all over everything,
and of course, X Day, friends,
X Day, Dos Equis, Double X Day,
the great double cross, 1998,
the July 5th weekend in Sherman, New York,
the sensual and sensationalistic,
if you ever wondered how weird
400 of Bob's most devoted followers are,
and some of them naked,
your vivid and unrelenting answer
can be right there in front of you,
July 5th, 1999,
the end of the world.
Friends, it's coming.
By the way, this is Zug's rift in the background music,
with, I think with Joe Newman also.
Friends, here's a quick zine review,
because it's a quick subgenius zine,
but this is a book, and it's called,
The Yeti Times,
and it's a printed amateur publication,
with excellent graphics and art,
called The Yeti Times,
and The Yeti Times is available for like a buck in stamps,
from Post Office Box 07442.
Got that pencil ready?
That's Post Office Box 07442,
Milwaukee, Wisconsin,
53207.
That's Milwaukee, Y,
W, WI, WI, 53207,
produced by Yetis for Bob.
It's a subgenius zine called The Yeti Times.
It's fully illustrated,
and actually is a great contact point
for many other subgenius zines.
It is for mature audiences only,
like most,
subgenius materials,
and, ah, yes, friends,
it's so good, good, good.
Let's close with our,
tonight's X Day hymn,
off of the X Day music tape.
Don't even know for sure which one's gonna come up.
Let's just hit it by random, friends.
Ah, yes.
Good night, little droogies.
Happy trails to you
Till we meet again
Keep smiling till then
Happy trails to you
Till we meet again
Keep smiling till then
Happy trails to you