Tell St. Peter at the Golden Gate that you hate to make him wait, but you just gotta have another
Subgenius Hour of Slack!
What?
Uh, yes, dear friends, we're working on the Subgenius Online History class at maybelogic.net,
and therefore this Hour of Slack number 1,199 will actually be a rerun of Hour of Slack number 569,
which is actually a rerun of the ESO Swamp Radio Show from February 27th, 1997.
What are you?
Nobody.
Are you blind?
What are you?
What manner of beast is that?
What the hell are you?
What are you?
Every man and woman is a star.
And that's why Dave's head is a glowing gasp.
A gasp.
All of their heads were glowing bags of hydrogen, and they walked around town wearing their bags.
And one little day, one little man said,
Your head is much bigger than mine.
You must have a much bigger bag.
Everybody is a star.
And yes, that man was the mayor of the town.
He had a great yellow giant for a head.
Unfortunately,
Dave, the village idiot
had what is known as a dwarf
star for a head
in fact it had collapsed
so suddenly and compacted
so tremendously
that it, although it had not quite
formed a black hole
the density of
the head of Dave
you know every man and woman is a star
Dave was a dwarf star
well one
square
oh millimeter or so
of the interior of Dave's head
was of such a dense
molecular, densely packed
molecular
structure that
that tiny tiny fragment
would be heavy enough on our planet
that if you dropped it
it would bore its way all the way
to the center of the earth
this is why Dave was not allowed
in most towns
his head being
altogether heavier than the
most nearby planets
his presence
tended to cause disruptions
in the orbits of other
inhabited
star systems
other planets that might have even cities
and old
civilizations that had lasted for thousands
of years
merely the gravitational
waves caused by the thickness
of Dave's skull
would destroy and wipe out
these entire civilizations
and that's why when Dave
would beg for a dollar
for a bottle of beer
most people in town
would go ahead and give him the dollar
spare change buddy
what the hell are you
cause every time he got a headache
everybody's got some kind of personal deformity
so my bag's a little bigger than yours
you know
and what's the difference between helium and hydrogen
my fucking corpus callosum
excuse my language
oh my god it's not even 12 o'clock
hmm
the townsfolk and the other
planets
civilized galactic federations
and so forth had to pretty much put up with Dave
because whenever he got a headache
it would cause earthquakes in their capital city
oh my time alone's doing nothing
this except he's doing nothing
this is aspen she's doing nothing
this old idiot herbal extract ain't doing nothing
I feel like my skull is spinning
I feel like the weight of the universe
is expanding out through my very
very very
my back
did you ever feel that way friend
did you ever feel like
the problems of the world
were weighing down on you so much
that your head was self collapsing
into dwarf star density
have you ever felt that way
well if you haven't
then you're probably not a subgenius
it's so dense in here
you lucky bastard
it's just like the yolk of an egg
she bastard
what did I forget
you can't say she bastard
she
it's like
like a little psychic yellow of an egg in here
it keeps me warm
it keeps me nurtured
that's all I need
I am a star
see everybody's brain
I don't even know those people
I don't need to drink Tylenol
I don't even snort that stuff
I'm different than that
I'm going here in my back
we've taken good care to raise you up here Dave
oh by the way
Dave Dave
there's something we needed to
Dave there's something
I hate to interrupt your
you
your fun little monologue
there but
you've heard about cloning and so forth
and the replaceable body parts
and well you actually Dave
are the clone of a master Dave
who is a very rich powerful man
who happens to have
just destroyed his liver through hard drink
and it's time for his replacement liver
and yes you were cloned from him
and have been raised as a poor bethlehemian
and a pathetic street wino
just kept alive
you and several other clones
several others have already been used for other parts
Dave I'm afraid your life is
the goal of your life is
come around
it's time for you to give up
that which you were bred for
which in this case is your liver
wait a minute
isn't cloning wonderful
too bad nobody cloned you eh Dave
wait a minute
you'd love the rich Dave
he looks just like you
and runs General Motors now I think
what
now wait a minute
I don't know whether I'm having a psychic echo spasm
or if I'm having some kind of corticolizing
I'm so on the corner
and I'm panhandling
and I see your voice
that say I'm cloned from somebody else
who's rich and powerful
and come on out from behind there
my little leg yoke protects me
my little helium hydrogen exchange key
how could it break in here
hey
hey where'd he go
hey a little voice
little garbage can
come back here
man
nobody around here
yoohoo
maybe I'm just sucking a weird dream or something
I gotta stop doing them methamphetamines
I'm just ripping my brain apart
I gotta stop snoring gasoline
I gotta stop
licking the bottoms of these allspice
nail clippings in my undercheeks
and re-spooking
I gotta do something
I gotta do something man
maybe
maybe it's a self-concussive realization
maybe it wasn't a little voice
maybe I
I am cloned from some rich and powerful person
I could take over
I could take over the church of the subgenius man
and make a lucrative mola
yeah
I'll be standing on top of everything
I could
topple a little petty giant
knit a little tie
that little two boots
wherever I'm staying
it's weird how these little voices in my head
always sound like him
I don't know
well gentlemen
as you can see
by our subject
lonesome cowboy Dave
the syringe implantable transponder
works beautifully
he seems to think
that there are voices in his head
in this case my voice was used
of course as the project chief
but it is amazing
is it not gentlemen
that our general electric tiny microchip
the size of a grain of rice
placed underneath his skin
injected with a
a vaccination
in his childhood
has allowed us
to dictate
as voices in his head
his entire life
you know there's no difference
in principle
gentlemen
between being forced
to carry a microchip
in your plastic card
in your wallet
or the little pellet
that we put in Dave's teeth
the principle
that big sister
has the right to track you
is inherent
in both
and the only difference
is a layer
of skin
or in Dave's teeth
in this case a skull
a very very thick
layer of bony carapace
let's turn the voices back on
Dr. Reverend Steng
I was wondering
yes yes
there seem to be
I've noticed in the literature
yes Dr. Bronner
I read all of your papers
and I am quite convinced
that what you have done
to this man
is a remarkable disservice
I see and hear
a picture perfect example
of a man whose personality
which was not in a good shape
to begin with
has been totally destroyed
and has been destroyed
immersed in your
falter world religion
you expect us to experiment
on animals
poor innocent animals
why not
I agree
Dave volunteered
for this thing
I see nowhere
in the transcript
you have given me
an example of Dave
ever giving his permission
written or otherwise
for you to conduct
this experiment on him
it seems totally remarkable
to me
how a man of your stature
could conduct
such an experiment
and receive grants
and so much money
to do it
Dr. Bronner
I think you've heard
the experiment
and I think
if you're going
to make an omelette
you have to
break a few eggs
I don't see
I mean
to a certain extent
this Dave
lonesome cowboy Dave
character
is little more
than a human egg
an omelette
so to speak
bubbling on the hot
sidewalk of life
how could you call
a human being
a fellow human being
an omelette
he's not a human being
he's a subgenius
I'm sorry
but your rules
don't apply to us
Dr. Stein
I agree with your work
can I say one word
yes Dr. Sotomayor
I appreciate
what I have been doing
the last few years
especially
I mean
Mark of the Year
to work with
lonesome cowboy Dave
and other people
Einstein
they infect
the whole Cleveland
project
I would like to know
if you can help me
find a possible
bank grant
for I have
a similar project
a country project
I would like to do
a similar size city
in southern Japan
oh well
I'll tell you
the investment opportunities
if you will connect
of course
I assume there's
fetus research
in your country
probably considerable
amount of fetus
organ trade
going on there
yes
I have no problem
with human donor
have you also
considered
genetic cloning
research
cloning research
for
to
well that's another thing
Dr. Sotomayor
there was quite out of line
complaining about
so-called human being
even if Dave
were a human being
this is a clone
of a human being
the original Dave
the master Dave
sitting over here
to my right
yeah that's very
very nice tie
you have there
Captain Dave
thanks for having me
the master Dave
there obviously
he was born
with the same rights
according to human being
or a subtenuous
his clone
however
I mean
how can one person
have more than
one set of rights
so
therefore the clone
being more or less
the same person
is going to have to
find his own
set of rights
Ivan do you mind
if I get a little
personal
postulation in here
I'll show a little
of my own perspective
after all being
the clone
donor
Lonesome Cowboy Dave
is not a human being
in the same way
you or I
would call
say perhaps
the Reverend Hare
or
Dr. Sagamoto
a human being
he's an experiment
conducted by the church
to reincur
the reprogramming
of thousands more people
and to stop this
X day thing
that we've been
we've all been talking about
that's all I have to say
Dr. Brunner can complain
all he wants
but the process
has been set in motion
Dave is contagious
everywhere he goes
in the city of Cleveland
we're going to see
the same
progress
in the disease
the virus
if you want to call it
a disease
we like to think of it
as a
new
oh just some
we're adding
some artistic
details
to the
fabric
of human reality
that's all
we're just doing
a little window dressing
improving
on God's
handiwork
why not
God gave us
that right
did he not
he made us
as unto gods
every man and woman
is a star
I believe
our secret leader
Alistair Crowley
Hubbard once said
I remember
I sit there
Parsons
at that nudist
oh yes
yes sir
Dr. Stefano Grappelli
of the Institute
of Psychic Research
in Rome
I was wondering
if you found
any sort of
repercussion
with the
lonesome cowboy Dave
perhaps
any psychic
example of violence
or trouble
with police
or
such a
psychological
exacerbation
yes
I'm glad
that you asked
that question
there was
an extremely
unusual
side effect
to the treatment
by which
whenever Dave
would sneeze
for a minute
plates
for instance
in the kitchen
would fly
across the room
jump off the shelves
and smash
against the opposite
wall
one time
we were in the
front office
and the files
flew out of the
file cabinet drawers
every time Dave
sneezed
of course
we had to
put him down
whenever he was
around any kind
of expensive
equipment
out on the street
most people
hardly notice
there's so much
violence
mugging
down there
on the level
the level
where he
where the
experiments
are usually
conducted
Petri dish
one
you know
the sidewalk
I would like
to ask a question
also of you
I am from
the institute
in Moscow
I won't need
to mention
the name
of the institute
where I'm familiar
with the
parapsychological
research
I've been doing
oh yes comrade
I would like
to say that
after the
upcoming election
will be a whole
different situation
in the form of
a union
and I'm
the common
of all of
the states
would be involved
in and
after what
you have said
reprogramming
making people
more malleable
pliable
will find
have to a
different problem
is there some
way we can
use your
research
and perhaps
make the
whole of
former
Soviet Union
similar
well comrade
as you know
Dobbsco
is marketing
the as we
call it
the electronic
leash
of these
implantable
biochips
to be any
corporate
or governmental
entity
we'd happily
assist
of course
our microchips
do have the
Dobbs trademark
built in
so that
although they
the subject's
allegiance
will be up
to the choice
of the
corporation
or governmental
entity
nevertheless
as you can
certainly understand
it's sort of
like the
Coca-Cola company
is going to
sell coke
in Russia
that's fine
but they're
going to have
their logo
on it
well
your people
will be
mind controlled
according to
your plans
however they
will respond
to the
smiling
face
image
of
Bob
that would
be
very
that is
fine with
us
thank you
very much
for answering
me
and as we
said
these
computer
chips
will link
the individual
up to a
vast
computer
database
so that
we can
in fact
follow
the
subject
and follow
their spending
their voting
habits
pretty much
their sexual
habits
up to a
point
we can
in fact
dictate
their sexual
habits
through the
voice in
the head
technique
we have
had some
subjects
they get
their ideas
from the
movies
or comic
books
or something
they pull
all their
teeth out
so as
they think
that this
will silence
the silent
radio in
their head
of course
that does
affect the
resonance
and we
have to
increase
the amplification
when they
pull out
all of
their teeth
but it's
rather
pointless
to tell
the truth
it's sad
I've noticed
Dave down
there is
bleeding
at the mouth
the one down
on the sidewalk
not the one
here in the
boardroom
certainly
I don't think
we're getting
enough
can you
enhance this
picture somehow
so we can
all see it
a little better
and bring up
the volume
somehow
zoom in on
screen 3
there
if you
pull in
close
you'll see
Dave
yanked all
his teeth
out with
those pliers
and has
thrown them
down in
the gutter
where our
servo robots
have retrieved
them for
the master
Dave here
in case he
ever needs
a new
mold
Dave
we're
back
it didn't
do you
any good
you pulled
your teeth
out for nothing
Dave
you're an idiot
I came to the
church
you didn't love
Bob enough
Dave
I'm gonna love
him more
listen to this
you guys
he'll believe
anything
Dave
you sinned
you pulled out
all your teeth
for nothing
that looked stupid
as well as
I was stupid
I ain't never
gonna find me
a day like this
Bob
was
but don't
cry Dave
Bob has a new
job for you
he has a new
bride for you
Dave
Bob has brought
you a new bride
see that goat
over there
in that pen
that she goat
over in that pen
that's your new
wife Dave
that's Hogan's
goat
you are the
husband of
Hogan's
she goat
last night
you told me
that was some
kind of weird
goat they was
gonna clone
and then you
said it was
the goat
that was using
to catch
nerve gas
and now you're
telling me
it's my wife
a fella's
gonna get me
a nice six foot
seven yeti
woman
that's good
no I'm
so confused
do you have
a problem
with the goat
Dave
would you
rather us
pick you
another wife
how about
this giant
this gigantic
eyebrow
mantis
an eyebrow
man
I can't
see it
my mind's
left eye
stroked
the eyebrow
mantis
slide
into his
retina
there
okay he should
be seeing
the uh
the giant
eyebrow
mantis
turn the
erection
knob up
to ten
he's gonna
be he's
terrified of
the mantis
and at the
same time
he's he's
sexually
aroused
oh my god
get that thing
away from me
this always
I'll bet you're
a Leo
I'll get away
get away from
you
oh my god
hey
so you see
gentlemen
not only
is the
experiment
oh get
away
get away
as you can
see gentlemen
the experiment
is not only
a success
but a lot
of fun
for we
researchers
you can
pull the
strings
of the
subject
as if he
were
a little
puppet
dancing
down there
on that
hot sidewalk
in the
inner city
surrounded
by the
broken
beer
bottles
and the
other
bums
and losers
while we
up here
in our
skyscraper
sitting at
our
computer
keyboards
may
make him
jerk
and
twitch
our own
little
pathetic
marionette
isn't he
and
he
suspects
of course
in fact
he knows
perfectly
well
his
state
station
in life
that's
what
religion
is for
boys
praise
Bob
eh
and
thank you
for the
excellent
demonstration
and quite
an illuminating
slideshow
it was
now
we take
credit cards
well I think
that's what
we're all
asking right
now
what will
the next
project
be and
how much
do you
need
all I
is to
fill the
receptor
holes
my friend
oh you
ask me
what I
need
I just
need to
fill those
receptor
holes
they used
to be
so full
those holes
in my
brain
they had
just the
perfect
molecule
fit
right into
that little
locked
place
now
the brain
holes
are empty
the brain
holes
are empty
tonight
the brain
is gonna
have to
make its
own
the moon
is shining
my eyes
are bright
but
the master
molecule
is gone
you look
pretty sharp
pretty cute
but you
ain't going
nowhere
anywhere
in that brain
hole suit
you got a
you say
you look
so cute
in that
brand new
suit
you think
you got
some
place
to go
you ain't
going
nowhere
so just
sit down
in the
chair
and let
Bob Dobbs
tell you
the truth
I told
you when
you were
ten
and I
told you
when you
were twelve
and I
told you
as you
were coming
on
up
when you
look
scoured
my son
think of
that
glimmering
pipe
my work
will be
done
I'm
leaving
soon
I am
there is
a great
mesh
in your
brain
and this
mesh
is composed
of tiny
holes
and these
have a
certain
shape
those are
receptor
holes
and they're
responsible
for your
sense of
self
and well
being
and pleasure
there's a
certain shape
of a molecule
that'll fall
into those
receptor holes
and make
you feel
real good
and that
shape is
a shape
oddly enough
of what
looks to us
just like a
common pipe
like a
doctor
grab
out
pipe
and that's
the way
if you can
find some
way to get
tiny pipe
shaped molecules
to fill
those receptor
holes inside
that
vacant mesh
in your head
well you'll
probably feel
so much better
that you'll be
able to do
better on the
job
get a better
become like
a great
stock whiz
or something
and get rich
overnight
on some
great idea
perfect vision
so of course
at this point
you're asking
hey man
where can I
get some of
them pipe
shaped molecules
is it like
a pill
or is it
something you
smoke
hey Bernice
I just want you
to try this
look what I got
at the pharmacological
well it's not
a pill
it's not a pipe
you place it
in your third eye
it's the
virtual
heart noise
trial
of
the
it's the
emperor's
new pipe
you just
here
you see this
thing
that I'm
holding in my
hand
there's
nothing really
in my hand
but it's a
virtual pipe
there's no
virtual in that
pipe
hey man
let's all
like smoke
some of what's
in this
pipe
in my hand
oh yeah
yeah man
I see that
pipe in your
hand
yeah let me
have some of
that virtual
oh whoa
whoa
I tried
marijuana
one time
and I tried
LSD
bananas
mixed with
coca-cola
and aspirin
but
man
and jimson
weed
and nyquil
but
whoa
this
virtual
pipe
oh
oh man
I am
going
inside
oh
far in
the pipe
is feeling
really man
the pipe
is feeling
really
it's pointing
I'm like
caved in
I'm caved
in man
I'm so deep
I'm like a
I am speed
lunking
dude
I am like
in the magma
oh help
sir
oh
my lungs
are crushed
man
I feel
that pressure
whoa
I am so
low
I think
man I wonder
maybe I'm too low
maybe I'm getting
too deep
who are you
am I ever
going to come up
who are you
hey man
don't come up
too fast
your head
will explode
you'll get
the
beans
whoa
wow
these anti
drugs
are so much
better than
those
cheap
conspiracy
street drugs
I don't want
to get high
anymore
ever since
I learned
the word
of Bob
I've been ready
not only to
come back
down to
earth
but to go
below
the sidewalk
the sewers
below
the upper
crust
below the
lower crust
down all
the way
yeah
I've learned
how to go
down
since I
gave up
those
getting high
kind of drugs
Bob's dragging
me all
the way
down
oh the
pressure's
getting
really
really hot
down here
you know
where Bob's
taking me
I'm
digging it
it's really
hot
what are
these
these flames
somehow
they're not
consuming my
flesh
but yet
they're burning
wow
this is
these Bob
pills
and this
virtual
Bob
pipe
this stuff's
really intense
I'm like
having a
before death
experience
I'm having
an
out of
inside
planet
experience
man
I think I am
too
too low
I probably
need to come
back up
man
is there
anything I can
take to
counteract
this non
drug
that I
didn't
take
hey
ref
what are
you doing
here man
crouched
on the
floor
isn't this
the coolest
club you've
ever been
in
oh man
I already
had three
multi-cassions
and I don't
even know
what the hell
that is
yeah
this stuff's
great
yeah
whatever it
is
it's free
too
yeah
where'd he
get it
from Bob
well I mean
it's free
once you
join up
you know
this guy
charged me
15 bucks
for one hit
he told me
it's free
once I
joined up
geez man
well you're
joined up
now here
take
see the
pipe
in my
hand
there's not
really a
pipe in
his hand
yeah
but they
believe
there is
a pipe
in his
hand
see the
pipe
here
take
my
pipe
Dave
have a
big
hit
of what's
in that
pipe
there is
no pipe
and there
is nothing
in the
pipe
but the
placebo
effect
is so
much
more
powerful
than any
real
drug
that the
subgenius
victim
is now
becoming
so low
so in
there
that he
it is as
if he is
looking up
from eight
feet
underground
feel like
they're
made of
mud
feels like
he's laying
at the
bottom
of a
hole
in a
box
underground
in the
dark
and the
top of
the box
is only
about an
inch
from his
nose
and it's
a real
tight
fit
and he
doesn't
know
how
to
and he
what
he's
doing
the
meat
shackles
give me
the body
like an
old
shoe
welcome
to the
other
side
remember
me
Benny
Gordon
back
in
New
York
I was
the guy
who
stole
your
shoes
and hit
him
in
the
garbage
can
then
you
struck
me
in
the
face
remember
yeah
I
died
later
no
thanks
to
you
yeah
side when they let me in Bellevue, they said I'd never be the same. I starved to death.
I thought about you when I died. This don't look like the green carpets coming out. Kind
of looks blood red. Hello, Dave. I'm sure you don't remember me. I was originally a
tiny puppy that you tortured when you were six years old. Remember me now? Now I am Dog
Demon, the bearer of vengeance for all torturers of tiny puppies. And meet my friend, the legless
grasshopper. We've all come to tell you that we remember all the things you did in life.
Yes.
I don't think this is going to be very pleasant. If I'm supposed to recount all my incidences,
so far I've only had three incidences. Oh, bad. I wonder what's next. Who's that weird
looking woman? Grandma, I've never done nothing to you, really. I'm sorry about the stove.
I'm sorry about the stove. It's too late for forgiveness now, Dave. It's too late now.
It's too late.
She's on this figure and burned just the way I left her when I ran out of the house.
Dave, remember your habit of sticking chewing gum under theater seats?
Yes.
I am a soul who once reached under the seat and touched your germ-ridden gum. Later to
die of a cold.
I'm sorry, bro.
You know, I'm trying to keep myself clean and have good personal attributes like that
and stuff, but you know, those things are so bourgeois.
Hey, Dave, remember me, Butch?
Yeah, Butch.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, I bet you're sorry now, Dave.
Get away.
I didn't mean nothing.
Maybe you shouldn't have stuck up behind me and pulled that little trick on me that one
time, Dave.
You know my personality, man.
Push me in front of that car, Dave.
Everybody in school knew I was a joke.
Everybody thought that I just fell in front of that car, Dave.
Were you jealous just because I was bigger and tougher and got all the girls and got decent
grades and had friends and had parents and had money and had a life?
Were you jealous, Dave?
What, you need to look at the white?
Yes.
I hated you all.
I hated that puppy for having hair.
I hated Grandma for having food.
And I hated you for having a car and girl friends.
In fact, I still hate you.
And that's why I don't mind being here.
Dave, meet everyone of whom you have ever been jealous.
They are here to gloat at your misfortune.
Thousands and thousands of people gloating, gloating at your total humiliation here in
the endless flames of, yes, let's say, in hell, Dave.
You're dead and you're in hell.
You see him, Facius, and you point fingers at me.
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
And here are snapshots and tape recordings of every stupid or humiliating thing you've
ever done.
Here, the files of every callous and thoughtless thing you've ever said or done.
Oh, man, they're flying by so fast.
Here, every betrayal.
I'm going to take you on a little animal.
Here, every lie.
Here, every time you've masturbated in an impure manner.
Oh, man, my eyes.
I'm going blind.
I didn't know we had such good cameras, did you, in all those?
You're all filling station restrooms, eh, Dave?
All right.
I don't know, but...
Here, the endless file of the times you picked your nose.
Here, the file of the times you wet your bed.
Here, the files of the times you didn't wash behind your ears.
Everything, everything in your entire life has been reconstructed, and you're going to
have to relive every single moment of it over and over and over again inside this little
black box.
You can read me and we're going to remind the sort of YouTubers that you'll share your
blackontos.
Oh, man, I went back to my house just to talk to Kristin Mom.
She thought it was her ride on the field where everyone thought I couldn't go ten mejores.
Heinz says, oh, Nick, you returned two years ago to theosters.
Steinhardt  localities??
mort merely strawberry?
What the fact is, I had insulation here.
site number kidding me out!?
anyI don't know.
Can we give Dave a chance to live his life again?
Do you think he's learned his lesson?
Oh, please, good sirs and dames.
Let's flip a coin and see whether he gets the eternal salvation or not.
All right, place the giant coin on the giant thumb.
Set the catapult.
Three, two, one, flip the coin.
It is flying.
Look at it.
Flying miles up.
Up, spinning end over end.
Dave is pouring bullets of suspense out as the coin slopes.
Oh, it's getting slower and slower.
It's falling.
It's falling back down to earth.
It's coming down and it's landed right exactly on edge and it rolled and it came to rest and the coin is on edge.
Hi.
How shall Dave's fate?
Be decided now.
It's just more.
We'll have to go through the suspense and flip the coin again.
Okay, there it goes.
It's just slow motion.
Okay.
Oh, that.
And so the endless suspense went on for another million years as Dave waited to find out whether any of the coins would actually land.
And one day, a million years later, it landed heads up.
Dave, you have won.
You have won.
You were allowed to dig your way out of your coffin and back to the earth in the year 1 million AD.
You have been forgiven by God and Satan and are resurrected into eternal life in whatever is left on the planet of your birth, where you now claw your way back up.
There he's tearing the coffin open.
He's digging his, choking his way.
But we're using his front teeth to dig his way like an entrenching tool.
And he's finally made out of the grave.
He's coming through the surface of the graveyard.
Dave is free.
Dave has escaped.
He has literally dug his way out of hell.
I'm free.
Hey, where can you get a good sandwich around here?
Inch and Juter Pie.
I might get one of those for you.
I'm Point .
How much.
I'm afraid of the knockout if he lives and dies outside this body.
I haven't some.
I'm spare.
I'm free.
Hey, baby. How you doing?
You know, I got...
Hey, how'd you just appear here at this spot?
You know, I just had some pretty strange things happen to me.
And, you know, this beautiful, gorgeous babe just appears as I imagine to think about it.
It's called serendipity, Dave.
Serendipity.
Serendipity. Or slack. You can call it either one.
Serendipity. I remember them guys when I was a little kid.
They used to be in the Thomas Brothers, you know.
You know, and one of them died of a heroin overdose, I think.
Yeah, serendipity. I could die of a heroin overdose.
That's my name, serendipity. How did you know?
I didn't know, sir. I just kind of guessed it.
Yeah, you know, I'm one of them intuitive kind of guys.
You know, one of your strong, silent types.
Yeah. Wow.
Hope I ain't smelling too strong. I just crawled out of a graveyard.
I think it kind of smells manly. I kind of like it.
You know, some people say it smells more like a goat.
But you in the mood for a cup of coffee?
Well, sure. Espresso?
Yeah. How about a cappuccino?
Can we snuff it?
Yeah, baby. We can do anything you want to.
Especially with legs like that, we can snuff it too.
Wow.
Is that your naturalistic hair? Or is that some kind of falsified hair?
I never saw that hue on a woman or on a human being.
It's virtual hair.
Virtual hair?
Yes, virtual hair.
You mean like it's feely-reely?
It's sort of like a holodeck hair.
You mean if I touch it, like, then I would automatically experience the sensation you was talking about in the aforementioned article?
Well, kind of, yes. Like a hologram.
Kind of, yes?
Yes, kind of.
What about, you sure that ain't a merkin?
You sure that ain't a Bob Dobbs feely-reely virtual reality merkin?
It really is.
Oh, okay.
It's a real merkin.
Ha.
You just lied to me.
You know, I'm wondering again.
It's a real virtual merkin.
Oh.
So then...
Does some of this seem too good to be true, Dave?
Yeah, well, the birds are singing and a woman in virtual work came up and just tried to ask me out on a date.
Are you looking at gift horse in the mouth, Dave?
No, I'm looking at...
I mean, we let you out of hell to relive your life and now you're complaining that maybe it's all too perfect or something?
No, I was just looking at the bus.
Bus stop.
I was reading the cards on the bus stop.
Snacko Funeral Home.
Georgia's Beans.
Hey, wait a minute.
Where'd the girl go?
Oh, whatever.
Well, Dave, we'll go ahead and admit it.
It is.
We put you in another one of those worlds where whatever you imagine is whatever you get.
And as long as you were feeling pretty good, you were imagining pretty good things and getting the girls and so forth.
But what are you imagining now that we've browbeaten you down and made you feel insecure?
Again.
Again, eh, Dave?
What kind of reality are you creating for yourself now, you poor, pathetic loser, eh?
He's surrounded by snakes and hush puppies and old, rotten...
I know this is all full of it now.
I'm surrounded by snakes and hush puppies.
And everybody knows you don't eat no hush puppies with no snake.
You eat no snake.
You eat cougar pie and...
We confused him.
And his entire...
Reality collapsed around him.
A huge snake.
We made him afraid.
And that of which he was most afraid surrounded him.
The moral of the story is, kids, you make your own reality.
Every man and woman is a star.
And if that was so, then how come it hurts when you stub your toe and how come your head ain't on fire?
These are the eternal questions.
To be answered only by the eternal verities.
Death and taxes and Bob.
The three things that you can depend on.
Old ragged bones.
Old ragged shoes.
I am a vagabond.
A vagabond.
Free as the wind.
Hey, buddy over here.
I got some snakes and hush puppies.
You hungry?
You feel like curling your toes up and squirming?
Come on over here.
I got it.
Hey, you over there.
I got lemonade, too.
You look at my parts.
Hey, you look like a demon.
You, you.
Say.
Say, Dave.
I'm a demon.
I noticed that you took all those lemons we handed you and made lemonade.
We noticed that you had that glass that was half empty and magically made it half full.
Yeah, and I got the one-eared eyeball pointing down like many convicts do.
But that doesn't explain it.
How come my life is such a mess, man?
I'm done squirming by you.
I bought your lemons with real U.S. money.
David, it's part of the seeking.
It's part of the journey.
You have to pay your dues.
In order to truly soar through heaven, you must first embrace the porcelain bowls of hell.
Yeah, I'm like some kind of mythic knight, Percival guy.
Yeah, I don't mind, sir.
Yes, it's the holy grail of slack.
And you're getting so close having gone through the terrible gauntlet of anti-slack.
Surely you must be almost to your goal of enlightenment.
Nirvana.
And it's true.
Here comes the nirvana.
By the way, Dave, you knew that nirvana means nothing, right?
Yeah, I knew it meant nothing.
And that's what I'm ready for, man.
Life's a nothing.
Because every time I get me something good, it turns out to be something bad.
And every time I get me something bad, it turns out worse.
So it's like a shifting sandy beach of $20 bills.
It keeps on changing and changing and changing and changing.
And I don't need nothing, blessed sweet oblivion.
I just need to get out of here.
Here then is your reward, Dave.
You asked for it from Bob, God, and all the others.
Back into the little black box eight feet underground in the cold and dark.
Here, Dave, is your nirvana.
No longer to face the woes and travails of life.
You may lie here in total slack and repose.
Yes, this is the slack.
This is the slack that Bob promised.
An eternity perfectly aware inside a closed black box, feeling the corruptigating worms
shoo their way through your desiccated, decaying flesh and finally to feel your bones dissolve
into powder as the box caves in and you have achieved nirvana and final enlightenment as
worm experiment.
Thank you.
You're happy, aren't you?
Maybe if only I could speak voice like that, she may even be the life and this is-
parents.
Rebecca just gave her a pair of Speck placards as free.
She didn't know how to survive, telling her that she was the Creepchat for the
last time.
He sailed in the 701
And anybody knew
There was something in his face
Loneliness could not erase
No thoughts, no sensations
No feelings, no recurrent memory
It's simply a moldy spatula
And those little worms kind of itch a little bit
As they crawl in and out
Oh yeah, yeah
Just me and the worms
Like a broken pup
He looked up from his cup
And drank his morning coffee
Wiped the dribble from his chin
There is nothing
Nada and nada and nada
Except
When his eyes met mine
He made a little whine
He came with an angel too
Then he whispered
I hate you
Our nada
Who aren't in nada
Nothing f ee thy name
Tha mean bhdus
Tha mued bhdus
Tha I those bdus
Tha toe bdus
Tha d ft be Eve
Neda dc
Tha bee b d overd
Tha brain bdus
Tha feet bdus
Thy hands bdus
The will
wouldn't be enough
Ya say you not having boyfriend
Hoy!
How did he know?
Once I had some pets
I let them starve to death
It was a funny little monkey
And a big white Easter bunny
They lived in little cages
And sometimes in rages
I'd turn them upside down
And drag my monkey all around
You shouldn't have dragged me around like that, Dave
You're my best friend
I drag my monkey all around.
Now ye shall be dragged around.
Look at monkey dragging Dave around his cage.
Let him be dragged.
Let him all be dragged.
Let his armpit hairs be braided by a tired chimpanzee.
No?
Yes.
Contaminated.
No.
Don't do it, man.
Contaminated.
Folks, you've been listening to ESO Radio and...
Einstein's Secret Orchestra with the...
With the Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave and myself and Michelle and special guest this week,
the Reverend Ivan Stang and the Princess We Are Doe.
Contaminated.
Being contaminated.
Contamination.
Warning.
Confused.
wnGame Informative.
Warning.
cry out, are you looking at my neck?
They shall be struck down by the Archangel
Bill.
Praise Bill.
The Bill genius
must be lax.
There is only
one gene that will work, though.
It's critical we get the gene.
We must not let Bob
get to the gene before the ceremony.
The gene must still be a virgin
when the time is nigh for
its arisal.
We need a virgin gene
clean of any impurities.
That's the only way this will work.
Where can we find the untainted gene?
The unsullied, pure
DNA formulae?
Oh, man.
I know where you can find it.
Where?
Where, man? Tell us.
It's in my head.
It's in my
words. Words
are like worms.
And they crawl
in your brain. I think he's right.
And they wriggle.
I think he does have it.
I think he has the perfect
undetaminated, completely
crushed gene.
It's like
helium and hydrogen
in the stars in your brain, man.
It's true. This man's brain
is so densely compacted that
the interior of it is like a dwarf star.
We've found what we need.
He's the gene genie.
He wasn't a pathetic loser
after all.
He was the one.
After all his tortures and torment,
it turned out that the gene,
the perfect, unsullied,
untainted gene, was
in fact buried inside
lonesome cowboy Dave's head.
Praise Bob, the world is safe.
Remove the gene.
This will make Dr. Von Neumann very happy,
Reverend Stang.
This will make Dr. Von Neumann very happy.
We have retrieved the gene.
We have retrieved the gene
from inside the head of lonesome cowboy Dave.
He's dead now.
And we, the conspiracy of overlords,
disguised as rebels
against the conspiracy of overlords,
have once again won.
The world is indeed our oyster.
The world is our oyster,
one might say.
Here it's clam or some sort of shellfish.
We all enjoy shellfish.
Let's have some more, shall we?
Yes, let's slip a few fresh in there.
More raw planets down our throats.
We have no love.
We have no heart.
We have no, uh, what do we have?
Everything we need.
Is that Dave corpse?
Mumbling something again?
I thought we removed
the perfect gene from his head.
I thought he was dead now.
I told you before.
Do not leave the corpse dead.
If it does not become putrescent,
the experiment will not work
and he will come back to life.
Oh, my God.
Chop off its head
and stuff its mouth with garlic.
It's too late.
He's already eaten all the garlic
and chopped off his own head.
He's coming back to life.
And here he is,
lonesome cowboy Dave on guitar.
Lonesome cowboy Dave
and the...
The corruptigating worms.
There can only be one.
There can only be
one.
One.
As Dave,
the resurrected Dave,
without the perfect gene
and with his head now hollowed out,
emptied and expanded.
And his corpus callosum,
the perfect conical shape
so that we can impact it
with all the necessary documents.
He now freed
from his...
...tasks.
He rides off into the sunset
on his tricycle.
Side-settled,
wearing that funny conical hat,
thinking somehow
he has made it.
But in fact,
it's made him.
...
Ever feel like you should have just said
no to that magic
carpet ride to electric
ladyland?
Ever feel so heavy?
Ever feel like your thighs
are so sick your muscles are
weak and your neck
...
Ever feel disconnected and
completely alone?
Ever feel
corrugated worms
burrowing through your
follicles?
Well,
if you have,
we can't help you a bit.
But we can help you get
your mind off of it.
So just write for free information
from
the Church of the Subgenius.
Got that pencil?
You can find out
everything you need to know
about how to make money
off of your corruptigating worms
by writing to
b-b-b-b-bob
at
p.o.bikes
181-417
Cleveland Heights, Ohio
www.subgenius.com
All of the above was from
ESO's Swampy
Radio on WCSB Cleveland
from the old days,
the show of the late,
incredibly great Chaz Smith,
who also played half the instruments.
Praise Chaz.