I hit that kid in the crosswalk.
Please, look for pedestrians.
Think of the impact you could make.
A message from the Federal Health Service.
Give me a small snack.
There's a lady who's sure
All the glitters is gold
And she's buying
A stairway to heaven
When she gets there, she knows
What did she know?
That the stars are all closed
The words she conveyed, what she came for
When it makes me wonder
How does that affect your books?
A sign on the wall
That she wants to be shown
Cause you know
Sometimes words have to mean it
In a tree by the brook
There's a songbird who sings
Sometimes all of our thoughts are misgiven
And she's buying
A stairway to heaven
There's a songbird who sings
Sometimes all of our thoughts are misgiven
You're having fun this time
It won't go
In case you don't know
Goodbye from calling you to join in
It makes me wonder
And there's a thing I've been doing for a long time
A feeling I get when I look to the west
And my spirit is crying for leaving
In my book I have written
Rings of smoke through the tree
And the voice is a-throwing
To me
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Make the noise
Your cat is humming
And it won't go
In case you don't know
The Piper
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
It makes me wonder
Why you
Dear lady, can you hear the wind blow?
And did you know
The stairway lies on a whisperin' wing?
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
And it makes us wonder
Dear lady, can you hear the wind blow?
And did you know
Your stairway lies on the wind?
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
And she's finding the stairway to heaven
And it makes me wonder
It makes me wonder
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Dear lady, can you hear the wind blow?
Just a spring before the May Queen
Your stairway lies on a whisperin' wing
It makes me wonder
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
And it makes me wonder
And you might find
A sign of love and hope
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
A star that's so far from home
And what you may be of hope
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Who shines white light and wants to show
How everything still turns to gold
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
You'll ain't with many hearts
But you will come to you
And love's a boy of heart
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Good callin' fancy
And lovely it's not a far
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Instagram troll
Baba J Gracias
And love's a boy of heart
I'm on my way
The star we watch
Oh oh oh
I'm on my way
He's a tella
Ba oh ba
Look how far away
away to heaven.
To be continued...
by the conspiracy.
We were saying that we'd never see Palpatine on television
or read about him in the news.
No, for all we know, he could be like Karl Rove.
He could be Scott McClellan.
He could be...
Yeah, I mean, Bush is more like those little Chinese,
those obsequious followers of Palpatine,
the little Chinese acting aliens.
Oh, yeah.
You know which ones I mean with the very flat faces
and they wore Chinese-looking clothing?
The Trade Federation?
Yeah, and they even spoke in a kind of an odd Chinese-ish accent.
Yeah, that really blew me away, actually.
Like how blatantly...
Like, I don't know, what a blatantly racist Chinese stereotype
or caricature that was.
Didn't Lucas get in trouble for Jar Jar Binks?
Oh, Jar Jar...
Mesa...
Mesa Jar Jar Binks!
Ooh, yeah, Mesa...
We're trying to forget that one.
In order to ensure the security and continuing stability,
the Republic will be reorganized into the first galactic empire
for a safe and secure society.
So this is how liberty dies.
With thunderous applause.
The war is over.
Lord Sidious promised us peace.
We only want...
The Secret Service wouldn't let me get close enough to do any teabagging.
The Secret Service let me get close enough to Nancy Reagan
to be within slingshot distance.
Oh, man.
The good old days.
Hours...
Or maybe four or five hours earlier,
before I was inside the Republican convention as a reporter,
looking at Nancy Reagan,
I was on the stage of the Rock Against Reagan Yippie rally outside.
Wow.
Rock Against Reagan Yippies?
Opening for the dead Kennedys.
I didn't even know who they were.
Wow.
Maybe who we were.
We were famous in the 80s.
Wow.
Briefly.
Secretly famous.
Anyway, yeah, that was pretty weird.
When we...
When we got off the...
I said a bunch of stuff against the Republicans and the Democrats and the commies
and the aliens and everybody else.
And then we got off stage.
As I walked to my car, we were being followed and photographed by guys in suits.
And, of course, there were cops on horseback here and there
just kind of keeping order, I guess, and making their presence known.
Did you smile and wave to them?
I went home, changed my clothes, and joined my mom, who is a Republican delegate.
And...
I was a reporter for the Austin Chronicle, and we both walked in.
My Bob button set off the metal detectors.
So you have a background in journalism.
Not much of one.
I just wrote a few things for different magazines in the 80s.
I got to where I really try to avoid having any kind of real job, and I only serve Bob.
Once more.
The Sith will rule the galaxy.
We are the hands of America
Making our country strong
We are the heart of America
Singing a marching song
The rise of Benziacs of menace
Who America is
And life and love
We are Americans
Drummer, plumber, soda jerk
Strike up the band
We are Americans
Stoker, broker, barber, clerk
United we stand
We're a voting population
A free and equal nation
Where freedom rings for our community
Freedom from war and freedom from fear
Who fights the battles for the free?
The common man is the king of the free
The common man reaches
Teacher, engineer, driller, miller, financier
Who wins the final victory?
The common man
Common man with common sense
Our poor fathers did it
Liberty's life
With love and faith and fight
We will spread it
Strong in the right
Never to weaken
The king of the king
Fight
You're on the air.
I, uh, I was just wondering what the actual topping was because the radio waves got destroyed while I was talking.
Because Stang said it would be really exciting.
What, what, what, what?
For the topping, you have your choice of, uh, a variety of, uh, fruit-flavored preserves.
Fruit flurbs?
That's right.
Um, you also have your choice of, uh, actually there are no toppings.
There's no toppings?
No.
Oh, crikey.
Oh, blisters on the sore, on the sore back.
The topping was the impending war of the worlds, which is happening out at Brushwood Campground.
But the Martians aren't involved in this one.
It's just the exes, right?
Or is it the Martians again?
Hmm.
I think the Martians are like a servitor race of the exes.
Well, they do their job, that's for sure, on this planet.
Screwed the place up pretty good.
Made it ready to go.
And convinced everybody that...
It wasn't them.
Yep.
That's the oldest trick in the book.
That's what all those, like, type of power types always do.
They do something horrendous and then they point at the person next to them.
They go to great lengths to avoid, uh, being known.
Huh?
They go to great lengths to avoid being, uh, known.
They, uh, they cover up their...
They cover their tracks pretty well, you know?
They don't want you to know they exist.
And their tracks are slimy, too, like a slug's trail.
That's right.
That's the only way you can pick them up is with that slime trail.
Yep.
It doesn't matter, though, if you carry a big salt shaker with you.
They're...
They're not quite slug-like enough...
Yeah.
...to be killed by such a primitive technique.
Well, even if you try to kill them with such a primitive technique,
they do have certain things underwritten into their corpus...
their body, you know, thing where they can't be exposed.
I wish I could hear the rest of the conversation.
You sound so clear and yet you can't hear a damn thing, can you?
Well, there...
I have that, uh, that gasp...
...power generator providing electricity
because the conspiracy, you know, won't help us.
Hmm.
And I can barely hear over the gaspower generator.
When that thing...
When we run out of gas,
I'm gonna have to put old Bessie and old Bossy to work peddling it,
except that I already sold them.
So it's gonna be me peddling.
I won't be able to continue too much longer.
That's why I can barely hear.
Also, the ear on this side is going out.
The ear on this side of your head?
Or the ear on this side of the world?
Or, you know, I mean...
The ear on this side, are we speaking in a political spectrum sense?
I...
I'm all over the...
I'm all over the place and yet kind of only half there at all.
So only half of some supposed ear is half somewhere else.
That's the way it feels anyway.
Well...
Who knows how it truly is?
That...
And isn't that the ultimate question?
How is it, really?
What condition is your condition truly in?
Wouldn't you like to know?
I'm holding one of those really holograms.
Like they say now, everybody in the string theory is like,
Hey man, I'm a hologram.
You know, like from God and stuff.
And I'm here to screw up.
And, you know...
I don't get it.
How come we're holograms?
I just love all those...
Not a very high resolution hologram.
I just love all those space cadet people who, you know,
they're so spiritual and whatnot.
And they...
You get into a conversation with them and, you know,
question some of the ridiculous things they believe in.
And they're like,
Well, didn't you know they've scientifically proven the existence of the soul?
Oh, yes, they have.
They've observed the magical energy field around the body.
And blah, blah, blah.
That's the soul.
I can prove the existence of a human soul.
How so, sir?
Mr. Doctor of...
Yeah.
All right.
A human soul could be trapped in a piece of paper.
Well, not just one piece of paper now.
Well, mine is trapped...
There are a number of documents.
Well, I'm talking about currency.
I'm talking about...
I'm talking about those six, six, six dollar bills.
Yeah, the subgenius soul is a gland,
a small, flat, green gland located, ironically enough,
in the bottom of the foot.
I know it sounds like a joke,
but that happens to be where soul, spelled S-O-U-L,
is located in the sole of the foot.
S-O-L-E.
Ha, ha.
Very funny, but there you have it.
Doesn't the gland have, like, an appearance of, like, a dollar sign?
That's where we got the symbol for the dollar sign?
Well, in the nation, there's a pound sign over in Britain.
There's lira signs.
There's all these different...
No, it's not that specific.
I mean, it's just a greenish-looking little ugly gland
that most, you know, what doesn't even...
isn't even noticed by medical science
because it doesn't really get sick in any way that hurts the foot.
Well, the ancient Chinese called it the hypohubris.
People try to treat the head
when the problem is actually this gland in the foot.
They try to treat your heart, your mind, your feelings, and so forth,
when really, really there's just, you know,
there's...
You just...
By the subgenius forbidden science,
even a lowly healer of appliances, say,
would be able to take on a...
would be able to heal soul problems
simply by being able to locate them.
And that's why a good foot rub feels so incredibly good.
You know the saying.
And why your feet smell so horribly bad.
That's where your soul is.
Yeah.
And your soul, friend, needs washing.
Your soul needs to be washed
in the...
I mean, in the spit,
in the fluid,
the love of Bob.
Your soul...
Think of it like it is sherry.
...must be cleansed.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You are cleansed.
You can wash the slacklessness away,
but Bob has to know
that you trust him.
Well...
You know, to a certain length,
you can trust him.
Only...
Only in the same way that you trust your doctor.
Why do you trust your doctor?
Because you know him?
No, you don't know him.
Because he gave you a big bill.
And the insurance company paid some of it.
Or you had to pay it.
Or you're fleeing from it.
Whatever.
Or he gives you pills.
That's how the medicine men of our society have their power.
They present the huge bill.
In another culture,
the medicine man might display his power
by showing a huge whatever.
But in our culture,
it's a huge bill for money.
That's just the way it goes.
We do worship the dollar here in America.
I mean, think of the titty and the phallic cultures.
Worshipping their things.
No, you don't worship the dollar per se.
You worship the power
and the ego gratification
that that dollar will buy you.
Well, all that money is,
it's just a measurement of work.
Yeah.
Yeah, you sound like a Marxist buddy.
I mean, you know,
as a measure of labor and so forth.
Yeah, perhaps.
Economists today,
I think they define it as a medium of exchange.
Like spittle.
Kind of like language is a medium of communication.
Money is a medium of exchange.
Jeez, they've changed commerce into a fornication art.
Well, it always has been.
Don't even get started on the conjugation.
Well, it does it by itself, doesn't it?
I mean, it's mathematical.
It has no choice.
Unless it wants to slack off.
These are the great mysteries.
Well, I don't know why that gland
can't just simply be removed.
You know, if it's causing so much pain to the humans,
like, oh, my soul is in agony.
You know, have you been walking around Public Square
too long with your toe sticking out of your shoe?
You know, what could be an agony that doesn't exist?
It must be a gland.
Well, Jesus and Magdalene were all about
an anointing of the feet.
Yep.
That's what they were all about.
I mean, as far as we know,
we don't know their beliefs about the Iraq conflict
or, you know, abortion.
We know they liked feet.
Jesus was a foot fetish.
Well, we have to have them
as our Lord and Master bless you.
But Bob worships the actual gland
that makes sign of the currency.
Bob worships nothing.
Well, no, that's right.
He doesn't really worship anything.
Or he does worship nothing.
Which is it?
Hmm.
Those are different, you know.
Bob's a nihilist.
Yeah, if you worship, you could worship nothing.
And then you'd be a nihilist.
You could not anything.
You'd just be like, you know, one of the non-conjugating,
14-year-olds.
You could worship the concept of nothing.
Hmm.
Or you could just worship nothing at all.
The void.
You're fulfilling your destiny.
Become my apprentice.
Learn.
Learn to use the dark side of the Force.
I will do whatever you ask.
Good.
To cheat death is a power only one has achieved.
But if we work together,
I know we can discover the secret.
I pledge myself to your teachings.
Good.
Henceforth, you shall be known as Darth...
Mom?
Yeah.
I swear I'll die soon once again.
I will have mediums,inverse maidens.
Looks like an ocean battle isences,
human Û coincidences have begun.
Merry Christmas, towards Christmas,
Bora's on a boat under waiting.
Thank you, my master.
She was packed.
She also did a one-woman comedy show called God Said Ha.
Yeah, well, well, she's doing another thing now.
And I don't remember the name exactly, but it was something like Letting Go of God.
And she was talking on the radio today, this is on This American Life on NPR.
They said she basically told her whole story of how she stopped believing in God
and all the crises she had to go through trying to cope with the fact that people just die,
having to cope with the fact that, well, actually having to stop and think as to what makes murder still wrong,
even though God has nothing to do with it.
It was so funny hearing somebody going through this.
Okay, now here's the thing.
A lot of Christians in this country have something of a persecution complex.
Catholics have a huge persecution complex.
A persecution complex dating back to the old days of Protestant supremacy and all that,
when people didn't trust them because they seemed foreign.
But then you also have, like evangelical Christians, a lot of them have a persecution complex too.
They have this belief that the secular humanist agenda,
which is really playing into the hands of Satan,
has been going to all these great lengths to take God out of everything
and to silence the voices of the believers.
They seem to have this belief.
Some of them do.
But they don't believe in Christ because they want to go beating the hell out of everybody for their oil and stuff.
Well, the reason...
You know, they're not real Christians.
They're like...
Well, sure they are.
I mean, I don't know.
Well, okay, I mean, even according to the book of Revelation,
only like 140-some thousand people will be saved when the rapture finally comes.
According to Revelation, there's only going to be like 100,000 people saved.
The rest of us all burn.
Here's an interesting statistic.
At any given time,
there are 140,000 people flying around in airplanes.
So what if one day all those people just flying around on airplanes just came,
they landed on a deserted earth?
Interesting.
Nothing but piles of empty clothes all over the ground.
Yeah.
Taken up.
Dust.
They'd have to start over again.
Yeah.
That's like the rapture.
Or the rupture.
Yeah.
Well, you think of it this way.
You can be saved by grace,
or you can be saved by a lunatic in a funny rubber suit,
and think of the Church of the Subgenius as your surrogate, you know, rubber suit,
because the evangelicals just don't afford the proper insurance and requirements on the craft.
You know, once we start leaving, things are going to get real hairy.
I mean, actually, physically, we'll start growing a lot of hair, most of us.
I'm sharpening my razor as we speak.
And, well, you can choose not.
That's one of the nice things about old rubber suits staying.
You know, they have that written into it.
They have what written into it?
That you don't necessarily have to become hairy if you don't want,
but you still have to be either saved by grace or by a guy in a trick potato, or whatever they call it.
Hmm.
It's a scary, scary world we live in, isn't it?
Yeah.
For most people, I mean, I can't see how the average Hunan bean sauce walks around daily and daily,
just not caring about these huge, you know, three-ton problems that are falling down everywhere.
Because they don't affect them immediately.
It's the immediate stuff that people worry about.
When you feel an immediate threat, that's when you're most likely to do something about it.
You know.
Boy, you throw us up along a lot of them cultures that came and went and stuff.
We're pretty stupid, though, when you think about it.
Well, nothing really changes, you know, throughout history and prehistory.
We're still the same dumb, dirty apes we've always been.
Except that we learned how to shave the hair.
And we learned how to split the atom.
Not too long after that, actually.
Well, somebody was saying these yetis of the Church of the Subgenius are actually sloth that got, like, smarter than beavers and stopped sharpening their teeth or something.
I mean, I know that sounds ridiculous.
Because it is.
But about 9,000 years ago, there were, like, giant sloths and, like, you know, temperate zone forest tigers walking.
Sabretooth tigers walking around?
Is that true?
Or did you make that up?
I'm not sure.
I'm not too well-versed on that kind of stuff.
And perhaps those were the yeti, these one-ton sloths, which actually, you know, just got tired of everyone in the world eating them, even though they could have eaten everyone else because they were so big.
And lost their...
You know, thing with their tooth, like beavers have, of wanting to chew trees or else their head will fall off.
So they became yeti, as if they could, and are now.
I find it hard to believe.
Hey, I'm going to get off this line because I can't hear anything.
I'm going to try a different phone or something.
I'll be calling back.
All right, best of luck to you.
Over and out.
All right, over and out.
I knew that was happening because you did not talk very many times.
Actually, yeah.
Yeah, I could tell that, too.
Actually, what I was saying before about the Christian persecution complex, I just don't see how it's justified when you have entire, like, publication industries.
You have entire cable channels dedicated to spreading their message, to spreading their beliefs, to proclaiming them.
You know, I mean, when 40% of the population identifies itself as born again or evangelical, when, you know, I just think it's so funny that they have this persecution complex.
And they have this perception that the media are hostile to them.
But if you look in the media, very rarely do you ever see religion actually denounced in the media.
And that's what was so amazing about what I heard this morning.
Well, it's a big lie, and that's what you have to deal with first when you deal with any media except for this kind of ridiculous thing that we're doing, is that they always lie.
We always do, too, you know, but it's like fun.
Well, ours is a lie in service of the truth.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's it.
And theirs is in the service of, like, a big, big fat paycheck that we're never going to see.
Yeah.
They give them the script, and they go up there, and they look good, and they sound good, and, you know, I was listening to that guy's talking about Ronald Reagan, Richard Nixon being the greatest president since Abraham Washington, and for the love of Christ, I, you know, it's, yeah.
Who's that one guy on the radio?
I was listening to him today, and he played, like, a clip.
Yeah.
And Al Gore was saying something like, you know, if it had been Republican judges appointed by a Republican Congress, no one would have accepted the decision of Bush v. Gore in 2000.
And then this guy gets on the radio, well, Al Gore's just a little crybaby.
You know, somebody needs to call him an ambulance.
Somebody needs to call 911.
Yeah, that kind of, you know, drives you nuts there, don't it?
Yeah.
I hate, I hate these.
Straw man argument.
That's what it sounds like to me.
You know, they're taking just, like, the most inane things somebody has said on record.
They love to bash liberals.
Oh, no.
Liberal is the ultimate dirty word.
And it's so funny because, like, you know, conservative does not have the negative connotations in liberal circles that liberal has in conservative circles.
Conservative doesn't even mean conservative anymore.
Well, yeah, well, these terms have all become meaningless.
Yeah, yeah, they're all meaningless.
It depends on when you're talking about classical liberalism or whatever.
216.
I don't know if you've seen the rest of the issue.
And you can tell us.
You can tell us right now.
If we are broadcasting, we're tired of these taped callers calling in.
These ones that puzzling evidence slips in.
There's really a tape caller.
This must be the slash caller.
We need the real callers to call in and tell us.
Slash passersby.
Are we on the air?
Travels along the street.
And I'm going to have to go froth.
Curious cultural artifact that we are getting.
I'm really getting nervous.
And this must be the track of the peen worm made in the sand.
The fresh sand of the literal.
You see the mark.
I'm having an anxiety.
An anxiety attack.
Here it is when we catch up with it.
Oh my.
Shiny black carapace as it burrows through the sand.
Terrifying.
Oh, I'm so anxious.
If we get close up.
As you see here, close up.
I really mean it too.
Most unprepossessingly, gigantic compound eyes, the three mouth parts or stalks, and the white beard underneath.
All give a very disturbing stop.
The smelting salts.
Yeah, we see a multi-masted ship.
Four-masted ship.
And the close up of.
All within real close.
Death Valley subsoil.
Realness of your.
And here is the hanged man.
And here, this is your card.
The dead Phoenician sailor.
Look, those are pearls that were his eyes.
Yeah.
Think of what might be an actually in NyQuil for the masses.
They could be like stumbling our brains and recapitulating.
Yeah.
You know, large portions of our MO for medulla oblongata and stuff and taking our corpse close.
I mean, you know, leaving things in there, you know, they just build up over a period of, you know,
you build a nano years, perhaps in this case, you know, nano periods of just long enough to start speaking new thoughts where there were none.
You know, terrible things are happening in my ashtabula oblongata.
God.
Yeah, it's polluted.
And the trash gland.
It is your birth that marijuana white trash.
To be.
Question.
Faith.
For us.
Yeah, actually, they can.
Here's the news on that Supreme Court ruling that happened early this week.
The U.S. Supreme Court in a 63 decision, I think it was.
Was it 63?
They ruled that the Federal Controlled Substances Act takes precedence over California state laws.
Yeah.
Which make it legal to cultivate marijuana for one's personal medical use.
If a doctor gives you permission to.
I love you, big brother.
Well, here's the funny thing.
All right.
This ruling is not as simple as a lot of people thought it was.
A lot of people think they were ruling on the controversial controversial issue of medical marijuana, but they weren't.
What the Supreme Court really ruled on was a legal issue of what takes precedence, state law or federal law.
Yeah.
And if if the Supreme Court snuck it in there because actually they couldn't test it on any of the grounds because it was too stupid.
And they came up with the species.
Yeah.
I'm working with a little old lady.
My daughter.
Well, here's.
Or why?
You know, actually, no, this this the ruling had nothing to do with the war on drugs.
I mean, it was totally not a drug related ruling.
Not at all.
The ruling they made had nothing to do with drugs.
Yes.
But if you're in California or Arizona and go get out of my house, you know, I have a disease and a prescription.
They'll say, well, we can still put you in federal prison.
No, they can't.
Only the feds can do that.
Why?
The feds can bust you.
State law enforcement.
They bust people for pot now.
State law.
When they really have to focus more of their efforts on destroying meth labs.
Meth is destroying this country.
Oh, meth is not destroying the country.
Come on.
Meth is.
There is an epidemic of meth usage.
But the reasons for that.
No, no.
Meth is not what's destroying this country.
Meth epidemics are a symptom, not a not a cause.
Oxi-contin abuse.
This is this is a symptom, not a cause.
All right.
People turn to drugs for various reasons.
But it's usually because.
They're not happy enough without the drugs.
They think they'll be happier with the drugs.
The structure of pain.
Which often they are.
It's like the fountain of age.
It's not the drugs that are destroying our society.
All right.
It's the stuff that leads to people taking drugs.
You know, drug abuse is a symptom.
America will never think in terms of this spiral.
You get caught in this in this loop of of like never having good enough material possessions.
And you end up in a little cracker box.
See?
See, the same could be said.
The same could be said about about anything.
Yeah.
You know, it's not so clearly it's it's ridiculous to say that meth is destroying the country.
What flavor under.
Black is destroying this country.
Do these do these people in power where?
That's the question we have to ask when they're coming up with this stuff.
Essentially, you know, like Foucault or Ludovico Vico would say they're essentially trying to control.
They view it as their job, even though they tell us the opposite.
That is their job to control our every.
Movement and behavior and thing.
Well, actually, this is.
Sexuality.
What you think.
What you read.
What you.
Very good.
Dave, you seem to have made the connection.
You see, this is this is what the Republican Party platform is really about when it comes to domestic issues.
Well, they claim we want to grow up to be just like them.
I mean, they claim to be in favor of, you know, life.
We're pro life and we're pro freedom.
You know, this is what the GOP keeps on saying.
But what it really comes down to when you look at their their stances on life and death issues.
What it comes down to is they have an agenda of taking the power of life and death away from those who live and die and putting that power into the hands of the state.
Yes, they want to say, you know, they want to tell people when to have children.
They want to tell people when not to have children.
They want to tell people when to die and when not to die.
Yeah, but if they want to have soul live forever, that's correct.
All you have to do is be and you have the rights of about a thousand individuals.
Now, isn't that funny?
Because once upon a time, a corporation was chartered to do a very specific thing and it was chartered by the state.
And I believe that you still get charges from the state when you incorporate.
Yeah, and the state still has a power to evoke your charter.
I gotta re-charter my corporation.
Yeah, you know.
Well, find the correct state, Stang.
You're in a state of confusion right now by thinking of good old Uncle Scant.
Scant, Scant, Scant.
He said, not normal. Take their passive to be normal.
People need to have their drugs for the rest of your life.
More money, more drugs.
Do you have any pills?
Sure.
Wrong.
Wrong, but acid to get normalized.
The
What's left of your brain?
Oh yes, and all your money to the Reverend Hyden Stang.
The
Anyone that flows in your veins
From the front of your clouds
Brings slack like rain
Let all control what's left of your brain
Oh yes, and all your money to the reverend I've been saying
Embrace the yeti blood
That flows in your veins
From the front of your clouds
Brings slack like rain
Let all control what's left of your brain
Oh yes, and all your money to the reverend I've been saying
The El Queso All-Stars, dear friends,
one of my favorite songs.
And before that, L'Emeur and Norelle,
which you can get more of at Heavy Confetti.
And much of Dr. Sinister's show
with Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
Governor Rock Gnar,
and other callers as follows.
And now, here's a little bit of the story.
I'm going to say something,
another word, but you can't say it
because it's in the book.
No, now you can, because it's after a while.
Let's watch our tongues.
Let's watch our tongues, Rock Gnar.
Don't, uh, don't, don't.
Leave the rules setting to me, please.
No, don't tempt the pinks, I'm sorry.
Think of it, yeah, think of it as a form of meditation.
Like people watch the end of their noses.
Look at the, you know, just watch your tongue.
Yeah.
And if it wags, it's a form of meditation.
Too much, there's a dog around trying to get your ass.
Ah.
Amazing.
And you know, that's bull crap.
Yeah.
In the old days, when they spelled America with a K,
now they have to spell it with two Ks.
Why two Ks?
One for each constitutional crisis they create.
Oh.
Ever since Ice Cube spelled it wrong,
now everybody wants to spell it wrong.
About the what?
Ever since Ice Cube spelled it wrong,
now everybody wants to spell it wrong.
Yeah.
Well, you know, like, there's a whole bunch of reasons
to spell America with a K, I guess.
I guess it's like a pun on the...
Well, that was a popular miniseries.
Like in the early 80s.
That was the...
ABC had a miniseries.
It was like on for seven nights.
America-ka.
Yeah, it was America and it was spelled with a K.
What was it about?
The idea that the communists had taken over America
and then everybody in America was living under like a fascist rule.
And gee, how is that any different than how we're living today?
Oh, I can think of a few differences.
Um.
See, here's the thing, Rocknar.
Here's the thing, Rocknar.
I don't like the shrill tone of the left
when it gets to be shrill.
I mean, like, I don't like shrill tones from anybody.
I mean, a good old vibrato tone.
It makes you...
A vibrato.
But, you know, what do they call it?
Tenor.
You know, when you speak shrilly,
when you speak shrilly,
it doesn't just make you sound dumb.
It makes your whole cause sound dumb.
So when you say that, gosh,
there's not much difference between us
and a communist fascist dictatorship,
I mean, that...
Come on.
Be serious.
If he's very serious,
I'm afraid to say...
I mean, we're going down that...
We've started down the slippery slope.
There's no question that we're heading
in the wrong direction
and that we could very well end up like that very soon.
No, you say that after one rigged election,
not after two.
I don't know how rigged the second election was.
How...
What kind of rigging have we uncovered
in this past election?
Well, in Ohio, they uncovered everything
and nobody in Ohio is allowed to have any idea
of whatever happened.
The rigging...
You don't know how to...
We're talking about margins.
...of the economy of anything.
We're talking about margins
in the case of these so-called rigged elections.
that are a fraction of the final margin of victory.
We're talking about maybe 10,000 votes
that are questionable in all of Ohio.
No, I don't think that.
And Bush won by over 100,000 votes.
I mean, I...
That's kind of spooky.
I cannot say my trusting friend,
I believe that,
because I listen to media
from different countries,
and they have these strange stories.
And do they have, do they have, like,
do they have spies planted
in our county boards of elections here?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This has to do with the computer votes
and so forth,
the addition of votes
and what is and isn't reported.
In a prayer.
You can throw in 14,000,
you know, ultimately,
that's how they did that.
And they did it in a couple other states.
You could put most of the focus on Ohio,
but you gotta remember...
Wait.
Wait a second.
In circumstances,
Blackwell was still the guy
conducting investigation
just like what your name in Florida was,
you know?
Yeah, it's just that, like,
in a lot of...
Man, okay.
Thank you for your call, sir.
I didn't mean it.
She was a commuter.
What I mean to say is that, like,
there are enough,
there's enough local control
in enough counties across the country
by people who are,
I don't know, I mean, like,
there's so many people involved
in this process,
it would be very hard
to make a huge conspiracy like that.
I just, you know,
I have no real hard evidence
that, uh,
I've seen no real hard evidence
that there was a serious fraud going on.
I mean, I can, I know that there was
some minor fraud here and there,
and that's every bit as serious
as the major fraud, mind you.
Because the result, the goal, is the same.
How do we even know that the numbers
that are being reported
about how many people voted for X candidate
Well, you know, that's been true.
and how many voted for Y,
how do we even know
that those numbers are even right?
Well, how did we ever,
how did we ever know
that any of those numbers
were ever right
in all of recorded history?
I mean, I mean,
if you raise that question,
if you say that,
how do we know that any of these numbers
are right at all?
Well, then, I mean,
then that's all of democracy
right there out the window.
Because we, how do we know?
All governments and administrations,
but figures and factions and so forth,
they all create their own spin
on what's coming out
to make them look like
they're doing their jobs real good.
Because I know I accidentally
worked for the government for a while,
and you push a lot of paper around,
you know, trying to get people jobs
or, you know, get yourself out of a job.
And you find that
they lie,
lie a lot.
But it's when they start lying
really, really weird
and really, really,
that's when you got to worry.
And what you got is like,
America is being lied to real hard.
And they're thinking
it's just the same
as one of those regular lies.
See, America's being lied to
so well, so effectively,
that I don't think that vote fraud
is necessary anymore.
I think,
and that may sound funny,
but it's actually dead serious.
I think that it's much more effective
these days and much safer
when you consider the legal risks
involved for the people
who are engaging in supposed
fraud.
I mean, no, it's much easier,
much safer,
much more effective
to basically fool the public,
to pull the wool over their eyes.
Excellent.
No.
Yes.
No problemo.
Trust me.
I trust you.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm primarily to blame
for regarding ë°áº§ description of At The Ripple fad.
are to blame for that refinery's
blast. The Ministry of Emergency
Situations says PR News
treats prisoners humanely and
continues to be a leader in torture.
On Wall Street 37
1066 1212
supporters say this is PR.
A federal judge has killed 15
people and injured PR News
in Washington.
You've got
all the things, all
of them, in all the right
places. Oh yeah!
Yes, indeed.
Wow.
Oh yeah.
All the sub-home
victories.
Crazy French
people.
Dogs like
graffitis.
Strange evidence of subgenius
conspiracy or harmless
fun.
What the show?
Dogs like graffitis.
Did you see that movie
Constantine?
Does it have shooting in it?
It's got Keanu Reeves in it.
I want some shooting.
He's got a gun.
He goes to hell or something.
He fights devils.
He does something like
the plot.
No.
I've not seen
Constantine yet.
I haven't either.
I don't know.
I don't know, folks.
If you don't know,
please call 848-4425
right now.
Well, I did.
Look at that little
special...
That's cool.
We need the people
that don't know what it's called.
You know.
It's obvious you know.
Green onion style rock song
with shotguns?
Yeah.
It's shotgun brothers.
No.
It's not what you know.
It's how you know it.
And who you know.
It's who you know.
It's not where you know.
It's when you know it.
Get me in a jean.
Oh, let it go.
Get in there.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm barred from the ministry
and defrocked.
President Bush delivers
about 1.4 million children
this morning at the
U.S. Naval Academy,
which he says is not finished.
The Muslim holy book
involved toilets.
Personal incomes rose slow.
The Commerce Department
says seven-tenths.
It said six-tenths,
but nine-tenths.
It said that reflected
a jump in PR News.
Washington.
Well, you know,
I mean, free speech
can just mean standing,
you know, I was standing
in line at the bank
the other day,
and this crazy guy
just, like,
stepped out of line, actually.
He was in line at the bank,
and he stepped out of line,
and he started going off
on this, like, thing
that, you know,
sounded, you know,
sounded kind of schizophrenic.
You know, you couldn't
quite tell what he was
trying to say,
and then he gets to the end
and he's like,
and what if you could be
given eternal life
by the blood of the lamb
and blah, blah, blah,
and I'll leave you with that,
and he gets back in line
like nothing happened.
What a heebie.
These people are everywhere.
They're the sleepers,
you know,
and they're starting to,
like, they're sleepwalking,
basically.
They're sleepwalking
through the day,
and they jump out
and say these absurd things
and go back to normal
like nothing happened.
Oh, wait until they do
what they've been
programmed to do.
They're going to be like
little Manchurian candidates
running around.
I stock up on guns
and ammo now.
This is my advice
to all of you out there.
Get your...
Particularly ammo.
I...
Really?
You can get a nice AK-47 now.
They're...
You can get the bigger clips, too.
They're legal now
that the assault
weapons ban expired.
No, get a Desert Eagle.
These statements do not
Well, you need one of each.
You can't just have
an assault rifle.
You can't have
just an assault rifle
or just a handgun.
You need to have
one of each, at least.
Get a 50 caliber.
Actually, you could
probably get one of those
like Chinese knockoff AKs.
You don't even need
the real thing anymore.
The opinions expressed here
do not represent...
Oh, we already did
that disclaimer.
...concentration gap
or the radio station.
Get a 50 caliber
Desert Eagle.
It's...
Action Express.
Everybody...
Oh, no, no, no.
I want a SOCOM.
It's the...
I'd like an RPG.
It's the HK Mark 22,
I think.
Smith & Wesson.
45 caliber.
Have you guys ever
seen a commercial
for the F-16?
Yes, we have.
It goes
boing, boing, boing.
I came upon...
I used to work
for a film lab
and they were
throwing out
a bunch of
slightly damaged
commercials
that they'd made,
I guess,
for the government
or for Lockheed
or somebody to show
to heads of state.
You know, it's kind of
droopy outside right now.
Droopy?
Yeah.
Is it...
I thought I saw lightning
out the window
out of the corner of my eye.
Lightning out the window.
That is the lightning
in your retina, my friend.
That is the light...
the actual lightning
in your brain.
I just heard
either thunder
or the Martian invasion
has started.
I can't believe it.
I can't believe
we're talking about the weather.
We have nothing better
to talk about.
Is that it?
Hey, for the people around...
If it is the Martian invasion,
this could be really important.
Well, you know, I'm hoping.
For it, but...
the smoke weed for that.
The fact is,
we don't have any information
on the situation,
so anything we say
is going to be
pure speculation, basically.
Well, somebody
will have the smoke weed
for that.
What's that?
Is it the Martian invasion
or is it Deep Colon?
Who's Deep Colon?
Hmm.
It's either both.
Actually, I'm glad
that I wasn't able
to get on.
You guys were really
talking seriously
about the conspiracy
of the nationalists
and the governments
and the corporations.
The old project.
See, I don't even like them.
You don't want
to get me involved
in those conversations
because I really do believe
in the concentration camps
and so, therefore,
I can only joke
about that kind of stuff.
Now, we all know
that this guy, Mark Felt,
who just came out
of hiding,
he's not the real deep throat.
Stang is the real deep throat.
Hey, I wouldn't...
He's got a really deep throat.
...customers
if I wasn't good at it.
Unfortunately,
so many people know
this is true.
There's your music, Stang,
and here's your F-16 commercial,
and here's...
And this F-16 reality
world, man.
Hey, how easy.
No, no, really.
I'm just saying.
The F-16,
this was a commercial
for the jet fighter,
the F-16.
The jet itself?
It wasn't a commercial
for a company?
for the Air Force?
It was a film,
and it was designed...
If you were the head of state
or the main general
of the head of state,
these guys would show you
this 10-minute film,
and it'd make you want to
buy a bunch of F-16s
for your Air Force.
Yeah, it's like for
an arms expo.
At the end,
and it was really slick,
it made me want one,
and at the end of it,
it showed, it said...
Now, this was in the early 70s,
and this kind of...
At the end of the commercial,
there was this roll-by
of the flags
of all the countries
that had purchased
this great new aircraft.
It was like,
Saudi Arabia, Iraq, Iran.
Just an incredible list
of everybody
that we have sent.
Isn't it amazing
that American companies
are selling these horrible weapons
to countries we don't trust?
Well, it's like...
Well, we don't really care about...
You sell them the insanity,
and then you sell them the cure...
You sell them the weapons,
then they're hooked on the ammo.
They have to keep coming back
for more ammo.
Because that's...
Because they're not used to it.
There's just not a lot in there.
You have a fight with them,
and they need even more.
It's not a great market.
It's a great market.
You know, you buy this part,
you buy this thing and stuff,
but you're going to need
a lot of ammo forever.
Of course everybody
needs a lot of ammo.
How many of you
have to have ammo?
All you need.
It's like with our religion.
First, we sell them the insanity,
and then we sell them the cure.
In perpetuity.
Yeah.
As I already said,
legally,
in perpetuity,
and everything.
I don't know.
Forever and ever.
Yep.
The Senate Finance Committee
and the Department of Health
and Human Services,
their mission is
putting an obstetrician
up on a slideshow.
He is being fired
due to harassment
and intimidation.
Part of the National Institutes
of Sloppy Science
bending the pressure
from sloppy sexual right
to lifers
suffering from AIDS.
All in the name
of scientific terrorism.
And numerous drug companies
and researchers,
they are afraid to speak up.
Documents obtained
by the Associated Press
show that the U.S. government
ridiculed and discredited
their own frequent
sexual financing.
So, folks.
It's a rough old world.
It's a rough old world
when we don't have
the air conditioning
or the hot running water.
Because the water
always runs dry.
Sooner or later,
it's all going to run dry.
Expect no less.
Just like those glands
in our feet are salt.
Sooner or later,
everything comes apart
one way or another,
Bob said.
And perhaps...
Now, whose law of motion
is that?
Uh, Fudd.
The second one?
Wasn't that Fudd's law?
Fudd's law?
Elmer Fudd's law?
No, no, no.
I can't remember
the guy's name.
The famous...
Swimish.
Scientist.
God.
Oh, well.
Dr. Paslow.
Dr. Paslow?
Dr. Short?
I'm Dr. Memory.
It was Dr. Memory.
No.
That's evil.
I'm in that loop again.
Damn.
It's been, like,
45 years.
Well,
I guess we must
find some
all the way around.
Very second.
If we're at this, uh,
if we've caught ourselves
in a loop here,
might be a good time
to, uh,
move along, actually.
Yeah, yeah, please.
Yeah, yeah.
We just explained,
we just explained
exactly how
the conspiracy works.
Yep.
Right.
We just said it
right out in the open.
And we're all expecting
a check in the mail.
That's right.
Check is in the mail.
Take the ball and run with it,
listener.
You are the next Bob.
Hey, you know,
we are all
Bob.
We are,
any one of us
might be, no,
we're not necessarily Bob,
but we might be
the next Bob.
That's right.
You could be
if you wanted to.
Could be.
You could be
if you wanted to.
It's all, uh,
I don't know.
I wouldn't want to,
and I hate
It's a burden.
It's a burden that is too much
for any one normal man,
and this is why
there's a lottery for it.
Yeah.
Because I know
nobody would volunteer for it.
Yeah.
Any one of us
could be the next Bob.
You know,
it's like the draft.
You're listening
to the hour
of Slack.
For more information
on the Church
of the Subgenius,
see
subgenius.com.