but now at the beginning of the 1980s I want to make another personal prediction
the 1980s will be the most catastrophic decade in the history of man and yet no one who will
accept what God has to say has to be afraid as a matter of fact you can be so excited that every
day can be a day where you are not only optimistic but saying this might be the day this may be it
you
and in the meanwhile Bob has promised that as we claim his promises he will sustain us even in the
darkest hours of history and give us a way out time for show live show for you now this is Doug
Smith radio operator I'm going to bring you a piece of that green cheese for sure welcome
subgenius radio
you
sponsored by the church
enchanted and raptured and bombed the past year resembles nothing so much as the the bad alternate
timeline that the hero of a cheap science fiction book or has to go back and fix
you
are that time traveler
yes
only your memory can be restored to you
you are the humble time traveler
I know what you mean though
it does
yeah that would explain a lot
it would explain the wooden headed people
coming up to us while we're taking our
sulfur baths
it would certainly explain all the money that's now going to be
flowing into
arms and legs
and think of how fully well laundered that money it is
it must be very
squeaky clean by now
just think about george the bushy haired one himself and counting that money back in some room
he's got to replace those behind the oval orifice
that's not what this is all about
no
it's all about uh revenge that's it
taking over mars
and uh yes eventually to take over to take back mars
yeah
take over mars to take mars back our rightful home
that we the true martians were expelled from mars and we're going to have to do something else
we the true martians were expelled from mars we're going to have to do something else
we're going to have to do something else
so that they the oil sheiks and the the oil billionaires and all the oily characters would have some
so we're living in the martian time slip
oh i can grok to that
in this time continuum
i can grok to that my water brother but by the same token
we were enslaved
we've got to go back in time and kill bob's mom
the psychic
after bob was born
enslaved thousands and millions and bazillions of years ago
does this mean that there's a
does this mean that there's a a big thing with all the money we want here at the front of our house and we can pick it up and and just
a big thing with all the money we want here at the front of our house and we can pick it up and and just
it doesn't mean anything like that it just means that we were kidnapped from our home world and we're stuck here with you twerps
yeah you guys you just you guys
go ahead make mine bob
Right.
Now.
Ha ha.
I.
Am.
An.
Antichrist.
I.
Am.
An.
Anarchist.
Don't know what I want, but I know how to get it.
I.
Wanna destroy the passerby.
Cause.
I.
Wanna be.
Anarchy.
No dog's body.
For.
The.
You.
K.
It's.
Coming.
Sometime.
Maybe.
I.
Give.
A.
Wrong.
Time.
Stop.
A.
Traffic.
Line.
Your.
Future.
Dream.
Is.
A.
Shopping.
Scheme.
Cause.
I.
Wanna be.
An.
Anarchy.
In.
The.
City.
I.
Many.
Ways.
To.
Get.
What.
You.
Want.
I.
Use.
The.
Best.
I.
Use.
The.
Enemy.
I.
Use.
Anarchy.
Cause.
I.
Wanna be.
Anarchy.
The.
Only.
Way.
To.
Be.
Is.
This.
The.
This.
The.
This.
The.
I.
Are.
A.
Or.
Be.
I.
Thought.
It.
Was.
The.
U.
K.
Or.
Just.
Another.
Country.
Council.
Tenancy.
I.
Wanna be.
Anarchy.
I.
City.
Use.
Anarchy.
Be.
Am.
J.
R.
Dear friends.
I am.
Be.
J.
R.
Our friend in England.
Did that.
Posted to.
Alt.
Binaries.
Slack.
Which is.
Where.
We.
all of our weird new audio discoveries or creations into the mix
and then suck them right off for each other's
and for use here on the Hour of Slack.
Now, that song Anarchy in the UK,
the computerized cover version,
was by someone named Jima, or J-I-M-A.
But what's interesting is where it came from.
It's a website called dictionaryoke.org.
Online dictionaries that sing the hits of yesterday.
You can basically program in songs, pick songs,
and if it can find the tune, I guess you feed it the lyrics or something.
Yes, that's www.dictionaryoke.org.
Some of the other weird little sounds and burblings
that pop up here and there on the show
came from Johnny Wishbone and I am BJR
and Fernando Nenny.
And from Artemia Salina,
all the regulars,
and Dr. New Monet,
the regulars, so to speak, on all that binary slack.
And now, I guess, Hour of Slack.
And of course, friends, we always hear lots of ESO Swamp Radio
from WCSB Cleveland,
which is on every Thursday night
and anybody can call in.
It's like about midnight Eastern time.
Time.
At WCSB Cleveland, WCSB.org.
Friends, that's Professor Chaz Smith as the host
and our caller there that time was Reverend Turin.
And, of course, Lone Cow Dave.
Lone Cow Dave is always there, even at Christmas.
And see, where I am right now, friends,
it is still Xmas, or about to be, something like that.
See, I never know exactly when each station
is going to play any given particular hour.
I'm not sure what the time is,
but I'm not sure what the time is.
I assume that they play roughly two weeks after I do them.
And so, this show may be playing after Christmas
or Christmas Day,
or sometime around these holidays and so forth.
But, and that's why it's not all Christmas stuff.
But, we have yet, nonetheless,
more to come from the great obtuse
from the Gabofam.
Math.
Bush.
Even weasel teats.
And Brother Clay, friends.
A lot of old and new Xmas hour of slack.
Old hours of slack.
And old me, young.
So separate.
You from Tulka.
Now you're in my evil clutches, Bob.
I'll use this MTV's on my list to turn you normal.
Shut up, pink boy.
No way.
I'll never sell out to the conspiracy.
Taste a little of my rocket pipe.
Alien tool.
I'll be back.
Bob Dobbs comes with rocket pipe,
head launcher,
Jane or device,
oligarch,
a tisma,
fighting Jesus,
and other action figures sold separately.
Some assembly required.
Batteries not included.
This toy falls apart in three days.
T-Bob.
And wrestling.
The bastards of the universe.
Too much is always better than not enough.
From Bob Dobbs.
And I can't do it so separately.
Gorgeous.
He can blow from head to toe.
He can do it so separately.
T-Bob and the bastards of the universe
will be back after this message.
Fixated On.
How's that sound?
It's so beautiful.
It's so perfect.
Question time.
Well sure.
He who are limited
all in love
Look,
Well, Tommy knew exactly what he wanted for Christmas.
He wanted an electric train.
He had the whole thing in his mind, even to the table where it was going to set it up.
He could picture the whole thing, and he would dream so hard that the whole thing would come to life right before his eyes.
Of course, Tommy was a pretty strong wisher.
And what he started wishing for was a pretty fancy looking train set with locomotives and freight cars.
And the station and the gateman.
The water tower and all the kinds of wonderful equipment and accessories.
So grand that you might think Tommy was waiting for something that just didn't exist.
But Tommy knew what he was wishing for.
I didn't do it.
Can I still have my dog?
No!
Boys and girls, everyone wants a Slinky.
You ought to get a Slinky.
Get your Slinky now.
You know what else let me down?
You're sloppy.
They had those big mugs.
It was a big magnet thing.
You're stinky.
And then they showed on TV somebody pulling a Volkswagen with the magnet that looked red.
I used to pull my Slinky, too.
It was red, and it looked like a Mighty Man thing.
Oh, wow.
Oh, you're a big red Slinky.
It was a big magnet.
There was another good one, too.
You had a big red magnetic Slinky?
It was a finger that would shoot.
It was like, you know, there was a lot of spy toys around.
Yes, exactly.
And it was a finger.
I can almost remember the song.
Double Agent Man.
I don't think I ever get along with five.
Secret agency woman.
The fingers you could get.
All different kinds of fingers.
Some of them would shoot little darts, poison darts.
Some of them would...
So there were the mind control.
Remember the little mind control devices?
Some of them launched little tiny nuclear-headed...
Nuclear-headed boys and girls.
See, this is the main problem.
Sam brainwashing.
Sexual devices or something like that.
Those were the best for me and my mom and Lisa and dad.
I sometimes, when I come home, I was sober enough to walk.
What was that called?
Marital AIDS.
Boy, that wasn't too obvious.
What, marital AIDS?
I had a...
No, you don't want to talk about it.
A secret Sam brainwasher kit where one kid would play the red Chinese interrogator.
Yeah, those were great.
And the other guy would play the American prisoner in the Korean War.
Did you ever play double Manchurian on that?
I'm glad to see battleship is still out.
Actually, I ended up attacking a school teacher.
You did?
Like three weeks after playing that.
The light went off.
Because this other kid deprogrammed me to.
It was called Six Finger.
That is a beautiful story for Thanksgiving.
No, you're wasting my time!
The戦隊 むしろ蜱虎を Smile the Korean War
Sometimes I think all that Santa crap is just bull.
Santa Claus is real..
imposs Bandicoot or what?!
The Child.
Who's the head man?
Santa Claus.
He was a huge beastly
bulging man.
You're so real.
How come we didn't get Squat last year?
But if you'll notice from time to time
he's basing it on this most joyous birth
of our baby dog.
What you're wearing.
The things that you're wearing.
Never mind what I'm wearing.
Come on, get out of here.
Those are some nice panties.
Hey, stop. Get your hand out.
Hey.
Come on, put your hand.
Well, I had no idea.
No, it's no big deal.
I don't, you know.
You're all right, man.
I understand Ed Wood was into that.
Ed Wood took the beach at Normandy
in his frilly pink panties.
And his...
And his entrenching tool.
And that's the important...
I want everybody from Sea Company!
For Christmas!
Over here!
The baby Jesus!
Yeah, keep it up!
And bow!
Let's take a...
Christmas Day, June 1944.
We kick some Nazi butt.
The Babylonian hussars entrenched deeply on the beach,
dressed in their crab suits
and their funny long underwear.
The cause of consternation isn't having anything to do
with their spiritual cults.
It has more particularly to do
with their religious doctrine.
And the Christmas Nazi devil
fought the Christmas army men.
They stood together.
And God won!
Hand in hand.
Until God lost.
And the devil lost.
And the devil cried his devilish tears.
They were salty.
They were finickery.
They were very bitter tears.
And as we collected them like tiny raindrops in a toxic pool,
we sat together and shaved.
And thanked our monkey we were born again in incandescent light.
Yes, the birth of the baby Satan.
On July 4th.
And now you can have it all.
Three thousand years ago.
One hundred percent vinyl chloride CID.
And celebrated.
The birth of our baby Satan
as told by various authors and eclectic scholars
from around the globular unit.
Including that announcer.
This announcement has not been a perfunctory announcement
but an announcement of the blessed anointing
and birthday of our Lord Jesus Christ.
For...
One bright Christmas morning...
...was born in
the cradle of tighter-knit Б VERY
The Rave
Jesus
The Rave Jesus
I know the Rave Jesus.
I've harkened to him since the Sherpa- nicеты
the Rave Jesus
I partook the rave Jesus
Oh,
Oh, I did that, my friends.
Well, rather, I pushed that button, I guess you could say.
And this music in the background is actually the Bishop from New York.
We've heard other burblings and sounds from Johnny Wishbone and, of course, ESO Swamp Radio.
And before that, Obtuse did all that Santa crap.
And slinky crap.
And the beautifully mixed holiday buying crap.
And you can get his free album on buying, but it's free!
Check their website, obtuse.iuma.com.
Yeah, and email them from there or something.
It's obtuse.iuma.com.
Great stuff.
But now, friends, now, a premiere, a world premiere, truly, of the latest, greatest new hit from Gary Grogfran of the band that dare not speak its name.
And he still dare not.
Putty Butt.
My baby just sits right there.
Dressed up in her underwear.
Jerry Springer is on the air.
She's a putty butt.
Putty Butt.
My baby ain't got much fat.
Her brain's not where she's at.
Not moved from where she sat.
She's a putty butt.
Putty Butt.
I'm sitting like Barry White.
Trying to get her to move at night.
Yes, I'm right.
She's a putty butt.
Putty Butt.
My baby ain't going nowhere.
Once a week, she moves from there.
So I can pat you under a chair.
She's a putty butt.
Putty butt.
Margarita.
Poop.
Wow, Stimpy.
We sure walked a long way.
I'm pooped.
Look, Ren.
It's St. Wizzleteet's house.
This must be the West Pole.
Hey, why don't we sing for him?
Yeah, then we can get our socks filled with sausages.
Well, hello, Mrs. Wizzleteet's.
Is Stinky home?
Stinky!
little street urchins to see you.
Huh? Urchins? What are urchins?
Some kind of newfangled dog?
Is that what you are? Some kind of dog?
Well then, you better bark like a dog.
If you're gonna act like a dog,
then you better crawl like a dog.
Honey, go get me my dog
walloping two by four from the shed.
No, no, no. We're here to send you a yaksmas carol.
Mr. Deets, sir.
Singing? Well, that's different.
Honey, go get me my dog
walloping guitar.
But let me sing you a song.
A little song I wrote to go something like this.
Oh, the big wooden chicken lived in the bush,
a big fat bush full of worms.
Hey, Will, I think it's time to get out of here.
They ate the chicken, and they all died the next day.
It is, it is turn over.
The time of the year
when all things sell, the end of the year, sale.
Oh, yes.
So come and get it, everyone, and just buy our products.
Now, are we, is Christmas, I'm a little confused
about what Christmas is all about.
Are we celebrating the birth of Santa Claus
or his death when they nailed him?
Well, that's the ancient, ancient subgenie.
But the present subgenie try to make sure that
we have our inventories cleared by now
and sell everything to the pigs.
Oh, yes.
Once a pagan holiday and now a shopping season.
And it was something else in between there.
But before it was, after it was a pagan holiday
and before it was a shopping season,
it was something else.
But I think they started a war over it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
If you haven't heard of me,
I wouldn't be surprised.
I bet you know my relatives.
Their names will never die.
My mother is a saint.
And my brother is a god.
But all I am is Jesus Brother Bob.
Jesus Brother Bob, Jesus Brother Bob.
A nobody relative of the Son of God.
If only I'd been born just a little sooner.
I'd be born in the first place.
Brother of God Junior.
I have to pay the ferry to cross the Galilee.
But not my brother.
No, not him.
He walks across for free.
I finally get to work about a quarter after nine.
Already he's turning water into wine.
Jesus Brother Bob, Jesus Brother Bob.
A nobody relative of the Son of God.
If only I'd been born just a little sooner.
I'd be born in the Brother of God Junior.
One day when I was home,
I heard a mighty roar.
There were a thousand people right outside the door.
Help us Jesus, help us.
Came the cheering from the mob.
But then they got a look at me.
A nuts it's only Bob.
Jesus Brother Bob, Jesus Brother Bob.
A nobody relative of the Son of God.
If only I'd been born just a little sooner.
I'd be born in the Brother of God Junior.
He, he died upon the cross.
I thought that I was free.
Finally people would get to know me for me.
Hi Bob.
Hey Judas.
Hey.
This was my big chance to finally get ahead.
The next thing you know he's rising from the dead.
Jesus Brother Bob, Jesus Brother Bob.
A nobody relative of the Son of God.
If only I'd been born just a little sooner.
I'd be born in the Brother of God Junior.
Everybody.
Jesus Brother Bob, Jesus Brother Bob.
A nobody relative of the Son of God.
If only I'd been born just a little sooner.
I'd be born in the Brother of God Junior.
I'd be born just a little sooner.
If only I'd been born just a little sooner.
Now you're blaming Jesus, you're blaming our Lord.
I sort of understand because I understood the way any old fool would understand.
There was no Jesus.
Jesus, no flatulent old woman waving her panties on the hill.
It's not that you don't want to.
It's that they won't let you.
No, they're ashamed.
Just a cry in the wilderness.
They're ashamed.
In the hot pursuit of wolves everywhere in the background.
I'm ashamed of them.
It's cold.
I'm leaving that city life behind.
I can't get my finger off the paper.
I can't get my needle back.
I'm going out.
I am dead.
Come on, cowboy.
No, man.
I was trying to hear you against your tree, and it started whispering to me, man.
No, you've been drinking.
There's the face of Madonna right up there.
There's the face of Virgin Mary.
I swear to God, look at it.
Isn't it?
What?
It's her Christmas witch coming.
It is true.
A Christmas witch?
I'll be whole.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, I guess it does look a little bit more.
Her breasts are so cold.
I know she must be a true witch.
I guess you could call her that if that's what she's talking about.
She's for real.
She's wearing Christmas ornaments.
It looks like a radar device.
What?
Yo.
Yo?
It's her.
What up?
Nothing.
What's up?
What a deep voice.
First Christmas witch.
I swear she had a much higher voice before when she called.
But are you the 29-year-old girl I've dreamed of for the last 25 minutes?
Yo.
Are you the 29-year-old woman I've dreamed of for the last 25 minutes?
No, but, um...
Can you?
I...
Yes.
I figure that, um, on the occasional guess that, quite frankly, that the people want
to listen to.
That I could quite entertain them.
You?
You could entertain them?
Oh, sure.
Quite frankly.
What do you mean by quite frankly?
And here's Frank!
I'm a sexy black male.
That's right.
We've got Frank here.
He's a sexy black male.
He says he works in the computer industry.
He's 35 years old.
Oh, no.
He runs skiing, fishing, and...
That's a complete lie.
Pardon?
But what's behind door number three?
I know.
That's right.
It's the monster woman of your dreams.
No, you're not gonna be the...
Behind door number three!
King, king, king.
Who is the king?
The money machine, says the queen.
Bing, bing, bing.
Bye, bye, bye.
My credit card makes me high.
My, my, my.
Until I die, die, die.
Swing, swing, swing.
Who wants the diamond ring?
Bye, bye, bye.
Yay, yay, yay, yay, yay, yay, yay, yay.
Hail Mother Mary, oh blessed lady.
Hail Mother Mary, I fell in love with your son.
Hail Mother Mary, turn me on and on and on.
Hail Mother Mary, thank God for you and your son.
Oh, oh, oh, Merry Christmas.
Merry, Merry, Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
Commercial America.
Commercial Yougmania.
Merry Christmas.
Commercial Babilonia.
Merry, Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
Hey, hey, ching kong and family, Merry Christmas.
Hey, hey, King Kong, let's dance to my happy Christmas song
Hey, hey, King Kong, let's dance
Let's dance
Hey, Mother Mary, oh, blessed lady
Hey, Mother Mary, I fell in love with your son
Hey, Mother Mary, turn me on and on and on
Hey, Mother Mary, thank God for you and your son
Merry Christmas
King, king, king, who is the king?
The money machine, says the queen
Bing, bing, bing, bye, bye, bye
My credit card makes me high
My, oh, my, until I die, die, die
Swing, swing, swing, who wants the diamond ring?
Bye, bye, bye, yay, yay, yay, yay, yay, yay
Merry Christmas
Commercial America
Commercial Germany
Merry Christmas
Commercial Babylonia
Cold as ice
Papa was not nice
He doesn't even care
That the rootless trees are in despair
Christmas is near
Let go of your fear
Forgiven, let live
Now and here
Children are pure
Ascent and rise
Santa is on tour
He pays a visit to every digit
That's for sure
If you'd be nice
Hey, Mother Mary
Oh, that's the lady
I fell in love with you
Hey, Mother Mary
Turn me on and on and on
Thank God for you and your son
Hey, Mother Mary
Oh, that's the lady
I fell in love with your son
Oh, oh, oh, Nina Hagen
Nina Hagen
Mm, mm, mm
What a doll, friends
A devil doll
And before that
A Christmas witch
On ESO Swamp Radio
From WCSB Cleveland
And that song
Jesus' Brother Bob
Is by
The Arrogant Worms
A band called
Posted by Dr. Lake Hume
And friends
Now we find ourselves
Pushing our way
Into a new century
Oh, wait
We already did that
Well, anyway
We still are pushing our way in
And the changes
Are not always up to us
But sometimes they are, friends
And we need to think of
What we're gonna do next
Well, actually
We don't have to worry about it
This is
Because
July 5th through 7th
The exodus will arrive
At Brushwood Campground
In New York City
And we'll probably meet you there
But if not
We sort of need to make plans
And I don't
I don't know, my friends
Exactly what we need to do
Maybe
Maybe we need to do
A winter revival
To get kind of pumped up
For
Materials
Okay, I know
You know
How has Santa been
So he
translating the new
into English
That's fine
We'll be right back.
Let the cat go, the man looking.
Get out of the way.
He said, man, don't bug me.
Get off my back.
I'm trying to dig what the cat's saying.
Jack said, ooh, they're pushing the Naz
because they want to dig his lick, you see.
Dig his miracle lick.
So the Naz say,
wait a minute, babies.
Tell you what I'm going to do.
I ain't going to take too far.
Six, eight of you cats.
That's what I'm going to take.
Twelve of you studs
and straighten you all at the same time.
You cats look like you're pretty boys.
You buddy with me.
So the Naz and his buddies
was goofing off down the boulevard one day
and they run into a little cat
with a bent frame.
So the Naz look at this little cat
with a bent frame and he say,
hey,
what's the matter with you, baby?
And the little cat with the bent frame,
he say, well, my frame is bent, Naz.
It's been bent from the front.
So the Naz look at the little cat
with the bent frame
and he put the golden eyes of love
on this little kitty
and he look right down
into the windows of his soul
and he say to the little cat,
he say,
straighten.
Boom, boom.
Cat went up straight in the now
and everybody jumping up and down say,
look what the Naz put on that boy.
You dug him before,
dig him now.
Yes, I can feel it.
Now you see the Naz are coming on so strong
and so fine and so great.
Talking about when's he going to appear next.
What did he do there?
He put it down once for the cat.
The cat dug it, didn't dig it.
Put it down twice, dug it, didn't dig it.
Put it down the third time, the cat dug it.
Wham!
Walked away.
Walked away with his eyes bugging out here
and they're bumping in there, everybody.
Naz coming on so fine and so strong.
They're pulling on his coattail.
They want him to sign the autograph.
They want him to do this gig here.
They want him to do that gig there.
They want him to make it the radio,
the video and all that jazz.
He can't make all that jazz.
Like a splendid cat's a cop
and the kitty's got his own lake.
But when he know he should show
to blow and cannot go
because he got some strain on him,
he sends a couple,
a couple of these cats that he's straightening.
So came a little old 50 cent gig one day
and the Naz couldn't make it
so he put it on two of these cats.
He said, boss, go straighten that little riff over there.
Boss said, take it off your mind, Naz.
We got it covered.
So on the way over, the boss run into a little old
20 cent pool of water
and he gets right in the middle of the boat
and all of a sudden,
land of a thunderstorm.
Lightning flashing and thunder roars.
And the boat goes up and down
and the poor cat's thinking of a minute
going to be the last.
And one cat look up and...
Here come the Naz.
Cool as anyone you ever see.
Right across the water, walking.
And the Naz is a little boy on board.
I think his name is Jude on board the boat.
He said, hey, Naz, can I make it out there?
Would you?
Naz said, make it, Jude.
And old Jude went stomping off that boat,
took about four steps, dropped his whole cart.
And the Naz had to stash him back on board again.
So the Naz look at these kiddies and he say,
what's the matter with you babies now?
He said, what's going on here, boys?
He said, what's taking place?
He said, what's all this fuss about here?
What's going on?
He said, man, he said, what's going on?
He said, can't you see the storm storming
and the lightning flashing and the thunder roars?
And the Naz say, I told you to stay cool, didn't I, babies?
Now the fame of the Naz is jumping.
The grapevine is shooting out sparks 40 feet long.
And they're talking about what he said
and how he stood up to all these big bad cats
and dug all that bad jazz and put them all down.
And what he said he gonna do and where he's gonna be
and how he's gonna be it till the grapevine is jumping so bad.
Now 16,000 of these studs and kiddies
in the Naz's little hometown where the cat lived,
looking to get straight.
Well, the Naz know he can't straighten them all.
There's too small a place to want to hang everybody up.
Nobody can make it.
So the Naz look out at these 16,000 studs and kiddies
and they say to them.
Come on, babies.
Just get on out down the road.
And there went the Naz, swinging away
ahead of all these studs and kiddies and 16,000,
stomping up a big, oh, big swinging beat behind them.
And their great necklace of love is supercharging
and charging to them.
And oh, it's brothers and brothers and sister to sister.
And the Naz is stomping on a sweet swinging beat,
going down the road.
And Naz talking about, how pretty are the flowers?
How pretty are the hours?
How pretty me?
How pretty you?
How pretty he?
How pretty she?
Naz had them pretty eyes.
He wanted everybody to see through his eyes
so they could see how pretty it was.
And to have such a wailing gorgeous morning up time,
that before you know it, it was scarfing time.
And these tall cats is 42 mile out of town.
Ain't nobody got the first biscuit.
Well, the Naz look at these cats.
And they say they kicking the sand out there.
The Naz say, you hungry, ain't you babies?
Say, yeah, Naz.
We digging you so hard what you putting down that we
didn't prepare, Naz.
We goofed.
Yes, that's what you call it.
So the Naz say, well, uh.
We gots to take it easier.
We wouldn't want to go ahead and order up something
you might not like, would we?
And they say, no, Naz.
You put it down, and we'll pick it up.
So the Naz step back a few paces, and he say,
oh, great swinging flowers of the fields.
And they said, oh.
Great nonstop signal of sound and beauty.
And the Naz say, stamp upon the terror.
And they hit it.
And the Naz say, straighten your miracle of the body.
The body went up.
And he says, straighten your arms.
The arms went up.
And he said, higher.
And the arms went higher.
And the Naz say, dig in further.
And they dug it.
And when they did, wham, the thunder went to.
And they look in the left hand.
It's a great big, sweet, stuffed, smoked fish.
And in the other, a big, thick loaf
of that gone crazy honey tasting nonstop sweet swinging
southern bread.
Oh.
Why, these polecats flipped.
Naz never did nothing simple.
When he laid it, he laid it.
Say, when the saints.
When the saints.
Marching in.
Go marching in.
When the saints go marching in.
Hallelujah.
I want to be in that number.
The saints go marching in.
Say, when the saints.
When the saints.
March in.
Go marching in.
When the saints go marching in.
Hallelujah.
All wants to be in that number.
The saints go marching.
Rubber, dig, dig, dig, rub in.
Oh, holy night.
The stars are brightly shining.
It is the night of our kiss.
Take your first.
Long laid, long laid, the world's different
hall of the father queen in the stone mountains west.
Ar Nerd gloss.
Our Nast's going wild.
Spring sand is ready to pop.
Fall.
Fall on your knees.
Oh, hear the angels voices.
Oh no.
Oh Mary.
Oh night, oh night, when Christ was born.
Oh night, oh night, divine.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Lord Buckley, the great, the old New Orleans beatnik.
Lord Buckley with that amazing rant on the Naz and the fishes and loaves.
And friends, that bobbled up Jingle Bells that we heard much earlier was from our own Reverend Yukon Jack.
Praise Yukon Jack and praise WICA, which plays this show.
And praise all the stations that plays this horrible show.
And we love you.
And I mean, seriously, it is.
We appreciate every listener out there, no matter how much they might hate this show.
And we actually love the holidays, too, because there's despite all the all that Santa crap, there's still a lot of slack.
And may all your Christmases, all your Christmases, all your Christmases, all your Christmases.
All your Christmases be white.
Thank you.
I love you.
You're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
For more information about the Church of the Subgenius,
write to Bob at P.O. Box 140306,
Dallas, Texas 75214,
or visit the Subgenius website at subgenius.com.
Thank you for listening, and praise Bob.
It's all Christmassy right now.
There's a bright green bob in the window and Christmassy lights.
Is there a DJA? Is DJA out there?
And devilish artwork that's Christmassy.
No, that's something just left for DJA.
It's all Christmassy.
It's all wrapped up in a perfumed ribbon-wrapped present.
Under the tree.
Well, leave the door open.
Open the door all the way so we can see if he comes in.
And those sugar plums.
Something's up the chimney hole in Satan's, isn't it?
Yeah.
Of Santa, I mean.
Otherwise, gosh.
I guess we have to wait till Santa comes, Dave.
Our beloved Santa.
I have wanted to...
Put your bag down for a minute.
It's so nice.
I was always so ready to learn.
It's great.
What?
For so long.
Christmassy Mary Xmas!
The preceding brought to you by your station in observance of the 450th anniversary of the Reformation.
Get.
Tiff.
Destroy.
Lone cow Dave, don't you know what they're doing to yourself?