I am seeking information about Bob. Let us see what is on the radio.
You're listening to PR News.
No, I don't think I can accept that program.
Nor that one.
The Self-Demons Power of Swat Team!
I cut my finger on a soup can lid. I got an infection and it spread to my dick.
It swelled up to the size of a human head. And then a mouth opened on it.
And this is what it said. It said it killed the Pink Boys.
But your job? Mom, go work and worship Bob Dobbs.
What are you doing?
We'll build a ship and take a trip. Come on and get a pay-write to coordinates.
Three and a half months in my garage.
Tearing parts off of old used cars. My groin at this point was unusually large.
I would occasionally hum while smoking cigars.
Our project was finished. The ship would hold twenty.
The power source was anything the crew would think was funny.
We didn't need the slack list. They're hapless.
Our work group is working. Escaping a stark fit.
On our way to Planet X-R-Sex. The next next.
The prairies quiver. Every pot of money shot at Connie.
It's an all-haas hour of work.
We're a bonanza. It's like a world without Tony Danza.
A fan to the pink shit that gets the charts.
In a world of dead hearts, I don't think.
Lobotomy and sodomy. We take a moment and we pause to reflect.
On the pinks that we feel and the planet that they wreck.
And we laugh like banshees and howl like comanches.
We're a victory dance in our underoos and panties.
Ah, yes dear friends. In our underoos and panties.
As the El Queso All-Stars sang in that classic old song.
Planet X-R-Bust.
And Tarzan's radio station is holding up beautifully here on the eighth day of 19X Day.
I don't know how many days we've been out here actually.
But Tarzan's radio studio was used to mix the bands and the ranters last night.
And it worked like gangbusters.
So it just goes to show if you leave old Reverend Stang.
With his old equipment.
His old Radio Shack mixer.
And his little borrowed other mixer from Reverend Heathen.
You did forget your reel-to-reel though.
Oh, and my 8-track. My 8-track recorder.
What about all your carts?
Anyway, it seems to work best when Reverend Stang is physically present with the band.
A foot behind them up on the stage.
That's the only way I can hear him.
I'm totally deaf.
I do this by kind of braille and watching the lips and the meters.
You know, the volume meters.
Well, maybe I should turn my amplifier up just a little bit louder to where you can hear it.
But everyone else's ears will just begin to bleed.
Yeah, right. Exactly. It doesn't hurt me.
No, it doesn't hurt you at all.
I can hear that bell over there. That great big bell.
Yeah?
I'm just guessing what you're saying.
It's not bad, huh?
And it doesn't matter on a subgenius show.
Amplify.
Yes.
It's kind of like kids in a sandbox anyway.
Let's see. I'm mic one. Hal's mic two.
And Reverend Angry Larry is mic three.
We have Reverend Angry Larry here today on Hour of Slack number one thousand five...
Insert correct number.
Aren't you lucky.
Yeah.
So...
Ah.
And I got my first good night's sleep since X Day started by staying in bed until one o'clock in the afternoon.
You're asleep now, Stang. You've got to wake up and get down to Caffeina's and sit up on the stage.
Oh, no. Oh, where am I? Oh, no.
Oh, Mom, I don't want to get up and go to school.
You... But I had the weirdest dream and you were in it, Hal. And you were in it, Reverend Angry Larry.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ugh.
That was a dream.
I actually did dream this morning that I woke up and decided to take some LSD, which I haven't actually done in many years because it makes my neck hurt.
Ha, ha, ha.
And then in the dream, just as it came on, I realized, oh, no, that was a dumb idea. I told my mom and dad I'd drive them around the shopping mall today.
My mom and dad are both aboard the saucers, so it was kind of a strange dream. But I woke up before I died either way.
Or before you took them to the mall.
Right.
On LSD.
Ha, ha, ha.
That sort of thing happens.
Well, there's nothing like suddenly having to deal with your parents on LSD. That's not something I'm recommending, kids.
Well, a friend of mine dropped an acid.
Ha, ha, ha.
And he was getting ready to chill. And suddenly his mom came to his door and said, oh, you've got to drive me and my church group around. We're going to meet a new writer.
Why don't you? Like, she writes kind of science fiction-y things.
And so he was barely able to hold it together, pretending to be normal, picking up the ladies, you know. His mom was directing, which helped.
And then they picked up the writer, Evangeline Walton.
Ha, ha, ha.
And she has a strange disease which makes her skin blue. But nobody was mentioning this, of course, out of politeness.
You know, so my poor tripping friend was trying to deal with someone with, you know, orange hair and lips and blue skin, you know, and everyone else just chattering away.
Things like that wait for you to take the drugs to happen.
Because any other day he wouldn't have had to go pick up this lady that was blue.
No.
Only the day that you drop acid.
I had a weird experience sitting around at my former in-law's patio.
They had a tarp on it and it had rained a little while ago and there were pools of water on the tarp.
And I was tripping. I looked at this pool of water and it was, it appeared to be shrinking.
And I was going, no, no, I've never had a hallucination before.
No, it, it, it, it can't be. What's going on here?
And it was a tiny little hole in the tarp.
And it really was slowly draining, you know.
But it waited until I was tripping to do that.
A ghost is in here drinking it.
Now, the puddle wasn't talking to you, was it?
No. I've never had anything like that happen.
Be calm. I am a puddle.
Well, I'm going by with what that girl that was eating the hot dog.
I was thinking of that too.
Yes.
Yeah, the complaining, whining, screaming hot dog.
Yeah, the screaming hot dog.
Who was that?
It was, I think it was designed as a scare film.
Yeah, it was an anti-drug film.
About this girl who dropped acid and her and her boyfriend stopped to get a hot dog at a vendor.
And she was holding on to it and she looked down and the hot dog began to talk to her about, you know, don't eat me.
Yeah, it's enough to turn you into a vegetarian.
Well, yeah, that.
Well, who knows?
Maybe your broccoli might start talking to you, telling you that, hey, I'm alive when you're cutting me up.
Well, one thing we learned out on Stang Ranch is don't name the animals if you're going to eat them.
Makes it a little harder.
Yeah, they raised a little calf.
They decided, normally they just sell, send them off to market.
But my brother decided, well, we'll raise one of these calves and take them to the meat processing place and get the calf back.
For dinner table.
But they named the calf Tap Tap.
And my niece was feeding Tap Tap and treated Tap Tap special.
And the day that Tap Tap arrived as a naked lunch on her plate, she became a vegetarian for about five years.
Wow.
Yeah.
The Lisa Simpson thing.
How could she tell?
Well, she just knew.
Well, the Tap Tap wasn't out in the yard anymore.
Right.
And frolicking around.
No, she knew that that was what Tap Tap was being raised for.
It was for their dinner.
It wasn't just going to be some anonymous cow wrapped in cellophane from the supermarket.
This was Tap Tap.
Now, my brother names his goats.
He always has about 80 of them.
And when they have kids, then he names all the kids.
And he really does remember all of their names.
These things look pretty much to you or me, they'd look all alike.
Right.
But they have, for instance, there's one called Twister.
And it was because the white spot on his forehead looked kind of like a tornado.
Well, that I can understand.
A cartoon tornado.
And he'd name them after wines for a while.
You know, one year all the babies would be named Burgundy or Chablis or, you know.
Boone's Farm.
But I asked him, you know, he's fairly close to them as goats go.
I said, I've never gotten a straight answer to this question.
It's like, what happens to them after you sell them?
And this last time I asked him, he said, I'll try not to think about that.
I believe they end up in Jamaican and Mexican restaurants.
I wish they'd end up in more regular American restaurants because I'd like to try goat more often.
And so this is X Day.
And we are the goats.
Bob is our shepherd.
And Bob is saying right now.
Our Judas goat.
I prefer not to think about that.
What happens to us, Bob?
What's Planet X like?
Oh, I don't want to think about that right now.
When the other deities go to Bob and go, what really happens to your followers after we rupture them up?
Oh, I don't want to talk about that.
Princess Wee is waving her phone at me as if she just located something that was lost.
Oh, no.
Her phone.
Is that what happened?
Her smile.
Gee, is that.
Her smile is returned.
She found her smile.
Which is always a very beautiful smile.
Your lost coat was left here inside in the nice drive.
Your lost coat was left and you've been worrying about that coat without telling me.
And you didn't want to admit you didn't have the phone.
Oh, I thought she said with.
Oh, well.
With the headphones on, I thought she said she lost her goat.
And she found her long lost goat.
Have you found your hat and goat?
Why a goat?
Well, there's certain aspects of X Day that always happen.
And one of them is losing really, really important things.
But then they come back.
For a while.
They do come back.
I had a video camera that disappeared for a terrifying three hours.
It was under a box in the back of my car.
It's always under something.
Kids, look under things.
And everyone loves under things.
What do you think subgenius is all about?
Hal explained that many times.
Yes, the underwear lurking beneath the clothing of existence.
The subligaculum that was known to the ancients.
Covering up our nakedness.
Yes, as ever had to happen after being banned from the Garden of Eden by the Urim and Thummim and the whirling swords of fire.
Oh, but now we'll take stay.
We can't.
We'll have a dance at Jake and all round about the kids are all dancing out there in the field.
We'll be hopping over the Hollyhocks and drinking the poteen.
The vampire leprechauns are stalking everybody.
Yes, leprechaunism isn't catching.
Not in the way you may think.
But you might find yourself shrinking a wee bit and being measured for an adorable little pair of buckled shoes.
This music, by the way, is made in Japan.
Of course it is.
It's from the game Monster Hunter 3.
When you walk into one of the little villages,
this stuff plays in the background.
Department of Product Placement Department.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Yeah, Capcom pays me.
Wait a minute, they're playing me.
They said they were going to pay me, but they're playing me.
Yeah, they're playing you.
I'm playing you like a sucker.
Wake up and smell the mucilage.
That wouldn't happen to a subgenius to get fooled or tricked or played
by a preacher or a salesman or anything like that.
No.
Preachers and salesmen lying or being wrong?
That's crazy.
Being snookered by Bob?
Could that ever happen?
If that was the case,
everyone would be asking for their membership money back now.
Oh, they do that all the time,
and they want the triple your money back thing,
and I have to point out,
no, you haven't proved that you didn't get eternal salvation yet.
That's going to take a while to prove that in court.
Yeah, that's a long time.
Can you prove you didn't get eternal salvation?
Can you prove damages?
An addendum to the embarrassment of the Christian great white throne judgment
is when they parade Stang and all those memberships.
The judgmental will be at the judgment.
Call forth.
I am recording angels.
Call forth Reverend Ivan Stang.
His name does not appear, Lord.
I work for the church of subgenius.
I'm not really supposed to be here.
Cast him into the lake of fire.
Oh, thank you, Lord.
The lake of fire.
That's what I most wanted.
Just, oh, thank you for not sending me to subgenius hell.
I have changed my mind.
Send him to subgenius hell.
Oh, gosh, that's terrible.
Oh, I'm going to live forever on and on in subgenius hell.
Oh, for the power.
The Briar Stang.
Right, right.
That's it.
Learn from the tales of Uncle Remus.
Yes.
Boy, I heard a politically...
That's kind of the whole thing.
I heard, I found a CD of somebody telling Uncle Remus stories at a yard sale, and I bought it.
And I was so sorry because...
I was so sorry because it had been all PC-ified.
Oh.
It had lost its charm.
You know, they had an African-American reading it, but he sounded just like a, you know, modern day.
Your next door neighbor with a can of beer.
Exactly.
No, he actually sounded more like Morgan Freeman playing God or something.
Oh, no.
And that's just not Uncle Remus.
I know Uncle Remus.
I knew Uncle Remus.
And you, sir, are no Uncle Remus.
Right.
Yeah.
Well, it's the same thing as Aesop, who was always...
He was also a slave, but smarter than the masters, telling these stories which encapsulate all wisdom.
And in the version handed down from African slaves by Joel Chandler, Paris, the original plantation dialect is preserved, which of course is now anathema, except in rap songs.
Right.
Exactly.
Yeah.
It's fine.
What goes around comes around one way or another.
You can't hold back something.
Soul.
That's what you can't hold back.
That's right.
A volatile quantity which will not be contained.
Just like here at X Day, where most of the subgeniuses could not be contained at Caffeinez
or this ultimate, or perhaps penultimate, Bobcast.
Well, you can't blame them.
Only the cool ones.
Because they know it's...
Here goes a huge load of slack moving out now.
Yeah, there's a truck.
We're watching a truck trundling down the road carrying garbage and subgeniuses.
There's an infant driving...
You make the distinction.
There's literally...
There's an infant driving the truck.
Right there.
There is.
There's a baby driving the truck.
I am not lying.
He's standing on his dad's lap driving the truck.
Yeah.
Just steering away.
Good for him.
Or her.
Well, it's nice to see you.
Thank you.
Well, I saw Reverend Dr. Sinsomniac in that truck smiling.
He's a new guy and having a great time.
Made some new friends.
I noticed there's a lot of new subgeniuses this year.
There are a lot of new subgeniuses and there were some that...
The old subgeniuses that they just got too old for X Day.
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
Well, they had to move off to other lands not so permissive as here at X Day.
We had G. Gordon Gordon.
Gordon is in Portugal now.
On purpose?
He had to...
Yeah, he had to...
Well, it makes sense for them.
They speak fluent Portuguese and Spanish, but they were a little concerned about President
Trump.
Did they yell all the time?
I'm sorry.
Emperor Trump.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean that.
It's just a slip of the...
By the time this show plays, we're going to be in trouble on the air.
By then, the election will have happened.
Last X Day, the recorded material lasted through November.
There we go.
The election drove Reverend Lonesome Cowboy Dave crazy.
And he didn't have far to go.
Well, that's true of any of us.
What was eating him?
What was the matter with the couple having a bunch of...
I was playing the recordings of us from X Day and he couldn't make it to X Day because
this time his body was sick.
Usually it's because his car is sick.
Or his dog, actually.
His dog, I think, was the main controlling factor in this thing.
It's not his car, it's his life until old Jake died.
I used to laugh at that because I haven't had a dog in about 15 years.
I grew up with him, but I felt like that's slavery.
And it is.
Most dogs don't know any better.
But then I inherited Pappy's old dog, Dammit.
And now I just can't wait to get back to Texas and watch Dammit run free some more.
The dog's name is Dammit?
Well, why not?
It was...
It's spelled D-A-M-M-E-T-T.
Damnit.
Sort of like Dashiell Hammett or Dammit.
All right, gotcha.
There's a Dammit somebody.
That's funny, though.
Because usually you're yelling at a dog that way anyway.
Dammit, dammit, dammit.
Chicken John's dog was named Dammit.
Right, with an I.
The I, right.
Yeah, and Reverend P's dog is probably Dog It or something.
Dog It.
Yeah, of it.
Dog of it.
And Reverend Andrew, Andrew the Impale, what was his dog's name?
Quickly.
He does a song about it.
Fuck it.
Fuck it, fuck it, fuck it, fuck it, fuck it.
That's his dog's name?
I don't know.
I'm just thinking since we're talking about its.
Yeah, well, on the broadcast version of the show, that's going to say beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
And that's fine.
I think that's funny.
They're fun.
Susie the Flusie and I both can see the word shit as a waveform.
Oh, and what it looks like?
Yeah.
That is good work.
It looks a lot.
It looks a lot like the shout on the Devo album cover.
They use the waveform of shout.
It's a longer than shit.
Yeah, she's drawing it.
Susie is drawing the waveform.
Kind of a little.
Yeah.
Oh, it's so much easier.
All you do is you look for that and you go, okay, that's, that's not, that's a beep.
I'm sure somebody could make a software that, that found shits, but they would also mistake other words, you know, and find things that sounded similar.
Slightly like that.
Well, if you were talking about a dog, like a shih tzu, it would only come out as Sue.
Right.
Or beep Sue or Bob Sue.
Bob Sue.
Well, that was a weird breed, the Bob Sue that they've made it.
They bred them over in China over centuries to grow the little, little one tooth would grow outwards and then up like a pipe.
Think how many generations.
Yeah.
They had to go through to make a pipe tooth dog.
Well, the Bob, Bob Sue.
An ugly dog, in my opinion, that's always drooling.
It can't close its mouth over its tooth.
It's wet fur.
It's a.
It has an underbite, I think.
I don't like dogs like that anyway.
I like it.
I think medium sized dogs are best.
I don't like the little bitty rat like ones.
Well, I have a basset hound and they drool too.
But yeah.
I like it.
Oh, X day where we talk about dogs.
Yeah.
I mean, but it's from a subgenius standpoint.
Yes.
You can talk about anything from a subgenius standpoint.
It'll sound about all sorts of justice.
Boring.
All different.
Shines.
It's boring.
Well, this all started around talking about Lonesome Cowboy Dave's dog and how is it a schnauzer or a Weimaraner?
What?
Lonesome Cowboy Dave's dog.
Oh, well, it's a dead dog is what it is.
What was it?
It's it.
It.
It's a great big Labrador, much like Reverend Heathen's dog, Bubba.
Bubba dog.
OK.
And I used to.
I'd forgotten what it was like to let a dog rule your life until I had a dog again.
And boy, they train you so fast.
Oh, yeah, they do.
You mustn't allow it.
And especially you must not allow cats to train you.
Cats don't train you.
They just do what they do.
No, they will actively train you.
Oh, no.
I have two of those too.
Yeah.
Cats secrete a special substance through their vomerosal passages, which they rub on you.
Eventually, they can get you to do their bidding if you don't watch out.
Cat ladies are humans who are completely far gone and in their thrall.
The Sissy the Flusy is a lizard lady that way.
They rub their gland, their lizard gland on her, and she's hooked.
Yeah.
Hooked, I tell you.
And afterwards, she saved one from the.
the freezing elements of a middle northern state or something like that.
They nestle in her bosom.
Yep, on the airplane, and she took it home.
So you see, if the cat will yowl early in the morning before you get up
and try to get you to get up and give it some food,
if you ever give in, even once, and give it some food, it will yowl forevermore.
Your only chance is not ever, not for the convenience of the moment.
Don't shuffle out of bed and do what it wants.
Do not ever start doing what it wants.
This is my advice, freely given, probably ignored.
We picked up two disemboweled mice up at Charlene's bed and breakfast in the last couple of days.
At a cat?
Yeah, that's a good cat.
Kings on duty.
Well, the cat saw Princess Wee get scared by a mouse.
She jumped on the table.
It said, eek, a mouse.
And the next thing you knew, there were disemboweled mice.
Corpses all over the place.
Corpses.
Well, it's like I said last night when we were up here doing our free jam with,
I forget, what's the name of our band?
Vulcan Jedi Mentat Dalek.
Right.
How's that?
I can remember.
Yeah, that's...
As we were playing last night, maybe it was just the noise,
or I would imagine that's probably what it was,
but there was plenty of mice.
There was plenty of mice shooting out from underneath the deck.
You know, I think those are actually voles.
I got a look at them and they didn't appear to be mice.
I vole you.
I vole everyone.
Yeah, either way.
But the voles did not like the band.
No, they did not like the band.
They were deafened.
The what?
Oh, check the vole meter over there.
Thank you.
We do have a vole meter.
We have a slackometer over there.
Oh, yeah.
We'll have to display that later.
It's not much good for the radio audience,
but it's one of those thermometers, you know, used for sales or whatever.
Only this is real and it shows the slack level.
And it was almost at the top last night.
Total saturation.
But then early this morning, it went way down.
Well, we have DJ Shaver to thank for bringing that.
That was a lot of fun.
His show last night was great.
I love his sock monkey reenactments of famous movie scenes.
He reenacted King Kong, Blue Velvet, Full Metal Jacket.
Yeah, Reservoir Dogs.
But he forgot to do the Exorcist, which is always a good one.
Right.
With sock monkeys, friends, if you can imagine.
He's manipulating them like marionettes.
Well, and he had Fay Wray.
Right.
He had Fay Wray that he took to the top.
He had trouble with the top of the Empire.
Oh, in 2001, where the...
Oh, yes.
The little sock monkey approaches the monolith tentatively and then learns how to build bombs.
Yeah.
Cool.
It's great what you can do with a sock monkey.
Oh, yeah.
And there's nasty things you can do with a sock monkey.
In our second childhood.
Infancy comes back again.
That he's working on something that has something to do with the amino acids with...
I think it was with the sock monkeys.
I don't know.
And so, some kind of a show that he was going to do.
Well, he was also talking about reenacting the human centipede with sock monkeys.
Oh, yes.
But he's going to need two more sock monkeys.
Two more sock monkeys.
Right.
And vomit bags.
Susie, I'd love to get you...
Susie's sitting there.
Could you share a mic with Reverend Angry Larry?
I would love to share.
I don't know if you could share a chair.
You'd have to bring your chair.
I would give up my chair.
You would give up your chair?
I would give up my chair for Susie.
The chairman...
Oh, my God.
The chairman of the...
Will you rest your boobs on my shoulder?
Awesome.
That's not going to get bleeped out, is it?
Lean towards the microphone.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my Bob.
The luckiest...
Where's the cameras?
Whoa.
Oh, wait.
I've got one in my pocket.
I forgot.
I always have a camera now.
It's so modern and futuristic.
Soon it'll be implanted in my head.
Oh, I can do it from here.
Oh, I know.
If I can wake it up.
Let's see.
It reads my thumbprint, you see.
Wow.
What?
Oh.
Oh, she's admiring my...
My...
My muscles and my physique.
Move your...
Hey, your hand is blocking her face.
Oh, that's good.
What, this is?
Yeah.
I can't see.
Oh.
There we go.
I have to do 10 of them.
He's got some muscles.
One of them come out hard.
Yeah, extend your arms.
There we go.
That's better.
Okay, for those of you on the radio right now, I'm getting a massage from Susie.
Susie the...
Susie.
I just asked for a massage.
She's just doing it.
Kind of a Japanese massage.
She happens to like my physique, which I find...
Amazing.
Oh, this is good.
Well, you're a rock star, Reverend Angry Larry.
Relax.
All that tension.
And a guitar player.
He's an oval man.
Only sax players get more conny than guitar players.
Where did you read that?
Frank Zappa said that.
Because it poked...
You know, with a sax player, he's got a big old horn poking out from his lap.
A guitar player has a big pole at lap level.
For his keyboard, it's a high level.
He's hiding behind a little table.
Yeah.
You know how to get a saxophone player off your porch?
How?
Pay him for the pizza.
That's a bass player joke, but we could use it for a saxophone player or a keyboardist.
Trombonist.
Because that's the other thing.
Banjo players.
Reverend Samantha is full of banjo player jokes.
Oh, yeah.
Of course.
There's that Gary Larson comic that showed...
Oh, yeah.
The people walking into heaven.
It says, here's your harp.
Welcome to heaven.
And they're down in hell.
It says, welcome to hell.
Here's your accordion.
I love that.
I bet Brother Cleve knows that one.
He's a squeeze box player.
I used to play accordion until I pleated my tits.
Oh.
Is that another word that's going to get beeped out?
Can you say tits on the radio?
No.
You can say titty, but you can't say tits.
I was informed of that just last week.
Oh, I see.
I was informed of that.
I pleated my boobs.
Yeah, there you go.
Who decides all this?
Yeah, boobs is a safe word.
It goes...
Where's the line that they do on radio now about, you know...
It's very vague these days, station by station.
Headmoms, llamas, tatas.
Melons.
Bazongas.
Bazookas.
Headlights.
Dirty pillows.
Yeah.
Ear warmers.
As we know right now.
Yeah.
Boulder holders, in which case your bra.
Yeah, those are all okay, but you can't say tits.
But you can say titties, because it sounds maybe more juvenile.
Yeah, it's cute.
Like poo.
You poo.
Oh my God.
Stereo.
You can say poo and...
Stereo boobs.
Wow, something happened where I lost my right side in my speaker.
Not like it matters.
There.
Oh, there we go.
I didn't do nothing.
It was a double negative, which means you did something.
Welcome to Tarzan's Radio Station.
That's the way things are done here.
Is Tarzan going to show up today?
Tarzan, I don't know if Lord Greystoke is...
Okay.
I mean, theoretically he's still alive, but...
He is alive.
But I just call it Tarzan's Radio Station because...
Why not?
It looks like something Tarzan would have in his tree house in those old Johnny Weissmuller
movies.
Yeah.
Well, the old one where he had a microphone dangling from a string.
We can't hear you, Susie.
The old one where he had a microphone dangling from a string.
I get my boobs right in his face.
That's so hilarious.
Oh, well, we'd have to deal with that.
Yeah.
He'll live.
Yeah, Tarzan's Radio Station is made of mostly borrowed equipment, and I think I did actually
buy this Radio Shack mixer.
Radio Shack.
And the M3.
I like it.
That was so weird.
The M3.
That wasn't supposed to be here, but you should remember...
Yeah, the M3.
...when I bought a pen.
engines should live.
Oh, yeah.
Well, let's take a look at ourPLK.
M1.
So, maybe it's not that aike.
Let's see what we found...
Okay.
So, but if we pick this one...
Oh, no, no.
We'll open the one on the machine.
We'll take a closer look at the machine.
Okay.
So, here's a DJ video we found.
That looks like something of a Disney prophecy.
You can build a theremin with the kits that you can buy there.
No, they don't do that anymore.
No, that was a bad business model.
It wasn't working anymore.
Let's get a young guy in here, the same guy that was a consultant for Borders before they went completely.
That's exactly right.
Let's get that hip young consultant from San Francisco.
He says he knows how to make a website.
Make it all about phones and pads and devices.
Well, we predicted that everybody would spend the next day looking at their phone.
I couldn't get the internet to work, so I didn't bother.
I don't use my phone necessarily.
I use it now as a watch and as a notebook.
I noticed that.
I use it as a notebook.
That's what I do.
If I have an idea, I just put it in there.
See, I can't use my phone for that.
I still write things down on little pieces of paper.
I don't have pieces of paper.
It just doesn't.
If you have the paper, you don't need batteries.
It's not going to run out.
I've got phone numbers and addresses on paper.
Oh, no, I still do that.
Every time, Princess, we...
She washes her phone.
I end up...
She's real glad I have that printout.
Oh.
Oh, literally, in the literal sense.
It's printed out.
Yeah.
Every time she washes it.
Every time it goes through the wash in some pair of pants or something.
Well, I guess I could feel so...
I just feel lucky that Reverend Lucy generally washes her pants with...
And there's money in it.
So when I throw the stuff in the dryer, take it out of the dryer,
there's always money falls out.
And it's still...
No, it's not coins.
It's always bills.
But they hold together because of the high-quality paper used by your government.
And so that buys my lunch that day with the money I found in her pants pocket.
She'll never know.
That she'll never know.
Put another one over on her.
Oh, great.
She's going to be listening to this show.
I just realized that myself.
Princess Wee's not going to like that about the repeated washing of phones.
Well, there's this thing called editing.
Just cough.
And she's listening.
Editing.
Oh, that's a great trick.
Bob Clampett, you know who he was.
The animator.
He told me that he would sit next to the censor
when they were screening those cartoons at Warner Brothers
and he knew something that he'd put in was come up
and he would lean forward and know the exact second and say,
do you have a cigarette?
By the time that's done, you know,
the offending piece of...
The animation has flashed past.
God, back in those days,
you were expected to sit and smoke a cigarette in the screening room.
Yep.
That was normal.
On the airplane.
Yeah.
In the supermarket, at the hospital.
Into your kids' faces.
The sailor next to you on the bus for thousands of miles.
Did people smoke in church?
Oh, they used to have ashtrays in the back of the pews.
Wow.
Yeah.
Yeah, they gave you cigars or cigarettes.
You had your choice when you went into church.
Wow.
That was the reason.
That was the reason so many people worshipped back then.
It was just for the smoking.
Just so they could go someplace to get free smokes.
Yeah.
Oh, hey, let's go to church, man.
Why?
To burn a fag.
Yeah, you get...
Wow.
Ay-yi-yi.
Ba-dum-bum.
Well, I've ground things to a halt.
That's also a...
Thank you.
Not fair for contemporary airplay or something.
He can't.
You can't take me anywhere.
You'd have to have a long explanation for the historical validity of that expression.
I pulled the music out so that we can hear Susie.
Uh-oh.
I'm smelling Susie right now, and she smells amazing.
She smells like a...
It's like eau de toilette.
It's eau de toilette.
She smells like a cherry pie.
Yeah.
We're talking about...
Pie.
By now, it's a tail-like pie.
There's a lot of flirty polecat smell goes around once in a while.
Really?
Oh, yeah.
I guess you just have to be...
Be in the right place at the right time.
Es sonce de l'eau, Todd.
I don't speak Spanish.
What is that?
Ah, yes.
X-Day.
Beautiful X-Day.
Think the sun might come out?
Maybe.
Someday.
Okay.
According to my rain-detecting phone, it's going to let loose with another gully washer
pretty soon.
Will it do that while we're waiting?
Are you waiting for the landing tomorrow?
It might.
Oh, my goodness.
It might be raining.
Maybe that's what it will take.
A real gully washer.
We've never been standing out there in the rain, have we?
No, we haven't.
Beseeching the aliens to descend.
No, we've been lucky in that respect.
We've been very, very unlucky in the other respect.
Fling off your clothes.
If the alien's actually showing up.
Turn your face up to the rain and believe.
Well, let's see.
Let's see if 7 a.m. is on this.
Oh, it looks like it is.
Now, of course, this weather tune prediction.
Oh, okay.
Here we go.
6 a.m.
Thunderstorms, 50%.
Sunrise at 6 a.m.
7 a.m.
7,000 degrees and God's thunderbolts.
Oh, yes.
Oh, no.
That's 70% chance of rain and thunderstorms.
Oh, now.
That's the prediction for 7 a.m. tomorrow.
70%.
70% chance of rain.
So, we're having a 7 a.m. wet t-shirt contest.
Yes, look at it that way.
With risk of electrocution.
Right.
We could all stand around naked, but then that would almost certainly ensure failure.
Yeah.
Obviously, I won't be flying my...
Maybe that's what it needs.
I was going to say, maybe that is what Bob is looking for.
There's not enough nakedness.
No.
Really?
Yeah.
That's fine for some of the subgeniuses, but then there's us.
Most of them have left.
Right.
Yeah.
Then there's us.
Oh, well.
I wonder what my right arm...
Through falling sheets of blinding rain, one might glimpse another body.
Obviously, I won't be flying my drone at 7 a.m.
I'd really look forward to doing that.
Can you fly it in here, Stan?
Not in here.
I was just thinking, though, this would be the last day that we could fake it.
The other one flies.
I'd fly over to the stone circle, stand around looking up, and I could fly the thing up,
except that it's about to damn rain again, I think.
Do a fake 7 a.m.?
Yeah.
Just for the documentary purpose.
Wow.
Like the one every year.
Yeah.
No, let's have not too much of that.
Now, listen.
Truth teller.
Oh, yeah.
Look at this.
Here's the weather tune.
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
Huge clouds of green oobleck are moving over.
And where are the little blue dot in the center?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, so there's...
And what's that red stuff?
The red is where it's really raining hard.
It looks like a brain.
It does indeed.
Looks like a human brain.
The weirdest weather I've ever seen.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, we're looking at my radar app.
Cerebellum.
Yeah, that's...
Yeah, there it is.
Uh-huh.
And it's green.
So it's a brain-shaped cloud approaching.
A green.
The brain from planet Eros or planet X.
Yeah, well, yeah.
That is definitely brainular.
Now, listen what happens when I bring the phone near the mic.
Oh, it didn't do it this time.
What was it doing?
It kind of happened when you were out here.
There was some kind of static that suddenly I could hear, but I don't hear it now.
Oh, well.
Okay, well...
Like when it's trying to do something, that's what happens.
Yeah, the phone is trying to escape.
Yeah.
I'm going to say fi on Wi-Fi.
UAV forecast for my unarmed flying air vehicle.
Well, you're a droneist.
Not good to fly because precipitation probability is 28%, it says here.
When does this Bobcast end?
You could get it right out and fly it between episodes of rain.
Nature's tantrums.
Yeah.
Well, we could end this.
We could end this and try to fly that thing.
Can we all fit on it?
It's big, but not that big.
It's pretty big, yeah.
Is it a big drone?
It's bigger than Wilman's, which is...
It is a very expensive drone with a gimbal camera on it.
It's like a steadicam.
Somebody gave it to me.
Whoa.
Thanks, Reverend Zyfod.
And it's nerve-wracking to fly it because it's worth a thousand bucks.
It's not a toy.
I was kind of envious of Dr. Cosmax.
He's a little tiny drone, which zips all over the place real fast and crash into your face
and won't cut your nose off.
This thing I've got would bite your face off.
Oh, my gosh.
The pressure is off.
The pressure is finally off as Pastor Pressure and Joyce head out.
Do you realize that Joyce is the only woman here who has ever been under pressure?
Oh, my God.
She just said that Joyce is the only woman who's been under pressure.
I don't get it.
His name is Pastor Pressure.
Okay.
Yeah.
That's...
Boy, your record's even worse than mine, then.
Real stud, I can tell you.
Real skirt chaser, huh?
Yeah.
Yeah, I know.
Don't take this the wrong way, but I really love your pickles.
Yes.
Thank you for the food.
This has been such an edible X-Day.
It has been.
Wow.
Thank you.
He says that he has also been admiring my pickles.
Thanks to the pressures, the nostrils, and the heathens.
Yeah.
That's a strange sentence.
We ate well thanks to pressures, nostrils, and heathens.
Yes.
Well, one heathen, but two nostrils.
Christ Bob.
We'll see you on the saucers tomorrow.
Good travels.
And there they go.
We'll see them tomorrow.
Yes, we'll see them aboard.
Well, because we're going to belly up to the bar at some point.
The cosmic bar.
After we finish fooling around, destroying cities, and saving national parks.
Yeah.
Then we'll all get together again.
Go, man, that was fun.
What next?
I'm going to take everything you have now.
I'm taking over.
Everybody becomes power-mad mega geniuses.
Go out and live on your own.
Uranus.
That's so cold.
Not comfortable up there.
Susie lost Uranus off of her headdress.
Was it ever found?
Yes, it was.
Somebody found it rolling.
They found Uranus rolling down the road.
They were rolling around, picking up crap.
It's another one of those sentences that you never think you'd ever hear.
I saw Uranus rolling down the street.
We picked it up and put it back on your head.
Perfect.
When you're a...
Among subgeniuses, you hear the strangest sentences that are being said for purely practical reasons.
Oh, that someone understands what you're talking about.
One time at Hal's place, I remember the sentence,
Be careful not to knock over the robots with that Tyrannosaurus skull.
And it was just said in complete practicality.
And to some people, they would go, what?
What?
But yeah, we know.
Yeah.
Well, we have to...
Our stuff is kind of crowded together.
You have to walk sideways sometimes through aisles between it.
And this was a life-sized replica Tyrannosaurus skull.
As large as that specimen ever got.
But perhaps they got larger than that.
Well, maybe we should knock this off and try the droney thing and just see.
Well, you can fly the drone and I can narrate if you leave it hooked up.
Sure.
Okay.
And Susie can sit down.
If you're using the drone, I'd better put on something that shows off some cleavage.
Oh, it'll be way up high.
It won't be close enough to turn anybody on.
But take a seat and a microphone and a headphone and a Dramamine.
Okay.
My machine's over in the car.
How many times have I fallen for that one?
Well, you know.
Susie's in the driver's seat now.
Yeah.
That's right.
This is...
Hey, do you want to rename the show, Susie?
No.
Okay.
You sure you don't want to...
We'll call it the Howlin' Larry Show.
The Howling Larry Show.
It could actually be, you know, the Howlin' Larry Show.
Yes, here we are.
Yeah.
Subgenius World.
The sun has never been out today.
No.
Curtained in cloudy red, he pillows his chin upon the orient wave.
But we wait for the possibility of a break in the clouds.
There's the infant driving the truck again.
Yes, that infant at the wheel is back with his giant truck.
He's got those evil baby eyebrows and those eyes that see too much.
I saw that someone brought a brain.
Now he's...
Look at him.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
He's a master of that truck.
He's interrogating peas.
He is.
He should.
Your papers.
Show me your papers.
Of course, the authorities have made it illegal to ride in the back of a pickup truck.
There he goes.
Here at the Subgenius Scofflaw Camp, these rules are simply tittered at.
Nine months old and they gave him a license.
Ohio is weird.
Rural America is like that.
Yes, it's not how old you are, it's who you are.
I bet he drives a Thresher, too.
Uh-huh.
And hasn't killed anyone yet.
Well...
The International Harvester, not the Grim Reaper.
They allow babies a certain body count.
Mm-hmm.
That's true.
I mean, yeah.
That's because they're so gosh darn cute.
Yep.
Oh, and there's Reverend Teeters LaVert.
Yes, the stragglers straggling in...
Yeah.
Because Caffeinus is still...
The nucleus, for what it's worth, of this hub of Subgenius activity.
X-Day still hasn't happened yet.
Yes, there is a pause, a silence, an eerie stillness before the dynamic pulsation of the X-Day moment itself.
Well, it's the calm before the storm.
But this morning it was a track event.
People were just pouring out of here.
What do they know that we don't?
They were running out of here?
Yes.
Maybe they'd concluded...
They concluded their pancakes and decided not to stick around.
There was a large pancake-related event.
I could hear nothing about anything except the pancakes we were missing.
It could have been a Scrapple-related medical crisis.
There's Stang's giant drone.
Ladies and gentlemen...
Oh, that's the controller.
It's raining.
The batteries are discharged.
Our ship behind us...
Uh-oh.
Does it need ultra-special batteries?
Does anyone here know how to fix an AccuJack?
Maybe he's going to get some expert scientific assistance.
There's good technical help here at X-Day.
Yes, the boffins can certainly fix up these ding-futzers and whatchamacallits.
Whatever these gizmos are, you gotta hand it to them.
I like that word, ding-futzers.
Well, you know, I'm talking about some kind of Weisenheimer device.
Something with a canoeter valve.
Yes.
And so, there it shall be instantly repaired when one gives it up for lost.
But we can't narrate the launching of the Stangian drone because it's delayed.
I've gone deaf. The music has stopped.
Can you restart, Susie?
Oh, there it is.
Oh, here's something.
Just act like it's back at your own radio station.
Yeah, I know what's going on.
I do everything at home. It's all overproduced.
You can do it now while Stang is distracted.
And when is he not?
Just manipulate the toggles and easily turn the controls.
Where's his porno music?
This would be much more lively with Waka Tiki.
Is there a bag of, box of tapes to your right?
Oh, the music is getting a little more lively now that you mention that.
I still don't see porn to it.
It still ain't 1970s porno music.
It's a little too stridently for screwing.
No, this is...
There's no...
I don't picture Harry Reams in any kind of film with this play.
Well, that's nice, though.
I'm happy about that.
This is like silly capering with nipples music.
Yeah.
So what?
Middle Earth porn?
Uh-uh.
I thought earthy porn was a lot different.
You know, I can barely hear this music.
I hope the mix is...
Oh, it's very loud in my ears.
Oh, that's it.
It's because you're so close to the radio.
Once again, I got...
I got the bum headphones.
Why are you...
Anyway, it doesn't matter.
As long as you can assure me that we're hearing the sounds of joy.
Can you hear yourself?
Yeah, I can hear myself.
Can you hear me?
Yep, hear you too.
That could just be the...
I hear the music.
It is just so soft and slight.
I was expressing concern that it might not be potted up correctly.
But then what do I know?
Oh, rough.
I'm a horny-handed son of the soil,
not an ingenious artificer of tiny electronical doodads.
But I love your horny hands.
Yes, turned into grotesque clothes.
Rookers.
Bowed by the weight of centuries.
You're clawed rookers.
Leaning upon my hole, I gaze upon the ground.
The emptiness of ages in my face.
And on my back, the burden of the world.
Time to stop.
For a delicious lemonade.
That's not lemonade.
Lemonade the negative.
Please don't take from me the one pleasure that remains.
I call it lemonade.
I call it getting laminated.
Back to work in 110 degree heat.
And then a spell of digging post holes in the hot sun.
But that's not anything like as hard as operating this radio bobcast.
Bobcast.
No.
On behalf of the church.
The church of the subgenius.
The post holes are done later, right?
Well, uh, you, yeah.
They're done after the plowing and the other things that need to be done.
We'll fix it in post.
Gotta milk the cows and chickens.
So all of that must be done.
Yes, you rise.
Those horses over there are gonna milk themselves.
No, they're not.
And, of course, the cottage cheese must be reinforced before it goes entirely bad.
Oh.
I gotta get out there and milk them bulls.
Yep.
Get that cottage cheese going.
Over in the woods, the loathly hag needs some repair on her candy cottage
because she's not getting as many children as she used to
and she's certainly even older now than she was when she first set up there.
See, now that you can blame the internet for.
Yes.
They don't care about candy anymore, not when they can play Candy Crush online.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Or some little old man with a twinkle in his eye might give you three magic beans,
so you better call the cops and have him hauled away.
So all the witches are driving white Ford Econoline vans with free candy spray painted on the sides?
Yes, with a clown painted on the side, too, just for good measure.
They're trying to keep up, but they can't keep up with the corporate clowning of major companies.
Ah.
There's the Stang drone.
My God, it's huge.
Did you manage to repower it?
Is it repowered, Stang?
This is 747.
Oh, no.
He's making the sound of what it should sound like when it is powered up.
Could you get the batteries attached?
Even if I had batteries, it's right in here.
Yeah, I saw that.
You wouldn't want to fly it inside Caffeinas.
Wellman flies it inside buildings all the time.
Inside KPFA.
That could be bad.
How much is this?
Well, if Wellman jumped off the Empire State Building.
Because this would chop your nose off.
Oh, yes.
Well, we don't want that.
I've already had it wasp assault my face.
We'll just put the Stangian drone on the table.
And you can imagine the magnificence that might have been had the batteries not been discharged.
Those things slice gills, India.
But it doesn't take exotic batteries, does it?
It looks like it takes ordinary.
No, it takes very exotic batteries.
Oh, all right.
So much for that.
It flies on adrenochrome.
Well, it's large enough to register as an aircraft.
I sent Reverend Obama $15 for the right.
Well, that's good.
Now you're legit.
If you pay us on time, we'll give it on time.
Well, I guess the baby truck is pulling out, heading back to Babyloin.
It's Nebraska.
Sit here on my lap.
Yes, sir.
Sit on your lap.
Some lap.
You need a lap dog.
Now, to go back to, we're talking about kind of like the nursery rhyme type thing.
I've thought about this before.
Yes.
With the nursery rhymes being so, you know, capturing children or just, yeah,
finding the magic beans with some old crone or old man or whatever.
Sissy.
Yes.
Would this change?
Would this change the whole Mother Goose stories?
Like, have they tried to make them more politically correct?
Or would it make it, like, not, you know, not acceptable for kids to read anymore?
The moment they mess with it, they destroy it.
So it's not supposed to be politically correct.
They never heard of that.
They're trying to warn kids that there are monsters.
And there are.
Old bags who will suck the flesh off their bones.
Throw them in an oven.
Yeah.
Well, it's usually old men that suck the flesh off their bones.
There aren't that many famous old ladies.
Toothless hags have to cook you first so they can, because they have so few teeth.
It's mostly the old ginches that are the bone suckers.
Oh, there's a lot of old cannibal.
The witches and stuff.
Takes one to know one.
The witch's oven actually softens.
The meat.
But then they also boil the victims.
They're all accounts of this.
They like to gnaw finger bones.
They don't have many teeth in their old gums, so the meat must be reduced to a pliable consistence.
And kids are tender.
Kids are tender anyway.
That helps them in their quest.
As in the Ray Harryhausen version of Hansel and Gretel, which you must have seen.
Yes, they actually do push the old lady in the oven.
In that one.
Do they actually eat her?
No, they don't.
But when they do, the malefic influence is destroyed and the candy cottage fades away,
leaving just a damp, sugary spot on the forest floor.
Well, I just wanted to clear that up.
Thank you, Dr. Howell, for clearing it up.
The animation in that short is superb, but then it would be.
Well, of course.
It's Ray Harryhausen.
Yeah, well, he's learning his craft, but it's amazing how much was inherent in that.
He does natural movements, which are very hard to do.
Sometimes the most natural movements are the hardest to stage.
Like a character casually walking backwards and looking natural.
Or, I guess my favorite part in the whole cartoon is where they spill the jug of milk
and it teeters on the edge of the table and falls.
With milk spilling out of it and breaks and fragments in the floor.
And the milk spreads, all animated in stop motion with cut-out wooden milk
and separately supported fragments.
Why didn't he just use a computer?
Well, he had to be in his garage in the back of his mom and dad's house.
Yeah, and the only computer they had was the size of, you know...
This campground.
Yes.
And it took Niagara Falls to...
It took a pool of thousands of vacuum tubes.
Actually, the first computer was composed of a thousand women crunching numbers.
Yeah.
There's a movie about that I've been dying to see.
I forget the title of it.
But Alan Turing and those guys were trying to crack the German code.
Yeah, it's the Imitation Game.
Oh, that's it.
Have you seen that?
Oh, yes, I have.
I saw it. Pretty good.
It's very good.
Yeah.
It's horrible.
I did to the man, but...
But good recreation of...
But yeah, it was done very well.
And also just the administrative struggle of trying to demonstrate that it was viable.
And then when they got it, they couldn't use it because if they automatically somehow knew what the Germans were doing,
the Germans would be on to the fact that they could, so they had to let their own people be killed.
Right.
Yeah, that's pretty tricky stuff.
War is hell, folks.
So don't do it.
But it'll be heaven tomorrow morning at 7 o'clock.
July 5th, 1998.
Yes, sir.
Yes, yes.
It shall happen.
We will overcome and splash our vengeance upon the earth.
We shall come to my heart.
You've been listening to the subgenius radio ministry Hour of Slack.
For free information, write to P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118 or see www.subgenius.com.
Praise Bob!