There he is, the guinea one! Get up!
The Self Genius
Power of
Swatch
Well, I'm just going to see about this.
Who are you?
I am someone who will call downstairs if I do not get an explanation.
Probably a nightmare.
I'm frightened.
Will you explain this at once?
Who is that man?
It's all...
He's gone.
Oh, no it's not.
Where do you think you're going?
Friends, this Hour of Slack number 968 is actually Reverend Susie the Floozy's Aliens episode of Bob's Slacktime Funhouse.
The bi-weekly show from amazing WREK Atlanta.
Greatest college station in the universe.
The other stations which also carry the Hour of Slack are also the greatest stations.
But WREK is one station which produces so much original programming that it leaks out into the whole world of other college and independent stations as follows.
Oh, have you seen Bob?
You ought to be here soon.
Yeah? Well, maybe.
Yeah, maybe.
I can feel the vibes in the air.
Ah, he's coming.
And when he comes, I run right through the jail door.
When I spot the driver with a second glance
Foot to floorboard impacts you now, gee
But here comes Bob
I ain't subtle in my ways of making friends
Girl, this bubble mess was caused by my neglect
Of course I'll pay him by the way I do it
And here comes Bob
I ain't subtle in my ways of making friends
No
But here comes Bob
Sometimes I will stoop to hitting two dork hoots without the frills
But that is just for casual acquaintances for stripped down thrills
Your car, girl, or mine it doesn't matter doesn't matter
Just be a little more confident
to know. But for affairs with standing
tower, I go after limousines.
It's always nice when something big
is acting as your go-between.
And for a group encounter, I'll hit
buses, mobile homes, or trains to
Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania.
It's hard to make
acquaintances in our big
town. The skies stare at
nothing much at all.
But here comes Bob.
Bob. I ain't so full in
my ways of making
friends.
Friends.
How quaint
it is.
Instant adulation comes to
some at birth.
One, two queens of corporate entities.
But here
comes Bob. Some day
they'll put me away. I'll think back
on active days. Most were worth
the minor scars. Some were worth the
damage cost. And the judge will say
to me, Bob, you've got a bad
means to a word.
Why an end?
An end.
But here comes Bob.
Are you ready for re-entry? We're ready.
Okay, Skipper. All set.
Zero X from central control. You are in
correct re-entry attitude and are
about to enter Earth's atmosphere.
Roger, central control.
Radio control over to you in five seconds.
Four, three, two, one.
Okay, you better start transmitting.
Right. Give me order.
Yes, sir.
Transmit. I will, sir.
Click.
What would you do if you thought someone
from another world was watching
you? Tonight
we present
Tales of Tomorrow.
Tonight's Tale of Tomorrow.
Appointment on Mars.
Mars.
Imagine, he says he's seen Mars.
In the year of our Lord,
3063,
it is a galaxy of peace
where not only worlds of different
civilizations have learned to live together,
but worlds of different life forms.
And this is the Galaxy
Bureau of Investigation,
the brain center of the universe,
where the great scientific and economic minds
of the planet are.
The planet's work in democratic unity
to preserve peace, prosperity, and equality among all men.
But powerful and evil forces throughout the galaxy
are trying to gain control of those GBI secrets
by which the democratic balance is maintained.
There's still a small group holding out in the caves
on the island, sir, but we should have them by morning.
The stars and stripes will fly over this island, too.
This war might finally be coming to an end, Major.
I certainly hope so, sir.
While below on the planetoid, the man responsible,
watches for the first sign of a falling ship.
Well, Mr. Stang, it was an almost foolproof plan.
Over here, Bob.
Bob. Over here.
Look at the flying saucer.
Oh!
Enemy plane, sir?
Impossible.
No plane can fly that fast.
That looked to me like it was from another planet.
I have to agree, sir.
It did look like it was from another planet, but...
Shall we report it, sir?
What, that we're being invaded by little green men from outer space?
Let's just keep it as our secret.
You can tell your son about it when he's born.
Major Spielberg?
Sir, yes, sir!
The space tape is coming!
You'd rather count the bubbles in ourselves to try
Cause the drops kick you in your side of your head and neck
The space tape is coming!
The human black side squash machine!
Carry through a wall Punch through solid rocks
Space tape is coming!
The space tape is coming!
Who is the one to hack the Microsoft computer?
Good man exalted highest wizard of them all
The space tape is coming!
Spread against my float Have my dough
Tough liver stone to wear down today
The space tape is coming!
clever disguises. But who am I?
Space tape is coming. Space tape is
coming.
We're doomed. We're doomed.
We're under attack from a form of light we do not
understand. You seem to be skeptical.
Those two flying saucers
are transports. What?
Aliens. Go, bitch.
Oh, God, no. Is today the 5th?
We need to get out of here.
All units, on the alert.
Saucer contact.
Ah! Look at the
window!
Hey, it's a flying saucer!
What are they doing?
Spaceship.
What do you make of that?
Yeah. They were here already.
We're driving down the street
sitting on the street.
Look at that.
Look at my IC.
I see flying saucers
landing over there. So I went
a little closer to see what I can get.
A good read. I don't believe
the plan is detected. The make-out
wasn't effected. They're gonna shoot
a behavior, a swipe,
and then I heard a leader say,
make them dance.
Na, na, na, na.
Make them play.
Make them dance.
Na, na, na, na.
We're not safe yet.
All right, I'll shoot him out of the sky.
Now, shoot it down.
Right.
Let it pass and then pursue it.
You got me?
Right.
It's gonna crash.
And inside the doomed ship...
All four engines are cutting out.
The air engine's dead.
No wonder, Fisherman.
All four chambers are stopped.
We're heading for a crash, Commander.
You better strap in.
You'll find straps in the cubby.
Are you getting any voltage?
No, nothing.
Yet fuel is feeding into the fission.
I'm gonna try and break the helix once we hit the planet.
That's where it's at, Mr. Reard.
At the rate we're dropping, you'll never make it.
We don't want to fall back to Earth, do we?
Talk about living on borrowed time.
Might be a case of out of the frying pan.
We're gonna be in the fire.
We've still gotta find a place to land, quick.
We're losing speed. I can feel it.
That isn't our only worry.
White lightning, white lightning.
This is ground beef control.
Do you read me?
Over.
I read only good books.
You must be way out there, pastor.
Over.
I'm high, all right.
But not on false drugs.
I'm high.
I'm high on the real.
The real thing.
Powerful gasoline.
A clean windshield.
And a shoeshine.
Over.
He's turning over.
Get thee behind me.
Are you in danger, pastor?
I'm all right, Roger.
Just a little argument with my co-pilot.
And guess what, Rog?
The little red needle's pointing to E.
And while that's always stood for excellent in my book,
I guess it means I'm out of gas.
You'll have to see.
Like me and my friends.
My favorite, M1570!
There's a flight leaving here in the morning
Destination was charted long ago
Now the captain is pretty and weighty
But the engine's still on the run.
are still I don't know
Waiting now for those
who still linger
With unflagging
it's great to every day
Reservations secured
by the Savior
On this one-way flight
to glory land
All aboard the master
calling from the runway
For our leaving
is almost at hand
Make your way
to the tonic of Calvary
For this one-way flight
to glory land
The UFO!
Something's happening!
It is opening!
Which one?
The one with the ever-widening hole in it!
A steadily increasing glow
seems to emanate from everywhere
Perception is confused
We cannot be sure
whether we're actually hearing
or experiencing something
telepathically
Oh, come on!
Welcome, friend!
Peculiar rays of shifting light
cause grotesque and eccentric shadows
to dance and play upon
a nebulous substance
which solidifies into form
and thus quickly dissolves
into spiraling vapors
glowing and vibrating
with tints and colors
you've never seen before
I'm embarrassed
You've never seen this as fish
where you, when you see fish
even esas
vosfority
Remember I was vapor
Remember I was just like you
Remember I was liquid
Remember I was someone too
Remember I need others
Remember I need oxygen
Remember I need to forget
There's nothing I've their there's nothing I've their
there's nothing I've there's spectacular
There's nothing I've her there's nothing ever
And it seems that something I touch under my nose
Remember I am human
Remember I thought just like you
Remember I had reasons
Remember I had friends like you
Remember I grew tired
Remember I could end all this
Remember I have memories
Remember I need to forget
There's nothing in but us
.
There's nothing in the dust
They slowly focus into their relationship.
The astronauts are here.
Thank you, dear friends.
I'm down.
I'm grounded, safe and sound.
Trailing clouds of glory, I'm down.
And I'm marching.
Yes, dear friends, I'm marching.
To dinner!
Because God Almighty, I'm hungry.
We're hungry!
Of course you're hungry.
I'm hungry.
We're all hungry.
So let's eat.
Let's eat!
And he said the word.
And we ate it.
And what was the word?
Bob.
Yes, dear friend.
There's nothing to eat here.
And the duck comes down with the magic word.
What is the word?
Bob.
And we ate him.
Eat him.
Oh, come now.
Just call me Bob.
Nobody really surprised me.
Hello, Connie.
Dobbs, I'm an admirer of your work.
Personal as well as professional.
Is that so?
Well, that's all you know about him.
The man's a fiend.
An absolute boorish.
You wouldn't believe the things he did to me.
And how.
You come in here and take our jobs.
You're dead.
I mean it.
Dead.
What's the matter with you people?
I was joking.
Don't you know a joke when you hear one?
I know you're my hero.
Please.
We don't want to hurt you.
This is my pipe.
How can one ordinary man have so many enemies?
That's a good one.
They shot me out of every room in the house.
We'll give that creep a taste of his own medicine.
You can even say that.
She's right.
He's got a great idea.
All right.
This tape contains the formula for the miracle drug.
The tape recorder here.
Is that recording good enough to identify the thing?
If we can intercept the waves.
Yes, sir.
We'll do our very best.
Something wrong with the recorder?
Don't think so.
Is their system the same?
Yes, it is according to the directions on the card.
There's so much time.
Yes, we know.
Click.
Please explain our desperate need to your people on Earth and help us obtain their cooperation.
We're going to need a lot of people.
The report we have just heard from our astronauts is truly amazing.
On the newly discovered planet, there exists a race of superior beings with highly advanced scientific knowledge, especially in medicine.
And furthermore, they have extended their hand in friendship to the people of the Earth.
Wow, what a terrific group.
Yes, you see there.
Way out.
Dr. P.
The newly discovered planet is located just beyond the body we know as Jupiter.
Is that correct, sir?
True.
Why wasn't it discovered before?
Planet X is very dark.
We cannot observe it with telescopes.
The new planet was discovered by Central Observatory while they were tracing strange radio waves.
Gentlemen, I can now announce to you that Planet X has been causing our recent magnetic disturbances.
Doctor, is there intelligent life on Planet X?
We can't tell yet.
It's possible that there is.
But the radio waves are not necessarily human.
We expect to learn a lot from Planet X.
It is our duty as Supreme Council to carefully study the proposal as set forth by Planet X and arrive at an early decision.
As physicians, my colleagues and I encourage you to agree to give consideration to this request for help.
We are looking for assistance and our reasoning is as follows.
We'll receive a wonder drug.
The organizations of women have no objection.
We acknowledge the sincere message of peace which was forwarded by the controller of the new planet.
It appears to me that we can learn humanity from these people as well as scientific knowledge.
Right, Bob?
Yeah.
The only thing he lacks is a little humanity.
Gotta look something.
From your remarks, it appears that we are in agreement.
The Council shall therefore order cooperation with the United States.
We are in agreement with Planet X.
Bobbie, there's nothing to be frightened of now.
On my planet, all of you will be free men, not locked away like animals.
Be free.
Find your own happiness.
I wanna go with Bob.
I wanna go to the boys club.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I just thought I'd have one for the road.
How about you, Bob?
Fair enough.
Oh.
Hey, Bob, save us a beer too, huh?
You'd better go now, Madge.
I won't go home alone.
Bob will take you.
I'll handle the whole thing.
Cool.
He's a genius.
A smart genius.
Oh, you and your shouts.
The never-ending frontier of the universe challenged his imagination.
Millions of tiny, dead, planetoid worlds like this one were merely charted and passed by
for the great and rich planet worlds beyond that beckoned with the promise of adventure,
exotic sights, and adventure.
New sensations.
But one man found what he was looking for upon this planetoid marked only on the charts
as Theta N1.
Barren, dead, but for a rich, single oasis of fertility where a lush and rich jungle
spawned a teeming, prowling, slithering form of life that existed to kill or be killed.
Well, our chances of getting out of here, even if I lock holes, are practically nil.
I'm not going to be able to get out of here.
Our only chance is to take the ship of our friends up there.
A new life awaits you in the off-world colonies.
The chance to begin again in a golden land of opportunity and adventure.
Feel the tension of unbounded lust.
See the trembling flesh consume itself in nights and days of uninhibited abandon.
Know the twisted passion of jaded desire.
Superior mutants, repent, quit your job, and slack off.
Are we controlled by secret forces?
Do you ever get the feeling that free will is a joke?
Do people think you're strange?
Do you?
Then you may be on the right track.
Give me slack, or give me food, or kill me.
Kill me.
Brains on!
Evil demons have kept the truth from humanity for thousands of years.
God has been misquoted all this time.
Jehovah is an alien and still threatens this planet.
Jehovah is an alien.
I am not immune to terror and menace.
You can fly, you may die.
Brains on!
You may die.
You might choose safety over home to live in.
I don't know why.
Maybe I'm too strong.
Hurry, the 10s come down July 5th.
Prayer is all we have.
We won't get a second chance at it.
Hey, Bob, say that's true, huh?
So what do you say, Bob?
What can I do?
Now we deserve a vacation.
Not you, Glenn.
You're flying back to Planet X.
What?
You're to be our first ambassador.
Whatever's fair, pal.
Fair enough.
I think not.
So I tried to call the police.
They heard the focus is to be in the field.
But I went out to tell the man.
They could be his assistant, and she didn't care.
I went to one of the military.
They said, come on, man, is this really necessary?
I called up the highest branch of government.
But they couldn't even talk.
Dancing with the president.
Mega bass.
Mega play.
Oh, my goodness, that's a space helmet.
Oh.
Come get your luggies together now.
Oh, my gosh.
Hurry up, girl.
Oh, Connie, it's good to see you.
Oh, for crying out loud.
Sorry you mustn't mind me.
I've been up all night, all kinds of things racing through my mind.
It's supposed to be.
I was nervous just before the ceremony.
At least, so I'm told.
I'm not a bit nervous. I'm quite calm.
Oh, I've reasoned this whole thing out.
Bob mustn't make a mistake.
It would ruin his whole life.
Okay, so you win.
I'm going straight down this minute to get our tickets.
Tickets?
Oh, I have my veil!
Let me stand still a minute.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I guess I'm just too excited.
Am I blushing?
Very calm.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I should have had better sense of the fact that a cheap little punk like you carry a gun.
All right, get my bag. We're leaving.
Come on, everybody in the living room. Go ahead.
Are they going to be coming along with us?
Yes, it would be very helpful to us if we ever get lost.
Because they can always cheer us up.
Well, I sure hope that doesn't happen to us this time.
Only joking.
You're on her side now for all I've done for you.
Who does what have you done for me?
I warned you.
Well, I'm not exactly grateful for that.
We are getting just exactly what you deserve.
And one of the girls is a dickhole to death.
I hate you.
I hate everybody.
You got my heart.
Sorry.
Oh, you wait.
Someday you'll need a girlfriend.
And then you'll give your country to me.
Going down?
No, I'm going up.
The 5th of July.
Mr. Tang.
Any past minute instructions?
Oh, you're quick.
You weren't anybody who hadn't seen you come into my office.
Oh.
Yes.
Stop.
Who else am I talking about?
Relax.
Get the red alarm off for me.
There'll be KPI agents all over the place if I have to see you.
Perhaps, Mr. Tang.
I don't like this being around when the council is voting its most important decision in galaxy history.
Right.
The conspiracy has now been unmasked.
And we're not going to let you escape so easily.
But I must go.
It is wretched for us all.
But please help me.
Ridiculous, Mr. Tang.
I've ordered a red alarm for them on Mars.
Benedict.
While I'm on route.
Keep me informed if you get any reports on it.
Right.
You'd better get going.
You'll miss your takeoff for every...
Goodbye, Doctor.
They're looking for the Earthman.
Will you call off the rocket patrol?
Now, children, the idea that you behave yourselves and let the Earthman alone.
Look, children, why don't you play in your trailer?
But that's a rocket ship.
Good.
Why don't you fly to the moon?
Yeah, let's go.
Let's go.
Grab your hat and we'll head up in the blue.
In a little rocket built for two.
Baby, we're gonna blast off.
And before we're through, we'll leave the cares that we know on terra firma below.
While we go singing and swinging on the moon.
Let's go.
Have a holiday on the moon, honey.
How can that noisy Earth below?
And if your folks ask about our house, honey, tell Mater and Pater we live in a crater.
We're really gonna enjoy a life of bees.
Living on moonlight cocktails and green cheese.
Mr. and Mrs. Space Commuter.
If you please, and in a few years we might produce our own satellite.
While we go singing and swinging on the moon.
Swing on the moon.
Moonlight cocktail.
I wish on the moon.
Bob, rise and shine.
Come on.
Bob.
Come on, Bob.
Get up.
Bob!
Get up!
Come on!
Come on, it's six o'clock.
Rise and shine.
All aboard the master's calling from the runway.
For our leaving is almost at hand.
Make your way to the top of Cape Calgary.
For this one-way flight to glory land.
Bob.
No!
Oh.
Now this flight is for all those daily need.
And their pilot is Jesus God's Son.
And the passenger's all for it safely.
They're prepared for this heavenly run.
My brother, don't worry.
Let this flight lead without end
For soon all those on board will say goodbye
Make your way to the cold edge of Calvary
And confirm your reservations to the sky
All aboard the last crew calling from the runway
For our leaving is almost at hand
Make your way to the cold edge of Calvary
I want to get a size of a piece, yeah?
Why, how can you tell?
I can, I'm just guessing.
After all, who knows what's out there?
Well, we'll soon see.
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
we present the biggest star in the universe,
none other than Cliff Richard Jr.
A shooting star will shoot you
When Mars goes to war
The man in the moon will jump on you
If you don't love me no more
If you don't stop making me lose faith
I will have you
Put up there in space
So just do what I'm telling you
Cause I got friends
Baby, listen to me
A shooting star will shoot you
When Mars goes to war
A man in the moon will jump on you
If you don't love me no more
applause
No one of the lads filled out the schedule of events for the day, and not one word about Susie's checking out for the Bider Week.
What?
Are you a member, sir?
No.
Pardon me, sir, if you're not a member.
Are you a member?
Ah, it's part of that junk we bought from Bob.
Well, why don't you look in the book?
It doesn't say the mark.
Copy, Bob, we only paid two quid.
No, it's not listed.
Are you wrapping it?
Yep.
Seems in a far flurry, that one.
Then the customer seems anxious to buy.
I haven't much time.
We haven't discussed the price.
That'll be five pounds.
Five pounds?
Five minutes to go.
Well, where are they?
Where did the Earthman go?
The Earthman?
Uncle George?
He's present again, Doctor.
Aren't they the ones?
Who hijacked the galaxy-quilliam supply last year?
Yes, we've been looking for them ever since.
Right.
Yes, Mr. President?
They were the whiffle, sir, once, just.
And he hung up.
Yeah, now the boss says it's a very bad thing for the country.
See, because this contract starts after the war.
Oh!
This president is a realist.
He deals with the fence as they are.
Yeah, right.
They'll be here.
Those people always keep their word.
You won't forget your promise, Bob.
Sure.
It's a joke, Doctor.
You're not going to let me in on it?
Aren't you going to let me in on it?
In on it?
Sure I will.
Sure.
And now, Doctor, here it is, as we promised.
The miracle drug which can cure all disease.
Not bad.
Whee!
It makes you feel like a two-year-old.
Why didn't you tell me you could make stuff like this?
Oh, just a little thing I whipped up when I was with the medicine show.
Every drunkest in New York is inquiring about Jane.
We start bottling it in a little bit.
Good morning.
And now, the spaceship is ready to take you back.
When you were here on your previous trip,
we recorded all the information to the smallest detail.
We have recreated your ship from that data.
It's opening.
I bet it is cold in there.
I bet there's food in there.
I'm saved!
I'm going in!
No!
Don't do that, sir!
It's dark and dirty in there!
Oh, but Mom!
It's full of bees and spiders!
You might poke your eye out!
Mom!
When did your father come home?
I'm going in, Mom!
There's a vacancy!
I'm going in!
Everything all set for the big party?
We're getting there.
I'm gone.
Susie here still loves the Whopper.
Man, this is one thing I really don't mind standing in line for, if you know what I mean.
Did you get her innuendo?
I've always hated that creature, the way she exploits her title and everything.
Girl, that woman's about as subtle as a rhinoceros horn.
I'm going up the backside.
In fact, I thought they put her in a state sanitarium.
They did, but they let her out.
Look at her record.
They stink!
I agree!
Ooh, finally, Planet X are bust for us, baby.
Gee, I wonder why those guards are bludgeoning Stang over there.
Hell, that dude has more kinks than a knotted slinky.
Hello, Susie!
Isn't this a beautiful day?
Oh, hey, El Diablo.
Ooh, great sergeant at arms uniform.
Especially dig the thong.
Are you a member?
Ooh, here's my subgenius membership card.
Boy, I've been hanging on to this son of a bitch for 23 years.
Hey, Susie.
Your seams are crooked.
I'm not wearing stockings. Those are probably just busted leg veins.
Oh, hi, Bob.
So what do you say, Bob?
I don't want to have anything to do with it.
Oh, my subgenius membership card.
Ooh, just give the great and wise a pair of oversized breasts and a happy ending, and they'll oink for more every time.
Oh, I'm shining.
Why does the sun rush to shore?
Don't they know it's the end of the world?
Cause you don't love me anymore.
Why do the birds
go on singing?
Why do the stars go above?
Don't they know it's the end of the world?
It ended when I lost your love.
I wake up in the morning
and I wonder
why everything's the same as it was.
I can't understand.
No, I can't understand
how life goes on the way it does.
Why does my heart go on beating?
Why do these eyes of mine cry?
Don't they know it's the end of the world?
It ended when you said goodbye.
Why does my heart go on beating?
Why do these eyes of mine cry?
Don't they know it's the end of the world?
It ended when you said goodbye.
Goodbye.
It remained for many minutes.
It ended when you first realized that i was failing.
Why  integration accepted this creation.
Why your desire came to rest you?
The rockets! Use the rockets!
Hello?
Senor Dolph told me to phone you.
Already gone?
If I were his mistress, this never could have happened.
We change our plans.
We begin the attack on Earth now.
Read the tape.
Does the tape show?
Red dots are decreasing.
Good.
Doctor?
We've begun broadcasting.
Stand by to attack.
Stand by.
Hello, and this is Crazy Chris Smith.
And welcome to another edition of Unethical Alien Abductions.
Here we are in the town of Dayton on June 15th.
The July.
1999.
Weird coincidence?
I believe not.
It's another unethical alien abduction.
Come on, boy.
Hooper, walk.
Come on.
A children and a reader.
The government was thinking,
ethical, walk in the park.
But for him, he did not see the future.
Or it was very, very unethical.
towns in the crack.
The state attitudes and the ways they got there.
But the Amendment Achievment Agency
said, male and female octopus tried to shoot at it.
Itsed for a responsive,
unethical Alaska fly-based operation.
Both do not eat anything.
But even so,
there applies this contract,
We have to fight people.
There's no other way.
Get back here.
Get back.
Man, that's the door.
Give me my door back.
My dead car.
Bunch.
That's enough.
Another word space addiction?
No.
It's just an unethical alien objection.
We've received a report that Commander has just taken off from Earth.
Good.
Your job is to intercept them at Planetoid Epsilon 30.
This is one job I'm going to enjoy more than I expected.
What do you mean?
I am the controller of Planet X.
To the people of the Earth.
I command that you obey the following orders.
Orders?
You will place the Earth under our absolute control and be governed as our colony.
What is it, governance as a colony?
If you do not obey these orders willingly and immediately, we shall destroy your civilization.
Double trust and think.
So we stumble right into a trap.
I repeat the order.
Earth will continue to exist only as a colony of Planet X.
That's a plot block.
The startling announcement touched off demonstrations around the world.
Some demonstrators urged capitulation, calling for peace at any price.
The majority, however, seem to favor strong resistance.
Opposing factions clashed violently in dozens of world capitals.
And police were hard pressed to restore order.
I demand the attack.
Come with me if you want to live.
Thank you.
course for Planet X in the Scorpion constellation. Over.
Right. Good. How are you feeling? You alright?
We would just like to get a little exercise. Well, on Planet X, you'll get
plenty. What's this? I think it's chicken.
Yeah, it doesn't taste like chicken. When you're rich, food
doesn't taste like what it is. My chicken is the star of the show.
Would you like some more chicken, Bob?
Yeah, well, less talk and more beer, my friend.
Thank you, sir.
Dad, Bob broke your beer. No, I didn't. Doug broke it. It was you.
Hey, Bob, save us a beer, too, huh? Right, right. Okay, Toast.
The guy who got us here, our good Captain Robert.
How do I know that?
Monica found another one of these mushroom things.
Hmm? And the hat's played to the airlock. Cool.
That's the third one, isn't it? Howard used to call these things space barnacles.
It's hard to believe he's dead.
It sure will be nice to lie in some good old-fashioned Earth-type sunlight
after 90 days of this. But I'm getting off at the next stop. You're not getting off at any
stop. You're in this for keeps, and don't you forget it. Nobody's gonna walk out on
nobody. What are you giving me, a true confession? Listen, wait a minute, seriously.
I think I saw that guy from Planet X. Controller? Here on
Earth?
Yeah. In the middle of the night, I woke up and the controller was in the room.
Ah, I think you were dreaming. That's what I thought at first. But you always
know if it's a dream when you wake up. What? Well, did he say anything?
He said that all preparations were made not to worry about anything. I wonder what he meant.
Don't ask me. What do you think? I think maybe we're
putting too much trust in Planet X. That's right. I don't think there's any
doubt about it. Maybe they don't have any water up there. Maybe they figure it's time to go.
We're only GOOD most people in the world, I unleashed the magic of
Ah!
You just practice sitting down on the camera.
Nonsense!
Is he crazy?
He must have.
Now let's go.
We're not  touching you.
Hey, listen to what we're talking about.
Look, look.
He puts a ogre down at his chest.
They are now on the flying side of Jupiter.
Do you see anything?
Check your readings.
The radar thermometer is reading 15 degrees.
Oh, so far from the sun, that's a high temperature.
It's the universe. Nobody knows its secret.
Well, we'll be landing soon.
Bob's boat was attacked here.
That dang thing just sits in that area.
And inside the doomed ship...
Zero X to Earth.
We have just touched down successfully on the surface of Mars.
Planet X.
All systems are go.
We'll radio a full report to you in 30 minutes ground elapsed time.
Click.
Well, Dr. Grant, what do you think?
My first thought is to get as many samples back to Earth as possible
so that we can look into the whole question of the possibility of life
existing on this planet.
Sure, but what's your initial reaction?
I think the atmosphere would be breathable,
but too thin to sustain life as we know it.
I agree with all Dr. Grant has just said,
but I've always been fascinated by that phrase,
life as we know it.
I have a feeling that we may encounter life as we don't know it.
Well, clearly there's life on Mars.
Planet X.
But I guess it's not life as we know it.
So this is Mars.
Planet X.
You know something?
I'm disappointed.
What?
Well, I mean I expected something different.
Disappointed?
All we did was come to Mars.
Planet X.
Disappointed.
Yeah.
No, I'm happy about it.
Don't get me wrong.
It's just that...
Well, it's kind of strange, that's all.
Nothing here.
There's rocks.
But no people.
No intelligent life.
Why not?
That's what I'd like to know.
Well, that's silly.
This is Mars.
Planet X.
You can't expect to find a life like ours.
Yeah, he's expecting to find the green-skinned monsters.
You know.
Oh, sure.
Wait a minute.
A liar coming out of the mouth.
No, you don't understand me.
Look.
There's nothing.
Only the barrenness and the howling wind.
Lonely plane.
Just nothing.
I don't know.
It's weird.
Makes me feel kind of funny.
Yeah.
It sounds like a poor barren.
Okay.
Yeah.
I tell you what.
I don't think we're going to find any very large mineral deposits.
Why?
How can you tell?
I can.
I'm just guessing.
After all, who knows what's out there?
Well, we'll soon see.
Look, ladies, I'm anxious to find out what's out there.
You want to come along?
You're going to stay here and dish a while, huh?
Hey, wait a minute.
Now what?
My rabbit foot.
I almost forgot.
I feel like that superstitious scientist.
Ah, it got us to Mars, didn't it?
Planet X.
Bart, I think the spaceship just had a little bit to do with it.
I don't know.
A Martian.
You guys from Planet X.
Yeah, I see a Martian out there.
Get away from me.
What?
There's nothing out there.
Yeah.
I can see a Martian.
You guys from Planet X.
Hey, there he is.
Look out.
Bart.
No.
Bart, put up your gun.
No, get away from me, Robbie.
We got to get him.
Get to get him.
Get your hands up.
Bart.
You're a Martian.
You guys from Planet X.
Gee.
Oh.
You shouldn't have done it, Robbie.
You shouldn't have.
You want to make an omelet, you got to break some eggs.
Look.
We welcome you.
Won't you kindly seat yourselves and be comfortable?
I'm controller of Planet X.
And I've invited you here to discuss something that's very important.
Discuss what?
Where's the spaceship?
Don't worry.
It's safe.
Sure.
We'll be right back.
Well, well.
It was quicker than we expected, Crick.
Yes, Rob.
It was almost too easy.
Such simple minds to invade.
The little one.
He suspected for a while.
But fortunately, he was the weakest of the lot.
Well, they're all gone now.
Do you think war will come around?
I doubt it, Frank.
Come, shall we have a look at their ship?
It may prove interesting.
Rocket for the courtesy of the American Rocket Society and Reaction Motors.
Oh, yes, Seekers, we've finally come to the end of the annual Alien X-Day show,
which I couldn't have done without able assistance from Mel Torme,
Niall Rogers, Gary Newman,
oh, little dollop of Rappo,
and big old hunks from St. Ann and Helena Handbasket from their Slogans Run CD.
Good subject.
Geniuses, who will be on board those pleasure saucers?
And I know it for a fact.
Oh, Seekers, this was just a simulated cautionary tale.
Oh, but let it light a fire under your ass
to do something before July 5th comes zooming down on us all.
Oh, yes, this has to be the year that it's going to happen.
And you're in luck because you've got just enough time
to write for free information
because Bob is going to cover our asses, Seekers, I'm sure of it, yes.
So pick up that pencil and drop a last desperate line
to the Church of the Subgenius at P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Because, yes, Seekers, there is just enough time.
Oh.
And it's going to be this year.
I know sooner or later Dobbs has to keep his covenant with his people.
Oh, it's killing me that the first time in nine years
I won't be able to make it up to Brushwood.
But, Seekers, that doesn't mean that I'm not going to be celebrating X-Day.
Because at 7 a.m. on the morning of July 5th,
I am going to be out in my front yard naked,
lying flat on my back with my eyes fixed on the horizon,
waiting for that first wave.
And I'm going to face raping bats to come zooming down on me.
And the devil can take the hindmost because we're not going to be here.
So go ahead and blow off your jobs and your lovers and your lives.
And tell him Susie the floozy said to.
Good night, Seekers.