From PR News in Washington, I'm Carly Fiorina.
Fiorina said she is Ted Cruz.
Fiorina says she is the man to do it.
Fiorina said Fiorina ended last month.
And said PR News is stronger with her voice.
B2B, B2B, we weigh the only set of lives lost will be by Ted.
PR's reports left one person dead and sick and five others.
A report released this week by a committee of scientists says PR News produced a completely unusual effect that damaged the subject's brains.
Those who got lower doses will make recommendations to improve PR News.
The Dow is 27 PR.
PR News would enshrine discrimination in the state's institution later this week.
Carly Fiorina is endorsing PR News in Washington.
Mr. Speaker, a message from the Senate.
The subgenius power of mob.
Bob.
Now here's something.
we may not have heard before from 22x day last summer dr howell reverend angry larry yours truly
and i'm not sure who else maybe mother miller and somebody named chip showed up but that may
come later i just don't know we're assembling these uh shows out of whole cloth and and kind
of winging it watched saucers never arrived yeah yeah yeah like you wanted to never spoken
boiling water this water will never boil smoked pot never whatever
there that water lays it down doesn't it yeah oh here reverend angry larry what like some of that
i actually have a she's going to
get me one oh okay be here momentarily you see how sharing and kindly and thoughtful i am oh yeah
no i i don't tell everybody that tell them reverence you know what if i tell everybody
that they'll go ooh the bobby that's my problem see like oh yeah you're really cool with the
teacher yeah yeah whatever but it's just like in that movie yeah well l ron hubbard had a similar
sad position you know
he did yeah you damned if you do and damned if you if you don't yeah poor old l ron not that i ever
met him or dealt with him i i helped kill him but that was indirectly i didn't mean to
so yeah
oh smell that pollen yes wafting on summer breezes through caffeina's restaurant
and gathering place here on x day the fifth or quarry of july are you doing all right there
powder nostril the year you look very very 2019 uh relaxed you are very full of slack sir so sure
about the legitimacy of this day how many times during human history for political and sacred or
reasons the dates and the calendars have been changed altered days added and subtracted
even a week in one well-known instance yes uh the uh wonders of the deep
uh the monsters of the air and everything that is happening uh see and land and so forth all right
here part of this show so don't forget to subscribe to support this show and also watch our other themes
go away as if there was any place to go this is supposed to be the music from house of frankenstein
in the back it is that was the music for professor lampini's carnival after lampini himself was
assassinated by hugo the hunchback hey uh now known for his percussive theme for the wolf man
i guess this is a low volume cd he also wrote the music for house of frankenstein
house of dracula the mummy's curse the house of mummies the house of the creature they're all
the house of jaws son of jaws son of the mummy son of the mummies curse from the mummy reverend
did you ever pay any attention to the monster high uh mythos no you uh you told me about
sun
something a couple years ago their movies are are kind of fun they're based on dolls but they're
they're teenage girls but they're monsters but they're teenage girls but they're monsters no
they're teenage girls and they're monsters yeah it's girls and monsters what's not to like the
girls are monsters well they could it could be that because it's a pink toy line aimed at tweens
that it would be really stupid and it kind of is especially if you spend a lot of money on it
yeah anything begun on a tie-dye and some
boys don't know why they're broken one of the day they are
well i guess i as of last glass Hassan
or six movies you're actually pretty if you're a fan of old universal monster pictures they're full
of inside jokes you see there's one that's like a frankenstein and one that's the dracula and yeah
draculaura is the daughter of dracula really he is the daughter of frankenstein she's only 16
days old and there's robecca who's an automaton but cute cleo is the daughter of the mummy and
she walks although she looks like a beautiful teenage girl cleopatra style she walks with a
little hitch in her walk cycle which only you and i and dr howell would know was a reference to her
dad the mummy right limp all the time limping yeah this tall long-legged stuck up she's kind of the
rich girl the rich girl of the house yeah except it's cleopatra yeah you know and her dad's a pharaoh
or something
in this case but yeah it's it's it's pretty fun there's a tragic romance between
the son of the creature and the daughter of the sea serpent because one's fresh water
and one's salt water is one of their names uh gillian or jillian yeah gill is it all is uh
the voice he's an earnest boy he has to wear a bowl over his head a water-filled bowl
oh so he'll breathe yeah so you can bring and uh laguna who actually is she's the although you'd
think laguna was the creature's daughter she's actually the sea surface she's australian and uh
oh is she hot well i haven't seen that one i hadn't been following it recently i didn't know
anything about her that australian accent is kind of kind of hot too
but there's there's a mexican girl who's a like day of the dead look okay she's a sort of a
skeleton the only doll that we bought was one they wouldn't say who she was the daughter of and i was
assuming it was cthulhu uh she's got tentacles for legs she's really weird looking now that's
undersea and most things like it turned out that the the the hidden gimmick was she's the daughter
of the crockett yeah okay okay so i'm just gonna let you know about that and we're gonna see you in
which is sort of
not as good as Cthulhu
no
Crackdown
they didn't
Cthulhu
there are no Lovecraft elements
in Monster High
that I saw
and Princess Wee and I
got to be
real experts on that
yeah
the webisodes
were little animated
drawn cartoons
about three minutes long each
and we called those
our crack
because we would
binge watch these little
three minute episodes
they had the same music
at the beginning and end
sort of like Clutch Cargo
a minute of title music
a minute of plot
a minute of end credit music
and then
but
twenty of those
in a half hour
oh
yeah
so
I will look into that
obsessive compulsive behavior
but girls
it's monsters
what's not to like
you had
you know hot rods in there
and it's everything
well it's not in the
when are they going to do a kids
show that's about hot rod monsters
why haven't they yet
or have they
because
today don't have those hot rods
anymore
no not really
you see
you'd have to have that
hot rod culture
that we don't have superheroes anymore
but look how popular those are
in the movies
so hot rod weirdos
yeah
which I'm not sure about
I'm all about those
just do a series where there are
hot rod weirdos
and then
how many
life would imitate art
and soon it would follow through
how many scripts do you think have been pitched
to Pixar
about hot rod
monsters
at least three
I would think so yeah
I would
the rat think movie
have you ever
seen the
the video game
Grim Fandango
yeah
if they could
be
you know
all the
games
every
they
have
does
ац
in
all right
you know
Jim
of Reverend Aaron.
First X Day for these two.
Happy X Day.
We know them from Starwood.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
If you want to know where the really cool hidden spots are around here, ask them.
They know.
Yeah.
His dad is Maruga Booker, the all-purpose musician, I guess you would say.
Uh-huh.
He's been in a lot of bands.
Many musical performers are going to appear there.
Oh, blessed, blessed silence, which I broke.
Somebody has to.
As you grope in the darkness.
That music isn't really appropriate.
I don't feel the suspense that that music is supposed to.
I had some suspense this morning for about ten minutes.
Yes.
And, uh...
Then it was the usual.
X Day, 24th X Day Drill.
I've been at every one except the last one.
What happened at 7 a.m.?
Who'd everybody stare at?
You and Philo?
Yeah.
It was just that way.
Oh, Philo.
Well, he, yeah, they should.
It's really his fault.
He got the potatoes thrown at him.
Yeah.
If it's anyone's fault besides Bob's, it's Philo's.
Yes.
That's...
Thanks, Philo.
He'll be all modest and try to claim that it's my fault.
Yeah, way to go, Philo.
Way to go.
Thank you.
Thanks a whole bunch, Philo.
Yeah, thank you so much.
Yeah, another wasted...
I'm glad I could help.
Yeah.
Well, uh, what was the...
Yeah, I got up at six in the morning because of you.
And what was the deal with the red and green?
Green tickets.
Oh, God.
Okay.
We had returned...
Some of you weren't here yesterday.
Returned trips.
Last night, Susie and I were going around handing out these green tickets.
Yes, I've got mine.
It turned out...
I'm not sure how this...
Why Susie was the one who ended up channeling this, but it was...
There were these green tickets that you couldn't...
It was the last minute thing.
They'd kind of replaced the membership.
They'd replaced the membership cards.
But we know who's a member.
But I...
Visually, now, there's only ten anyway.
So we handed out these green tickets.
And then this morning, I asked her, after the saucers didn't arrive,
I asked her why she had handed me this other bag of red tickets.
And she got a very sheepish look on her face and realized she'd gotten confused.
That red meant real.
And green didn't.
It did not mean go.
And that we were supposed to have the red tickets.
I see.
So next time, if it's pills next time, take both.
Just take both.
Take both tickets.
You cannot...
You know, we've got to look out for every option at this point.
Yes.
We're desperate.
I'll admit it.
My mind wasn't on it.
I should have.
I don't want to wait for the saucers 25 times.
But I will.
I will.
That's going to happen.
That shows your faith in Bob.
Yes.
That you will come out each time knowing that Bob will set it right.
I'll keep coming here, too.
Yes.
I don't live in Ohio anymore.
But you'll come all this way.
I don't live in Ohio at all.
Right.
Well, but I don't even live up north anymore.
I live a thousand miles away now.
Oh.
Deep, deep in a forest.
Deep in the heart of Texas.
Where no one bothers me and my two children.
The dogs.
Two bounding dogs.
Yeah, only now Princess Wee is going to go back with me.
And her mom.
So there will be human companionship, finally, for once.
Oh, my God.
The clowns are here.
Oh, shit.
Well, there it goes.
That's it.
Okay.
The whole tenor of the event has changed from slackful and calm.
To very uptight and scared.
A what?
Very uptight and scared.
Yeah, uptight and scared.
Because, yeah, now I'm uptight, Larry.
Don't give drugs to the clowns.
Hey, did they get their pills?
Maybe they don't need the pills.
It is possible.
We love clowns.
They taste funny.
Yeah, down there in the ring.
Down in the ring.
Not up in the stands with us.
Slobbering on us.
Spreading their baby wieners.
They're flaming baby wieners everywhere.
That's right.
I forgot about the baby wieners.
Yes.
I wish I could.
A flaming bicycle.
Yeah.
The clowns have done some real stunts out here.
Many people have been nearly injured or killed.
I mean, this is, you know, this.
Shut up.
Rivals, you know, Evel Knievel.
Yeah.
You know.
If Evel Knievel was.
Rode a bike over a flaming car.
Yeah.
First year.
Then it was flaming.
I don't even want to say what it was.
You guys need to.
I don't want to tell the audience again.
I don't want to think about it.
Over a flaming school bus.
Filled with baby wieners.
Wieners.
Yes.
Entries.
Favorite.
All for the editing process to resolve.
A flaming school bus.
There was some jamming last night.
I don't.
I barely remember.
Is that what you call that?
I was actually on stage shuffling around and staring at what was going on.
There were some.
All I really remember.
Good notes played on the stage.
Reverend X doing some kind of.
It sounded beef hearty.
That jam last night.
On the.
The.
Him.
Through the.
Megaphone.
Or him playing.
We didn't have any.
We didn't have a single mic on stage.
No, I know that.
I was up there.
But they did have a megaphone.
He was playing guitar.
Oh, during that part.
Right.
Yeah.
Okay.
You were playing some bass, I think.
I was playing bass and drums at the same time.
During that time.
It was a heroic effort.
It seemed like it was a broken.
Stumbling rhythm.
With jerky spastic.
I thought it was great.
Yeah.
Spastic.
I remember that.
It was not the same old thing.
It's doctor music.
And actually, Princess, we was playing killer flute.
Oh, I know.
But you could only hear it if you stood right next to her.
That's is a.
Sex.
Guy.
It's.
Yeah.
There.
Crap.
Good.
Yeah.
It's.
Ha ha ha!
You got the tickets to go!
Go baby, go!
It's like a machine.
A ticket dispensing machine.
Woo!
Get your tickets right here boys.
Step right up.
Get your tickets.
Get your tickets boys.
Right up!
Ha ha ha ha!
I didn't have to play TV!
But yeah, there's no microphones up there, so yeah.
No flute amplifications.
We're missing some parts this X-Day.
Not just flute related.
The excess tight bits and pieces of us and the campground.
Just as the Native Americans always said.
Yeah, we never know what it's going to be from year to year.
Boy, my immune thing.
I hope they're having fun with my immune system.
I hope they're really having a ball with it on their damn Exos spaceships.
And my memory.
And my morals.
And my hair.
There must have been a real bald Exos stuff.
I wanted the whole top half of my head.
For his wig.
Those are trophies.
In their way of thinking.
They count coup on the humans.
They have the wall that has the predator trophy head.
The alien trophy head.
The human trophy head.
Right.
One of the ancient bobs trophy head.
And the bleeding head.
And all of the presidents.
Of the United States.
The hall of the presidential heads.
Yeah.
Didn't you say that you had the baby that Legume had?
Yeah, that's kind of a mystery.
I was trying to remember if I had.
I thought it was going in the subgenius museum.
I think maybe that's where it is.
That I left it in Texas because it was too dangerous to bring here again.
Well, yeah.
Because if it actually did reanimate, we'd all be in trouble.
Right.
It can be seen by appointment only.
You know, I had my second heart attack right here at this stage two years ago.
And it's been that whole muddled thing about May 7th.
Oh, yeah.
The May 7th movement.
Yeah.
It turned out the original date was a telephone number.
And the real thing was not 75 but 57.
Which would be better weather.
Depending on where you are.
Not always.
But then there was this hint that it was really supposed to be somewhere in the Antarctic.
So, on May 7th.
Which is much more temperate time in North America.
But down there it's...
The only creature that would show up there would be guar.
Yeah.
And you know it's a trick.
Oh, yeah. Of course.
On the ice shelf.
Boy, whatever happened to guar?
Old odorous got ruptured.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Now the fella that used to play bass.
Beefcake?
Yeah, but it's not Beefcake.
It's the manager of Beefcake.
I actually knew three different Beefcakes.
Well, one of those Beefcakes is now their vocalist.
Well, it's Sexy Kushner retired.
Oh, yeah.
He was the sub-genius.
Yeah.
Yeah, I remember when he...
I married him.
Yes.
At Ground Zero in New York City.
Married one of the guar people.
Yep.
Sexy Kushner.
I like telling people you used to open up for guar.
His sister was really cute.
Yeah?
She was married though.
Oh, well.
She was big.
Yeah.
I only heard about the fact that he was at X Day and somebody popped an earth...
Legume had made a globe filled with...
With fake blood.
Right.
And of all the people to get splattered with fake blood on his vacation...
Was one of the members of Guar.
He'd come here to get away from that and not wear the foam rubber suit and not get splattered
with blood.
Who gets splattered?
Him.
Yep.
By the same token, who got injured in the premature explosion and dynamiting of the
bleeding head of Arnold Palmer?
The one doctor at the camp.
Dr. Tillis.
Oh, geez.
Yes.
He took head shrapnel in his chest.
Oh, my God.
Shrapnel from the head in his chest.
Well, it was rubber.
It was foam rubber.
This wasn't a true bleeding head, obviously.
It wasn't actually really Arnold Palmer's head.
No, we wouldn't have been able to dynamite it.
It was the best replica we've ever had.
Right.
And it really was dynamited accidentally too soon.
And it went off too near him.
It was all...
Everything was thrown out of whack.
I think it was a lot of work because my wife of that time, Reverend, someone else
insisted on doing a belly dance right then.
Oh.
And it was starting to rain and Leguim was going, we've got to shut off the head.
I was going, there's nothing I can do about this.
And I just had to watch it all on TV.
Right, right.
In real time.
Yeah.
Yes.
Speaking of Guards, Sleazy P. Martini has got his own show on...
Oh, yeah.
Sleazy and Philo share airwaves on the book.
Yep.
And now my show is on ISO.
I didn't know that.
OSI 74.
Yes.
Oh.
Yeah.
Now, are you going to the Horror Host Convention?
Which one?
Well, I've heard...
I've been reading in Scary Monsters magazine...
It's not Monster Bash, is it?
Well, there's Monster Bash, but...
Is that a different one?
No, there is a Horror Host.
Yeah, there's a Horror Host Convention and there's some Sir Graveson.
Yeah, well, that's me.
That's what I thought.
Yeah, that's me.
But it...
I mean, that's not me.
That's somebody else.
Yeah.
Well, okay, but...
Someone with a slight Hungarian accent, sort of.
Could there be another Horror Host with...
There was Sir Graves Gasly.
Yes, that's what I was thinking.
No, there was Sir Graves Gasly, which was the Detroit horror movie host.
And I grew up watching him.
And then when...
Maybe that's the name that I saw on the list.
Well, because he's long dead.
Right.
But this was a Hall of Fame thing.
Oh, then that would be Sir Graves Gasly.
Horror Host Hall of Fame.
Right.
And so there was always the other...
There was like the Son of Ghoul and the Son of Ghoulardy, blah, blah, blah, and all that.
There was always the Son ofs.
And I didn't want to be the son of Sir Graves Gasly.
It just didn't sound right.
So that's why I came up with Sir Graveson.
Yeah.
I know.
Ghoulardy people, they're ghouls.
Yeah.
Ghouls.
Real ghouls.
Yeah.
The Detroit ghoul just died.
So, yeah.
Which he was also the...
Yeah.
The Cleveland ghoul.
Too cool for a ghoul school.
Yeah.
Philo and I both shared the Fort Worth horror host, Gorgon.
Oh, right.
You knew him.
Gorgon from Nightmare on Saturday nights at 7.30 and lively 11.
What you looking at, Channel 11?
Good looking.
It was the station owner.
Yeah.
He was also the horror host and the kiddie show host.
Right.
How often does that happen?
That seemed to be the thing that they used to do back then.
Yes.
It'd be like the weatherman from Channel 4 or whatever would, you know, he would go
on and do...
Bill Camfield.
The great Bill Camfield.
He had a tragic personal life.
His wife had serious mental illness.
She was rich.
That's probably maybe how he ended up running that TV station.
Yeah.
She caused him great grief and terror in his real life.
And yet every day he put on that icky twerp fright wig and hat and entertained us kids
before the cartoons and Three Stooges.
What a thing.
Philo and I could easily perform the slam bang theater intro theme, but we will spare
you that for now.
Maybe later during the...
We should do that for Doctors for Wotan.
Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na.
How long was the show?
We could do that.
How long did they keep the show going?
What was the time of the show?
Long, long time.
How many cartoons did they show?
I never thought I'd see any of those clips, but they're on YouTube.
They're kinescopes.
There's quite a few of them.
He was kind of a...
Might have been Ernie Kovacs.
Ernie Kovacs inspired a bit, because he did some fourth wall breaking and weird, kooky,
trippy things, all with a thick Texas accent.
There was a lot of...
I told you to shut up!
Gorgon, on the other hand, was...
He had those apes, the apes that go in and out.
Yeah, his pet apes were the cameramen who would lock the camera off, throw these ruby
rubber masks on, and then prance around in front of the camera.
Ajax and Delphinium, yeah.
Yeah, these are very important.
These are...
Every subgenius has these iconic local figures in their lives.
Look to your memories, and you'll see that there are these weirdos that may have served
as role models.
I remember well.
Oh yeah, without knowing it, maybe that crazy guy that sold the used cars late at night
on TV, maybe he's really one of your Shorterpersavs without you knowing it.
In a sense, it's always possible.
Of course.
What?
What are you doing out there?
Philo's doing...
Philo is doing sign language to me.
Yeah, sign language for...
For the differently hearing-able...
Ba-ba-ba-ba-ba.
And now he's...
I love you?
Is that what you said?
I love you.
Huh?
He's a palaver.
He's palaver.
More laughter?
Palaver.
Okay.
Dr. Drummond, why don't you get off your old tottering geyser butt and come up here?
Duff.
Good God.
What a slacker.
Oh, this is great, folks.
Dr. Philo Drummond is coming up.
The pink definition of slacker.
Yes.
The blazey.
Oh, those are some really nice pink Crocs you're wearing.
Thank you.
They're not Crocs.
They're Nikes.
Oh, those are Nikes.
I'm sorry.
Those are endangered species, you know.
But they are pink.
Here comes the feedback again.
They may be pink, but their money is green.
Philo's aura is already making everything sound real.
So, yeah, I wanted to talk to you about Sir Graveson's show.
Oh, yeah.
If you're interested in doing your own punch-ins and stuff.
Yeah, you're going to tell everybody on how to do that on the air?
No.
Okay, good.
Well, no, you wouldn't.
Reverend Stank forced me to come up here.
You were out there doing the hand gestures like you were trying to land a plane.
Yeah.
I was saying...
Philo gestures hypnotically.
It's me and you who talk big business later.
I'll have my guys call your guys.
Okay, I got you.
And now we have a bit of a blabber going on about...
That's not my imagination.
...the distortion of certain elements.
Yeah, so it sounded really bad before I ever got here.
At an unacceptable level.
I could hear...
I was way down there at the other end of the...
Camp.
...at the very...
Almost imperceptible end of the camp where you can't even know it exists.
Yeah.
I was just looking from there and I was thinking, that sure sounds shitty and I'm not there to
be the cause of it.
That's what I thought when I was a long ways away.
Well, but it's your amp is what all of this is running through, Dr. Drummond.
So there's either that or nothing.
Your amp is the only conductor of this system.
I'm not even adjusting it.
I don't even know what's happened to it since I left.
But it did get worse as soon as you sat down.
It's gotta be...
My voice just brought the situation to the forefront.
Yeah.
It changes the bell curve.
It can't draft my mighty voice.
We do hear an unusual sequence of buzzes and hums.
That's why Abraham Lincoln couldn't do public addresses with a microphone.
Yeah, like the voice of steel.
Yeah, because his voice would blast out the microphone and completely overmodulate the
system.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Yes, the recording in old Honest Abe's day was not up to our standards of today.
They had like a one watt system back then.
It ran through James Watt's one horsepower.
They stuck it in James Watt.
It was just...
Reverend Watt.
Half a watt goes in here.
Watt Default.
Yeah.
What was that you say?
It comes out here.
So, anyway, later on...
Yeah, we'll do that.
...we'll do that.
Because that's...
It's really...
It could be fun.
And if you want to do that...
It will be fun.
It'll be oodles of fun.
Subgenius TV on the Roku.
What I really want to do is...
Channel OSI 74.
If you have a Roku box, look it up.
You won't be sorry.
No, there's some terrible stuff on there.
CZP Martini's got a show on there.
And he will make you laugh.
You'll see what TV would be like if Subgeniuses took it over.
Everybody else's show.
Yeah, we got it made in the shade.
Someone replace me, please.
I'll go get my beers.
Rub, rub, rub, rub, rub.
Replace me.
Secret Stride number 274.
Uh-huh.
More louder.
This is how I get here.
You put the right channel on the right side and the left channel on the left side.
Great.
I got Stang's Ear Funk now.
This will be great.
Yes.
I'm going to put it on the left side.
You're not going to put your earphones on.
Yeah.
Your head phonics.
You'll get hooked on that.
Well, at least we got somebody intelligent on here, Dr. Hal's ears, for me to do something
with.
We're just going to get to the bottom of certain persistent X Day rumors that have been percolating
through the camp, bubbling up through the psychic substratum here at X Day 22.
Quick.
Get the text out.
I'm going to get the tarot cards.
I'm going to figure it out.
Do you have your cards read every now and then?
Do you have someone read your cards?
I did, but then they went blind.
Oh, well, you see.
It just did not work out well for them.
Which tarot was the one that was used?
It was Vinton and Old Relay and probably not the best idea.
You know, Cthulhu, Ketag and all that.
The Book of Thoth.
Oh.
All right.
As a preview of the Ask Dr. Hal show.
How's that?
Well, we're going to do that now.
Just a preview of the Ask Dr. Hal show, which I assume will be performed tomorrow, since
there seems to be little enthusiasm for enacting it today.
And right now, we have Reverend Joie de Vivre with her special question.
I'll do my best to answer it.
And that is, if you're interested, you can ask Dr. Hal.
I'll do my best to answer that.
But that's basically what the show is about, answering questions.
Of course in the show, classically, we have other people.
We have good people in the show.
So, here is, then, that question.
Thank you for your donation.
And the question appears to be, why are the Blue Ridge Mountains blue?
The Blue Ridge Mountains of Virginia, no doubt.
as noted in the famous song
heard in so many Laurel and Hardy movies and others.
So why do the mountains look blue?
Distant objects tend to because they are distant
and the shade of blue is dependent upon the distance involved.
The atmospheric haze confers blue on any distant object
as well as the sky itself.
So the Blue Ridge Mountains of Virginia
are most often observed from a distance
which renders this effect vigorous and live.
.
And thus they need not defend their name
from angry cartographers wishing to give them
the name of some trendy individual of the present time.
And here I thought it was just a bad case of blue balls.
The Blue Ridge Mountains of Virginia?
Yeah, think about it.
They've been standing up there that hard for that long.
The blues just kind of traveled up the shaft
and that's it.
At that point.
Yes, they were larger and are being ground down
into tiny rocks, each one in its own way, they say.
A fractal portion of the giant mountain
that can be seen behind it,
rendered down into these essential chunks or chunklets.
One small pebble could be the result of it.
The entire continental system of massive,
geological upheaval worn down by counter forces.
It could have a terrifying pedigree.
No one could possibly guess at or understand.
Just some little rock under your foot.
How in the hell are you sitting there wearing a six-piece suit?
That's not precisely correct, but you see...
I just realized,
I have pockets about me containing various objects.
I prefer to have...
Gloves.
I'm being asked now why I'm wearing pants.
You know, it's been said that in the new world,
we won't need pants.
And I understand the stubborn consistency
of this eternal principle.
You just gotta find a way to stop the chafing first.
Yes.
Well, remember, there are many things out here at X-Day,
and I'm specifically speaking of ticks,
which may be anxious to gain an intimate acquaintance with you,
and if the way for them is easy,
that acquaintance may come sooner than later.
All these crawling arachnids find a human heat signature
as the human passes beneath them,
and they'll be able to be seen in the tree
where the creature is waiting,
and then they drop down,
and being so small,
one usually doesn't even notice them,
until later one finds them partly buried in the skin
and partially engorged with the blood of you,
its human host.
Furthermore, these here ticks give you Lyme disease
and all sorts of other delicious flavors.
Yes.
And now all the listeners can hear you.
They can feel that itchy, crawling sensation on their scalp
as the ticks slowly set themselves in.
They are not insects, but small arachnids,
and looking at them closely reveals the standard arachnid anatomy.
But these are little blood-sucking spiders
that are after your vital juices,
and to contaminate them with disease,
and it could be their own fault,
as does the kissing bug,
the terror of the Southwest,
that bug that creeps on you at night
and scrapes off your skin
and laps some of your blood,
but also manages to get its feces into the wound,
which festers and becomes the breeding ground
for Chagas disease,
an endemic condition found in the American South,
Southwest, and Northern Mexico.
The Sonoran Desert bioregion
is home to these large insects,
which bestow their kiss at night
while one is asleep and helpless.
I also brought to X-Day a special scorpion light,
since I happen to have one.
When you shine it at the ground,
every scorpion that you hit with it
will fluoresce like a neon sign.
It's the most intriguing sight.
And who would guess that there were so many scorpions around?
The scorpion light makes this very plain.
It is an ultraviolet light,
which shouldn't be looked at directly.
I just brought a finger death light.
I put it on the end of my finger,
and it just blinds everybody I point at.
Temporarily?
No.
Permanently?
Yep.
Uh-huh.
Ooh, that spiked.
Yeah, I found out before,
I thought it would be a nice little E.T.
I thought it would be a nice little E.T. light there.
You know, like phoning home.
Yes.
And blinded the whole campground.
That's why we couldn't find the saucers.
We couldn't see them coming.
Again, something about the incompatibility of phones and phone systems.
I am very impatient when this is offered as the excuse for everything
that doesn't exist.
It happened, or could have happened, but it did not happen.
Are these phones of such central importance
that they can be charged and credited with the operation of our affairs?
Even our special festivals and meetings?
Nay, let it never be so said.
I know not what course others may take, but as for me, the KISSY app is the...
only indignity I have been forced to bow the knee to.
Oh, you're now on the dating apps there, Dr. Howell?
No, in order to do my podcast in San Francisco,
I have to get into the building of the Impact Arts Hub there,
which is so new, so modern,
that the only way you can get in is by taking out your phone
and downloading an app called the KISSY app.
And when it works, the door clicks and admits you
to the building.
But when it doesn't work, you're out there in the rain
with your bags of radio stuff, with homeless people screaming at you,
and for some reason, the KISSY app is just not working.
It's collecting information, or you touch it,
but it doesn't respond the way it should.
And so it is.
And just to get into that building, I had to purchase a cell phone.
Well, it made you buy it, too?
Well, how else can I...
Well, to do it, I have to have a special phone
that has the KISSY app installed, and so I do.
I just figured they'd give you the phone for free
to have you on the station again.
Oh, no, they don't give anything away.
In fact, we have to pay them station dues
in order to continue with that enterprise.
So, I can't remember, did you get up
and head out for the parade ground this morning?
Oh, yeah.
Of course.
You bought me like me.
I got up into the sky and waited for the descent of the saucer.
Of course, it could be that the saucers will burrow up through the ground,
but that would be something entirely unexpected.
Sting's just always hoping for that hollow earth kind of theory, I think.
He wants it to be in the ground.
He just wants to be in the ground early.
But even if they are underground,
they have to come out through some convenient hole or opening
that they control not to crash.
They have to crash through the soil in some unseemly fashion.
That would show that everything we were taught
was extremely skewed somewhere and distorted.
Yeah, that's about right.
And the protocols of Bob were many and varied.
And Sting brings beer to the people on stage.
Some were allowed to swim in the ocean,
and they grew strong.
Some were not sinuous like their brethren the fish.
Others tasted various artisanal beers
and drank sample after sample.
Their heads rang with the bubbles of good cheer.
The horizon sloped and dipped alarmingly,
and a staggeringly good time was held by all.
Meanwhile, Reverend Lord Angry Larry
brought in a tempting selection of beers.
And the
audience was amazed.
The audience was amazed.
I just came to check out this big dickhead.
Yes, it's still here.
And that's for the Bulldada auction.
This huge dickhead is one of the things that's going to be sold.
Oh, no, I've seen bigger.
So?
Well, it's certainly of an exceptional size.
And if it's going to be offered,
I'm sure there will be much interested competition for it.
Philo's already coughing on it.
It's not the cough that carries you off.
It's the coughing that carries you off.
And yack, yack, yack, yack, yack.
Well, let's see.
We've...
Also got action happening on the stage tonight.
The main stage, isn't that correct?
Because there's no rampaging thunderstorm
as predicted a few days ago by the weather pages.
Yeah.
We got theoretical stuff happening.
We'll see if actually it turns out.
We're supposed to have rants and jams all night tonight.
And some good guitar playing up there on the fiery stage.
Yes, good guitar playing.
Uh-huh.
Sadly, air quotes do not translate.
They can't transmit over sound very well.
No.
Well, it's a good thing.
Because that gives some backbone and culture to this event.
We're already cultured enough.
It's steamy and moist.
So we won't go too far.
Now to get to the bait.
Keep playing.
Thank you.
Alternative conditions of those beings.
marine mo Tabii ta bait
sci fe reproduce
man face
inspires runs man baby Penis muchoup a
until the twins come, but each is only half of the split god, the ex-god, which is Loki,
and Niji, which is the yoga of the gods, and the trickster. He is my true son and finger,
who I'll split into the same, so metal from the surface of my hands, as I irritate them
to suit me. I don't just need a hamburger, I need the hell out of it. She is a harlot
and a fornicator. My kingdom is on the earth, not that I want it. A good deal is in the
wallet of the beholder. Know ye this, knowledge of earth, pagan of the moon, is not a disarm.
Extremism is a defense against the great order of patriarchy. Through my discipline, nine
armies can triumph. The harlot will bribe thee with the rams of time, but the harnessing
of it is unclean and shall lead to perdition. The divine king will be killed in the plaza
by his own clowns. Darkness will fall. The Philistines will raid you.
If you act stupid, them three children will come indeed, with their pistols, and their
minds and their tools shall be all stirred up together. The image will be made flesh,
and thy dreams will be found over the head. The voice of the prophets shall be listened
from their bowels, and they may witness the sound of their eyes. You may not know what
you're really thinking, but that sign shall ye know them, and they shall command the source
of all knowledge, which is like unto a book of the score. Knowledge grows everywhere,
and they shall receive the sacrament from the angels, of light which preserves the
rights in heaven. The chariots of the earth shall reign and will rise well in the place,
while the number is still. I always lie, and I'm always right.
My name shall spread there on the earth, and my name shall be known. Everything comes
apart, and I'm not a man. I shall not be a man, but I shall be a woman.
They are strong, but they are not men.
I am a man, and I am a woman.