Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
Oh yeah
It's time for slack.
Or learning.
Sensitive artistic endeavors.
Artistic?
As is.
What sweet music!
You need replenishment, my son.
What sweet music we'll be playing tonight.
Oh, a Mendelssohn.
Hello, Stranza!
I love to sing, and I love to move, and I love to sing, and I love to sing.
I love to sing.
A blue RT-42.
A singer!
A crooner!
A rapper!
Stop!
Stop the rappers and crooners!
Taking over the music business!
Listen, mama.
If you must sing,
we will teach you to sing like we want him to.
This little bunny rabbit has no brain.
There's absolutely nothing inside this cranium.
It's empty.
It's as hollow as your heart.
And check here.
The special alimide bits that conduct messages from deep space.
What a face.
What a pair of blistering blue ears.
This is the child of the future.
And you're invited to spank freely.
Ow!
You're some genius!
Fully!
That's mine, Bob.
I'm so glad you're here.
A fat young man, perhaps too fat to carry out his dreams,
to plan, to propel, to include himself in his own okay wishes.
Is that like P-H-A-T or F-A-T?
Oh, yeah.
Is it?
Conspiracy is holding that that boy back. They're holding him back physically the pressure of the fear group
His own fear group is oh wait look he's come to the gong show
The little animated subgenius is about to wash it out of him. He's watching the pokes being gone
and
for each thing that is gone a
shave of the knees a haircut and more
Muscles from the neck and I'll proceed downward and disengage the heart bone
This is the part of the human anatomy, which is the most difficult to discern and figure out
Pagalach
I'm forever blowing for
American Idol, whose is nothing new
Chetro let me talk please I may not have much time
If he thinks that I
Well, I'm not but I won't and he'll wish he hadn't
I have something to tell you that boy sounds excited doesn't he well no wonder
He's just had his first taste of a safe sober uneventful suburban existence
Chetro let me talk please I may not have much time
Chetro let me talk
Okay, okay
Nor El Pref
Did that
Friends Nor El Pref Reverend Nor El Pref of heavy confetti dot com if you want to know more about that
If you want to know more about that
Welcome to hour of slack show
Number 939 it really is
That some old some young some live some dead lately. I've been calling in to dr. Sinister's show
Radio synesthesia on WCSB in Cleveland on Sunday nights because
He seems to be capable of having a conversation fancy that and friends the artists and collectors of
Alt dot binaries dot slack that great hangout on usenet
Provided a heaping bounty of bounties
And we must give special thanks and praise to those people like new Monet self Slayer
Mr. Fernand and Andy Lee Murr
As always
The letter K the saint Bucky
Saint mutant blackout and even
Ezekiel Tito Garacas
And puzzling evidence and ESO
But most of all friends
Lonesome cowboy Dave in his one brain cell
Speaking of which let's get back now to the gossip
About Mrs. Alzheimer
Mrs. Alzheimer gave
Freud spelled in Yakub the mad cow disease
And that's why
I have to find some kind of medicine
That'll defeat the P test
For Alzheimer's
The P test for Alzheimer's
Do you know if anything that I could take
It's not that I have Alzheimer's or anything
But I'm gonna take this test
You know it's a P test for this job
And they want to give me the Alzheimer's P test
And I was wondering if there was any
You know if they
I know for if you like pot heads can
If they eat enough Jimson weed
That'll negate the pot or something like that
If you eat Jimson weed bad things will happen
Yeah I know
I was just saying that just to influence young people
And to
Damaging their nervous system
Dr. Sinister advises you to go out
And eat poisonous plants
Yeah I know a guy who
These hick guys in Virginia
Didn't have anything better to do than
Try the Jimson weed
And the guy
Sort of came to
Taking a dump on his
Living room floor in front of his parents
He spent six
He spent the next three weeks
In a hospital bed
For the insane
Yeah the thing with the hallucinations caused by
The plants in that family is that
You can't really tell they're hallucinations
From what I understand like it's
It's not like a psychedelic thing
It's just
Your mind is going off
So where did you say you get some of this stuff
I think it grows in some people's yards
Yeah actually it does
It grows and it has
A lovely flower
Yeah in fact I've seen
Like in Tower City I
Think their decorations one year
Had some weird kite
It was built like a kite
But it was in the shape of one of those flowers
These people are wasting their money on crap
There's organic versions
In PCP, Angel Dust
And all that there's organic things
Certified USDA organic
Coca plants and
Deterra plants
Yeah Deterra that'll make you want to fight
They used to make this in head shops
Back in the day
Before you know
When we thought the ring was destroyed
There was this
Stuff in the head shops called
Bobbo's Better Blend
Which I later
Came to realize the ingredients included
Deterra
Which would just make you want to get in a fight
It didn't make you particularly high
It just made you want to pick fights with people
Sort of like some other
Herbal drugs I know of
Like alcohol
It just just oh god
And I almost did get in a fight
With a 7-11
Employee that I'd always disliked
I walked in and just
He didn't get the cartons of coke
Fast enough or something I
Just started screaming
At this guy
And then he just about kicked my ass
So the moral of the story
Is kids don't
Buy your legal highs at head shops
Unless you know what
Those ingredients are
That's right folks
There's a good chance that you could end up
Having to use those
Diapers a lot sooner than you thought you would
That is right
Always always know what you're taking
Especially when it's
Something like the Daytura
Right here's the rule to live by
Anything that makes it harder to pee
Is anti-slack
Oh oh oh yeah that's a real shame
Because one of my favorite
Or anything that makes you pee uncontrollably
One of my favorite things
Has caused some difficulty urinating
And like I can't take it
What guys?
Something they just recently pulled from the market
Oh a veteran?
Oh god that stuff's deadly
That's in most cold medicine
Not anymore
Now it's pseudoephedrine
Yeah
Which is not really as speedy
But you can still use it to make crystal meth
Which is why the government gets curious
If you buy a lot of pseudofed
That's horrible
Conspiracy street drugs man
Whatever happened to
The old fashioned ways of getting high
Like cramming a bucket of nails up your exit wound
You know the manly ways
Getting them endorphins going
Chewing on some old
Razor blades
That was the way that we'd get high
In the Dobstown brigade
When we were in training
Play mumbly peg
Yeah with the bones of your enemies
Yeah
Them was the days
Back then
When
Bob used to whip us into shape
Everything's all gone to hell now
Since Commandant Dobst
Left the camp
Don't know
What he's been out
Don't blame him for leaving
We're gonna take another call right now
That's Dave
You're on the air
Yeah that was me I'm sorry
Hello
Yeah you're still here
Oh I kept on
I kept on
I was just gonna ask a question about
Concerns about
Down humans
Downer humans?
Downer humans which may also have downy fresh syndromes
They may be harboring
Creutzfeldt-Jakob disease
And not even know it
Well yeah each and every one of us is probably carrying this virus
Around either in their wallet
Or probably in small parts of their pockets
It's half a virus and we're gonna take another call here
Oh they hung up
Before I could get to them oh well
Have you ever noticed how the logo for the
Special Olympics looks an awful lot like
The people who participate they're flapping
Like crazy oh I've got a terrible terrible
Joke that's probably gonna get me in some trouble for saying this
It's actually a Burger King ad they're gonna use those people
As meat I'm sorry
You know what's even better than winning a gold medal in the
Special Olympics
What? Not being retarded
I don't get it of course
That is a no no no no
We're not trying to make fun of those
People I'm just trying to point out
That I would rather
Not be eligible to participate
Than be a winner well you know though
There's another way of looking at that
A lot of those people are really happy
Yes they are
They have that I don't know
Something you do know look
They do know it too and what about bowling for dollars
What's better than
Not winning bowling for dollars
Bowling for dollars
Not having a huge
Macrocephalic head that gets mistaken for the bowling ball
Oh wow
Cause that happens to a lot of these kids
The world is
It's a hard place
It's a hard round place
With three holes in it
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
That's right
Attention car buyers
Now let me ask you a question
Do you have liquid respiratory medications
Like albuterol
They make things easy
That's right
For more information call 1-V-F-I-T-A-D-D-S-9-6-1
Man by day
Beast and devourer of the unwary by night
Who is this creature
Whose origins lie in medieval Europe
As a potent symbol of fear
And the violence that lurks at the center
Under the veneer of civilization
The slavering
Quavering
Gelatinous werewolf
The one who
Has its huge corpulent bulk
Slid across the plain
Leaving its slimy trail behind it
The werewolf
Or the werewolf worm
As it were
Slithering and glithering
Like some
Ancient
Hideous beast
Too symbolic to even mention
And the emphasis is on mention
I might add
The strange things that ever met your eyes
While the tradition that we seek
In uniting the water with the air
Yes
It represents the coming together of matter and spirit
Right now over me
This positive force that we know
We know we can perceive
With our obvious logic and reason
But of course
Ha ha ha ha
Those fools
They will never understand as we do
It's like an endless knot
One you can't untie for
Well you could untie it if you just had a little bit of strength
You could just pick and work
Gonna tie one on eh
I'd like some coconut milk
But uh
I'm gonna tie one on
Right over here
You tie one on over there
And I'll just tie one on over here
And tie one on over here
It's on
I'm aware of that now
Please
You know plants may be calculating creatures
To most people
The word computer
Conjures up an image of a PC
Squatted on the desktop
According to a new study however
Complex computations
May also be underway
In another bit of office equipment
The potted plant
Right over there
That's right the potted plant
That brightens up the window sill
Is calculating and considering
And performing vast and complex
Networks of computations
Unlike traditional computation
In which a central computer
Or central processing unit
Or CPU
Carries out programs
Distributed emergent computation
Lacks a central controller
Instead large numbers of simple units
Get that CPU out of my nose
Interact with each other to achieve complex
Large scale computations
Now these plants don't add
Subtract, multiply or divide
But they do seem somehow to compute
Solutions to problems
Of how to coordinate the actions
Of their cells most effectively
Many biological systems
Appear to carry out this type of
Distributed computation
For instance
Ant colonies
They are one example
Of nervous systems and immune systems
One favorite example among biologists
Is slime molds
Which exist for most of their lives
As single celled
Rubbery gelatinous blob like
Amoeba type creatures
When their food supply runs dry
They somehow figure out
Through local signals between cells
How to swarm together into
A pulsating slug like
Multi-cellular organism
That produces the spores
That give rise
To the next generation
Ah, rising the generations
Raising and rising
And they're above the dairy lane
Those dying generations
That pass on
Fish, flesh or fowl
Every child seeks
From the time he first dies
This is no country for old men
The quest for more ice cream
The young in one another's arms
Oh,
Buzzing evidence
And K-Rob were mixing
While Dr. Howell and Dr.
Philodrummon spouted
In the trance
And you can tell, can't you?
And I guess sometimes they read from
Old subgenius
Sacred pamphlets
Depending. Anyway, that's all from
KPFA station in Berkeley
Every Friday morning they've done that
For 25 years
See subgenius.com
For information
Or links about that
If you're interested in
Downloading that show for free
There are some terrible
Terrible jokes coming up
And one great big but
But, but, but
That reminds me of this guy
I once knew, he was just a head
And this is kind of a parable I have to tell you here
He was born by some freak of nature
He was just a head
And he moved into this apartment one day
He was finally able to gather up his courage
And live on his own without assistance
And there was this really hot girl down the hall from him
And one day he finally got up the courage
To go down there and talk to her
And so he rolled on down the hall
And then rolled up against the door a couple times
Hoping she'd hear him knock there
And opens up the door and looks down
And sees him there
And says, oh, hello
And he says, yes, I'm uh
I'm gonna change his name
For the sake of protecting him
We're gonna say his name was
Jack
I'm Jack from down the hall
And um
I was just wondering if you'd like to go out sometime
And she said, oh well, um
Maybe, you seem like an interesting guy, but what would we do?
And he said, well, uh
We could go to a movie
And she says, oh well, how would you see over the front
The seats in front of you
And he said, oh well, um
We could go dancing
And she said, well, I don't know
How would you dance?
You don't have a body
And he said, well, how about we go bowling
And she said, uh, you know, I'm afraid you don't
You might get accidentally used as a ball
How would you bowl?
So he's very depressed by all this
And he rolls back down the hall
And he bounces back up into his bed
And he says his prayers before going to bed
He says, dear ancient elder gods of destruction
Please grant me
One favor
I have never been born as a head
Please make me something other than a head
Anything else, I cannot bear to be a head
Another day
So he, um, next morning he wakes up
And he's not a head anymore, he's a grape
So he
He gets up and looks in the mirror
With his, um, metaphysical eyes
Because physical grapes don't have them
And he sees himself there
And he says, wow, I'm a grape
And, uh, very very proud of his change
And very happy
And he rolls on down the hall and tries to get up to that girl again
And she's really big enough to knock on the door
So he just waits until she, uh, comes out
On her own business
And she opens the door and looks down and sees a little grape there
And, uh, picks him up and eats him
And the moral of the story
You've been reading way too much Kafka
The moral of the story is quit while you're ahead
Ugh
Boy
There are more convolutions in that
Than the top of that bird's head
That's what you call a shaggy yeti story
Yes
Yeah, it made me weep a little bit towards the end there
You started to, my legs were atrophying
I was crying for the, uh, 300 megabytes that went down
And he metastatically saw himself in the mirror
He didn't see himself as a grape
He saw himself as grape
You know what I'm saying, Jellybane?
He was a truly grape man
Uh, well we've, you know, we've had a lot of, uh, uh
Experience with oracular disembodied or, uh
Discarnate heads, heads without bodies
Heads high
Huge eyes following you around
Heads of celebrity figures launched
As this kind of a ritual sporting
Slash religious event
Errant feet walking next to you and stuff
With no people connected
But, uh
It gets harder every day to, to identify
These body parts and their meaning
Within the context of, you know, like
If you're taking this on a subconscious level
You wanna make things work for yourself, you know what I'm saying?
And then, you know, it means
Maybe you're not going anywhere or you're invisible or something
I don't know
But, but the quandary of being just a head
You know
In a way you're ahead of your time
I don't mean that as a joke
Because in the future people will basically be
Just
A, a head floating in the air
Well it's better than being just an ass, isn't it?
Oh yes
If Bob wins then the human race will evolve into heads floating in the air
But they'll have big genitals hanging down
Just like Bob
Well an ass is functional though
You could go, you could go on speaking tours
You could probably, uh, have a
Have a lot of friends that maybe irritate you a little bit
And stuff
You could be a politician, most of them talk under their asses
A politician? Most of them are asses
A televangelist
Oh, that would probably be your combined activities
You'd be speaking politically about the Lord
And, um, you could live well
That's right
You know, I think we're all evidence that
The decay of society is being brought about
Partly by poor management of water treatment plants
Because a lot of heavy metals are getting into the tap water
Yeah
And it's leading to an increase in the... Rock on, Jim!
...to believe in fairies and auras
And are still allowed to drive cars and leave the house
Without being accompanied by an adult with a stun gun, for instance
Well it makes your spine heavy
It's one of the major problems with driving
It makes you... All the heavy metals make your
...heavy. Your spinal fluids literally
Become like liquid metal
Color number four, you're on the air
...in your car seat, you know, that
And it makes it harder to sell
Not to mention the brain damage
No wonder my pants don't fit the way they used to
Damn
Right, yes, the aluminum in the water... Your organs aren't even the same
It's not the problem with your pants
It's that now you have perhaps an errant leg
Like the errant feet that follow you around without bodies
Perhaps your members become engorged in some way
You looked at something you shouldn't have seen
You know
We've got stuff in our drinking water
That didn't even exist
Oh yeah
...elements 20, 30 years ago
They were brought here long ago
Very, very long ago
And left for you and me
They don't like us
Yeah
They throw a small dog at a foreigner
Which you always wanted to try
Yeah, you might do that now
You are now permitted everything
Unfortunately, everything is permitted
It will be de rigueur
Do what thou wilt shall be the whole of the law
Everything is permitted
Halim al-Dab
Halim al-Dab?
It's permitted but you still have to pay for it
I should play some of his stuff after
And then it becomes de rigueur
It's forced behavior and you have to keep repeating it
Like that same dried monkey in the movie
That you keep seeing when you sleep
Come speak to yourself
Dave, again
Not everybody sees the dried monkey in their sleep
Yeah, I remember
We were talking to the giant snowflakes
That run it everywhere
You guys gotta slow down a little bit
You guys go like way too quick
Maybe you're just too slow
No, I'm not slow
I hear everything you say
And the other guys say
And I hear it again in the radio
And now
From Reverend Ezekiel Tito Garacas
Whoever he is
What promises to be the next big hit song
Or really rather the new technique
That will supplant hip hop and rap
Okay
Here's the situation
My parents went away on a week's vacation
And they left the keys to the brand new Porsche
But they mined
Well of course not
I'll just take it for a little spin
And maybe show it off to a couple of friends
I'll just cruise it around the neighborhood
Well, maybe I'll just take it for a little spin
Maybe
The final
The
Thanks to some caring and determined individuals
These dolphins are considered nuisance animals
Today these creatures are dodging cars in the bathroom
There is plenty here to eat and to drink
And a lot of open garbage cans
Are unloaded and opened
The animals race out
Happy to be in the bathroom
It's a makeshift home for two happy nuisance animals
Happy nuisance animals
But
It's
Such
Such a
acid I've ever seen anybody eat in my life.
Pills, pills, pills, Bob.
I can't begin to understand.
We are trying to transmit it to my head.
Listen, it is not my fault.
The thoughts are not my thoughts.
I'm sure now.
That's what I thought they were laughing at.
You're the king of my head.
Your head.
Hey, are you smoking?
No, but the pipe is.
It will help you.
It's going to help everybody.
This is disgusting.
Stand up, baby.
You know, I tried curing part of my trouble recently
by licking the cover of the Book of the Subgenius,
but it didn't really seem to help.
I'm kind of hurt.
Did it lose its charge over time on the bookshelf?
Help, O'Keefe.
It's the little spot inside.
In Chapter 19, there's a spot that says,
lick this spot.
Oh.
Duh.
Well, the cover used to help me.
Maybe it was all in my head,
like all too many things are.
Well, actually, help, O'Keefe,
you've been a subgenius for a long time,
and I bet you have a real old copy, right?
Fairly old, yeah.
Yeah, well, there were some accidents
when we had those copies around the house
when Civet, my daughter, was very young.
Right.
She would baptize the Books of the Subgenius.
And you're laughing,
but actually it's quite literally true.
I believe it.
And that might account for some,
if you felt like,
felt a psychedelic kick
from licking a cover of Books of the Subgenius,
that may be it,
because they don't all do that.
You have to buy 10 or 12 of them
before you'll find the one that makes you high
any time you lick it.
Well, now, I did have...
You know, if kids are going to go out
trying to get high,
really, you're going to have to plan to buy
about a dozen copies of Books of the Subgenius.
Well, now, my nice ex-wife
did let a Seventh-day Adventist
into the house a couple of years ago,
and there was a copy of
Revelation X on the coffee table,
and this woman picked it up,
and she dropped it real fast,
and her hair began to smoke,
and I knew that was still a viable copy,
and I'm glad she did,
because she could have spontaneously combusted it.
Well, I really liked that chair she was in.
I would have hated to have seen it go, you know.
Oh, that makes a wonderful event for the children.
So much better than when the police officer
shows up and scares them
to see a woman's hair smoking on its own,
perhaps reaching that...
Did anybody ever catch,
the conspiracy that was combusting people?
Was that ever explained?
I mean, was it like crop circles
are done by hippie artists?
Were spontaneous human combustion cases
just really weird Dada artist projects?
As a matter of fact, yes,
it can be traced all the way back
to the early 1920s, actually.
Oh, before that.
I'm sure there were cases before the 20s.
I mean, when you saw it,
it had become a massive artistic movement,
the human combustion.
The anti-futurists in the 20s.
In fact, the first ever talking sound motion picture
was a Dada film of spontaneous human combustion.
Yeah.
That's something they don't tell you
in the film history classes.
Yeah, it was called Andalusian Kabassi
or something, I think.
Or Andalusian Sausage.
Remember the part where they,
they actually slipped the little eye socket
into the leather belt
and then they let it fly out
and then everybody...
And Hanson's armpit hair crawled out of it
while the moon went crazy.
But that wasn't...
That was a cool movie.
But that was kind of an answer to the futurists,
you know, the few...
Wasn't that Ernst Buniel and Salvador Hitchcock?
I think it was...
That did that?
Curtis Mayfield?
No, it was the one,
it was the talking eyeball, I think,
was responsible for the whole project.
And that's why we were...
Remember the blue lines we had to take out of each page?
We had to, like, excise the whole tract
because of the crap we had to go through.
Don't you guys...
Yeah, those old-timey surrealists
were ahead of everybody.
Oh, Edward versus the Baptist.
I remember that.
Right.
Hey, hey, um,
want to hear my Marcel Duchamp joke?
There's an old pensioner, see?
And he keeps going to his hotel
and he goes up to the concierge at the desk,
and he says,
well, when I give you my key
or I come for my key,
I will announce my name.
My name is Andr Martin,
and I will say my name
and I will say,
room 29,
you will give me my key.
So every day he does this
and the concierge says,
well, the old guy, you know,
he's getting short on his forehead
and he's giving me the keys
and he says his name
and stuff and he goes up.
So one time the guy comes in
and he says,
Andr Martin, room 29,
and the guy gives him his key.
And just a few short seconds later,
a man comes in,
he's all disheveled,
he's bleeding,
and it looks like somebody
hit him real hard on the head.
Part of his ear is ripped off
and his clothes are ripped
and he comes up and he goes,
Andr Martin, room 29.
And the guy goes,
hey, buddy, you can't fool me.
Andr Martin just came in
and got his key and goes,
I know I fell out of the window.
Huh.
Well, no, it wasn't a real joke.
It was just kind of a...
True story.
...attempted.
Wait, is...
No.
There goes another 300 megabytes.
That was...
It was a joke.
Damn.
Yeah.
Three-ring existentialism.
Get it while it's hot.
Get the rings while they're hot, man.
Never mind the existentialism.
You got to deal with that every day.
You know what I'm saying, jelly band?
The, the, the, the, the, the,
the final, the, the, the, the, the, the,
the, the, the, the, the, the,
the final, the, the, the, the, the, the...
Caller number four, welcome.
You're on the air.
What's it?
This is both of...
Mad cow, mad human.
I told you earlier...
Dad, is that you?
God?
He got out of the home again.
Inappropriate.
Oh, wow.
I feel certainly a lot happier...
That got bounced.
...now knowing I'm not that guy.
That got dropped.
What's wrong with this person?
I don't know, but he...
Well, I think I do know what's wrong with him.
Well, for one thing, he's obviously got a serious speech impediment,
and he should consider...
getting some speech therapy for that.
They do offer programs nowadays.
Yeah, but it sounded kind of good, though.
I mean...
Yeah, yeah.
Maybe we could...
I can't hear him at all from...
I'm on the furthest tin can down the line of strings,
and he's, you know, from him,
and so I couldn't hear...
I couldn't even hear...
He's not only...
Just a tin can, not even someone talking in one.
Right.
So...
Yeah, it was just a...
I could hear a tin can.
That was it.
Is he really institutionalized?
Is he...
Why do you get such weird questions?
I...
Can't say why.
Got me.
You got me.
Creepy, crawly, creepy callers.
Pychosephalic.
Huh?
Pychosephalic people.
Pycho?
Even smaller than microcephalic.
Oh.
Even worse.
You're going to start getting calls from youth for Christ people.
Well, as a...
As a...
Burr.
A head-sized, overly endowed person,
I personally find this talk about cranial capacities and head sizes somewhat offensive.
Why?
Well, you know, we...
Don't you believe in the natural order of size?
I'm a...
I got a big one.
I got a huge head.
I got a size 8 head.
Oh, whoa.
Whoa.
Size 8.
The head around which the sun revolves.
Feels a whole size 8.
Am I amazed?
I'm so impressed.
Woo.
Well, what if you had a size 3 hat?
Wouldn't...
Don't you think there would be a modicum of embarrassment accompanying your...
I would probably have a lot more slack if I had a size 3 hat size than I do with the
gigantic, Fellini-esque 8 12 that not only I, but my poor tiny...
Oh, listen to who's talking.
I knew Stang back when he was a fetus, but I shook the jar too hard, and look what happened to him.
Well, my head has been the same size since I was born.
That's the hellish aspect of it.
Actually, you're a fetus.
You talk and make jokes about people that are just a head, but that's what I looked like when I was born.
My dad almost had me killed, and I...
It turned out that I basically am a dwarf who has a...
Side condition of giantism.
Oh, gosh.
And so that may help explain the sort of al cap...
The nasal...
Sort of proportion of my own physical body, which I've noticed turns some types of girls on.
That's Drew's argument.
Call it number four.
They like that Tasmanian devil kind of physique.
The danger factor.
Yeah, well, it's the ape thing, you know, monkey card dance fetish, that fantasy thing.
I never feel as alive as when I'm right on the verge of maybe being ripped to shreds.
It's kind of a problem, but it's exciting, too, you know.
Well, that's the Yeti in you, Pope.
Hell, Pope Huey.
You know.
It's the Yeti inside, shrieking to get out.
If your head gets too small, it could conceivably condense, actually, to a point.
To an infinitely smaller point.
Well, then you have to get one of those little football helmets like they have at the department store.
I mean, the fast food chain when you go through and they give you...
I'm talking about your head becoming infinitely small.
Like, uh, shrunken down to a tiny single point.
Imagine your conscious head shrinking to a point infinitely.
Oh, tiny heads on radio synesthesia, friends.
We had a special guest call there from Hell, Pope Huey.
Uh, the collages are by Lemur and yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang, king of all butts.
Butt, butt, butt.
Hey, dig this.
Huh?
You said you like, uh, acid cases?
Yeah.
What?
Acid cases.
Yeah, cases of...
What about the, uh...
Yeah, cases of acid?
Sure.
...by Devo called Automodown.
Automodown.
By Devo?
Down in Youngstown, where the crazies live.
Acid head goon in the noonday sun.
Didn't mean...
Didn't mean to do it.
In the noonday sun.
He mowed them down with a 55 Dodge.
He didn't mean to do it.
Ride them.
Mow them.
Automodown.
Down in Youngstown.
Where the crazies live.
Automodown.
True story.
Down in Youngstown.
Where the crazies live.
Man, that's cool.
Acid head goon in the 55 Dodge.
Didn't mean to do it.
I know that song.
That's cool.
In fact, Occupant does a great cover of that song.
Shut the fuck up, man.
You sound like you got a speech impediment, man.
You just get your hair lit fixed.
What's going on?
He made fun of the way I talk.
Why did they make fun of us?
Why do they...
Uh...
...throw things at us?
Mr. Bus Driver, please open the door.
Oh, there's no more music playing.
How about everything's dead now?
Oh, no.
There was quiet for a minute.
We were real, real, real quiet.
Like, real, real, real, real quiet.
Ffff...
Oh, yeah.
When I lost the Raj least I'll give you one.
Oh, for fuck sake it's time to go off.
Oh, yeah.
Just trying to get free.
Them old fashioned punks.
The old Russian clown.
Bodies in the street
At the Moor Down
Noon in downtown
Bodies with no feet
At the Moor Down
Down in Youngstown
Bodies got the blues
At the Moor Down
Noon in downtown
Bodies with no shoes
Nothing had gone in a fifty-five dodge
Didn't mean to do it
But a sidewalk run in a loom day
Something the one he had to lose it
At the Moor Down
Down in Kentown
Got the Acubeat
At the Moor Down
Robotech sound
Got to move your feet
Hit the retro style
You can spare a beat
Turn around the way the Spartan boys used to do it
Now it's time to show that we're all evil
An occupant's here to prove it
At the Moor Down
Down in Youngstown
Bodies in the street
At the Moor Down
Noon in downtown
Bodies with no feet
At the Moor Down
Down in Youngstown
Bodies got the blues
At the Moor Down
Noon in downtown
Bodies with no shoes
Nothing had gone in a fifty-five dodge
Didn't mean to do it
But a sidewalk run in a loom day
Something the one he had to lose it
workloads listen to the song
Do you have a
Do you have
Occupants version of Auto-Mo-Down
There you have it.
Erect Iraq.
Whatever it was.
You know, alternative radio, one of the alternatives is like going, you know, stick some sharp object in your ear hole.
You don't have to listen.
That's right.
You can always...
You can still listen and not listen.
There's so many choices you can ignore.
You can always stick your head in a bucket of ice water and probably won't hear a thing we're saying.
Boy, would... I think I need something like that.
I think I need to immerse my whole spiritual being in a bucket of the most frozen water there is.
No, Dave. Desire is the problem.
Thinking that you need that is itself the problem.
Our desires must be extinguished.
You know what movie I just saw recently?
I just saw Altered States for the first time, speaking of submersion.
You ever seen that?
I'd never seen that before.
Oh, Altered States?
I was very pleased.
Well, you know, that's one of the great bad things.
Ken Russell did such a Ken Russell-y job on that film that the screenwriter, Patty Chayefsky, had his name taken off of it.
Patty Chayefsky, yeah.
Patty Chayefsky wrote Altered States, which is loosely based on John Lilly's experiments with ketamine.
Which is free-based on John Lilly's experiments.
And the movie, like all of Ken Russell's epics, is...
Sometimes inappropriately laughable and with an especially melodramatic and hilarious ending.
I know people who have taken DMT and gone into...
William Hurt banging himself repeatedly against the wall.
So that the power of the love will bring him back from his state of being at universal oneness with the...
With the Yeti.
What a premise, Jerry. You're sitting on a goldmine.
That flat-ass is as big as...
Come on over and have a drink with me.
Sit down. We'll sign the contracts tomorrow.
Look, there's a 50% deal on this one.
Sign here. And here. And here.
Anyway, it was cool where he took the drug and suddenly there was fireworks going off around him.
And the Indians were laughing at him.
He was stumbling around.
I have been there, dude.
I have been there.
Wait, what part of...
Is that new?
She turned into the lizard that was blowing away in the sand.
Did you actually go to that part of Mexico?
I know there ain't...
I know there ain't a listener out there who hadn't had that.
That beer.
Too many.
Now, Dave, what drug are you on?
I'm on the facial hemorrhagic.
You rub it into your skin. It's an antedendral.
It starts to break down the molecular surface.
And so you not only have to shave, you...
You lose a lot, so...
I'm also using one that reconnects the synapses in the back part of my brain by the M.O.
By the medullar oblongator.
And the government pays for the medication?
Well, they pay for the right.
They pay for any substantial growth in revenue.
Do you get a pinch of this, a dash of that?
Sometimes referred to in the trade as a sleeping beauty boilermaker.
Take no notice if he begins to levitate.
It's a common side effect.
The...
The final...
The users of drugs...
Drugs, dear friends, on the other hand, are placing themselves in grave danger.
They can never get as truly fried as they want to be.
They gotta take one on top of the other.
Sometimes they take so many that when they forget one or two,
they later get mad at themselves for it.
So to keep mentally levitating, they always need more.
Sooner or later, they burn out and become too slacked to react.
As they say, the brain tunnels through which they once excavated and blasted with such drunken zeal begin to cave in.
The abuser wakes up one day impaired.
His muscles feel ravaged.
His nerves nullified.
There's a hollowness inside, but a hot hollowness.
And discomfort mounts to panic as he realizes he's annihilated one brain cell too many.
His teeth grind.
His cells shrivel, yet seem to scream for more when there is none.
His skin exudes bitter greases from every pore, as if he were getting a long overdue oil change.
Everything's clammy and numb to the touch.
His eternal itch gasps and convulses with the amputation nausea.
The electric glue of his brain becomes tacky and stiffens.
The snot-like shock fluid in which the brain once cozily floated has drained away,
and the dried husk of grey matter slams against the rough cranial walls with every movement of the head.
The gyroscopes inside the ears' balance tubes wobble crazily, and the world is no end up.
The floor lurches and shifts its steepness and changes its slant right and left.
The bed is right under his feet.
If he lays down, he suffers the slow ovals, the bed seeming to spin very slowly end over end through space.
He goes to the bathroom to expel the bad water, but his urine smells burnt and leaks out in a weak radioactive dribble.
He looks in the mirror.
His skin is Krishna blue in pallor, and he worries that the quiet interior shattering noises he hears are the sounds of his blood crystallizing.
His heart beats.
His heart starts to dry hump the back of his throat in hysteria, for he knows that to die on drugs is to doom his soul to eternal earthbound wandering in a purgatory where the liquor stores are all closed.
If the nental eye is intoxicated, the very soul is intoxicated when the body dies, it doesn't know it's dead and so never heads for heaven.
Laying on the floor, glowing feebly in the dark,
the wretch moans out,
The drug is dead.
The drug users lament.
I can't decipher anything.
Put me where you want me.
Give me rubber blankets.
Eventually his cohorts show up and give him succor in the form of more, and the wheel starts rolling again.
The conspiracy encourages, blatantly,
a useless, empty pattern of suffering.
Disorganized Odd  integrations sleeping,
The anti-reality sleep drugs like alcohol and downers are legal pretty much,
while the wake-up drugs are only available.
You can tell which ones they'd rather you take.
Chico, California. We have time for two more calls.
Chico, you're first.
Yes, I am basically a loaded person.
Gosh, the more loaded, the more callers call in.
Thank you very much.
In fact, I mean, there's just so much that...
Okay, thank you, sir.
Hollywood, Florida. Go ahead, Hollywood.
Yes.
Roxbury, Massachusetts. Good morning. What's on your mind?
Hello?
Yes, sir.
I'm calling from Roxbury.
Roxbury?
I'm happy and I'm glad because I'm not me.
I sit here to die to death on the outside.
We were bad and...
Roxbury, thank you.
Next call is from Detroit.
Hello, yes. Thank you for taking my call.
Kill everything. Kill everything.
Kill, kill, kill.
Okay, thank you very much.
Kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill.
You made that point.
Thank you very much.
She died yesterday.
Next call is Overland Park, Kansas.
Good morning to you.
My...
Well, he died.
I think my husband was going to kill people when he was 20 years old.
I think the New World Order was exposed to asbestos in 1929.
It's atrocious. We should be ashamed of ourselves.
Thank you.
That's Overland Park, Kansas.
Next is Cliffside Park.
Cliffside Park, New Jersey.
Oh, hi. How you doing?
Good morning.
Yeah, I guess the...
I don't remember the...
Thank you.
Next, Fort Lauderdale.
Good morning.
Are you there, caller?
Yes.
I'm...
Hi.
And...
Uh...
SARS syndrome.
Infestation.
Uh...
SARS.
Um...
The...
The Sto-o-otic...
SARS infection.
Well, thanks, CDC,
for SARS.
SARS...
Uh...
And...
SARS...
Uh...
Um...
If you want to keep an eye on that...
Friends, does this show sometimes make you feel like you're on some kind of drugs?
Some kind of...
Does listening to this show make you wish you weren't, that you hadn't done the drugs?
Well, maybe that'd be a good idea.
Maybe next time you should leave the drugs alone and just come to Bob, friends.
You know, Jesus loves you.
And Bob, well, he doesn't actually even know who you are.
We're not going to try to kid you about that.
But whereas Jesus doesn't really care about your money, Bob does care about your money.
I mean, this is a prosperity ministry, friends.
We want to take your money away from you so you won't be enslaved by that handcuff of the conspiracy known as your paycheck, your ability to pay your bills.
We'll take all of that on our shoulders for you.
Are you going to end wage slavery?
Are you going to put an end to wage slavery?
I'd want a way to put an end to wage slavery.
It's put an end to your wages.
And just put you up straight up and sit beside a waiter.
A damn.
Slave the way you want to be.
Thank you very much.
A ludicrous idea.
But I don't.
I don't.
Do you?
I don't either.
No, I don't.
How long has it been?
Well.
Four, five, seven, any numbers you know?
Can you have numbers in your head now?
Oh, no.
I don't like to think about it.
I remember when I used to have a pile of them.
I block it out.
Sometimes I would block them out.
I used to put them like in little.
Piles.
I would have the sevens and the twos.
Oh, yeah.
And then I would put the fives and the fours.
Oh, that's a good way.
Yes.
And that way I was anti-localized.
And at the same time I was everywhere like.
These space-grown crystals are so pure that they're going to bring revolutionary advances
in electronics, which will benefit every one of us.
In fact, they're so.
Attention.
Clear all channels for possible emergency re-entry.
Oh, no.
Not again.
Stand by.
Video signal coming in.
On all channels.
Just as I thought.
Somehow, this silly bird trips the emergency system every time he comes in.
And I think he knows the last on us.
Not trying is caused by those things on your testicle, son.
But don't worry.
They will fly away like the Japanese wind.
You'll be set free in just a moment of pain.
It's a prophecy.
See, everything Dave says is prophecy.
It sounds like insanity, madness, man.
But it's prophecy.
It's a big man.
It's like a dreamer guy.
You know what I'm saying?
He's a dreamer.
You know, he sees things that don't exist and things that might exist.
He's a big man.
I'm a little man.
He's like Moses.
He's like Jesus.
He's like David Koresh.
I'm a pair of scuttling claws crawling across ocean floors.
Oh, you of so little faith.
You have passed asunder and yet have not spread your obeisance and your tiny little legs to
Zeus.
You shall be punished.
Wait.
Wotan.
I'll take that back.
By Wotan, you shall be punished.
Sounds like you're hurting that place.
No.
Wotan backwards is not-aw.
Not-aw.
Whoa.
Not at all.
It's like really cosmic in here.
Yes, of course it's cosmic.
Everything is threaded the same way.
The little mystery is hidden in each word.
Wotan spelled backwards.
Not-aw.
The-moied.
even play their music that has lyrics because it at least not on the broadcast shows but that you
can find out more about them at trashfish.com uh you can generally find out information about
subgenius events at subgenius.com i can mention that in cleveland there is a devival at on may
22nd at the beachland ballroom which will feature the band's man the amino acids and others and
preachers such as lonesome cowboy dave yours truly reverend ivan stank reverend nicky death chick
and reverend carter leblanc so you know it's not all just us old people and uh and in london
england on may 15th at the foundry they've been having a lot of devivals at this club in in
london
and you can learn more about that at may 15th event if you want to from this website www.lackofbob.com
and lack of bob is spelled l-a-k-o-f-b-o-b lack of bob with no c in it uh some puzzling
kpfa evidence in sue and uh or sue me and by the way the writing
address for subgenius if you don't have internet stuff is post office box 204 206 austin texas 787
20 you can email me stang at subgenius.com
i am not the fig plucker or the fig plucker's son but i'll pluck figs till the fig plucking is done
you guys don't waste no airtime no we don't
We squeeze every last drop out of it.
We suck the meat off the bones.
Do it, do it.
You see, these giant squid of the species Architeuthis doxia
are actually isostatic,
which means that their body in the water has no weight,
enabling them to hover.
Ah.
And their prey comes to them into the grass.
Okay, I'm writing that down.
Let's see.
Tentacles and their two long arms.
With the sucker-strewn pads at the end of each palpated appendage.
Wait a minute.
Okay.
Now, right here, you see, they hang upside down in the water.
What was that?
Isocentric?
What was it again?
The prey swims right into.
Iso what?
Iso-tired.
I can't do it no more.
Was it isometric?
Isometric.
Iso.
I.
So-tired.
S-O.
Iso.
M.
What so?
I don't know.
T.
I just, I just.
Isometric.
R.
Did I say isomorphic?
I said isostatic.
Isostatic.
Oh, darn.
All right.
Now.
Isostatic.
Where's the eraser?
I need an eraser.
I'm going to erase this.
Hey, no way.
You can't.
All right.
Now, I.
Now, I can't remember what I.
Oh.
You erased.
Now, I can't remember that.
T.
A.