If any wives are listening, will you please cover your ears tightly now so you can't hear me?
This is for husbands only.
Hey, let me drink, will you? I need a drink.
At the moment, his body needs its accustomed alcohol more than his bruises need medical treatment.
Yeah, yeah. Why?
Why?
Perhaps we'd have more m-
Shut up.
Not yet.
When?
I don't know.
Creep. You creep.
Well, that's all.
Yeah, I don't know.
We de-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-le-the start of our regularly scheduled program
In order to bring you a special report from...
Here is NBC News correspondent...
Good evening.
President Mishkin is about to address the nation.
His subject is mandate, and the White House has done nothing.
Mishkin is speaking from his house in...
He went there after flying from...
to welcome and decorate...
at the crisis aboard...
to postpone tonight's speech from last Thursday.
Now here is the president.
President Mishkin is speaking from his house in...
I'm ready now.
Everything's set?
Good.
Now, I'm going to inject 10 cc's of something else.
Here.
There.
Now cut away the dioramata.
Entirely?
Leave the brain exposed?
Yes, yes, I'll fix that.
That's an ugly name for what you're asking me to do.
I know.
But there's a better name for it, Ed.
The Self-Genius Power of...
You know what you're doing, don't you?
Yes, I do.
But you have a moral obligation to this sort of thing.
What?
What's that?
The monkey.
This is no monkey.
I've tried every way I can think of to get a human being to demonstrate on.
He's tried insane asylums, penitentiaries, everywhere.
No one will listen to me.
Well, in a way, you can't blame him.
Why?
Well, blessed with my so-called moral concept.
Perfect.
Let's begin.
On the second day, Bob appeared.
Yeah?
What about him?
His face was caked with the sweat and dust of travel.
Hi there.
Hmm?
Hmm.
I see.
Ah.
Here.
Is that so?
No.
Well?
Why did you tell me this story?
Because your name's not Bob.
Bob will come as sure as you're born.
Thanks to the launcher.
Launcher!
The story you have just heard...
is a copyrighted feature of the Lone Ranger Incorporated.
The Lone Ranger Incorporated.
Things bother me, and I vent. I write it down.
What's your latest obsession?
Just the fact that people seem to be getting dumber and dumber.
You know, I mean, we have all this amazing technology, and yet...
computers have turned into basically four-figure wank machines.
The Internet was supposed to set us free, democratize us, but...
but all it's really given us is Howard Dean's aborted candidacy and...
24-hour day access to kiddie porn.
You know, people...
they don't...
they don't write anymore.
They blog.
Instead of talking, they text.
No punctuation, no grammar.
LOL this and LMFAO that.
You know, it just seems to me that it's just a bunch of stupid people
pseudo-communicating with a bunch of other stupid people
in a proto-language that resembles more what cavemen used to speak
than the King's English.
Many of our beloved friends are what you call...
conspiracy theorists.
Or conspiracy nuts.
Or a bunch of fucking fruitcakes.
But...
uh...
and many of the conspiracies that they...
talk about are quite real.
And have affected our lives.
The J...
the assassination of John Kennedy.
The crashed UFOs.
Pathetic.
Those are the kind of aliens that crash their goddamn saucers.
That's not the ones we're talking about.
The George Bush conspiracy.
The fashion conspiracy.
That's actually one of the bigger ones.
It...
But nothing is as huge and monstrous as the conspiracy.
And the
The...
The mighty conspiracy ass.
And, uh...
You know, most of us do have to go back to work on Monday.
But the important...
The thing that you can learn from the word of Bob
is how to kiss ass without ever letting the lips actually touch that butt cheek
of...
of the man.
If you know what I mean.
So friends, uh...
So we're trying to re...
lead a return to decadence, sure.
But not trendiness.
It's all been done.
Friends, this is not a joke.
It is a religion.
It's a living, breathing, fucking, and farting religion for today.
Not for some 2,000 year old guy who hasn't answered his telephone messages in years.
Actually, that sort of almost describes me.
But, uh...
We...
We don't have anything against Jesus.
In fact, uh...
Jesus is just alright with me.
It's...
His fan club.
weaknesses raised by nameless people
only the
it's
neighbors
only the
theirs
Hurt you, hurt you, Hob.
I sure am.
You've got it.
You're the pole, then.
Yes, that big, huge...
How big are you?
There's over five million square miles of me.
That's bigger than...
You're right.
Thick in some places.
17,000 feet high.
Didn't know that.
That's right, pole.
Oh, my...
That's right, Bob.
Wonderful, Bob.
Right?
Yes, pole.
Never rises on you, right?
Correct.
It's dark.
Trip, trip, tilt it at 23 and a half degrees, pole.
Pole, right?
Bob, Bob, Bob.
Not fit for human life?
Yes, yes, Bob.
I see, I see, Bob.
I see.
Really?
My ice, ice, Bob, Bob.
Act, act, er, er, er, er.
Four inches, four inches.
Why so little, Bob?
And I'm Bob.
And I'm very dry.
Less than seven inches.
Thick, thick, thick, thick, thick.
Heavy, heavy, heavy.
Thick.
Huge, huge.
Nobody, but Bob, really knows for sure.
Pole.
Okay.
I-7-11 says so.
Whoosh.
Pole.
Oh, okay.
Tell the boys and girls.
Okay.
That's my Bob, Bob.
Nice talking with you today, Bob.
Nice talking with you today.
Okay.
Good job.
Listen, man.
I mean, why can't I be cool?
Bob's from Texas, but he's really not.
Pardon me?
Bob, no, Bob is not from Texas.
No, no, no, Bob, Bob is not really from anywhere.
No, Bob, Bob, uh, is, he's from...
Bob is everywhere.
Bob even kills his own show of need be.
Bob turns off the radio.
As you should have done by now, too.
I mean, what the hell are you up at this hour for?
What can you expect now?
What?
Oh, yeah.
They're trying to steal our show.
Yeah, they are.
Yeah.
You know, push a button, I'll do a thing, and then anything I want happens on the air.
Yeah, it's really a good, good way to do it.
And it's been that way for...
For, uh, a quarter century, and you were there at the beginning.
Yeah, you know, I think I was.
And my cat was there, too.
Yeah.
Back when I had a cat.
So, uh, what are we going to do tonight here?
We're going to celebrate the, uh, the 25th year of show, which happened on June, in June, I think on June 23rd or 5th.
Oh, man.
Well, can I press the cough button then?
Oh, no, no, no, man.
This is going to be a simple show.
This is a simple show, yeah.
He did it anyway and made him cough.
Oh, God.
But now we're at the new KPFA.
Oh, the Hunt.
It's much warmer than the other one.
We're at the other KPFA, at the old KPFA.
We're in just a little apartment with cold water and no shower.
And there was a shower there.
There should have been.
There should have been somebody's old, real bathroom in the middle of it.
That was a great...
I like that.
I think during emergencies, they'd go down and either use the shower and eat his ice cream
or go down to Mobius Rex's house and sit on his rotting Persian rug.
And wash themselves with a dirty towel.
Yo, Adrian.
Whoa.
So you remember how to do this?
Praise Bob.
Bob is fired.
Bob's fired.
He's been listening to us.
Bob does not have body light.
That's the good part.
The bad part is you now have his job.
It's the Church of Bob.
Bob's speaking to me.
Welcome to the Church of Doug.
Everyone's nice.
Bob showers everywhere.
Even subgeniuses have treated him with a smile.
Hey, Paul, that's the wrong name.
It's the Church of Doug now.
Yeah.
I get to do what I want.
It's on the Unmistakable Evidence Show.
The first thing I decree in my land is no Ivan Stang and no Philodromin ever again.
No Michael Pappi.
Ew.
Most of all.
His collar's just blathering on.
Oh, here's a relative newcomer to the show.
He's been on the show some of that 25 years.
Yeah.
Okay, we're tuning up for the show.
Okay, let's tune all the instruments.
Let's get ready for the real show to begin.
Every particle blasts.
Bob is fired.
Bob is fired?
Well, that's probably a good thing.
Bob is earth, wind, fire, and water.
I only have one light.
And miscellaneous organic compounds.
I'm gonna live as a Bob.
Bob cannot be delivered or eviscerated for your sins.
No, but he can have a bad ground to come a lot.
I'm kicking somebody's canteen.
I'll tell you what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna reach under my bed here.
And that's no weird metaphor.
There actually is a metaphor.
I'm gonna cross-vent to a brain out of Ivan's stained heart.
Hi, honey.
I'm a blow-up doll.
And I've got a phylogenetic blow-up doll.
Hey, it's Holmes.
Hi, honey.
I'm Holmes.
Yeah, but you suck at blow-up phylogenetic dolls.
Fantastic, Holmes.
How the deuce do you deuce such fantastic blow-up dolls?
How the deuce are you?
Well, I, uh...
It's filled with air.
It's not real.
Well, it's, uh, large.
I'm inflatable.
It's a balloon, but it will suffice.
You used to listen to talk.
Poor Bob has commanded me to speak through...
Oh, go ahead.
You're mistaken.
Commander Bob speaks only through me.
Bob speaks through me.
No, no.
Bob only speaks through...
No, me.
Speak through me.
Me.
All right.
We're not going to have a Bobfest at this early hour.
Bob has commanded me to...
Uh, well, well.
Pipe down, Bobbies.
No, no.
Bobbies are huge.
Look, Friday nights are 12 a.m.
And then also, uh...
My favorite time of day is always Friday nights at 12 a.m.
Like now.
Bob.
Oh, yeah.
It's so now.
It's happening.
It's so real.
It's cool.
Bob, Bob.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Ha ha ha.
Whoop!
Good guy.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
And, of course, we don't want to not mention the Mongoloid show Saturday night if you want
to see most of us here.
Some of you.
We'll be there.
Some of you will be there.
You'll see us live, live, live, live...
And we'll be wearing clothes.
...and wriggling on the wall...
Unlike tonight.
...unable to get away from the agony of your viewing of us.
We're doing the show totally naked.
That is what you'll see at the show.
It's...
Totally naked.
...in Call the Divider.
but it's actually a mongoloid concert.
So come and hear hours and hours
of rip-roaring mongoloid rock and roll
interspersed with feeble sallies
by feeble sally, myself,
and Reverend Dr. Ivan Stang
with various and sundry laundered guests
succeeding all expectations.
But not who.
But not you.
Not you, gee.
Gee.
Not ye.
You know, I'm really nervous
because I'm expecting all these special guests here
and I made all these pizzas.
Yeah, I know.
I don't understand.
This is a most stressful situation
because our special guests have not yet darkened our towels.
And we don't know what might have happened to them
en route to the event.
Anything.
Dark towels.
It might have been, you know.
Tonight's episode.
Like, uh...
Of dark towels.
That movie, The Mist, you know.
They might have been gobbled up by a 40-foot praying mantis.
You'd never know.
Oh, wow.
Or dark towels.
This is where the sex goddess is.
I don't remember that scene.
The first known picture of sex goddesses.
The sex goddesses.
Yeah, that's a great classic picture, all right,
from the motion picture,
The Five Thousand Fingers of Dr. T.
Yes, very much.
Friends,
the sex goddesses are already here.
Dark towel, a subsidiary of poo water towel.
The sex goddesses are here,
and they are we and I.
We.
We, I.
Why?
And what that was, was puzzling evidence.
That was not the real show, no.
That was, uh, the, uh...
replacement show waiting for this show.
The puzzling evidence show with
Duggling Wevidence, the host,
Dropped or How,
Bagary Gabrogfran,
Bishclops Joey,
and that, uh, Mongoloidapalooza show they were referring to
isn't going to happen because it already did.
And so did the Baltimore subgenius devival
and the Amsterdam dam,
and we even just got back from
Stang Ranch, Texas,
where we did nothing.
We had a happy new year.
And a merry, very merry excesslessness, must this.
And, uh, Dave, the lonesome cowboy,
should be calling in soon.
But in the meantime, Princess Wee and I
have a song to share with you.
It's,
one of her favorites, uh, one of her favorite bands.
Actually, before we get into that,
I should plug a video by the Amino Acids
that you can check out.
Yes, the Amino Acids actually been working on a,
a sort of a feature film,
but, uh, that band is going to release it
in a series of shorts.
And part one, short pant, is out.
It's called The Beginning of the End.
And if you're on the, uh, intrawebs,
you can see it at something called
FatalPictures.com,
as in femme fatale.
It's spelled F-A-T-A-L-E Pictures.com.
I'll give that address again.
Because it is a suitably infabulous beginning
to what shall surely be declared
the full metal opus of our generation,
nay, our very home planet, I tell you.
For which rod-wielding manjack among you
can deny that with this,
seemingly Earth-produced short video,
we see revealed, as if from beneath a bloody blanket,
the very few char of brain-butchered mere humanity?
Answer yes!
Shall they not indeed fall like pins?
Row upon row of them until, as Gort told in prophecy,
they all end up on their heads?
Which is it, my friend?
Which shall it be?
And what of the bozo contingent?
Shall our path lead to slackness,
decimation, or slack enhancement?
We must needs choose our futures carefully,
and let this motion picture be a lesson to you,
which you can see at fatalepictures.com.
That's www.fatalepictures.com.
As if it said fatali, pictures, dot com.
The amino acids first movie,
and it really is a wonderful thing.
Oh, those aminos.
And so let's go to this,
what is this band, the MPE band, dot com?
Well, MPE band stands for Maggie Pearson EJ,
and they originate from Philadelphia, Pennsylvania,
and this is an originally Lambert, Hendrix, and Ross song.
Well, let's just play it.
Bum, bum, bum, bum, bum.
Ba-dum, ba-bum, ba-bum, ba-bum, ba-dum.
Ba-bum, ba-bum, ba-bum, ba-bum, ba-dum.
Mindless told me
What?
That I was right out of my head,
the way he described it.
Huh?
He said I'd be better dead than live.
I didn't listen to his jive.
I knew all along
That he was all wrong.
And I knew that he thought
What?
I was crazy, but I'm not.
Oh no.
Mindless told me
What?
That I was right out of my head.
He said I need treatment.
Drugs?
But I'm not that easy.
Let he say.
I was a type that was most inclined.
Went out of his sight to be out of my mind.
And he thought I was nuts.
Makes no more ifs or ands or buts.
But she's really nuts, they say.
They say as a child I appeared a little bit wild
With all my crazy ideas.
But I knew what was happening.
I knew I was a genius.
What's so strange when you know that you're a wizard at three?
I knew that this was meant to be.
But I heard little children were supposedly dying.
That's what got into the vodka one night.
My parents got frantic, didn't know what to do.
But I saw some crazy scenes before I came to now.
Do you think I was crazy?
I may have been only three but I was swinging.
They all looked like angry young men.
They all looked like Anderson and Oswald Einstein.
So I should have a story if they just couldn't understand the idiomatic logic that went on
in my head.
I knew that I was crazy.
I had a brain that wasn't sane.
Oh, they used to laugh at me when I refused to ride in all the double-decker buses because
there was no driver on the top.
What?
No driver on the top?
This chick's twisted.
My analyst told me that I always threw it out of my head.
But I said to your doctor, I think that it's you instead because I got a thing that's unique
and new.
To prove it I'll have the last laugh on your cause instead of one head.
I've got two.
And you know two heads sound better than one.
Oh, I'm sorry.
And dear friends, that is our motto.
But at least for Princess We Are Doe and myself,
two heads are definitely better than one.
Because between the two of our heads, we've got maybe one brain cell.
She's got one half, and I have the matching half.
And it's fun that way, as long as we're together.
Apart, we're cripples, I guess.
All we can do is our jobs.
It's funny how we can do our jobs with only half a brain cell.
Most of the people around us only have half a brain.
But we stretch that half a brain cell as far as it'll go.
That's the way. That's the sub-demus way.
And we have some good news.
Despite this sort of dour music,
this is the soundtrack of Kenneth Anger's movie Lucifer Rising,
which I like to run in the background,
because it runs for 40 minutes straight without a break.
But Reverend Stang, I wasn't finished.
I had to tell everyone about the MPEband.com.
Oh, that's right.
And also that that's from their new live covers CD,
but they have many original CDs.
This is the first CD of theirs that's all covers.
That's Maggie Pierce and EJ is the name of the band.
They play out in Cleveland and hereabouts quite frequently.
They're one of those bands that's great,
has produced, self-produced a whole bunch of albums.
They play all the time and have a huge following,
but they don't have a record.
They never got in good with the conspiracy,
you might say.
Which may be good.
That may like with us,
that may mean that they'll have a productive multi-decade career.
And although,
you know,
sometimes I envy Britney Spears.
Why couldn't we have been thrust into stardom over this Bob thing?
So that by the time we were 26,
we could be burned out public meltdowns.
Uh, yes.
Probably because we couldn't keep a straight face.
Probably.
Um,
friends,
you can,
uh,
we have some good news about,
Reverend Magdalene's child custody case.
You may remember the bizarre situation in which a New York family court judge
took the child away from a family,
the Bevilacquas,
because they were subgeniuses.
That was the main reason.
Now,
of course,
that became laughable news on the internet.
And,
uh,
we're able to donate a little bit more to their,
case,
which recently turned out just fine because the dad who had the biological dad who had been given custody of this child because he was a Christian and not a subgenius.
Well,
that dad,
he kind of got busted driving the wrong way down a one way street,
drunk,
evading the cops,
hitting a wall and falling on the ground.
He was fleeing with a passenger on a school day.
Luckily,
the passenger was not the little boy whose custody is disputed.
Anyway,
the evil dad,
despite his religion is in jail for a year and Reverend Magdalene and,
uh,
her husband,
Jesus have the little boy combo back.
She also gave birth to a new little creature,
a little boy,
uh,
in December,
around the,
about the time that Jesus's son should be born,
who has been dubbed because,
well,
she broke her coccyx delivering this mighty child,
this mighty Uber squirt.
And thus the child is dubbed Reverend bone cracker.
And here we're here on hour of slack number 1133.
We welcome Reverend bone cracker into this world,
harsh though it may be.
Uh,
no doubt little Reverend bone cracker raised by subgeniuses will help make the world a brighter place for us by cracky.
Yeah.
And so,
well,
Dave still hasn't called up.
I'm not surprised.
He's,
he's a cowboy,
you know,
and luckily I've prepared some wonderful collages on the,
uh,
theme of the conspiracy.
Yes.
The conspiracy of the normal people,
uh,
which we will use into,
I'm going to let,
uh,
let some insanity build up.
The collages that follow are by Fernanda Nanda,
Lima,
and separately other ones by Reverend Norell Pref.
I think the first three are Lima.
And then after that,
it's some preffian and then,
and then some preaching.
From the Baltimore revival and Papa Joe Mama singing the sparse bangles banner.
And,
uh,
we'll be destroying intelligence right and left and Dr.
Howell preaching at the Atlanta,
uh,
the vival.
And so we proceed.
My bad part of me every night for such a long time.
My bad.
Be fine.
Be strong.
My back.
He's gonna save my drink.
Station.
Hey,
my bad.
You've been you got.
Suppose you were walking down the street one day,
gang,
and you heard this,
bet.
You've done to the guy who whistle and say,
I don't work.
You can have a chief.
Too bad.
For me.
And when strangers come around,
we think you're funny because these people think that the factory girl,
the more beautiful it is.
she is. That's right. Not only
pros, that different girls have
different ideas of what's best.
Hey!
Weed is not getting
work done. Weed is not getting
work done. Wasted, wasted.
Weed not been able. Wasted valuable
time. Weed wasted. Wasted
not been able. Weed wasted valuable
time. Endless time.
Time. On a constant stream.
Endless fail. Weed has failed.
Weed has failed. Failed to pull
our troops out of Iraq.
Done. Failed
the American people. Failed to pull
our troops out of Iraq. Cannot get that
job done. Weed failed to pull
job done. And that's the worst
record in 20 years.
My record. An endless
an endless pose.
Weed a chip, chip, chip, chip.
And we don't. Cannot get
that job done.
We'll go left to right just the way we've introduced people.
Senator Clinton, what is something you don't know the answer to?
Well, everything.
If you can name one specific thing, one specific thing.
That's Senator Mike Revell.
Senator Obama.
I think we're going to have to have a serious
conversation about.
But Senator Don.
Senator Biden.
Policy.
Senator Clinton, you said there were a host of things
that you don't know the answers to.
Well. Senator Edwards.
I think we have an enormous struggle.
To try to restore the power in the country and the democracy
back to the big corporate interests and take it away from the American people.
Congressman Kucinich.
I wrestle with the president and the vice president based on lies.
Serious wrestling.
Is that okay?
We're not left wingers, nor are we right wingers.
Now, we may vote left wing or right wing or whatever, something like that.
Actually, as they get more extreme, they kind of start to meet at the other end.
Oddly enough, we're sort of in between.
We pick in the pockets of both of them, like in that famous old thing.
The thing is, and we love money.
Money, man, money's right down.
It's right up there with froth and almost as good as slack.
You can get slack without money, but money really helps.
But Bob is no communist.
He's a salesman.
It's there.
We don't want everybody to be equally poor.
We want everybody to be equally.
Rich, but without working.
Or without working on that bullshit.
And so our political party is called patriotic, psychotic and narco materialism.
We're psychotically patriotic for anything.
You know, I'm up for any program, but we're anarchists and yet we're materialists.
People used to ask Nemslo, who the hell do you think you are?
And Nemslo said, I don't have to think.
I'm Nemslo, king of all anarchists.
That's a true subgenius talking, friends.
Oh, say can you see during X days long fight.
The face of the world.
The face of all dogs.
If you stare at the sunlight.
Bright eyes and broad grin.
Train mark pipe at his chin.
Give subgenie slack.
As we fight off the normals.
And the Reagan.
Scram.
Look there.
Melted skin, bone and hair.
When fired from high saucers floating in air.
Oh, say does dog's pipe blow from smoke this direction.
So that we live free as birds.
Not like pig.
Human.
Terrors.
Oh, yes.
Yes, Dave.
Yes, right in the pig urine pen.
Like he said, the very final stanza.
Have you been watching the primary directions?
No.
Why not?
Dang.
You're supposed to be a credible witness for the defensibles.
That stuff will rot your ass.
You're brain, man.
Oh, I know.
That's the good part of it.
And when it starts oozing out.
But sometimes it makes you smell pretty bad.
Man, how can you take that, Dave?
Well, I, the first thing I noticed was they get what's called flaky gravitas, which is
a PR endorsed form of elucidation where the brows are furrowed, you know, so like somebody
plowed in there and they can plant the seeds of doubt.
And then they got the, they got the big old scowl going and stuff.
But they're not going to get the big old scowl going and stuff.
There's a smile underneath, like for kissing babies and stuff like that.
So I, I, I sauntered down to local party headquarters and I told them they could, you
know, I knew where they could find a lot of babies they could kiss.
And the guy treated like a common person.
You know, I don't understand.
There's just not the outreach to the normal citizenry there used to be.
Yeah.
I wonder why they're doing that.
I don't know why anyone doesn't think that is.
I, I don't get that either.
Really.
I don't have to think.
I'm Nenslo.
That's beyond thought, isn't it?
Yeah.
But then would a Nenslo-ish type character vote for a Huckabee?
It was such a whimsical sounding name just because it would make his brain go.
I heart Huckabee.
Hucka, Hucka, Hucka.
That was a good movie.
It also sounds like in swear words in Dutch, maybe.
Well, now Charleston, who vacated the station and took the good music with him, was feeling
sad about our future world, where he figured our president would be either Giuliani or
Huckabee and that made him sad.
Well.
Because it looks like the demarcated craps are going to run one of two unelected, un-elected,
electables, which, you know, that may be part of the plan.
If only no one voted at all, then what would happen?
Well, maybe that might be a better solution to the, well, it's not like a Mycroft Holmes
adventure or something, you know, or solutions 90% or otherwise, but, you know, we could
just set everybody on fire with a flame charge, maybe.
Well, you know, Princess, we, and I, as we were driving up here.
We were slowing down for the hidden speed cameras that dot our path these days in modern
America.
Is that true in that part of town?
There are a lot of them now.
Well, we found that out suddenly every day.
She started getting letters saying, here's a picture of you speeding and you owe us $100
in East Cleveland.
She had been driving 35 miles an hour through what was sort of secretly a 25 mile an hour
zone.
That's a lot of money.
It's a little bit more than $100 in East Cleveland, but there were robots that snap your picture
when you do that.
And then they wait a month or two or three to send you the bill.
So that you don't know that you've been doing wrong until you get about 10 of the bills
stacked up.
That's the horrible scenario that everybody has been predicting and now they're
doing it to we or have done it to others.
They're doing not only to we, but to us.
Big Brother is watching Big Brother watch you.
Yes.
From a toilet urinal.
You can't see it.
Right, exactly. It's frightening.
Some cities are more wired than others.
Cleveland, they probably can't watch you the minute you leave your house,
but as soon as you get onto a major thoroughfare, they can see you all the time.
Now, with some equipment, they can see inside your house, but that's expensive.
Want to stay cost-effective at all times, at least while the project's ongoing.
Right. So, you know, rather than investigate people like us,
they're going to be looking for marijuana smokers, for instance.
Now, if I were doing this synoptic spy ops, I'd be looking for bare-naked ladies.
I don't care who's having a puff now and then. I'm glad they do.
Well, they do, and you can see the pictures somewhere on Wired.com.
I think they collected together all the naked pictures spotted on Google Earth by FBI and other agencies.
I thought they went after moonshiners and pornographers.
Oh, moonshiners and pornographers?
Yeah.
That's when they used to have the real old-fashioned remotes back in the 1920s.
Oh.
Now they go after errorists.
Yeah, people who confuse themselves with the air they're breathing.
Yeah.
They get lost in the sauce sometimes.
Mistakers.
Blow me down.
Not slackers, but...
Mistakers.
And not misgivers.
But if only they would take the misgivers, but only they give the mistakers.
100 years.
100 years in jail.
And sometimes it's misacronystically spelled M-I-S-S-E-D hyphen S-T-E-A-K-E-R.
It's like, you know, you missed out on the good stuff from being a mistaker.
I understand they have no misgivings about doing this either.
Now, we were speculating how a vandal or somebody not like us, but an antisocial person,
might want to vandalize those...
Robots that are everywhere.
One with large hair and big, beefy, man-like chests.
Well...
Go around and pound the machines, build them into the concrete.
Well, the prob is that every robot probably has another...
There's probably another camera watching that robot...
I know that.
...to see who comes up and vandalizes it, right?
Or the robot appears to only be looking at the traffic, you know, the speeders,
like Princess Wee going 26 in a 25.
But...
Uh...
But really, they may also have a wide-angle lens on the back of their heads,
so that when the criminal comes up to spray paint the front of it,
it films them from the front and the back.
Or a wide angle on the other three sides to cover the other 360 degrees,
so you're completely covered all the way around.
Right.
Because some of these lenses are over 180 degrees and will take up almost the entire concave space.
Indeed.
And you never know if the robot isn't just a silly-looking low-tech decoy,
where there's a real robot filming you and the law-breaking cars and the vandals
who are trying to stop the first decoy robot by spray painting black over the lens.
Not that anybody should do such a thing.
No, we wouldn't counsel it.
Because you would get caught unless you were to drive, like, scope it out first,
then park around the block.
Then put on the ski mask.
Then stroll up.
And you shouldn't vandalize with that spray paint can.
But you'd...
We've always said that.
Now the bozo...
You should never use...
You should never...
You should only vandalize your own property.
Right.
And there probably are some surveillance cameras on your own property,
so go on out there, kids, and put on the bozo mask and enlighten the universe,
but only do it within confines of your property taxes.
Because if not, somebody is watching.
And they're not even certain why they're watching you.
That's the problem, isn't it?
Key wrecked.
But now I have friends who get off on being watched.
They deliberately...
Not only do they have their TV on all the time
so that the man can watch while they're watching
and see what they're watching,
but also they turn on their webcam night and day
so that the whole world can tune in
because they want to be seen eating.
And reading.
And writing emails.
Running out of toilet paper at the wrong time.
And having sex.
Especially having sex in front of the webcam.
That is apparently the most fun for many young couples today.
And old couples.
What kind of perverse slant has it incised into our culture?
I mean, think of all the millions and millions of people
that are into elderly sex from a voyeuristic standpoint now.
They just want to see 90-year-olds banging away on each other and stuff,
making this...
That's hard to see.
Because it's weird, you know?
It's different than,
no, I've been watching 19, 24-year-olds going at it all day.
It's boring.
Two seniors, one cup is the latest internet fad video.
One cup.
Two seniors, one jug of Jenkum.
One set of teeth.
Or one set of uppers.
Yeah.
Well, I don't want to see what they're serving up.
I do.
Because I'm not...
I'm not far from 90 years old myself.
I mean, I'm only a little...
Well, I'm more than halfway there.
But you're also a cultural humpagrass.
Meaning you'd like to...
You know, if you heard people were diving out of windows in Spokane,
you'd want to be, you know...
Filming them.
Something like that, yeah.
Yeah, I'd want to film them.
And sell the footage to CNN.
Well, actually, first, as Puzzling Evidence put it,
first you make the art,
then you insure the art,
then you burn the art up,
then you collect the money on the art.
And that's how you get around the art business.
That is a brilliant...
And the art conspiracy,
which keeps good art in circus sideshows
and bad art in the museums with big price tag.
And also those big-gallon drums burning away.
Oh, and they also keep the good art on college radio stations.
Yeah, man.
This is so much different.
It's so different than all the Huckabee stations
that I've been bombasted to all week
trying to figure out who's going to be the next criminal.
Dave, that's where I think you're driving yourself nuts when you do that.
I think I know I'm driving myself nuts when I do that
because I begin arguing with appliances.
So you're driving yourselves nuts.
Right.
All of my schizophrenic selves,
all of my different multiphonic personalities
begin arguing with appliances.
But you still get the picture that it's not done.
In 2008, it's arguing with your appliances.
You can kick them, you can swear at them,
but these complex philosophical questions
just go right over their heads
or the cooling element, whichever.
Right.
And who's really the servant?
The appliance?
Or are you the servant to the appliance?
Well, we know that we, the consumer,
is the product, which is the...
Oh, never mind.
Well, when Bob sells you something,
it's not the product you're buying.
It's Bob.
It's Bob's sales job that you're buying.
It's Bob's, sure, let's call them lies,
that you're forking out that money for
because it makes you feel good.
It's not that owning the product is going to...
It's not that the product's going to do that much for you.
You probably won't even use it.
But it'll remind you of that time you bought it from Bob.
Don't you know?
Yeah.
That's what...
One of them big kudos at the ecclesiastical primates
was just letting people know that dishonesty was the truth.
And that, well, I'm sure...
And Bob is God.
Well, we've already done that there.
Bob is God and the politicians are all the devil.
Individual devils or demons?
All of them.
Oh, they're all one big...
Make a part of the devil.
Well, yeah.
Little devils that become one big devil
when they transform at the end of time.
In some...
Steven Spielberg movie.
You guys let me know when you're done talking about devils
because I don't believe in those, so I can't...
What about angels, Princess Wee?
I don't believe in them either.
But you are like an angel.
Well, that's so sweet that people say that.
You told me one time she was a devil in underpants
as you were running, fleeing from a hatchet.
That was a compliment.
Well, to most poor po-buckers who live in the woods,
when grandma's chasing you in underpants with a hatchet,
it is a compliment.
She's a devil in underpants!
She loves you enough to want to kill you.
You know, that kind of thing.
At least that's the way I remember it.
First slices I got.
I still got scars from it.
I don't think I'll ever grow out of it either.
Like how orcas say that I balance my halo well on my horns,
but I don't know what they're talking about.
That's just balloon art.
And she keeps her white feathery wings
wrapped up with her long pointed tail.
Well, that's the way it should be.
I mean, a synesthetic stick, yeah, religion,
or, um, not personages like the demi-urges.
Is that a devil in your left pocket?
Or are you just happy to see me?
Or is that an angel in your right pocket?
Or are you just a little flaccid this week?
No.
How come everybody assumes that the demonistic urge
has to do with your lower chakras there?
Well, I think the demonistic urge
has to do with your lower chakras there.
With your income.
Oh.
How much, you know, the more devil you got in you,
the more you can make.
The more angel you got in you,
the more somebody else is going to make off of you.
Well, that's a crappy way of...
Yeah, I know.
That's a stereotype way of viewing the world.
Actually, it's not just all angel and devil.
It's we're devil and we're angel
and all sorts of things in between.
Right.
And the thing about this was,
I was hoping for there were a bunch of things in between.
You know, they wouldn't even have to have horns
or wings or halos or anything like that.
They could have stun guns
and they could have like tiny bio...
Taisers.
Like they used to have in China and stuff,
you know, big headdresses or...
Nah, I don't know.
Oh, what about the jammy devils
that I was reading about today?
It's a confection that's made in Terry Pratchett books.
Jammy devils.
Mm-mm.
Well, if you have had any experience with children,
you know they're all far-extended
and require an awful lot of water.
And they're all splashing and stuff
and you don't want to get involved with that.
Well, every time somebody lets some...
or breaks wind,
a devil gets his horns.
A blessed day it is indeed today.
Yeah, and I think I smell a two-horner in this.
A two-match special is what...
That was the name of one of Brother Cleve's albums.
Well, isn't that what Richie Valens said?
At the Sodium Empire event last Global Tuesday,
I think it was,
when he was commenting about President Butch,
Bush, not Richie Valens.
What's his name from Venezuela?
Caesar.
The great Caesar was talking about the great Caesar
and made a, you know, a whiffy thing like,
ooh-ooh.
But everybody in the media of America said
he made a fart joke.
And everybody in the Soviet pluralistic baboon area
said, oh, well, I don't know.
They said that he was saying he was the devil
because he smelled like a fart.
Infernal.
Sulfuric.
Belching up from the very bowels of the earth.
The volcanic, the evil-smelling jenkum of Gaia.
Yes?
Well, every volcano that goes off,
that's Gaia presenting the innocence
with a big flow of jenkum.
It's her flow.
Her jenkum flow.
Yes.
When the lava comes belching and bubbling up out.
And the poisonous gas goes to the, you know,
runs downhill.
Why?
Because the prisons are kept,
the prisoners are kept in the basement
and it wants to kill them first.
Then it kills the janitors who live just above the basement.
Then it finally kills the big man on the top of the hill.
And they all end up on their heads,
every one of them.
Don't they?
Yes, they do.
In every game,
no matter who wins,
they all end up on their heads,
sooner or later.
Yep.
And the soles of their shoes are ignited
by the starry vistas we choose to neglect.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, and neglect is such a wonderful thing to a subgenius.
Why, it's the backbone of our slovenliness and uselessness.
It's more than benignness.
It's a form of creamy fulfillment.
Dave, and you know,
I'm proud of all the medals you've gotten for neglect
in the church over the years at the Bobby Awards.
I only got one.
Well, see, we...
We neglected to...
That's right.
We, with the accent on we...
Yes, we neglected to give you the rest
because we wanted the prize next year.
No, we was too bad and lazy to make the Bobby Award, you see.
It's true.
Well, we'll get around to those.
When we finally mail out the Bobby,
we'll get the Bobby Award.
When we get the Bobby Award to the winners,
they'll be getting three years' worth of them.
Maybe when Joseph, Daddy of Jesus,
makes his round two-its.
That was a real relief
because I thought you were going to say
three years in the joint.
Or, you know, that's three years with a joint or two.
That would make me seem like...
You know, ironically, I can't smoke those joints
because they make my joints hurt.
That sounds like a joke,
but now that I'm old,
I can't smoke those joints
because it affects my joints.
It affects my joints.
It's my arthritis, you know, rheumatism.
Don't you also have fits of cannibalism with that, too?
And you want to...
Well, no, that's the thing.
That's the sad thing.
Since I had to quit smoking joints,
there's nothing to cure my cannibalism anymore.
I had medical marijuana to cure cannibalism,
and they took it away from me.
Have you tried those...
They call them pup chews.
You get them out.
They're not Walmart.
Even Walmart pee tests you for cannibalism.
Yep.
It's a conspiracy.
You know, and we sound like...
When you say that word conspiracy,
then you sound like a conspiracy...
Coo!
A crackpot!
But how else are you going to find out what's in that pot
but by cracking it?
Really?
You know, the conspiracy...
Crack your knuckles if the pot makes your joints hurt.
Or just crack open that pot
and look at the secrets inside,
the secret wisdom of all ages,
which is that the mace...
...sonic, satanic, Jewish conspiracy
doesn't exist compared to the subgenius
sex goddess conspiracy,
which is so much bigger and more long-lasting.
Because where theirs lasts a thousand years,
ours will last a billion years, yes.
Our own conspiracy.
In the meantime, we have to live with them and it.
Actually, not for much longer.
Something's going to happen?
Soon?
Yes, the show's going to end in about seven minutes.
Oh, seven minutes?
Yes, and I'm going to start wrapping it up now
because I have powerful rants to play at the very end.
I thought you were going to start wrapping.
Well, we've been wrapping and I'm going to wrap up.
First, I should say that the Cleveland officers
are listening to Hour of Slut number 1133,
which is out of order, in a way,
with all the others that will follow
because...
The Clevelanders are lucky enough to be
in the confusing state of Ohio
where we do this show.
And for those who want information
on why we do this show,
it's the Church of the Subgenius.
And you can learn about that
and when the world ends
at subgenius.com.
Don't forget to give the address.
Don't forget to give the phone number.
You know, the prisoners out there
who can't get on the internet
do need the address.
So I'm going to give it.
And I'm going to give them time
to get their pins ready
to write this in blood.
Right, I thought you said
get their pants up.
But at least you didn't say that.
It's subgenius or Bob or Hour of Slut
or Reverend Stag or Princess We
or Relevant to Cabin Dave
at post office box...
Oh, counselor.
Counselor.
No, be quiet, Dave.
I'm giving you...
You're a lovely wife,
a question counselor.
No.
It's box 181417.
Cleveland Heights.
Not Cleveland Buffs.
Bluffs.
But Cleveland Heights
in the Buff.
Ohio.
44118.
Naked Cleveland Heights?
Cleveland what?
Cleveland Bluffs.
And now, Dave,
I want to thank you for calling in.
I would like to thank you
for allegedly writing down
the last few comments.
And now we're going to go back
into the mind of Norrell.
George Bush
and Dr. Howell
in Amsterdam.
And finally,
a little end of the lost horizon
and goodbye.
Long may it reign.
Broad for your life.
Central intelligence
had been destroyed.
Terrible blunder.
The CIA must be full
of those agents.
And I'm sort of reading backwards here.
What do you think?
It's also just plain stupid.
People want to see it.
People want to see it
and need to see it.
There's torture on those tapes.
Really bad.
They have choices.
I'm mystified.
Whatever.
Destroying intelligence.
You don't have money to fund the war.
But you're going to spend it.
You're going to grow up.
People grow up.
You can get enough kids
to grow old enough
to get enough kids
to get their heads blown off.
For the president's abuse of it.
That Bush just trusted.
In Iraq.
In the United States.
I am purged by God.
The white override is veto.
America's override is veto.
The president's desire to deny it to them.
Bush just iced more things up.
Slack is what the subgenius must have.
Slack is the soft voice.
Slack the luminous cloud.
We in ourselves rejoice.
And although you may laugh,
snicker and titter at subgeniuses
for thirsting after slack,
while a dying world collapses around them,
the subgeniuses may have the last snicker
because it will ultimately be found out
that you also need slack.
You were born with original slack.
But the conspiracy,
which is what wants you to work for a living,
wants to take away your original slack
and sell you in its place false slack
for which you must labor at meaningless toil
interspersed by grief.
And perhaps even enjoyable patches of meaningless leisure.
Yes, that's how it is.
Because the conspiracy Reverend Stang was talking about
is, as he pointed out,
not just the John F. Kennedy conspiracy,
the 9-11 conspiracy,
or even the Sofa Bed conspiracy,
if anyone can remember that.
That was an actual store during the 1970s in the US.
And one of the worst conspiracies too,
not that I have time to go into it.
None of these specifically, but all together,
for they all have a story.
All mix and meld into one overarching super-conspiracy.
The word conspiracy comes from the Latin com,
meaning with,
and spheros, to breathe,
as in inspiration one takes in a breath.
In a conspiracy, all breathe together.
They may not plot together,
but they breathe together,
because they think together alike
as one giant, crawling hive mind,
or to speak more narrowly, vacuity of mind.
An organism which operates autonomically,
and has automatic checks to cut down any stalks
that may have the temerity to grow taller
than any others of the field.
And so this conspiracy was detected by J.R. Bob Dobbs,
and it is we, the subgeniuses,
who eternally struggle to elude its blandishments,
and concentrate only on ours.
Now, I'll also say that many people
in the world,
insist that we tell them,
they insist that we reassure them,
that what we do is all a joke.
And we are happy to do so.
It is all a joke.
It is a form of satire.
But satire can only work
if it is about something.
It must be trenchant.
Because the form of something is humorous,
it doesn't mean that the substance
of what is introduced and discussed
is not to be considered,
is negligible, is inconsiderable.
Rather,
it is something which supports
the entire tottering structure of satire,
humor, and saleable items and commodities.
Therefore, there is something to it.
And that thing brought us,
me and my friends, them,
here tonight,
to participate in this
seventh annual Amsterdam Subgenius Frog Cup.
It came to me in a vision.
Long, long ago.
I saw all the nations strengthening,
not in wisdom,
but in the vulgar passions
and the will to destroy.
I saw the machine power multiplying
until a single weaponed man
might match a whole army.
I foresaw a time
when man, exulting with his might,
and the technique of murder
would rage so hotly over the world
that every book, every treasure,
would be doomed to destruction.
Look at the world today.
Is there anything more pitiful?
What madness there is.
What blindness.
What unintelligent leadership.
A scurrying mass of bewildered humanity,
crashing headlong against each other,
propelled by an orgy of greed and brutality.
The time must come, my friend,
when this orgy will spend itself.
When brutality and the lust for power
must perish by its own sword.
When the world is destroyed,
it will be destroyed.
And praise Bob.
Dear friends.
I could walk out as a bum
and drop my diving wheel.
This afternoon,
Wang Mei will be at the library
to borrow a few things.
That will be about 12.30?
Yeah.
10.30?
That's right.
Yes?
Yeah.
He said,
then call on the Mason-ass-face.
My image has just changed.
The man with the scab-like,
war-gold mind.
Why did you wait in boots
to order to get a clean clean?
Well,
we saw him at the red-eyed
in Sly the Lay with the triads
here with an ad-gib and a door.
How did you know it?
We saw Mr. Hentix
that was standing his down
slumped his chest.
Dart, dart.
Did he through the window?
No, through the window.
Touch anything?
No.
Dart.
Ah.
Go ahead.
Well, he went local.
Yes.
The range.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Through the window?
No.
Through the window.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
.