And, uh, oh, thank you much, George.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
George was actually the first radio hipster to interview any subgeniuses officially.
But, but.
But, and that's a big but.
Yeah, I know.
No ifs.
But, uh, see, before that, it was all right-wing people that interviewed us for some reason.
And they ate it up.
That audience loved it.
Now, I dare the audience of George to keep listening.
If, uh, you have never heard, uh, subgenius radio programming before, I don't know, you probably ought to switch over to a commercial station now.
Because what you're about to hear is, I don't know, it's probably too experimental for you.
Too intense.
You'll probably be offended by the political and moral messages which make the anarchists and the greens look like the moral majority.
Right.
But if you do listen, please try to listen in headphones.
And, uh, preferably tape it also.
Uh, otherwise you won't be able to believe later that you even heard it.
Dear friends, because the sounds of the church are such pretty sounds.
Ladies and gentlemen, please leave your sets adjusted.
We're having operating difficulties.
Oh, this is terrible.
Oh, uh.
What?
Ish!
It's not.
It's a...
BД über satu....
БД certainty einen...
БД banyak час I just hope you don't catch it in the video and expect my overpowering CabinЛад Lion ... and then let him leave.
This is a hopeless situation.
FM in Dallas, Texas.
And I feel good.
The subconscious will listen and absorb this message.
Exactly.
Hey, what's going on here?
The subgenius.
Hour of swag.
Welcome to the end times, boys and girls.
We're going to shock shock the house with your brain to whirl.
Bob is getting down with you here tonight.
Bob is getting down to help your plight.
Bob is coming here to ease your strife.
Karma suckers let Bob into your life.
Big Bad Bob.
P.O.
This is Walter Teasdale reminding you that it's often a photon that light releases,
but truth is, not everyone gets the picture.
Hoping your time is all time and all your unpermissible truths are happy truths.
Here is your host.
Who sits on the right hand side of Bob?
None other than...
The Reverend Ivan Stang.
The sexiest man on earth.
A young Adonis who's irresistible to women.
No, I can't wait a moment longer.
I've got to have sex with you.
You shall have sex.
You shall be rich.
Rich in limitless sexhood.
You've got me all worked up.
Stuff again out of bananas.
Psss.
Pss.
Ohh.
Bob is...
Sex.
Mobb.
Manhattanararakzal Advents 과 house
Mobb?
Mobb.
outdoor way
keluar
bar
Bob is sex.
That's your key phrase.
It will trigger the entire message without your being aware of it.
We are controlling transmission.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
Three, two, and one.
Now to continue with the tape recording.
Well, it once was a man.
The world's greatest salesman.
And he had devised a plan.
To get the shackles from my feet.
I am, oh now he's gone.
A martyr for the cause.
Bob is my own.
And he's coming again.
Who knew that the first shot.
Was gonna be the last shot.
But he's got a hard driving pipe.
The gas smoke all through the night.
And I don't hate to be hurt.
But you don't know.
He's gonna keep on squinting.
Bob is my own.
And he's coming again.
Oh, ho!
Oh, yes, yes, yes, dear friends.
This is our Slack number 79.
Believe it or not, first time in this time slot.
Nine o'clock Sunday nights.
And like I said, dear friends, you've got to listen to him.
And I'm gonna get to this thing in headphones.
I am dead flat serious.
You must do it.
This is Reverend Cleve Duncan, who's also keyboardist for the Del Fuego's.
And you can see him here two weeks from now.
He can save us from the many and bad.
With just a shot from his mighty sack.
If only he could make it back.
From the land of the dead.
Far until that happy day.
We can only drink and say Bob is my own.
And he's coming again.
I know he can make it.
Without him, we can't take it.
We'll lose the pieces of our minds to the big boys and the wimps.
Until the day that he comes back.
It will be a world.
We can't stop.
Bob is my own.
And he's coming again.
Dear friends, you can call 823-3-4.
And talk to the Will of Dogs about what's going on here.
Oh, a couple of the George audience have already called.
And so they wanted to hear some Devo.
You already have.
You've heard Devo in three different pieces already.
Believe it or not.
Just ones you didn't know about before.
Oh, yes.
Help me, somebody.
Thank you, Brother Cleave.
Our guests tonight, Hal Robbins, Paul Mavridis.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
Welcome once again to the horror and the love of the word.
Bob!
Look, I don't care what you reporters think.
I wasn't doing anything in the parked car with Reverend Anne, except discussing church.
Oh, do we need to do that again?
Okay.
But it would be wrong.
That's the Clapper Loader, the best boy in the Dolly Grip who'll just bear on strike.
I'm sorry to tell you that, Mr. Stang.
but they say that this production can't move on until their demands are satisfied.
Well, let's go on with the press conference.
We were just discussing church business.
What about monkey business, Mr. Stang?
What about that little blonde we know you've been squiring around?
Reverend Ann is a devoted student of Bob and Connie.
She's a Connie-ite.
Where was Connie while all this was going on?
Just because she's not part of the Orthodox Stangian People's Covenant denomination of Dobbs Yeti resurrected,
that doesn't mean I won't let her work for the church.
And that's all she was doing in the back seat of the car with me up by the barn.
No further questions.
Outside of the radio station.
And I ended...
I don't know.
Nobody knows.
Go ahead.
Let Jerry Falwell take over the church of the subgenius.
That's fine with me.
But you see, that would be rather difficult since they're now a mixture of Pentecostals and Baptists and we are...
Are a hideous amalgam of cultish, gibbledy-gook nonsense.
Here, here now.
Let's not backslide.
Fight the good fight.
Oh, I quit.
I've had enough.
If I'm not allowed to brag about my extramarital affairs,
what did I perform for the church?
Even though that wasn't actually...
What?
Six, six, six, six, six.
It's going, amen.
According, everything's going fine.
No trouble.
It's over, friends.
Everything's fine.
We've got to get some money.
That dirty, perky, shark-backed, black, wharton, filibuster, wharton, perky...
Wharton.
A woman like to escort Reverend Stang out and lock him out of this place.
No, no, no, no.
You've got to see this guy for what he is.
He's a maniac out to rule the world.
What can I do to make you understand him?
I love you.
Have I already said, ah, yes, dear friends?
The rewards are worth the effort.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
The harvest.
There, okay, now it's...
Q, night of black shooting tape.
45-minute hour of slack intro.
Q.
And then we'll only have to do 15 more minutes worth of this.
My friends.
And you are...
No!
Ah!
For those of you who are listening to the hour of slack for the first time.
In other words, this is something we don't do very often.
Maybe every 10 shows we play things that will somewhat explain the church of the subgenius,
if that is indeed possible.
And if you are...
indeed listening in headphones
and listening quietly
it will make a lot more sense
keep in mind dear friends that this is not
an imitation subgenius
church radio show
this is not some spin off
denomination it's not the butt naked
denomination praise butt
but the original
orthodox stangian mega
fist temple lodge of covenant
people's church of Dobbs Yeti
resurrected
praise Bob
so do call the Will of Dobbs at
823-7490
or 828-9500
if you value your soul
superior mutants
repent quit your job
slack off
the world ends tomorrow
and you may die
well no probably not
but whatever you do just keep listening
the end times is here
at last the step by step process
is revealed this is it
the only faith that promises
action thrills success
in sex and business
having all the guilt
but none of the guilt
to really great
but we'reeli
you deserve so much
and other than
this
reckless
without
for
I
a
read
I
act
press
You gotta let my people go, go, go
Or they're destroyed
Are we controlled by secret forces?
Do you ever get the feeling that free will is a joke?
Do people think you're strange?
Do you?
Then you may be on the right track
Are you abnormal?
Then you are probably better than most people
Yes, your time shall triumph
But you've tried everything
You ain't seen nothing yet
Learn to think big
Develop the tricks of length extension
Bring your weirdest dreams to rampaging life
Stand direct for your own abnormality
Get sack and fall again
And
The student of Dobbs' training is practically forced
To bring his strangest desires into rampaging life
I used to get embarrassed of all my glass madness
Now I get paid
The pinks pay me fabulous sums of money
For what they used to put me in jail for
Thanks to Bob
Dobbs has seen to it that he exercises this abnormality
To do otherwise, he teaches, would be not to be
Nothing short of spiritual suicide
Oh, oh, oh
Bob is a way of life to millions
Now, the rest of them don't even know
He's the one true living slack master
With the spiritual know-how to help you bash through
The locked doorway to financial heaven
He is the one real shortcut to slack
Now, see another dimension on your TV
Yes, fear the stark fist of removal no longer
Become physically attractive overnight
Attain status, luck, prosperity
By blowing them off
Bob's promises to widen the scope and nature of abnormal behavior
To explore new ways of going over the edge
And coming with you to the end of the world
Right back
Plus, to bring back those who couldn't make it on their own
To help you create the highest possible earnings
From the psychodynamics of abnormality
To turn conspiracy implanted personality disorders around
And channel them into an illusion of creativity
That will fool normals and get you sex
You've only got to find Yunus
So wanted to accompany the
I malign that
Talk about that amusement park
We'll never be able to raise the money for that amusement park
Sure can go to Westward Park
Chilling in a cafe.
Yes, and...
Listen to that reaction.
You know, the shower of razors,
and a lot of fun in the funhouse.
Of course, my favorite, the distorto chamber.
It seems there are some people who have been locked in there since 1944, but...
A six-million-year cycle will end in 1998.
Dobbs sees the world entering a new aeon,
which, in a few years,
will bring more wondrous and miraculous change
and carnage, insanity, and destruction
than all of mankind's history and prehistory before it.
Bob brings a new destiny for America,
a time of cataclysmic economic change
that will offer untold riches and power for those in the know,
while billions of deserving conspiracy dupes
fry in hell on Earth.
Uncontrolled thinking, controlled by Bob,
will usher in a spiritual rebirth
and a cascade of astounding mysteries,
supernatural riches,
and a restoration of lost psychic abilities
that will totally transform the lives of those who dare to seek them and pay for them.
That's right.
You're lucky to live in the end time.
Here's more money, Bob!
Here's six, six, six.
Anybody knows that.
Hello, you're on the air.
Oh, more money?
Hey, yeah.
Do you have a short question, please?
Hey, solid by solid.
Hey.
Repeat.
Repeat your question.
Um, I just had a few brief questions.
My name's Jesus.
And, um...
Hey, I've heard of you.
I've read your book.
Hey, Jesus, how you doing?
Yeah, my favorite part was where they...
It's autobiographical, right?
Where they kill you.
Yeah, ugly girl.
They handled you to the, uh...
That's my book.
Yeah.
Um, well, I just had a couple of questions, philosophical.
Number one.
Um, if you were traveling in a car at the speed of light,
and, um, you turn on the headlights, what would happen?
Let's get on with it.
You'll crash into your own headlights, so I would, uh...
As light solidifies, it becomes of a texture...
Wow, get on with it, then.
...blocks of matter, which will crash in your radiator and damage the front of your chest.
Headlights?
H-E-A-T-E.
Okay.
And, um...
One more.
I-I-I was looking through, um, A Guide to the Subgenius or something like that.
A Guide to the Subgenius?
Or it was, like, a subgenius book?
It's not the new edition from Science History.
No, that's a counterfeit, uh...
It said in there, one passage, that too much is better than not enough.
Always better than not enough.
Is that true with hemorrhoids?
That is true with everything.
No, it's never true.
Bob Dobbs, uh, said it.
Uh, I believe it.
That settles it.
Yeah?
One must ask oneself, what is enough in the case you mention?
It's words to live by for every young teenager out there.
You should be concerned with, uh, other things, like the fact that this area is going to be barely inhabitable in 20 years,
and most places will be a lot worse off.
That's right.
What are you going to do?
Too much ultraviolet light is always better than not enough ultraviolet rays.
It's going to be hotter and wetter, and there's not going to be, uh, much water.
...walking organic mutants.
Yeah, too much poverty and horror is always better than not enough.
Poverty and horror.
Wise up!
They're out to get you.
The difference are being silenced by a global conspiracy.
Weird men arise!
Find out who they are and how to smash them!
You probably already knew that the U.S. government is a sham.
Something prompt up there for you to blame.
But did you know that the real powers that be are not even people?
That they are actually shambling?
Unbelievable?
Unmentionable?
Unthinkable?
Things?
For the first time in man's history, I, uh, I'm president.
Ooh.
And, and, and, and I can do this with dash and daring do.
No.
You're too old.
You're out of touch.
Huh.
I don't think I'm out of touch.
Asked for too old?
Well, I have a very good memory about...
all the things back in my life.
For example, I can remember...
Senator Benjamin Hill in 1878.
When we were less than 70 years old.
Heh.
Ooh.
Good times and bad.
Ronald Reagan.
You can see and understand the America of dirty streets and poor people.
The problem isn't being poor. The problem, the problem is, uh, uh, uh, money.
And...
So, poverty isn't, uh...
Uh...
Juh...
Sss...
Uh...
Juh...
Sss...
I...
Uh...
Okay.
I'm supposed to be the big reactionary.
Alright.
What, what people do you think you represented?
The John Birch Society was praising you.
Oh, yes.
Alright.
The John Birch Society.
Sure.
Milton Friedman.
Certainly.
The far right.
Alright.
As a matter of fact...
Uh, uh...
Uh, a few Republican panaceas, myself, and people like myself, organized a task force.
People outside government and inside.
Uh...
Well, this little group gathered and we very carefully would open the car door with the
window rolled down, shove the man's arm across the window, and then break it.
The backbone of America.
And then break it over the window.
Uh...
And then the pressure came on.
That hidden longing came out and, uh...
Gunshot.
Gunshots.
And so forth.
Oh, oh, what a lovely piece of tape editing there by Douglas Kahn.
Isn't it incredible?
Uh...
I just...
You know, we both recommend Doug...
Thanks, Doug.
I was like, oh, careful, isn't this hell?
And now he the
씨
That's right, Bob t-shirts that you can get by mail from the Weeping Cyclops Insignia
Company serving the public since God knows when.
And their P.O.
Box number, you got that pencil ready?
This is their P.O.
Box number, not ours, but this is where you can order these shirts, is P.O.
Box 595-148 Dallas, Texas 75359-5148.
Thanks, Weeping Cyclops Insignia Company for supporting KNON.
And dear friends, you can actually win one of these shirts.
That's right, we're announcing a contest at this moment.
And the first three of you to call the Will of Dobbs here at 823-7490 or 828-9500 with
the answers to the following question will win a subgenius t-shirt.
Now, here's the question.
In what year, according to Dobbs' prophecy in the Book of the Subgenius, will the Omicron
Epsilon time intersection occur?
Eh?
Now get out your Book of the Subgenius, friends, and call 823-7490 or 828-9500 with that answer.
Or you can write to our box number, but it's first come, first serve.
So you know, we might only get one call tonight with the right answer.
In which case, you ought to write.
But write quick.
So we get it right quick, you know what I mean?
And the rest of you are saying now, Omicron Epsilon time intersection?
What is that anyway?
Well, geez, man, it's only the worst crisis this universe will ever face.
Of course, many people think about X-Day, the arrival of the men from Planet X on X-Day,
1998.
Oh, that might be the end of this planet.
But what happens at the time intersection will determine whether the entire universe
ends then at that point, that year that you're supposed to call in with, or continue for
as long again as it has already existed.
So again, this is not X-Day.
The answer is not 1998.
Don't even bother with that.
No, no.
No, we're not talking about X-Day.
You didn't listen.
You've been calling in.
Or you can write to the Church of the Subgenius.
Also, you just write us for information if you want to get some free material.
At Bob, P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
That's Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
And the Weeping Cyclops Insignia Company, again, is Box 59514.
8 in Dallas, Texas 75359.
So let's see who's going to win.
Let's go.
Now friends, we've already had ten calls that said 1998.
We've got one winner.
One winner.
Who is that one?
Brian Maddux.
Old praise Reverend Brian.
But you're going to have to get your book of the subgenius and look real close.
I'm not going to give you a hint what page it's on.
It's in there.
There it is.
Slack.
What is it?
Well, if you have to ask, you'll probably never know.
You were born with original slack and an infinite supply of it, but the conspiracy has most
of it now.
They don't even know what it is, but that hasn't stopped them from stealing it away.
How do you think you ended up a slave to their so-called work?
True slack is, by definition, insubstantial.
indefinable. It is a kind of direct perception unfettered by common sense. It is not merely
laziness. It is rather a kind of active sloth. Slack in its pure form makes happiness seem like
agony by comparison. Next to slack, the nirvana known to mystics and saints is like endless
torment. Slack is different for each person, although for much of the world, slack is nothing
more than a good meal. One might call it something for nothing. But the normals, the mediocratons,
the somnambulacks, and pseudo-sub-slans have tried to make it something which we've been led
to believe we must work to buy. It is this yearning.
The normals have tried to make it something for slackness separates us from them. The human may live out his entire life in a grinding cycle of slacklessness, his hours consumed by meaningless toil, interspersed with meaningless leisure.
Yet he never feels cheated. He thinks it's natural. Perhaps we should pity them, but face it, most people are venal jerks, half-witted cattle racing each other to be
first.
The normals are the first of the slaughterhouse, stampeding you along with them.
And there's something else that a true subgenius knows, Joe. When we talk about the conspiracy, I know that you're all cultured, I know you're all literary, I know you're used to thinking in circles, but there's one thing you should know.
The conspiracy is no metaphor.
Joe, when we talk about the conspiracy, are we discussing some literary poetic monster?
Say no!
No!
No, we're not joking! We're talking about a living, breathing, firing, and giving a strength that wants to consume you!
That wants to take away your slack, children!
Are we going to let them take away your slack?
No!
Say no!
Tell me something! Who stands in the way of the conspiracy?
I don't know!
Who?
I can't hear you joking!
Bob!
That was the Pope of all New York!
It's 1-4-0-3-0-6, so think about it!
When you cast your mojo patches, when you ride through Dallas, Texas, when you think about it!
Think about it!
$1!
This is Dr. Onan's Wotan Band!
Bob!
Did you get that?
Thank you!
What do you really think?
When you read that spin magazine to find out about those critical independent singles,
did you get that spin magazine from the priest?
Say no!
Absolutely not!
The next rule of the Church of the Sogenius is that the Church of the Sogenius will help
you pull wool over your own eyes.
You see, ladies and gentlemen, ever since you were a little bitty baby, you have been
sold other people's wool.
You've been sold your parents' wool, your church or synagogue's wool, your school's
wool, your college's wool, your girlfriend or boyfriend's wool, your husband's wife's
wool.
But here we want you to pull your own wool over your eyes and relax in the safety trove
around your own illusions.
The reason we want you to do this is that once you've got that wool over your eyes and
you're immersed in those illusions, in five minutes you'll be so bored, you'll start
to know what God wants you to do.
You'll start thinking for yourself.
Thank you.
Goodness gracious, what a simply horrible patchwork of noise that Church of the Sogenius
is.
I listen every week to gather evidence and ammunition for the citizens for normalcy.
Let me tell you, we're not going to get those Sogeniuses.
We're going to get them right in the gonads.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to say that.
I don't use words like that.
This tape, all about Satanism, drugs and rock and roll, is proof positive that this
so-called church is going to send the world to heck in a handbasket.
All those demented Beelzebub kissing hop heads make me want to toss my Nestle's dollhouse
cookies with their talk of buckets of pills from that low-life pusher J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Why, they're so high on drugs that they can't even keep any continuity.
Too many children listen to these tapes and subscribe to the insane doctrines of the
Sogenius Foundation.
They're led down a deceptive road to what these weirdos call slack, like that heathenist
idea of Nirvana.
I say that slack should be taken up like the excess yarn in my knitting and pulled until
it sees the light of a normal day like the rest of us do.
So what should any decent-minded American do?
What can they do when faced with one of these zombies for Bob?
Well, first off, give them a bath in Pine Sol.
They usually stink to high heaven.
Then ship them off to the nearest normally accredited deprogrammer.
Well, they'll get bombarded with enough People magazines, arid extra-dry deodorant, and Regis
Philbin fan club material so they won't be able to think anymore the way it should be.
Then they'll feed them real dogma about the glory of the world.
The stories of the home shopping club, Wingo, Zingo, and the evils of Mandingo.
We cannot stand by while our standards and principles are made light of by these possessed
fools.
Normals of the world unite.
Oh, dear friends, and quit calling in with those contest answers.
We got all three winners.
I can't believe it.
Dave Bales.
Hey, guys.
Great.
Douglas Hooper and, yeah, Reverend Brian.
So...
And that was the Citizens for Normalcy tape you just heard.
Thank you.
Wouldn't you like revenge on these mediocratons, these pink boys, these box-dwelling Barbies and Kens?
These normals who have made normality the norm?
Pinks.
Pinks are but living stereotypes, insensate meat puppets and mere food tubes who lack
and fear the spark of originality that ignites every fucking soul.
Within every person, there's some good and there's some bad.
And it's a choice.
You choose whether you want to love or hate that person.
And for myself, I just choose to hate most of them.
Whoo!
Now, when a subgenius says that he hates, what kind of a hate is he talking about, children?
Is he talking about your average run-of-the-mill hate?
Like, oh, I just hate Reagan.
That's pathetic!
Or even worse, the nampy-pampy pitiful little...
I just hate my...
I just hate myself.
No!
What we talk about when we talk about hate is an all-consuming, an all-encompassing,
an all-pervasive hate!
An infinite hate!
A hate that knows no bounds!
A hate that extends to the very end of all known universes!
A hate!
A hate as black as outer space itself!
We're talking about the nampy-pampy pitiful little...
We're talking about an all-consuming hate!
And who is this hate directed at, children?
There are certain men whose repugnance and hideousness is so all-pervailing...
That's it!
We call them...
We have a special label for these men.
Idols of hate!
Now, what is an example of what we call an idol of hate?
What is an example of what we call an idol of hate?
One such example of what we call an idol of hate...
Is?
Is old Mr. That's-Just-His-Royal-Hate.
We've got a lot of these in Arkansas.
The, that's just his way, redneck.
Oh, you mean he's totally obnoxious and sadistic?
Well, that's just his way.
Oh, you mean he's splitting your face open?
Well, that's just the way he is.
Oh, did he try to genocide an entire race and destroy half the world?
That's just his way.
Well, I think that's valid, I accept that.
But this is just...
This is just my way.
That I enjoy bathing in the blood of just-his-way people.
That's just the way I am, is that I just enjoy making lampshades of the flesh of just-his-way people.
That's just the way I am.
And if you can't dig that, I guess you're just on some kind of judgmental trip.
But it's, you just have to let the hate flow.
It's a very, very beautiful process.
You just, you just let it happen.
And what are some of the other, what we call idols of hate?
What are some of the other idols of hate?
What are you, idols of hate?
I think you know who we're talking about.
Mr. Pinkboy, sir.
Mr. Conspiracy, sir.
Mr. Closet Nazi Corporate Executive, sir.
Mr. Filthy Rich Mind Control TV Evangelist.
Hope you don't even know what we're talking about.
You were just clicking through the channels.
But by God, you gonna hear me now.
Sir.
Mr. Secular Trevenist.
Hey!
Treveno is launching Van Dobbs from public school system.
They won't even, they won't even teach Bob in the public schools anymore.
But I think we know who's gonna have the last lesson, don't we?
Yes!
Now, what kind of,
Oh!
But you can't compare yourself to any kind of human hate.
Well, you could say, oh!
Oh, I hate as much as John Smith does.
Or, or, well, I hate as much as, as Mary Jones hates.
You can't compare yourself to any human hate.
You've got to compare yourself to the divine hate of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
If you could realize for one femtosecond,
how much this man hates you.
Oh, that was J.R. Hyperkleets in Boston.
Why are you getting out of his head?
Just like a drive-in movie.
Out by the scenic pond.
Oh, great.
Tonight they're showing Terms of Endearment.
I need no conspiracy as much as it beats me.
But I mean, Bob will get them.
Just you wait and see.
They think they're all Frank Capra, but they're just a bunch of geeks.
Monday night is football, and Tuesday night is bridge.
Let's all go do the laundry and check what's in the fridge.
Christmas, Easter, Halloween, it's enough to drive you nuts.
But the long, senseless march into slacklessness may soon come to an end.
Oh, it won't be without a bitter struggle.
But at least there is hope.
For in this, the twentieth century, we have seen the coming of a savior.
A beacon of slack.
A banner behind which we may unite.
It is the coming of J.R. Bob Dobbs and his mighty Church of the Subgenius.
...do with it whatsoever.
...as to whether man will destroy himself...
Yes, the animal kingdom.
...from the face of this planet.
Now that's a very discerning comment.
...this is man's destiny or potential.
You've lost you enthusiasm for your job, and you think you're bored and you're willing to quit, and you're about ready to walk away.
Wait a minute!
Thank you.
What?
But, but, but,
but what's wrong with hate?
No, that wasn't actually,
what?
Anybody knows that?
Yes, the six, six, six club
had got a new host now.
Those six, uh,
six friends had better
come on.
pull in their horns and, well, you know, they're just, they're out of control.
Are you serious?
The psychopaths of the church, they can't touch us in old-time hierarchical.
We're the original fishers of wallets for J.R. Bob Dobbs.
I actually have Bob's autograph.
Hello, I'm Floyd T. Reprothel, general manager of this radio station.
We've been getting lots of support for our programming from you listeners out there, and we're grateful.
We especially appreciate your comments on the subgenius show at 4.30 on Saturday mornings.
Believe me, we intend to do something about those comments.
As of now, the so-called subgenius show is on probation.
We'll be monitoring the show closely for irregularities and inaccuracies,
as well as for the allegedly offensive portions of the program that apparently were too intense for some of our listeners.
Because we care.
We care about your patronage.
What about the slosh fund?
What about the secret photos of Stang and My Little Pony?
What I do with my spare time and off hours?
I mean, a preacher is a human being, too.
I can't be expected to stand there at that pulpit 24 hours a day.
I'm sorry, you have to be expected to be in the public eye, constantly scrutinized.
That's fine.
I don't think I should be docked all that pay just because of one dream.
Now, Mr. Stang...
Mr. Stang, could you please turn to page 27 in your budget here?
That's the revised standard version.
Now, this is all in code, is it not?
Self-esteem.
Well, it depends on what you call code.
So, when it refers here to He-Man, that's actually...
That's actually you, correct?
No, He-Man is the senator from West Virginia, as a matter of fact.
Oh, I don't expect you to believe that.
Are you sure you're on the same page here?
Oh, okay, right, I've got it.
Okay, 27, go ahead.
The sum here is $63 million.
Where was that supposed to be delivered to?
Uh...
Well, let me consider...
Let me consult with my lawyer.
You know, I can't expect to remember every tiny little detail.
Mr. Stang, are you familiar with the Drummond Amendment, sir?
Just a moment, your honor.
Senator, my client wishes to read a statement into the record at this point.
Very well.
I did not and will not ever admit...
Could you speak a little louder, Mr. Stang?
...to the specific dream sequence...
Go closer to the microphone.
...that these Dream Monitor reporters have recorded of this alleged encounter,
which I assure you is absolutely unsexual in nature,
between Reverend Mandy, Reverend Ann, and myself.
Just answer the question.
Are you now or have you ever been a member of the human race?
No, I can absolutely deny, categorically deny...
...the human race.
Mr. Stang...
He's got an extra tailbone back there,
and my brother has a supernumerary nipple.
I have proof...
We have the nipple and the cockaxe on display as exhibit means.
No one is completely informed of human genes,
except perhaps our Yeti cousins in the Himalayas.
In the Himalayas.
And so you see, that's what Mr. Stang testified,
and that's what made him America's sweetheart.
We have a marvelous show today, folks.
Our very special guest is loved and admired.
He's been a great humanitarian.
Please welcome one of America's oldest and most respected kids,
Ivan Stang.
Besides balancing with Michael...
...is a man who many of you may have already seen on television shows,
such as the Lou Gordon Show,
Tom Snyder's Tomorrow Show,
To Tell the Truth,
and What's My Line?
He's been the subject of articles in Motor Trend,
Newsweek, Automotive News,
Penthouse Magazine,
and newspapers all over the world.
He is the only man in all of the sales fields
to have a place in the Guinness Book of World Records.
He is, simply speaking, the world's greatest salesman,
and has held that distinction every year for over a decade.
He is the head of the Subgenius Foundation, Inc.,
an organization that markets its own unique system of sales training aids.
He has been nominated for the Horatio Alger Award
for his outstanding rise from poverty to the top in the business world.
And Simon & Schuster Publishers will publish his new book entitled
The Book of the Subgenius.
If there is anybody who has created a more enviable reputation
in person-to-person, one-at-a-time, belly-to-belly selling than
J.R. Bob Dobbs,
I defy you to name him.
What you are about to hear is truly an experience with
Bob.
Thank you.
All right.
How are you?
I like you.
There's a balloon for you.
I give balloons away, too.
Thank you.
Thanks for coming.
Thanks for coming, baby.
Pass a few of these on.
These pins here that I'm giving out,
I think are three of the strongest,
strongest words you'll ever see in your life.
I like you.
I give them to everybody that's...
Listen to those swinging love corpses.
Oh, that rare, rare tape of J.R. Bob Dobbs himself
is from Reverend Frank from the round table discussion
Clench in Arizona.
I'm sure you hope we still have our old audience
now that we've moved to prime time.
I'm assuming that we may pick up some of George's folks,
his new wave experimental rock and roll audience.
But on the other hand,
we probably don't really want all of George DeMarc's audience
because all of his friends are in the same room.
Although probably half of them are potential subgeniuses
or at least potential undeclared closet subgeniuses at best,
which are the ones we're interested in.
Probably the other half are nothing but young pinks
who sort of like to think they're punks,
but who at any rate are really just conformist,
nonconformists who really believe that if,
as long as they're up on the latest underground,
really happening music,
that this'll make them cooler than everybody else.
Oh, friends, if only it was that easy.
I was there in that stupid position myself at one time, of course.
Of course, in those days,
that was when KNUS was the most avant-garde station in Dallas,
believe it or not.
That was when Frank Zappa and Jimi Hendrix
were actually underground unknowns.
Devo was 16 years old like me
and Sid Vicious was still in diapers
and whoever the heck is cool now
was just a gleam in his daddy's eye.
I know I'm afraid I don't have any higher hopes
for the quote,
new wave or new music unquote audience anymore
than I did for my hippie compatriots
back when I cut my hair to a burr,
my once long hair to a burr haircut in 1972.
That was when I saw the rednecks
that used to try to beat me up suddenly growing long.
I realized at that point that the youth movement was sold out.
Well, what happened to the 60s?
Same thing that's happening now.
A few of George's audience are committed to the weirdness,
to true freedom and originality and slack
and will be so throughout their lives
in many different disguises.
The rest will just talk and talk about it,
but they'll be stuck in some teenage time warp
where from now on your idea of what's cool
has already been cemented into place.
You're destined, friend,
to be nothing but another target audience.
And you'll deserve nothing but that
because you'll be nothing but a pink.
At the age of 40,
you'll still either be wearing your current hairdo
or you'll be trying like hell to dress halfway between that
and what's currently fashionable,
just like all the sportscasters will be doing.
Yes, you'll look like a sportscaster of 1998.
Uh, and you won't find Bob
because you won't understand him.
Or you'll get it all wrong and think you need Bob
and buy him for 20 bucks.
Except it'll probably be $500 by then.
Now last week when I was in San Francisco,
we got a call from a poor wretched teenager
who wanted to know what happened to the 60s.
And I think you'll be touched by the pathos
that you hear in this lad's voice.
And when Lies and I give our response,
you'll know that we're telling the truth.
And everybody stay tuned after that
for the American Music Party.
Music that shall never die.
The wisdom of Robert.
Hehehehehehehehehehe.
Oh, that pop is good.
It's impossible to do everything tonight.
What I know...
What happened to you,
you people who actually were able to experience it,
I was...
What do you mean?
I'm 14.
The Reverend Howe is 12.
And staying here, I think, is 9.
Timmy has to tinker.
Hehehehehehehehehehe.
Oh, we sold it to the conspiracy.
We hippies, represented by the 18 people in this room,
sold the 60s to the conspiracy.
Everything.
And it was well worth it.
They went and, of course, modified it into, uh,
opunk, heavy metal...
Oh, there's nothing wrong with it?
But it's just a margarine commercial jingle these days.
That's just a hollow imitation punk and all that.
It's just like a hollow...
They don't even understand what they're doing
when they do most of the rituals they do.
It's almost like a mythology or a tradition
carried on by people who don't understand.
They might understand, but they don't care.
That's the thing to remember.
I understand, but I don't care.
I understand it, I don't care.
I don't know what to tell you, son.
I'm still waiting for the 1860s to come around again,
and I've been bitterly disappointed.
Point it up to the flam.
Parallel flam. Parallel flam.
We all like to think we're marching to the...
to the cadence of a different drummer.
Have any of you noticed the absence of Suicide Man?
Did you know that he moved to...
He moved to the worst...
So he finally killed himself, huh?
Suicide Man.
Well, you don't care about Suicide Man.
Friends, if you want to get some information
about the Church of the Subgenius,
just write...
Just request some info about Bob
from Bob at...
P.O. Box 140306.
Dallas, Texas 75214.
I'm gonna let this new Zug's Rift...
Man, Zug's Rift comes out with a new one every week now,
it seems like.
We can actually get them at record stores.
This new one's called Water.
Kraze Bomb!
Who the hell is this?
You think Graziella's pot
Speaker 2 shoes is, uh...
No, it ain't.
Are you crazy?
guitar solo