Are you too stupid to see what's going to happen? I know what's coming. Have I got to beat you to make you understand?
It's going to end more horribly than anything in all history. That much I know.
And that the very door of the day of the wrath of God is at hand.
And that if you plan to get saved, you'd better do it now.
In this temple lodge of the Church of the Subgenius of Little Rock, and before we begin this sacred spouting,
I think that we should all bow our heads and let's all have a minute of noise.
Have we started yet? Oh, damn.
Hey, where's the Puzzling Evidence music? When does it kick in? About four, right?
Is the show on right now?
Well, that is a matter of discussion.
Okay, so we're waiting for the call from Brushwood Folklore Center, where the subgeniuses are standing out there.
If we get the call from Brushwood confirming that the end of the world has happened, that's when we'll have it?
That's when we need to start running west as fast as we can.
And thumbing our noses at the chaos.
When does the over end of the world happen at each place?
Well, it officially happens at 7 a.m. Central Time, so that would have put it at 6 a.m.
Is that right?
Let me tell you, we'll be on our way to 5 a.m.
At 5 a.m., we'll be counting down.
5 a.m. is the time.
Of course, that's the time the show is normally drawing to a conclusion,
and you...
Hopefully, we'll be able to work the end of the world in just before the show ends.
Time marches on.
Just because the world is ending doesn't mean we shouldn't.
Right, just because the world is ending doesn't necessarily mean that the show doesn't have obligations,
as does the show that comes on after this, because it's only the world as we know it that's ending.
The world as we don't know it will continue on for eons, centuries, decades even,
mightily zooming along in a way that we never thought possible.
And bouncing energy off into space.
Because it will be the future, and we'll enter the thousand-year millennium
into the weakness of the eternal void.
So often spoken of by those people who come to my front door when I don't want them to.
That's great, it starts with a handshake.
Exits UFO's outer space.
J.R. Dobbs is not afraid.
He is the eye of a hurricane.
Watch your money burn.
Thinks are their own needs.
Yet he's every own needs.
Feeding on a purse with great strength.
End times are close at hand.
Uber woman over.
Man liar in a fire.
Representing all we hate.
With a government for hire and a combat site.
The best is less of genie in a hurry with a con breathing down their neck.
Group by group, normals falsified.
Full fart.
Look at that love playing.
Fine.
Then.
Uh oh.
Oh no.
Population they don't know.
Save yourself.
Serve yourself.
Pink serve their own need.
Yeti serve your own need.
Time to plunge your own seed.
Yeti with a rupture in the rubbered in the right.
Right.
You super slack maniac.
Slam.
Fight.
Fright.
Light.
The strikes you died with in lack of aieteness here at 12 seulon to hope you claimed them
to be in vain.
Am I right?
Who cares if you have a eaten you won't have grace on so as my Cavalier Bob aisphere
on the dance floor?
Hold up.
Hey that turd.
Say that damn rascal of a-
I'm sorry.
I told you that Après Sales after youormone.
Let's see who we kill next.
My name is Chaz, and I'm broadcasting you tonight from my little holding cell here.
All quarantined, all strapped in my suit, pressure suits all pressured up.
Yeah, it's here.
The ship is waiting, hissing away, spewing out its little steam.
Waiting for the moment, the final countdown.
And that's where we're at.
Just hours away from the final hour.
The final minute.
The final second.
And...
X-Day.
Thought it'd never get here.
It's kind of a...
It's kind of late now.
We're there.
There's nothing else to do.
Just sit, look out the window, and wait for the light.
X-Day.
Is your pleasure ship hovering above, waiting for the final hours to pass?
Is your alien sex goddess waiting for you somewhere in Eurasia blue?
X-Day.
X-Day...
Sleepo.
Yeah.
Chaz and I have been planning which reruns we're going to run
since there's only another week of broadcasting left on the planet.
Oh, God.
I've done 638 hours of sleep.
Down to a few hours now.
And we're going to start rerunning number one.
I mean, for what radio stations are left.
Right.
And what were you thinking of doing, Chaz?
I don't understand how a lot of this is going to take place.
I don't understand how a lot of this happens.
I just know that it won't fail because of me.
We all are in this together as a team effort.
We're going to make it work.
And I don't know how to make it work.
I don't know how to do most of this mission.
But I do know that I can assure you that my piece of it is going to work.
And it won't fail because of me.
On X-Day, Neeky will return to us all the greatest tapes that we ever recorded.
Praise the Neeky.
He has been keeping it.
Oh, God.
That's so good.
Neeky has been keeping all of our lost recordings in a special vault.
You hear that?
Those will all be returned to us on X-Day.
Oh, that's so glorious.
Jayner will get his 8mm films back.
Oh.
You know, your first show will come back.
Actually, I never did lose anything.
Will I get those videos that I erased by accident back?
As long as you saw them.
You mean everything I've ever seen?
You know, that you never got around to looking at?
Uh-huh.
Even if I've only seen it for a fraction of a second.
What about events that I've never taped that never were taped?
There's a thing called the new program.
What?
This is too damn confusing.
I'm getting out of here.
Will then be done.
They will have been done.
When you want to do a wonderful new show, that show will materialize in your hand.
Yeah, the new program.
Email the program.
Do I buy it next day?
Pleasure shirts are on their way.
Quit your job.
Keep your stuff.
Black Jared Ops has got your back.
Hail Connie.
Hail Bob.
On your knees, self-righteous love.
Give it up.
Give it in.
Find yourself a Yeti kit.
New religion radio.
Hell poke.
Gonna blow.
Pay to find out what you know.
Pass the pipe.
Take a trick.
I'm telling you, this is no joke.
Spirits see you steer clear.
A tournament.
A tournament of lies.
Offer me solutions and you offer me alternatives and I decline.
It's the end of the world as we know it.
It's the end of the world.
Offer me solutions and you offer me alternatives and you decline.
All the leaders alive in the other world will be.
The end of the world as we know it.
There's, like, it into the top Garth Dix.
Antique the end of the world, your own bottom Jeter.
The time will be John Doyle, you ain't been here long enough.
Checking out Bob Gix is coming, your Expand Signs planet.
If you're up the draußen season is like practicing.
Bob may be in there or standing over.
Nicole Jewellyn
I can begin only onisoft now.
quite from where you are.
Well, the same sort of way
that we had before,
which seems truly
indicative of some
excess activity,
but the means
provided this illusion
that the master
subs deliberately
and intentionally
fed to the only.
What I think is
personally rather interesting
is the way the shadow
moves across the face
of the continent,
and as it moves,
the end of the world
is on one side,
and the world
still exists on the other side.
The falling magma,
the destroyed planet,
with airplanes flying out of it
and people running,
horses, animals galloping.
Those wise...
So does Ivan Stank
think he's the guy
in the cowl,
or is he just Darth Vader?
He thinks he's the guy
in the cowl, yeah.
He's the one that
Darth Vader throws
into the deep hole
and blows up.
Yeah, and he also
plays piano
in Weird Al Yankovic's...
Oh, I'm sorry,
I've got the election music
on here.
Oh, yes.
President, uh,
Senor Bush.
One of the big election news
that we did have
which seemed to change
everything since...
It's not funny, sir.
It's not funny.
They stole the election, sir.
Friends and neighbors
of planet Earth,
I come to you
from a long, long ways off.
I come from a planet
that is similar to yours.
Your many fears,
tensions, and frustrations
are no longer ours.
I hate them
with all my heart.
They are in my heart.
I hate them
and to be destroyed.
You are not ready,
but we will still save you.
By 1998,
every normal,
mediocritan,
pink boy,
admin,
Trekkie,
and hippie
is gonna be trying
to get on board
with the good ship dogs.
The great ship dogs.
Or they're gonna fry
along with everybody else.
When those aliens get here.
Of course,
such a prophecy
immediately arises
our cynicism.
Is it possible
that the end of the world
will come in July 1999?
Perhaps.
Or is it just another
of those prognostications
which have haunted man
through the ages?
But the old ones
are coming back.
I'm going to let them through.
So we gotta get ourselves
through from these two stones here.
There.
To those two stones down there.
And we can actually sort of
will ourselves into the saucer
which is hovering in the next dimension.
It's about time.
Yeah, it's not an actual physical thing
of saucers coming out of normal reality.
It's saucers coming out of an alternate reality.
The tools of conquest
do not necessarily come with bombs
and explosions and fallout.
That looks like people demonstrating outside now.
Outside the station.
Demonstrating about the end of the world.
It should not happen.
They're demonstrating about
the end of the world
and whether or not
we've properly recognized it.
And it's not completely correct.
There's those people on one side
that want to make sure
that we have taken full, you know,
regard to the end of the world
and that we have recognized it
as the thing that it is.
And then those people
that protest the end of the world
and refuse to, you know,
participate in it.
And those are the ones that we need to,
you know, somehow or another,
convince that this is
the end of the world.
Remember now, the end of the world
is occurring in three minutes.
And it's just so great that,
I just think it's so great
that it coincides with the birth
of our country.
The anniversary of the birth
of our great, great country.
That country that was founded
by John Philip H. Bush.
And I think it will be great
about the end of the world.
No more mosquitoes.
Back 3,000 years ago,
when our fathers and our forefathers
and our five fathers came forward
and founded this nation
with John Philip Sousa,
one nation under God,
under Vishnu,
under Krishna, under Bob,
primarily under Bob.
But hovering over populated areas.
Those were the ones that could see
the fortunate few,
the free, the proud,
the end.
All of our lives,
we have fought this war.
Tonight, I believe we can end it.
Tonight is not an accident.
There are no accidents.
We have not come here by chance.
I do not believe in chance.
When I see three objectives,
three captains,
three ships,
I do not see coincidence.
I see providence.
I see purpose.
And now, for more live coverage of X Day,
we move to a field outside of Avebury, England,
where it's 6.30 a.m.
and the European subgenius conclave
is awaiting the saucers.
We are now amid the ancient monoliths
and standing stones of this magically charged
crop circle pocked land.
How much time have we got?
Four minutes.
Let us break bread, my friends.
Let us drink from the scepter.
Let us drink our last beer on earth.
Praise Bob.
It is good.
A little rubbery.
It is our last beer on earth.
Slither.
The last holy elixir.
Ah, the keeper of the Otis drinks from the scepter.
This man is not saved.
One more.
All the subgenius drinks have been sifted.
He will be the first to die.
He'll be the last to live.
He's giving us a countdown.
And that's worse.
Time, time, time.
What time is it?
My clock's wrong.
Two minutes.
Two minutes to go.
Two minutes to lift off.
We know when they're here, damn it.
Two minutes to pay your $30.
There will be no last minute knock-down sale.
Look at these sheep.
They don't even realize they're about to be incinerated in the afterburners of Paul.
Oh mighty goddesses in heaven that sit upon the UFOs, we await thee.
Come to us.
And I drink my last drop of holy elixir upon this planet waiting for you.
Drink from your own cup, popey boy.
I believe it is our fate to be here.
It is our destiny.
I believe this night holds.
For each and every one of us.
The very meaning of our lives.
One minute!
This is the last time I gotta get up before seven, right?
Oh yeah, yeah, we'll have to do this.
I'm sure all the drills will have paid off by this time.
We'll be ready.
I've been drilled too damn many times if you ask me.
Oh boy, this is exciting now.
It's gotta be one of these episodes, right?
10, 9, 8, 7, 8, 9, 10.
6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Let's make it time!
We're tired of your phony fireworks.
Barco, you have earned this.
What about, uh, what about this, uh, reputed, uh...
Jesus, Starfleet that was, uh, supposed to have shown up.
As you see, they have just left the hangar deck at Lunar Central and have cleared the airlocks into the colony.
The crowd of scientists and technicians are going wild.
What a space ovation.
The sheep know something's up!
$30 for eternal salvation!
The sheep are starting to run!
Look, the sheep are shedding their wool.
That's not shedding, it's burning!
They're burning off!
The sheep are starting to walk away.
I think they sense...
One minute!
The anal probe is approaching.
One minute, you say?
One minute.
Do you feel it?
I feel it!
Can you feel it in your bowels?
Can you feel it in your fingertips?
Ah, look at...
Look into the heavens, there is what...
There...
No, that's a crow.
Sorry.
I forgot my towel.
40 seconds!
Here's our opening!
Papa Cho, we've gotta launch the head or they won't come!
Bring the head forth.
20 seconds!
Ladies and gentlemen, this is a...
An important moment.
15 seconds!
We must launch the head at the actual second.
Start the countdown!
10...
9...
8...
7...
6...
5...
4...
3...
2...
1...
RAISE BALLS!
We're still here!
Something must have gone wrong.
Hold on, hold on!
Oh!
Hold on...
I was ten seconds fast.
10...
WE CAN WIN IT!
WE GOT THIS!
7...
6...
1...
4...
3...
NO!
2...
1...
NO!
Ahhhhhhhhh!
Ahhhhh!
Look the sheep are running even faster!
We are now in celebration of the great occasion of the second...
On this occasion we have planned a lunar party. We hope all young people throughout the solar system will join us in celebration of this great day in outer space.
Bob?
I can't help thinking, what if you're wrong? What if all this, the prophecy, everything is bullshit?
Then tomorrow we may all be dead. But how would that be different from any other day?
That's utter nonsense!
The future is always nonsense, until it becomes the past.
Because some things never change, and some things do.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one!
No!
We interrupt this program to bring you a special news bulletin.
They destroyed the world.
Already hospital facilities have begun to crack under the strain,
and civil defense authorities state that the situation is much the same as before.
The entire country is in chaos.
Martial law is now nationwide.
Our fellow countrymen are dying.
The very foundations of civilization are beginning to crumble under the dread assault of that horror long feared.
Bob?
Colorado Channel, this is a class one emergency.
All civilian traffic is barred from streets and highways.
Stay in your homes. Stay in your homes.
I got exactly what I wanted!
Hello world!
Chaz here.
ESO Radio, broadcasting live from the pleasure ships.
Oh yeah!
Where you gonna go?
When the sex goddesses come for you.
Gonna go to the place that's the best.
When I lay me down to die.
Going up to the spirit in the sky.
Bob?
It's where I'm gonna go when I die.
When I die and lay me to rest.
I'm gonna go to the place that's the best.
And it's so beautiful from out here.
It's so pretty, the earth.
It's just that little blue and white, little marble hanging there.
Gosh!
That's where it all began.
We'll see ya.
Goodbye.
It's so very lonely.
Your two thousand light years to come.
Failure is not an option.
Check orange light sequence two.
Yeah, well, at least out here in space where we don't talk about nothing, there's lots of continuity.
Check emergency override switch.
It was a scary week, but we feel better now.
Okay, we've got everything in perspective.
It's all okay now.
It's not us.
I brought the doctors with me to talk about that very show.
I've still got those orange lights inside my helmet.
Except that one of them's just turned green.
And I'm still blind.
But don't worry, little subgeniuses.
This war that we're trying to start on the air right now,
is it for you?
How long you been on board Bungo, John?
I mean Jane.
About fifteen minutes now.
Oh, jeez, I thought it was fifteen years.
I've been on for fifteen thousand years.
Well, there's no real time, is there?
No, it's whatever time you want to take or have or be on.
Oh, my God, it just never ends.
It's like a loop.
It's time control finally, as Bob promised.
Now that I'm on the escape mode, I can't do anything.
I'm on the vessels of the sex goddesses, having spent my thirty dollars on Bob.
Now I have time control.
Yeah, friends, you can wrap the movie a strip of infinity around your little finger like a ring and wear it when you go to dances or parties or perhaps even bobs.
It's the end of the world.
Hello, am I on the air?
Yes, you are.
Oh, good, good, good.
Um.
Are you enjoying X Day?
Yes, it's right here.
It looks like a beautiful one.
We're sorry, your call did not go through.
Oh, no.
Oh, a conspiracy is jamming these calls.
We're sorry, your call did not go through.
Will you please hang up and try your call again?
This is a recording.
Sir, X Day is...
We're sorry, your call did not go through.
Sir, X Day is jamming.
Will you please hang up and try your call again?
Can I please talk to my family?
This is a recording.
X Day, can I...
All these young kids on here.
Can I please talk to my family?
It's X Day.
All right, all right, all right.
Hang that phone up.
I'm back, I'm back.
Oh, hi.
Hi.
It's great here at X Day.
Um, we, the saucers, of course, didn't come again.
Those went away.
We had to go back.
We were up early.
We're gonna have bacon and eggs in a little while.
Oh, the eggs were bacon and eggs.
Reverend X Day sings us some patriotic songs.
Well, I guess you'll have to soldier me.
And Princess Lee is making cantaloupe sundaes.
And, well, it's just a great time here.
We're just having a wonderful, wonderful time.
And, uh, did anybody...
Were there any survivors at the end of the world?
Of course, yeah, we had, uh...
Some of them, yeah.
I'm always...
We had a lot of survivors.
This is the meaning of...
And practically everybody survived this time.
There were some deaths from the previous couple of nights, uh, activities, but that's to be,
you know, to be, uh, anticipated.
Did you say that some people did not survive the party?
Uh, yes, that's right.
Uh, some people were...
The party in my pants.
Um, unfortunately...
Yes, like, look at Hal.
He's certainly in the spirit of X Day over there.
Yeah.
Look, he's taking on the party.
He's taking on the party in my pants.
I'm a UFO and I can't...
Oh.
What's he doing?
Well, who's perfect?
It's only human, isn't it?
Although very unusual to see the teeth green as well as the...
Uh, so, uh, what can I tell you?
Anything else about, uh, the report here from X Day?
How about the emanations of Bob?
As they appear?
And Bob, Bob, uh, Bob was here and, uh...
I thought it was him.
...each of the, each of the worshippers went through and kept his behind.
Which is the...
I'm not sure what the ritualistic task that we must do.
We all kissed the brown eye of Bob.
Not out in the here and around.
It's crude, uh, superstitious parody.
It is, uh, parody.
Actual sub-key of subgenius religion.
Okay, well, they're calling us for breakfast, so I'm gonna be, uh, heading out now and I'll
be...
Well, thank your lucky stars that you can draw your breath on this X Day and, uh, may
the benediction of Bob follow you into the, uh, outhouse.
Okay.
Okay, thank you, too.
Aye-aye-aye-aye-aye-aye-aye.
A bear went a great loyal subgenius in the great America.
No, it was wrong again!
Hold on!
Wait a minute!
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
Oh, wait a minute!
We must have done something wrong.
We've been abandoned in our moment of triumph!
Maybe this is a good time to be back.
Maybe all of our watches are wrong and it still hasn't happened yet.
Maybe we're on the sources.
I'm keeping hope.
It's the last time we buy those cheap Christmas burgers.
Hey, maybe we are on the sources.
This just isn't fair!
There's still...
There's still thirty seconds to go on this one.
Come back, Bob!
But thirty seconds!
There's still thirty seconds to go on this book.
Run, Bob and Joe!
Okay, this time we're gonna get it right.
We have to get it right.
Fifteen!
Unless he was causing it to goof up.
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
There's something wrong here.
There is...
I don't think...
Are you sure about the day?
Is this the...
The fifth or...
Well it's a fifth.
I don't see anything up there.
I know what's wrong!
We've got to drink more Holy Elixir!
More elixir!
I don't understand it.
Everything was done as it was supposed to be done.
The prophecy tells us...
It was a lie, Morpheus.
The prophecy was a lie.
It was all another system with control.
I don't believe that.
But you said it yourself.
How can the prophecy be true if the war isn't over?
I'm sorry.
I know it isn't easy to hear, but...
I swear to you it's the truth.
What are we gonna do?
I don't know.
Laugh.
I don't laugh.
Why don't you?
You should.
Yeah.
I'm gonna try to do it.
I have a better idea.
Yeah.
You talk too much.
What's so funny, Tuts?
Are you still laughing at that stinking joke?
Me?
No.
Yes.
I hate to change the subject, but, you know,
if this is the fifth time that the X's were supposed to be here
and have not actually arrived,
and since it is now 4-0-1,
we have not received the...
That is a problem that I didn't want to bring up,
but now it's here.
It's only because Bob has been able to, once again,
avert the invasion before they even got here.
Unless everybody's getting everything wrong.
The scales of the luck plane have, therefore,
been shifted in our direction one more time.
We have lucked out again, as it were.
So to speak.
Everyone should be alarmed and prepare for imminent disaster.
Wait, wait, wait.
We're not supposed to be relaxed and happy?
No, because we haven't yet crossed over that mysterious terminus.
That barrier.
Oh, there it is.
There's the barrier.
Oh, good lord.
What a sight, that.
It's only 16 inches high.
Look, it's just a model.
Wow.
Yeah, okay.
Not as bad as I thought.
So, there's the barrier.
And you're saying that X-MOMENT 705 has been achieved?
Yeah, and marching bands around the world break out their instruments.
Sharing that, once again, we have been spared.
Of course, some of us that have been praying for the day for years and years
have been waiting for the sex goddesses from the exorcist dimension.
Okay, I don't know any sex saucers over there.
I don't see the end of the world.
I'm looking to the east.
We're hiking up the side of Mount Shasta here.
It looks sort of like...
I can see off into the distance.
There's some kind of light off there on the horizon.
It's like a...
It could be dawn, though.
It could be an explosion.
It could be dawn.
The dogs down there?
You see them?
Well, the shock waves will take a little while to get to us, I guess.
Yes, uh...
Give me slack, you frickin' lunatic.
Fucker!
I'm out of frickin' slack!
Oh, the sad state of affairs this church has befallen, brothers and sisters.
Where are we going when even the faithful can come to the center of the spiritual universe,
stand amongst these sacred stones, and still be cast out from Bob's sacred midst?
We're being tested.
It's not only an insult that the exorcists did not come, but they shit on us!
Yeah.
But I heard Pope Black this morning...
They shit on us!
...when I heard him on that show on the BBC telling him,
Oh, are we a suicide cult?
That's what they asked him.
Are we a suicide cult?
I can only think of only one thing.
The only people who commit suicide in this cult are those who don't join this cult!
Yeah!
Hallelujah!
Praise God!
For $30, they could have avoided it all.
Just one person, perhaps it was just one person who didn't join, that stopped us from reaching
our sacred sales goals.
You know, that's the secret of all good salesmen.
You gotta have gold!
Yes!
Gold is here!
There are two!
It was not our money!
It was these two!
They drove us, drove the saucers away!
The subgenius coffers are short by $60!
Anyone who's seen Glen Gary, Glen Ross knows the sales business is a cutthroat business.
$60 short!
And we're doomed for nothing here.
That's $40 here.
The Exorcist saucers ran out of gas and needed $60 to fill up the tank of YouTube.
$60 worth of blame!
They're somewhere on Mars right now.
They're circling Mars right now going,
Can't find a filling station.
And yet I wonder how many other subgeniuses are listening to this very moment, thinking
in themselves, oh yeah, I'm a subgenius, oh yeah, I buy the book, I watch the Arise video,
but I never bought my $30 love offering!
Know what happened happened and couldn't have happened any other way.
How do you know?
We are still alive.
Sal doesn't think it happened.
I think it is X Day now.
Today is X Day.
I agree with you.
There is this problem once again.
I don't feel different.
Nothing quite happened.
Well, it's because it actually hasn't happened.
It's because, as usual, we have been saved once again.
Oh, is that how it works?
It's just kind of automatic?
That's how it works.
Like your bank account.
Just said in the book.
Just like Bob said.
If it doesn't happen, it's only because he's been able to save us once again.
That's all.
He was able to grab the edges of the ship.
Mostly from increased daytime.
We're going to go live to Bob's house right now.
Make the luck slide down straight into our direction.
And now we have the recipients of that device.
Here comes Connie.
Looking like, uh, like Mary Tyler Moore.
Little Bobby.
The new mechanical robot dog.
A book in his hand and a great burden upon his back.
I looked and saw the Bob.
In this plight, therefore, he went home and refrained himself as long as he could.
That his wife and children should not perceive his distress.
That he could not be silent long.
Because that his trouble increased.
Oh, my dear Bowles.
I, your dear friend, am in myself undone by Bowles.
Reason of a burden.
A burden.
A burden that lieth hard upon me.
Moral Bowles.
I am for certain informed that this our...
Papa Joe!
Ladies and gentlemen, Papa Joe Bow-Bow!
Ah, yes.
My subgenius brothers and sisters.
Welcome to X-Day 2002.
The final reckoning!
The servant tonight is a gentleman.
Titled, The Manipulation of Man.
Oh, it hurts!
It hurts!
Because you see, my friends, the conspiracy relies on certain formulas to enslave its underclass.
Cheap amongst them, of course...
...is the example of sex.
Yes, you see, sex, it used to be free.
If there's one thing that was obviously free at one time, it was sex.
Not only could we never have existed without it, but neither could any of the other creatures on this planet.
I want more sex!
But for some seemingly unknown reason, all of a sudden, sex has become one of the most expensive and commercialized conspiracy theories.
Commodities!
Oh!
How much do I know?
I guess $30!
Nowadays, if you want sex...
Woo!
Everybody!
...you have to beg.
Plead!
Jump through some sort of wedding ring.
And pay through the nose to get it!
No! I have my hand!
Oh, my God!
And when you do get it, friends, there's not only strings attached, there's chains!
AIDS!
Oh!
Of course, you might also die from AIDS or rot to death from some disease obtained in the process.
But hey, that's just the cost of doing business, right?
Wrong!
There was a time, dear friends, that sex was free and plentiful.
In pre-conspiracy times, if you wanted the joys of sex, you just took it!
You can't be sexist!
And if you're a partner,
they usually just grunted in gratitude.
No guilt, no obligations, no hassles!
Just wham, bam, thank you, madam!
But now!
But now, what has the conspiracy done, my friends?
They've got their claws stuck in that organ!
And the only free sex you get now is the advertising type you see on TV!
No!
That's not sex!
My friends, if that's the future of sex,
you can take your Viagra and shove it!
Yeah!
A new team!
But that's just a small example, my friends,
of how the conspiracy sells you that which was once your birthright.
The ultimate example, of course, is slack.
Yeah!
The great slack!
It used to be the most common,
the very most common possession of every man, woman, and child.
Then the conspiracy swooped down and snatched it away,
repackaging it,
into something that you had to buy,
and then trying to sell it back to you at a profit!
Now!
Now not only do you have to buy slack from the same bastards that stole it away from you in the first place,
you have to endure the absence of slack!
So if you want to, say, relax,
what do you have to do?
You have to suffer some sort of torture
to earn your right to buy back the slack!
I'm talking about a job!
No!
Oh!
But brothers and sisters,
it gets even better.
The conspiracy not only denies you natural slack,
in order to create themselves a, a market for their manufactured slack.
No Sir.
That's not good enough.
The conspiracy what they sell you in slack
isn't even real.
It's false slack!
No No No!
Contaminated slack substitute!
No! No! No!
No! No!
My friends, it doesn't even have any nourishment at all.
We in the church call this Nutra-Slack.
Because it may taste real, but after a while you realize it isn't, friends.
The only thing you get out of it is a headache.
You can buy truckloads of Nutra-Slack, my friends.
Consume it and you'll never feel satisfied.
You'll just feel the need to buy more.
Because it seems to you that that empty feeling is some sort of withdrawal system, but it ain't.
Alas, nothing could be farther from the truth, my friends.
The fact is that sick, queasy feeling you get at the pit of your stomach when you return to Monday morning,
that isn't the absence of conspiracy pseudo-Slack, my friends.
No, sir, it's your body's natural rejection to the slack-draining effects of anti-church air.
Give me a break, Bob!
Now, friends, some of you in the audience may not realize what anti-church air is.
It's my sad duty to inform you.
That's the badass gas they put in the air ducts, in the office buildings, in the workplaces.
It's a special gas that Mad Dr. Mingler put together for the Nazis in order to work against the Allies.
But, friends...
Give me his!
Well, compared to the conspiracy, Hitler was compassionate.
Because he only used it in wartime!
Adolf gave orders only to let it drift across enemy lines during an advance.
But here, friends, the conspiracy, they spray the stuff on the air filters of every office workplace on the planet.
These guys will stop at nothing to make you miserable.
They'll even breathe in themselves just to make sure nobody else escapes its terrible effects.
Friends, that's the worst kind...
The kind of a fanatic.
The kind that will endure unimaginable pain just to spite their enemy.
This!
This is the kind of creature we are dealing with!
No other animal on the planet, my friends, would harm itself to spite another.
Oh, sure, the wolf may gnaw off its arm in order to escape the trap.
But these sons of a bitches would rather take the entire world down with them screaming,
than let it go!
And a single subgenius remained free!
No!
Subgenius!
It's called the doomsday option, my friends.
And don't you think for a minute they won't press that button.
They're following that fucker right now, just waiting for proof that their time of power is at an end.
And friends, that day is today.
July 5th, 1998!
No!
Now I sense that there are a few disbelievers in our midst.
Some of you don't believe it's July 5th!
Some of you don't believe it's 1998!
Some of you don't believe in Bob!
Oh, the blasphemy!
The blasphemy!
But he's here, friends, and we can prove it.
Because just look at the way the conspiracy operates!
Like Slim Pickens and Dr. Strangelove, they'll not only detonate that doomsday device, they'll enjoy doing it!
Taking a power trip all the way down!
into that big explosion.
Now friends,
we've got sad news for Slim Pickens
and his conspiracy brothers.
Because the moment those bombs
start flashing, they're going to
discover their enemy
isn't here.
Bob Dobson and his faithful followers
will be whisked away to a
pleasure saucer and a pleasure world
and a whole new universe
that's filled full of slat.
A perfect planet. A perfect planet
A planet of pink where pinks
and normals don't even exist.
And best of all, friends,
the greatest gift will not be what this planet
has, but what this planet
does not have.
No more normalcy!
No more conspiracy!
Unabundance of slat!
Do I hear a praise ball?
Praise ball.
The best part, my friends,
is that when the conspiracy takes this planet
down screaming, we're going to
give them everything they thought they
wanted. The whole damn planet.
And they won't even have to share it.
Except maybe with a few trillion
radioactive roaches
that survived the detonations.
Terra firma.
Love it or leave it.
The subgeniuses have made their choice.
We paid our $30 for our saucer
reservations, my friends, and my
advice to the rest of you is don't wait
until the holocaust in order to poop or get
off the potty. Because seating and
availability are going fast.
Do yourself a favor,
friends. Get off! Get off
this planet! And take back that which
is rightfully yours. Free slats!
Take it back! Free slack!
Take it back! And most of all,
my friends, refuse the bogus
anti-slack
and all its peak manifestations.
And, lest
we forget, you must also
accept Bob Donalds!
Bob will break the chains of conspiracy
bondage and lead us from this
hellhole. Frith,
I'm sad to have to tell you this, but just
yesterday, you could ask Pope Black if this
didn't happen, some reporter had the
gall, the gall to come
up to us and say,
is the subgenius church
a suicide cult?
Fuck no! Yes!
Well, the answer, of course,
is yes!
But not the way they think, friends.
It's not suicide for the
subgenies. It's suicide
for those who refuse to join the
subgenies. Go get a baseball!
My friends,
some of you may be wondering
exactly if it wasn't 7 a.m.
1998. When is 7 a.m. 1998?
The fact of the matter is, you just
set your watch at 7 a.m. The moment
you see those pleasure saucers
landing, you click it in place.
It is 7 a.m. July 5th, 1998.
Don't you forget it!
If you're going to remember just one
thing here, friends, tonight, I want you to
leave here with one little saying on your
burn into your brain. And that
could probably be best epitomized
in the words of Mr. Miller,
who wrote a song about it called
The X's are coming
and the pinks are blooming.
So you go out there, brothers and sisters,
and you carry out the word of Bob.
Because the fact of the matter is,
if you ain't for him, you're
against him. And that ain't
a good place to be on X day.
I want you to raise your praise, Bob!
Raise Bob!
The other and other, gentle mars,
immortals loving, feline bars, daddy driving, fast cars,
bang, Reverend Ivan Stank, Jesus Christ
and Princess Wee, smoking for Robin, so do we,
Reverend Susie, such a floozy, Dr. Pissoff, St. N,
one more time, I know you can, innate Christian,
Reverend Geo, doctors getting right, right!
It's the end of the world
as we know it.
Bob feels fine.
What do you think happened there
16 minutes ago
that world ended at Brushwood?
Well, the shadow is heading this way.
I can see the destruction on the horizon.
It looks like a light, but it's really
explosions happening
simultaneously.
It's carpet bombing.
A hydrogen bomb carpet bombing.
Where they just lay on a whole layer
of fire.
I don't envy them out there.
Every three inches a new bomb.
In a sense, we are
just trying to blow that half of the world away.
And then we'll work on this half.
These days, women
because there's no collars out there.
All of the collars
in Northern California
are sleeping.
Or they're
sucking on their little pacifiers.
They're eating their pablum.
They're eating their little toy poodles.
They're having
lunch of
tuna salad.
They're all a bunch of
little slimy
slimy chickens.
Just a bunch of little
babies out there.
Hehehehe.
Yeah, if they were alive
they would call, but they're just a bunch of
chickens.
They're unsure of their balance.
Can you put out that one sound
that penetrates sleeping people's heads
and forces their eyes open?
Cut out.
Sex. Sex. Sex.
30. 30. Sex. Sex.
Pay $30 and get sick sex free.
Uh-huh.
Sure.
Now over here you can see the
lump heads and
other groups.
I'm not sure where we take the tour from.
Here. But, uh,
I'd like to thank all of you for
coming along with us this X-Day and
exploring the possibilities.
Maybe the ranting of
the small group of
so-called individual
Bob Jobs people.
What?
Alright, alright, alright.
With egg on our face and
blush on our cheeks,
we now leave here ruefully shaking our heads
to speak of how we
need to learn to live.
And now we're running downstairs.
Because when you get to the end of the world,
you want to run a lot.
You want to run ahead of the chaos.
You want to just sort of keep ahead of the madness.
Like outrunning a thunderstorm when you're a kid.
Here we go. Now keep on running.
And think to yourself,
there's no place like
Bob.
Knowing her fate,
Atlantis sent out ships to all corners of the Earth.
On board were the Twelve.
The poet,
the physician,
the farmer,
the scientist,
the magician,
and the other so-called gods of our legends.
But not Bob.
Though gods they were.
And as the elders of our time choose to remain blind,
let us rejoice and let us sing and dance.
And there was much rejoicing and singing at X-Day.
But we'll have to wait another year.
Hail Atlantis.
Hail the sex goddesses.
Because they did show up at X-Day.
A new day.
Yeah, we went over the rainbow.
Into the mitochondrial Yeti DNA Level C.
Well, we're gonna have to go north and south and east and west.
And we gotta wait another year.
Yeah, but we're gonna fill up a new pipe.
We're gonna wait for the sun to shine.
We're gonna turn around and take our time.
We're gonna break the seal to the other side.
You know, from the valley,
I hear the muffled cry
of all them poor sheeple.
That we left behind.
And we're gonna take that next evolutionary step.
Yeah, we're gonna climb on those rocket ships.
We're gonna build the vessels if we have to.
We're already testing the engines.
We're already testing the systems needed for this trip.
We're on the ride, yeah.
Mitochondrial Eve, thanks for the ride.
We'll take it from here.
She may be.
Okay, what do we need to do?
I mean, to be ready for the next step?
For the end of the world.
We're not, you know, we're not there the next day.
Shouldn't we do something in our own houses or something?
I think you should go out and live your life
just the way you've always wanted to live it.
From the next eight minutes.
Should I just, like, continue to, you know,
consume and spend money and take care of things like normal?
Yes, exactly.
Yeah, you should do that for another eight minutes.
And we can see the spaceship starting to hover in the sky.
I can see another hero above my house, too.
And the world has ended many times.
It did so at the end of the Permian period.
Yeah, well, it didn't actually, I mean, the world as a metaphor
for the description of present times may have ended.
Did Bob beat us at tic-tac-toe again?
Once again, he managed, we put our zeros up there.
He put his X's up there at random,
and yet his X's went right across the board.
And our zeros were all over the place.
Bob won again.
Oh, the dejected. Slunking away.
Slowly wander off.
Oh.
Slinking away, their tails tucked between their legs.
Shame, the Discordians laughing at us again.
The Christians saying things like,
you know, you're a little bit too old to be a Christian.
But see, Jesus gives you salvation for free.
Kill me now!
Or kill me right now.
Praise to you to be.
You exist in good faith.
Bless him, hell yeah!
Oh, it's a plane.
Oh.
Bob, damn it!
I'm pissed as hell!
And not because I'm not on those pleasure saucers,
but because these pigs and armors are still breathing air.
They're walking away in disgust.
Look at them.
Look at them wandering away.
Turning their backs on by.
They're not even afraid!
Bob and the Discordians laughing.
Boys and girls, it's time for you to pass a fire.
I was here in the middle of the summer.
I was just gonna be coming.
I'm dream of pleasure ships from high above on July 5th next year.
I don't know if I can answer both myself, because I'm not myself.
Subtap out and mute and pause.
Go to sleep,
and dream of flying high
on lullabies
and dreams that Bob has now
Sex goddesses and squid
Shall hide away
The smiling face of Bob
Will keep you safe till your second
By counting sheeples
Follow foals
To the hell
They build
Follow blob
Follow foal
Go to sleep
And dream of times when we
Will meet to sing
And praise the name of Bob
Sex goddesses and squids
Shall hide away
The smiling face of Bob
Will keep you safe till your second
Sex goddesses and squids
Shall hide away
The smiling face of Bob
Will keep you safe till next day
And stun that soir
Robin sneak just doomsday
07 0000 007 0000 0000 0000 0000
0000 0000 0000 0000 los o23 0000 0000
0000 0000 0000 0000 0zeorart 0V
0000 0000 0000 0000
0000 0000 0000 0000 in the Flo match
0000 0000 0000 0000 0000 in the Flo match
0000 0000 0000 0000 0000 0000 in the Flo match
0000 0000 0000 0000 in the Flo match
As we know it, I feel fine.
I feel fine.
I'm saying that's what we would encounter.
He's in pain.
He can't stand right here for a second.
He must kill himself to relieve himself of such problem.
This picture of the universe conforms to what we know.
Appropriateness seems to be the watchword for this sight.
Instinctively somehow, it looks and feels innately different.
Deathmonger from a hellish place of his own design.
A good dose of reality helps keep the psyche sane.
From a pain-encrusted forest, through a knife-wielding kill fest,
we came across a tragic remedy.
Through disemboweled plains of pleasure,
we could not make it to the sauce.
Apparently, Bob came and did something with all of us.
You have your answer.
Now go.
It slithers running away, it lookies even running away from me.
He's disassociating himself from this shameful, pathetic charm of a church!
Well, you could try the portal method.
You could visualize the portal opening and the dimensional UFO letting us onboard.
He slathers his O, but what's a B?
Two slashes, O, two slashes.
Da-da, O, da-da.
That's 3.
3 short, 3 long. 3 short.
That's S-O-S, but what's Bob?
B-O-B.
Two short, three long, two short.
Yeah, but what's Morris Code for a quotation mark?
Pope Black, Pope Phil Monty, Papa Joe Mama, Reverend Ed Fred, Reverend Mickey Finn,
and the other Euro subs heard there at X Day Europe 2002 at the Crop Circles of Aithbury,
taken there from Reverend Matthew Williams, excellent DVD of that show.
We heard, in and out, we heard Saint Anne and Helena Handbasket doing that song,
The End of the World As We Know It, R.E.M. being owed an explanation,
and Chaz Smith.
It was heard on ESO Swamp Radio from WCSB Cleveland years and many X Days ago.
And more than anything else, the Puzzling Evidence Show with Dr. Howell
and Dr. Philo Drummond on KPFA Berkeley on X Day 02.
Friends, also, we heard lots of little warped-out fiddly bits and collages
by the great Fernanda Nandili-Murr and the great Reverend Jartow.
The whole show is tossed by yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang, Sacred Scribe, Church
of the Subgenius, and this is my last show before X Day 2003.
This is Hour of Slack number 896.
We're at www.subgenius.com.
See you on the saucers.