Stay tuned for the Hour of Slack.
And this is your announcer, Reverend Ivan Stang.
And this is your show.
Hideous. Wonderful. Show.
The Soap Genius Hour of Slack.
Abandon all hope, he who enter here.
Ah, can you give me a sentence with the word isthmus in it?
Ahem.
Isthmus be my lucky day.
Welcome to the night, Tizzy.
Ah, yes, dear friends, it's a pretty modernistic show tonight.
We've been doing all these very linear and thematic shows lately.
But tonight we're going back to the basics, the old sad stuff.
Ah.
The.
All new old sad stuff from the Church of the Soap Genius.
Because this is the surreal Hour of Slack.
This time we're illustrating the decay of civilization as you know it.
And, uh, of course it's not going to make much sense, but in that respect it's probably more real.
In fact, some things will be too real for the polished ears of the modernists.
We have the intention to work.
Yeah, we're going to work.
So, uh, stand by for alive and, uh, un-uh, undead material from Doctors for Bob and the Swingin' Love Thorses, dear friends.
It's intended to be taken as a way of life.
We ourselves wish to work.
We must ask ourselves whether this document represents for us a way of life.
It certainly does for me.
A way of life.
It's brilliant.
It's very brilliant.
It's very hump you feel for the fact that this world has, you know, moments stood there.
We would appreciate when you'd call me and ask if you can bring some information for this documentary.
Recommended US 때문에 wei niğıc,
Should come back.
so I think that that's, uh, uh, one of the many things that was coming to my attention
Right here to the site, isn't it?
What was that place, though?
Yeah, it was the military base.
sex, the divine battle, but is there an unbridgeable, undestroyable barrier between men and women
that will keep them forever warring against each other?
Sure there is.
And if you don't believe it, you'll see it.
I think so.
This is Dad's new slacks.
It's 11 o'clock right now.
Right now.
We're having a great time tonight, aren't we, Dad?
So what are we still standing around here for?
Where do you want to go?
Well, how about out of here for starters?
I've got to get my wife and my kids.
We're still on alert, Billy.
I just want to go out and dig Wanda up out of the damn freezer.
You just get a meat hook.
You hear me?
You got me by the ankle.
I'm a horny.
I need her down.
She's frozen or dead or thawed out.
I need dinner.
I need supper.
Thaw her ass out.
Thaw her bitch out.
Have her in the microwave and get her.
I'm a horny.
Heat her up.
I'm ready.
See, I ain't got time for any foreplay.
I'm going to make some sex.
Make some dance.
Don't pull out in front of that car.
That could be Wanda in that car.
Well, tell her.
Put her in the car.
I need someone to drive me up to the Piggly Wiggly to get some cigarettes.
I don't care if she's dead.
Take her up to the Piggly damn Wiggly.
The Wiggly damn Piggly.
Don't bring that curved pig in there.
Get that curved pig out of there.
If you're going to use a curved pig, use a curved pig holder.
Don't put a damn curved pig in a straight pig holder.
They don't know how to use a damn thing.
They don't know a damn thing about a curved pig.
I'm going to bring a straight pig out there.
I'm going to see that bitch in a freezer bag next week.
I'm going to be in next door.
I brought this weapon.
I put my heel under her arm with an ice pick in the freezer.
She'd be cut up with a chainsaw.
Oh, well, yeah.
I just take.
You know when a girl's got nubs.
Hell, I wouldn't kick her out of bed for bleeding to death.
I wouldn't kick her out of bed for eating flesh.
I wouldn't kick her out of bed.
Hell, she can eat frozen corpse crackers in my bed anytime.
Hell, yeah.
She's a good looking heifer.
I like her.
And I want her.
I want her.
I want her now.
And her name's Wanda.
Get that cow out of there.
I ain't talking to you Wanda.
I'm talking Wanda.
Yeah, Wanda.
Get her out of the.
Wanda.
I know I sent her that rocket ship up into the sun.
But get her out.
I'm warning you.
Hell, I.
She had nothing to get her hot.
So I just threw her in the fireplace.
Hell, she didn't even get her chain.
Maybe she'd get off on that.
Get off to.
Toll the judge or shock the little geese out of me when I went to her doctor's prom concert
at the Slice House the other night.
Listen to my tale then.
But why will you call me mad?
Could a madman have written songs such as these?
I'm not insane.
I'm more sane than Charles Manson.
Son of Sam both put together.
All I want is life, liberty, and the pursuit of happiness.
And my pursuit of happiness includes machine gunning 120 innocent schoolchildren.
If that's mad, go ahead and lock me up.
Just because I enjoy washing my face in the blood of infants.
Is that mad?
Is that a reason to lock me up?
But hell, that wasn't nearly as bad as that time they, that time they, that time they
shocked the living gey out of me.
So, they let me tie the
bandplate in my head, and in my head everything just, justlocks risky looking hy Lei.
So then I create another.
Every city in right there always says it sounds like Sai Hanoi.
You know I was just calling.
You know I should have said it first.
All of a sudden, I'm a Losing Sense.
Come out and beat that pretty bitch or she got me.
And now being here, I can't help that.
Oh, that was fun.
That time I had to play chicken with Jones,
and I didn't have a car, and he had a Mack truck,
and the bridge collapsed,
and we had ground zero of a nuclear explosion.
Oh, yeah, that was fun.
That was a good old, good time compared to that time they...
that time they...
shot the living GEE out of me.
¶¶
Well, hell, that was...
Remember that time they had me...
they had to throw me on that needle that was so large
they had to lower me onto it by helicopter.
And even that wasn't enough to anesthetize me.
¶¶
Remember, they chained me down with rope,
they tied me down with chains.
They put me in that room where you don't get any of the good pills.
¶¶
Remember that time they cut my genitals in half with barbed wire
and then peeled a Band-Aid off my amputated arm.
¶¶
Oh, yeah, that was fun.
That was a big old party.
Yeah, that was fun compared to that time they...
that time they...
that one damn time they...
shot the living GEE out of me.
¶¶
Abandon all hope, ye who enter here.
Now what's so funny, huh?
Well, that was what you've heard there was
Jane or Hyperclete's Not With Doctors for Bob
with some band in Seattle
that happened to learn the songs quick enough
to actually do it.
There's a verse.
There's a version of Half-Assed Drunk coming up here
which you will definitely want to catch
because it's the most apropos performance, really,
of that song.
Also, you heard Jane or Hyperclete's
and Sterno Kekever ranting there,
lecturing about Wanda in a freezer bag.
Now, some of you may take that as sexist,
sadistic, absolutely abhorrent
and absolutely abhorrent.
Absolutely of no socially redeeming value whatsoever.
But that's because you're too dense to get it.
See, this is reverse Bulldada.
You know Bulldada.
You know what Bulldada means.
It's like the Bulldada of the latest exploration
of advanced surrealistic morealism
in which the mind is filled with dirt and lugs
which trickle like mutilated centipedes
down the sides of the cranium
to find shelter and rest inside the now sightless eye sockets.
And, you know,
it's pretty much a household, you know,
given common knowledge now, household word.
So, uh, uh, what?
Oh, we're getting police banned here.
Wow.
X.
Jeez, this is awful, Dad.
Claude's loaded on dope and he's killing people.
Tell it to the X-mas bunny, kid.
We, uh, friends, we have tuned in
to some, uh, pirate broadcast here
or somehow we're being interrupted.
Our signal is being interrupted.
Our police, man.
The other two head arms, uh,
and, uh, one cute little pussycat.
One dog food zip nine.
Come in.
Woof, woof.
Good news, boy.
Clong wasted the pussycat.
We need two minutes, then.
Jump in those...
You're sitting in a puddle of excitement, aren't you?
But he's dry.
He squeals fast up police street to the terminal bar
because he needs another shot
because the street is tough and dirty.
Not like at home,
where everything he fears
stands ankle-deep in tears and detergents.
Oh, I'm just having a good time, people.
We're out to clean the thighs.
Uh, dear, where's the dead cat?
Uh, it's in the soap dish.
Uh, but there's soap in the soap dish.
Yeah.
Uh, the cat's in the soap.
What?
Yes, dear.
There's a whole dead cat
in every bar of dead cat soap.
Ah!
Oh, no!
Over the Edge.
The story of Peggy
and what a woman feels
when she must find out for herself
the things her husband does not know
and face the fact
that life must go on
even over the edge.
Woo!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
Your tongue offended me.
Rip it out!
Ow!
I love you.
Is that before or after the bob pills?
Everybody who goes to hell
comes back a millionaire.
Honey!
Don't tell me you haven't heard about Pepto-Visimol.
My dear, it might take about ten months.
Hospital tests prove it.
Oh!
Besides being a lecherous drunk
and just possibly one of the most evil criminal minds
of the entire worldwide conspiracy,
he looks like Gomez Adams without a mustache.
Is he the better tobacco?
That's all.
The new drug of the century.
No, Bob is not smoking tobacco.
Contraband.
That's right.
You have to get a prescription now
to smoke tobacco
and go down to your pharmacist
and say,
I'd like a half ounce of tobacco.
But Bob is smoking
the meriphase of lupina,
have a prop zipilops,
the Tibetan herb.
Stay tuned in next week
for the scientific explanation
and explorations
into the bowels of that plant.
This is Diane,
and it's the last interview of the semester.
Yay!
And we have in the studio,
yeah, the best for last, right,
we have a band in the studio
that I know nothing about,
so this should be incredibly interesting.
It's the Swinging Love Corpses,
and if nothing else,
they have a great name.
So, um,
why don't we start
with some introductions?
Everybody, introduce yourselves.
Well, I'm Philo Drummond.
I play saxophone.
My name's Leif Calabanga,
and I play saxophone.
I'm Dr. Ray Hay,
and I own the Swinging Love Corpses,
but don't worry,
I only use them on the weekend,
so we're safe.
I'm Sphinx Drummond,
and I play trumpet,
and sing lead vocals,
and play saxophone and guitars.
Well, actually, there's one main member
who is Mojo Skippy Butcher,
and he's our drummer.
But he has...
He's playing a bar mitzvah right now.
He's got a bar mitzvah to play.
Oh, too exciting.
Somebody offered him, like,
$10 million to play it,
so he couldn't turn it down.
Let's talk, and maybe you guys can give us
somewhat of a description of your music.
It says here in this book that you just gave me
that the only...
Only mystery jazz acid surfer music
to be created a thousand miles
from the nearest ocean.
Well, that was the genre
we were into a few years ago,
or about a year and a half
when the book came out.
We've gone through several genres
since then, like mystery jazz.
We invent them,
and then we exploit them
to the fullest, and then we throw them away
and come up with a new one.
That was when we were in our surf phase.
We had been the leaders
of the Pioneer,
and the leaders in the Midcoast Surfing Association here.
We popularized the concept of...
Barge wake surfing.
You know, you can catch a barge wake
and go all the way down to New Orleans.
To New Orleans, really?
Right.
And on a regular surfboard, this is?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, regulation.
If you go too fast,
you can always flare your skinner,
so it's no problem.
Oh, that's really good.
I've never tried that on the Mississippi, but...
You can hang 11 right over a sandbar.
Yeah.
It's a beautiful thing.
A sandbar, right.
That chick's gonna have 12.
Yeah, that's right.
But we...
Yeah, that was...
We've kind of passed through that phase now.
We're more into goofrock.
Now we're into goofrock.
Goofrock?
Well, how long have you been together?
I mean...
Well, these two have been together since birth.
We were...
Yeah.
We were Siamese twins originally.
He and I are brothers.
And he's a cousin,
separated at the third nostril.
He was a cousin,
and he's like a step-neighbor-in-law,
is what he is.
How do you become a step-neighbor-in-law?
Step-neighbor-in-law, exactly.
In our neighborhood,
it's a real painful...
It was real easy to do.
It's a real painful process.
It requires, like, these...
Most of the kids have...
Bamboo shoots up the nostrils,
but you smooth it up.
You have to have your glands altered.
Your glands altered?
Oh, that sounds kind of a...
Glandscaping.
Do you go to, like, a normal hospital
for this procedure, or...
No, you go down an aft into that...
Aft into...
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Glandscaping place down there.
I am originally from...
I'm from Afton, so, uh,
no Afton remarks.
We used to be proud, actually.
It's one of the few glandscaping offices
in the city.
In the whole Midwest.
Oh, really?
You can't just go anywhere.
The only other place you can go is in Tibet.
You have to go to Tibet,
is the nearest...
Well, it was an art of the home office.
Tibet or Afton?
Tibet or Afton.
You don't really have much of a choice.
Well, that location burned down.
They had, like, some anti-third nostril openers
that were protesting out front,
and they burnt down the, uh...
I understand Carter went down
to make sure that...
I'm sure the anti-third nostril election
was straight up and up this week.
Yeah, but nobody really cared.
And actually, that interviewer
did not get around to playing
the music of that rather interesting band,
the Swinging Love Corpses.
So, here.
Yeah, it's about time we saved the universe.
We hadn't done it in at least a week or two.
It's a tough job being as important as we are.
A lot of people don't realize that
rock bands have...
They have greater callings in life
than just playing music.
You know, a lot of times
we have important things to do.
Really important things, you know,
like maintaining the balance
between the negative energies
and the positive energies, you know?
Like, yeah, the what?
What about the groupies?
Yeah, the groupies.
We have the groupies to worry about, too, you know?
Are we ready?
Yeah!
It's free determined, and this is our fate.
We're singing this song, so you can relate.
We are going to save the universe.
This time.
We are all grown.
We are grown as men.
We are all past.
The age of reasoning.
It's our mission.
It's our task.
It's all for us.
Just you.
We are going to save the universe.
This time.
Don't you worry.
Don't have no fears.
Don't gather room.
Because the end is near.
It's never season of someone.
They know what they are.
We are more than a band
We are in control
And we are more than a band
We are going the same way you've ever
Yes, dear friends
Well, now I'm sorry
I understand why they wanted me to do a new pledge drive reminder card
In the meantime, listen to that
Oh, it's beautiful piece of music there
This is...
This is from some old 78 record
From China, Between the Wars
Called China Night
Sounds like the theme to Seven Faces of Dr. Lo
稕 immun kiyoru
宜 candor
Raime Mitsuyoshi
Chiakun
Beowik
ты
scoop
hot
Not for a second.
I'm an E-Rotator.
Different failure.
Successful.
I'm an E-Rotator.
Dumb body, Mitch Campbell.
Took Miss Mousy on his knee.
Pray Miss Mousy won't you marry me.
Dumb body, Mitch Campbell.
Really does.
I'm an E-Rotator.
Okay, well I just wanted to get shots of you doing the show at some point.
Oops, do I clean that up?
Say we got a good solid quarter of an hour before we have to put up with any of that stuff.
Yeah, that's what they say out there in the cold Berkeley morning.
In the formless darkness of the morning.
Okay, now we're working on the Berkeley morning now.
We're chopping it up and adding with it some of the other things.
I'm a reporter for the Berkeley morning.
Aaron, 848-484-425 in the Berkeley morning.
Individual.
You did nothing.
What can I do?
What can you do?
No, what can I do?
You can do nothing.
What can you do?
What should I do?
You shall do nothing.
What will I do?
You will do nothing.
What will?
What can I?
How are you?
Oh, no.
Watch out.
Oh, no, don't do that.
Don't do that.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, okay.
Ah!
Ah, that's, uh, our dear friends there at this KPFA in Berkeley,
which is where that last little bit came from.
Dear friends.
And, uh, funny how these, uh, funny how these knobs,
these knobs in front of me,
do you know any girls with knobs that work?
No.
Everybody wants to get into the act.
And we'll just slow down and we can have Aeohippus lovechild tell you about what kind of prehistoric
animal you were in the first place.
You know.
But no, you're too busy gibbering and squeaking in the blackness of the void.
I'm sorry for you.
I think...
Yes, I pity you.
I think he has the vibes of a trilobite.
Ah, stuck in a little rock, all curled up, looking like a little, uh, well, kind of...
It used to be called a trio trilobite.
Come out of your shell.
But not no more.
Now called color here at 848-4425.
A pathetic little limulus.
A horseshoe crab.
They used to pitch at quaits.
At Quait Tower a million years ago.
And now we're, uh, pitching those horseshoe crabs.
Yes, but the angle of the pitch is...
Impaling them on, uh...
Something different.
The steel spike that would normally be used to hook normal...
Uh, Steven's steel spike, uh, stuck through the head of the old, uh, trio trilobite.
Yeah, right.
Leave a message, cause, uh...
Hello, you're on the air.
The Bengals will win.
Yes.
Tigers for...
Ikki, ikki, stomp.
Ikki, woody.
Leavers eviscerate pumas.
Iron squash elephants.
Hey, I can't show you the best of your horse.
Okay, now, if I was running around the antenna faster and faster...
And when I get to a certain speed, he'll disappear.
Uh, I'm telling you that, Ikki.
You're in trouble now.
Okay, here comes...
You're in a heap of trouble, Bob.
Okay, get ready, caller.
It's... it's not our fault.
It's because of Doctors for Bob.
Uh, which follows...
At least, uh, the Jane or Hyperclete's part of Doctors for Bob follows.
With, uh, jokes you're too stupid to understand.
Followed by jokes...
You're too solid to understand.
Followed, finally, by, uh,
Jane-er's ultimate statement about heavy metal rock.
Uh, tokin', smokin', cokin'.
Thank you.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
Doctors for Bob proudly present...
Jokes You're Too Stupid to Understand.
Part 2.
There was a young mathematics pr- student.
I believe he was Polish in descent, if not in origin.
He was assigned the following linear equation.
E times the square root of...
times dx over the cube root of y times p.
He first traced the x-intercept and y-intercept of the equation,
and then took the complex root of each factor.
After this, he, of course, multiplied by the vector quantity
of each infinite geometric sequence.
However, he put his studies away in order to attend Stravinsky's Rites of Spring.
He returned to resume working on the equation.
His spirit was, however, quite a f-
flame after seeing such a work,
and he made the following mistake- mistakes.
First off, he consulted a non-Euclidean rather than a Euclidean logarithm table.
He then computed the sine rather than the cosine of the formula.
And then, while figuring the general bi- nor- binomial expansion,
he accidentally multiplied by...
a positive rather than a negative integer.
If you...
While contemplating a young female who sat opposite him in class,
he incorrectly figured the area between two curves,
his mind being more interested in the young lady's curves
than the curves on the mathematical chart which he was consulting.
I guess it was what you might call a case of degenerative conics,
extremely genera- degenerative conics in this case.
I believe he was contemplating her triangle rather than Pascal's
when he calculated the infinite geometric sequence between his heat flux,
because his heat flux was a bit higher than it should have been.
His final answer?
Why, it was thirteen, of course.
Of course, anyone with a fragment of a frontal lobe remaining
knows the correct answer is fifty-seven.
Did I say something wrong?
You have been listening to Dr. Sir Bob's
Jokes You're Too Stupid to Understand, Part Two.
Be here next time when we begin a thirteen-week course
entitled Jokes You're Way Too Stupid to Understand.
Anyone understanding the entire course
and is able to produce genuine laughter in the correct places
is eligible for a bachelor's degree in the field of his or her choice.
A polygraph will be used to separate real laughter from laughter which is phony.
Good evening.
Good evening, and now we present Dr. Bob's Jokes
Which You're Too Solid to Understand.
Jokes You're Too Stupid to Understand
Dr. Bob F.
A film by
By
Jesse
Dr. Bob F.
Doc
lez
Hear
R further
cuts
The
brutal
guitar solo
solo
försö vol window
just
You take three hits and you just find yourself in another dimension.
You take four hits and you'll just be screaming,
Oh, God, please let me come down.
Oh, come on, it couldn't be that strong.
Smoking, eating in the back, and it keeps on talking.
Smoking, smoking, smoking, smoking.
Eating in the back, and it keeps on talking.
Smoking, smoking, smoking, smoking, smoking.
Talking, talking, smoking, talking.
Talking, smoking, talking.
Morning, morning, and something's all wrong.
I lost my job and I can't find a ball.
I've been trying that and I can't get laid.
I finally did collapse and I can't get paid.
I finally decided to commit suicide.
I put a razor on my arm and I let it slide.
I finally got up to the front of the gates.
But I told Link, Peter, Matthew,
I have to wait,
because
I'll
be
cold.
Smoking, eating in the back, and it keeps on talking.
Smoking, smoking, eating in the back, and it keeps on talking.
Smoking, smoking, smoking, smoking.
Smoking, smoking, smoking on.
Talking, smoking, talking.
Talking, talking, talking.
Talking, talking, fucking.
Welcome to M Levitt Channel,
where howONGI'm적 Gillian
and I'mGीdevium.
our segocon Isaac
for this wouldn't of ci Sheng
you got the shhtل
Thank you.
¶¶
Oh wow man, Jane or Hypercleet's in Generation of Degenerates.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Skol, let's go get some skol.
Hell yeah.
She said gas pig.
Hell, I can't stand for a solid pig or a liquid pig.
I just want a gas pig.
That's all I need is a damn gas pig.
I got $300 if you can get him a damn freezer bag full of Wanda.
A freezer bag full of Wandas?
You can get over here now.
Gas Wandas.
You can't get it at the Piggly Wiggly or the Food Fest anymore.
Oh, you can't buy a pig freezer bag.
They like to sell them.
Or you can get pig teeth.
I remember Joe Taylor said that one night he had a damn 55 shanty with his pig teeth.
Whole bag full of pig teeth.
And then a pig tooth stop sign.
His damn stop sign made out of pig teeth and pig tickets.
Yeah, he didn't know he was supposed to go to a screeching mall when he saw it.
And then 11 pill pig ticket farmers.
He thought it was the cow vertebrae cut out by them air warden stop signs that he was supposed to stop at.
Oh, do you see those cow vertebrae trees with the 14 toes?
You can't arrest me, officer.
I am not drunk.
I might be half-ass drunk, though.
Half-ass drunk.
Hell, you know you are.
When you got a hangover and it's all hung over backseat of your girlfriend's car.
Half-ass drunk.
And I'm feeling blue.
Well, a flood come then and it washed away my den and my water bill's still past due.
Half-ass drunk.
Just you and me.
Sergeant Carter haircut, gomorrah mile hookup, living off a LSD.
Half-ass drunk.
I ain't feeling quite right.
Well, it can't be Monday cause I don't remember Sunday.
My head's a-singin' Saturday night.
Sweet love songs.
Half-ass drunk.
You know my head feels odd.
Well, baby needs food but his daddy needs a lude.
Well, the baby better find himself a job.
Half-ass drunk.
Hell, I'm drunk as .
Well, I used to have a job but I'm sick of getting robbed so I finally just up and quit.
Mama had a fit.
How bad was that of a movie title?
Wasn't an office job?
Man's mai-con in his fortin'兵.
Well, they ain't westin' like me.
Half-ass drunk.
Hard to get some rest.
Well, that's my policy accolade.
Well, they said the light was red.
Now, a couple of folks, well, there were 22 injured.
And, well, there was one guy that was gimped up pretty good.
He kind of had to walk like this for the rest of his life.
And, well, he had multiple fractures.
And, well, they, like, had a tube running up through his nose.
I think that was the only way he could breathe.
And, well, there was this one fellow.
It was kind of weird.
They found pieces of the same guy on the front and the back of the same car.
I don't really even understand how that could happen.
They ought to run some kind of scientific test or something.
I don't know.
And a couple of folks did.
Sure looked green to me.
Have a strong.
I'm a victim of lies.
There's nothing wrong with me, Your Honor.
I can see.
Hell, I got two damn DWIs.
Have a strong.
Oh, woe is me.
I finally found a job.
Now I'm looking for a blowjob.
Wonder if the warden can see.
Well, they don't really pay.
But it's steady every day.
Breaking rocks till they're broke as me.
Have a strong.
Close your eyes and I'll kiss you.
Tomorrow I'll miss you.
Remember, I'll always be true.
And by the way, I'll hug you deep.
And I'll send.
All my lovin' to you.
They called it the Reagan Revolution.
Now, I'll accept that.
But for me, it always seemed more like the great rediscovery.
A rediscovery of our values and our common sense.
Common sense told us that when you put a big tax on it,
the economy bloomed like a plant that it could cut back
and could now grow quicker and stronger.
Our economic program brought about the longest peacetime experience.
And we're still the first nation in our history.
Real family income up.
The poverty rate down.
Entrepreneurship booming.
Ground.
Explosion in research and new technology.
We're exporting more now than ever because American industry became more competitive.
And at the same time,
someone has actually begun to reduce their stockpiles of nuclear weapons.
You made me suffer in this song.
And on Jesus' birth,
and on Jesus' birthday.
What do you think, Dad?
And on Jesus' birthday.
Yes, friends, it's a pretty interesting hour of Slack, don't you think?
Here we have this religious radio broadcast.
We haven't said one word about our guru, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Haven't said anything about Slack or any other...
Oh, there they go.
Ow!
Well, I guess we have something to say about Slack.
Oh, man.
Ah.
I don't know about you, but I've been having a fun time with this show.
Because I'm sick of Bob.
I'm gonna kill Bob.
If I see him coming down the street, I'm gonna kill him, man.
I'm gonna kill him.
It's like a bunch of boogers.
You tell me how you gonna do it.
It's only five foot three.
We went out there in the cave and there's that big thing that weighs a hundred pounds.
I said, what is these boogers doing there?
They're supposed to be in Jones's nose.
Last time I saw those boogers they were in Jones's nose.
Now here they are in a cave fixing to drop off.
Well, there was bats up there.
They had the bat shit.
They had the purple devil electric batty guana pig toes pig tooth telephone pole tree and
bitch and bat snot fixing to drop off the edge of that cave.
But it's like a cyclopean eye of Odin.
That's what I told Smith that time.
He told me about that.
He rolled that eye out there with the soda pop bottle.
And I said, it's like a cyclopean eye of Odin.
He tried to say I wasn't.
Just a bunch of damn.
I said, what the hell do you mean by that, son?
I was sitting in here trying to, just trying to drink a beer with my woman with my mattress.
He tried to tell me that he thought that he was going to drop a cigarette butt down there.
And I said, well, you ain't going to drop that cigarette, but you ain't going to throw
that damn cigarette butt at me.
Just because you put it in the ashtray.
I know you were trying to throw it inside my eye and blind me.
I know.
I was sitting in here looking.
I was trying to pack up my woman's ass.
I couldn't ask him.
I was looking for a date with him.
So he tried to put my eye out with that, by putting that cigarette in that ashtray.
That's why I had to beat his ass.
I seen it too.
I saw him.
I saw him over there order a beer.
That's because he wanted to throw that beer in my face.
I don't care if it ended up in his stomach.
That's because he's a lousy aim.
I know he wanted to throw that beer in my face.
That's why I had to kick his ass.
We don't care.
Bob eats oak trees for breakfast.
Wait a minute.
Bob grinds up damn light bulbs in his nose and snorts them up and packed.
And Smith hangs up his damn ass.
Why is that bird trying to whistle at my girlfriend?
I'm going to have to kick Jones' ass because of that.
Why is that car signaling?
Is he trying to wink at my girl?
I'm just going to head on with him.
I'm going to play some chicken with a cop car.
I ain't even got a car.
I'm just going to play chicken with my body.
Hell, they can't stop their cowards.
They don't kill me.
They're chicken.
That's the way it is.
Wait a minute.
Stop.
No.
Hold it.
Quit it.
Stop.
No.
Quit talking.
Quit playing.
No exit at all.
Don't be quiet.
Quiet.
We must have silence.
If anyone talks, it'll be ruining the whole thing, man.
We can blow one damn sound vibration.
We can blow up the whole world.
Stop screaming.
Everyone hold it.
Stop it.
Stop ranting.
Turn it off.
Turn me off.
Pull my plug.
We pull this plug, the Janer device down, sterno device down.
I've got this.
Uh.
Tune here.
This is a perfect thing to lead into the next show, which is normal music or just the
right kind of abnormal music, I guess you might say.
But this here is, we got a collection of Japanese and Chinese 78s transferred to tape by Dan
Meyer of the Institute of Scientific Santa Clausism.
This is the Japanese version of Tennessee warts after the occupation.
I think that anyone who doesn't have their tape recorder running now should turn it on
record.
This is a very important piece.
You'll probably never hear it again.
Tennessee warts.
Yeah.
Well, it was, um, Kit Smith and I once lived in t
uni bill, my dad went to college and sent their types in that box.
So I just came to Mahgjustwari with lots of sekhtob and, you know, so just, I met good
pickup there, but I was st azt doubt me.
So I adaptal much to Tennessee with what I know.
To my loved one
And for me
Oh, Wilson
My friends
To my sweetheart
From me
Sari Nishi
Yume
Anote
Sea world
Natsukashi
I know
That I am
No matter what
But I'll always be
Here to say
To my sweetheart
Oh, Wilson
Sari Nishi
Yume
Natsukashi
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
system. I was playing God in the game the last time we did it.
You got murdered too, didn't you? No, they didn't
quite get away with it, but that was something I hadn't foreseen. But a bunch of them
started conspiring to murder God. And that's the kind of game it is.
Almost anything can happen.
Well, we know how the period begins.
We know that in order to operate the brain, coffee is
while Colombia is second to neighboring
Brazil in sheer coffee volume, producing
oceans and rivers of steaming coffee. It surpasses Brazil
in producing premium Arabica beans. In fact, Colombia
grows only quality Arabica. Only two
billion coffee trees harvested year-round. That's a lot
of good coffee. Gurgling down the throats of America.
We find a creature, yes, a living
actual bug of the
northern Ohio swamp area. It's called the Dobson fly.
Dobson fly? The Dobson fly, which is, you can go
see a stuffed, mounted example of this hideous, vicious
beast in the Cleveland Natural History Museum. The Dobson
fly, while surrounded by lovely
butterflies and not-too-alien-looking dragonflies, you'll
notice that the Dobson fly has the head of a
vicious red ant.
With tedious, clicking mandibles, and the body, a body that
resembles the tail of a rattlesnake.
Horrible, flapping, leathery wings. Yes, the Dobson fly.
This is not some biological freak that we're making up. I'm
afraid there are thousands of Dobson fly larvae. Now, they are
in their season, their 50-year season.
A devolution life.
It was in the 40s.
In the 1940s was the last time the Dobson fly cycle reached its peak.
And thousands died as these pincher-like beaks of billions of dark Dobson flies attacked
the suburbs of Cleveland.
Oh, the days of Velikovsky. I thought it was Wassily Kamilovsky.
And every time you swatted a Dobson fly, a million eggs would fly.
And the eggs would squirt out of its ruptured abdomen.
Each egg hatching into another million Dobson flies.
And each time you tried to squash one of those, it would hatch another million.
A devolution has no plan.
You see, friends, man likes to think himself the grandest thing in all of God's great creation.
But indeed, no, it is the great order of the insectoride.
The great brain of all collective insect hives and tribes is a billion times smarter than
any single ego-centered human brain.
Certainly, one Dobson fly or one tick may possess a rudimentary brain, but they can
communicate by radio with each other.
And the millions of each species each forms a great brain of that species.
And those brains get together to form brains.
And let's face it, you're outsmarted, Mr. Earth Boy, Mr. Human, Mr. Two-Legged, Mr. Tool-Using Primate.
You, you, a little bit higher up on the pyramid.
That's right. If you can, once you've signed up, if you bring in five more friends,
Let's climb the ladder!
you'll climb the ladder.
The ladder of the web.
Until you're sitting right under the abdomen of the great spider herself.
Friends, information, information, information, friends.
It's not like we're adding poisons or evil preservatives or anything.
No, no, we're just filling you up with knowledge.
Information, information, information.
No, no, we just want you to have fun.
We want you to join with us in the brotherhood, in the sisterhood.
Under the web, the great spider protects us.
Yes, she protects us. She nurses us.
We may nurse at the teat, at the information teat of the great spider, of the sticky, sticky web.
All we think is yes.
We need to find something.
Look at Chaz.
He's got a giant organ of his with a wax mask on his face.
Princess Wee is sneaking up behind him.
She's tiptoeing up behind Chaz.
She's reaching out to lift the mask from his face.
She's going to do it.
She's grabbed the mask.
He turned around.
His hideous, hideous face.
Now he'sícios up.
He's diagonally pointing in the getaway.
I know that.