To turn on the machine, this is Radio Yerevan, my name is Hans Ivanovich Hagen, and this
is the news.
Wake up, puppet boy!
This is Doug Smith, radio operator, I'm going to bring you a piece of that green cheese
for sure.
I am Buck Nugget!
Welcome, dear friends, to the subgenius hour of slush!
Slush!
Yeah!
What?
The message is now part of and registered in your subconscious mind every time you say,
see, hear, or think.
Yeah!
what's your key phrase it will trigger the entire message without you being aware of it
repent quit your job driven to the brink of false sanity by the conspiracy's false reality
and the pressure of a crumbling world then this may be for you
uh yes dear friends as we listen to oh dr onan cannabites music and praise bob
the pastor buck neck it is here we got a full show
go ahead buck try to spit it out
he's trying to say it
girl
he's trying
come on buck spit it out he's trying to buck is trying to say his trademark theme he's been having
he's been having girl troubles lately though and he
it's high get the eye yeah poor buck
oh friends welcome to the hour of slack we've got some nasty nasty preaching and some
horrible rock and roll
you know it's going to be hard to follow that last show that was an incredible
perfect k-n-o-n show and i hope you understand that you're not going to get that kind of thing
on most stations wait a minute it's showtime time for the subgenius hour and a half the show that
dare not even exist join us now as we rocket away out of normal time into showtime with your
favorite horrifying horror host mobius rex and you'll hear the voices of puzzling evidence
while you're watching this podcast it's very often we try to get asmarket of people's
in the become honest and to a whole not that we attach a math and a home is an
for link within the reference reviews for we fill we have live online coverage in the
and the mind's grip on what it knows is at its weakest.
The dead hours of the morning between 4.30 and 6 o'clock.
This is the time when ancient superstitions and night fears
have the greatest hold on human thoughts.
The time when those who sleep are deep in their dreams.
And this is the hour when on the church of the subgenius radio show
the doctors of the air operate without warning.
We inhabit a twilight world, a world which feels the rising sun.
Long after nightfall, when the witching hour has been dead for three and a half hours,
we rise from our coffins and go forth to stalk our living victims.
You, our beloved audience, good hunting brothers, help!
This is Dr. Howell, wailing in the night,
for that which lived, which is dead, and for that which is dead, was dead, and in fact was never alive.
So we're lonely.
And now for all you early morning listeners who are up with the chickens,
here's the Farm Report.
Brought to you by Bob's Feed and Grain Storage of Dobstown.
So our bean futures continue at the market rate while most animal feeds are up today.
All futures continue to look pretty.
It is moon, but that's what you should expect if you're a hog.
That's because most farm-dwelling parkers know the end of the line
is food around the corner for somebody else's breakfast table, and maybe even yours.
Because if you have four legs, hooves, or trotters, and you live on a farm,
if it isn't the Grim Reaper, it's the International Harvester.
And now this.
It's the Subgenius Show.
Yes, if you weren't aware of what's been going on,
then you're probably just the sort of person to listen to the Subgenius Show,
the indefinitely long, infinitely boring corridor of horrible horticultural and biological facts.
This is the voice of Radio Subgenius,
bringing to the Greater Bay Area the unadulterated, infrapulated,
vocal incarnation of the sub-divine epistemology of subgenialism.
I'm your host, Dr. Howell, and during the next hour and a half,
Mobius Rex and I will chair the open forum of subgenial issues.
Yes, it's so exciting I can hardly stand it.
How about you, Mobius?
I'm gasping with amazement as I fall back asleep.
And with pleasure as one views the incredible expanse of subgenial opportunity.
I'm Dr. Howell, and I'll see you next time.
Don't you think it would be a good idea for you to turn the radio on?
Did you hear what he was saying?
What do you gentlemen like to escort Reverend Stang out and lock him out of his place?
In all reality, help me somebody.
She ain't got no legs.
Pull the lever down and go, my legs are on fire.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
Listen to that beautiful music.
Oh, yes.
We're going to try to take phone calls tonight.
We tried last week and had problems figuring out which of the 19 buttons to push
and how to push them right.
But I think we're going to do it this time.
So, friends, we're going to start our telephone outreach on the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
And if you will call, if you will but only call 823-749-0.
Yes, and we'll try to minister to your needs and try to open up your slack gland,
your third nostril, and see if we can either convince you of the truth, Bob,
deliver some slack, or else smite your ears in your confusion.
Because, you know, friends, I know that a lot of our listeners think that we're crazy.
And you know what, friends?
I don't care.
Because I've got slack.
And most of you, unbelievers, don't even know what that is.
Oh, yes, I've got Bob in my life.
So I know I'll be safe in the pleasure ships of the sex goddesses from Planet X
when the tribulation times come and you unbelievers will fry in a hell of your own making.
Praise Bob.
And how do we know this?
How can we be social?
Sure.
Friends, it's because we've got faith.
Faith, friends.
You don't use your mind to think about your religion.
Nay, nay.
You've got to let that Bob signal from outer space come through, beamed from space straight
into your skull, loud and clear, unfettered by your pathetic human notions of good or
evil or job or free will.
Ha, ha, ha.
No, friends, the word of Bob is a direct word.
It is not written in some roundabout symbolic manner.
You do not put your own interpretation on it.
You do not try to figure out what it means.
You just do what it says.
Bob said it.
I believe it.
And that settles it.
So there are all you Rudy Pootbee spectacle slabs of wimp meat.
I picked the god Dob's terror of the funky gods out of my nose.
Pardon my language, but ha, ha, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let the sons of God and man bear witness even.
In the belly of the Thunderbird, I've been casting out the false prophets.
And you probably think we're kidding.
You think it's a joke, a big joke.
Oh, yeah, Church of the Subgenius, a big joke.
I suppose Bob is a joke, too.
I suppose Slack and the conspiracy.
Oh, it must be some fantasy dreamed up in the diseased mind of Reverend Stang and all
his thousands of compatriot buddies.
Well, you go ahead and think that way, friends.
Well, it looks like we can try to take some calls here.
If we can.
We'll continue with the media barrage.
We've got a real hellfire show dreamed up tonight.
And if nothing else, we'll just segue from one thing to another.
Because, friends, this whole show is just one big segue between the American Music Party
show and Norm's show.
We're the masters of segue, which, by the way, for you who aren't into showbiz terminology,
a segue is like a dissolve in a movie.
It goes from one thing to another.
This music is by DK Jones.
Beautiful.
All right, dear friends, it looks like we've got one.
We got several on the line, but we're going to try.
We're going to try to take it in here.
But go ahead and pick it up.
Hello.
This is an hour slide.
I'm looking to make a note of it.
Friends, we're desperately struggling to.
Okay, Chris.
Is he on the air?
We're struggling to get someone on the air.
No, he is not on the air yet.
But, friends, pray with us.
You've got to pray.
You've got to get down and pray.
Massage your foot glands, friends.
We're trying to get us.
Somebody on the air.
We're trying to get some salvation on the air.
I hear a rotten buzz every time you do that.
George.
There's one here.
Well, dear friends, we're struggling once again with the technology over here.
No.
I don't know how Norm does it.
What subgenius is.
I guess they must mean that word subgenius literally.
We tried.
We tried to do the phone.
There's a lot of people calling.
And, God, I pushed all the buttons they told me to last time.
But, friends, we're just going to pretend to continue with the beautiful media barrage tapes here.
Ah, praise Bob.
Oh, by the way, we've been getting a lot of mail here at the Hour of Slack.
We appreciate that.
We're getting mails, tapes, and so forth.
Ah, so we can do everything but put you on the air.
And we're trying very hard to do that.
Thank you.
Did you hear what he was saying?
Is it possible that the end of the world will come in July 1999?
Perhaps in the form of an atomic holocaust?
Such a forewarning of ultimate doom could generally be dismissed out of hand.
The White House will confirm an order to use the atom bomb.
And our first target will be the initial landing place outside Los Angeles.
Those missiles have all gone off.
They pushed all the buttons.
You know what that means, don't you?
Either we fired first and they're going to try to hit what's left,
or they fired first and we just got our missiles out of the ground in time.
Either way, we're going to get hit.
So what are we still standing around here for?
Where do you want to go?
Well, how about out of here for starters?
I've got to get my wife and my kids.
We're still on alert, Billy.
No one leaves us.
This facility.
Oh, come on.
Of course, since all human life has been under the surface of Earth for 16 years,
there was no actual loss of life in the sense we know it.
The strange worshippers pull at their faces.
Despite himself, a strangled cry escapes Brent.
As he sees the ghastly heritage of atomic radiation,
the bomb is indeed their maker.
The bomb is indeed their maker.
Hey, Tony, let's have some.
Get out of here.
Get me out of here.
Kill Bob.
Yes, sirree, Bob.
We're going to get down.
We're going to beat this tongue.
We're going to beat down them tongues of those that use.
If their tongue offendeth thee, rip it out.
That's what I say.
And if thy music offendeth them,
rip their ears off.
And begin to speak to thy tongue.
I mean, hell, this turn the other cheek thing can be carried a bit too far, you know.
Leave.
I believe we're going to be able to do it here.
I keep this down.
Okay, now, Buddy, Pastor West, hang up the phone.
And I should be able to catch this person on the air.
Phillip.
Yes.
Oh, we hear you, dear friends.
I'm on the air now, huh?
You are indeed.
This is Aura Slash.
You are the first person to speak back to us from out there in listener land.
This is a great subgenius of a room.
It has been done.
Now, can we help you?
Can we deliver a healing, a sickening?
I'm really strung out on Reagan Youth Movement here.
Strung out on the Reagan Youth Movement?
That's right.
What?
Why, we're all members of the Reagan Youth.
We've been out killing normals for Reagan.
And what about the Dick Army Corps?
The Dick Army Corps?
The Dick Army Corps.
Right.
Take your fist, your right hand, bolt to a fist, put it on your left tit, and go, Dick.
Now, stretch your arm out.
Army.
Dick.
Dear friends.
Now, that'll get your blood flowing.
If you're tired of Reagan Youth, if you're worn out on that, just go for the Dick Army
Corps.
I feel better already.
Oh, man.
That's next.
Oh, praise Bob.
What else can we do for you?
Oh, I really don't know.
I...
Let him try that, Stang, and call us back when you're done, okay?
Thank you.
And keep massaging that foot gland for us, Bob.
I'll try my best.
Praise Bob.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, you know, friends, that's a new...
That new...
That chant one is new on me.
Friends, is that another phone call coming in?
I think so.
Same.
Well, we'll...
Friends, it's beautiful, isn't it?
That's what I'm saying.
I mean, hell, this turn, the other cheek thing could be carried a bit too far, you know?
Hey, neighbor, let me give you some advice.
The Russians are about to pulverize us.
You're not to live tonight.
That is if the crazy Arabs pull the right, don't get us first, and the fire will rain
down.
From the skies.
The fire will rain down.
People die.
Remember what's wise.
Time's just not fair.
There's nothing to fear but fear itself.
Tarı Force.
There's nothing to fear about fear itself
I remember how the siren was bursting into my brain
How it sounded as it began to stop
The gurgle of a death rattle
But silence did not follow
The awful he
And I couldn't see
I couldn't stand it
The smell
The terrible rotten smell of burning flesh
I was so sick
I cried for help
That I wrote the letter
Won't you leave you
Be with me
Make me cry
You're just cloud
Get a positive
You're fine
Andcen
Just a player
Triple
Up
Like
Bird
Hequelehr
Why did we come all this way?
Friends, we got somebody here ready to testify for Bob once again.
Let's give it a try here.
Oh, my.
That was terrible.
We lost him, Stan.
Yeah, we lost him.
Another listener gone by the wayside.
Another soul.
Another soul lost.
It's sad, sad, but that's not much.
We got someone on line three and on line one.
Let's check line one.
Check line one.
Oh, you did it again.
This is KNON.
You're on the air.
Yes.
I want to testify for Bob.
Oh, please do, dear friend.
Well, it was amazing.
I was sitting here in my house tonight listening to the show.
I've never heard of Bob before.
But.
But as I was listening to the music, my little girl, she's only six years old and she's been missing for two years now, I think.
And she came back in.
She walked right in the door of the house.
And I said, well, how did you get here?
You know, and she just said that a man with a big smile on his face had brought her here.
Had led her there.
And then I looked outside and there was a car.
And the man just drove off.
And lit his pot.
And I never saw him again.
That was beautiful.
Thanks for sharing that with us.
Good night.
Thanks for sharing that.
Oh.
Praise Bob.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, friends, so far we've gotten two calls of witnessing for Bob.
Now, Buck, when you want to get the other one, let's see you hit that.
Friends, we're going to go back to media barrage.
But the trouble is that all this knowledge I've got hold of is useless.
We're going to come back in just a moment.
We're going to have some strong comments.
We're going to talk about this.
And we're going to continue with it.
It's no wonder one group of kids said we're the generation that's been born under the mushroom cloud.
All right.
This is the subject of radio ministry.
Hour of black on K-N-O-N-9-0.9 in the left excess.
Praise Bob.
Hello, dear friend.
Hello.
You're on the air.
Yes, we're on the air.
Is Bob there?
Bob.
Friend, I'm afraid you haven't been up on the.
We're the our guru.
Bob Dobbs was shot and killed two years ago in San Francisco.
Well, but victim writes letters to us.
Victim of a cover up.
Yes, he can speak from the beyond life.
The before life.
Yes, he does.
All right.
Well, what's the latest on Bob?
Let's hear it.
The latest on Bob was he's been writing me letters.
He's been writing you letters.
What did they have to say?
It's kind of confidential, but he was a little.
Well, he's still.
You can tell it's Bob because he's basically.
Talk about our ratings and.
Yeah, you know, he's very willing to sacrifice any member of his flock, no matter how high up in the church they are.
If if that really was Bob anymore, need not be said.
Oh, I understand.
I understand.
Either that or it's the conspiracy trying to split the church up again.
That would be nothing new, would it?
Well, God knows we don't want to do that.
Heck no.
Yeah.
Well, any any question or do you have anything wrong with you?
Need a healing or anything?
Well, nothing really wrong with me.
I'm just really missing Bob.
I was really strung out.
Oh, hey, we'll send more.
Money and we'll be able to buy Bob's way out of hell, my friend.
Are you going to buy Bob's way out of hell?
If we don't get enough donations from subgenius ministers, we're going to have to start cashing in the canisters full of compressed souls.
Well, we've got stashed.
I'm already on the third mortgage on my house for y'all, man.
Yeah, well, I mean, you can get a house back, but getting those souls back from where we have to sell them to when we need to raise money ain't easy.
Where do you where do you sell the house?
Huh?
Where do you sell it?
We used to get them converted.
To rocket fuel.
Well, space bankers.
Are you serious?
That's yeah, that's that's one story.
I don't want to think about we just use them as but we got to go.
Bye bye.
Oh, another line.
Let's see.
Hello, dear friend.
Are you on the air?
Yes.
What?
Bob, we're going over like Pontchartrain.
You're going over like Pontchartrain?
Yes.
Bob, Bob, eat your apple and go to your room, Bob.
No, Bob.
Bob.
Oh, friends, I believe it's a mystic message in code.
No, Bob.
Bob, we're not going to do that today, Bob.
We're going to need we're going to have to get Bob into the station here.
I can't handle these kind of.
Yeah, I like these kind of calls.
They're called permission calls.
And we'd like a lot more permission calls.
We'd like a lot more of you to call and give us permission.
No, Bob.
No permission.
I'm sorry.
No, Bob.
Okay, see you, Mom.
Bye.
You mean they ain't going to give Bob slack, friends.
No slack for Bob.
Well, now what about the hate calls?
What about the people out there that hate this church of the subgenius?
What about you who think we're Satanists?
What about people who hate everything?
What about the ones who hate every last little thing?
We've got another call.
We've got a Satan call here.
Oh, well, I hope that's a Satan call.
Oh, no.
Oh, that one's gone.
That one's gone.
Oh, no.
What is this?
There's some sort of interference coming in here.
Listen to that.
That's strange.
At least it's in stereo.
Friends, do you consider this a waste of the airwaves?
Well, if you do, then...
No, no.
Look, the TV's talking back.
Something's wrong with my TV.
It's giving me answers.
I think you've made your point.
Your program will combine the powerful effects of subliminal mental suggestions with the
tried-and-proven plan to follow.
I can't say.
Let me show you how it comes together.
I can't.
It's not a joke.
Oh, my God.
I never got to see it.
We didn't have any jokes.
Oh, my God.
We made everyone get up and listen.
And nothing was funny!
Friends, we made everybody get up and listen.
And nothing was funny anymore.
Nothing worked.
I can't.
Hello? You're on the air.
How's it going, guys?
Well, I don't know.
Not bad. Pretty killer, actually.
Man, I hate you.
All right.
Yeah, tell us why. We want to know why you...
You want to know why I hate you?
Yeah, yeah.
It's because you don't play the crayons.
He wants to hear something he's heard a million times before.
No wonder he hates us.
We only play stuff you've never heard.
I want to hear the crayons.
Well...
I'll hate you until I hear the crayons.
But he's got us there, Stang.
There's no way we can please this guy.
That's right. We can't please you. That's it.
Oh, there they went.
Okay.
Hello? You're on the air, dear friend.
Huh?
She was calling...
Are they calling...
Did I hear Aunt Em calling for Dorothy?
Friends...
I'm gonna have to give a PSA here.
Listen to that beautiful background noise.
The free Joey benefit, folks.
Thursday, February 6th at the Circle A Ranch.
That's also known as the Twilight Room.
Located at 2111 Commerce Street downtown.
There will be a merely $4 benefit to help with the defense of war chest tourist Greg Joey Johnson.
Who was arrested and convicted for being part of an anti-war, anti-Raygun protest during the Republican...
Convention.
Bans to...
Let's see.
I know all about this.
Okay.
You lay out the bans here, Buck.
I was gonna nest this paper anyway.
Okay.
It's a...
Two by four.
N-O-Y-B, which means none of your business.
Reverend Buck naked with more drunk cowboys.
The Underground.
Also stand-up comic Anne McKinney from the Ladies Against Women comedy troupe.
And the video of Stoney Does Gallop by Stoney Drip will be featured.
Come on and support the political rights of freedom of protest against government and
war and death and pills and budget busting stuff.
So if you want to know more, just call 827-3189.
You're on the air.
No, that wasn't it.
That was the wrong number.
Sorry, we gave you the wrong number, folks.
Don't listen to that number.
Hello?
I was just wondering if Bob was going to be attending the resident show.
Bob Dobbs, in order to attend a show, Bob has to re-corporate into this physical plane.
I don't know if you all understand that.
that Bob has actually literally been killed.
Now, some say he has resurrected,
some say he has re-erected,
some say that Bob Dobbs can only speak to us
through tape decks and mysterious messages
written on walls in the bodies of cockroaches.
But I'll be at the resident show.
Well, do you think the residents have anything to do
with the appraising of Bob?
I'll tell you...
Directly?
No, no, definitely not directly.
They know of Bob.
Just as Bob knows of them.
But Bob knows about everybody.
And he knows when you've been sleeping,
he knows when you're awake.
I'm asleep right now.
Well, he...
I'm sure he...
Uh-oh.
Oh, wait a minute, you guys.
Who spilled show?
I'm getting show spilled all over my lap.
Okay, anything else we can do for you?
Uh...
Death and damnation?
So, damnation, one dollar is available here.
I don't have any money.
Okay.
Well, then, we can't help you.
Bye.
This is a church.
They don't seem to understand.
You're on the air.
Yeah, I saw Bob last night.
That's what they all say.
I swear he was here.
He was right here next to me.
He...
Really?
I mean...
Now, are you putting us on or...
I swear.
I mean, that's like somebody saying
Jesus appeared to him the other day.
I wouldn't lie to you.
I was just laying here in bed.
Well, what did he do?
I was laying here, and suddenly,
I felt something in the bed next to me.
And then I go,
I go, oh, my God.
And I saw it rolled over, and it's Bob.
And Bob said,
Bob said,
Sting, he said,
there's something I've always wanted you to do.
And I said, what is it, Bob?
And he said, fart in my mouth, please.
Please.
Bob said that?
Bob said that.
That, friend,
you just convinced...
You just convinced me that it was Bob.
I told you it was Bob.
I can't think of anybody else besides Bob
who would do that,
and I don't know why he would,
but it sounds so somehow Bob.
It sounds totally Bob, doesn't it?
Yeah, he's...
He's...
You know, Bob works in mysterious ways.
I mean, I couldn't believe it.
It just changed my life.
Well, now, did it...
When he did this...
When he asked you to do this,
did he want you to pyroflatulate
or to flatulate normally?
To flatulate normally.
That's weird,
because usually he wants you to light it.
Does he want you to light it?
Well, yes.
As a matter of fact,
it's one of the main rituals of the church.
It's pyroflatulation.
I didn't know he was into pyro.
You bet.
And not only that,
but excremeditation, of course,
is a daily meditative ritual that we do.
Have you ever read our subgenius pamphlet
or the books or any of that stuff?
I haven't read them lately.
Well, you ought to check them out,
because they'll let you know
which of your bodily functions
are more holy than others
and how to get the most slack out of
abusing those bodily functions.
Yeah, yeah.
So, you know,
first send a buck to the station
and then send a buck to Bob.
Okay, well, I've already paid Bob.
Oh, have you?
Yeah.
How much did you pay him?
It was $27.50.
Plus the gas that was expelled
when he demanded.
Of course, plus the gas.
I think I heard some of that gas
just a second ago.
Listen to that.
There it is.
That's it.
The church air.
Oh, yeah.
Smell that church air.
Whoa!
Too much church air, friends!
That's it.
Too much is always better than not enough.
That's what Bob said.
Praise Bob.
Well, we're going to have to continue
with the media barrages here.
We got some important preaching on tape.
All right.
Oh, okay.
One more here.
Okay, just briefly.
The TFL stand.
Table Football League.
Bring Tony in here.
Hold it.
There's a lot of buzzers in the air here.
We got it.
Go ahead, Buck.
We had a tournament recently
for the Table Football League.
Oh, no.
The first time a rookie.
No, not the Table Football League.
Go ahead.
The TFL.
And we had a rookie make it all the way to the top,
the Wazonian Doctors.
Next was number two,
the Uptown Beachcombers.
Then the Oaklawn Thingette,
Okie Cronies,
Dallas Assassins.
At number six,
Dibock Killer Worms.
Then the Metro Milkmen,
North Oak Cliff Goon Squad,
Chaos City Crushers,
Downtown Underground.
At number 11,
Kossie View Kamikazes.
Then at the Eastside and Architects,
number 13,
Midway Thing.
14,
the Mexican Mafia.
15,
Gomer City GIs.
And then following with that
would be the Santa Fe Diplomats
and the Trinidad Pterodactyls.
Come to our next tournament
at the Stonely P,
February 15th,
Saturday night.
It'll be the Stonely P Bowl.
That's right,
the Stonely P,
right there at Stonely.
The P Bowl.
Not really at Stonely, maybe,
but right across the Stonely Hotel.
You'll find it.
930 Sharp.
Ah, yes, probably.
That was the Table Football League report.
You see,
subgeniuses have to invent their own sports.
Team sports,
you know,
they're somehow,
they're fun,
but too normal
if that's all you do.
So subgeniuses have to invent their own games
and Buck has resurrected
the great game of table football,
if you remember that from high school,
with a folded up piece of paper
flicked over bottles of beer.
And the only world championships
in that happened here in Dallas.
Well, friends,
we're going to go,
we're going to avoid,
well, one more call
and then we're going to,
we're going to call it a night
and go back to,
all right,
let's give this one a try.
You're on the air.
Hello?
Yes.
I want to testify for Bob.
All right, testify, testify.
Testify.
Hey, brother.
I was a successful lawyer and a doctor.
He was a lawyer and a doctor.
I hear them all testify.
That's right,
but then I found slack.
Then he found slack.
Yeah, yeah, hallelujah.
Then I quit both of my jobs.
Praise Bob.
Praise Peter.
Oh, yes.
I grabbed my wife by the diamond ring
and I threw her out of the house.
He grabbed his wife by the ring
and he threw her out of the house.
Oh, yes, friends.
I put my kids in their toy Mercedes
and threw them down the driveway.
He threw them down the driveway
in front of the car.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Now I raise digital cat food for a living.
Digital cat food
and he makes a good living on it.
Help me somebody.
Oh, yeah.
Here's some sprouting now.
There it was.
All right.
Oh, you have digital cat food there, too.
Yes, digital cat food.
It's spreading.
It's made of pluses and nothing.
Ah, yes, friends.
You know what?
If you could listen to this man,
you'd have a spiritual devival at night,
at now,
in your own bed tonight.
Yes, sir.
You can have a revival in your own bed.
A devival.
Or you can have an invival.
You can invert it and get,
oh, friends,
the things you can do.
Sex hurt is real.
Oh, my.
And it's not what you're thinking.
Sex hurt.
It ain't tying them up or anything.
It's just love.
It's just love them until it hurts.
Love them until it hurts.
Something hurts so much,
you just can't keep going.
And that's slack, friends.
Oh, yes.
Oh, slack has done everything for me.
Slack is dripping down their legs
in a great torrent of love.
Oh.
It's religious urges
and so it's so wonderful.
Well, is there anything else we can do for you?
Like read our sacred P.O. box
so that you could send for a pamphlet?
Oh, my gosh.
That would be a healing experience.
Yes.
The very sound of hearing the P.O. box number read.
About to have the wallet healed by Bob.
The wallet will be removed.
Oh, my goodness.
That which has burdened you,
we shall take upon ourselves.
And that's, friends, get a pencil.
Write to Bob.
Ask for our pamphlet.
And a love offering would help.
But remember the station, too.
And that's Bob at P.O. Box 14030.
306 Dallas, Texas 75214.
And we'll read that number again
at the end of the broadcast.
Thanks a lot, dude. Praise Bob.
Praise Bob.
And we're going to go back to media barrages,
I think, right now.
We're going to have to stop the phone calls.
I want a personal message, though,
to all the ladies out there.
Okay. Please do.
By the way, this is KNON Community Radio.
Yes.
And we're 90.9 on your FM dial.
And you're listening to us in Grapevine,
Plano, Midlothian, Dallas,
and Fort Worth.
And I'd just like to say...
Say it, Buck. Come on.
Say it.
Oh, he's trying to argue.
Don't be asked this about his high end, Tom.
This is the plague show.
The show that plagues you and plagues us.
Three.
The people you want to leave
forces us to get on the effects you're hearing.
That's our problem.
Listen up.
Well, we're watching the station right now.
You hear in the background.
Is that an antenna in your pocket
or are you glad to hear it?
And there was a little spooky sight.
Is this a real show or is this a fake show?
It's a tape.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You broke the show.
Please help me.
I'm scared.
Somebody give that kid a fix.
Don't worry.
It won't be long now.
Please help me.
I'm sorry.
We're not going to help you.
Wow, I'm funny, please.
Comprez-vous que je dis?
Well, all the salads, all the...
Okay, we'll have to roll that back.
That was fine.
I think that really worked out well.
And it's free.
Just send us a large amount of money.
Shit or get off the car.
No, come on.
What, what, what?
What?
Oh, there's someone who wants to talk to me.
Yeah, okay, put him on.
Hello?
Can you speak?
Hey, do you guys got degrees in this?
Are you cool with that?
Yeah, it's hard.
I'm gonna miss you smaller than you are.
Can I get a whip, brother?
Can I get a whip?
Can you get a high?
Let me hear it, brother.
Can I get a whip?
Can't hide if you're broke, Frank.
If he's more unpronounceable than you are.
He makes less sense than you do.
He's more non-existent than you are.
You cannot hide from your own friends.
You can't hide from Bob, because he's younger than you.
His face is in more places than yours is.
He smokes more prop than you do.
Help somebody.
You can't hide from Bob.
You can't hide from your own friends.
Help somebody.
Can I get a witness?
Can I get a whip?
You can't hide from your own friends.
Help somebody.
You cannot hide from God, but you can try.
You can run as fast as you want to.
You can run as far as you want to.
You cannot run away from the old man.
You can't start your own chain song without being started with.
You can't launch a turbine overhead.
That doesn't make any sense.
Go help me somebody.
You're not going to win this, so help me.
This is KNON 90.90.N FM.
And I'm Texas.
Copyright 1986 by the Subgenius Foundation and the participants.
I tell you.
And silence them with the final solution.
Greatest bugaboo of them all is Static, the unconquered,
who grinds his crackler in your ears while he laughs in your face.
The home of the whistlers, squealers, and howlers is to be found in tuning elements
and transformers of poor design in faulty wiring or unskillful operation.
Other cracklers usually are found hiding in run-down batteries,
poor wiring connections, defective rheostats, shoddy condensers,
and dust between condenser plates.
The machine gunners of the crew have their headquarters in the incorrect gridlock
while the anvil chorus of the blacksmith comes from dust in the condensers and from weak batteries.
But how can you test your radio for these signals?
With a sledgehammer, tap your vacuum tube.
If they emit a hollow ping sound, your vacuum tube should be replaced.
If you have a steam-powered radio or television set, exchange it for an interoperable one.
And if you have a steam-powered radio or television set, exchange it for an interoperable one.
You'll be glad and you'll be marching on to eternal victory with the Church of the Subgenius
in sight and color as well as in scintillating sound.
Help me, please.
Soon we, the doctors of the air, will have to leave you.
But now, listen to these words of inspiration and wisdom.
Inspiration and wisdom, friends. That's right.
That's what Pastor Naked is ready to give.
He's gonna play a song for us here in the studio.
Right, we got the whole band. More drunk...
More drunk cowboys here.
And by the way, we're doing two shows this weekend.
And the first one, we said a little bit about it before.
The Communist Martyrs Benefit.
Thursday, February 6th at the Circle A Ranch.
That's the Twilight Room at 2111 Commerce between Central and Pearl.
And you can hear bands like 2x4,
N.O.Y.B., which means None of Your Business,
and Underground, and of course, Reverend Buck with More Drunk Cowboys.
Also, Saturday night, we're playing with an artist.
Architects and Grinding Teeth, both bands from Houston.
Hardcore type bands.
And you'll hear More Drunk Cowboys again.
But anyway, right now...
Buddy, you ready?
Okay.
Yeah, Pastor Naked and...
Reverend West here.
Yeah, they're gonna go ahead and try to play a song.
If we can get our equipment together, they're gonna do it live on the air.
And I guess, yeah, I guess we're gonna put Tony on the...
Tony's gonna play the organ now.
Okay, the alien organ. Okay.
Whenever.
One, two, three.
One, Two, Three, Four...
The Exes have landed,
Earth's UNDER...
Their control,
The golf station
Skys proving
For cities
Radio-active,
We don't know what their game is, but their name is unpronounceable.
We don't know what they came for, but what they aim for is impossible.
They are not human beings.
In the second year before the millennium of the day of God, come Wednesday, as in the
twinkling of night, there will come among the occultism, which are like unto thy great
white brothers.
They come as men, as graven images, as the whirlwind and as the clouds, and they are
not human.
Holy prophets were mingled with me.
And hoplites were people of thee Who have landed their machines to follow
in our tracks.
God's vision stands proven, a world without slack.
Oh, that was beautiful.
Thank you, Pastor.
Pastor, you rock!
naked. We're going to try to put
another one on the air.
You're on the air.
Hey. Praise Bob.
Praise Bob. Praise the word
of Bob. Or kill me. I heard that.
I heard that.
Yes? Yes.
How can we help you in
ten words or less? Can you
just tell me how I can reach Bob?
You, well, first... You can reach
Bob through that most holy
gland, your wallet. That's right.
And it's right in your back pocket, and you
can reach Bob by slowly unpeeling
a few of those green
pieces of commode paper that you hardly need
anymore, and you just kind of get rid of
and sending them to B.O.B.
To Bob?
That's right, Bob. Praise Bob.
Would you like to hear the sacred P.O. box?
You see, I have sold
everything I own in
trying to get in contact with Bob,
but I still get nothing.
Well, my friend, you're
going at it from the wrong direction. Bob doesn't
want you to be poor. He wants you
to be rich. Rich
beyond your wildest dreams without working.
And if you don't send that money to
Bob, he'll never get it. He'll never see it.
He doesn't want all your worldly goods unless you
have a lot of worldly goods.
Uh-huh. So, what
you can't... Tell him the parable
of the old woman, Stang.
Uh, Pastor Naked, I'm sorry,
I forgot. Oh, yeah, okay.
Now, see, it all depends on
how much, how much,
you know, you're given out of
how much you got. Say a rich guy,
decides, well,
I'll give the church of the subgenius
five dollars. Now, he ain't giving much.
And then you got this old lady
who, she ain't got a cent in the world,
but she sends, all she's got
is 50 cents. If she sends 25
cents of that, we'd rather,
who'd we rather have, that rich guy that sends
five dollars or the poor little old lady that
sends everything she has and it's only
25 cents? Well, heck with
the old bag. Take the money. That's what I said.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Yeah, we'll go with the rich guy. We'll see you, dude.
Yeah. Praise Bob.
We got another one? Yeah.
Hello. Praise Bob,
you're on the air. Uh, I
live in Garland and I deliver
pizzas. I knew it.
I knew it. I could tell you're a pizza salesman
before you even spoke. I was reading your,
uh, I was whiff reading your
edge right here on the meter.
Oh, they said that's
true, but I never believed it. I could smell
that, that pizza now steaming
at me through the microphone. Go ahead, son.
And I delivered a pizza
to,
to the ticket said Bob and,
and it scared me and
I went to the door and it was
Bob. It had to have been
the same Bob. Praise Bob.
There is only one Bob. Bob is
never changing yet. He never changes.
And you know, Stang, you know, we get calls like this, like
on every show it seems like we get
another contact with Bob and yet out there
would you believe there's a, there's a
world of Dobbs atheists that don't
even believe in Bob and yet we have all these
contactees calling us constantly.
Does Bob live in Garland?
He lives everywhere. He lives in the heart and mind of all
free thinking subgenius.
Come on, Stang. No, he's got suburban homes in a lot of different
places, a lot of different little families he likes to keep up.
I think there's one right by South Garland High School.
Well, we'll keep it in mind and thanks son and praise Bob.
Thank you.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I want to go to hell.
All my friends are down there.
Yeah.
So goes a certain popular joke.
Oh, yeah.
He said, yeah, I want to go to hell.
All my friends are down there.
So goes a certain popular joke.
When the flame's at your toes, when your eyeballs melting,
and you realize that this is going to go on forever.
Maybe that's so-called quote popular joke,
unquote only quite so funny.
Oh, yeah.
All your friends, their eyes will be melting, too.
It'll be funny.
Were the records to stop here, my son, it would indeed be a
wonderful start.
It's a wonderful story.
But these faithful records are very careful to point out the
darkest day in your life.
It is stated here that in the year of your Lord, 1973, you
turned your back upon your God and once more began to walk in
your own ways.
But, sir, I've come back.
I've come back, sir.
I'm closer now than I've ever been before.
My God, I've come back.
Yes.
The record shows that in the fourth watch of your life,
you returned to the fold.
What an awful price you must pay for your foolishness.
Because you turned back, you have lost your reward.
You shall enter heaven as a servant without a single soul to
your credit.
You can be the moon this time around.
Oh, it's unfair.
It's so unfair.
I've worked so hard for the king of all these years.
It's unfair that I should lose all my credits now.
Oh, my.
You knew all of this before you backslid.
Show him the way.
Show him his record.
What?
No!
August 21st, 1973.
You mean you aren't going to church again today?
Babe, you know, Barney, you know this is my only day off.
I don't have to live in church to be saved.
Dana, if you aren't careful, you're going to miss out with
the Lord completely.
Come on, Kim.
.
. .
. …
We lost another listener, friends.
Another soul's damned.
Oh, they're damned.
We're not doing our job tonight real good, friends.
Oh, it's sad.
You know, it can be pretty risky trying to get saved on this show.
Because you have never accepted Jesus Christ as your Savior,
you must go to hell.
Oh, please.
I don't want to go to hell.
I'm only 14 years old.
I'm too young.
I never even had a chance to be a Christian.
But I'd like to be saved.
Couldn't I become a Christian now?
No, child.
It is too late.
But you wouldn't send a person to hell who never had a chance, would you?
But you had an opportunity when you were seven years old.
You could have called the hour of slack.
Let's play those tapes for this listener and see just what she did wrong.
Second.
Nineteen.
Sixty-eight.
For as long as I've known Christ, I've tried to make him real to you.
When are you going to accept him and be saved?
I don't know, Cindy.
I don't want to hurt your feelings, but religion just isn't my thing.
There's plenty of time.
You are lost and there is no place found for you except the lake of fire,
prepared for the devil and his angels.
Prepare.
Take her away.
For the harvest.
No!
The harvest.
The harvest!
I don't want to go!
You think, oh, it's a popular joke.
You think it's funny.
No!
Yeah.
What have I done?
You can't hide.
You don't know what hell is.
You don't know that.
Oh, you think you know.
Popular joke.
Yeah.
You think you know what hell is.
You don't know what hell is.
Oh, it's funny.
It's funny.
There ain't no water down there.
Ain't no water down there.
Ain't much air either.
You're going to be thinking about those days when you had so much church air.
We thought the church air was never going to run out.
You had a big popular joke.
I'm spending my children's inheritance on church air.
I heard that one a lot in the 90s.
They thought it was funny.
Funny then.
It ain't so funny now, is it?
Well, the conspiracy was a joke, didn't you?
A joke.
What they thought.
They thought it was a joke too.
And slack.
Oh, yeah.
Looks like a funny joke.
A popular joke.
Yeah.
That flash of nuclear radiation seared the skin off their back.
They're going, oh, is this Bob?
Or is this slack?
Or is this what they mean by the conspiracy?
Is it a conspiracy?
Huh?
There's no manner.
We are the damned.
We switch you to the 16th tee, where we will show you in slow motion,
Arnold Palmer, U.S. opium champion.
I began to drive faster and faster.
I was in lunar landscape.
So.
Serene.
Calm.
I drove through it with the indifference of a fly crawling over the face of the moon.
Attitude corrected.
Hold.
Even though we're traveling at 23,000 miles per hour, I feel like we're floating.
It's...
Bob Meltdown.
I'm here on the 7th.
We're on a subgenius death ship.
We approach San Francisco.
Our mission, destroy anything.
Somebody help.
Help me, please.
Has this ever happened to you?
Meltdown.
Please remove all humans from container area six.
Be really...
Doug, pull over.
We gotta scrape the collar off the front of the show.
If we have another collar...
If we get another collar on the front of this show smeared like that last one, we're gonna
be in trouble.
We're gonna be in severe heat damage.
Well, I don't think we should drive the show so fast.
Well, you're right.
It's just stupid to keep wasting fuel running over listeners like this.
There is no collar.
There never has been a collar.
You're listening to tape.
All the collars are gone.
The show was just a tape, right?
Yes.
Launching a probe...
This joke has been real.
Well, but they did survive and they're willing to give us their wristwatches and most of
their...
That's what I mean.
Imagine listening to this show and surviving.
...inferior organs.
Unfortunate.
Yes, it was.
We do have some...
Some doctors were still here.
Good morning, tiny collar.
Don't drive any faster.
Yes, well, it would have been nice to hear your message, but at this hour, we're asking
all messages.
Just my little...
Ten minutes left to...
Ten minutes.
...rotate your message toward the war and off the planet.
So aim high with us.
Oh, friends, you can aim high, but the show does have to leave the planet.
We don't even have that 10 minutes puzzling evidence.
I was just promising you.
I ought to give a little bit of...
A little bit of...
Oh, Buck's trying to get it out.
I'm trying to get the...
Oh, sorry, Buck.
He's trying to get it out.
I can't.
I'm too nervous.
Oh, no.
All right, friends.
Well, the California Show guys will say it for you.
What we've been playing tonight, there's been a lot of media barrage tapes cut by myself
and Reverend Byron...
St. Byron Werner in California
with Douglas Willman
and Buzzing Evidence.
You've been hearing a lot of the
More Than an Hour, Less Than a Show
show from Berkeley, California
on KPFA.
We trade shows quite a bit.
We rip lines off.
You were also hearing some of that
good subgenius,
that popular joke material
that was the St. Jane or Hyperclates
who you've heard so much about
of Doctors for Bob
playing with Dr. Ray Hay
and some other show regulars
from a band called
The Swinging Love Corps.
All subgenius bands get together
once every equinox
at a festival of life and love
and death and hate
called Dockstock.
Last time we got to watch Bob
crash and burn from a height
of three or four miles
like a meteor.
Quite impressive staying
and I got a little bit of Bob
smeared on me.
Takes years to watch.
Wash it off, friends.
Get that beautiful slack power off
once you got it on you.
Well, we're going to do the trade.
When you finally get it right,
you do so good in TFL.
Oh, listen, there's the
Legs of Fire theme
by Mark Mothersbaugh.
And you can listen to that
while we get ready for
the Monday morning show.
Norm's not here.
By the way, everybody,
this show is invited to take a play.
It's going to be at the
LA next Saturday morning
and go see Nina Hagen
and her UFO church.
That's right.
Nina Hagen invites all subgeniuses
to come to her UFO church
in Los Angeles.
All you got to do is fly out there.
That shouldn't be any big deal
for most of you.
Remember, friends,
there are 10,000 UFOs
each 20 million miles long
circling the Earth
at any individual time.
Let's all get together
as we sign off
and say boom
to all our lovely,
space burgers.
You know,
the ohm is the laid-back chant
for those new-age sugar daddies.
What we're into
is the new squirting universe chant
of huh, huh, huh, yeah, yeah,
praise Bob, help me somebody.
Preacher, my legs are on fire.
Friends, this is the
subgenius radio ministry
hour of slack
preparing to sign off.
Oh, listen to that.
Bye, everybody.
Friends,
and I know that
you'll want to write to Bob
at P.O. Box
Dallas, Texas
75214.
You don't have to send any money,
but you'll get a lot more pages
per penny.
Let's just put it that way.
And meanwhile,
do contribute to KNON.
I mean, let me put it this way.
The other big stations in town
will let you have the time to write.
They'll let you have slack,
but they'll only let you have
a minute of slack.
KNON is the only one
that will let you have an hour of slack.
I'd like to tell them
if they want to see what life would be like
without KNON,
just turn the channel.
That's right.
Oh, praise Bob, friends.
It's so nice to be back on the air
with the whole cast and crew
of the hideous subgenius scary show.
Good night forever.
We'll let the norm creatures
come in and take over
and hang in there
because this is going to be
a...
Oh.
Well, they're here.
Oh, more creatures.
Bob, Bob.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh.
Bob, Bob.
Bob.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
As you can tell, Norm is not sitting here.
If you're watching on your radio, we're the ones on the far left.
And what we have here tonight, say what?
That's one of our old gags.
One of your old gags?
One of your radio gags.
I don't want to get into your kinky sex life.
Anyway, this is Monday morning, and what we're going to talk about this morning, since Norm isn't here,
is what do you want to be doing in the year 2000?
Now, the way we came across this is a week ago I resigned from a job saying,
I never want to get back into the certain business again.
Well, guess what? A week later, I'm just at a different place.
Same business, different place.
So what do you want to be doing in now 16 years?
If you've got a girlfriend already, do you want to be with that person?
Or if you've got a boyfriend already?