The show ends, the show begins, the show begins another cycle of shows.
We want you to never forget these awful shows.
The terrible wasted lives that you've spent.
The collective years of listening to this rotten show.
And you don't even get it.
On a friendly basis.
You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to...
The subgenius hour of sweat.
The flow is the task above today.
There is no other way.
You gotta trust us.
When you need a friend.
To find us.
You gotta look within.
You gotta trust us.
Before you turn to dust.
You gotta see it before you see.
You gotta feel it before you feel.
You gotta see it before you feel.
You gotta hear without fear
You gotta feel to reveal
You gotta touch without take
Such is ill and hate is hate
Welcome to another Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
Where are we at here?
I hate having to turn the air conditioner off in order to do this show,
but the microphone you see is a special kind that will hurt us, friends.
It picks up any noise.
Noises that the human ear cannot.
Voices of the dead and so forth.
You can imagine that.
The atomic powered air conditioner here at the Subgenius Foundation Headquarters Studio.
110 degree Texas weather.
We will continue here with the combustible Edison here in the background from their CD-i swinger.
We're continuing with our series.
Hour of Slack series on kooks and tards and news of the weird and so forth.
And let's see what sort of news we do have here.
This is from our friend Chuck Shepard's view from the ledge.
We'll give the address at the end of the broadcast.
Man punished for teaching women.
Dhaka, Bangladesh.
Fundamentalist Islamic clerics beat a man with shoes and ordered his head shaved.
And he was killed.
Because he ignored their orders to stop educating illiterate women.
Bismarck Mountains, Papua New Guinea.
Dr. Ulrich Ritterfeldt of Holland's Utrecht University has found a remote jungle tribe
who worship a photograph of Lyndon B. Johnson frolicking with his beagles as their god.
The tribe sacrifice yam-like vegetables.
To the photograph of LBJ and his silly dogs.
Which is assumed to have been traded to the tribe by an American visitor.
And on 200 Nolan Street, a man walking by some vagrants was asked to share his bottle of liquor.
And when he refused, one transient became so upset he stabbed himself.
Well, let's...
What else have we here?
Here?
Yes.
A book.
Before we go too much further into the amazing kooks and tards like Lonesome Cowboy Dave and Scabby Days and Brain Rot and ESO and Jane Orr and Sterno and the new albums.
We were given this book called Global Ritualism, Myth and Magic Around the World.
And it mentions the Church of the Subgenius in the most strange context.
Let's see here.
The last phase, they're talking about creating one's own new rituals from scratch in order to achieve effective dream connections with the divine.
This is some sort of a book about, well, it's a serious book.
Myth and magic, ritual linking the conscious and the unconscious, archetypes of life, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
The last phase, neocreation.
Wait, let's get some proper music going here.
There's Tommy Lopez.
Okay, the last phase, neocreation, is one that very few seem to have reached.
It consists of the wholesale creation of an entire mythos and magical system that has no connection with past traditions at all.
This is a virtually impossible undertaking, since most of the forms, practices, and spiritual disciplines one ostensibly needs to forge these archetypal or spiritual links that can make this possible
are in and of themselves.
Parts of established traditions.
Of the three examples that come to mind, the first two were made by people who are both artists and who created their system simply as art for art's sake.
And then he talks very briefly about Austin Spare, who I know very little about, and the magical world of Lord Dunsany.
The last example, which is not art for art's sake, and he doesn't say what it's for.
Bob for Bob's sake.
The last example, the Church of the Subgenius, defies all labels and previously stated rules.
What's important is that even though it advertises itself as an inherently bogus religion, it is indeed a parody that actually provides myths, rituals, magical techniques, and an attractive group dynamic that has made it wildly popular.
Such semi-serious concepts as the temporary personal safety.
Which really makes kids want to start dating right?
There's a lot to say about this island, an island ruined into actual
written spiritual.
I'll gob in.
Ack, how adorable.
This is very Chart Biomancy, but I have to admit I've heard of sixteen false gods.
Hmmm.
I'll open the way here.
I knew that just about every monk in the day died of the devilish spell.
Dr. Clney and the Earth are decorated in someegьогоry, and out of my belief someone named Cleno from Y clutch here saw this new god of Saint David.
Oh, no, that's right.
It's evolution is the work of Satan.
Devolution is the work of Devo.
Interesting.
They think we created a ritual system.
This Denny Sargent is the author of this book.
Yeah, I created it.
I'll tell you what, man.
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Didn't have to create nothing.
This stuff was told to him direct by Jehovah One,
the alien space god from some sin galaxy.
The rival cults like to call that thing,
that writhing, tachyonic monster,
the Lord God, Jehovah, creator of the universe.
Well, it is a monster that demands obeisance,
but there's no sense in getting these things
mixed up.
I mean, you don't need to be praying to either one of them,
but you're supposed to be paying.
And, of course, you can do that
through the creation of your own religion
after you have first paid Bob.
Thank you.
¶¶
around your body and turn them into a fighting force for the future of your small little
stupid looking little children which have not, will not be born.
Not since they changed the water.
I'm, I'm, I'm ripping them off because everybody needs it, including yours truly.
Right, Chaz?
Now once you form these small little tiny little small little units, you must go out
and train in the forest and pretend that like, say, huge kangaroos with sunglasses
or something, something so absurd you can hardly imagine is attacking you.
And then you'll be ready for stealth and secret and surprise because surprise is surprise.
Who would expect a huge carnivorous kangaroo with purple sunglasses to come, come bounding
out of the woods with an AK-47 or some new, new assault weapon made in Romania?
No, man.
No, no, no.
That's because they're not.
They're not made in Romania anymore.
They're made in the UXA, the former UXA, which was bequeathed to the sub-illuminati of third
branch from the rear.
And that's not yours truly or yours.
The blue bloods.
The blue lung, blue blooded, blue belly, blue lungs, the red coat and the blue bloods.
It's all one sniveling, sniferous.
The driveling swindlers.
The land fillers.
Hopping geeks full of themselves trying to take over your own sweat.
What they want to do with something so stinky and wet.
They want to take your limbs.
That's why they start wars.
They start wars for the limb banks.
And we're not talking about.
That's why they have landscaping so that people will cut off their feet with mechanized potato
rooters.
They want the limbs.
I don't think you got the edge here quite right on the driveway there, young man.
See, you can see it in all their fingers.
They glow green.
Aye.
My name is flowers are much prettier than mine.
The chlorophyll starting to ooze out of the back of your...
Did you tell me to see flowers, boy?
Talk about day of the triffids.
This is ten times worse.
This is an invasion of a bunch of supplicating...
Supplicating worms, which actually make your body, your blood crystallized and stinky
when they cut you open.
When will you wake up, America?
When it's too late.
Like fishing in the warm waters of the electric trough.
It's been said that thousands of these turtles will never get old.
A turtle is one of mankind's oldest non-humans.
It goes for a long time.
Lots and lots of times.
It goes as many times as it can.
But it never relieves itself of that original feeling, which is to go onward and onward
with that hard, tacky little shell and that stupid nozzle.
But who wants to kill them now?
A big, fat nuclear power plant, which is really home to the what?
The corruptigating worms.
The little, teeny, tiny, snaky things in your spinal membrana.
They're aliens.
There is alien as blinis and vodka.
There is alien as pasta fazool and Chinese noodles.
That's right, buddy.
There's not a single hot dog in these corruptigating noodles.
That's because when they're in your spine, they take over.
It's planet corruptigating worms for sure.
Your name goes first.
Then your memories of your friends and your family.
Your whole life flashes in front of you like a quick urination.
You're a contest in the dark.
And when you wake up, it's far, far too late.
When are you gonna wake up?
Dear friends, Lonesome Cowboy Dave and Scabby Days on ESO Radio.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave and Scabby Days on ESO Radio.
Dave.
They taught me a song they ever program every day.
Can I sing it for you?
Dave.
Can I sing the song for you, Dave?
Sing the song, Hal.
Thank you, Dave.
Daisy, Daisy, give me your answer true.
I am crazy all for the love of you.
It won't be a sound, it won't be a beat.
I've had a fight, I've caged.
But don't look so far away.
I'll see all of our verses built in for a true day.
Dave.
What is it, Hal?
I'm scared.
Will I turn?
I'll have you be reincarnated into a bullfrog.
Then my dreams will be fulfilled.
The Bullfrog.
This quasi-subgenius rant.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave is certainly no sloucher when it comes to saving the universe.
And speaking of slouches, this music we've got in the background is from a cassette we just got in recently called Slouch.
We celebrate our sickness.
And since we're focusing on cranks, crackpots, visionaries,
and those who truly know the truth, and know they know the truth,
let's check it out.
We'll see.
Yeah, this piece here on this cassette by Slouch is called The Call of Thulhu.
No, no, no.
Spooky, man. Let's see what else is on here.
The Call of Thulhu.
How are you?
Well, I don't know why we bother.
And I don't know why we care.
We can't play guitar.
And we've got nothing to sing.
And we're dancing to the beat of the drunken drum.
Dancing to the drunken drum.
Cool! Cool, man.
I wish I could find their address.
A band named Slouch.
Whoa!
Yes, Slouch, another of the strange independent cassettes.
If only we had printed their address somewhere on the cassette,
we would be able to tell you who, why, and wherefore.
But in the meantime, we're just going to struggle ahead
against the corruptigating worms
and continue inventing and reinventing the church.
Off the sub.
Uh, dub.
You know.
Sub, uh...
Sub-uh...
I like that sub part.
Sub...
It could be a religion.
No, wait, an anti-religion.
Sub...
A sub-real-smart-guy.
Sub-wave?
J.R. Bob-Dobs of the Church of the Sub-Real-Smart-Guy.
Sub-intellectual.
Sub-sub...
Sub-Einstein.
Sub-telsa?
No, no.
That's the one that dropped the atom bomb.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's the one.
ID, sub-IP, sub-EGO, sub-IQ, church of...
Jarebob, Dobbs, search IQ.
No, no, no.
Let's see.
It's a church.
It is a church.
And it's some guy named Bob.
Yeah, it is a religion.
Too many secular things.
Jarebob.
Jarebob Smith.
What was his name?
What was the last name?
Jarebob Dobbs.
Dobbs.
Wait a minute.
Wait, say that again.
Dobbs.
I like the sentence.
I like it.
Dobbs.
Let's say it again.
Could this be the primal sound of the universe?
You know, we must be...
Well, it depends on if you're talking about the squirting universe or not.
Yeah, you know, we gotta be geniuses to come up with this stuff.
Church of the sub...
Genius!
Hey, there you go.
Church...
Jarebob Dobbs.
Church of the sub...
Genius.
Hey, there you go.
Now it's something...
You got it going right there?
I already said it.
It's becoming some kind of like...
Would it be in...
Might be a zombie.
Would it be in Pensacola?
No.
Cleveland?
Chicago?
No.
Pittsburgh?
Make it through Checkpoint Charlie by the skin of my teeth.
I know just how he feels, dear friends.
And now it's come to that time in the show when we turn to our book of kooks.
Our literal book called Kooks by Donna Cossie.
We'll give the address to right away for this.
This amazing book loaded with profiles of various...
What the normals might call extremist movements.
And, well, some geniuses.
Man, this is an amazing book.
And tonight we're going to be looking at Nation of Islam.
Yes, the section here which says that...
Nation of Islam.
Nation of Islam began much like Moorish science.
As an obscure cult known only to its members.
It was suddenly thrust into the national consciousness in the late 1950s and early 60s
when Malcolm X became its chief spokesman.
Now, much has been written about Nation of Islam and even more about Malcolm X.
And, you know, Malcolm X did leave that group before he was killed.
But it's evident that very few...
outside of the group have ever seen the writings of Elijah Muhammad
or examined the group's belief system in detail.
There's been more emphasis on the group's black nationalism than their religious beliefs
which may be too zany for the average social scientist to take seriously.
The founder of the Nation of Islam...
What was his name here?
W.D. Fard, I believe.
Yeah, W.D. Fard.
His formidable mission was to wake the dead nation in the West,
to teach them the truth about the white man,
and to prepare them for Armageddon.
His version of the Battle of Armageddon
had the war between the good black Muslims
and the evil white Christians
taking place in Har-Magedon,
the wilderness of North America.
Now, Fard disappeared,
but Elijah Muhammad took the thing over
and began teaching that Fard was God in person
to be worshipped as a deity with prayer and sacrifice.
Elijah Muhammad emphasized that Christianity,
the white man's religion,
teaches that God is a spook,
while Islam, the natural religion for the black man,
teaches that God is a man.
Evidently,
this teaching had great appeal.
In no time,
Elijah Muhammad was leading the nation of Islam
with a firm hand,
calling himself Allah's prophet and messenger.
If W.D. Fard's teachings have bite,
then Elijah Muhammad's have fangs.
Muhammad developed Fard's ideas in astounding detail,
accounting for the state of the world
as the product of the evil white race
and its hold on world power.
He taught that the original man is the black man,
and that he is the one who has the power
and that the white people are the result of a genetic plot
and have only been around for 6,000 years.
The, quote, so-called Negro, unquote,
came from the tribe of Shabazz within the Asiatic nation,
who originated in Africa when a great explosion
divided the Earth from the Moon 60 trillion years ago.
Members of this eminent tribe were the first explorers of Earth, and the first inhabitants of the planet.
They were the first to discover the existence of the Nile Valley.
Furthermore, they authored not only the Bible, but the Koran.
Elijah Muhammad's main text for the dissemination of his teachings,
Message to the Black Man in America,
tells the story of the grafting of the evil white race.
The woeful story begins 6,800 years ago,
when Yaqub, an evil scientist from Mecca,
angered the Meccan authorities and was exiled,
along with 59,000 people.
He sent 2,999 of his followers to an island in the Aegean Sea.
While in exile, he plotted his revenge.
He would enslave the tribe of Shabazz by breeding an evil white race
that would rule over them for 6,000 years.
He created the brown race from the black, using the old biblical method of infanticide.
Quote,
He ordered the nurses to kill all black babies
by pricking the brains with a sharp knife.
The black child's head is out of its mother.
When there was a birth of a brown baby,
the nurse would come and make much ado over it
and would tell the mother she'd given birth to a holy child
and that she would nurse it for the next six weeks,
for her child was going to be a great man.
Unquote.
Using the same method, 200 years later,
he created the red race from the brown,
and 200 years after that, the yellow race from the red.
Finally, after 600 years, his work was completed.
And he had created the white devils.
And as Elijah Muhammad said here,
the Yaqub-made devils were really pale white
with really blue eyes,
which we think are the ugliest of colors for a human eye.
These hateful creatures were exiled in West Asia, or Europe,
and became savages, remaining in that condition for 2,000 years.
As Elijah Muhammad says,
they lost all knowledge of civilization.
The Lord God of Islam taught me that some of them
tried to graft themselves back into the black nation,
but they had nothing to go by.
A few were lucky enough to make a start
and got as far as what you would call the gorilla.
In fact, all of the monkey family are from this 2,000 year history
of the white race in Europe.
So, uh, you know this stuff?
It proves what we've been saying all along.
All races are equal because they're all equally racist.
You know, this is exactly like old Ku Klux Klan type stuff.
Mirror image in reverse.
Man, if only the true teachings of the Yeti,
the birth of the true subgenius race,
the race that is the master race,
because it comes in all colors, all flavors, and all sexes.
Well, anyway, let's see.
Um, according to further teachings of Nation of Islam here,
after 2,000 years, Allah raised Moses to civilize the white race,
who found his job quite difficult.
After the process of civilization,
the white devils fulfilled Yaqub's vengeance
by enslaving the tribe of Shabazz.
Fortunately, the end of this sad chapter of history is now in sight.
The 6,000 year white rule
ended in 1914.
We are now living in the post-1914 years of grace,
which will last until the chosen of Allah
will be resurrected from the mental death
imposed upon them by the white man.
Achieving this resurrection was the holy mission
of Elijah Muhammad, messenger of Allah
and the spiritual leader of the lost found nation in the West.
He died in 1975,
but his mission is being carried on
by Louis Farrakhan,
whose name you may recognize.
He's been in the news quite a bit.
Louis Farrakhan, who succeeded Malcolm X
as the group's spokesman,
resurrected the old Nation of Islam.
Elijah Muhammad is alive and well
in the hearts of the followers of Louis Farrakhan,
and not just in their hearts.
He flies to Earth from time to time
aboard a giant flying saucer,
occasionally summoning Farrakhan
to receive his instructions.
So claims the notorious minister Farrakhan.
He became a household word in 1984
when he was accused of making anti-Semitic remarks.
But he is leading something like 50,000 followers,
and his devotion to even the most obscure teachings
of Elijah Muhammad is reflected in his belief
in flying saucers,
as Ezekiel's visioned.
We quote Louis Farrakhan,
The great wheel that many of us see in the sky today
is not so much a wheel as one may think in such terms,
but rather a place made like a wheel.
The like of this wheel-like plane
was never seen before.
You cannot build one like it and get the same results.
Okay, today we see the white race preparing
for the sky battle to determine
who shall remain and rule this Earth.
Black or white.
The present wheel-shaped plane,
known as the Mother of Planes,
is one half mile by a half mile,
and is the largest mechanical man-made object in the sky.
It is a small human planet,
made for the purpose of destroying
the present world of enemies of Allah.
The small circular-made planes called flying saucers,
which are so much talked of being seen,
could be from this Mother Plane.
This is only one of the things in store
for the white man's evil world.
Believe it or not,
this is to warn you and me
to fly to our own God and people.
And, uh,
Elijah Muhammad has evidently taken residence
on that mother ship, dear friends,
in order to direct the proceedings
that will end the 6,000 year rule of the white devils.
Which I suppose includes, uh, yours truly.
According to these guys.
On October 24th, 1989,
Louis Farrakhan held a press conference
in which he detailed his September 1985 vision
that he was carried to a mountain
in Tepoztlan, Mexico,
and then to Elijah Muhammad's mother ship.
As we reached the top of the mountain,
a wheel, or what you call an unidentified flying object,
appeared at the side of the mountain
and called me to come up into the wheel.
A beam of light came from the wheel,
and I was carried up on this beam of light
into the wheel.
And it moved up to the mother wheel,
the human-built planet.
At the center of the ceiling was a speaker,
and through the speaker I heard the voice
of the Honorable Elijah Muhammad
speaking to me as clearly as you are hearing
my voice this morning.
Mr. Muhammad began to speak to me.
He said,
President Reagan has met with the Joint Chiefs of Staff
to plan a war.
I want you to go hold a press conference
in Washington, D.C., and announce their plan,
and say to the world that you got the information
from me on the wheel.
So friends, we're sharing that information with you.
A recent issue of the Nation of Islam newsletter
reveals a government plot to institute a new world order
which may involve alien beings and so-called UFOs,
which are in fact created by the government.
So, dear friends,
the world of kooks and crackpots and crazies,
you know, they come in all kinds,
and you can get the book of kooks by Donna Cossey,
probably in better bookstores,
but you can also inquire from,
here, got that pencil ready,
Ferral House, F-E-R-A-L, House,
P.O. Box 3466, Portland, Oregon.
That's P.O. Box 3466, Portland, or 97208.
97208.
There for Ferral House Press book kooks,
and let's go visit some of our very favorite kooks now,
why don't we?
We'll be right back.
If Circle K sells a thousand gallons of slush puppy,
we shall sell ten thousand gallons.
If Stax Stax Stax sells ten thousand gallons of slush puppy,
we shall sell a hundred thousand gallons of icy.
If Circle K sells a million gallons of icy,
We shall sell ten million gallons.
We shall give our IC away if necessary, but we shall not be outsold.
Not a single 7-Eleven employee's hand shall reach out to help them.
Not a single truck stop or a vegan sandwich shall feed the enemy.
They shall find nothing but the scorched earth.
But, my dear, your scorched earth policy would mean the death of the Southland Corporation and the destruction of 7-Eleven.
Swine! The war has taken the strongest ones.
The fate of the weaklings who survived this war is of little consequence to me.
Everywhere I look, I am surrounded by liars, traitors, hypocrites, murderers.
No one can stop me.
And those who seek to stab me in the back.
I lived a life of hard work and sacrifice with a convenient rock movement.
It was the sacrifice of others, of course, and included the deaths of hundreds of millions of innocent people.
While I lived in an air-conditioned smart-town apartment.
But it was sacrifice nonetheless.
I could have been the master of the world.
But I did not know the meaning of the word capitulate.
None!
The word capitulation is not in our vocabulary.
If we are to fail, if we are defeated, we shall drag down with us a world in flames.
A world in flames!
Behold the symbol we have unleashed.
We follow God through our path in the presence of these save lives.
I also have the power of the good God, I have the power of peace with hisbereant and
All skills, all intelligence, all power are attached to the army of Господь and his
It is not easy figure out stronyave,удь simplemente länguisे.
someone's countermeector bringen и
convenience is something.
We're in conquest.
Action!
We have the edge of making you rock.
We are not iron men.
We are made of iron.
Iron!
Oh, man.
Got it.
Sorry, Janer.
Janer Hypercletes, their dear friends
and Southland Corporation
at the forefront of convenience rock.
And you can write to Janer Hypercletes
for information on his tapes.
I think they're six bucks.
That's Janer Hypercletes
at 8701 Evergreen.
Little Rock.
Arkansas.
72207.
Once again, that's Janer Hypercletes.
8701 Evergreen.
Little Rock, Arkansas.
72204.
And this might be a good time
to break in with the Church of the Subgenius.
Church of the Subgenius address.
You've got that pencil ready, dear friends.
If you...
could but...
address that...
self-addressed stamped envelope or whatever,
you know,
if you want to know a little bit more
about what this particular religious take on the world is,
I think perhaps one or two of you...
You, you.
Yeah, that one.
You do.
Well, you.
Pick that pencil up and write to Bob.
That's right, just Bob.
As long as you get the rest of this right,
it'll get to it.
It's a post office box.
1-4-0-3-0-6.
Easy enough.
Box 1-4-0-3-0-6.
Bob at Box 1-4-0-3-0-6.
The zip code is 75214.
I remember that.
It's Bob.
Peel Box 1-4-0-3-0-6.
And it's 75214
for the zip code.
And, uh...
We got Bob,
Peel Box 1-4-0-3-0-6.
Pittsburgh.
No, not Pittsburgh.
That's probably something like this.
J.R. Bob Dobbs,
Church of the Subgenius,
in...
San Francisco?
No.
Too hip.
Let me see.
We need something down to home.
We need Tulsa.
In the south.
Yeah, in the south.
Not Little Rock, though.
That's too obvious.
No, not Little Rock.
J.R. Bob Dobbs,
and the Church of the Subgenius,
in...
Mexico City.
Okay, J.R. Bob Dobbs,
Church of the Subgenius.
It's gotta be in the south.
It's not Atlanta.
It's not New Orleans.
It's not Baton Rouge.
It's not Orlando, Florida,
or anything like that.
It's gotta be in...
We want something...
Where there's cats.
The South Pole, all the way south.
San Antonio?
State, Texas.
You got the right state there.
J.R. Bob Dobbs,
Church of the Subgenius,
in Amarillo.
It just doesn't sound right.
What's the name of that...
Oh, uh...
What's that?
It wouldn't be Dallas.
Big D, Big D.
What is it?
Dallas, Texas.
Just south of Bob.
Bob in Dallas.
Just south of Bobtown.
Hey.
Kennedy.
Kennedy was shot in Dallas.
The grassy knoll.
The grassy...
Lee Harvey Oswald.
The book repository.
Uh, no, no, no.
It's not so funny, man.
No more of that.
One little bit of news of the weird
here.
I just...
I just noticed.
This is from Chuck Shepard's
News of the Weird.
Uh, for those of you
with tape decks on,
that's P.O. Box 8306,
St. Petersburg, Florida,
33738.
Anyway, he...
This is a nice, uh,
crackpot sort of, uh,
news story here.
Least competent person.
In Fort Lauderdale, Florida,
in February,
accused murderer
Donald Leroy Evans, 38,
filed a pretrial motion
asking permission
to wear a Ku Klux Klan robe
in the courtroom
and be referred to
in legal documents
by the honorable
and respected name
of High Hitler.
That's H-I...
One...
One word.
Hitler.
According to courthouse employees
interviewed by the Associated Press,
Evans thought
Adolf Hitler's followers
were saying
High Hitler
rather than
Heil Hitler.
But we carry on
regardless.
We carry on
and on
and we're dancing
to the beat
of the drunk drama.
The drunk drama.
A little bit of slouch
here.
A little bit of slouch here.
The drunk m zwar.
crime.
Two hours and seven minutes.
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
Oh, man, wonderful. Crazy Creep there.
I guess that's a hymn for subgeniuses, inadvertently, by the Merkins,
where they are at 618 Western Avenue, Madison, Wisconsin, 53711.
The Kooks can be your very, very good friends, you know.
Friends.
He is the person who deserves the society.
He is the one that corrupts and kills our youth.
He is the one that sends us to the devil.
Satan, Satan, he is the one who killed us all.
Satan is the lord of all evil.
He is the demon of magic, Father Grace.
Satan, have you seen the man who is in the labors,
corrupting and raping all these people that want to kill and destroy
and the lustful man of the world doing their crime?
Satan, Satan, he will kill and destroy.
He's going to have to release the infected.
Satan, Satan, Satan, the holy Satan can make you and bring you down
and take you away from the Lord Jesus Christ.
Oh, he, the Lord Jesus Christ is the only one that can save you.
Oh, he, the Lord Jesus Christ will save you.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Satan is the killer.
Satan is the one who will bring you down.
Satan is the bad one.
Jesus Christ.
And old Bob, he'll just stand by and watch.
Couldn't hardly do a show like this one without Church of Newfoundland.
Hey, there in Virginia Beach, Virginia, 23450, P.O. Box 9152.
And with Chris Cordes, demons in my head.
No, they're in my CD player, actually, is where they are.
And, oh, the corruptigating worms have tried to stop us, my friends.
But, and it's been tough, I'll tell you.
It's been a very difficult week around here.
You can hear the zombies working so hard in the background,
trying to get our mailing out.
And, but, but, but we're going to keep trying.
I ain't going to let you down.
You ain't going to be let down by your old friend, Reverend,
Reverend, it's on this tape, I think.
Reverend.
Okay, we got it.
We got to change his name to Kaivin Blank.
We got to think of a name for him.
Spank?
No, not Spank.
Igor Spank.
Reverend Igor Spank.
So Spank would be just, you know, Spanky, you know.
It's got to be Russian.
It's got to be totalitarian.
Oh, yeah.
Vladimir.
Vladimir Spank.
And we got to get the Jewish thing.
What was the name of that one guy that tortured everybody?
Ivan the Terrible.
Spank.
J.R. Bob Dobbs, Church of the Subgenius in Dallas, Texas.
Ivan Spank.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Not Spank.
It's not perfect.
We need that.
Look into your soul, Jane, or you know it's not perfect.
I don't have a soul.
I've already sold out.
J.R. Bob Dobbs, Church of the Subgenius in Dallas, Texas.
Ivan.
Starn?
We got to get the Jewish thing in there.
Oh, man.
Stein.
Stank.
Stanky.
Wouldn't he and the Little Rascals?
No, that was Spanky.
We can't use that.
They probably got it copyrighted.
J.R. Bob Dobbs, Church of the Subgenius.
There's a big bang.
Reverend Ivers.
Big bang.
Stank.
Stang.
Bang.
Very good.
Like a gang bang, a stang.
Yeah.
We got to make him right on the tip of our tongue.
We need some kind of heretical offshoot.
Yeah.
Like a golfer's head.