Truth is, this is the Ornette Lena.
Whoever named the Canadian River found his ex-wife and remarried her, but his wife would have none of it.
The Ornette Lena.
In a moment, I'll tell you the incredible story of the longest and shortest mold.
They both lived to celebrate somewhere else.
The Ornette Lena.
Alright, go ahead.
I don't know what to do, Joe.
I got no place to turn. There's nothing I can do.
Well, come on. What's it all about?
Who do you talk to when you find out your son's an addict?
When did you first figure that he might be using narcotics?
He's a dope addict, Joe.
That's all I can do to keep my hands off him.
Alright, now what's he done, Ed?
First, I couldn't believe it, but tonight Ellen and I went to his room.
We found this.
Where'd you find this, Ed?
In his room.
I had it hidden up on the shelf in his closet. I found it tonight.
Looks like a...
Some genius!
Power of...
What?
Why?
Stang has proven hardy.
But Stang has...
The chances of him...
Who?
Stang.
From the Spanish, Miss Daniel.
Meaning untamed.
Stang weakening.
All for the sake of money.
And you know it.
You've taken him so very far, stud.
Pull out now, Stang.
And I'll come, stud.
Are you willing to kill him?
Fuck, Stang.
Pull out now, Stang.
And I'll come.
Preaching on sex.
Think about romance.
Think about fatal attractions.
You will groan when your flesh and body are spent.
The lips drip honey.
Honey.
Drink cum.
Great job.
A relationship.
Sex.
May your fountain be blessed.
May her breath satisfy you at all times.
To have a growing erection.
Let me share with you today.
Enter into the arena of sex.
Sex.
Sexual.
You know what?
Every now and then I just have to come.
Are you ready?
So beautiful and so harmless and so wonderful.
Sexual landmine.
Word and a flatter.
Listen to me, fellas.
I want every guy in the room to lock eyes with me for just a second.
Lush in your heart.
Your words say no, but your eyes say yes.
Look lustfully at a woman, at a girl.
Sexual landmine.
Maximize.
Listen well to my words of insight.
Smoother, smoother than oil.
I got news for you.
Are you listening?
Can anyone help me?
Do you have any suggestions?
If you love me.
Love Bob, come with me.
Yes, that was a wonderful number by our orchestra organist, Raymond Price, here on the Bob Hour.
Yes, yes ladies and gentlemen.
We're glad to have you here.
My wife, Zelma.
Our dog, Snavely.
Did you tell him about Bob?
Okay, sit down everybody.
Can you hear me?
Can you hear me out there?
Yeah, yeah, I think it's time for a song.
Ladies and gentlemen, do you want to hear a song?
Bob sucks.
Crump his ass.
Kill him.
Dog guanubisантes.
Fuckin' know-it-normal GADA sustan-
Careful, my young students.
You cannot stay in this state all day.
Why not?
Yeah why not?
It is inevitable that you are drawn back into human drama.
Desire.
Suffering.
Everything that exists in this imperfect world.
Shit.
So we get drawn back into human drama, and how important we think that is.
Then we do crazy stuff.
We have to go back to the ball so we can get the freedom of being like a, like a dish of
multi.
Yes.
And then back into the heaven.
back to the drama, the suffering.
It's kind of a crappy deal.
C'est exactement ça.
An absurd theatrical we must play out
back and forth from pure being to human suffering.
But isn't the drama and suffering less
if we do the ball thing every day?
Don't call it the ball thing.
Call it pure being.
Well, doesn't the pure being ball thing
make the day-to-day suffering easier?
No, it doesn't.
You're wrong.
No, we're going to do this every day
and we'll show you it'll make it easier.
I'll prove it to you.
Human drama is inevitable.
Suffering cannot be diminished.
You cannot escape, Tommy.
You'll see.
Existence is a cruel joke
that entices in a form of desire.
It's a theater of desire.
My little body hurts.
It's painful.
Mr. Data,
what do you know of homosexuality?
Intriguing.
Accessing.
It appears to be a means of pleasuring
between two males.
But I am curious as to why you should ask me such a question.
Mr. Data,
as your commanding officer,
you must obey any order
no matter how deranged or insane I choose to give.
That is correct, sir.
Federation dictates it.
Mr. Data,
I'm going to take down
my Starfleet regulation issue trousers
and when I do,
I want you to
drive me home.
I must obey any order you give me.
Make it so.
Engage.
Must stop.
You must stop or you will hurt the captain.
You have killed the captain.
You have ruptured him in two.
It's cleft.
Nine out of ten top Hollywood stars
depend on facials to keep their skin
just right for the camera.
There's a reason why this fragrant white facial
is the choice of lovely,
lovely women everywhere.
In recent tests,
facials really make skin lovelier
in a short time.
Really?
The right care for delicate skin.
I am the key master.
I am the gatekeeper.
One of the men of sedentary...
Breckenrod.
trouble.
Riw Quando você chega emirante
y vamos doctorando
em REMIDşam que não dorme nhưng
ath skirts
iceberg
long
and incorrect
Jaw absolutely
long
speed
Sing when I want
No need to say please to no man for a happy tune
Oh, I love my Rosie child
She got the way to make me happy
You and me, we're going in style
Cracklin' Rosie, you're a storm-eyed woman
You make me sing like a guitar strummin'
Bring on your baby girl, the song keeps runnin'
Oh
Play it now, play it now, play it now
Oh my baby
Cracklin' Rosie, make me smile
Girl, if it lasts for an hour, well, that's all right
We got all night
To set the world right
Find us a dream, but don't ask no questions
Yeah
Oh, I love my Rosie child
You got the way to make me happy
Yeah
You and me, we're going in style
Cracklin' Rosie, you're a storm-eyed woman
You make me sing like a guitar strummin'
Bring on your baby girl, the song keeps runnin'
Oh
Cracklin' Rosie by the Rudy Schwartz Project.
You can learn more about the Rudy Schwartz Project CVs.
There are quite a few of them from schwartztone.com.
We'll give that address again later.
This is a sexy hour of slack.
Dear friends, number 1068, Bob Corb, baby.
I'm going to do the credits differently this time.
I've got to prepare my online course in subgeniusness with Maybe Logic Academy.
I'm Professor Stang now, and I'm in a big hurry.
That's maybelogic.org, by the way.
Anyway, the show started with Lee Murr, as always, just about always.
One of his intro cut-ups.
The Geeks of Dubious Sexuality helped us out there with a little Stangian cut-up.
Noriel Preff did a great job.
And the Bob hour there was Sterno, Pope Sterno Docs and Doctors for Bob from Media Barrage No. 4 in 1981 or something.
A little clip from a movie called I Heart Huckabees,
which is wonderful.
Wonderful movie.
The tasteless Star Trek cut was from National Cynical Network, and there will be more of that.
And there is more of that at nationalcynical.com.
Lee Murr did some facials.
And friends, that's about it.
In fact, he's going to do a little bit more of facializing here.
Back to now Lee Murr.
Everyone loves him.
I'm going to keep talking.
I'm going to talk a lot.
There you go Mr. Cr mascotta.
As he does things and says weird things.
And goodbye take home benny.
Get down this.
Be careful with that ear right there.
Can't hear you?
All right.
So you hipster chicks got over 50 pairs of dark martins,
throw those cuties under 110 in five four.
That's right, if you're under 18 and got the face of a China
dog and never much cared for guys your own age,
then Uncle Bob's is the place.
Gonna lay down like this now and look up some skirts.
Oh, yeah.
Danny's not loud, and Uncle Bob's no sort of under way loud.
I'm the coolest cat's this side of the Rio.
If you're missing a wiener and don't like school,
then don't be a fool.
Get on down, down up here to the Stink Finger Cafe.
Open 10 AM till 2 PM every weekday
by special permission of the government state
licensing board.
An oasis of fresh butterfly lips and adolescent sweater fruit,
all ripe and throbbing for Uncle Bob
and his heavy meat crystal.
Yes.
Oh.
Don't be scared, lovely ladies.
That's just a little bug that hangs out of my mouth,
kicking back on the flip side.
Hey, y'all.
My name is Bug.
I like to drink something red.
It has a sort of funny smell.
And it comes from a hot horn.
But I can't tell you where that horn is.
I like to laugh at celebrity suicide.
I like it when little children are used as human shields.
I'm the one who shot Kennedy.
Me, Bug, and not me, Harvey Asbach.
I'm the one who should be praying to God.
Baby, no!
No!
I want everyone to die so they can all go back
to heaven and relax.
I'm tired of wearing this body.
Have to feed it.
Have to keep it moist.
Have to constantly protect it from those who want to hurt Bug
or eat him.
Also, I get these terrible pains in my anal region
that hurt really bad.
Let it make good things.
I have a green slimy snot gush out of my butt
and this causes hemorrhoids.
And because I'm a bug and not a dog or person,
I can't reach back and scratch them.
And they itch terribly.
I have to get back to Uncle Bob's mouth now
so I can rub my butt across one of his teeth
and leave bloody poopy smears.
Yeah, whoever smelt it just does it.
Just yesterday, a friend of mine sniffed out a tropical tree
some hundred yards away, exclaiming about the power of the scent.
I smelled nothing.
Does he have a history of this in his family?
Until I pushed, well, her family.
I pushed one of the deep creamy white blossoms
flush with my nose.
And then I detected only a mild musky odor.
I'm sorry, but it is the same when we go mushrooming as well.
You mushrooming?
You know?
A mushrooming problem.
She's always the first to realize that stinkhorns are about.
All right, now stop right there.
Stinkhorns, as you may know, are very dramatic mushrooms
with names like Phallus impudicus.
Yes, they're the drama queens of the fungal world.
Which erect from the soil in a form so true to their name
that is scarcely credible
and whose aroma brings in sticky-footed flies.
Which will then disperse their spores.
And the point of all this is...
I usually see them as soon as I smell them.
Our difference in olfactory acumen has nothing to do with, say,
the considerable difference in the size of our respective proboscis.
Don't underestimate the humble fly.
Just let me get my sleeping bag packed up here.
Yes, I wish you'd quit fidgeting.
We're trying to get some...
Whoa!
No, he's rolled into the...
That's terrible. I'm sorry.
Now you're sleeping...
How are you going to sleep in a wet sleeping bag?
I'll have to find somebody with a dry sleeping bag.
A warm, dry bag.
Try those little children over there in that campsite
that doesn't have any...
Pants?
Any pants on it.
I'll have to get them out of bed.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'll try and get them out of bed.
A little frotter so-dy noise there.
Actually, I have no idea if that's the way his name is pronounced,
or if he's even a he,
but I'm pretty sure he is.
Anyway, before that puzzling,
evidence from KPFA in Berkeley
with Dr. Howell and Dr. Philo Drummond,
and you can find all kinds of that sort of thing
by way of quiveringbrain.com.
That's Philo's website.
Before that, Uncle Bob and Bug
was from National Cynical Network.
See nationalcynical.com for more of that,
thanks to Phineas and Arco.
And now let us hie to 9X Day
for the oracle that we call the...
Ask Dr. Howell Show.
Here's one that will require visual aids, I think.
Oh, all right.
What is the nature of the symbol atop this staff?
See brandished item.
Oh, well, will you look at that.
The Leaston Fellow brandishing a...
What a beautiful staff it is.
That's what she said.
A staff of the Masonic Order
from a symbolic...
activity performed by the nobles of the Masonic Temple.
And the crescent of the Masonic Order
is there with three links attached to it.
Now for those three links,
you would have to go into,
or perhaps past,
weirdos like Manly Palmer Hall,
who said in his book,
The Secret Teaching of All Ages,
that these three links completely were equivalent
to the Christian faith, hope, charity,
or the Trinity,
itself of the Father, Son, and the Holy Ghost.
But, of course, anything might be possible.
The central figure is time.
And this shows that this primitive precursor
to the Church of the Subgenius,
the Masonic Order,
was also concerned with the problem of time control,
one which, as subgeniuses,
concerns us all.
By the way, that Manly P. Hall's
classic book of...
kind of an occult encyclopedia
is now
free online.
But that isn't as fun as the huge,
bad-smelling book itself
with a black leather cover
that you have to
haul down and open up.
Actually, my dad
gave me his guilt-edged
copy of that book.
He had the deluxe copy.
It's a really important book
to those of us who have put together subgenius books.
It is proto-subgenius stuff.
We do not so much stand on the shoulders
of giants as we hump furiously
at the backs of the necks of giants.
And Manly P. Hall
is one of those giants.
If you ever get a chance to look through
his huge book,
which is half illustrations,
it may answer some of the questions
you've wondered about
looking through the book of the subgenius
in Revelation X.
As above, so below.
Well, many of the figures in his giant text
have to do with Alcanon,
which is the alchemical symbology
and allegory.
And what's odd is the sort of weak
namby-pamby way they're shown
instead of the vigor of the actual alchemical texts
and books if you look at them
or if you see them.
I will say this.
If you are thinking of starting your own religion,
Manly P. Hall's
Secret Wisdom of All Ages
is a great handbook.
He's been there.
Yeah.
In all of them.
Excuse me, Lieutenant.
You seem to have lost the will
to communicate with others.
Though,
there was a young lady from Venus
whose body was shaped like a...
I do not enjoy riddles.
Did I say something wrong?
It is a secret note only to Klingons.
You have friends here.
With all due respect,
this very person here
is difficult to say.
Words are not always easy for me.
Be gone!
I care about you.
Enough!
Of course, but
I am programmed in multiple techniques.
For what we consider love, sir,
I would need a Klingon woman.
A broad variety of pleasuring.
Klingons do not allow themselves to be
probes.
It could be a dangerous mission.
Shall we begin?
It is very difficult to say.
But I know you will do the right thing.
I am ready.
Today,
I am a warrior.
I must show you my heart.
I travel
the river of blood.
Open.
No!
Please,
be quick.
Wait!
It is a long mission.
I am a big dog.
The true test of Klingon strength
is to admit one's most profound feelings
while under extreme duress.
Thank you.
Captains of security, come in!
This is truly trying my patience.
So,
you should get into uniform.
Don't pull your love out on me, baby
If you do, then I think that maybe
I'll just lay me down, cry for a hundred years
Don't pull your love out on me, honey
Take my heart, my soul, my money
But don't leave me here drowning in my tears
You say you're gonna leave
Gonna take that big wide turn
Gonna fly right out of here
Without a single word
But you know you'll break my heart
When I watch you close that door
Cause I know I won't see you anymore
Don't pull your love out on me, baby
If you do, then I think that maybe
I'll just lay me down, cry for a hundred years
Don't pull your love out on me, honey
Take my heart, my soul, my money
But don't leave me here drowning
In my tears
Haven't I been good to you?
What about that brand new ring?
Doesn't that mean love to you?
Oh, doesn't that mean anything?
If I throw away my pride
And I got down on my knees
Would you beg me back, you worthy please?
There's so much I wanna do
I've got love enough for two
But I'll never choose a girl if I don't have you
Push it in, pull it in
Every gal in town is a girl
After little Goop Goop
He's the biggest Yoo-hoo
Trimming, kissing, birdie women
But they whisper, what's your secret fashion?
Little Abner says, Bart
We call Great Spirit
Where's the axe?
I love Goop Goop
I don't care
I'm coming
Well, it's about time
More poke, he's stupid
Big lummet
Stink, poke the lunch
Poke, bob, bob
The
You mean that big handsome boy?
Bob
Oh
Oh, my
I'll never be able to understand technique
Big sloppy
Oh
Quit complaining, Lucifer
Bob
Bob, Bob, sweet patootie
Come on, stick it out
Stick it way out
I'm gonna make love to her like she always wanted me to
Most ignorant as critter I ever did see
I'm gonna make love to you
Powerful, romantic love
Enormous corn porn
He's heard
Bart, Bart, Bart, Bart
AMY
Um
Jake
Damn
Close
Yo
of the time, I guess.
I'm in the other 20%, friends.
So thanks to Mula Mutata for the
movie clips, and before that,
The Pork was by
Norrell Preff, and is from the
1940 Little Abner
movie.
Rudy Schwartz Project did
Don't Pull Your Love,
and Data and Worf
Have Sex was courtesy
of National Cynical
Network.
And now,
more Dr. Howell on
sexual dimorphism.
Millions of years ago,
giant
dinosaurs roamed
the earth.
The Atlantosaurus
stretched out its long neck,
its tiny eyes
darting to and fro
as it
its wet and wide mouth
opened, who
roar
inanely in the Jurassic
Song.
Now, what of
dimorphism, sexual
dimorphism, in the
dwarf male,
in humans?
Hmm?
No.
What is this twilight world,
this world that fears a rising
sun?
In snow geese, which nest
in tightly packed colonies,
it has been shown that mated
males will try to force
to might on neighboring
female.
They defend their own female
mate until all her eggs are laid.
Oh shut up・ ! died ? Oh shut up !!"
And then they make attempts on nearby females.
This mixed strategy might result in their fertilizing only one more egg on average,
or sometimes even less, but this is still a significant genetic payoff.
Access to eggs can be achieved by less overt methods than goose race, gift-giving, or bloody combat.
There is a strategy that seems almost unbeatable, and I wonder why.
Ignominious though it may seem, more males have not pursued it.
It is to become a resident dwarf.
Some males become miniaturized, living inside or on the females as a portable sperm bank.
Darwin discovered this strategy when he worked on barnacle taxonomy.
In some species, he found the males had degenerated into...
tiny, teensy, weensy, almost parasitic forms consisting of little more than reproductive organs,
with a crude physiology supporting testicles.
These degenerate males led some observers to claim that the females were hermaphrodites,
or as said in the east coast of the Americas, morphodites.
But actually, the male has evolved to become almost...
purely a copulatory organ, permanently lodged in residence.
Do I have to draw you a picture?
This kind of strategy has led to some of the more extreme forms of sexual dimorphism.
In the vertebrates and the insects, extreme sexual dimorphism normally is because of selection for the male fighting and weaponry used to acquire a harem.
When a male opts for an unshakable monogamy,
the opposite dimorphism is the opposite.
The opposite dimorphism develops.
One well-known case is the marine echeroid worm, Bonelia, common in the rocky bays of the Pacific Northwest and in the Mediterranean.
When young Bonelia hatch, they are sexually undifferentiated, free-swimming larvae.
The transformation of their tabula rasa is effected by the bottom on which they settle.
If it is unoccupied, the larva becomes a female.
She grows into what is essentially a giant tongue, almost three feet long, with a walnut-sized body at one end.
She uses her huge proboscis to pick up food from the bottom around her.
Males originate when a larva smells the scent of the female's outsized tongue.
If undifferentiated larvae are placed in an aquarium with chopped-up female tongue,
or an extract of the proboscis, they change into tiny males, scarcely more than 1 20th of an inch long.
In nature, the dwarf male settles on a female proboscis, transforms, then lodges himself in his mate's uterus or beside it.
There he remains for life, leaking out sperm at appropriate moments.
This strategy is known for marine sow bugs.
And for some nematodes, parasitic in rat bladders.
But it is not only of the lowly orders.
There are dwarf male fish.
Various species of deep-sea angler fish are dramatically dimorphic.
The female is a fearsome-looking predator of the abysmal, dark, lower reaches of the ocean.
She has a thick-set body with massive jaws, well armed with teeth and a luminous lure.
This latter wobbly, wiggly appendage is an organ developed from the first spine on her dorsal fin,
which projects out in front of her toothy mouth and blinks, luring inquisitive victims.
Male angler fish are so completely different that some were classified as separate species,
until taxonomists discovered them in connection with their female mates.
The male starts off as an unremarkable, surface-dwelling young fish.
But after a while, he develops immense nostrils.
And instead of a luminous lure, he grows a special tooth-bearing bone from his first dorsal spine.
His mission is to find, perhaps smell out, a female and clamp securely onto her.
In some cases, the attachment becomes permanent.
The male literally becomes part of the female.
He grows into her in such a way that their circulatory systems fuse,
and the male's mouthparts are completely useless for feeding.
He depends entirely on the female.
Presumably, he even reads the hormonal messages of her bloodstream,
to determine when he is to, uh, let go his cloud of sperm in one ecstatic moment.
Gah!
The dwarf male has traded mobility,
and the opportunity for multiple mates for a relatively secure monogamy.
This strategy has been explained as an adaptation to females that are rare and widely dispersed.
But it argues against the virtues of monogamy for the male individual,
since it shows that its evolutionary end is a degenerate dependence, even parasitism.
This will be the case,
where the environment has a low energy level,
and the male is not able to
have a large energy content, such as the dark, deep sea.
But where there is still fecundity,
selection on females to be large.
Normally, the larger a female, the more eggs she can lay.
Huge size, however, will not help a male get more mates when they are rare and widespread.
His mission is simply to find one and stick to it.
Thus, in the kinds of anglerfish and relatives that are common on coral reefs,
or in the icheroid worms that feed by moving about and have a high rate of encounter,
dwarf males simply do not exist.
The male then becomes a tiny resident,
not as a convenience to the female, but simply because this has been the most successful male tactic.
It is a female dispersion,
and the ability of males to control the precious few large female gametes
that make males into chest-thumping gorilla boys,
or degenerate dwarfs.
For the better and the best is the bearer of superfluous and tiny gametes.
The body is only a secondary concern.
Access is all.
This has been an essay on the natural history of sex.
Join us next week
as I, Dr. Howland Owl,
will continue to explain
the mystery of the birds and the bees.
See you then.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
www.amara.org
www.amara.org.co.uk
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
Uhhhh...
Delicious.
More urine, please.
Mr. Worf, you have drank all the yak urine we can synthesize.
Our replicators are breaking down.
Ch-chaw.
Mr. Worf.
But it is a warrior's drink.
I'm going to have my diarrhea beamed directly to your plate.
Hm, excellent.
You honor me.
Mr. O'Brien, engage.
Right, two second delay.
No, no, now.
Do it now.
Right, now in two seconds.
No, engage now, engage.
Right, in two seconds, engage.
No, not two seconds, engage.
Not two seconds, two seconds, engage.
Right, engaging.
Mmm, our ch-chaw.
It is a warrior's dish.
Captain, I need you in my quarters.
Make it so.
I need you to help me with the ancient ritual of Huck to Clock or Klingon Buttsex.
Hm.
Computer.
Lubricant.
Irregrate.
Warm.
Hm.
Huck to Cluck.
Ahhh.
What have you done to the captain?
I haven't, I, I don't know.
You appear to have ruptured the captain completely.
I am now commander of the Enterprise.
I believe you need me to help you.
What about number one?
He will be my number two, if you get my meaning.
That was a joke.
Oh.
All right, what's going on in here?
You are no longer in command, Mr. Riker.
What do you mean?
Data, what's wrong with you?
I'm going to have to drop my trousers.
I will hold him.
No, what?
Oh, no, please!
Oh, God, Lord, no, please, Jesus!
I have ejaculated over 1,600 cubic milliliters of my own hydraulic fluid into his mouth,
effectively killing him.
You have dishonored him.
You're next, Klingon.
Oh, I mean, good job.
Do-wop-da-maga-maga, do-wop-da-maga-maga, do-wop-da-maga-maga,
do-wop-da-maga-maga, do-wop-da-maga-maga, do-wop-da-maga-maga,
do-wop, ba-ba.
Do-wop-da-maga-maga, do-wop-da-maga-maga, do-wop-da-maga-maga, do-wop.
Snuggly-maga, cuddly-maga, snuggly-maga.
Strip-nagged, you sweet maggot.
Pretty children all clap and sing.
All the bong-beams smack and ring.
I get so hot watching brown eyeballs rot.
Strip-nagged, you sweet maggot.
Lovely maggot, oh, so sweet.
Well, strip maggot, you sweet maggot, all the stars are shining bright.
Strip maggot, you sweet maggot, two mezzanine pearly white.
Jump, jump, strolling down the lane, to a happy refrain.
Strip maggot, you sweet maggot, lovely maggot, oh so sweet.
Gorgeous white dipped hair is larva.
Larva, germ spreading grub of my dreams.
I'll pour the wine while you court me with your slime.
Slug the maggot, slug the maggot, slug the maggot, slug the maggot.
Do-wop-ga-magga-magga, do-wop-ga-magga-magga, do-wop-ga-magga-magga-do.
Strip maggot, you sweet maggot, pretty maggot walk by my side.
Strip maggot, you sweet maggot, gonna make you my maggot bride.
Mend all my socks while we do the maggot rock.
Strip maggot, you sweet maggot.
Maggot, oh so sweet.
Lovely maggot.
Maggot.
Maggot, oh so sweet.
Joe Newman, the Rudy Schwartz Project.
Who else?
More on that at schwartztone.com.
Before that, the tasteless Star Trek from nationalcynical.com.
Thanks to Phineas Narco for that.
The background music.
The background music right now was by me, Reverend Ivan Stang.
The Bach that we heard earlier, jazzy Bach, was by Kenneth New at www.kenneth.nu.
And Norrell Preff of norrellpreff.com did the cut-up.
And now for such cut-ups, we use metal grinding tools.
The communication.
Of metallic communion.
The ecstasy of mechanism.
Holding or mounting your work rigidly for checking, milling, drilling, shaping, grinding.
Boring.
Welding and pattern making.
Yes, a quick, accurate adjustment to any desired angle.
Set with protractor.
Easy to use.
Three standard sizes.
Experiments were also made.
With this blade set up as a trepanning tool and a drill press.
It was found that only small discs could be cut out efficiently
because the equipment became too heavy for enough stiffness to cut out the larger discs.
Also, it was too messy a job because the white facing of the cardboard became soiled from oil and dirt.
Cutting out by hand as described was the best way.
And of course, there was always the grinding of the small rods.
The large ones ultimately give out, while the small ones continue.
And give the most satisfaction.
Or so I've always been told by kind people.
You hurt my feelings.
I'm sorry.
But you had to do it anyway, didn't you?
She's a very powerful person and I have lived with a lot of women.
Obviously.
And she used me to teach us about the inevitability of human drama.
So?
Is that where you get off the ride?
Hell no.
I didn't think so.
Looks like you saw some truth.
What'd you see?
Well, the interconnection thing is definitely for real.
It is! I didn't think it was! It is!
I can't believe it! It's so fantastic!
It's amazing.
I know.
But it's also nothing special.
Yeah, because it grows from the manure of human trouble.
You see, the detectives, they just wanted to gloss right over that.
But in fact, no manure, no magic.
Did you hear some of that?
Some of it sounds pretty good.
I think...
I think this case is closed.
Is it ever really closed?
Hmm...
Frankly, I'm excited.
I think all these sindentalks still don't know the truth.
Well, this case is a complete more creative leap, which is why the slice claims havesun
Okay, grab your Captain.
It's concepts.
Bobo.
He's looking at the movie.
Good work.
Love is love, Bob is love, Dickie, sticky love, Love is Bob.
Bob is love, Bob is love, Bob is love, Love is love,
Bob is love, Bob is love, Bob is love, Bobby scores.
Bob is love, is love, Bob is love.
Bob is love, the kinda love that makes Bob Grinn.
Bob is love.
Ooh-ooh
Uh, I thought it was about hate.
Ahhhhh!
Isn't that what you really need?
Or hate?
Hate the conspiracy!
Hate your job!
Hate the normals that stole your slap!
Make Bob your Bobby!
Bob doesn't love you!
Bob hates you!
Or Bob is hate!
Without hate there can be no love!
Bob Minitani!
Fiends Bob!
Hear what I say!
Without hate there can be no love!
without hate...
without hate, without hate
without hate!
One! Two! Three! Four!
Five! Six! Seven! Eight! Nine! Ten!
Thirteen! Four! Four!
Five! Six! Seven! Eight! Nine!
NAMUWAMI!
GET OUT!
What is this crap?
True facts are pigments of your imagination.
Ladies and gentlemen, what do you think about the future?
The things that are happening in America today are like a Sunday school picnic.
Are you tired of running against the powerful evil forces and about ready to give up?
Many people in America today are walking down the journeys of this life,
unmindful of the present turbulence.
Terrible, ruthless killers.
Unless we have some rapid changes in our country,
our easygoing life of 40 hours a week workload,
two or three weeks of paid vacation a year will soon be over.
They had to be annihilated.
I'll be here, baby.
Baby, I'm a lover, not a Christian.
Proud murderers, rapists, traitors.
This thought thrills my very soul.
12 inches. Get out. Teach sex.
I personally believe that premarital sex,
is necessary.
And now, we will go on to discuss
seven erotic zones of passion in every woman.
The first one is the TV world.
Intersex, it's nothing more than a spawning house for sex.
Raw sex and violence.
The front door to adultery.
Ladies and gentlemen, addicted to government reports, legalizing marijuana.
The president of the United States has been killed.
Ladies and gentlemen, the governor of California has been killed.
Christians, they'll kill you.
In fact, it's their policy to kill people frequently to keep the population terrorized.
Take your children away from you.
Don't be bashful.
Have some candy.
Cruel slavery.
Everybody, over here.
All right, keep moving. Move, I say.
All right, right there now. Right there.
Whee!
Strip a woman naked.
What do you mean, it concerns me?
You must be joking.
You do not have a soul, but only a body.
And when you're dead, you're dead.
I dream of the hour when the last congressman is strangled to death on the guts of the last preacher.
Does this turn your stomach?
You'll be able to do nothing about it.
We will kill you.
And they will kill you, too.
This goes on night after night after night.
Things seem unreal.
These things seem unreal.
Communism is good.
Christianity is stupid.
Give up. Yes.
Yes.
Ladies and gentlemen, we will be slaughtered like cattle, shot down like flies.
Why don't you give it up?
We mustn't come just when we feel like it.
Profit and pleasure.
What about the almighty dollar?
Many people love their money.
Where's my mama and my daddy?
Shh!
Will you come?
Hey, I tell you, I'm talking about pianos, right?
My very sexy lady friend, Margaret, phoned me the other night.
You know, Margaret, short, dark hair, lives in Halifax, not short of a bob or two.
Well, she was having a bit of trouble getting an old grand piano, which she
bought into her house and asked me if I'd nip over there to York Cessna Shire,
you know, in my soft top rascal, to give her a hand with all the removing and all that, you know.
Well, as soon as I got to her big terraced house, I could see what the problem was.
The piano was far too wide.
To get through her front gate.
So after a cup of tea, I asked her if she thought about, you know, taking it up the back passage.
Well, she said she had considered it, but didn't think it would fit there either.
Well, before she knew it, I had it out by the back door and I told sexy Margaret to
stand in front of me and to help me guide the old instrument in as I gently pushed it forward.
Tell you what, one quick shove and it was home.
Well, after that, she then said she fancied it in the back room.
I mean, she knew what position it was.
She wanted it in up against the wall with the old legs firmly on the carpet.
You know, I was so knackered.
I told her I wouldn't be able to manage it unless I rested for a bit.
Well, after getting my head down for a good ten minutes, I was up like a rocket
and quickly stuck it exactly where she wanted it.
You know, now she then went to get two candelabras to put on top.
And when she returned, I could not believe my eyes.
I'm not kidding.
I never knew she had such a big pair.
Massive they were.
And when I held them.
You know, to give them the old once over,
I could see that one was slightly bigger than the other.
Well, as it turned out, her boyfriend had given her one on her birthday.
And so would you believe, had her ex-boyfriend Charlie.
And she said Charlie's was about half an inch bigger.
But when you put them side by side and look to them, you know, at arms length,
you can hardly tell the difference. Well, at the end of the day,
she was so thankful about the help that I'd given her and said she wouldn't have
known what to do if I hadn't come that day.
But you see,
she's happy to lend a hand.
Now, sexy Simone was moving the other day
and she got me around there to help us shift, you know, a few items.
First, the large clock in the hall.
Mmm, baby.
Well, I felt nervous about handling a grandfather with such a big dong.
Still, I got a firm grip and indeed felt privileged to handle such a fine piece.
Well, with a bit of assistance from sexy Simone, I soon had it out and in broad daylight,
took it up the back.
And I was able to get it out of my van and slowly slid it in.
Now, I then asked sexy Simone if she was going to take her burglar alarm.
She said she wasn't going to as she'd never used it and indeed had never had it on.
She said she always had it off when she was at home during the day.
And not only that, any night she went out, she had it off then too.
Well, I was surprised that she didn't want to keep it.
It was a very large and expensive model,
which she had positioned just below her window upstairs.
Hey, it looked lovely, it did.
Then is the time I'd walk past her house,
look up to her bedroom window and admire her big box on full display.
Funny what some people leave behind and say it really is, you know.
But I mean, you know, if you've got any children, perhaps, you know,
teach them to play the piano because, you know, they'll enjoy it in later life.
And that's why I'm fingering the keyboards at every available opportunity.
Yeah, Fat Harry here at the keyboards.
A little...
Smoochy piano sounds for you, baby.
She comes and she goes,
walking stridely on her toes, catching Bob Bob's eyes.
No surprise,
for Connie Bob's attention is her prize.
And Connie comes and she goes and she strikes a sexy pose and Bob is entranced.
She will dance.
And she goes and she goes and she strikes a sexy pose and Bob walks away with swelling in his pants.
Connie,
yoni,
Bob doves can't get enough.
Puppies, horny.
Then Connie shows her stuff.
So Connie comes and she goes and the C1 girls that's
running down her way.
And she goes and she takes a peg.
Breaks the peg.
And that's when Connie takes him down the peg.
Here Connie comes, there she goes, leaving Bob in the clothes of like he asked.
A glee.
Till he pees.
For Connie is a sexual panchee.
Connie, yoni,
he hardly has to try.
Puppies, horny.
And that makes Connie sigh.
Now Connie came and she's gone, but Bob's hardly alone.
As long as he has luck,
he'll be back.
Bob doves will always get another crack.
And that's how Bob and Connie gets slack.
Music to watch Connie by, by Popes Lilith von Frau Mensch, dear friends.
And before that, Fat Harry White fingering the keyboard of love.
He's got a Myspace thing under the name Fat Harry White.
Prior to that, a Nor-El-Pref tribute to Negative Land.
And the song before that, Bob is love.
Bob is hate.
It was by King of Slack, Bill T.
Miller. More at BillTMiller.com or KingofSlack.com.
Just some great stuff there.
And a little bit of soundtrack from that movie, I Heart Huckabees.
This is the subgenius radio ministry hour of Slack.
For more information on the Church of the Subgenius radio shows, books, online
courses, etc. See subgenius.com, which also has our mailing address upon it.
And now, Lee Murr brings us a message from our sponsor.
And Neuro Manson will see us out.
Praise Bob.
Ladies, here's a sensational beauty tip direct from Hollywood.
When you want your hair to look its radiant best for an important date, do this the night before.
Give your hair a glamour bath with waste fat.
I certainly agree with that.
It leaves the hair simply gleaming with natural glossy fats and oils.
And what's more, your hair stays that way for days.
Oh, still.
The gun is penis.
The penis is good.
The gun shoots seeds.
The deeds.
The penis, penis shoots good deeds.
The penis shoots good deeds.