One rice, the human rice. Well, and plus the subgenius rice, but not everybody, they didn't put that on the census, I noticed.
That's right. Negroes, yes, but not subgenius.
No. Oh, well.
Keeping the slack man down.
Yeah, that's right. Keeping the slack man down. The pinks.
From PR News in Washington, I'm more competitive with young people abroad.
Vatican spokesman told Vatican Radio that attempts to link me to an alleged cover-up have failed.
President Obama threatens flooding in several major cities.
He's proposing a child suicide law in Germany.
Johnny Carson says Washington.
From Washington, this is PR News.
Authorities say PR's bad.
PR's bad.
Thousands of anti-government protesters in Thailand, many of them flocking to that country.
Ask those who live in the Delaware Valley.
And you might hear, thank heavens it's not Philadelphia.
The U.S. has no plans to Americanize PR News in Washington.
I didn't catch your name, mister.
Dobbs.
Most young people will continue through life as normal, responsible citizens.
Others, the shunted and unloved, the unguided, the seekers of thrills and kicks,
are candidates for the slave world of lifelong...
How does it happen?
Where does it start?
What are the signs?
The pattern is generally the same.
Bob?
Take a lack of responsibility, the inability to make right choices,
add to it ignorance and indifference,
and top it off with a desire for escapism and kicks.
The sum total is then...
The Self-Genius.
Power of Swag.
This is the real action.
This is the test.
The time to separate the man from the boy.
Willpower, individuality, character are slipping down the drain.
In their place comes Bob.
Don't be chicken.
Now, hang on to your hats, cause we're ready to blast off on a trip through space with...
Ah, yes sir.
Okay everybody, here we go!
I believe in the power of the...
Bob!
Ah, Jesus.
And what's the church of the sub-genius?
Oh, you don't know about that?
No, we're trying to learn about it.
That's a mojo.
The Reverend Ivan Stang made a parody church down in Dallas while high on acid.
And you're gonna have to look it up on the InnerTube.
You know, the church of the sub-genius is a parody church of a regular church.
And also there was a lot of fucking and doing drugs too.
Sounds like the Catholic church.
Jesus.
Bob.
Bob...
That's what I mean!
God,
that's what I meant by,
the government's motto is to keep the mad nations away from tomorrow.
The rabble as쳐.
God is hurting the rich.
The dominion,
your answer.
The modernists, those who wish to see proof of Bob.
But I don't care what they say.
I'll keep preaching.
If you go down, pull them with you.
Praise Bob.
Help me, somebody.
Let there be slack.
See www.subgenius.com
Some men, they go through their whole lives with only one ball.
And that's fine, you know.
So I've read, and well, I guess I figure that you're not really punished if I leave you with a spare.
But what is father?
Bob.
Entertainment, isolation, paperwork and violence.
Gentle, conditional, democracy in silence.
Endless collapse continue, endless recovery.
Unweld pública, with знать noits.
We will be firing at one darling.
Thank you.
and all the success for planning.
I would wait a lifetime
if it takes that long.
I know she's out there
For I have heard her song in dreams she sings to me
Her angel's voice, a symphony
Is she in a garden or a meadow fair?
Does the dappled sunlight shine ribbons in her hair?
Does she sit patiently, smiling as she waits for me?
She's my millionaire girlfriend, she's my life
Once I finally find her, I'll get permission from the wife
We will all live in a castle
My beloved
And my millionaire girlfriend
And I
She's a stolen secret
From a pirate's chest
I will wear an ascot
And a suit that has a vest
And I will put it on
As I watch God no more than long
She's a fairy princess
From a song of old
I will have a toothbrush
That is made of solid gold
And I will watch TV
As my manservant flosses me
She's my millionaire girlfriend
She's my life
Once I finally find her
I'll get permission from the wife
We will all live in a castle
My beloved
And my millionaire girlfriend
And I
Does not matter to me
If she's pretty
Or cute
Counts as what she's
Got at City Bank
Chase Manhattan
Or even Washington Mutual
When my search has ended
I will cherish her
She will sign some papers
Give me power
Of attorney
And what's hers
Will be mine
In perpetuity
She's my millionaire girlfriend
She's my life
Once I finally find her
I'll get permission from the wife
We will all live in a castle
My beloved
And I
You
My beloved
And I
My beloved and my millionaire girlfriend
And I, my beloved and my millionaire girlfriend
And I
It's 11.30 p.m.
Do you know where your children are?
I'm surveying with a magazine.
Eat me along.
Eat, eat, eat, eat me along.
I am surrounded by freaks.
Hey, you don't know the half of it, lady.
And there's one of the freaks now.
I don't like being called a freak that much.
Die, ugly normals.
But I have news of a freak.
Did you read Pravda today
while you were scouring the items for items?
Did I?
Did I read what?
Pravda.
And it's about a nine-year-old girl
giving birth to a perfectly normal child.
Well, that's happening all over the place now, isn't it?
Well, isn't this...
I know an eight-year-old girl
who's just had her time begin.
You had an eight-year-old
who just had her time begin?
Well, it wasn't my eight-year-old.
Well, you shouldn't have said that.
But, no, I think we said that last week
and it had something to do with the cow snot or something,
the stuff in the...
in the snot that comes from the cows' udders
has the growth hormones in it.
Yes.
Right.
Which, yeah, but...
I could use some of those myself.
Well, apparently...
Stumpy doesn't mind being small, though.
Stumpy can fit in small places.
As long as Stumpy can stand up and salute,
who cares about the rest?
But also on Pravda was a...
There were pictures of the trees on Mars
that's been going around as...
NASA has been fibbing about something.
And then in the very last frame,
it explains how they're just...
It's an optical illusion.
But it's amazing that you don't hear about these things
in the good old UXA where corn cobs were born.
Well, they quit publishing the Weekly World News,
although I understand they still have a website.
That's not very good.
Pravda is fun in much the same way
the Weekly World News is.
It's got a lot of Bigfoot news, celebrity news,
three-headed chicken type stuff.
Hot Russian babes.
By the way, Dave,
I still haven't done the credits.
Well, I thought it was like 9.20,
so I better shut up.
Well, no, you can...
But I do need to let people know
that the very last collage was by Mr. Rection.
Before that, the song Millionaire Girlfriend
was by Jonathan Colton,
the ultimate...
As Dr. Leguim called him,
the ultimate superhero.
The genius songwriter.
It turns out Reverend Back It On Up
was the one who turned Leguim
onto JonathanColton.com.
We heard The Large versus Dr. Howell,
a collage by Lee Murr,
a collage by Mr. Rection,
and that song about the passport,
Don't Need No Passport,
that was Pilgrim Speakeasy.
Pilgrim Speakeasy,
and they can be found on CDBaby.com and Facebook,
and...
MySpace.
Pilgrim Speakeasy.
I could be wrong,
but I think they're from Finland.
We had collages by The Large,
a little clip from Mr. Sistar,
an old Stang minute of slack,
and Opie and Anthony were talking to Mojo Nixon
about the Church of the Subgenius.
That was Mojo Nixon telling those pink boys
about the Church.
The Large,
Reverend Maynard Brainard,
Reverend Sodi,
and of course,
Fernanda Nandy Lee Murr
did the collages that opened the show,
and that is all I have to say about that.
Well, it was quite well said.
Quite well said.
You were succinct,
and you were wearing the clamps as usual.
I was sinking.
You were lip-syncing your own vowels
in front of a mirror?
Yeah.
I thought you gave that up for Lenten holidays.
Ever since I lost my hearing,
it's the only way I can...
I can't hear myself talk, you know?
Well, at least you haven't lost other things.
I mean, hearing is bad.
Don't speak too soon.
Sight is bad.
Princess Wee isn't here.
But why?
She had a meet.
She's...
Because she's designing Starwood
single-handedly, practically.
She had to go to a meeting
and make sure that Starwood will happen,
and it will.
And the new site,
she went to visit the new site,
Wisteria Campground,
and it's just about like...
Brushwood.
It'll be just about the same,
but not as cold,
because it's in southern Ohio.
Is it near Cincinnati?
No.
No, it's way...
It's more near Athens.
Mm-hmm.
It's lovely down there.
It's actually in Pomeroy.
Quite a few mounds down there.
Yes, and they even made their...
They built their own turtle mound.
I didn't know what Princess Wee
was talking about at first.
I envisioned a big,
big pile of turtles,
but it was a mound,
like an Indian mound,
shaped in a tertalian shape.
Isn't that...
That's exciting to me.
Well, it's a good,
well-appointed campground
with showers and everything.
Now, X-Day is still where it's always been,
and that is coming up,
and that's what's been keeping me busy
is trying to get ready
to start getting ready for X-Day.
It's funny how much effort you put in.
Even though you know the world is going to end.
Especially when you know the world's going to end.
You have to think positively, Stan.
It could actually happen this year.
Well, sure, sure.
But for that matter,
it could happen in the next five minutes.
That's thinking real positive.
Right.
Hurry up, X-Day.
I think what needs to be done
is to have people remove the blinders
and to look squarely at the outcome.
Wait, I'm so bored.
Things have already been done.
They've been preordained,
and they already have happened
in different dimensions,
and they're just waiting
for that saddle-up moment
when everything flops like an eagle.
Right.
Where the sun doesn't,
there is no more sun.
Where Bob don't care to look.
Well, there's no more solar system
as we know it.
No sun to speak of.
Man, I was,
I told you,
I've had the bad habit
of reading the comments
after the news articles.
Yeah, me too.
And there was the news article
about global warming,
and apparently,
somebody must have prompted
the teabaggers
to all say the same wisecrack about,
well, you're going to keep
the whole solar system
from warming up next,
Mr. Al Gore.
He invented the internet, you know.
If we were students...
I've heard that so many times,
I've about decided,
yeah, Al Gore did invent the internet.
And Obama is a Muslim communist
who hates our freedom,
and no Democrat ever,
works.
I've read that today.
I was informed...
No, they don't pay taxes either.
Right.
No Democrat ever works
or pays taxes.
Only Republicans and teabaggers
ever work or pay taxes.
Although, oddly,
they seem to have
an awful lot of spare time
to add comments
to Yahoo.com news articles.
It's amazing how,
I thought that their lack
of spelling ability
was perhaps a plant
by this covert shadow government.
Yeah, yeah.
That they,
they talk about
meaning the shadow
covert government
was not on their side.
It was against their,
it was on our side
or not,
no, they're,
well, you know what I mean?
Kind of, pretty much.
Well, all I know is that
the, the, the,
the people who hate,
really hate
the, the government.
I mean, more than I ever
hated the government,
and that's saying a lot.
They seem to agree
with the president of Iran
on quite a few issues.
I know.
It's funny how that,
you know, how do you,
how do you make
all that stuff jibe?
Logically,
but I guess you don't have to
because you don't use your mind
to think about your religion.
They move the dog
and all of dogma
take away the veil of death
and what you see
is what you get.
That's the problem.
They don't,
people are not,
that's, they're not,
not pantheistic
or xenophobic.
It means they can only see
in the, the mindset
that they're in right now,
which is American mindset,
259.
Well, I, I'm the same way.
I can only see things
as a cosmically expanded mind
of a subgenius can see things.
That's because you receive...
Which is like from the bottom,
I can see the sides
and top of the barrel.
I'm, yeah, but you're not
like the average American
because you receive
your mediated messages
from perhaps Bob,
perhaps extraterrestrials.
I don't know.
Alt.slack.
Alt.slack, certainly.
And any other place
that you care to look
when you can and when you do.
But the average American
listens to the old hot media,
the propaganda media
of the 30s,
which tells them
and makes you wonder
what it's like to live in a world
where nothing that you hear
is true and yet you
fervently believe all this stuff
and you're really, you know...
I read a headline today
that bald-faced stated
polls grow.
Grieve.
And I thought,
that doesn't make any sense.
That's impossible.
I mean, no.
Polls grieve.
Hmm.
At the loss of their mourn.
That's the problem, too.
It's not even mourning
where most of my telephone polls exist.
That's a totally subcontinent...
Your mourning poll.
I have, oh, I found...
I found something good in the news.
A prophecy,
not even a Bob prophecy,
one of my prophecies came true.
No one, no slack for anyone ever again?
No, no, this was, well, yes and no.
I was reading an article
about a new powerful beer
that some brewery in Scotland is making.
And I've been hearing about
heavily fortified beers,
but this one is 32%
alcohol beer.
It's 53 bucks a bottle.
And here's the name of it.
Tactical Nuclear Penguin Beer.
Nuclear Beer.
As predicted in my underground movie,
Let's Visit the World of the Future,
available free on Google Video, I think,
which has the people of the future
injectifying cans, entire cans,
that have needles on one end,
and a plunger on the other,
injecting cans of nuclear beer.
Now, my nuclear beer was
part fortified alcohol,
or grain alcohol,
and part amphetamine,
methamphetamines.
And if you'll notice...
And nuclear weight.
Not only are they making
nuclear beer in Scotland,
but here in the U.S.,
you see many alcoholic beverages
that are packed with caffeine
and power drugs, you know,
or whatnot.
The Guarana and stuff.
Yeah.
So forth.
Yes, this is all the rage.
But it's part of a very old tradition.
As far as the fortified ales go,
every anniversary in the British Isles
for some important event,
they try and get it up,
but 32 is a new record.
But I, myself, have ingested the 28%,
which makes you stupid after one.
It's just annoying.
It's just like,
yeah, I had a beer, man.
Stupid.
I had that experience.
I had been reading...
Well, one of the subgeniuses,
Dr. Lobotomy, said,
hey, look how terrible
these people in socialist countries,
in real socialist countries, have it.
It was a news article about...
Like China and Russia, right?
Well, now get this.
The workers at the Carlsberg Brewery
in Copenhagen, Denmark,
are on strike
because they're not allowed
to drink all the beer
they want any time anymore.
Now they're only allowed...
The workers at the Carlsberg Brewery
are only allowed to drink during lunch.
And that's how hard they have it
in those socialist countries.
I know.
And when they fall down on the machinery
from being able to drink all day and stuff,
somebody pays for it besides them.
Well, now that's what they were...
Well, indirectly, they do
because they have high taxes
in these Scandinavian countries, I guess.
Well, the reason these workers were so upset
was because nobody asked them about it.
They were used to being consulted.
Before there was a big change.
And suddenly the management had announced,
no, you can't drink on the job all day anymore.
You can only drink at lunch.
Now, here in the land of the free,
I know that for most companies,
if you come back from lunch
with the tiniest whiff of beer on your breath,
you're docked pay for two weeks,
you know, or something worse.
Or you just put the zero tolerance.
When I was a young drunkard
working in the industry,
working in the Dallas film business,
it was...
Everybody had two beers at lunch.
That was just normal.
You know, it was expected.
Sometimes you would have four
and you would be stupid
when you got back to work.
And it wasn't fun.
Well, if you were stupid,
then you got in trouble.
But if you could function on a couple of beers,
which most people could in Texas,
that was okay.
In fact, it was legal to drive down the road
sipping on your can of Lone Star
as long as you weren't drunk.
On the other hand,
when I read about that Carlsberg Brewery,
I got so...
It planted...
It was like the best advertising in the world.
I had to go out and try some Carlsberg beer,
but I bought the kind called Elephant,
which is fortified.
Yeah, 7.2.
And just as you say,
it wasn't like having one beer.
It was like having a beer and a half.
And I was kind of,
well, I can't get my work done now.
I can't work on this important stuff.
I have to work on this beer.
I have to work on an hour of slack.
Yes, I remember the days
when you would have a few at lunch and stuff.
And the first two,
when you got back to work,
the first two hours would just fly by
and you were having so much fun.
And the last two were just really,
really horribly slow.
Just like school.
Just like life, Stang.
Yeah.
Without slack or without Bob,
after reading some of your works,
I'm starting to think that Bob
is a lot more important than I thought.
He's the kind of person or icon
or whatever that I used to just want to go
up and punch in the stomach real hard.
Maybe urinate on his foot.
Oh, he'll pay you for that
if you can find him.
I mean, he loves it.
He's into that kind of thing.
He's kind of kinky.
I don't think that's why I like him now.
There's nothing you can do
that he doesn't want you to do.
Well, I like that he fornicates trees.
And I remember the old psychopath
Pathfinder saying,
I had adultery.
I committed adultery with an adult tree.
Adult tree.
Yeah, I remember that.
And when I heard that Bob was doing it,
I realized that it was probably something
I should be doing, too.
I could probably be a wood borer in some way
if I, you know, set my mind to it.
And I think, well, not really.
I don't think anything.
Lucky you.
Just like Bob.
You have reached the state
that every subgenius aspires to.
Break no-think.
The state of no-think.
Break mind.
It's beautiful.
Well, I suppose not really beautiful
because words defy and decry and despise.
Right, you don't have words
when you have no mind.
Not even pictures.
I would desecrate those same spots if I could
or make them with my body, you know?
That's a beautiful thing.
And this beautiful music in the background,
by the way, is by Ron Slabe.
Pyrosonic.
It's, what he had playing last Starwood.
He composed this for the Island Fireworks Show
or the Fire Tribe Dancing, Juggling, Fire Eating.
This isn't the one that ended up in the small,
the explosion.
No, that was another group.
That was the Time Machine Fellows.
That's to Ron's deck.
Cash Starburner, in fact,
was the guy that,
that caused the explosion at the last Starwood.
You know that,
I almost got my legs sheared off
by a door of the structure that blew up.
It's on the video.
You can see this door in night vision
coming straight towards the underside of the camera,
which would be my legs.
But Bob or God or the devil caused it,
or the wind caused it to suddenly change direction
and it zipped off to the side
as if I had a,
a fire.
Force field.
But we won't,
we won't have any more of those happening out at Brushwood
because there won't be any more Starwoods out at Brushwood.
No, no more Bob facial implants.
We'll have to blow things up elsewhere.
No more Bob facial implants in New York State.
Oh, I know people who won't go to Burning Man anymore
because you're no longer allowed to use a machine gun
or use explosives without a permit.
Or an exposed cerebral cortex.
God, that is yucky.
Oh, you actually, you can do that.
Well, you can, but you may not.
I'd hate, it's awfully sandy environment for, for that.
That would be horrible.
Yeah, you get a lot of grit.
I mean, I'd, I'd break every video camera that I take out there.
I would think that if you walked around with your brain exposed,
it would get pretty gritty pretty fast.
Well, here's a 40 and a side note to that.
The grit that could accumulate in your head
and it could go into your skull
is very similar to the giants that the Indians were scared of around here.
Um, in this area of where we're speaking and stuff,
there are these giants, these macrocephalic giants
who have very, very large foreheads
and they're all gritty as if pockmarked with sand
and as if the skull itself was a sandy surface.
And some of the less erudite members of the tribe
have postulated that perhaps Vikings, um,
who didn't want to intermarry after the little ice age,
whatever it was when the weather wasn't so good,
so nice and got crappy for a while like it is often.
Yeah.
It was real warm, I guess, a while ago
and it's getting warmer again, perhaps.
Anyway, it's not important.
Anyway, these giants had huge, huge shell-shaped, um, sandy pocked skulls.
Forehead skulls.
That's in the Bible too.
There were giants in the earth in those days.
These were what we...
But they were just broke Swedes.
These were what we call the Yeti.
The Yetis of the Himalayas and, uh, who then migrated to Mount Shasta.
Right.
They live underground.
Yes.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, how.
Uh, I don't know.
Uh, uh.
Well, right.
To quote Philo...
Hey, we got farced!
Pardon?
We got farced.
X-Day got farced.
What happened was, uh, uh, good Reverend Motomac,
the sex god, sent out his annual press release
about the subgenius X-Day end of the world festival
where we gather and wait for sex.
And he sent out a press release about the subgenius X-Day
we're going to have to wait for the world to end on July 5th this year
and have done every year.
And he sent that press release out and like most years,
most of the news services ignored it.
But Flash News picked it up and the next thing we knew,
disinfo.com was talking about the church
and I got about 10 orders that way.
And then farc.com started to put up a, uh, carried that news.
It's, it's, the news release itself is full of misinformation,
misquotes,
Thank God.
everything wrong,
Right.
but they did spell subgenius right without an O.
And, um, so we, that's why I'll be able to,
to send you a check for this phone call.
$5,000.
This long distance phone call you had to do.
Yeah. $5,000.
It's cause I mean, you, I remember back in 2007,
we were, we, I'd have been sending you 20,000 bucks
after being farced like that.
A brief farked on a phone call.
The times have changed.
It's like, I, all I can think of is Steinbeck or somebody or whatever.
I know.
Who wrote Grapes of Wrath?
I'm sorry.
I'm so ignorant.
I forgot.
I just think of swirling oak bowls and dusty things and, you know,
farmers being forced into the, you know,
into the concentration camp so they can learn how to focus more properly
when they're using, you know, the little headwear they use
when they have the mind control games.
Have you ever tried those or been tried by them?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, sure.
I haven't.
You know, it's all the rage among the 11- and 9-year-olds and stuff
to strap a metallic balloon toy on their head
and focus on a ball and make the ball rise and fall.
I found myself doing that at Winterstar last time.
You were looking at your own decomposing body in the bathtub
to calculate the process, I think.
The things have changed.
I've noticed computer memory is real cheap now,
and so are bad memories, but good memories are dear, dear, dear,
very dear, very expensive to keep a good memory in your head.
You have to keep a lot of the bad memories,
but all the good memories are expensive.
Or else you'll make the same mistakes over and over again.
Yeah, yeah.
I was thinking in the psychosociopathic plus realm myself
when you mentioned that I didn't think I was hearing me,
you know, the errand hollerings of any people locked up in the monastery
or something for cripes sake, you know.
That's the devil locked up in that monastery, man.
Don't, whatever he tells you, don't believe him.
Don't let him out.
The lovers of the scaly foot do not believe this thing.
Of course.
You know, that's the way things are run around here.
And what if X-Day doesn't work out around here?
So what if we don't get out of here so they don't have to...
We'll be sitting around begging for spare climate change.
And as you can scan, we shall get any other than errant mind control
from every source as over-mediated monkeys.
That's what I feel like.
I feel like a research.
I feel like some sort of lab.
Monkey or something.
You kind of look a little bit like those ones that are raised with the terrycloth mothers.
Well, don't you know about associative environment and testing and so forth?
Of course I look like Mark Mother's paw now.
My feet have all grown back in.
Man.
That's the way it works.
Once you're in an environment for long enough, you begin to resemble your environment.
Uh.
Yeah, that's concrete.
That's glassy.
We're concrete and we're glassy and plasticky looking.
And, uh, hey, I, uh, we were talking earlier off the air about how the government doesn't
have to force you to be hooked up to machines because everybody can't wait to be hooked
up to their machine.
They get up in the morning and put on their headphones and take their iPad and their iPod
and their iPhone and their iMind and their iCar and their iVac.
And they're hooked up to a van and they stang away down the road, all hooked up to everything
they do.
They're hooked up to a machine.
And then they go, they, they, they roll their car up to Walmart and they crawl into Walmart
and climb onto a little machine and tootle around Walmart on a little golf cart or the
supermarket.
What would Australopithecus think of us right now?
Think of us as some sort of, uh.
Probably.
Like an easy kill.
Like look at that mass of meat.
And they're so slow.
We don't even need a very good hand axes to bash their brains in.
Well if there was a real time based continuum that made sense, we would be the cargo cult.
Not we, I don't wear any of those clothes.
But the, the Australopithecans would become the new, you know, sausage farmers and delinquents
and people like that.
And they would raise the banner and, you know, so on and so forth.
There was a new Australopithecus, well, an old Australopithecus discovered, newly discovered, some excellent skeletons.
I read I had to go and...
They think it might be, not really be Australopithecus, they think it might be one of the many, too many perhaps to conceive of,
of pre-human humans walking around hanging out at pretty much the same time.
Yeah, there were a lot of other ones besides us at one time.
That's the Yeti diversity, man. That's what we need.
Now, you know, the thing about, well, not an Australopithecus, an Australopithecus girl wouldn't look that hot to us.
But a Homo erectus woman seen from young Homo erectus...
Homo erectus walking neck and down the road, seen from behind, you'd start following.
Now, when she turned around and looked at you, you might, that might take a little getting used to.
It may have taken some getting used to.
There might have been a lot of getting used to and such like going on back then.
I guess we may never know.
Well, that's called hag syndrome.
It's in every town in the nation.
You're cruising down the street, you see some hot babe, you know, from behind.
And then you turn around.
And I look at her and she's 94 years old.
Her body's just well preserved.
She has no teeth, no eyes, certainly no third nostrils because she's probably only got one to begin with.
Maybe she's a little flat for ears.
That's a beautiful thing.
Ben Franklin pointed out that as women age, the first parts to age are the visible parts, the face and hands.
But the parts that you don't see are oftentimes continuous.
They continue to look pretty much like they did when they were young teenagers for quite a long time, in some cases.
The kind that, in fact, that I was looking at on the Internet just earlier today.
Oh, I read that the 3D pornography is on its way.
Oh, God, I hope so.
Well, according to Nefier's minions, many parts of their bodies continue to live forever.
And that's why we can, what did you say about buying a different one?
Well, some, our bodies don't live, most of our parts don't live forever.
But I was reading about my little buddies, the rotifers, the little barely visible to the naked eye creatures.
Some of them are too small to see.
I see them a lot because I keep them, you know, I raise them.
I have a rotifer farm and a water bear farm and so forth.
It was, it has been discovered lately that when rotifers,
well, they basically can't be killed.
What?
You can deprive them of all heat, all air, all water, all everything.
You can put them out in space.
They will dry up into little pill-shaped things that will last.
You can fit a thousand of them into a little thimble.
And they'll last for years and years.
And the next time that water falls upon them, why?
They come back.
They come back to life.
And even though their DNA has been destroyed by radiation or drying or whatnot,
these creatures have the ability to absorb DNA from other creatures
and automatically rebuild their own with it.
Now, what if we could, you know, I've got a lot of busted chromosomes from all that LSD
that Mojo Nixon was talking about earlier.
I've got a lot of busted chromosomes from all that LSD that Mojo Nixon was talking about earlier.
That I had to take in order to get a job for Bob.
And that was a long time ago, obviously.
So you're saying there's a lot of freaked out...
An hour and a half ago.
I wish that stuff would come on.
God.
Stangy rotifers around?
You're saying that there's a lot of freaked out, flippy, stangy rotifers around
that won't die forever because they're sucking everyone else's DNA to make their own
and just don't believe in dying?
Right.
Why can't we do that?
Why can't the subgeniuses pick up an idea from Microsoft?
Micro creatures like rotifers and do that very self-same thing.
You know, we have been working for years on trying to encode the text of Book of the Subgenius
into the DNA of cockroaches so that the book will always be in print forever.
Because they do live an extremely long time.
Even, I mean, not as an individual cockroach.
Well, they reproduce and they survive well.
Yes.
But really, we should be encoding...
I'm going to turn the Book of the Subgenius into phylodina rotifers.
Those are my favorites.
Wow.
Well, that's an important discovery.
I'd shake the halls of science, at least in Dobbs Town, because you stumbled on something
there.
Give up the idea of implanting roaches with the knowledge and use the rotifers.
Right.
I don't know.
I like it.
Yeah.
And they really will live forever.
Of course, the problem is that over the years...
It's a copy of a copy of a copy.
The text, certain words start to become misspelled.
Next thing you know, all the rotifers are going, praise Bill instead of praise Bob.
Well, then they'd have to die, too, because if they became associated with anything entropic,
eventually they would start to wind out of control.
Maybe they wouldn't die.
They'd just keep on mutating.
Oh, yeah.
That would be weird.
That would be kind of sad, I think.
I wonder if we will keep on mutating.
Or if we'll just stagnate.
Well, we've already stagnated.
That's not the point.
I mean, us personally.
You and me.
Well, no, I know.
That's what I mean.
I've got a pretty weird-looking toenail that makes me think I'm still mutating.
Yeah, I keep on growing new things.
I have another large egg-shaped thing on my head, only on a different side.
Really?
Well, I think you've seen this one before and said all you need to do is lance it.
Well, I actually use Sir Lancelot's lance, and it still didn't work.
Oh, my night, you have to use sandpaper.
Or a sander, actually.
A belt sander.
It smells horrible, doesn't it?
You know, when you burn away one of those big warts on your head?
Because that's kind of what they are.
Some of them are cysts, and some are bros, and some are warts.
And you can lance the cysts or squeeze them out.
I've seen them as big as an egg.
An actual?
A little duck egg?
The cyst being removed from a human body.
Not my body, thank goodness.
I had one right under my eye once that was quite scary.
Did you ask the doctor if you could keep it or take it home with you?
As a matter of fact, the doctor and the nurse leaned closely over me and started to squeeze it.
And I envisioned them being squirted with foul-smelling cyst juice.
And I said,
Are you guys sure you don't want to cover that up while you squeeze it?
And they both looked at me and rolled their eyes like,
What a stupid idiot!
And at that moment, they were both squirted with the most foul ichor imaginable.
I mean, it must have stunk up.
And it sprayed all over the doctor's face, all over the nurse's clothes, across the room.
It was a beautiful, beautiful thing following that condescending look that doctor gave me.
That was not my regular doctor.
That was an emergency doctor.
And there were reasons for keeping the excreta from your thing.
You see, there's still a little slice on my face where that cyst once was.
Everything that could have harmed you is gone.
Everything that could hurt you is a memory now.
Yes, you're right.
Sit back and relax and know that your fluids are being used to further the pursuit of science.
Pull the when.
That mankind will march forward.
Pull the when over your own eye.
Release the winds of the hounds of Hades.
Just get it over with and drop a bomb.
No, you can't say that on the air, can you?
Can you?
I remember when I was a hero back in 19...
It's domestic terrorism jokes.
Well...
The satire bands are definitely in effect for those right now.
I guess if you check out a website, you're kind of collusional.
Is that true or is that just scuttlebutt?
It depends on the website.
If you check out subgenius.com, then you'll know what's going on with subgenius.com.
At least they won't come to your house.
And you'll learn about the revival, the subgenius church revival meeting in Shanghai, China in May.
There really is one.
They keep having to put it off a month because people keep getting scared to do a weird religious meeting in mainland communist China.
But I think communism has become so capitalist, it wouldn't matter what the commissar thought, if this was good thinking or correct thinking.
If you gave him enough money, he would probably come out there and deliver the opening massage.
Right?
Right.
I know what happens when Chinese people first lay eyes on Bob.
They crack up.
Because, let's face it, to them, Caucasians are funny looking.
Big noses.
I was going to say, he looks like a dumbass white man.
And he's the most, he's the whitest white man.
Just as poor Chief Wahoo has exaggerated features that are supposed to look like an American Indian, Bob is like the cartoon white man.
In fact, Bob...
And Chief Wahoo have a lot in common.
Their expressions are kind of similar.
Sly.
Losing teams.
They look sly.
They are sly.
Yeah.
I understand why some people would be upset with Chief Wahoo since, you know...
On the other hand, I can see why people might be able to take a joke, too.
Seeing as how I don't look at...
Every time I see a picture of Bob Dobbs, I don't go,
Oh, I'm insulted.
Somebody's making fun of Wasp.
Male Wasp.
Well, white dudes.
Well, they didn't necessarily steal Bob's continent, though.
They didn't necessarily come along.
Well, that's true.
Still 90% of the people steal everything.
Well, yes and no.
Yes and no.
Not Bob's continent, but his ancestors' island of England was certainly conquered over and over again by the Danes and the Romans and the French and the Germans and just about everybody.
It's not just about the Danes and the Romans and the French and the Germans and just about everybody.
And they conquered everybody back, so it doesn't count.
Well, everybody does that.
Everybody gets conquered real bad, and then their time comes.
Remember when Persia was the most civilized place in the world?
Remember when Mongolia had the most advanced civilization?
Remember when Spain was cooking?
I'm sure there were...
And the South Americans were very civilized.
America and Central America, Mexico.
Everybody gets their turn, and then they get the smallpox or the whatever.
You know, something.
Somebody comes along and invades them with video.
So what's going to destroy the American empire?
Video games and movies and TV and Texas textbooks.
How about indolence and stupidity?
That helps, too.
Yeah, but that's what we want.
We're subgeniuses.
Insolence and indolence and stupidity and insolence.
But we want the same thing that the conspiracy wants.
No, man.
We must want something more sublime, perhaps.
We want the cool version.
Hey, Dave, it's about time.
It's about space.
It's about two men in the craziest place.
I'm going to rip off this chest merkin right now
and go and play my stand-up bass fiddle for a couple hours.
How about you?
I am going to go straight home.
A cup of neocraft, perhaps a salute to the west wind,
and maybe a few arguments with some stray dogs on the way home.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, you know, it's just an exciting life for us.
Home. Home. Home.
Okay, and with that, that's it.
I'm going to cut you off, but I'll keep the little,
I'll keep the little end, I'll keep that end piece, okay, Dave?
What?
Don't worry. It's a religious thing.
Oh, I love that kind of stuff.
And good night.
I don't want to have to cut this artificially later to get it down to time.
Bye.
Okay.
That was it. That was it, baby.
And we've, this music in the background was Ron Slabe's Pyrosonic.
And we'll take that out and we'll put on a little bit more of,
uh,
collage here, I think, uh, after this ID, there's the large and lemur,
and everything will be just groovy.
Everything will be just.
You're normally such a slacker.
It's the first time you've heard of him.
Are all four of you guys in here?
Is Phil in there?
He just, yeah, yeah.
Can we?
Yeah.
Do it with four?
Yeah, all four.
Okay.
What are we doing?
How do we, this is, this is.
Oh, the other one.
They'll do the comedy.
How about this is Phil, Phil, Pete, and Dave of the Fireside Theater.
This, okay.
This is Phil.
Phil.
Let's take it again.
Yeah.
Oh, Pete and Dave.
Okay.
There we go.
Yeah.
All right.
You over here.
You just shut up.
This is Phil.
Phil.
Pete.
And Dave of the Fireside Theater.
And we're listening to The Hour of Slack.
Hack, hack, hack, hack, hack.
Because we're subgeniuses.
And we're slackinging off.
Started typing at the heart.
And now.
Now.
Started typing at the, at the, at, at the heart.
And now.
Now.
The stock market has been seen floating in the sky among a cloud-shaped man who's believed
to be PR news in Washington.
Hard time.
Slime.
Some genius Hour of Slack.
I believe you need to be an enabler of success and an exemplar of this review.
Be an analyst, analyst, analyst, analyst, employee, customer, partner, your company, or your client objectives.
If you do this, you will define your own success and get others to follow you to the organist.
My first PR was at the Washington PR at the PR News.
What?
From PR News in Washington, I'm angry about being sworn in.
Uh, um, and, uh.
Pink Floyd claims this is PR.
You want to inspect on you?
Good, that's a wonderful thing.
Pick a lesbian.
Suffering 80 years out of her body, she's all gone!
Oh, my God!
Oh, Jesus!
Lady, put down.
Oh!
Feet up!
Well, it landed softly for coming out so hot it didn't go but about 15 feet after it landed.
Thank you.
There is a God.
I know I'm a God.
Give me my pen.
If you say go, people of Minotaur.
When the public in school hears a woman's name window link on the screen,
We're set on this event 오케이 askeduna.
Do you edited such a whimsical troublemaker?
Give me a break, will you?