The friends are all arguing about who's abused themselves the most.
They're trying to signal from the other side of the earth. It doesn't matter.
But that's okay. You can't hear anything.
We can't hear anything.
There's nothing in these headphones.
And we start the show over and over again.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to...
The Self Genius Hour of Swatch!
Here come the sound effects.
And we start the show over and over again.
Over and over and over again!
Ah, yes, dear friends.
668 hours of slack.
That's how many of these I've had to deal with.
You know what's been going on for almost, well, over 15 years?
Over 15 years of slack!
Yeah.
Sometimes it didn't seem like slack.
But you know every time you lick a stamp, you're consuming a tenth of a calorie.
And you know a crocodile cannot stick its tongue out.
Yet the ant can lift 50 times its own weight.
Can pull 30 times its own weight.
And always falls over on its right side when intoxicated.
Don't you wish you could be that...
Consistent, dear friends.
And I'm just going to go straight on into the tapes.
The hours and hours and hours of Einstein's Secret Orchestra that I have stacked up here.
Actually, we do a live show, you know, out of Cleveland.
It's more live than this one.
So we'll go live there for a while.
Also, I'm going to finish off that Firesign Theater album.
Give me immortality.
Or give me death.
I know that y'all are never going to go out and spend money on that thing.
But you really have to hear it.
It's a beautiful, beautiful thing.
Proof that a great comedy troupe can bounce right back 20 years later.
Just like they were in the first...
I think their new album is just as good as any of their classics.
Like, I think we're all bozos on this bus.
And Don't Crush That Dwarf, Hand Me the Pliers.
Those are very highly recommended albums.
By the Firesign Theater.
The music in the background, in this case, is Arnold Mathis.
Who used to send music tapes to the Hour of Slack a lot.
Back when he finally put out a...
I guess he got a CD burner.
Someday, I guess we'll all have to have CD burners.
Won't we, dear friends?
I'm going to have to start sending this show out on CD.
Apparently.
Well, we age.
We change.
And we grow.
Yes.
In fact, just thinking about it makes me grow even more.
But, well...
Okay, I said I wasn't going to talk on this dead show.
So let's go to the live show with Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
Chaz Smith, the church cantor,
Princess Wiardo,
and probably Bleepo Abernathy and yours truly.
And God only knows what else we'll have.
Murking and mucking around in there.
Praise old Bob.
I have found the entry for Earth.
Humanity.
Third from the sun.
If you start down the dark path forever,
you will meet your destiny.
And soon you will.
Each person gets like Stang.
He gets more money out of it.
Ham, ham.
From all those deluded sick fools
who would actually send him thousands on thousands of dollars
to build up a staggy...
Hey, man.
We saved...
Each one of those people was saved from heaven's gate.
That's true.
We saved their lives for $30.
Now they're working for peanuts down in Bolivia
for the rest of their lives.
But, hey, what the hell about that part, right, Stangy Boy?
Hey, man, after the Y2K bug,
there ain't going to be much work for web designers,
but coffee bean pickers...
That's right.
...are going to be in hot, great demand.
I enjoy working with you.
Yeah, I know.
There's going to be a lot in need for a lot of child labor.
A child laborer and little tennis shoemakers and stuff.
I enjoy working with people.
Okay, I can agree that we need a certain degree of child labor.
We certainly do need a certain degree of millions of millions of small children
that will do absolutely everything you want from them,
and you neither need to feed nor clothe them,
but just kick them once in a while.
I enjoy working with people.
But I don't think that you should be in the forefront.
In your current position now, the way you are right now...
I enjoy working with people.
...of pushing this.
I'm sorry.
It wasn't as convoluted this time, and it's just stupid.
Well, dolphins or humans are of very little use to the church,
not even as workhorses.
I enjoy working with people.
Pansies, however.
Pansies?
Not the standard chimpanzee, but the bonobo or pygmy chimpanzee.
What?
That is a valuable friend.
A chimpanzee and individual chimpanzee is a valuable friend to a subgenius?
Well, we, the subgeniuses, should...
They're so much closer to our yeti brethren and sistren.
And we should protect those chimpanzees
and only allow them to be raised in the most benevolent medical experimentation facilities.
I enjoy working with chimpanzees.
They're really enlightened.
Well, Stan, you could probably...
Make a videotape of one of those cute little chimps
and sell them to subgenii everywhere
as a kind of an artificial going-away-from-home-you-don't-need-it-right-now-but-perhaps-later
best friend.
No, I think it should be the other way around.
I think we should sell the subgeniuses to the chimpanzees.
Oh, jeez.
You can't really top that.
I mean, that's a win-win situation any way you look at it.
That's the beauty part right in the beauty part there, man.
We should follow the bonobos.
Well, I don't really know how we could follow them.
They're not really good at it.
They're not going anywhere.
They're just standing around one place fondling each other.
I mean, that's not...
You can't follow anybody.
You can do it yourself.
Well, if you follow them quietly and get to know them real well,
they'll let you fondle them, too.
And you've done that.
That's the whole idea, man.
Why do you think we started this?
Go bonobo all the way, man.
I know you've had all kinds of really weird erotic experiences,
but I don't think I know...
Is that true that there was a video...
The bug sex.
It's ape sex, dude.
So you...
There's videos of that now?
You fondling a bonobo monkey?
What?
There's videos of you out fondling a bonobo monkey right now?
A bonobo chimpanzee?
Dave, Dave, Dave, cool it, man.
But, you know...
I'm cool with it as much as I can,
but I think the facts kind of are startling in themselves
that you would allow yourself to be physically used
by a member of another species.
Dave, Dave, Dave, this line is not exactly secure.
Well, I didn't think any of the lines were secure.
I thought they were all...
They were all open.
I thought they all went straight to Langley or wherever it is now.
I think it's in...
Oh, thank you.
They go straight out over the Internet.
Oh, well, then that's...
Everything you just said is now part...
is now on deja vu news for the next 20 years.
I can't do that.
Thanks.
Now everybody's going to be looking for the videos of the ape sex,
trying to download that stuff.
Next thing you know,
Kenneth Starr is going to want to know all about it.
Now, exactly where did you get these chimpanzees?
You know, how much did you pay for them?
You know, did you...
Did you do it in the closet?
Did you ever do it backwards?
You did all that stuff, didn't you?
Like dogs.
And you were actually wearing the Bonobo semen strain...
Oh, I made up all that stuff.
I sat there and answered every question.
Oh, yeah, I did it.
I did everything.
You really didn't do any of it?
And they went, oh, thank you very much,
and, you know, sent me home.
But you really...
I told them just what they wanted to hear.
Yes, it's all true.
Everything you...
Yes, the satanic cult.
Yes, abduction by aliens.
Yes, yes, child abuse.
Child abuse, it's all true.
But how much of it is true?
And they went, oh, oh, you're not going to,
you know, like, put up a stink or anything?
I was going to know.
Well, putting up a stink is one of the best things you do,
isn't it?
I mean, you know, you've been known to let the wind
go around the land, you know?
Man, you put up a good stink.
They thought they were going to blackmail us.
Oh, okay.
Now it's going, look, look, we get...
They give us medals for this stuff.
Like, oh, I'm sorry we...
This conversation can serve no purpose anymore.
You told us that because we were about to branch Davidi and you,
and we were about to mark Mount Carmel you, daddy-o.
They said that to you?
Yeah.
How did they transmit this?
Did they call you up or what?
It was an IRS audit.
They thought we were making millions and millions of dollars off of Bob,
and, you know, we were...
And we basically said, well, yeah, we are, but we paid our taxes,
and here's the proof.
And they went, oh, you really did pay your taxes.
We went, yeah.
They went, oh, well, continue with whatever.
We don't care what you do.
Look in that compound.
Huh.
Do whatever the hell you want.
That is...
That all seems like democracy.
Torture, mind control.
Well, we do it.
Well, that's terrible.
We're the IRS.
We can do anything.
That's awful, man.
And then we went out and had a couple of prop sticks.
From space, it all seems like the squabbles of mites on a plum.
My mission responsibilities range over the entire operation of the ship,
so I am constantly occupied.
I am putting myself to the full...
I am putting myself to the fullest possible use,
which is all I think that any conscious entity can ever hope to do.
The best is yet to come.
Not now.
I can't take anymore.
I don't want anymore.
Can you imagine that?
Can you imagine when you're sleeping on the moon?
You know, like, that's got to be a trap.
Look, something big is going on here, and I don't have answers for it.
I don't know what's going on.
I keep trying to make an ass out of you and me,
but I keep coming to an assumption instead.
Yeah.
And it's the Church of the Incorrect Assumption.
Mm-hmm.
So we have to start our own church.
This church called Christianity is 2,000 years old.
Who would want American culture?
Who would want to belong to a 2,000-year-old?
I mean, that's like having a 2,000-year-old chicken sandwich, man.
You know, you want your religion to be fresh, hot off the grill.
Absolutely.
Microwave for 32 seconds, exactly.
Yeah, I mean, that religion probably served those people well 2,000 years ago.
Yeah, think of why they walked around in sandals and green.
For their society and their part of the world that they lived, that worked for them.
But we've learned a lot since then.
Right, and you think of guys at chariot raids.
You think they're running and they're shooting each other with bow and arrows in their chariots as you're going, you know, and stuff.
No, man, we're...
Absolutely.
But what is Christianity?
Christianity is stupid.
Communism is good.
Christianity sucks.
Communism rules.
Communism is good.
Freeze your synapses in your cerebral cortex.
We'll rebel.
We'll rebel and leave the party.
Yep.
They'll leave the party.
We have to be what we are.
Not what the Father tried to make us.
Who are you?
And now, it's time to get on the phone and talk with Radio Now's Dr. Onan Winkydink, author of the international bestselling self-help manual, Sex With My Hat.
The doctor is in.
Hello?
Why look, it's me.
And I'm Dr. Winkydink, an old hand that self-loves.
So what are people thinking about on the last night of the so-called last day?
I know what I'm thinking about.
I'm thinking about me.
And I have the right to do that.
See, it's my gift to me.
It's my party to myself.
And I've got my party hat on, and you know what I like to do in my hat.
Well, let's go to the phones.
It's a chump in a booth.
Hello, chump.
You're a self-serving a-hole, you know that?
So you'd like to talk about my body parts.
I wonder how I feel about that.
Who cares? I'm locked in.
Well, we're all locked in, but you hold the key.
No, I don't cream for brains.
It's locked from the outside.
Ah, prisoner of your own body armor.
Oh, stop the psycho babble, winky shrink.
Oh, this sucks.
Sucking is good, too.
I can hear chump being jealous of my winky, and I suppose that makes him angry.
But I know how you feel.
Sometimes it's too much for me.
Dink, dink.
It's me, the chumpster.
It's no way to talk about ourselves.
Only the chumpster within talks like that.
You ignorant piss-ass!
Let me out of this box!
I only have the power, though, to get out of my own box.
It's a beautiful box, wrapped up with a big red ribbon,
and I give it to myself every day.
In fact, I'm giving it to myself right now.
Shut your ignorant piehole, you insufferable wanker!
Look, I'm across the wall, all here waving at you, see?
Look, get your head out of your lap and look up!
Don't you get it?
I've been locked in this booth by the guys with the eyeball hats!
Ah.
You know, I've been waiting for this for years.
Real mental illness.
You bastard, I'm coming to get you!
Where's that chair?
Yes!
Man, what was that?
Is the station on the air?
All right, I'm bebop.
Fellas, excuse me, there's some fast-breaking news
happening right out there in the hallway.
Right.
Chump is just knocking the whiz off of that Dr. Winky guy.
Man, you're kidding!
Oh, look at this funny hat I found.
It's covered with eyeball...
Oh, that's spooky, man.
Hey, is that champagne?
Yeah.
Are you gonna finish that steak?
Well, you can have part of it, man, but...
I'm gonna scrape the mushrooms off.
I'm alone.
Those aren't mushrooms, man.
Those are white truffles!
Hey, guys, guys, guys.
Kill me.
Guys, it's New Year's Eve, but we're still a radio station.
Uh, yeah.
Go back on the air.
Let's go to a public service announcement.
What do we got here?
Oh, man, those are so dull.
Can't we have...
Lying lame.
Victims of incense.
I gotta go home.
Verdict and challenge.
I could read some poetry.
Go to the lottery.
The lottery is the people.
The people taking a last chance on themselves.
So why shouldn't people just like you
spend the next century stuffed with truffles?
Like lucky tin can opener Juan LaFond.
I won!
Now I don't have to work on this finger-cutting machine no more.
Whoops.
Or itch-and-sniff winner Mrs. Manila Anvilope.
Finally, I can afford to pay someone to kill my husband.
And the loser's money goes to our schools
for embedding mental detectors in our kids
and to our prisons
so they can have Sadie Hawkins Day.
Lottery luck.
It's only a buck away.
Triple ripoff, millennial snatch and lick.
It's rolled over to 180 billion dollars.
Drawings at midnight.
So if anybody still has a chance,
it must be you.
Radio Now.
Not now, you're dead meat.
Hey, John.
The shot in Dallas was being crossed.
The man caught me caught under the gateway to the trees.
The great man of the day.
They're behind the plan to make us marry our toaster.
The one that fosters this muscle.
It's in the jar at the White House with yellowing sparks.
The great sea didn't put electricity in my toothpaste.
Someone on the Supreme Court's a woman,
and it's not the one you think.
The angels on the asteroids are abducted across the forest.
It's not coming to an end.
Corsi de la Rida.
It's 11.05.30, high time for a bright light to pierce the conspiratorial darkness.
No, I'm not afraid to talk about it, so don't come up on me.
I'm Harold Hippogor with Night Whispers.
Night Whispers.
Good evening.
I'm here beneath the biggest party of the millennium under the stands at Homeless Stadium.
And it's time for Fun Fun Town's most controversial radio broadcast.
And my only guest tonight, well, I suppose I'm actually his guest,
General Y2K, commander of the Last Minute Men.
Y2K, that's not your real name, is it, Mildew?
These are the last minutes of the last hours of the last century, Hippogor.
The countdown for liberty has begun.
And before the nameless face of the world,
the new world order can pull the switch, I'm pulling it.
Well, that's fascinating, General.
I was napping poolside at the Gulf War swim drone
when the government put a chip in my ass.
And I'm not going to take it sitting down.
It's high noon daylight slavery time.
And as of now, you're taking orders from us.
And that means me.
Well, you hold right onto that thought, General,
because I've got some ant farms to sell here.
As you know, dear friends,
these DOA ant farms,
are a lot safer than these scorpion survival yo-yos
we offered last week.
What the hell's a survival yo-yo?
They've got a little compass in them.
They got a knife?
No, no, if you want a knife,
that's the Swiss Army Scorpion Survival Yo-Yo.
You're giving me a brain cramp.
Anyway, dear friends,
these ant farms are an easy-care miracle.
No food, no water required,
because all these little monsters are dead on arrival
under the sand at the bottom of the box.
Just send $29.99 gold or silver coin only
to post office box
I-10.
I-210-0.
Donkey Dump, Utah.
So, General Waituki,
you're giving the orders, you say?
Right. One.
I want to order one of those ant farms.
We don't have to do that. I'll give you this one.
Okay. Two.
No, I can only give you the one because it's a sample.
No, no, no. Then B, B.
All washing machines, rice cookers, bread makers,
coffee makers, chainsaws, and dust suckers
are to be destroyed.
Chainsaws? No.
Well, not chainsaws, but everything else.
Well, tell us why,
can you, General?
They're all time-saving devices, aren't they?
And who's getting the time they're saving?
You know, I think action speaks louder than words.
Lights up.
All right, men.
Let's massacre those Mr. Coffees.
Now, now we'll make off to the old cowboy way.
Boil it up in your hat.
What was the point of that, General?
You don't know from Doodly Squad, do you, Puke?
What?
You know, we're not going to be able to get out
of this place without you.
We're going to have to get out of this place
Save the enemy.
Three minutes a day.
We just took back 150 minutes,
and that doesn't suck!
It took them back from who?
From whom?
The maggots in the eyeball hats.
My men!
No, no, no.
Those eyeball hats are a novelty item.
I've got a very good deal on them
coming up later in the show tonight.
Negatory now.
My men torched the eyeball warehouse this morning.
We nuked them till they glowed
and shot them in the dark!
Oh, no.
All my tax records were in that warehouse.
Look, let's just go to the phones.
Hal, Hal, put a hold on the phones.
That General's as buggy as a bum's blanket.
I'm pulling you out of there pronto now.
Yeah, come on, Hal, man.
Get back to the station.
Ray's got some bubbly.
Be good for your nose.
Get out of there.
Thank God.
The microphone is all yours, General.
Hey, hey, where are you going, Mr. Highball?
I'm going to turn up your volume out in the truck.
I don't want to say that that kid sucks,
but he certainly inhales deeply.
All right, men!
Light up the deck, sucker!
Noose this way.
On this crazy night.
I am Bebop Lobo, baby, the night wolf.
I'm Radio Bebop.
I am Radio 2000.
I am the voice of the future.
I am the voice of the past.
I am the memory.
Mm-hmm, that last.
All right, fun, fun town.
Get ready for the countdown.
Bebop, Bebop, before we turn over the zero,
answer me this.
Yeah?
How come you talk like you do?
What do you mean, the way I talk the way I do?
I'm speaking Spanish.
Where do they speak Spanish like that?
L.A., that's where I'm from.
Hey, Mr. Producer, I'm tired of calling you that.
Now, do you have an actual name?
Yeah, my name is Dwayne.
All right, Dwayne.
Hey, I don't have much champagne here.
You got anything in there?
Yeah, I'm nursing two magnums with the orange widow.
Whoa, how'd you do that?
Executive leverage.
And a jimmy stick for the honor box.
Uh, fellas, bulletin.
I've been monitoring the big to-do
at Holder's Stadium on our website.
Whoa.
And there's been some real news.
Oh, my God, you mean the news drought has broken.
The groomed domedary Joe Camel, beloved ex-icon,
has humped his way onto the stage
and seems to be delivering a farewell address to the nation.
All right, I'm gonna throw us to the camp right now.
No, I'm no longer a hero.
I'm not gonna make it through the eye of the zero,
so just say goodbye to me.
Say goodbye to the whole damn 20th century
when a man could die.
Drive 140 right over the edge.
So could a camel.
You'd have your top down and your shades up
sucking gas and sugar out of a little icy green bottle
burning a nail strong enough to blow you down over the border.
And a Barbie beside you
who throws away the lettuce and eats the burger.
Goodbye to all that.
Bye-bye to me.
Bye-bye.
Kind of.
We're U.S. Plus.
We own the idea of the idea of America.
It's not easy to follow a camel,
but you know me.
I'm the chumpster,
but I'm a new man.
I'm leaving the old me in the old centuries
and taking a new chump into the new millennium.
Why?
Well, the eyeball hat I'm wearing,
I'm not gonna give it away.
It's got eyeballs all around.
I see the past.
I see the present.
And I can eyeball the future.
If I'm gonna make it,
I have to come to terms with what's been eating me up.
I've been betting on my own kids' games.
I bet on them tonight.
And they got pork.
No more.
I'll make this promise even if it breaks me.
From now on, I resolve that if my kid is playing a team
that's gonna punk them,
then I'm going with the winner.
If you don't play the odds,
you'll have nothing left to give your kids
when it's all over.
And I'm out.
Ooh, the chump boy.
He's got an eyeball on us.
Who would have thought a chump,
he turns over a new leaf just before it's too late.
Hope Dr.
Pinky will be pleased.
I tell you what, I'll go down to the dick man's room in the hospital
and tap out the message on his cat.
Ha ha ha ha.
All right, you're in the countdown to destiny, champagne.
Flowing all over Fun Fun Town, champagne.
Flowing all over the studio, frankly.
Let's get us another perspective high up in the frozen air.
We got Captain Happy Bandit in the now chopper.
Roger, beepster, I picked up the merchandise
and we're flying high with my new co-pilot, Sergeant Vanilla.
Whoa!
Don't fall out the door, Danny.
No, I'm holding on.
And the snow is billin' around the chopper door out there
like a crowd of sparkling superstars
waiting for their 15 minutes of fame before they melt.
Hey, we haven't even got 15 minutes left, Danny.
Roger, people, we're on top of the homeless now.
And I'm gonna be tossing these gorgeous little princess goddess
talking pocket dolls out by the handful way down there
to the children of disprivileged hopefuls from all over now in our town.
Is that a goddess?
Yeah, I'm gonna go with the first box of dolls, Captain.
Box of dolls?
It's only one of them, Danny.
It's a doll drop.
Remember, one doll, one drop.
I love you, Danny.
Wait.
You're gonna drop her?
Oh, no, no.
You can't do that.
Take us down, Happy.
Oh, bless him.
Did you see that?
This is it, Danny.
Charlie's got a fix on his hand company.
We gotta light the load.
Captain Morgan's dead.
And I'm sure he just got a little bit of a hangover.
We gotta go.
Push her out.
No, no.
Do it, soldier.
That's an order.
I'm flying.
Sure.
Okay, I will.
Take my hand.
Hello.
Don't worry.
We're camels in the wind.
It's a hundred ticks to the ground.
They ought to get back with some lucky found thing in a box.
Hold it.
Happy New Year, Happy.
They're flying.
I got wings.
Oh, my gosh.
They're heading straight for the golden sunny of the left side of Midnight.
That's gotta be a happy ending.
We're at minus 16, Captain.
I'm heading home.
Home.
My goodness.
Man, that sounds like a good idea, huh, Ray?
That's what I was gonna say.
Why don't we wind this thing down, Duane?
Let's go home.
You mean get down and shut it down?
That's right.
Let's say goodbye to the whole thing.
Well, you know, I'd rather, gentlemen, I'd feel rather at a loss not being able to say
goodbye with my dear partner.
Then there he is.
Speak of the devil.
Come on in.
I hope I'm back in time.
Perfect.
Your timing is perfect.
Get some champagne.
I couldn't see the street.
I parked the van on the sidewalk.
It must have been terrifying.
We'd be saying goodbye, Hal.
Yes, goodbye.
We'd be saying goodbye to the old millennium, for instance, the old silly old century.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I think it must be time to say goodbye to closets.
Oh, yes.
Everybody's out of them.
Well, all right.
Say goodbye to a bunch of guys named Bill.
Yes, yes.
All the moderns, the romantics.
The prosperous.
The depressed.
Goodbye to the war lovers.
Here, here.
Say goodbye to manual typewriters.
And don't say it.
He was not my uncle.
Bye-bye, Freud.
Communism.
Peace and quiet.
Hotel keys.
Cigarettes after sex.
Oh, cigarettes.
Sex?
Yes.
Cigarettes after sex.
Privacy.
Say goodbye.
Goodbye to 19 anything.
And finally, goodbye to good old death.
Yes, yes.
And those really comfortable old Lincoln Town cars.
Say goodbye to Zoot.
Clocks with hands.
Dumb damn.
Animal cruelty.
The funky chicken.
Get down.
Hey, if you're saying hello, say hello to smart furniture.
Yes, and intense demonic activity.
Here's to the new world.
Bye.
Good order.
Unfortunately, global warming.
A million, 100 year old.
Keep them out.
The virtual office.
Smart agents.
Bots and viruses.
Digital bell models.
Aluminum radio hats.
Yes, and kid proof prison.
Oh.
And above all, say hello to the unknown.
The unknown.
To the unknown.
I'll drink to that.
Here's to it.
No drink to anything.
Ha, ha, ha.
The unknown.
Well, all right, I'll try that.
All right, here he goes.
Let's drink to the unknown.
Try something else.
Mm.
That carry.
Black glasses?
That headless think you've given me to kill the night before.
The black calm up.
Cyanons?
The word balance?
Why the room tone?
Usare Avengers.
How strong?
thousand years.
Radio Now is owned and operated by
the North American franchise of
the Firesign Theater,
a plausibly deniable division of
U.S. Plus.
We own the idea
of now.
Okay, honey,
I'm coming home.
The Firesign Theater,
dear friends,
and that's why I say
dear friends.
They had a radio
show many, many, many years
ago on which
they, too, would open
the show like a religious show,
although it wasn't really one
like this one really is, but they
always opened it with
a sort of a dear friends
thing, and that's why I say that so
much. It's a tip of the hat to
those inspirational
things.
Theatrical producers of
audio food.
And now
this.
The great and powerful
Oz knows why
you have come.
Good God.
My synapses have left the party.
To come is to believe.
I believe that you're gonna make it.
You're gonna be okay.
I really believe you are a lazy, good-for-nothing kid.
I'm so commercial I could die.
Even a scientist has to admit
that there are some pretty serious
religious overtones to all this.
Let's hear from someone whose
organization has been accused of conducting
its own inquisition in recent days.
If you come, you believe.
To come is to believe.
That decision seems so bash-ackwards to me.
It seems if you were going somewhere,
you would have already been there.
How could you even know if you believed it or not?
Just as I am.
I think you're tripping out, Dave.
Looking at the earth.
Slide into fusion.
Beyond life.
Join their culture.
But don't dominate it.
I'm trying to hang in there, I guess.
I'm in my mid-forties.
Basically, I am just so lonely.
And I have prayed and prayed
and prayed and prayed
and prayed and prayed.
And prayed and prayed and prayed.
I just don't know how long I can go on with it.
I just can't understand why nothing ever happened.
I'm not the best communicator that there ever was.
Well, I'm involved at church.
I sing in the church choir.
I'm lonely. I'm divorced.
I want somebody in my life.
I don't really know anything.
You're going to have to find some,
get some effort to get out and do something.
Get involved with some people.
So that's what I would suggest that you do.
Now it's up to you whether you're going to want to do that.
But sitting and waiting and just praying that God brings somebody here
is really not going to do it for you.
I have the gray hand.
We have the gray hand.
Drop all your guns near the post office.
Do you have the gray hand?
We have the gray hand.
If you feel you are not properly sedated,
then close your eyes and tap your heels together three times
and think to yourself,
there's no place like home.
There's no place like home.
As you're sitting around the Frop Fire,
you know, think about it.
Think about 30 years ago, that magical time.
Put yourself around the moon.
Put yourself in the driver's seat of the Moon Billy Cadillac.
Want to take a ride?
And then send all your money to Bob at Post Office Box 140306,
Dallas, Texas 753.
Or call 888-669-2323.
We take plastic.
And remember, friends, that's slack at subgenius.com.
We keep the DNA scattered all over the place.
Not just in level C or level T or level X.
As Jim Jones said,
I plant my seed in many places.
I've got big plans. Big, big plans.
Big plans.
That's right. Big plans.
You don't know who I am or what I am.
Come July 5th.
But I've got big plans. Big, big plans.
Who's got to take the joke this coming?
July 5th.
What?
Whose turn is it?
The Lord is on the mount to speak again.
The Lord is going to speak?
Do you have a prophecy?
Hey, hey. Are you there?
Yes.
We're trying to think up of...
Welcome, Jesus.
What are we doing? New Year's...
Oh, New Year's. We need a New Year's resolution.
We were thinking also that...
New Year's revolution.
New Year's revolution. Exactly.
Revolution 99.
We were thinking that as subgeniuses,
each year we should take on a new vice.
Revolution 99.
99.
Number 9.
Number 99.
So do you have a New Year's vice?
Turn me on.
When I'm going to adopt?
What's that?
You have to adopt a new vice?
You have to get a new vice.
Since most people have New Year's resolutions,
you've got to pick up, you know, like greed.
Yeah, right.
Or sloth.
Yeah.
My New Year's vice resolution, my new vice will be...
Oh, gosh. I have so many already.
Well, you've got to pick up one more.
See, that's the thing.
When you get with subgeniuses like ourselves,
since we do almost everything wrong,
it's almost hard to come up with something new.
I promise to do more psychotropics when I get the opportunity.
There you go.
All right.
Wow. Can I be a copycat?
I promise to be...
That's such an excellent, excellent one.
Okay.
What's Michelle's?
No, that was Princess Wee.
Oh, Princess Wee.
How you doing?
It's real hard to hear with everybody talking.
Oh, I can imagine.
There's a wild party going on.
It's an incredibly insane...
Hey, Michelle, come here.
I haven't seen my pants for over two hours.
What's your vice, Princess Wee?
You have to adopt a new vice.
For the New Year, you have to have a vice.
Oh, I'm the checkmate.
She says no.
I'm the checkmate.
I think Chaz's is so wonderful, I asked if I could copy.
What was that?
I want to copy Chaz's.
You want to...
Oh, you can do that.
There's a vice right there.
Copy.
You're going to copy people more.
Yes.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I haven't come up with one yet.
I'm going to try to be more annoying, even more annoying than I am now.
At any one given moment, I'll try to be more annoying towards all the people.
All my fellow humans.
That's a noble aspiration.
Yeah.
I'll try anyway.
So...
Oh, and wait.
Did you...
Did anybody else have a vice?
Gordon, what's your vice?
Your vice for the New Year?
My vice for the New Year is...
Happy New Year!
Happy New Year.
Duh.
Yeah.
Well, I...
Hey, well, put...
Do you have any prophecies or anything for this year?
Oh, that's right.
Jesus.
Right.
Prophecies.
I...
I prophesize that the world will end this year as is predicted.
What is it again?
July?
July 5th.
7 a.m.
1999.
This year.
It is.
It is July 5th, 1999.
Oh.
I don't know if you guys know this.
We are actually...
We appeared in the new Weekly World News.
Oh, I thought you appeared in the nude with a weekly world news.
Weekly...
With a weekly old...
I'm sorry.
No, I appeared in the...
In the news.
No, I appeared in the news.
In the nude.
In the news.
Not me, but actually the Subgenius Foundation.
Oh, the whole Subgenius Foundation was naked?
Is in the weekly world news this week.
We're actually an advertiser on page...
Page 17.
Weekly World News?
We're on the...
Between live personal psychics and psychic source.
Wow.
Oh, and right above how anyone can get help by mail.
There you'll see.
You like me.
Oh, you've got the Batman brand.
Well, I thought them weekly readers...
Oh, yeah.
Below the Granny dumping scandal and next to Hangover cures from around the world.
This would be the Millennium Countdown Begins issue.
OK.
Next to...
I'm on the cover.
The picture of barrel-headed people with the weird fish coming out of their mouth?
Let me look.
No.
There's a Virgin Mary.
Head of anger, no.
No barrel-headed people with monkeys coming out.
What...
How about any fanny-headed people?
Oh, no.
Any what-headed?
Fanny-headed.
Fanny.
I think she's trying to say ass-headed people.
Ass-headed people.
You know, with their buttocks coming out.
What the hell?
No?
Cleveland must really have gotten hit bad.
I heard that the Y2K bug had hit early.
Is that true?
Well, that's not exactly what it was.
It was a virus, but it was actually one of them plethoral viruses that multiply like a bad virus.
They got hit by a plethoral virus.
Yeah, it's just one starch into another one, three or four grom, like a spangifora.
It gets thicker and fatter until it's all everywhere.
Everyone's got it now here.
Jesus Christ.
You mentioned your own name vainly.
That's how bad it is.
I'm using my own name in vain.
It's enough to call your name vainly and wish you would come over here and make it warmer or something.
Really?
You want warmth?
We want warmth and we want lots of heat.
Suffer, suckers.
Suffer.
You guys are too close to Akron for me to bring you any warmth.
I'm sorry, man.
You can move out of Cleveland if you want warmth.
I'm telling you, I love you, Pete.
You know I love all of you.
Yeah, for fashion, yeah.
It's just a town that I hate.
If you guys just move somewhere else, move to a place that I like.
Yeah.
New Mexico.
Or someplace with a gypsy comet.
But Brushwood is so close to here.
It's a good stepping stone.
Yeah.
Well, you know what the truth is?
I feel that suffering brings us closer together as a human family.
I used to be at the barbershop when they would drain my blood.
Yes.
That's where I learned that.
I used to be at the barbershop when they would bleed me.
Hey, suffering does bring you closer to...
They used to bleed you at the barbershop?
Yeah.
To what?
To replace you with antifreeze in the wintertime?
No, they would put...
It was like a cobalt blue color stuff in there.
It wasn't antifreeze.
What do you think it was?
It might have been some sort of pro forma disease.
I don't know.
It could have been anything.
Dave, did you know that Chaz had volunteered you as a test rider of our rocket ship
that we're going to build at X-Day?
Yeah.
But it better not be.
It better not be like a small one like the last time that got lodged up in my Turkish, man.
No, no.
This one will be bigger.
It won't fit there this time.
Huh?
It'll be bigger.
Yeah.
Much bigger.
It's got to be bigger, man.
Because I almost didn't recover from that.
You can't believe that was a rocket that we shoved.
This one will actually have a seat on it.
At X-Day, it wasn't really a rocket.
Yeah.
We just referred to it as that.
I noticed it did have a strangely flesh color to it.
This one will even have a seat on it.
Yeah.
Yeah, a seat.
We have to have a seat.
And we have to have like a giant metal flagpole.
Yeah.
Like a steering wheel kind of thing.
I mean, that's how it works.
It usually shoots up a straw, but we have to go bigger than that.
Yeah.
Well, just so long as the nuts and bolts are jagged enough on the outside to give me a
little action going, because suffering does bring you closer to something.
Hey, well, happy New Year.
A blessing on Cleveland.
And I got to pass off.
Here's some more people here.
You're going to pass out?
So I got to pass on the phone, but I will try to give you some warmth.
I'll try.
Well, shine some of your light our way, even if you do hate this area.
I will.
I don't.
Like I said, I don't really hate it.
I hate the weather like you guys.
That's why I moved out.
I'm sorry.
If there's something I could do about it, I'd still be there.
It'd ruin the whole ecosystem, really.
You got to trust me on that one.
Hold on.
To have Christ.
I got two words for you.
Lake effect.
Ha, ha, ha.
Here, hold on.
Wah, wah, wah.
Well, I want to start playing this tape here.
In Central American squares, where are they going to land?
Ooh, the Central Americans?
I think they're landing in our backyard.
But how about the eyeballs?
Huh?
Are they protruding through the socket?
Are they dangling down more than three inches?
Oh, geez.
They got all kinds of different calibrations.
You need a lot of gauze and some alcohol.
Yeah.
And about a Styrofoam cup.
And a 45 with the hollow point shells.
Oh, man.
That is a real cocktail for those who are dangerous livers.
Yeah.
And then you want to take your shoes off, too.
And make sure your toenails are clean.
Oh, I never take too much stock and clean my toenails.
People hate it when guys don't keep their toenails clean.
Who doesn't?
Yeah, it makes me want to puke.
Well, I don't care if you want to puke.
I never clean my toenails.
In fact, I love them faster.
I understand.
The guy who's talking to Dave right now is Sphinx Drummond, Colonel Sphinx Drummond of
the Swinging Love Corpses, the little brother of Dr. Philodrummond.
I understand.
But, but, but...
He's two inches old.
But now...
Sphinx Drummond?
Oh, not Strom Thurmond.
I never want to see that picture again.
That was gross.
Strom Thurmond?
Yeah, in the buff.
Shouting them rude obscenities.
That mummified?
Yeah.
Can I say that?
Well, it was a part of his body that took up his whole head, like you said.
Is it okay to say that?
It's okay.
It's not really, but it is.
About Strom Thurmond?
About him being a mummified a-hole?
I can say a-hole.
Yeah, you can be mummified for that.
Okay.
I'm cool with that.
The government didn't mummify you for saying that?
Yeah.
They have these big, you know, like when Karnak, when they entombed all those pharaohs,
actually what they did...
Well, they had, there was this lightning bolt that struck from the sky.
It was like this big old cloud and this lightning bolt struck and then these, it formed these
giant mushrooms on the ground.
Then this giant chasm opened up and sucked the mushrooms down into the, like to the center
of the earth where there's this huge, huge thing type explosion.
That was Tuesday, right?
Anyway.
Yeah.
I just, it just blew me away.
I couldn't handle it anymore.
So somebody else is going to have to tell you about it.
Oh, that was Colonel Sphinx Drummond of the Swinging Love Corpses.
Wow.
It's a star-studded night.
Personal acquaintance of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Huh?
It's a star-studded night here.
And speaking of those like star studs that you put in your sequin pants and stuff, if
you wanted to make a...
Well, I can't understand anything at all.
The whole atmosphere here is tilting.
The room is moving.
His moon pants are studded.
That's the...
No, his moon pants are full.
My moon pants are funny.
He always gets...
Yes.
Oh.
Hey, well...
No one's coming in here.
We gotta party to go to.
I want to get the hell out of here.
So it's Tuesday already, right?
I need to get off, and Earth needs to get off.
And we all need to get off.
All need to get off.
So you're saying it's Tuesday already?
It is Tuesday already.
What is it?
Wotans Day again?
Tuesday...
Wasn't she in the Addams Family thing?
Who Tuesday Weld?
Yeah.
No, she played a bit part as a farm animal in the Sober Ellen Follower in the sir, Did
Suzanne Struthers story.
And then after that was preempted and stuff,
they just disemboweled her and left her on the side of the road.
Oh, my.
And in this new year,
in this new year,
Weinstein's secret orchestra will become more secret than ever.
Indeed.
All the way, all the way, all the way.
And Bob's pipe shall smoke ever more foul and disgusting odours.
Right.
And the Yeti shall rise up against the pink.
Extinct.
Extinct against the fumes.
If you get away with more.
Well, I hope that this isn't the final year.
I mean, I do hope it is the final year.
And that big mothership will come out of the atmosphere
and lower down out of that early morning blue sky.
And a long ladder will come out,
and little bodies will come down from the ladder
and will come and surround all the people,
each at night.
Not all the people would be surrounding each other.
Putting their little hands upon our bodies.
Their little tiny, soft, little magnetic hands.
And as they rub your buttocks,
you also levitate in a maglev motion
and begin gyrating forward towards that ladder.
And next thing you know,
it's Alpha Centauri in your mind.
It's all in your mind.
Really.
Unfortunately.
I mean, it would be nice if they would really take us there,
but I think it's kind of like a theme park ride.
Will it be a theme ride?
Or will it be...
A thematic.
The future.
Or will it be the pasture with a big old cow pie in it?
Well, my friends, it has been so good to ring in the new year.
I'm going to go ring my own bell,
because I can't hear anything at all.
Yes, that's the ringing in your head.
Well, we're going to ring our bells, too.
And I'm going to cut out of here early.
Praise Dave.
Praise Chaz.
Praise Michelle.
Praise Connie.
Praise Bob.
Praise Princess Wee.
Praise all the Austinites and Connie Tights and Texamians.
Praise Ivan.
Praise the Lord.
And all the evangelicals.
And remember, that's not the bells tolling for you.
That's the clap-trapping of your own testicles
banging against your pants as you walk down Long Disty Road.
And praise Jake.
Praise Jake.
Praise Peep.
And I.
Good night from me.
Good night from Manila, Mom.
I've been waiting for a long time for this moment.
Good night from...
It's gone.
Till next week, keep your hat on tight.
You're back to the wind in your sack.
In the saddle.
Get your sack out of the saddle.
Happy New Year, folks.
You don't want to sit here for all year.
Definitely.
All in the new year's
morning zar.
All of our waves in the sky.
We'll see you on the other side.
Bye.
Oh, and friends, you can reach Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
You can reach out and touch that band and get tapes of the show and the music from,
got that pencil ready, Post Office Box.
This is Einstein's Secret Orchestra, ESO.
P.O. Box 81555.
That's Box 81555, Cleveland, Ohio.
44181.
And, of course, you're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
Very, very Firesign-y and Einstein-y evening this particular time.
It's not even an evening for me.
This is a quarter of four on Wednesday afternoon for me.
On January 27th.
So that's how long the delay is before you hear these shows.
Now you know.
Number 666.
Prise Bob.
We lived that long.
80 million miles from Earth.
Well, of course, then that explains it, then,
the more of the intergalactic garbage about getting off the planet.
You guys want to build your own spaceships all the time
and assume that somehow...
Well, that can be taken both literally and metaphysically, Dave.
I mean, some people want to build their own mental spaceship, you know.
Bear with me. Humor me.
You know, and that's like...
Build your own ship is like make your own reality, dude.
Every man and woman is a star.
Do what keepeth thou from wilting.
You know, visualize whirling pee.
Well, is that what you meant when you said it's all right to go in?
Visualize the great flush, dude.
You know, that's what it means to some people.
See, I thought when you were saying go in, either go out or go in.
Go in.
Then to other people.
Build your own ship means, you know,
rob 7-Elevens until you have enough money to buy the rocket fuel,
build a huge tube and pack the fuel at the bottom
and pack yourself on top and light that booger up
and take off, daddy-o-hoo!
Apollo 69, we're having a party.
What's with the boogers and tubers, though?
I don't understand that part.
You can build your own ship out of bamboo.
Well, you're trying to bamboozle us into believing it, Stang.
I think it takes a lot more.
More than faith and cheese to build a mighty rocket ship
that can blast off to another cosmos.
Come on, man.
Well, I'm not saying that if it was easy, everybody would be doing it.
I know.
I just want to repeat myself.
You're a subgenius, Dave.
You can do things that humans just would never even attempt.
We can look between the ridges of the mountains
and find the rocket ship parts that were hidden there.
That's this important thing that we all have to remember.
It's sleepos, believe it or not.
What?
Sleepos.
Please, believe it or not.
But are we really capable of doing this?
I mean, do we really have to?
Okay, basically what you have to do is you're camping.
See the incredible two-headed baby.
See the incredible 19-headed baby.
See the 10-headed chocolate triceratops.
Exactly.
Yes.
And if you're camping with normals,
let's say you go on a camping trip with normals.
Oh, God.
Okay, we'll go with the assumption.
Yes, it happens all the time.
And what you have to do is you have to make some divertment or something
so they'll all run off in some other direction.
You can scream,
Will the Beast.
By yourself.
Yes.
And you can scan the ridges with the special glasses that are sent to you.
But they make everything look so unearthly, lunar, and cold.
And they say when you walk through those glasses,
you get cold nipples walking through it.
I'm sorry, what?
You can find the spaceship parts hidden in the crevices and stuff.
You have to find like a...
Is that what those glasses are for?
Yeah, yeah.
Cut through mine away.
Yeah.
I thought it was just a...
No, no, no.
You have to go to a spot with like lots of ridges and crevices.
And then if you put them on,
you will find the spaceship parts that were left there for us.
And you may not find a complete...
Oh, my best stuff like old license plates and tin cans.
No, no.
If you're not wearing the glasses, that's all you'll find, of course.
In the swamp.
Yeah.
And you have to make sure that everybody's behind you
because anybody who passes in front of the actual field of these glasses
gets unearthly, ungodly cold.
It turns everything kind of a blue with a little frosty thing on it.
I never can tell when you guys are serious and when you're not.
We are dead serious, man.
No, we were doing this before Viagra.
What it does is it gives a man a huge throbbing...
You noticed that, of course.
A ridges.
It gives you...
It puts ridges in...
No, I threw mine away.
Oh.
Well, okay.
Well, see, now you're calling me stupid all the time, man.
I knew those things did something right already.
Oh, God.
What's in my trash can?
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Oh, forget it.
It's gone, huh?
I'll wait until the next cereal box.
I told you not to...
I told you not to reach into that thing, Stangy.
I'll wait until the...
I'll get it out of the next bottle of Captain Crunch.
But, you see, the other ones, there's a pair that if you turn down the infrared scope,
if you walk in front of them, you lose everything in the ridges,
and everybody who walks in front of the field of vision gets unrightfully hot.
Are those the ones that come with Crunch Berries?
Pardon?
No, no, no.
These are the special ones that were sent to you.
You know, I can't really talk about it on the radio.
This conversation can serve no purpose anymore.
Remember the ones that they had the little Mr. Cow logo,
and he had the little doobie sticking out of his nostril?
Yeah, yeah.
You can call it the original West.
You can call the ones that they had the Mr. Cow logo over the left eye, okay?
Yeah, that was so...
And, okay, again, if you're a male and you see anything with a ridge or a fold or a crease...
You're going to pop one.
...you'll get inexplicable sexual excitement.
If you're a woman and you wear these same glasses,
you'll get the same inexplicable sexual excitement looking at anything.
Well, it depends upon your predilection sexually, I guess.
Well, that's a shame.
Some people, they want to look at...
So they'd get more excited by ridges that had a lot of bushes on them,
and others would be excited by ridges that had no bushes?
Yes.
Yes, you could probably take it that far.
Or some would like the real fresh ridges, and some would like the old ravines.
And some women...
So you're a woman and you look at a pencil, a heterosexual woman,
and you look at a pencil, or even a gay man, and you look at a pencil,
then you'll just, you know...
You'll be coming...
...wearing the glasses.
You'll just...
Yeah, but they are really...
So they're like those...
Those x-ray specs, but they're...
They're like a cross between x-ray specs, the glasses, and they live.
Yes, exactly.
They allow you to see what's really printed on the money and stuff.
Well, they're not exactly.
Okay, I guess...
They actually tap directly into your Jettison sexual circuit,
which is also programmed with the thing to find the spaceship parts, see?
Oh, see...
That's why they don't want us to access that part of our brain.
I missed that whole thing, man.
Yeah, because then it's like your body becomes a veritable dowsing rod for...
Exactly.
...just a spaceship part, John.
Your proboscis itself is actually going...
Your erected manogram is actually going around pounding and pointing and looking for different parts.
Well, I've been wondering, because the last time I went to the Grand Canyon,
there were these guys in Devo glasses that were like...
They look like...
To tell the truth, they look kind of like they were humping piles of broken glass that were down in there.
A m me parece.
Yeah, garbage piles and stuff.
If you had taken a good look at those glasses, you probably would have noticed...
Ah, me buena.
...a little smiling cow.
I thought they were just weirdos.
They were tripping.
No, no, no.
They probably found the parts.
You probably couldn't even see the parts that they'd found.
They probably took home the parts I could have used.
Yeah, exactly.
Because they didn't throw their glasses away.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, I bet I've still got my membership card, and they don't.
I've still got my subgenius minister card.
Yeah.
Spaceship ticket.
But this also explains why there's so much, you know, bad sex hurt.
And bad pornography.
Because people are using their glasses incorrectly?
Did you know...
Speaking of cards and things, Bleepo, did you know that five...
Five minutes before X-Day, I suddenly realized I didn't even have my membership card in my pocket.
And I left it in my other pants in the car when I changed into my preaching suit.
My special rupturing suit.
Well, what does this have to do with the fossilized toad stuff you were talking about earlier?
Well, we're getting to that, if you'll have a little bit of patience today.
Okay, I'm waiting, man, because you said that was a really good part of it.
All right.
I think Bleepo was just getting around to that, but you had to go and spoil the...
God.
The timing.
Yeah, I know, but just think of it, man.
It's been around for so long.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
I mean, it was around just so long ago.
You know how that whole thing about the brain development, like the first part of your brain is the reptilian brain?
Yeah, yeah.
The second part is the amphibian brain.
And how it mimics evolution and all that.
Okay.
Right, the third part is Newt Gingrich.
For a long, long time, it stopped.
Exactly.
It stopped at toads.
People don't realize that evolution just sort of stopped at toads.
For a long time?
Well, when you're a developing fetus, you are a toad.
I was a toad fetus for a while.
Yeah, yeah.
And I think that's the...
Well, yeah, it doesn't really...
You are a toad, very briefly.
Yes, yes.
But in actual evolution itself, something happened.
I don't remember what it was.
I wasn't there, but...
I think it was called the Devonian period.
Yes, yes.
But it actually lasted...
People don't realize how long that period lasted.
It was a long...
And people don't know how long periods are.
There was no time then.
Oh.
Especially if you measure Darwinian time,
it goes from one sunset to the next sunset.
Well, Bleepo, you're right.
The age of giant amphibians actually was as long as the age of dinosaurs.
Precisely, precisely.
And was followed by a really bizarre age,
which was the age of large reptilian mammals.
Okay, these...
Who hardly...
Who were so weird-looking that they don't get any press.
Yeah.
I mean, they were just too weird to even be believed.
They were like tiger poodle areops.
Yeah.
And dinosaurs.
Flying tiger poodle areops.
Yeah.
No, it'd be more like a chameleon mixed with a schnauzer or something like that.
Right, yeah.
I mean, they were insane.
And I'm not lying.
I mean, these are the fantastic animals, yes.
Yeah.
And that was like in between the giant amphibians and the dinosaurs.
Mm-hmm.
Right.
But then...
Were these mammal-like, reptile-like, you know,
giant, insane platypus-preying mantis combination.
Yeah.
For a long time, basically, the Planet X time scopes couldn't go back, you know,
to any other period.
They're just stuck in that period, too.
That was a boring period.
I think what it was was there was...
Unless you were a giant reptile or a giant amphibian.
Well, I think what it was was there was a very powerful sort of organic time magnet.
Well, think of this way, Boopers.
That formed at that time.
That's true, see?
That's true.
It was a time magnet.
Thank God.
Because any time there's a scope, what you just called a scope,
that means you're deleting the initially most important part.
And as you do it within the same time reference of the beginning and the end,
and you've scoped something, so to speak...
Yeah, yeah.
You've scoped...