Ladies and gentlemen, it gives me great pleasure to present Batman.
Batman.
Oh, by the way, it may sound strange, but...
What?
Ah, okay.
Gosh, what does it mean?
The self-genius power of...
S.T.A.R.F.
I am S.T.A.R.F.
Oh no no no no no no no no no no no no no no.
What is it?
It's a laugh riot.
That grinning devil.
Tonight, once more, we can all sleep peacefully in our beds,
secure in the knowledge that there is a Batman,
and just eight years old.
The Steaming Sack of Black Part One
In the beginning,
there was only
Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob.
Aaaaaah.
For more information, visit subgenius.com.
Look at it this way. At least you didn't lose money on this accident.
Well, not as much as some.
Well, because it's a continuing guarantee.
Right.
It doesn't expire until I expire.
We don't know what year this is. The next day could be tomorrow.
Well, the eternal salvation or triple your money back doesn't expire until I expire.
Right. Oh, no, no, no. Until, if you don't get eternal salvation.
Eternally.
Right. It doesn't expire until you can prove that the eternal salvation.
Oh, no, it didn't keep you alive.
Oh, my God.
You can die. It's just the eternal part of the salvation.
You have to prove you didn't get it for eternity.
Okay, so I could have got like a decent chunk of salvation, but not eternal.
Now it's like 105 bucks. Triple your money back is 105 now.
True enough.
Okay, so what's the going rate on one year of salvation?
Oh, it doesn't work. We don't break it down. It's eternal or nothing, man.
If it's 105 bucks.
It's all or nothing.
It's like, what's the going rate?
What's one year of salvation's worth? I mean, and so my 35 versus the one year of the market rate of salvation.
Oh, I'm going to have to leave that math to you, man.
That's kind of a personal decision.
It is. That is something.
What's it worth to you?
Well, I mean, it depends.
We should work on that. Yeah, we should work on that. We'll come up with an answer by next year.
Like a chart of the market price of salvation.
Bring the chart next next day. Next day.
You know, I'm on it. I'm on it.
Yeah. I'm on the way to bed.
Yeah.
I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean.
Here you go.
You're normally such a slacker.
It's the first time you've heard of him.
Are all four of you guys in here?
Is Phil in there?
He just, yeah, yeah.
Can we?
Doing with four?
Yeah, all four.
Okay.
What are we doing?
How do we?
This is, this is.
Oh, the others.
They'll do the comedy.
How about this is Phil, Phil, Pete, and Dave of the Fireside Theater.
Okay.
This is Phil.
Phil.
Let's take it again.
Oh, Pete and Dave.
Okay, there we go, yeah.
All right, you over here?
You just shut up.
This is Phil.
Phil.
Pete.
And Dave of the Fireside Theater.
And we're listening to The Hour of Slack.
Because we're subgeniuses.
And we're slacking off.
From PR News in Washington, I'm charged with unlawful entry of animals inside the White House last night.
Heavy equipment maker Caterpillar says Canada remains closed to the public today after yesterday's incident in the Canadian country today.
Inside there.
Bob says that did not turn out to be the case.
There weren't more.
More.
Act it alone.
On Wall Street 321716, profits are soaring sky high for Ebola Airlines.
According to the Labor Department, you're listening to PR News in Washington.
Smoke gun.
All right, come on up out of there.
I'll shoot.
No.
You alone?
Yes.
You live around here?
No.
You've got 15 minutes to get out of Dodge.
No, please.
I just woke up.
All right, let's go.
Water.
Need water.
Why does Indian come to white man for water?
Young brave.
Hurt bad.
Water far.
Need water fast.
Get 15 minutes to get out of Dodge.
We go now.
Go in peace.
Say, you know.
Now, now, now here is kind of an interesting thing here.
Since, uh, it's, uh.
Get 15 minutes to get out of Dodge.
Well, uh.
Now move out.
You can ride out of here free or you can ride out rope to your saddle.
Take your choice.
Get exhausted doing this.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, you're doing it.
And then patriotic.
Eat for a little
Yeah.
We didn't start it, but we by His grace are going to end it.
Hallelujah, let's do it. Oh we love you Jesus.
Oh,
Let the Holy Spirit fall. He's here. Feel His power.
Kids, you've got to change things.
We've got too many Christian grown ups that are fat and lazy.
Do you know Muslims train their children from the time they're five years old?
We want to reclaim America for Christ.
How many of you know that this is a pretty sick old world?
This is a sick old world.
I'm here to be trained.
I'm here for an education.
I'm willing to be trained.
I'm willing God.
I'll do what you want me to do.
I'll say what you want me to say.
In Jesus name.
Amen.
Dear friends, this is Dr. Gordon.
And if I can have a few minutes of your time, I'd like to think about some things aloud with you, so to speak.
Now, I'm just a dying old man.
Older than most of you.
And you are dying younger people.
Men and women, probably.
But what I want to talk to you about is this whole idea that you've got to be afraid when you die.
Because if you haven't done right, then you're going to go to a bad place.
Yeah, you've heard that all your life.
And I'm not just preaching to the choir.
I know a lot of you people out there really think that Bob is a much more sensible alternative to a lot of this crap that's going around in the name of something up there that just has to tell you what to do, how to think, how to procreate, who you should kill, who you should not kill, who you should subjugate.
And you know, it's just been going on for so long.
Because it all started off when, you know, we crawled out of the mud.
And sort of stood up on two legs and were basically, unfortunately, due to the development of something called the frontal lobes, became separated from the landscape.
And then all of a sudden, stuff that had been natural just went on.
You didn't worry about it.
Boom!
It was scary.
Yeah, friends.
Bad stuff going on.
Earthquakes, thunderstorms, landslides.
All of that.
All those things.
Giant animals that you never saw before that came out and ate your whole family.
Well, stuff happens, right?
I could say another word, but in an attempt to not have this exorcised, I will say stuff happens.
And everybody just sort of feared it and cowed.
And every time stuff started happening, everybody crawled into the back end of the cave.
And, ah, what did we do?
And then somebody with a little bit more.
I don't know what to say.
Exploitive nature or just a smart guy or a sub-smart guy said, hey, you know what?
I know why stuff happens.
Everybody said, what?
What do you mean you know why stuff happens?
I can tell you why stuff happens.
Up there in the sky is a great, mighty man.
And his name is Nobodad.
And he makes stuff happen.
And, you know, I know this is true because he has spoken to me.
And so I must tell you that I speak for Nobodad.
And Nobodad will tell you what is right and what is wrong.
And, well, okay, you know, you get the picture.
It starts off in the jungle or at the edge of the caves or on an alluvial plain.
It doesn't matter.
Next thing you know, there's a special branch of people who interpret.
Why stuff happens to people who really can't even begin to think about that because they're too busy suffering under the stuff that happens.
Yeah.
And we call it religion to tie back.
Religere.
To tie back.
To take us back to the old concepts.
That there is an omnipotent being who watches over us.
Or maybe it's beings.
Maybe it's three or four.
Maybe it's twelve.
But there's a bunch of them, man.
And you better watch out.
You better be good.
You better not turn this way.
You better wipe your butt that way.
You better not eat this.
You are not allowed to marry within 1 25th of your bloodline.
And, excuse me, you better shave your head, clip your hair, and have your women genetically, pardon me, genitally mutilated.
Yeah.
That's what we call religion.
I got a book.
Well, so do I.
Yeah, but my book's better than your book.
What do you mean?
I've got...
This is written by God.
I was the first one that used a doctor pitch.
And since then, it's evolved into television.
But now, they can't say that the man who is making the pitch on television that's doing the voice for the advertisement is a doctor.
You're not allowed to say he is a doctor.
Unless he really is an MD and has a license or a surgeon.
But in the olden days, we didn't care anything about the laws.
We just went ahead and we were doctors.
If you had the appearance and the ability to talk, you became a doctor.
In fact, my father was an eye doctor when I was born.
It was a business he knew nothing about.
But he went into the, what we call, a glimmer.
And he got a box when I was a young fella.
Set it out in front of a saloon in Montgomery, Alabama.
Covered it with black muslin.
Had four or five pairs of frames out there with different glasses.
You can buy the same thing in the five and ten cent store today.
But he used to stop customers along the street as they were on their way to the depot, as they said.
The depot to catch a train.
And he'd say, just a minute.
I think you need glasses.
Would you try these on?
At one time, my father sold a pair of frames to a fella.
He told me about this.
He couldn't quite get this fella to admit that he could see good through the glasses.
So my father took a pair of frames that had no glass in them.
Took out his handkerchief.
Wiped them off very good.
Put it on.
Said, how do you see?
The fella says, they are wonderful.
That's the best pair I've had on yet.
He said, now don't take these off.
Let your eyes get adjusted to them.
You wear these.
This pair is three dollars.
And the guy bought them.
There were no glasses in it.
He had a pair of empty frames.
And that is the truth.
I swear by that.
And you see, it's just salesmanship in anything.
It's just salesmanship.
The Steaming Sack of Slack Part 2.
Bob the UFO Guy.
fish
Bob the UFO Guy
For more information, visit subgenius.com.
Thank you.
Hello friends and welcome.
Tonight's sermon is entitled
Free Thought.
You get what you pay for.
Now the church of the subgenius
has always encouraged
free thought, friends.
Don't get me wrong.
We've always been behind free thought.
You know that. I know that. Everyone knows that.
It's only when you want to know
what you think
that we charge a donation.
And that's also why
the church says anything worth knowing
is worth paying for.
Now you have all these
so-called normals.
These average Joe blokes.
The mediocre majority.
The folks who have to go to school
to learn how to learn.
Oh yes.
They think they know how to think.
Because why?
Because they got a piece of paper.
A piece of paper, friends.
That says they know how to think.
A diploma, friends.
Created, maintained, signed, sealed,
and delivered by who?
The conspiracy.
Oh sure.
They pay good money for that piece of paper too.
Let me tell you.
You pay a whole lot of money for it.
More than we would ever dream of stealing from you.
Investing for you.
But does the conspiracy
teach you
what you think, friends?
Hell no.
The conspiracy teaches you
what they think.
Why they're so scared
that someone out there might in fact
trip upon the truth
and think a real independent thing.
They thought for themselves.
A thought funk without the guidance
of the conspiracy.
A non-conspiracy concept
that they force you
and everyone else
to go to their conspiracy training schools
for the most formative
and most imaginative
of their years.
And they won't let you out, friends.
Not until you conform
to their normality.
Or one of their carefully selected
alternative normalities.
Oh yes, you know what I'm talking about.
I'm talking about those hippies,
those punks, those skinheads
who wouldn't be called dead
thinking anything
but the hippest, punkish,
skinnest thoughts.
Oh sure, friends.
They think they're thinking.
They think they're rebelling.
But they've only joined another branch
of the conspiracy corps.
Oh, they're out of the army, alright.
And they're into one of the other armies.
The conspiracy octopus.
Oh, but I disobey
all the laws and everything
that they tell me to do.
Friends.
That's just reverse psychology
they're using on you.
The conspiracy is a master of reverse psychology.
They want you to disobey them.
Just say no means just say yes.
Why do you think they call it dope?
They want you to pacify
your brain with drugs.
They want you to transmit AIDS
via every natural orifice.
And every unnatural one too, friends.
It gives them something to waste your time with
to avoid getting slapped.
While simultaneously providing junk food
for thought
to fuel their media hype.
Something for them to market
and then take from the market
and then black market
and then ban and then regulate
and all the while you think
it's just happenstance.
Supply and demand.
Who are you fooling?
They do the supply and demand
and they do the demand too.
And you think you're so clever
because you cheated
on last year's income tax.
Oh friends.
So much for your free thought.
It was worth precisely
what you paid.
Nothing. Nothing at all.
And I bet you still don't know
what the hell I'm talking about.
Oh no. I pity you.
Wherever you may be.
Oh how I pity you.
And Bob pities you.
Even more friends.
But let us not here
in the church of the subgenius
get too smug, too self-righteous
too high and mighty
because friends we all know
there's plenty of what?
Pseudo subgenies out there
who just pretend
to think for themselves.
Why do they come to the church friends?
Because they think it's cool.
They can't understand what we're talking about friends.
It sounds like a big joke to them.
A riddle. Something to laugh about.
Well ha ha ha.
That's just fine and dandy.
We'll take your money friends.
But we ain't touching your soul.
Hell no.
And then again it's not like you give a lot of money anyway.
You're afraid to know what you think.
You're scared.
You're frightened there may not be anything.
Well friends there's only one way to find out.
And that's to put your money where your mind is.
And if you don't get a quick
prompt response in six to eight weeks
well friends you can just assume
the worst. Tell them that address.
And praise Bob. Amen.
From PR News in Washington
I'm not sick and therefore not contagious.
Meanwhile the World Health Organization
says I'm sick and therefore
contagious. Meanwhile
the Secretary of Defense is seeking
to force a nurse to order PR's reports
for all US troops returning from
Ebola frickep. Meanwhile
Fiat Chrysler is recalling
two trucks for half a million problems.
Meanwhile PR News
continues to accelerate.
This trend won't be sustained.
Meanwhile Dow
Dow is 1660
A new UNICEF report
shows a spike in Italy
across southern Europe.
The PR News program
is not likely to have much of an effect.
Meanwhile,
this is PR News in Washington.
PR News is having little
effect so ending it shouldn't
hurt the economy.
First we must get out.
We must get off, we must get off this place.
We must leave, we must get off, we must get off.
Now who gonna talk for you on Earth?
Who gonna say the words?
Who gonna pronounce the final epithet that's gonna take you off of this world?
Who gonna speak for you on Earth?
Who gonna talk for Earth?
We know who speaks for the nation.
But who speaks for the planet?
Who speaks for Earth?
Coal ganons of steel,
hombres without hearts,
human beings without minds,
a world of pain, no luxury,
no comfort, no delight,
suffering at every corner.
Enjoy yourself, enjoy yourself.
Earth, Earth, Earth.
We must get off, we must get off, we must get off this place.
We shall all know, there is no future.
We have destroyed the land we live in.
We have taken the Earth, and we'll save the Earth.
This is the way it's been done for billions of years.
And this is the slim, charred face of evolution.
This is the slow, pebbling, slumbering, lumbering face of evolution.
This is the way it's been done for billions of years.
Ah, yes dear friends.
Welcome to Hour of Slack number 1,494.
By the way, we're going to have some internet-only shows coming up.
For those who only listen on broadcast radio, you won't be able to hear these special ones except on the internet.
Because they're just too naughty.
That'll be number 1,493.5 and 1,494.5.
Friends, the...
The music in the background is from the Psychoskeletons.
This tune called Some Dumb Thing.
If you Google the Psychoskeletons, you'll find albums on SoundClick.
And the background music for the next few minutes will also be by the Psychoskeletons.
And The Large sent us some music.
Again, recently. A whole lot of it.
We'll be hearing some of that. And we did hear some.
The guy that was singing about Bob.
And kind of a high voice.
That was The Large, believe it or not.
Actually singing.
For those who have an affinity for Finnish.
Yes. Yes, actually I have a description from The Large.
Feel the groove. The spirit of Bob.
Or even, quote Bob, unquote, is strong in me.
It's moving on the face of the waters as well as in every corridor, passage, hallway and alley.
And it will eventually get everybody.
Everybody. That's insane.
Dolphins, rainbows.
And napalm.
Damn dirty hippies.
My mind is flowing.
P.S.
It's not me who is writing this.
P.P.S.
War is coming, man.
P.P.P.S.
I am better.
Better than better.
Better than best.
Do you want to bet?
Thank you, The Large.
Praise The Large.
Actually, there's more of that.
He did quite a bit of ranting.
But I got to do the rest of these credits.
The song we just heard.
Or whatever you want to call it.
Earth First.
That was Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
Recording live on the air right here in this station's studio.
WCSB.
Professor Chaz Smith and Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
And here's some more psycho skeletons in the background.
The rant on free thought was, of course, Father Joe Mama.
Also known as Papa Joe Mama.
Oh, and we're playing a new little segment.
A one-minute segment that Reverend Dew Eight is sending us.
Kind of collage crazy stuff.
The steaming sack of slack.
We played the first two of those tonight.
That's Reverend Dew Eight.
Oh, Nate Eagle is the name of the carny barker.
Talking about fake glasses.
And doctors.
And G. Gordon Gordon was on there very carefully saying,
Stuff happens.
The Jesus Camp mixdown from the movie Jesus Camp
was done by Reverend Cuttlefish.
Leemur, Fernand and Andy Leemur,
did the smoking gun and the PR news.
And our titles.
And I think that mostly covers it there.
Oh, let's go back to what The Large said.
The Large said in another email that had his music attached to it.
He said, Bob is speaking to me.
It might be the Bob.
Not sure.
We'll tell you.
When I do know.
Actually, it says, will you tell you when I do know.
But I think he meant, we'll tell you when I do know.
Not sure if it ever happens in this life.
I'm glad I can change between the worlds of dimensions
and avoid the waves of probabilities ever collapsing.
It's quite easy when you get the hang of it.
People might think it's difficult, but it really isn't.
It's easy to grasp.
Just like it's very easy to understand how the whole world we live,
and what we live in, is a pyramid scheme.
Haha.
Praise Bob.
Bob equals the path.
I am the paver of the path.
The right path.
If you are the right person, you will walk the right path also.
You cannot even take the wrong path.
Right equals wrong.
Or Job 11.1 says, but now stretch out your hand and strike everything he has,
and he will surely curse you to your face.
I don't know what the hell that means, but so doesn't anybody else either.
There is no hell.
And there, there is no hell.
Praise Dave.
I think that's Dave.
That was the large writing, and now it's Dave.
So what is frightening?
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to interrupt.
You said something was frightening.
I did?
Well, if I said that, then you better pick up on it, man.
I missed it.
Well, I'm scared already, but I just wondered why I should be scared.
Well, the large said, one plus two equals zero.
And three plus two equals three.
And three plus two equals one.
Therefore, one equals five, and one equals three.
Therefore, Bob Dobbs.
End of transmission.
Oh, and then he said, say hi to Princess Wee.
That's tricky math.
Oh, hi, the large.
So there you go.
There we go.
And here we come.
Did you tell him to heist to Napa?
Another finished swear word with Nappa?
You said, smell my belly button.
Actually, I haven't.
Does it really?
It's true.
Smell my belly button.
Smell my, that was in, you know, hey, smell my belly button.
Say that again in Finnish.
That's like the cow's macky sense of humor or something.
How do you say it in Finnish?
Pardon?
How do you say that in Finnish?
Again.
Heista?
No.
Nappa, belly button.
Heista, Nappa.
Heista, my Nappa, buddy.
You can heista my Nappa, okay?
Well, remember the large was the guy that we called Reverend Angry Lonesome Cowboy Larry.
Larry.
That's one of his names.
Oh, that's not the Finnish one, right?
That is the Finnish one, yes.
Well, Bob isn't Finnish.
Well, that's when I was staring at the crayons, and I realized that Bob was Finnish.
I'd used up all the paper, and I'm sorry.
Bob isn't Finnish with him yet.
No, Bob's not Finnish with him yet.
So Dave, how's everything going over there in Ashtabula?
I fear to hesitate to ask.
Well.
But did anyway.
I'm under, I'm having problem with nasal grippage.
I'm sure the collective audience doesn't want it, but individuals might want to hear it.
But I have various parts of my body removed.
No, Dave, no.
Removed?
Yep.
And given the scavenger elves who forage here in my idyllic verdant backyard, and not one
so far has even offered a morsel back.
I leave food out for them.
Sometimes I shoot the bunny rabbits for the horns.
I hope they're not-
It's antler season.
Body parts you really need to.
You know, like the double mean baby head.
Or the paras, I mean that parasitic twin hanging off the back of your head.
The gibbers and mumbles.
Well, that's a way of putting it.
Parasitic too.
I don't know if they compete with common dentures in like people, like 93 years plus or something
like that.
Unless they've already been previously indentured, you know, just like they did with the servants
and old age.
Yeah.
So you didn't have the double mean baby head removed from the back of your head, right?
No, I told you just kind of like, it didn't evaporate.
It just kind of like disappeared.
So I realized I had half of my face was used to be covered like for about four years.
This huge purple and a big like booze mark and stuff.
And I thought it was a birthmark.
But you know, they said if you have a baby, you can have a baby.
You can appear at any time, even if you're already been born for like, you know, years
and years and stuff.
You mean like a wine stain?
Yeah, like a wine stain.
Wow.
And you just had this appear over half of your face?
No, I gauzed and daubed myself regularly with all kinds of excrements and ointments.
They've procured from the farthest lands of the East.
And like comb Chinese on herbal stores and stuff like that.
And one time I got my shoe.
I lost my shoe in a gutter over there.
And I was like picking around in the gutter because I could still see it.
And somebody came by me.
I was horrible.
That's what it is.
If you focus on the wrong, I was going to call it religion, but I mean political philosophy.
If you focus on the wrong, you're going to be a bad person.
I'm a strong one for the long amount of time.
There are really grave collision in there.
Wow.
You know, I'm embarrassed.
That sounds bad.
This show is freaking me out.
Yeah.
But what if you were to become, you know, oh, I don't want to say it.
Insane.
Go ahead.
Use the word.
It's not a dirty word in the Church of the Holy Spirit.
this genius. This music
in the background, by the way, is by The Large.
Freak out, freak out, freak
out, freak out.
Far out, far out.
Is it going to be like this forever?
Unfortunately, it might well be.
If you talk to current
quasi-physicists nowadays,
like a sperm donor or something,
all these people who think
that they've got these little amoebic
tiny little brains,
and they can somehow get in with these
big government corporations
and stuff like that.
I'm not supposed to talk about that.
Dave's off the hook, Princess Wee.
I guess he is.
Dave's off the hook, man.
I think we ought to let him just keep running
like that.
Don't unplug him.
Go for it.
I tried to call my baby the other night.
Do-do-do-do-do.
Remember that song, Off the Hook?
No.
Slow-eyed salmon, reptiles.
I can't remember.
It's okay, Dave.
It's all right.
It was a long, long time ago,
and everything will be okay.
You remember back when I first got out of there,
don't you?
I mean, I helped you when we moved into,
I think it was Chaz's backyard
or something like that over on the east side.
You mean when you got out of the
place where they were keeping you?
Yeah, when they let me out of there, yeah.
Are you talking about the
time that you ate that pepper,
that scotch bonnet pepper in Chaz's backyard?
No, he's talking about when they let him out
of the psycho ward.
Oh.
That's what precipitated it.
Do you remember that?
Yes, you ate a raw scotch bonnet pepper,
a whole one.
You just crunched it down like it was a tomato.
Like you knew what you were doing.
And then in a few minutes,
your joints started to get warm and tingly.
Yeah.
It was covered in potato salad and I didn't see it.
I was just such a swine.
I just like shoved it in my mouth and stuff.
I was like, what the hell?
And suddenly I was transported to sunny Mexico.
I was like getting ready to watch an Aztec ritual murder or something like that.
It was pyramids and it was like that Martin Denny's music from the early 70s.
Like, you know, weird baboons crying in the background.
Who?
What?
When?
Where?
What?
And stuff.
Oh, man.
Here comes the weather patrol.
That's not the patrol.
That's the large again in the background.
Actually, this is one of his many bands.
This is with somebody else called Naka Mafia.
A tune called Pokey House.
Have you ever been to Pokey?
Oh, yeah.
I wonder what that means.
I think I've probably been there.
Stay the time.
The institutional way of thought is the only way of thought that keeps you and remind you
of the state of mind.
Did I just hear somebody in Finnish in the background tell me to smell his belly button?
Yeah.
With an impairment device.
Well, what do you think about which...
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Me.
prognosis for the future.
The prognosis for the future is terrible.
Especially if you're any of the endangered species,
such as human beings or subgeniuses.
Look out.
Yep.
Now we're even starting to have to worry about the normals.
Well, who cares?
I don't really care about the humans so much.
But the subgeniuses' fate until X-Day,
you know, the humans have us between a rock and a very, very, very soft place.
I was going to say between a rock and a marshmallow.
Yeah, the rock is going to win.
The haters always win.
Like in that movie, Dawn of the Planet of the Apes.
Princess Wee and I saw that.
And I don't think it'll be much of a spoiler if I tell you that the haters win,
just like in real life.
Because the haters are better at hating than the peaceniks are.
See, here's the belly button part.
That's what the Internet's all about.
It tells you what you can find, whatever you most want to hear,
told to you over and over again by millions of other anonymous losers and cowards.
Over and over again, you can be told everything.
You can be told everything you most wanted to hear.
And that is why the Internet makes us stupid instead of smarter.
There, I said it.
But I wouldn't necessarily say anonymous, because people might mistake me for people who were...
I don't mean the group anonymous.
I mean the anonymous cowards that get on the Internet.
Oh, wait, that is the group anonymous.
Oh, well, no, I'm kidding.
I don't want them coming after me.
No, sir.
They'll out me.
You should be allowed to kick kids, I think.
I don't know.
I don't know either.
But I'm open to learning.
You've been a professional bowler for the last 37 years, just as I have.
And what would you say was your very most irregular passage of, you know, what was your worst bowling match?
When I prayed to the bowling ball to win me the match and it didn't, that was when I lost my faith in God and bowling balls.
And bowling in general.
I should have known better.
After Santa Claus, I mean, you'd think I would have learned, but no.
Oh, well.
Could be worse.
At least it's this Bob religion that I'm brainwashed in.
Well, when you think of it incorrectly and you close your eyes, really, you know, like try and focus on your pineal gland,
you realize that Dobbs and God and banking either is very often useless.
Yes.
I mean, Dobbs or God or Dobbs or God.
Well, I don't know.
They're useful for blaming things on.
You can say, hey, stuff happens.
Praise Bob.
Damn Bob.
Whichever.
You can't curse Bob?
Yes, you have to.
Or we'll kick you out of the church if you do nothing but slavishly praise Bob and wander around on your knees.
You have to, with your butt up in the air.
With your butt facing Bob.
Yeah.
You have to pray.
Eventually, you have to, you know, be snapped out of it and prove that you're not a complete dunderhead by killing Bob or symbolically doing so.
Of course, you can't ever catch him.
You can't really kill him.
Yeah.
I'd like to, like, some really feminine, really hairy, like, dancer in a tutu and stuff like that.
But he's not.
He's really rough and stuff.
Bob's not insecure.
And he will let you.
You're welcome to take your frustrations out.
You're welcome to take your frustrations out on him by hitting him and bashing him.
I'd challenge any other religious gurus or messiahs or saviors.
Oh, wait.
No, I guess Jesus let people beat on him.
Even though he was God, he just let people pick on him.
Yeah, or let you take the placard match home.
But his fan club says that he needs a lot of help.
Yes.
Because Jesus and God are not very strong anymore.
And it takes a lot of right-wing Christians to do their jobs for him.
Yes.
The kind of gods Jesus and God apparently are, according to some of their fan club members.
I'm not going to put down every single one of them because they occasionally get some good deeds done.
Yeah.
Like, close down all the abortion clinics in Texas.
You know, there's only 20 places left in Texas where you can get an abortion.
And most of those places are five hours away.
So, congratulations, humans.
There will be a lot more of you soon.
Mostly little water-headed po-buckers, to quote my dad and Bill Hicks.
People who take orders well and who do what they are told.
That's who will survive.
And the sub-G will probably mean the nut under those rock-and-hard, you know, granite s'mores you were making back there in the backyard.
Bob sold it.
I smoked it.
That settles it.
I'll do what Bob said.
Yes, that's all I'm going to do.
But at least...
Well, except when I can't understand what he's saying, which reminds me of this show sometimes.
Well, that's what tests the importance of our linguistic skills.
That's what proves that semantics and misdealings and rhetorical falsehoods and things like that, we get a chance to the miracle of radio and a bunch of...
To really see it.
Wait a minute.
I have to backstep a little bit.
And I have to sit down.
Yeah, I almost said something I shouldn't have said.
Just sit down carefully, Dave.
Are you suddenly talking about us again with the idiot talk?
No.
No, I was...
One segment of the audience, which is exactly like 2% of the audience, I think is what the quotable figure is.
2% of the audience have nasty, mean ideas about your pro-scripture for health.
And happiness and somewhat non-causal existence from time to time.
And do you know these audience members personally, Dave?
Or are you just speculating?
No, I'm talking like straight from the bird's...
Straight through your hat.
No, no.
From the horse's mouth.
I didn't mean to call you an equestrian.
Only a plasmodic vision of a horse of some kind.
You know, wild and free.
I'm just trying to put in my two centaurs worth.
You complain about certain people.
Like 2%.
No, no, no.
Those are the ones I'm not complaining about.
I'm complaining about the 98 percenters.
That's everybody but me.
What?
That's different.
I don't understand when you speak.
Russian.
That is different, man.
That's unusual.
That's unique.
It's, you know...
No, I don't.
You thought it was different, man.
Yeah, yeah.
Just like she said.
Man.
Have you noticed that a toilet paper tube does not work as it likes it?
1940s sounding radio show device.
On a cell phone.
No, it works in a radio studio, but not on a cell phone.
Because there are actual liquid mics in front of your very eyes.
Well, because the cell phone already sounds like talking through a toilet paper tube on a regular microphone.
It sounds more like talking through a sewage plant basement with all the machines on.
The hydrocephalic geeks and the jumping lemurs.
The better lemurs of our day, you know, transfer so easily that you can, you know...
What were you talking about?
The better lemurs of our nature, did you say?
I'm not quite following this.
What is...
I'm trying to be a good follower, Dave.
Like battered lemur syndrome, perhaps?
Maybe you've been there, I understand it from a clinical standpoint.
Or maybe for, you know, from some outreach clinic, man.
Yeah, man.
I'm not saying you personally battered lemur or anything like that.
I'm like, as if to French fry it Korean style, you know, I'm battered a bit and then, you know.
I wouldn't even need a tennis shoe that way.
You know what I'm saying?
No temporary tennis shoe for you?
Nope, not anymore.
I got the word from Dr. Grossman.
Hmm.
He said, I've only got 25 and a half.
More years to remain in the squat position left to me by my grandparents and my Uncle Poopy.
So you just had to cut the temporary tennis shoes right out?
Right, like straight right on out of there.
No crunchy tennis shoes for Dave.
No, you can't even put like leafy greens on to like spruce it up.
Like, oh, he's got some boat there.
You know.
What the hell is going on in this show?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I am really, um, I'm just too brave.
What happened?
We went off the rails.
We went, we went off the hook.
And the background music stopped.
I stopped it.
I turned it off.
Dave and I have co-opted the Hour of Slack into a cooking show.
A lemur cooking show, if I'm hearing correctly.
Yes, we're talking about lemur cookery.
Great.
And tennis shoe cookery.
Well, there's so much for PR news.
And smoke guns.
And all those other, and Man Rifle and all those other shows we play.
No more funny titles for Hour of Slack.
You guys are going to cook lemur.
It was, you know, it was guilt through association.
Free association ain't free, man.
That guy's already half cooked anyway.
Anyway, not half baked.
I wouldn't say that.
But certainly he's been through the oven.
I know that much.
Poorly cooked.
Poorly nuked.
Poor, very poorly nuked.
Left in for two seconds when 35 was what was required.
Princess, we made a whole bunch of lemur this for Thanksgiving, which was two weeks
ago for most of our listeners.
She made lemur pudding, lemur stew, lemur bones.
Lemur stuffing.
Yeah, lemur.
Oh, the lemur stuffing was my favorite.
Mm-hmm.
And, uh.
Jellied.
We had jellied lemur.
That's right.
Cran lemur.
Mm-hmm.
Cran lemur?
Ter lemur ducking.
Oh, my.
The ter lemur ducking was, I don't know.
I didn't really like it.
Really?
Yeah, that was, well, because fowl and primates don't really, well, are lemurs primates?
I think they are.
They're related.
No, lemurs are like, they're like little weasels or.
No, no, no.
They're not.
Aren't they like.
They're, uh.
How about bad guys?
They're badgers, maybe.
Perhaps a form of exotic badger.
Well, the prep for that was a real wolverine, so I probably won't do that again.
I mean, lemurs aren't eggs and they're not monkeys.
They're lemurs.
If you didn't like it.
Oh, yes.
That's right.
They're climbing trees and they're related to monkeys.
And, yes, sort of.
And they come from Madagascar.
Yeah.
But they're very, they're only related to monkeys like we're related to monkeys.
Not very closely.
Well, that, that explains your horrors.
Less than picking out the weird bones.
Yeah.
And, you know, I thought in the first example you might have, you know, done a small hologram
and like with a point projection of some kind, maybe a little barbecue, Texas style, you
know, to get people all warmed up and plenty of free coffee.
And then when everybody's sitting down, squeeze.
I've never had barbecued hologram.
Is that good?
Oh, it is.
That's a good one.
I'm going to have to eat that.
That's about all you're going to have to eat in the future.
Barbecued hologram.
Yeah, roach steaks.
The actual food will be roach crap steaks.
Ew.
Made from roach crap.
And the holograms are what make you feel better about it.
It looks like a juicy hamburger you can eat the hell out of.
But really, you're just eating the hell.
Man, you got a bucket?
Ew.
Bob said it.
He was, he was.
His dates were a little off.
Bob said you'll all be eating roach crap by the year 2000.
Give him a break because he said that in 1955.
But you know, they are talking about feeding the world using insects and they've been,
I've read several news articles where they're softening us up to get us ready for mealworms
meals.
Dude, I'm about to hurl.
You're going to have to stop that.
No, I'm sorry.
By the way, I'm quite serious.
The time is coming.
Do you remember, Kate?
Do you remember the future all?
I don't know.
I don't I don't know too well.
But something's gotten so revolutionary about downloaded and updated prayer paper that
's going tokeeper hundreds of thousands of children at a point the world is a little
bit more there.
And on and around and around and around and around in your background.
You got to keep going and around and around.
And there's so much to that.
ffentlich
obrigado.
they were. You know, you'd start off
at a little bistro and having some great
snacks, and then like one layer
would wear away as the drug wore
off. So in the green is
lemur crap.
Exactly.
Well, that movie Snowpiercer
actually had an interesting, now
that I'm thinking about it, the people
on the Snowpiercer train
are faced
with the rude awakening that their meals
have actually been made from
roaches.
Bugs. Slurry of
bug jelly.
It's got a lot of protein in it.
The time will come.
Well, some even used to believe
way back in the days of sophomoric
humor that
cockroaches could be called as
an elegant treat for
radiation sickness because they seem to show
very few effects.
Like, living
next to a nuclear power plant doesn't seem
to do anything to them, but to the
73-year-old grandmother
living nearby gives her cancer
in about five and a half seconds.
Well, therefore
eat roaches to fend off
cancer. There you go. There's the answer
right there.
Deep fried.
Therefore, and that's what
I love about all those syllogisms
and like if three equals two,
four equals five, then
four equals six.
Therefore, bob dogs.
Yeah, exactly.
It's the perfect conundrum. Is that the right word
or is it?
Condom.
If three equals five, then
slack.
Well, it's some kind of greasy
receptacle, that's for sure.
Slack. Indeed.
Well, and friends, you're listening
to the hour of slack
and
meal bugs
made into meals.
Meals on wheels
and six legs.
Carried on the backs of lemurs.
Your community with meals
on wheels.
With lots of buggy-woogie treats.
Well,
bugsters and buggies,
I should give the
final credits, which is
that we're
we've avoided once again
talking about J.R. Bob Dobbs
for most of the time.
Bob.
But you can see strange
pictures of Bob on
subgenius.com
including the strangely
formed new
old original Dobbs head
photograph. The photograph
of a prematurely aged
and jowly Dobbs
from which
the famous classic Dobbs head
portrait that you all have
tattooed on your foreheads
comes.
As ride theory
said about the new Dobbs head,
his fizz is risen.
Yea, though ye walk
through the uncanny valley,
of the half-toned salesman.
Speak and see and hear
no evil, for the new Bob
is with you. His odd and
changed puss discomforts
thee. He preparest
a web page before thy
frenemies. Milk flows
from thy nose. Thy cup
is spitaken.
Goodness and mercy, it
shall follow thee all the days of thy life
and you shall dwell on this
.jpeg forever
and ever.
Subgenius.com
Thank you Ride Theory for that
little explanation for the new
Dobbs head.
Thank you Lonesome Cowboy Dave
for calling in.
Bob, you did you job.
Thanks Papa Joe,
G. Gordon Gordon,
Fid Chooley,
Cuddlefish,
uh,
Lemur for dinner,
Einstein's Secret Orchestra,
and Dave, I'm gonna cut to, we have to get
to go now so I have to play a song. And the large!
Oh and the large. Yeah I do, I
actually do have to cut to a song
now by Reverend Andrew the Impaled
at 17
X Day on somebody else's
keyboard so forgive him if he hits a
rote, rote non every
now and then.
Hits the road Ron. Okay.
At least he's not tapping cylindrical
devices down his nasal area and his throat
and more like he used once to did
like last week.
Well it happens every time.
Okay, okay here it goes.
Should I leave you on so you can hear it Dave?
Might as well,
uh, yeah. Okay.
C-T-G-A
I got some fresh DNA
I got it for you
C-T-G-A
Why you get me? Ain't nothing better to do
Oh you're C-C-T-G-A
C-T-G-A-A-C would go nice
With my C-C-T-G-A-G-A-G my advice
Let's get down today.
In a sapiosexual way
What kind of girl? She's a sapiosexual
Yeah I know what that means
And it's not hot, at least to her
Cause she digs intellectuals
Yeah she likes geeks
Well you're new to the scene
You might be kind of keen
Do you know what I mean?
When I say I like them genes
Oh C-T-G-A
I got some fresh DNA
I got it for you
Oh C-T-G-A
Why don't you come get with me?
Ain't nothing better to do
Oh you're C-C-T-G-A-C-T-G-A-A-C would go nice
With my C-C-T-G-A-G-A-G my advice
Let's get down today
In a sapiosexual way
Some cotton girls take all the time to pretty up
But they're just for the day
And it's gonna fade
Some other girls they only wanna shake it up
Get drunk and laid
Well that ain't for me
She might be up till three
But with a book of poetry
And my C-T-G-A
I got some fresh DNA
I got it for you
A-T-C-G why don't you come get with me
Ain't nothing better to do
Oh C-T-G-A-C-T-G-A-A-C would go nice
With my C-T-G-A-G-A-G my advice
Let's get down today
In a sapiosexual way
You saw a woman
That I caught under your subtle reference
To a movie that not more than ten thousand people have seen
Among there and there and there
Well I know the difference
So how'd you like to mix it up with me
Yeah my C-T-G-A-G-A-G
I got some fresh DNA
And my C-T-G-A-G-A-G my advice
Yeah my C-T-G-A-G-A-G my advice
If you want the kind of guy that makes you laugh
Take you by surprise and you realize
He wants you because of the mind you have
Now do you empathize
To be perfectly fair
You should be aware
We'd make a nifty pair
If you have the M-C squared
For my C-T-G-A
I got some fresh DNA
I got it for you
Say T-C-G why don't you go with me
Got nothing better to do
Your C-C-T-G-A-G-G-A-A-C
Would go nice with my C-C-T-G-A-G-A-G
My advice let's get down today
In a sapiosexual way
Say let's get it down today