Musik
Das 노Check
deine sie noch es olds
Relativ neu, voller, erst, groß, genuend, wunderschön, groß, riesig, perfekt, cool, spezial,
hier, hier, laberend, einfach, ultimat, best, natürlich, wach, spezial, schön, schnell,
schneller, schneller und viel mehr.
Ah, ja, liebe Freunde, es ist wieder Rerun-Zeit, aber ihr werdet glücklich wissen, dass wir
nicht das gleiche alte 3 Weihnachts-Hour-Schlacht-Show-Reruns in einem Rundum machen werden.
Nein, ich werde es alle in nur dieses eine intensive, totale Rerun-Show kompressieren,
außer dass es nicht die ganze erste Hälfte ist, die mit einer neuen Weihnachts-Schlacht-Zeit
für die Weihnachten und Heilige Tage und die Heiligen-Hand-Tage, wie es für einige Leute ist.
Eigentlich muss ich doppelt arbeiten, weil es die Saison der Verkaufszeit ist.
Selling, yes, oh, you wouldn't believe what the elves have done over in this subgenius
catalog.
But, uh, anyway, happy, uh, whatever you do.
Uh, yes, this music in the background is, uh, somebody named Kenny Wayne Shepard.
Yeah, there's an album called Merry Axmus, a guitar axmus.
It's cool, man, cool!
And, uh, praise Bob and, uh, ho, oh, oh!
Oh!
Um, um, um...
You put the stick up my hip, dip, dip, dip, dip.
Who was that man?
He shoved it up my can.
und habe mich auf diesem Weihnachtsbaum verletzt.
Jaaa!
Wirst du es stoppen?
Wuhu!
Ha ha ha ha!
Als dieser Engel hörte
chop pa pa pop, chop pa pa pop
ging ein schrecklicher Angst direkt in mein Herz.
Diese Pinzentröte stingen mich.
Rambo jambo rambo jambo nimm ma ding dong.
Du wirst nie wissen, wie du so gut bist.
Wuhu!
Wer hat den Stumpf in meinem Rumpen gepasst?
Wer hat den Kinn in meinem Rammel in meinem Ding-Dong geschnuppert?
Wer hat den Wood-Burret geputzt?
Wer hat den Stick in meinem Hüft-Hüft-Hüft geputzt?
Wer hat diesen Busch gefangen und in meinen Hüft gehalten?
Er hat diesen Engel gemacht, bitte für die Gnade!
Ich würde ihn schlagen.
Es ist das psychische Zeitpunkt des Jahres.
Weißt du, wo deine Gehirnzellen sind?
Es ist bereits 9 Uhr.
Geh nicht in den Hintergrund schauen, dass ein Hund ihn getötet hat.
Geh nicht in den Bar gehen, weil der alte Frankie gestorben ist,
am Hintergrund.
Ich meine, ich bin im Wohnzimmer.
Oh, kann ich die Gehirnzellen heute Abend verkaufen?
Ja, er hat die Kugel zurückgebracht.
Ich werde dich nicht mit Gehirnzellen verhelfen.
Du ist gut.
Ich werde dich mich nichtï Gehirnzellen füllen,
ich werde dich nicht ans ganzchen Schild f 것은 lassen.
skif Greece
I'm gonna have to, I'm gonna have to.
It could be his head wasn't screwed on just right.
What we as manufacturers sell you is fun.
The faith of a child.
You spend a lot of time thinking about the future.
You spend all the money you've got.
Barbiedox.
Women rape would be more like their life by role-playing with Bach.
Wir haben die Marketing-Scheme für Kinder-Toyen gewählt.
Sie werden nicht mehr so stark sein.
Sie werden Ihre Kirche als Fahrzeug benutzen, um diese Toys vor dem Krieg zu bringen.
Es wird ein Wunder für Kinder sein.
Aber wie wird die Waffe zwischen Gut und Schmerz in Ihren Marketing-Schemen dargestellt, Mensch?
Gut hat viele Muskeln.
Gut. Gut!
Die primitiven Welt-Sozien sollten diesen Wert-Gesetz akzeptieren.
Gut hat physische Attribute, die auf die menschlichen Wünsche gehören.
Sexualwünsche.
Die Wünsche, die in Kindern verbreitet werden, werden durch das Fahrzeug dieser so genannten...
So, die Farmer haben gesagt, dass sie in der Kirche sind.
Die Batterie ist nicht gut.
Sie ist neu, von Kenner.
Wo die Illusion das ultimative Waffen ist.
Wir müssen unsere Toys kaufen.
Ja.
Der alte subgeniale Marketing-Scheme.
Er wurde 1984 auf Dockstock gedreht.
Und ich und Tom Friedes.
Ähm, Angels, die wir auf High gehört haben, war von den Philistinen.
Der Kollage, der sich heißt All the Money You've Got, ist aus dem großen Obtus-Christmas-Kollage-Album,
den Sie für gratis bekommen können.
Schauen Sie auf diesem Website abtus.iuma.com.
Das ist Obt... Entschuldigung.
Ah ja, und nächstes Mal, die echte Geschichte des Weihnachts.
Von Michael Shelley.
Schnell.
Er hat mich in den Gästen-Zertifikat und Zuzu's Pedals gekauft.
Und das ist die echte Geschichte des Weihnachts.
Die notwendigen Batterien sind nicht eingegangen.
Diese Geschichte wird drei Tage lang veröffentlicht.
He-Bob und die Bastards of the Universe.
Zu viel ist immer besser als nicht genug.
Von Bob Dove.
Gorgeous.
Seh gut.
Kann von Kopf zu Kopf.
Wie Kai.
Ich kann alles selber.
He-Bob und die Bastards of the Universe werden nach diesem Messer zurück.
Santa Claus.
Ja.
Genau.
Da milchte er was für Weihnachten würde er ein elektrisches、、
er hatte das gesamte in ihrem Kopf rein selbst bis zum Tisch, wo er es auf Ninja-Klubs
Musik
Es ist die sixty next
die midnight
grad
end of the year sale so so come and get it everyone and just buy our products
yeah are we is chris i'm a little confused about what christmas is all
about are we celebrating the birth of santa claus or his death when they nailed
him well that that's the ancient agents of genie but the presence of genie try
to make sure that we have our inventories cleared by now and we sell
everything to the pigs oh yes once a pagan holiday and now a shopping season
and it was something else in between there but before it was after it was a
pagan holiday and before it was a shopping season it was something else
but i think they started the war over yeah
oh
Musik
Friends, try to imagine
somewhere in the snowy north
a
the Santibob
trudging mindlessly
through the Himalayan snows
driven by strange
forces to complete his
nameless errand
and he may show up
at your house, my friend
if you've been a bad subgenius
or a halfway subgenius
or if we keep getting tangled
up in these other shows and having
strange microphones
How did that
paternity suit ever turn out
between Dobbs and Santa?
And who? His dad
Santa Dog
I don't know
St. Nicholas, this is fact
St. Nicholas punched
another bishop in the nose
and bloodied his nose
Really? The historical
St. Nicholas?
Over the trinity of
God
The original St. Nicholas
in Turkey?
Upon Bob
Who the hell is God?
Yeah
Asked Dobbs one day
Suddenly
a lightning bolt struck from nowhere
on that bright sunny day
Bob did a backflip
and from that day on he too
was a believer
And from the snow
a little child bearing flowers emerged
A chip?
What else was on the table?
Each one a dirty flower
St. Nicholas
The historical Santa Claus
is originally lived
as the caller knows
as a bishop in
was it Constantinople?
Yeah, like one of those
It was an ancient Byzantium
Asia Minor
in general
Yes, he was
known for
sneaking out
into the rooms of young women
and leaving
gifts
Life-sized lumps of coal
complete with a fake beard
and a CIA Wall Street credit card
A saint he was
the girl said
St. Nicholas invented the CIA
You got it, brother
He snuck into people's houses
through the chimney
You got it, brother
He knew when they were sleeping
He knew when they were awake
You got it, brother
But like the CIA
He was protecting them
St. Nick was a creeping
stinking spy
He knows when you've been sleeping
He knows what you've been eating
Hey, man, my kids still believe
in St. Nicholas
And who keeps that belief alive
in their fevered, sick little brain?
Madison Avenue, of course
No, the surveillance community
under your direction
And the Reynolds Tobacco Company
Miller Bear
If you're bad, he punishes you
If you're good, he rewards you
He's probably the closest thing to Jesus
walking the earth
He's the closest thing to Big Brother
He rewards those who knows
when they are smiling
when they're awake
I think, I think really
if you want to make a deal
you have to do it with, you know
Could Dr. Claus in fact be
the wandering, quote, milkman
rumored to have fathered
our savior, J.R. Bob Dobbs?
Well, we find it a very likely possibility
from the falsified documents we have here
And also the fluffy beard
that often grew on Bob's feet
You better watch out
You better not
You better not tell anyone
Santa Claus is coming to town
The End
My command is
Checking it twice
Gonna find out who's nobody in there
Santa Claus is coming to town
This is the music game
He knows when you're awake
He knows when you're in bad or good
So be good in this goodness sake
Oh!
You better watch out
You better not cry
You better not tell anyone
Santa Claus is coming to town
Do you think I'm psycho, Mama?
I've seen my ex last night
Oh, I'm sorry
Mama
We all saw X-Mas last night
At a dance at Miller's
A vision of Christmas that was dancing in Stank's head
It would not lie for them little sugar plums
And berries dropping toxic things
All those little sugar plums
All those sweet and dead plums
The poison in the plums
Material plums
Biological agents
Who only take 15%
It came with our plastic boxes of bags
And away we go
And now
It's a good day all right
A salute to Mr. and Mrs. Duff
Shop as usual.
And avoid panic buying.
It's two days old Christmas.
A million things to do.
Clean the house.
Put on tea.
Company is due.
Where are my relatives?
Why haven't they showed up?
I bet they're at the airport.
I forgot to pick them up.
Once again,
as in olden days,
happy golden
be miles.
Let your heart
all be out of sight.
All in sight.
wish everybody
on Christmas
all the
good
Von Mutated Christmas, Freunde.
Have Yourself a Merry Little Christmas
von No-L.
Vorher war es ein Jahr altes ESO
und Michael Shelley hat das echte Geschichte von Weihnachten gemacht.
Von der Tarkin Records All-Star Holiday Extravaganza.
Ich spiele viel davon.
Also schaut auf www.triage.com
Für das auch.
Die Tarkin Records ist auch auf www.triage.com
Und jetzt die Jeff Rose.
Untertitelung des ZDF, 2020
Wenn ihr mein Wort verfolgt habt, verfolgt ihr mich.
Und euren ewigen Sohn.
Ihr habt gefunden, dass ihr nur dafür verfügen könnt,
Gott zu geben, der sein war.
Aber ihr konntet nicht dafür verfügen, dass ihr es nicht macht.
Der Sitz still steht.
In der Dunkelheit, wo es wäldern und nasseln ist.
Herr, bitte geben Sie mir nur noch eine Chance, Herr.
Ich will nicht in den Himmel, Herr.
Ich will nicht in den Himmel.
Und die Kinder sagen,
dass sie lachen und spielen können,
die gleichen Töne wie ich.
Der Hühner wird das Verurteilung.
Untertitelung des ZDF, 2020
Die Antwort? Ja, definitiv.
Nehmt das und schüttelt es auf die Tube, markt Sicherheit, in die fülle Stelle, nenn es die Twilight Zone.
Wir meinen nichts
von diesem Jesus und Gott.
Wir danken dir für all die
schönen Dinge, die du uns gemacht hast.
Dieses Weihnachtsfest.
Wir freuen uns über all das.
Wir versuchen nur,
deine Fanclub zu verurteilen.
Das ist alles.
Das ist, warum wir diese Blasphemie machen.
Aber wir wussten, dass du das wusstest.
Du bist in allem und allem.
Jesus.
Ich konnte ihn sagen.
Gegrüß Gott und Bob und Jesus.
Nächster Thema.
Jesus und die Atheist.
Könntest du Jesus als Terrorist sehen?
Und die Wissenschaft.
Das ist das Leben von Brian, oder?
Und die griechische Mythologie.
Und die nördliche Mythologie.
Und die narrotische Mythologie.
Und rainy about snow.
Musik
Smiley and chill baby, you're safe in here.
Come down, still as snow.
I'm dreaming about the kids you guys have.
And if everyone can come back right.
May your dreams come true.
May your days be close and short.
And may all your dogs spend you right.
Oh holy night, the stars are brightly shining.
It is the night of our dear Savior's birth.
Long lay, long lay the world in terror and repining.
The pit and the stone found its rest.
A thrill of hope, the weary world rejoices beyond our grace.
A new and glorious day, a new and glorious day.
For it's gone, fall on your knees.
Oh hear the angel voices.
Oh night divine, oh night when Christ was born.
Oh night, oh night divine.
Have yourselves.
A groovy little solstice.
Mithras won his fight.
Oh ho ho, ho ho ho, come one, come all.
It's He-Bomb, hey kids, you can help the mighty.
So King of Christ overthrows the evil normals with new Bob-Dogs.
Action figure with rocket fire.
What I wouldn't do from Bob-Dog.
Get new more talk-loving pebbles from you, no?
I'm a talk-loving space cadet.
Life support system down to zero coco.
Feeling space-free.
Have some of my new coco pebbles.
Now so trompery.
Mmm, smells coconut.
This coco-lectable.
Blow.
Roll of friends.
What do you think?
Is it the nativity of Santa Claus that we're trying to celebrate here?
Or is it the horrible death of the Santa Claus?
Santa Bob? The Santa-i-Bob, as he's been referred to in some early prescriptures.
So separate, so separate.
.
Die Jethro's, Freunde, ihr müsst wissen, wo ihr zu den Jethro's schreiben müsst.
Die Jethro's sind auf 212 und eine halbe Miller Avenue.
Das ist 212 und eine halbe Miller Avenue, Portsmouth, New Hampshire.
Portsmouth NH 03801.
Santa Claus is coming to town was by Corporal Blossom.
Information on that mutant Christmas is available from www.triagemusic.com
or www.triagemusic.com.
www.detritus.net
I'm Reverend Ivan Stang, friends.
You can reach me, send me tapes or whatnot at Post Office Box 807 Glen Rose, Texas 76043.
And friends, as always, the hour of slack is brought to you by the Church of the Subgenius.
It's all Christmassy right now.
There's a bright green bob in the window and Christmassy lights.
Is there a DJA? Is DJA out there?
And devilish artwork that's Christmassy.
No, that's something just left for DJA.
It's all Christmassy. It's all wrapped up in perfumed ribbon-wrapped presents.
Under the tree. Smell that cinnamon.
Open the door all the way so we can see if he comes in.
And those sugar plums.
Something's up the chimney hole.
Satan is his name.
Yeah.
Or Santa, I mean.
Otherwise, gosh.
I guess we have to wait till Santa comes, Dave.
Oh, beloved Santa.
I have wanted to put your bag down for a minute.
It's always so ready to let him be.
What?
For so long.
Hey, Bob and Mary X-Men!
Hey, Omar!
Oh, man.
Oh, my God.
Now, Dave, don't you know what they're doing to yourself?
So good a good day.
Merry fucking Christmas.
To you!
Merry Christmas!