Okay, we're rolling.
Hey, church, put the church in order.
Here we go.
Hey!
What?
Who am I?
I'm the record.
Genie the record.
Genie the magic record.
Why, I can do anything.
Oh?
You don't think so?
Well, I'll prove it.
Alakazoot, I'm a whistle.
Whistle.
That was easy.
Alakazing, I'm the self-genius.
Our self-match.
Here's your host.
Yeah, by this time, we're going to present you to the electric church.
Hey, we're going to dedicate to the feedback family.
And all the human beings and you people.
And if you all stand up, put your right hand across.
Whatever you can find, put it across.
Oh, wow.
You know, you just stand up and, you know, uh-oh.
Yeah, okay.
I'll tell you what.
Yeah, we're going to get into all of that.
Don't worry, man.
Don't worry.
You don't have no program.
Just relax.
When I say toilet paper, that's when you come rolling out, okay?
Well, kid, then you want me to play Recorded in 1738 in the Benjamin Franklin Studios?
Some of my friends have prepared a song.
I'll tell you what.
I'm going to play a song that they desire you to hear.
And I would appreciate it if you would listen to it.
Also, please play it for your friends.
And even after election day, please run it off once in a while to remind you that I am in Washington and will be watching out for your interest.
The song will now be sung by the Lang and Glee Club.
Well, I'm up in this room
Looking all around
Well, I look out my bellybutton window
And I see nothing but a whole lot of flowers
And I'm wondering if they want me around
Well, what is all the fuss about out there?
What seems to be the sham?
Cause, you know, if you don't want me around, babe
Well, I'll be glad to go back to the street, babe
And even take a longer rest
Before coming down to shoot again
Man, I remember the last time it was good
They were still arguing about me then
So if you don't want me now
Give or take
You only got two hundred days
If you don't want me now
Make up your mind
Where I'm at
Cause I ain't coming this way too much more again
Well, you know they got pills for ills and thrills and even
Spill the lot for you
Oh, I just forgot that.
I feel evil.
I'm evil
If you want some more, you'll come to the right place.
Well, since my babies left me
I've had to pay to jail
Cause down the island is the true home of the rich man.
Get out of here, I tell you!
Okay, here we go.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Heh.
Two for the money.
Two for the show.
Do it right!
So, here we go!
We got d flavored!
We're going for the money!
I swear
I'll do anything
I wanna do, John
All my life
They all feel bad
Friends, Jimi Hendrix could be a really funny guy,
and this show is dedicated to funny Hendrix.
And unless you're a victim of Hendrix mania like I sometimes am,
you probably haven't heard these versions of these songs.
We even have Hendrix preaching later.
Our man in Dobbs Town, G. Gordon Gordon,
found a huge mass of rare Hendrix in Bob's Falls.
Recordings unheard since 1970,
and tonight we're playing the funniest,
and maybe the most surrealistic.
Oh, God.
You always are a part of me
I see you in my dreams
I see you when I dream
You are my catastrophe
Okay, we got it.
Okay.
Look Old Viana
Here comes a flew
The thirteenth of many times
Just like a fool
Triple-breasted, green, red motherfuckin' dark-toed
Playin' the violin
Hittin' wrong notes
Woah!
Look Old Vianna
It's comin' my way
When it's around, I never have a happy day.
He gives me bad luck by rubbing his ring.
See that? I just broke a guitar string.
Oh, look all beyond her.
He's falling at my baby.
Now she says she's gonna leave me in her bed.
I don't need a bath.
Look like him hanging around.
He's knocking on my door.
Now my house is burning down.
Crackle, crackle.
Pop, pop.
Look all beyond her.
This is the end.
He just now said he wants to be my friend.
When it's around, I can't do nothing right.
He's got me wearing shades in the middle of the night.
Look all beyond her.
Yeah.
Look all beyond her, baby.
Get away, get away from here.
Wow.
Look all beyond her, yeah.
Look all beyond her, baby.
Look all beyond her.
Where's my shotgun?
I can blow this fool away.
Get away from here.
Look all beyond her, baby.
Yeah, hey.
Look all beyond her.
Look all beyond her, baby.
Should I get my doner with a place on her side.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah yeah.
Yeah yeah yeah.
Yeah, oh, oh, oh yeah, yeah.
Yeah yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And that's all I got.
Oh, yeah.
The Oh, look up to me.
When I go naked.
Down the lane.
Yeah, yeah.
Holders and goldens.
Oh, I'm about to turn my plow on you.
I'm about to turn my plow on you.
I'm going to ride on all these red riders.
The night of the night.
Oh, my God.
How do we hang out like that?
If you look around you,
you will see a few minds being blown.
It's happening.
It's happening, baby.
Yeah.
I hope you're enjoying your ride.
Oh, yeah.
Let's get the existence of God issue aside for a later volume
and just stipulate that in some way, self-replicating organisms came into existence on this planet
and immediately began trying to get rid of each other,
either by spamming their environments with rough copies of themselves
or by more direct means which hardly need to be belabored.
Most of them failed and their genetic legacy was erased from the universe forever,
but a few found some way to survive and to propagate.
After about three billion years of this sometimes zany, frequently tedious fugue of carnality and carnage,
New Waterhouse IV was born in Murdo, South Dakota,
to Blanche, the wife of a congregational preacher named Bunyan Waterhouse.
Like every other creature on the face of the earth, Godfrey was, by birthright, a stupendous badass.
Albeit in the somewhat narrow technical sense that he could trace his ancestry back up a long line
of slightly less highly evolved stupendous badasses to that very first self-replicating,
which, given the number and variety of its descendants,
might justifiably be described as the most stupendous badass of all time.
Everyone and everything that wasn't a stupendous badass was dead.
As nightmarishly lethal, mimetically programmed death machines went,
these were the nicest you could ever hope to meet.
And that's right near the beginning of a book I'm loving,
called The Cryptonomicon, or actually just called Cryptonomicon by Neil Stevenson.
I love this book, and I have been in hog heaven listening to this,
a lot of Hendrix stuff that I never heard before, which is saying something.
And in fact, we will, well actually Lonesome Cowboy Dave should be calling in any minute now.
I've got another couple of Hendrix songs.
You might not...
You may have heard before, but not these versions.
And also, he'll be preaching at the end.
A lot of...
Oh, I'll turn Princess Wee on.
She's here.
A lot of really good stuff came off of a commercially available four-CD box set
called West Coast Seattle Boy.
And when I was writing the credits for this show,
I was writing the initials of that album.
West Coast Seattle Boy.
West Coast Seattle Boy, WCSB,
which is the radio station in Cleveland from which we're broadcasting tonight.
And I'm sure you'd rather hear this Hendrix music than me,
but that's too bad, because this is the hour of slack.
And when we get instrumentals, we sometimes talk over them,
and I just told you where you can find them.
This actually is called Villanova Junction Jam.
And actually, I don't think it is on WCSB, West Coast Seattle Boy.
It was on something that J.R. Bob Dobbs recorded.
He used to run around with Hendrix a lot,
and he left a lot of tapes in Dobbstown,
and apparently Dr. G. Gordon Gordon dug them up.
We are so lucky.
Yes.
I could go on and on about that, and I might.
Here, we can just turn this.
Here we can just turn this.
My kids weren't real big Hendrix fans, and my parents hated it.
But Lonesome Cowboy Dave probably knows all about it.
Yeah, I'll tell you all about it.
No, not really.
I won't be rest of reason right now.
Well...
Is everything okay there, Dave, where you are?
I mean, by okay, I mean...
Well, I don't know what I mean.
Well, I have to hold the phone up to my head, funny.
I'm just going to make a comment before we begin.
I know that many times we layer our performances
with different aspects of the absurd,
and also there's the unexpected occasionally
and the other things that create laughter.
There's often many, many sophomore jokes
about...
...experienced inflations and things like that.
But if you think about it really, really, really, really hard,
if you really try to put your finger on any one particular thing,
I think we're just like rats in a maze
running around and grabbing the cookies at the right time
so we get, like, genetic overpoints.
Yeah, so?
Well, I was hoping if we got some genetic overpoints,
we might get, you know, a little bit of ubermatch.
That's credit.
Ubermatch credit and underpoints.
Ubermatch credit?
Hey, did you catch that song about X-Day
that I just played, the Hendrix song,
called...
Yeah, I know.
...The Stars That Play With Laughing Sam's Dice?
I don't understand that, though.
It was like Hendrix's secret...
A secret subgenius, yeah.
Well, he...
You know, Bob...
Bob...
Dobbs actually started the church of the subgenius in 1953.
And when Hendrix was just starting out,
he may have been a subgenius,
but I think he was a good subgenius
and schismed and started his own religion,
which he called the Electric Church or the Electric Sky Church.
Unfortunately, their church headquarters, believe it or not,
was not much better than ours.
It was...
And it was somewhere in New York.
Huh?
At least it wasn't in Dallas.
Right.
Which I guess is the home of all evil.
Well, there's a story about Jimi Hendrix in Dallas
where he...
I don't know how many concerts he played in Dallas,
but this was the one I saw when I was 15 years old.
And it sounded terrible to me,
because where I was sitting and the place it was in.
But as I...
I read in a book that when...
This would have been 1969.
And Hendrix was backstage getting ready to go on
and these Dallas cops walk into the room
and they look at Mitch Mitchell and Noel Redding
studiously avoiding Hendrix.
And they said,
if that N-word plays the Star Spangled Banner,
he ain't gonna leave Dallas.
He's alive.
Well, needless to say,
Hendrix went out and as people in the close rows describe it,
it was a great show.
Unfortunately, the bootleg that I heard of it
sounded like what I heard,
which was a giant auditorium made of concrete.
He did play the Star Spangled Banner.
He did.
Yeah, he did.
And he left Dallas alive.
The cops ran off with their tails tucked between their legs.
And I wonder if he did that song, Mr. Bad Luck.
Which I played earlier.
Which...
Wasn't he one of the original founders of the town, Mr. Bad Luck?
He was kind of like a Mr. Potter's guy in Capitals.
It's a wonderful life.
Like, you know, a real curmudgeonly old capitalist
who'd do anything for...
And originally cornered the oil market.
Are you talking about Jimi Hendrix or Bob
or that Dallas cop or which?
Um, Mr. Bad Luck.
Oh, right, right, right, right.
Sorry.
My tummy's upset.
I'm distracted.
It's true.
I have a very sneaky feeling that perhaps you can't even hear me.
Because you guys sound like you're...
Well, Dave, I think the station's bad line is being bad.
Your phone sounded fine earlier, right?
Well, it sounds terrible here.
It sure sounded fine to me.
It's...
It sounds really bad here.
It's making that special WCSB ocean noise in the background.
Well, to me, what I'm hearing are squirrels.
I'm not using my landline.
I'm using the one I just called We Run.
Right, I know.
It's not your fault.
It's the...
And it's not actually the station's fault.
It's the phone company and the university work very, very, very slowly together.
Because I guess that's their idea of slap.
But it isn't very...
It's not very good for this show.
They keep on taking breaks to go in and get a beer or two and stuff like that.
And taking a little drive, you know what I mean?
Stuff like that.
Dave, I hate to say it, but this is really sounding bad on this end.
Well, she might try and call again.
Yeah, why don't you do that?
I'll just...
I'll tell you what.
Call back.
I'll play the song My Friend, which is four minutes long.
So why don't you call back in four minutes?
Four minutes.
Okay?
Thank you.
I'll call back in four minutes.
Okay.
Okay, bye.
And that means I have to do this.
Okay.
It said, come around to my room with a tooth in the middle and bring along a bottle and a present in.
Come along with a hole in the wall and bring along a present in.
Sometimes it's not so easy, especially when your only friend sees and talks, walks, looks and feels like you.
You feel walking, same like him.
Must turn the page right now.
Well, I'm riding through L.A. on a bicycle built for fools.
I see one of my old buddies and he says, you don't look like the way you used to do.
Well, I say, some people look like a coin box.
He says, like, you ain't got no coins to spare.
I just pick up my prize.
I ride from underneath the payphone and come with breath right out of my hair.
Yeah, but sometimes it's not so easy, especially when your only friend sees, looks, talks, feels like you.
And you do the same, just like him.
Well, I just got out of Scandinavian jail and I'm on my way straight to you.
But I'm feeling so dizzy.
I take a quick look in the mirrors to make sure my friend's there, too.
And you know that I don't drink coffee, so you fill my cup full of sand.
But the frozen tea leaves on the bottom, cherry lipstick around a broken edge.
And my phone, that left, may you talk.
This talks, looks like you.
And you feel and talk just like him.
Do parts of the song very, very moments.
Lastly, you can listen to what he says.
Fill my cup.
W house.
W room.
You do it all, task, multitask, every time, right?
papaya talk po us it's it's apple pie bun
if I get through this to say
that I get
You have to full reading,
get prepared,
and text
Well, well, well, well.
I hope that when Dave calls back, things will work better.
It's kind of some sort of magical situation that this board runs on.
Sometimes the magic ain't there.
Boy, it was really getting...
Oh, well.
It was getting too crunchy.
What did you say, Princess Wee?
Yes, it's a crunchy noise we get on that line.
And if it doesn't work, I've got more of that Captain Beefheart sung by women.
But hopefully this will sound better.
What?
No.
Hi, Dave.
This is weirder than before.
It's crunchy.
Can you hear me at all?
Yeah, we can hear you clearly, but there's this nasty background crunchiness.
I can't hear that on your end, but my signal is clear, right?
Well, it's very bad here.
And I'm afraid we're not going to be able to subject the listeners to this crunchiness.
I don't think.
It makes me sad.
It's tragic.
We got a suggestion.
We need to block out line one first before Dave calls in.
This isn't line one.
Line one is blocked.
Oh, okay.
It's line three.
I see.
This is the only one we can get, apparently.
Okay.
Well, thanks for the try there.
Yeah.
Dave, do you have any messages that you can say over the scratchy crunchiness?
Well, will they be clearly understood by my audience?
When I make these pronouncements, I'd like to make sure that each and every one of the
young people I'm talking about, they understand these subgenius values and the virtues and
the things that we're expected to do.
As long as I don't turn any music on, yeah, they can understand you.
Well, I can't.
I can't even hear any music.
All I can hear is you.
There isn't any.
That was all really clear, what you just said, Dave.
I think the listeners got that message.
That wasn't the message, though.
Oh.
That was the preface.
Oh, that was the preface of the message.
Okay.
The prepuce of the message.
The prepuce.
Well, yeah, it was the intro of the message that was set up.
That was the foreskin.
Okay, so whip it back and what's the message?
Well, the message is, of course.
To maintain these virtues and vices and to advertise our benign aspects and to more thoroughly
pronounce each punishmental value that's incrementally added to the core delusion of
the entire spectrum.
Now it's getting to where your message is being lost.
I think.
You mean verb?
Well, it was lost before you started emitting it, I think.
I think.
But it's, the sound is crunchy.
Very.
It sounds like a bad radio sound effect that's supposed to be fire burning, like somebody's
crumpling paper.
That's fire burning.
Only there's kind of an ocean in the distance.
It could be a plosive device planted in the microphone system because I noticed each time
you said ca-ca or any sound with a ca or a hard plosive piece.
I think it's a sound that it sounded like the burning you were talking about.
The aforementioned emission of the particles in between.
The P sound.
Right.
That's one way of putting it, if you were going to put it anywhere.
But I think, you know, we might fry our organs just trying to get around the idea.
To scope it, to fully grasp it.
You know, line three is the only one that lights up when somebody calls.
Ah.
And somebody tried earlier.
In the show, which is, denotes someone who is not a regular hour of slacklist for them
to make that attempt at all.
So, Dave, I guess we should, well, it's not too, it's not too horrible now.
No, the listener.
Now that we don't, but I can't, you know, if I, if I put the Jimi Hendrix music in the
background, it's, it's really not, they fight each other.
The crunching.
Yes, yes.
And the crunching, actually, we should have.
We shouldn't do this.
The crunching sounds like a bad broadcast signal and that's not what's happening.
The signal is fine.
It is the, the, but either my ears or the phone line are guilty.
And how about your ears, Princess?
Oh, no, I can clearly hear all the mushing and the crushing and the, it's like dull popcorn
popping.
Dull.
That's the problem.
So you can hear, in other words, you can hear line three.
But if you were to take your headphones off and just listen to, you know, if you were,
but you can tell it's not coming from here, but it is.
It has nothing to do with you, Dave.
But what I'm going to do is move on and, and I'm afraid we're going to have to continue
this conversation hopefully next week.
Even if we have to pick you up in Ashtabula and drag you here and put you in front of
a microphone and then take you back home again, which I really don't want to do.
So I'm going to go back.
There's, there's, there was this Hendrix song called Calling All Devil's Children, where
it's just a jam for the first three minutes.
But the last three minutes, the jam kind of goes under and it sounds like he's standing
on a chair preaching to a room full of people.
Now, like the famous slow, long version of Voodoo Child.
That's actually, it was actually done.
It was done in the studio and he staged the make the audience to make it sound like it
was in a nightclub.
Did you know that?
Yeah.
I not only knew that, I think that maybe in some other transgressionary existence,
I might have authored that same piece.
Voodoo Child?
Yeah.
The long version.
It's.
Yeah.
It was a, well, it was, it was foreshortened because of the, you know, you know, lack of
equity.
There was too much of it.
No.
Okay.
Well, we're going to go back to this song, All, All the Devil's, Calling All Devil's
Children, in which Jimi Hendrix is a preacher.
So, um, I have to say good night, Dave.
You do sound better on this end.
I don't know.
Has anything changed?
It doesn't have any, no, no, no, nothing has changed.
It has nothing to do with you or anything you can do.
Just like our lives.
There's nothing you or me can do about anything.
It's terrible.
Oh, well, okay.
It's futile then.
It's due upon the doodoo.
Okay, doodoo.
See you later.
See you.
Bye.
Alright ladies and gentlemen, tonight our guest speaker is Mr. Artin Jackson.
Yeah.
Right.
Go, go.
Right, the main point, the main point, the main point I'm trying to say right
It's gonna be completely lost.
You're gonna be living out of confusion.
Confusion!
And I'm gonna say, it only takes about three or five minutes a day by yourself at home
to define yourself, to figure yourself out, to find out what you wanna do with money.
Right?
Right!
Yes, money, there's so many things happening in America.
What are we supposed to know about it?
What are we gonna know about it?
We're gonna fight this, we're gonna know about it!
Yes!
We're gonna be in the light.
And if I were you, I'd be like...
I'm gonna wait outside, I'm gonna tell about it, I'm gonna wait outside.
I'm gonna fight this.
Hold on, hold on.
I got nothing.
You gotta save yourself.
What do you mean, listen?
You're not listening to me, are you?
You're not listening...
Yes!
I'm listening to you!
No!
You're gonna run out of confusion if you don't listen.
Oh, there's a fight!
Fight it, fight it, fight it, fight it!
Come on, come on, come on!
Come on!
Oh, I'm trying to give you more seconds.
All right, here I...
I'm trying to give you less than...
One, two.
One, two, three, four.
Five, three.
The retail giant says this is PR News, Washington.
The retail giant says this is PR News.
And where it all belong
The earth goes down on their knees
Looking for a little ease
She stuck out her tongue and the fun begun
She stuck it out at me
And I just thumbed my nose
And went on washing my clothes
The dark curtain descends
A mysterious presence is lurking in the gloom
Reaching out with invisible hands
Aha, if only mobs were alive to see this
Huh? What's that?
Don't you remember?
Don't you remember, you old friend?
Bob?
But you're dead
I've come back
And I have a little something for you
No!
Be loyal
Shh!
Quiet, you two
I'm receiving some sort of signal
A warning
A cry for assistance
It's no good
I'm losing contact
What is it, Mr. Z?
I wonder if we'll ever know
Hi, pal
I see you're still hard at work on the
Bob?
Murder
Is there no hope?
Actually, Forbes
I have a question for you
Have you ever seen this man?
Bob?
Be loyal
Ah, Weasel
You're back
Any luck?
Yes, but
It has something to add
There's been a change in plans
What's in the package?
You'll find out
But first, I must say this
Tonight at the costume party
I advise you to abandon your plans to come dress as
Bob?
What?
But why?
The costume was designed by an expert
And it isn't the dress
I'm not a
Get up
He's stolen the show
Did you say
Bob?
Get up?
Where is he?
I must speak with him
Would you like some punch?
You poor fool
I've traveled halfway around the world
And waited four long years for this moment
Ah, satisfaction
Friends, that last little bit there was
Caught up by Reverend Exister
I don't know the origins of it
It's something called Paradis Zone
Before that
The Captain Beefheart song
Lick My Decals Off Baby
Was not performed by Captain Beefheart
But by a band called Kiss Kiss Kill
And that's off the album
Mama Kangaroo
Philly Women Sing Captain Beefheart
And we may have some more of that
This music in the background
Boy, this is the one that went great
With Slaying the...
With the Royal Ludroth in my video game
In a murky, underwater lake
Well, lakes are usually underwater
But this one was especially underwater
And it's funny how ballet-like
The killing of giant amphibious monsters can be
If you've got the right background music
It wasn't even in slow motion
But it kind of seemed that way
You know?
Here's another nice bit
From the early part of Neal Stephenson's novel
Cryptonomicon
It describes the moment when this young math whiz
He's kind of an aspie
He's not very socially adept
But he's a math genius
And he's about 12 years old or so
And the church organist
Or organ teacher
And he's a math teacher
Explains to him how a pipe organ
Like in a church works
The organist, math teacher
Sat down with a few loose pipes
Of pencil and paper
And helped Lawrence figure out
Why it worked
When Lawrence understood
It was as if the math teacher
Had suddenly played the good part
Of Bach's Fantasia and Fugue in G minor
On a pipe organ the size of the spiral nebula
In the world of music
In Andromeda
The part where Uncle Johann
Dissects the architecture of the universe
In one merciless descending ever-mutating chord
As if his foot is thrusting
Through skidding layers of garbage
Until it finally strikes bedrock
In particular, the final steps
Of the organist's explanation
Were like a falcon's dive
Through layer after layer
Of pretense and illusion
Thrilling or sickening or confusing
Depending on what you were
The heavens were riven open
Lawrence glimpsed choirs of angels
Ranking off into geometrical infinity
Believe it or not
I actually know how he feels
Although it wasn't a math teacher
Explaining organs that got me there
Although it may have had something to do with organs
I suppose
And here's something to do
Oh, well
Well, uh, yes
Uh, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful
Let's just be quiet and listen to this
Lovely, um, underwater
Royal Ludrath slaying music
By Jimi Hendrix
It's called New Rising Sun
New Rising Sun
Thank you.
From PR News in Washington, I'm participating in one of the worst massacres in France as retribution for a mayor who did not endorse bad PR.
Oradour sur Glanin.
The Dowd 616457-641-61-1838.
An 88-year-old former member of a Nazi SS division says this is PR.
And this is Hour of Slack.
And that was, well, Leamer.
The mighty Leamer does PR news things.
And the song we heard before that was the...
The Captain Beefheart song Plastic Factory, which I think was in his very first, well, maybe his second album.
That was being sung by someone named Lisa Christ Superstar.
Really?
Yes.
Lisa Christ Superstar.
And in a minute I'm going to play Crazy Little Thing, Captain Beefheart song by...
Only it's done by someone named Mia Johnson.
Friends, we haven't talked about Church of the Subgenius stuff much tonight, but we don't need to because what we've been doing is playing the things that helped make the Church of the Subgenius what it is.
Don't blame Jimi Hendrix or Captain Beefheart entirely, but let me put it this way.
The first albums or records I ever bought, number one was a 45 of Monster Mash, which my brother promptly sold.
I broke, but I forgive him.
The next, then I bought nothing but movie soundtracks for a long time because I didn't care for this rock and roll stuff.
But I like the...
Oh, brother.
The Monkees did some songs I heard on the radio, and my first rock album was Last Train to Clarksville.
But then my experience with rock and roll started to snowball.
And the second album that I bought was Magical Mystery Tour.
The third album I bought was Jimi Hendrix's Are You Experienced?
Because at this point I went, some of...
This is rock and roll stuff.
This isn't rock and roll.
This is science fiction.
Are You Experienced? I consider to be a science fiction album.
And actually, Magical Mystery Tour is certainly a fantasy thing.
The next album I bought after...
Are You Experienced? was Frank Zappa's We're Only In It For The Money.
And...
And my...
At some point, I think in my junior year, my friend turned me on to the Captain Beefheart album Trout Mask Replica,
which I have proved on previous shows I know by heart.
I don't know anything else by heart.
Simple.
I don't know anything else by that band called Heart.
This is the Hour of Slack, broadcasting this particular recording from WCSB Cleveland.
Although you may be listening on another station in the future.
But it'll be your now, you nowists.
And...
For more information, of course, subgenius.com.
All you have to do is spell subgenius.
Or write to P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
I think.
And now back to the...
God, this is great.
It is.
I'm just gonna leave this on.
We'll play the Beefheart next week.
Ha ha ha.
Ya ya ya ya ya.
.
guitar solo
This is WCSB Cleveland, 89.3 FM.
Friends normally, Radio Synesthesia would be starting right now,
but I just got word that Radio Synesthesia had a little bit of car trouble.
Dr. Sinister won't be here for another 10 or 15 minutes.
Luckily, I have this fantabulous Hendrix instrumentals
that I was planning to play in the background, so...
What's this one called?
Oh, this one is called Untitled Basic Track.
It was a song that no one knows what the lyrics were to go to it.
It's a mystery song, anyway.
guitar solo
Thank you.