1, 2, 3, 4
I look mad
And then the evening goes
Do I really look like a guy with a plan?
You know what I am?
I'm a dog chasing cars.
I wouldn't know what to do with one if I caught it.
You know, I just do things.
I'm not a schemer.
I try to show the schemers how pathetic
their attempts to control things really are.
He'd use the computer room
as if it were an amusement gallery.
And a fully clothed man frozen to death in a shower.
If the image wasn't so ugly, it'd be laughable.
Definitely not drugs or intoxication.
The bioanalysis on the tapes proved that conclusively.
Could be some form of space madness we've never heard of.
But I suspect I can no longer turn my back on Cadet Stinty.
The rigors of space travel have somehow twisted his mind.
He's gone crazy.
Space madness.
Oh, my beloved ice cream bar.
How I love to lick your creamy center.
Ow.
And your oh-so-nutty chocolate covering.
You're not like the others.
You're like the...
You're like the same things I do.
The crack papers.
The four-inch football leather.
The dog bread.
We're not hitchhiking anymore.
We're riding.
Stop it.
You're talking crazy.
It feels like your skin is being torn right off you
and then you ache all over and get sick and you can't breathe.
Your nose runs and you have a high fever and then you pass out.
But when you wake up, it starts all over again.
Under theיהw civilization.
The power of research.
Such a stupid, ghastly, tragic mistake.
All right, you listen to me.
Don't pay any attention to him.
He's drunk.
You sure?
Well, gymsh evet can cause a man to have visions.
It fits, too.
What I can't figure out is how.
You, you, the tongue of death.
What? Why not?
die you die fine yes you are the red guys died that's go anything else no hey oh you can see
the difference between a real cigarette and marijuana and there'd be no mistaking the
texture or contents if you were to handle them the darker one has been rolled in wheat straw paper
in most of the reefers a double thickness of paper is used now in the language the addicts
use among themselves marijuana is referred to as Mary Jane pot weed or tea they never say to
each other let's smoke a marijuana cigarette they say let's turn on or let's blast the joint
oh that's different some of your relatives want me to smoke a piece of pipe over here
well then everyone loses their minds
oh
I'm guaranteed to give you what you need
wake up every morning
make the world stampede
yo with me make we roll some weed
man charge nigga now I must proceed
yo with my turn and woof steps speeda
please don't make me fight keep tip I think shot leader
why me knock you out like a pot load creed
body blows buster yo shit making you bleed
just feed or die die make flows and dead peter
need more information ho boy then just weed
aye ya you can read all about the pure breed
do the normal that's why do the red fast either
oh yeah
yeah
man
it's a hell of a battle
a little trouble
money
no
we face a little STEVE
Topic in the traffic
Open up the car, open up the car
Low and near retake and bass crazy kickin' it
Looking for a star like mine, you can't find it
Looking for a star like mine, you've been blinded
Open up your morning light
And sing a little prayer for us
You know that if we all just stay alive
And see the peace that I feel
I grew up on the crime side, the New York time side
Stayin' alive was no job, had second hands
Moms bounced on old men
So they're all gonna be like me
Then we moved to Shaolin land
A young youth, you're rockin' the go-to
Low goose, only way I begin to G-York was drug loop
And let's start it like this, son
Rollin' with this one and that one
Pullin' out gats for fun
But it was just a dream for the team
Who was a fiend, started smokin' booze at 16
And runnin' up in gates and doin' hits by eye stakes
Makin' my way off fire escapes
No question I was speed for cracks and weed
The combination made my eyes bleed
No question I was flow off and tried to get the girl off
Chicken up like boys on board boy
Forever, forever, forever, ever, forever, ever
You went to school to learn girls
Things you never, never do before
Why I ain't I for E except F for C
And Y2 plus 2 makes 4, na-na-na
I'm gonna teach you
All about love, yeah
Sit yourself down, take a seat
All you gotta do is repeat after me
Come on, come on, come on, let me show you what it's all about
Boy, that was a fun
devival we had in Amsterdam
with the Scandahoovians and the
other Euro-foreigners.
I loved
Dr. Howell in Seattle. I
was so glad that he was there.
It was fun to be there at that strange
devival.
Well, you're becoming quite the world traveler
now. Well, I have to
admit, whenever the
normal creepy bobbies
came up, I would go and stand
and say hello to Howell.
They were just so scared of Howell's impressive
intelligence that they would go away.
Oh, they are like
moths fluttering around
subgenius luminosity.
Yours as much as mine.
You know how I deal with the creepy bobbies?
Howell, get them off!
Get them off! Get them off! I lift up my video
camera and point it at them.
And suddenly the roles are reversed.
And they're like,
Oh, what are you doing?
I lift up my video cam from which
cometh my strength. But what are worse
are the ones that fall in love in front of
that camera? The ones that you point
making them go away and they go
boing, boing, boing.
Oh, am I going to be a YouTube
star? Yes.
I guess so.
Hey man, I'm going to put a cigarette
in my eye and do it in my ear and I'm
going to drink another beer.
There's a big fad
on YouTube of
youths doing
heavy drugs, especially
salvia lately, and filming themselves.
That occurs to me that they're not really
very forward-thinking youths.
They must not be planning to run for
president or get a job. They're feeling their
ways along, but it's true.
They do, they're so compromised
that maybe they're doing the good work
of when everyone is compromised,
no one can be compromised. When everybody is shown
on YouTube vomiting
salvia. Yeah, only a few.
Two sour, old, uptight
Jesuits will be the only ones
who haven't degraded themselves in front of
the entire world.
Then who was going to care
about propriety?
It was?
You know, the frop in Amsterdam was so
good that I forgot
to take videos. I still haven't come down.
The frop in Amsterdam was so good
that Ratnar has forgotten that he's not
in Amsterdam anymore and hasn't been
for months. Right, and I end up
having these bizarre dreams where I'm not going to be able to do anything.
Our Amsterdam kind of mixes
with Kentucky. Now that is
a curious analogy.
I'm getting back to KFC, the parlor.
Surprise, surprise, surprise!
That's a funny cigarette
they just handed me.
In Contuxter-dam?
Or is it
Amsterdam-y?
A marijuana cigarette was found
on the floor of one of your classrooms.
And another
was found in the girls' gym.
And that's enough to start
a big crusade in Sanibel High?
Mr. Burroughs, please understand
Miss Williams, like many of us,
believes in the progressive theory
that there is no such thing
as a bad boy or girl.
Well,
there's a high school in Indiana.
I don't know whether they
followed your progressive theories or not.
They had no problem
three years ago.
But out of a total enrollment of
1,200 students,
285 were found to be using
marijuana or heroin.
And this dreadful condition
was only uncovered
through a horrible accident.
One student, desperate for money
to pay for his habit,
sold bennies for quarters and dimes
to kids in elementary school.
It was the death
of a 13-year-old
who had been addicted to marijuana
and then to heroin
that exposed the ugly facts.
But by that time,
it was too late for 41 teenagers
who were addicted.
It can happen here.
Oh!
Hey, what's going on around here?
Whoa!
And Bob Frown went around all big
and said,
they can be
So he puffed and he puffed
until he choked.
And he choked and he choked
until he puffed.
And he bobbed up his joke.
A lonesome character,
Cowboy Dave.
They're all mangled up by
Lean Murr, who also did our titles.
And this is our annual
educational space madness
drug war show.
Before the lesson there,
we heard some radio synesthesia
from WCSB Cleveland
with host Dr. Sinister,
callers Priestess Pisces,
Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
Dr. Howe, Governor Rocknar,
Nomany Mark, and yours truly
on WCSB,
Cleveland.
I'll say that word again.
WCSB Cleveland.
Prior to that,
that great mashup is by Girl Talk.
See MySpace slash Girl Talk Music
for more on that amazing individual.
That's actually one person cutting up
millions of other people.
Lee Murr and I collaged the opening
to the show, you might say,
opening the ears, eye.
Uh,
but it is the psycho skeletons
who perform this homage called
I Love You Special K.
Yes, certainly.
You might understand exactly how I feel
But you don't care, I know
That's what I'd love you to do
Special K, Special K,
Special K,
Special K gives you half of what you deserve
All those minerals and vitamins
is the great test
Would you also like some strips
of bacon and fruit to finish it off
Or perhaps you'd like a medium cup of coffee
Special K, Special K,
Special K gives you half of what you deserve
All those minerals and vitamins
Is the greatest
Would you also like some taste
Would you also like some strong
Or perhaps you'd like a medium cup of coffee
Citizen of the mutually assured revolution
Be nine and be kind
You went too far and forgot where you parked your car
Pain, disease, slavery, war
You say you wanna eat your Special K
Right this way
Hup, hup, hup, hup, hup, hup
Special K, Special K, Special K
They say it's women's food but will it make you gay
No
Hup, hup, hup, hup, hup, hup, hup
Hup
Hup, hup, hup, hup, hup
Hup, hup, hup, hup, hup, hup
Special, Special K
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
From PR News in Washington.
I am Iron Man.
I first dropped acid when I was 18.
I was over at these people's house one night.
This guy I went to school with was over there and asked me if I wanted to try some acid.
I had read about it in the newspapers and heard a few friends talk about it, so I was curious.
I was pretty jacked up on marijuana, so I decided to try it.
And I dropped it.
I don't know what I was waiting for, a flash or a rush or whatever,
but I kept sitting there waiting and waiting and nothing was happening.
So I got up and then went to the dresser and put on a pair of pink capris and a green and brown blouse.
I thought the colors were beautiful.
So we tripped down to Market Street and I decided to buy a hot dog.
I was very hungry.
And I had put mustard and ketchup and relish in the usual.
And I put the hot dog up to my mouth and somebody started screaming.
I didn't know what was happening, so I looked up at my friend Terry and said,
Did you hear that?
Didn't you hear someone scream?
He said no.
I got the hot dog up to my mouth again and I was ready to bite.
And the scream got louder and it hit me.
No, it couldn't be.
And I looked down at the hot dog and there was a face on him.
Eyes, nose, a mouth.
I had put the ketchup to where it looked like his hair.
And he started telling me that I couldn't eat him,
that he had a wife and seven kids at home to support.
And I stood there with this hot dog and asked Terry,
Do you know this hot dog is talking to me?
And he says,
Nah, let's get out of here.
He thought I was just faking.
And I told him,
Look at the thing, he's got a face.
And he's screaming.
And the guy finally looked over and he got on the same trip that I was on.
And we sat there carrying on a conversation with that hot dog.
Finally, I decided I was just hallucinating,
so I put it in my mouth and bit down.
It screamed so loud that you could hear it all over town.
So I had to throw it on the ground and step on it.
And I was jumping on this hot dog in the middle of Market Street.
I realized that I had murdered it.
And I took off screaming down the street, scared.
I was reallyquaossed.
..
So my wife calls me.
My mom tells my dad something.
I got away with it, so six guys struck me all the time.
And me and my wife?
We beyond heart were told to結 agriculture
Where's AP?
C'day.
commaggio
intelligence
resources
就是
Thank you.
a corporate state.
Blogs, I always wanted to just call...
You can flog your blog,
but they're more fun to write
than they are to read, generally.
Oh, yeah.
There aren't enough hours in the day
to read such an enormous teetering tower
of bitching and whining.
Oh, absolutely.
But it is...
The nice thing about reading
other people's blogs a lot of times
is that their trifles
are so much more interesting
than your own.
And when you read about their discontent,
you feel strangely comfortable.
You feel comfortable yourself.
Exactly.
Sometimes you find out
that there are powerful beings
from another dimension
that are secretly controlling your mind.
That's really screwed up.
I'd hate to think
what they pay for their internet connection.
Oh, yeah.
What makes you think they pay?
I think we pay.
I think we're all being mind-controlled
by existential aliens
from you-know-where.
Well, here's the thing.
With the mind-control state,
the key is really to fill your mind
with misguidedness
and misleading garbage.
So let your mind wander
through misleading things
and then the mind-control
sort of short-circuit.
Well, all roads lead to Rome.
You can wander through thickets of error,
but as long as you keep a-moving,
you'll eventually find your way
out of the labyrinth
and be better than before
for the journey.
Well, all trails...
Except for all those thorn punctures.
The misleading things
all lead to Bob.
All roads lead to Dobbs, too.
Do you think Bob tried...
No, Bob simply succeeds.
I think that Bob should be represented
on the door
that it's leading to him
where you go there
with, like, little bones underneath
and his head is like the skull
in that one.
Ooh, this is getting spooky.
That's a scary door.
I don't know whether I want to go through that door.
No, the road has gone through you
in many more ways than you can think of.
At least in this parallel world.
Some of them are...
What's the opposite of parallel?
Parallels are weird.
I prefer, um...
Usually, the parallelogram, for example,
kind of freaks me out.
I hate being in parallel hell
and not even know it.
Then there's the perpendiculargrams.
Oh, man, those guys really suck.
I think they should not let them go to school
or to have jobs.
But who was in control of the school on the jobs?
Those perpendicular dickheads.
No yeti left behind.
It sure ain't Bob.
It's the perpendicular dickheads.
They've been perps for years
and now it's about time...
It's time for them to do the perp walk.
Yeah.
Backward.
I'm supposed to give a message to Sinister
from...
Oh, let's have it.
Oh, yeah?
...that he has...
is releasing another...
Another what?
Excellent.
He's releasing another conflict.
He's releasing a...
It's a conflict.
...cloud of unknowing.
It's very conflicted, yes.
I would say conflicted.
But then, if you know two beans, basically,
there is a conflict there,
a conflict of worlds.
Maybe...
Maybe those parallelograms...
Those parallelograms are affecting him.
I should probably keep an eye out
for any parallel...
Watch out for the trapezoids, too.
...things going on in my household.
Priestess Pisces
on Radio Synesthesia WCSB
with host Dr. Sinister,
Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
Governor Rocknar,
Dr. Hal Robbins,
Nomany Mark,
and others.
And before that...
What?
Oh!
A little clip from Schizopolis.
And before that,
a sorry blues there,
warped by Lee Murr.
And the voices,
the weird, weird, weird, weird voices
that made you think, like,
you took too much or heard too much,
that was also by Ogo Dis,
or Dice, or whatever.
Um...
But now, we're going to go back to X-Day,
and where they holler for Philo's head.
Bring us Philo's head.
We may launch it, they say.
Bring us Philo's head,
so we may launch it.
That's old subgenius stuff.
We don't do that head-launching stuff anymore.
I was wondering if we could kneecap launch.
No, we're not going to stop anybody
from launching a head.
It just doesn't have our imprimatur anymore.
Right.
Well, the, um...
Uh...
The apostate, Jane or Hypercleets,
really is the only person
who should be launching Arnold Palmer heads.
And...
And so he does.
Right.
But not where I...
Not under my watch, no.
No.
Let's leave that to right where it's laying.
Many are called, but few are chosen.
And some fall by the wayside,
and some of the chaff is burned in the furnace
after the tares are gathered.
Yeah.
Cool.
clean Fuckin' O O W Wrangles
F Önőty
It was학교
I haven't heard you talk for like 20 minutes.
Pick a song ut you can't handle it.
a record
Somebody
call a lawyer
I need to
find it
Somebody's
whiplash
blindsided
rear-ended
Somebody
call a priest
I'm the
lost wise man
from the east
and I got
to town
long after
the party
ended
Somebody
call a
wrecker
Somebody
call a wrecker
call a junk man
Never lived in my heart
but a tin can
And it's banging
like a string
going leaking
like a city
It'll be a miracle
if I live
Somebody
call a wrecker
Call a wrecker
Bob Walkenhorst
from his CD
called The Beginner
You can find more
at
bobwalkenhorst.com
See, madness,
as you know,
is like gravity.
All it takes
is a little push.
Ha ha ha ha ha
Oh
Ah ha ha ha a
Take Scooby,
I did it
Oh do I
Just like
On my
All the fucking
My friends
the one who
fucking
right here
They
gotta
remember
There
where
be
Closer
TV hard
I'm taking the time to fuck
Take a touch with my soul
I'm taking the fucking human
I'm getting ready to bring myself
I'm getting ready to be human
To be human
I'm taking the time to fuck
Take a touch with my soul
OKDES, channeling the amino acids
There
it seems like, for a second.
A song called
Navel Sounds Like Whales
Clubbing Baby Cigarettes
in Kabul.
Has anybody seen the new
Jack T. Chick movie that both
Stang and I are in?
I have not. I was actually going to mention
Jack Chick, though, because on one of my
recent road trips to
pretty much banjo country
Virginia, I stopped at
a rest stop because I got
distracted because somebody was doing a Civil War
reenactment and kind of threw me off.
That can be distracting
when those mini balls come whistling.
Yeah, and so I pulled off
into this rest area and I noticed
in the map holder
there was a Chick track, and so then I looked
and in the other map holder on the other side there was
another, and it was like an Easter egg
on a Chick track. A beloved soul winner
Easter egg. I want to go on a
big tour of the South leaving
the Cthulhu
Chick track everywhere. Chicks are
attracted to Chick tracks.
That's right. Chick tracks
get red.
Cthulhu's attracted to graveyards and heavy
scents. But seriously, there's
a long documentary
about the life and works
of Jack Chick and his associates,
the artists and
flim-flam
men, rapists that he associated
with. Yes, these creationists
the guy who talks
about how there were only 30 dinosaurs
and they were all on Noah's Ark.
That guy turns out to be
well dipping his wick
where society doesn't sanction.
So is he now on one of the late
night slumber psychic
parties and stuff where each one of them
have to remove their masks at different times?
He's dead.
What is the title of this film?
Well, it's called God's Cartoonist.
And then the subtitle is
well, I've got it in my bag.
That would be Michelangelo, wouldn't it?
He sent me a copy of it two weeks ago
and I still haven't seen it.
I figured I'll watch it on my
escape vessel when I've
got more time.
Have you ever seen Michelangelo's Underground Porn?
You'd have plenty of time for that, boy.
Oh, all of that stuff was porn.
Now, are we featured in the new
Bill Maher movie, Religious?
What?
Well, we're
featured on the Religious website
that Bill Maher has.
Get off of here, or don't.
Well, we're featured
under Miscellaneous Other Religions
right next to the
Flying Spaghetti Monster.
Oh, my God.
Has it come to this?
Do we have to declare war?
And we don't have any meatballs.
But we still got the big cheese.
I have one.
Well, I thought you were the big cheese
and we're going to say something about it.
That Flying Spaghetti Monster is kind of
Cthulhoid in appearance.
It gives me a feeling of unease.
People are laughing and joking
and yawking it up.
They won't laugh on that side of their mouth
when they feel those pasta tendrils
creepily sliding around their necks.
They won't even have that
I've been touched inappropriately
by his noodley appendage.
Anyway, the Chick movie is called
God's Cartoonist, The Comic Crusade
of Jack Chick.
Directed by
Papa Joe Mama.
Which name should we use?
Jack Chick doesn't know that
the Papa Joe Mama of the subgenius
was that nice, polite young man
who interviewed him, I don't think.
Until this moment.
Maybe Jack doesn't know.
Because I know Jack listens to Radio Synesthesia.
Oh, he does?
With his tongue in his cheek while the rest of his mouth
was being removed when he was talking to the chicken?
If you ask Bernie, you'd think...
I should be upset that I've parodied his tracks
many times.
Those tracks are a great format.
New parodies come out all the time.
Droppings are better than actual tracks
because you can smell them.
But we're all headed the same direction.
Well, those are his digestive tracks.
It's different.
From the religious ones.
I would imagine that digesting
the Chick track would be difficult.
You may want to add, maybe soak it in some
vinegar.
They need to make a digested edition
of the Chick tracks, actually.
There's a story that
cartoonist Dan Klaus
took LSD and he sat on his bed
reading a huge pile of Chick tracks
and by morning he was ready
to convert.
Fortunately, he came down.
I've been there.
I mean, a good Jimmy Swaggart
rant will almost turn you.
It's so internally consistent
that you've got to watch out, you know.
Except for these bogus religions.
Some of those preachers
know who's listening.
Swaggart would often go,
you but television, watching for fun,
smoking on that joint.
You think this is funny.
And I'm going, oh my God.
He's in the spirit.
He knows it's me.
He can see.
You're not going to think
it's so funny when the flames
of hell are looking at your behind.
Sure we will, because they'll only
be speeding us on our way up
into the welcoming blackness
of outer space.
I would welcome any flame
were licking my behind right now.
Now let's keep it clean.
Is it that cold outside?
It's going to be tonight.
It's going to drop down
to the freezing cold of outer space.
Now see, that proves it ain't
global warming.
That's a hoax.
It was cold today.
But what about global warming?
We're all going to be stuck
in a vacuum just like that
Colombian coffee can.
We'll have air for a while.
It's not going to be good air, though.
Church air, one soul per breath.
You don't need that soul, friend.
And I should add that the
Jack Chick movie, God's Cartoonist,
is in fact great.
I saw it, and it is a
laugh-out-loud gut blowout
directed by Kurt Kirsteiner.
I saw it, and it is a
For more information on that DVD,
see monsterwax.com.
That's monsterwax.com.
The music in the background, by the way,
is Einstein's Secret Orchestra
from Witch Disco.
Out of print.
And now, Lonesome Cowboy Dave
shows off his double-mean baby head
to the video camera.
I'm growing a double-mean baby head.
Huh?
I'm growing a double-mean,
baby head.
It's still there.
The mean baby head is still there?
Yeah, it's growing out the back of my neck.
Yeah, I don't blame you for keeping it.
It's coming out the side, right here.
Keep that hood on.
That's what I wanted to...
I was trying to look outside,
underneath my ear.
I thought I heard it mumbling.
No, that was me.
It bothered me still,
because people are trying to use the right words.
Trying to say the right thing,
and I don't see the word.
You know,
you know,
you didn't place like an emergency room right here?
Sherman Fire Department.
There's a drool stain on the...
There's a lot of drool stains on the back of the hood
where it's been...
Sherman.
It's trying to...
It was trying to chew its way through the back.
Yeah, I could tell.
It looks...
I could feel it moving around
and telling it down.
Down on this side.
See?
Now I make my...
This kind of motion.
Do you have a history of this?
In your family?
No, no, no.
I ain't got no family.
You're the only one.
Yeah, I'm the only one.
Probably.
I got a pretty long history of it.
For the best.
Go back to...
No.
I don't know.
Go to your...
Mm-hmm.
Huh.
saladSo amazing ao dizzy
trabalaa
ok
don't
do that
take
dick.
kGs ikke afoper'mig
wasted and everybody's drinking on the job. The garbage man got trashed. The janitor got messy.
The taxi driver got smashed and the waitress, she got tipsy. In Kansas City, New York City,
great big city, itty bitty city now. Everybody's drunk and everybody's wasted
and everybody's drinking on the job.
Well, there's a whole lot of places that I ain't been, a whole lot of things that I ain't seen,
a whole lot of things that I ain't seen.
There's a whole lot of things I'll never be. The generation that would change the world is still looking for its car keys.
The terrorists got bombed. The president got hit. Security was tight. Yeah, the Secret Service got lit.
The FBI, CIA.
The DWI, USA.
Everybody's drunk and everybody's wasted and everybody's stoned.
And there's nothing that's gonna change it.
Cause everybody's drunk and everybody's wasted and everybody's drinking on the job.
The Rainmakers. Everybody's drunk and everybody's listening to this show, The Hour of Slack.
For more information on everything, especially J.R. Bob Dobbs and the Church of the Subgenius and archives of this show,
see subgenius.com.
And what's left is...
Leemurg and Bob on the loose at X-Day.
A councilman from Dearborn, Michigan is outraged over a 911 call.
He wants to know why no charges have been filed against a police officer who admits to confiscating marijuana from suspects and then baking it in brownies.
And once he and his wife were full and high, they thought they'd overdosed and called 911.
I think I'm having an overdose at a school with my wife.
Overdose of what?
Marijuana. But I don't know if it had something in it. Can you please send rescue?
Do you guys have fever or anything?
No, I'm just... I think I'm having a fever.
I think we're dying.
How much did you guys have?
I don't know. We made brownies. And I think we're dead.
Time is going by really, really, really, really slow.
Well, instead of being charged...
Perla.
Sorry.
Instead of being charged, the police department let the officer resign.
His wife was not charged either. So far, police officials have not commented on the case.
Oh, I didn't hear nothing.
Listen.
Now listen.
Just listen.
Well?
The thing for us to do is to...
We're going to barricade ourselves in this room.
Sure. Suits me.
Hey.
Stand to the right of the door. Stand to the left of the door. Stand directly in front.
Then open the door.
Yes?
Wait a minute.
Oh, no.
Any of you smell anything?
You mean that funny smell?
What? We smell just like an... an animal?
That's it.
I know what that signifies.
So do you.
Odor of predatory animals.
Exactly.
Well, what are the physical characteristics?
Oh, I...
You know, I...
Long, slender, pointed fingers.
Oh?
What else?
Eyebrows meeting across the nose.
Oh.
Sharp, pointed, elongated front teeth.
Like mine?
Tendency towards an airy body.
Oh.
You...
You mean...
Wheating cheese and a tough kind of curly hair.
Oh, please. Please.
Go on, Professor.
Stupid black fangs and smelling foully of tobacco smoke and stale beer.
Oh.
I'm glad.
Undo me in the back.
I'll have to take my dress off.
Well, I...
I just got out of fresh underskirt.
Yeah, take it off.
Yes.
All right.
What...
Would that do?
Here, let me see.
Hmm.
That needs immediate attention.
Unbutton the flap and get vile.
Hmm.
And I believe that concludes this two and a half hours or so of slack.
And please, look at your arms right now.
All right, hold your arms.
Hold your arms above your head, everyone, please.
Look around you in the...
In the group.
Anyone you see without a wristband on...
Kill them.
They have to be right here next to Princess We right now and get them there.
Will you please shut down the system?
Okay.
All right.