Usually radio announcements merely recommend a product, but this station provides its clients with a special service.
The Subgenius. Our host.
In the radio studios of art, the technicians, the entertainers, the commentators, the administrative personnel,
daily unite their efforts in the creation of programs to please and entertain a vast radio public.
Ah!
The wide variety of broadcasts include group discussions, political speeches, and comedy.
On this program, frank opinions are expressed in response to their leaders' questioning.
Questions of the day are discussed and opinions and attitudes freely expressed on issues of the moment.
For there is keen interest in a radio program that invites personal participation by the public.
This is...
This is Independent Radio in a Democracy.
Sir, hadn't you better buckle up?
Now buckle this!
Enjoy your little nap. I'm off to the warm embrace of my afternoon enema.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
It's another one of those triple X rated internet only hours of slack.
Well, I suppose it might end up being broadcast illegally somewhere.
Yes, indeed.
And it's inspired by the fact that we can.
And now, as we always have in any hour of slack show,
lots of collages by Federico Fernandinande Lemur.
The great Lemur.
Only in this case we can play some that normally would appear only in their home territory of alt.binaries.slag.
Become a welcome guest and ask through adventure apps.
No, no
The cookie is.
The cookie is
No, Lindsay, please don't!
Eric Elcom
Then, Leo Levi
No, no, what do you mean no? No, I don't want to go for a ride, a ride. Now that's a good idea.
Heineken, fuck that shit. Heineken, fuck that shit. Heineken, fuck that shit. Heineken.
Fast Blue Ribbon! Fast Blue Ribbon! Fast Blue Ribbon! Heineken, fuck that shit. Heineken.
Fast Blue Ribbon! Fast Blue Ribbon. Fast Blue Ribbon!
For the glasses
That beer's gonna get warm
One thing I can't fucking stand is warm beer
Makes me fucking puke
Pass Blue Ribbon
Heineken
Fuck that shit
Pass Blue Ribbon
Heineken
Fuck that shit
The Punk Group
A new...
Oh, by the way,
I should mention the new title there of the show
was by the Bishop.
But what we just heard was
the Punk Group
fine song there
called Heineken.
Every year, thousands of listeners
never contributed.
If you are one of these people,
fuck you very, very much.
You're not the first one to say that about the masked man.
Gee.
He's the loner.
Heineken
A prime Brigade
Yeah nor
LOL
Whole
****
solo
song
LOL
peu
PUT THAT IN THEânds
recomend
10-их
Dandwicha la chichora
Dandwicha, Dandwicha, Dandwicha la chichora
Now if you're hungry for some bologna
And you got buns that you wanna show me
Open up wide, you can eat this
Azkama that's really bony
I wanna get down into your jujubes
And I think I'm gonna flick em
Your titties all smelling like chocolate chip ice cream
And I think I wanna lick em
I got some hot people that run frozen but ya
Ya gotta say please
I'll dig into the thigh every time
But you hold the cottage cheese
And for dessert we can do the worst
If I'm a whipped cream in your pie hole
And don't flinch when you feel a pinch on that
Pretty little taco
Cause I've tried to pry your beaded clams there
That will not budge
So I went around the corner to keep on trying
And I got a little fudge
Dandwicha, Dandwicha, Dandwicha la chichora
Dandwicha, Dandwicha la chichora
A pile of potatoes, Wendy's
But she doesn't lend them
She moves a couple of tits more than a cart's dick
Bring a burro spaghetti with a beer in a can
The bad ones that she doesn't like
Step on her fifth leg
Save some chilaquiles for her
She's going to breakfast tomorrow
And some more chips for her
We're divorced, we don't want to get involved
White or integral, I don't care, I don't care
Mama chapata, mama chapata
And here are her chapatines
Dino, triple, pronto, doubler, quarter, pounder, whopper, double
I want to make her a sandwich
A tighter dance
Better than lamb, a spicy Italian one
I want to dance with the bora
But with the machichona
Dandwicha, Dandwicha, Dandwicha la chichora
Chankwicha achichona
Molotov did that song, Chankwicha achichona. I'm pretty sure that that's fairly dirty.
Let's see what's in the bag tonight. The thick yellow-green discharge from his genitals to your
lip. Oh, oh. And now we're going to move on. We're going to talk to Ribka. Hi, Ribka. Hi,
I have oral sex. All right, Ribka. Okay. Bye-bye. Bye. And we've got back Rib calling in. Hi,
back Rib. Hi, how are you? Very gross or dirty. And this is the result of upbringing.
I'm fine. I have a penis. She has a thick yellow penis.
It's gross. I heard that there was a way to get rid of that, but I don't know how.
Your butt can't do it. Really? Someone told me that vibrates. You're vibrating, but won't do it. No,
no. All right. Have fun. Okay. Bye-bye. Bye, back Rib. The S word, oh, shit. That's Old English.
It appears in Old English, but it's not common. And there it just seems to refer to diarrhea.
Do you have a bathroom problem in your house? It's a very busy place, isn't it? Where everyone in the
family...
has to brush their teeth, wash their hands, take a dish.
Here's the moon pants song. Mooney, mooney, moon pants, ejaculating your moon pants. That didn't
come out right. Mooney, mooney, moon pants, ejaculating your moon pants. What are moon pants?
Pants like the asterisks.
And that's war to the moon.
Hard driving. Hard driving blues rock.
Sounds like Kilbilly.
That's a Kilbilly.
That's some Kilbilly music.
Woo!
I'm a mean old Kilbilly.
I'm an X.
I've been sitting around way too long
Hell, right on Monday, I gotta get up
Oh, it's your modest alone
And I wanna get home
Mama
Oh, yeah, you're just gonna get over there to me
Let it all in and I'll spread it and go back down
Count those hotcakes that you will drive way up there
In between your legs like cheetahs
You'll be back in a minute
Take me to the bottom
Just hang it out there
I love it
I don't like how old I am
Can I stay away like that?
You look so old
I think I want you to feel my love
Yeah
Feel my love
I got a love for you, ma'am
I got a love for you, that's true
Woo, girl!
I got a love for you, baby
I gotta grow a thing to you
See that girl
Look, she's another
A thunderstruck sissy
All night long
Oh, man!
Feel my love.
Yeah, I want to tell ya
Feel that boy, I got love.
Feel my love.
He told me how.
Tell my daddy.
Ask the tree.
Feel my love.
Feel all that love.
Feel my love
Baby, feel my love
Feel my love for you
Cause I want you
Feel my love
Oh, mother!
My love
Oh, baby
Oh, baby, baby
Feel my love
I got another cry for you, mother
My love
Oh, see that man
What man?
He's got his hands in his pockets
Oh, that?
He's got his nuts caught
Oh!
In his lapidary pockets
Pockets
Feel my love
What love?
Throw it out my way
Oh, man
Feel my love
Throw it out
Oh, my love
That's all that I have for you, baby
It's so sweet
I've enjoyed it so you can
Feel my love
No
I don't have a sec
You didn't
And I do
The Swingin' Love Corpses
and before that friends
Joe Offric
and now more limer
Beaver
This episode was the very first script written by episodic shoplifters
starring Beaver
I think it's better if you don't look
What would I want to see?
June, look at
Mm-hmm
Gee, Dad
A horse
Yes, very nice
Look, dear
Just handle this
Yes
Look
Yeah
Oh
Uh-huh
Oh, uh
June
Pants off
What?
My word
Oh, two
Whoa
Yes
Uh
Oh, one
Ward
Yeah
Oh, yes
Ward
Oh, oh
Oh
Yes
Ha
Mm-hmm
Oh
Oh, Ward
Oh, yes
Oh
Mm-hmm
Yes
Oh
Mm-hmm
Ah
Oh
Yeah
Oh, my gosh
Ha
Oh
Yes
Hmm
Gee, Dad
Mm-hmm
Oh
Oh, you boys better get on to school
I'll put the tools away
Oh, okay, Dad
So long
So long, Dad
They are now planning for
Sex on the streets
In every major city from coast to coast
The music that they're planning to use
To crumble the morals of America
Is this rotten, filthy, dirty
Lewd, lascivious
Junk
Oh, rock and roll
Sex
It's the beat
How this beat gets them
Four hundred teenage girls
Which were interviewed
Asking why they had illegitimate babies
They said not just the word
The beat
Who's behind it all?
What this mysterious PT
Called sex
Sex
The fertility rights of the jungle
Those are the same beat
Incorporated in this modern rock
Just threw them up
The fertility rights of the jungle
Sex
The beat
It's the beat
That will destroy people's minds
The fertility rights of the jungle
Seat
Rock, rock, rock and roll
Sex
It's the beat
The beat
It'll destroy people's minds
It's the beat
The beat
They are now planning for
Sex
On the streets
In every major city
From coast to coast
Rock and roll
She's mine
Bug, bug, bug, bug, bug, bug, bug, bug, bug, bug, bug, point
Cums lurking off the Oregon coast.
With more on that, here's Cheryl.
We pick up more moisture, too, as we slide into eight inches of new cum.
Swirling and churning along Interstate 5 yesterday afternoon.
Also, too, notice these little puffies here.
I wouldn't be surprised to see a few more propping up later
as that moist cum continues to pour into your butt.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Scattered cum showers remain in the forecast,
along with cloudy cum scattered about Seattle, Olympia, and Tacoma, Washington.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
I've been convicted of wanton sexual encounters.
Connie?
Now, who was that?
You're in big trouble now.
Was that Lenny Bruce?
You've got a lot of splatting to do.
That's the Queen of England, isn't it?
Queen Connie Dobbs.
Her Majesty Queen.
Dissexed.
Feel ill.
That's exactly it.
Because you're getting...
She does not wish to be dissexed.
She has childbearing hips.
You ever notice that about Regina Vaginas, whatever her name is, Ruthless Betty?
What's her name?
They live forever.
A horrible thing.
The Queen's a royal stew.
I'm cured.
Well, the Queen Mother lived to be 9,000 years in Methuselah years.
Different frog years.
Of course, they hate frogs.
Lesson one.
Grr.
Lesson two.
Lesson three.
Grr.
也很漂亮。
请进。
Check it out, check it out.
This is a real, real ghost shirt.
Made famous by the ghost dancers.
啊!
nekano.
Have a good day.
阿 ramen.
Hot reason why.
Friday night .
Who's rising again?
死牛 .
Yeah.
сх。
胶卷。
Ah!
Yeah.
The rabbit.
Psychotronic Babel.
Nothing a Psychotronic Babel.
As if to wake the sleeping eruptions around the town.
You have been convict.
Uh.
of wanton sexual encounters.
Do you know what that means?
I've been wanting some sexual encounters.
And wanton?
I've been wanting one for a long time.
And still, my people have yet to come.
Come, come, come, come.
Our newborn king to come.
Our finest gifts we bring, come.
To lay the king, come.
Come, come, come, come.
So to lay him, come.
When we come.
On my bum.
Me and my drum.
The King's
53 years old?
Oh, now I'll need a fake ID to rent ultra porn.
And the Lord Jesus Christ quoting that verse.
Fags and dykes.
That jackass behind that black robe is a genuine hero that lives in god awful killing machines.
There's some little thing wrong in a piece of that equipment.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Some little thing.
Something wrong.
God did it!
Spitting in the face of God, the only real important enemy.
The vicar of Christ!
Evangelizing the world with the wonders of fagdom.
Come on!
The evidence is overwhelming.
It is not right.
And it's all one way.
God hates fags and God hates dykes and God hates Melissa Etheridge.
It is not right.
God hates this evil god forsaken town.
Slam that mother and grandmother.
Fag propagandists.
Makes America killing machines.
That would allow itself to be famous for one thing.
It's Sappho of Lesbos time.
Mother and grandmother sitting around up there in that space station sending emails to their friends and in an instant of time.
Yeah.
This god awful fag nation of ours.
But a militant fag.
An aggressive fag.
A pushy fag.
Evangelical fag.
That idiot Bush is talking about praying for these cybolical.
Christ inmates of hell.
Fag.
Name Steve.
Steve.
Praying for them.
Yeah.
God almighty killed them and cast them into hell.
Italicized and underlined and if we could put it in neon lights.
Fags and dykes.
Your preaching is a lie.
Come on!
The doctrine that we deliver.
Lord.
Slam that space shuttle to the ground in little fragments as it relates to the killing machine.
That fag pimp Bush.
Sitting around.
Ready to push the buttons.
And the San Francisco Chronicle just published technological killing machines.
You see that streak going across the sky.
It is not right.
Kill them all at once.
Lord.
Punch one button.
Honor.
This is our report.
Mmm.
Hm. Well, a smart workman would cut that nut off with a hammer and a greasy chisel, so it would slip, like this.
Amazing!
Um, the S word, oh shit, that's Old English. It appears in Old English, but it's not common, and there it just seems to refer to diarrhea.
Those are my rapist noises. You see, it sounds like I'm just whistling a tuneless whistle, but the
really means
that's the sound of the sperm coming out when a guy's raping a chick.
Now, you're gonna be subjected to a song that I made up.
Horny with a chick, horny with a chick, horny, horny, horny horn, horny with a chick.
I'm too sick to get the horn of those horns.
Horny with a chick, horny with a chick, horny, horny, horny horn, horny with a chick,
Horny with two chicks.
Horny, horny, horny, horn.
I am too sick
to get a horn?
With two chicks.
I'm gonna be a horny in my socks.
Horny in my socks.
Horny, a horny, horny horn.
I'm gonna force you into bed with me.
Horny with two dykes.
Horny, horny, horny horn.
I'm too spiked, to get a horny with two dykes.
Horny with two dykes.
Horny, a horny, horny horn.
Horny with two punc one P's.
Horny, oh horny, horny horn.
Horny, oh with two punk chicks.
Horny with a pregnant chick on roller skates.
Horny, oh horny, horny horn.
How do you get horny in your socks, you wonder?
Well, maybe I'll just have to demonstrate to all of you someday.
See, this one time I had an itch in my foot inside my socks,
and that's how I came up with the idea of horny in your socks.
I eat lots of horny with a chick food.
It gives me energy to get horny with a chick on.
Always be careful what you drink and how you mix your drinks,
because if you're not careful,
you'll throw up all of your horny with a chick food.
Horny with a chick food.
And then you won't have energy to get horny with a chick on.
Joe Offrecht, the great Joe Offrecht,
with his song Horny with a Chick,
thanks to the Temple of Dionysus Sabazio.
And now a song by Reload.
Actually, it's one of the guys in the punk group.
And it's a song originally by Devoe called I Need a Chick.
And it's a song that I wrote for my band.
I need a chick.
Well, I need a chick.
I need a chick to suck my dick
I need a dog to lift my hog
I need a cat to stroke my back
Well, I need a chick to suck my dick
I've been poopin' and shittin' and dyin'
I'm thirsty, ain't got no feel to plow
No hole for my pole, I fuck a pink store
I need a chick to suck my dick
I need a dog to lift my hog
I need a cat to stroke my back
Well, I need a chick to suck my dick
Gonna find her, gonna find her
Gonna get down on my knees and eat her
Cause she's the move
Yeah
Well, she's the move
I need a woman who understands
There's nothing more spiritual than dog-style love
I need a chick
I need a dog
I need a cat
Well, I need a chick to suck my dick
I need a dog to lift my hog
I need a cat to stroke my back
Well, I need a chick to suck my dick
I need a chick to suck my dick
Wow!
Well, I need a chick to suck my dick
I need a chick to suck my dick
I want that thick white hot cum on my face right after it comes out of my ass, baby.
Baby.
God knew that when he did will to create a new little soul inside the mother...
Uh-huh.
...is essential in all sex instructions.
Mmm, yum.
Get your fingers out of my...
Oh, your breast's beginning to grow.
Oh, I hug you a pat on your...
Oh, no.
So wonderfully has God designed our bodies.
Uh-huh.
Oh.
That's wonderful, isn't it, mother?
Flows out again.
Through the vagina.
Mmm, yum.
What's it worth to you?
Uh-huh.
It's a perfectly natural bodily function.
And a holy one, really, when you consider that it's part of God's wonderful plan for creating new little souls in his own image.
Oh.
This is a natural thing.
A holy thing.
Oh, baby.
God is preparing your body for the wonderful calling of motherhood.
Uh-huh.
Use the slipper on you first.
How about licking the bowl?
Uh-huh.
God planted the little seeds inside old Bess's tummy, and they grow into puppies.
Oh.
Bess has a tiny opening in her body, and it stretches open so the puppies can come through.
Oh, gee willikers.
Oh, golly.
Oh, ew.
Oh, gee willikers.
I...
Well, mothers have a little opening between their legs.
Yeah, that's right.
You mean, Mommy has a hole in her body?
Gee.
Uh, Sex Education by I.M.B.J.R.
And now, some cut-ups by his fellow Britisher, Reverend Chartot.
She's at who?
Mother.
Since this morning.
Have you seen her?
If I'm supposed to make a fuss and kiss her hairy cheek, I won't.
What do you kiss, little prince?
Where's Henry?
Upstairs with a family whore?
Not yet.
Let's hope he's grown up like his father, Simon Pure, and sex in history.
Tell me, what's Philip like?
I hear he's quite impressive for a boy of seventeen.
My lord!
And you are impressive.
I'm Eleanor, who might have been your mother.
Impressive.
Your grievances, if we have understood them, have to do with Princess Alice and her behind.
You see my problem?
Clearly.
But it's yours, not mine.
Authority.
It's got my troop ass on purple cushions.
It's all over it.
That makes it mine.
Now hear me, boy.
Suit gum.
She has some surgeons looking for a lump.
We'll state the station like two sursays.
Does your suit gum naturalization like two sursays?
I'll wash my gills and your suit gum through the holidays until I win.
Why will I?
Out of duty, dear.
Impressive sex.
You're better at this than I thought you'd be.
Stop looking in my eye!
And then it pops out.
No, but they're just gelatinous balls of jello.
What are actually, what are eyes other than mucilaginous spheres?
Modified.
They're just booger glands.
Eyes are pretty amazing things.
I'm fine with just having to accidentally have lenses on them and have them there.
There might be a guy or something.
Eyes are, I remember when I studied eyes in biology class or something.
I just remember being just completely amazed at how amazing they are.
They are really amazing.
There actually is an eye expert here.
Yes, my father was an optometrist.
Oh, I thought you said he was an eyeball.
Turn reality into like, you know, chemicals.
And then your brain does things.
Yeah, a photon dance.
How do you know it's reality?
I don't even know you're really seeing anything.
That's the truth.
What is reality?
Well, the convex part of our eye blot.
It's all a big joke.
Take the red pill or take the blue pill.
Yeah, they're both upside down.
I could show you what reality is if I had a...
A plunger?
A two by four.
I'd whack you up in the back of the head with it when you got a plunger.
I thought you were going to say a plunger.
I haven't done that.
Oh my God!
Was, was he just masturbating?
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my.
Did we, did we rub his nose in it?
I was horny up against a chick when I went to see Ozzy Osbourne.
I'm just kidding.
But I was horny up against a chick when I went to see a punk rock band called The Accused.
I, I positioned myself in a big crowd up against her, got close to where she was, positioned my leg up against hers.
She turned around and looked at me once but didn't really pay attention.
I think it was much of anything.
But then I went and told a couple guys that knew who she was.
I was horny up against her.
And it must have gotten back at her because one day when I was walking around at the mall, she gave me a funny look.
Horny with two smother me chicks.
What's a smother me chick?
They smother my dick with pussy juices.
When I fork them.
I'm a squeaky voice.
Perfect.
Dang me, dang me.
They ought to take the rope and hang me.
High from the highest.
Woman, would you wait for me?
And I was strumming the air guitar by strumming my cock as I did that.
People should fear me because...
I got a big cock.
Wait upon him.
Lead him to my bar.
Oh.
Feed him with their waxen thighs and piece of cobweb morph.
And I.
Boxer.
If it's to make an ass of me.
To fright me.
If they could.
Oh.
To swear.
I love them.
Methinks mistress.
You should have little reason for that.
These beautiful four by nineteen flags come all the way from Radio City, California or
they're made by the organizations there.
Many organizations have put in almost everything they've got about precious bodily fluids,
pieces of hair, old strings of wax, and believe me, they made the kids awfully happy tonight
with this wonderful, wonderful emission.
Look, look, look right here.
It's creamy and only one of them is melting right there.
The other one is standing so firmly.
That's the one with the flags.
These beautiful blue-white, red-white, red-white...
And look at those cheerleaders go by with those bugle-encrusted broomsticks wedged firmly up their nether regions.
The latest fad is...
Bob prophesied the broomstick up the butt is supplanted of tattooing and savage primitivism and so forth.
Aren't they adorable?
We're glad you called us for masturbation.
Thank you.
If you don't spend all of your spare time alone masturbating, it may indicate a serious problem.
The problem, however, is lack of masturbation, even though we know that masturbation is physically harmful.
Masturbation is a form of masturbation.
Masturbation is touching and handling your sex organs in a way that creates hair on your palms or makes you sterile or weak.
Some figures show that a total male population masturbates with a total female population.
Many people have sexual thoughts about all sorts of things while they're masturbating.
Whatever these fantasies are, it's important to remember that things could mess up your head.
You'll probably hear a lot of scary things about masturbation from people who know the facts.
Remember the disgust.
Especially the part about hurting your school nurse.
If you'd like to masturbate your nurse practitioner, try putting warts into the end of the penis.
This is a dirty sexual urge.
We hope the information we've given you will help you get stuck in the vagina and have to be removed through a toilet paper tube.
Thank you for your extension.
Goodbye.
Hey, did you catch the Willie Nelson picnic?
Yeah, Bill Clinton was there.
And Willie said,
Hey Bill, we'll see you later up on the roof.
Ha ha ha ha.
What does that mean?
I laughed but I didn't know what it meant.
Because the first time Willie Nelson played the White House, him and Bill Clinton were getting high on the roof.
Oh my, is that true?
Absolutely.
Oh wow.
But Bill didn't inhale, did he?
He just kind of like put it between his butt cheeks and smiled.
Bill was blowing Willie's shotguns, man. What are you talking about?
Bill was blowing Willie on the White House roof.
Santa Claus went away and never returned to the White House ever again.
Well that better know W blowing Satan in the front porch.
Yeah, I mean the oval on the lawn or whatever.
Bill came out with his blue dress and threw it at Willie and said,
Put this on, bitch.
Ha ha ha.
Ha ha ha ha.
That that was the fucking
no nun hon!
I've been specifyin' that
I'll get you,,oses!
Eurovision.
There's a poor missionary.
He saves fallen women from sins.
He'll save you a blot for five dollars.
My God, how the money rolls in.
Rolls in, rolls in.
Rolls in.
My God, how the money rolls in.
Now my grandma sells cheap prophylactics.
She punctures the head with a pen.
Cause grandpa gets rich from abortion.
My God, how the money rolls in.
Rolls in, rolls in.
Rolls in.
My God, how the money rolls in.
Now my uncle is whittling out candles
from wax that is specially soft.
He says that they'll come in real handy
if ever his business falls off.
Rolls in, rolls in.
My God, how the money rolls in.
Rolls in.
Rolls in, rolls in.
Teaching a parakeet sex instruction is fun.
But the old method took too much time and patience.
This record is specially designed to teach
any healthy normal parakeet sex instruction.
By using a scientific new method that is acknowledged to be far superior.
Because a carefully trained voice, specially chosen for excellence in clarity and diction.
Hello, baby.
Repeats over and over the same words, the same phrase, in a manner that most parakeets are most likely to imitate.
Always place your parakeet near enough so that he can plainly hear the inflection and sound of every word.
In this first recording, a little parakeet has just discovered that the neighbor's dog has given birth to a litter of puppies.
Out of this natural situation arises the first question usual in all sex instruction.
Hello, baby. Want a kiss?
New from Dobbs Cove. Tasty prairie squid spread.
Salted and unsalted varieties available on the East Coast only.
The radioactive cloud is now over Little Rock.
Crager shat piercingly.
Come on, let's go.
Poo, poo.
P-N-E. We can go.
Come on, let's go.
Poo, poo.
It's very easy, just poo, poo.
Let us go.
Poo, poo.
Artemia Salina did that and the previous.
The last time I saw her, I was in a coma.
The parakeet pussy song.
It prays Artemia.
I have no new messages.
Saved messages.
Saturday, February 3rd, 9.09.
You better fucking call me back on my cell phone.
I'm done doing this thing with you, chasing you,
until the part where you exhaust me.
Well, you have already.
What the fuck are you doing?
So you really want it to be over?
Is that what you want?
Are you gonna be a happy boy then?
And I guess so.
That's what you told me.
So I guess I should just listen to that.
Call me back, Mark.
You better call me soon,
cause I'm done chasing you.
I can't express this to you enough.
You know, sometimes,
you only do this so many times,
and then it just becomes fucking old,
doesn't it?
...
See, it's a fluid philosophy, friends,
which is lucky, you know,
I mean, you don't always want to be good.
And, uh,
we certainly don't know what the right
thing is, and we're always learning new
things about the church, like the
sex Connie.
Now, here in the
subgenius, we all know about it,
worship and fear Connie Dobbs,
the primary
wife of our primary
wife, Bob.
Uh, and, uh,
but then suddenly somebody started talking about
the sex Connie.
I've never heard of the sex Connie, I thought Connie
was sex! And now I hear there's a
a sex Connie!
This is like the, the,
the essence of sex, this is a sexy
version of the essence of sex, I guess they're
talking about.
Fade message.
Saturday, February
3rd, 9th, 15th,
6pm.
All I can say is, if you're out at a
fucking bar, when I went
to your house, drove
by you, you saw me,
and you just drove by me,
and I called you to
apologize, to tell you
how much I meant to you,
how much you meant to me,
if you're at a fucking bar right now,
I will never, ever
forgive you, ever.
Because if you could be having a good time,
then you know what, fuck you, and, you
know what, you're right, then I need
to move on.
But I hope you know what you're doing.
Because I'm not fucking
playing around anymore. You know,
what do you think, the world is gonna fucking
chase you forever, Mark?
That, you know what, everybody's
gonna fucking chase you because you're
Mr. Wonderful? Yeah.
Well you've got some flaws going on yourself,
so you know what, when I call you and apologize,
they call you a million times
to tell you how much you mean to me,
that should mean something, but obviously it doesn't,
so you fucking have a good time
out at a fucking bar, but I'll tell you what,
if you're there, don't ever fucking
call me again.
Can we play this message?
This next one is called
the Kindergarten Orgasm
Dance. In the
kindergarten I had
orgasms, back in the
kinder I had orgasms,
kindery in
the kindery,
back in the kinder I had
orgasms.
When I hear an imitation
of a chick pissing herself,
ooh my underwear,
ooh my
dress, ooh my
dress.
Back when I was in elementary
school, I really hated
it when girls wore
dresses because it would
expose their sexy
legs, and I would get so fucking
horny I couldn't concentrate
on my schoolwork, so
I made up this little chant
back then that I would always do under
my br- under my br-
They wear
They wear dresses,
stupid dresses,
why
do they wear stupid
dresses?
Sometimes I would disguise it in code form
instead of saying, when dresses
I would say, ah-ho-dees,
they wear ah-ho-dees,
stupid ah-ho-dees,
why
do they wear stupid
ah-ho-dees?
Dee-lee-lee-lee-pa-dee-le,
in the
johnnies,
you know what I mean by the johnnies?
The underwear.
Maybe I should say
about
stage door johnnies,
Dee-lee-lee-pa-dee-le,
in the
johnnies,
Dee-lee-lee-pa-dee-le,
in your
johnnies,
Dee-lee-lee-pa-dee-le,
in your underwear,
in your wear,
in your wear, in your little
underwear.
I'd love to be able
to go to a party where I can yell out,
I want to hear some
pervert music!
So what I mean by pervert music,
it doesn't have to be
overtly
pervert music, but
it does have to,
for no particular reason,
psyche up
to
wanna do sexually perverted
things to women
and or girls.
Like that song by the monkeys,
I Saw Her Face, Now I'm a Believer,
when I hear the beginning of it,
it, ah,
it psychs me up to wanna do
kinky sexual things.
You're in big trouble though, pal.
I eat pieces of shit like you for breakfast.
You eat pieces of shit
for breakfast?
No!
Sage message, Saturday,
February 3rd, 9,
29, PM.
Well, you won.
Not only have you ruined my day, but you've ruined
my night, because I'm too
upset to even think about going out to bed.
I'm gonna have fun.
Fun? I wanna be with you, and
I wanna be with someone who doesn't wanna be with me.
So, yeah, that would be a real good time out
tonight, huh?
Anyway, I know that I gotta move on,
and I'm going to, and mark my words,
if I don't hear from you shortly,
I'm moving on, because I'm not gonna play
this game tomorrow. And I know I keep
saying that, and I know I keep calling you back,
but it's fucking draining, Mark, and I'm tired
of it. And I've chased after you
once again, all fucking
day and all fucking night.
So, you know what?
Have fun with your fucking
stubbornness, and you know what?
I hope the next fucking woman that you date,
or girl, maybe I should say,
puts up with your stubbornness, because I can't
deal with it. I've given you everything.
I've said to you every
possible thing that I could say. I basically
came crawling back, even though, you know
what? It's not only my fault. It's
us. And, uh,
you know what? You continue to fucking
torture me, and, uh, I just
hope that you're really having a good time.
And I know you're probably not, so
whatever. I hope you got what
you wanted from all this, because, uh,
it's just fucking sad. So,
um, I'm moving on.
I'm going to bed, and I am
certainly moving on tomorrow morning.
Goodbye.
You're just a good man,
so,
um,
you beat me,
I swear to God.
Uh...
Um...
Oh, baby.
Why don't you follow me back to my hotel room?
They got some pretty pictures on the wall I want to show you.
Say you want another drink?
Bartender, give me another colada of milk.
That was what you wanted, wasn't it?
Huh!
Why the hell am I talking when my tape deck ain't running?
That's what I keep asking myself every night before I go to bed.
Some things in life are a bummer, baby.
But you're a beautiful thing.
Oh, baby.
What can I do for you?
What have you got there to say to that guy?
The poor service boy couldn't do that.
The company man wouldn't accept the service.
Ap concealment?
I can see it
It's back in line
Bang, bang, bang
I've got a dick made of steel
Got a plate of grass
I get all dressed
It's back in line
Bang, bang, bang
Well, I'm going to tell you
I'm a noob
I'm a soldier
I'm on a land too
And you say to me
Boy, you're cheap
Well, you don't cut me any slack
Have some brains
And you've got法
All of it
That f년
And you know me
Well you're cheap
Young and poor
Big lady steel
I've got some bad friends
I get hunger
I eat the grass
I drink some wine
With ice and spirit
I saw a dick
Made of steel
I got the brat
Now I get hungry
I eat the grass
And I eat the grass
On the override
I'm so hungry
I eat the grass
And I eat the grass
I drink the grass
The Swingin' Love Corpses once again.
And a special thanks to Einstein's Secret Orchestra, Swamp Radio, and WCSB.
Whence come the live radio clips?
Ah, yes.
You're listening to the Subgenius Radio Hour of Slack,
the XXX-rated show number six.
You can get more information from www.subgenius.com.
Or you can send material to me, Reverend Ivan Stang.
You can email me, stang at subgenius.com.
Or write, Stang, Post Office Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
44118.
Ah, yes.
Once again, that's Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
44118.
Don't be afraid.
Bob loves you.
Everything's going to be just fine, really.
Just come with me, and I'll tell you all about it.
And Bob...
Chateau Aubrillon, 1959.
Magnificent wine.
I love French wine.
In fact, I love the French language.
I have sampled every language.
French is my...
My favorite.
Fantastic language.
Especially to curse with...
Nom de Dieu, de putain de bordel, de merde, de saloperie, de connard, d'enculé de ta mère.
You see, it's...
It's like wiping your ass with silk.
I love it.
Page message.
Wednesday, February 7th, 9.34 p.m.
I'm going...
I'm going to the hospital because I...
I...
I'm going to the hospital.
You don't fucking care.
You got a fucking blue appointment.
I hope you're fucking happy.
I'm...
To replay this message, press 1.
Why do you say you feel trapped in a man's body?
Well, sometimes I get the menstrual cramps.
Real hard.
That's correct.
Don't get too proud of this technological terror you've constructed.
But the new stage at X-Day is cool.
I moved in with my 43-year-old Bible.
The tranquility-based stage is cool.
It's not a technological terror.
But by the time I had learned to feed it what it needed,
my own needs had grown to the point where I could see in its little head...
Well, that's not a little head.
A...
I could see somewhere a glimmering of intelligence.
That's not a boa constrictor, and would you please let go of it.
I'm trying to pass water through it, sir.
Oh, that reminds me of a joke about Milton Berle, who had the largest member in show business.
And Dick Shawn, you remember Dick Shawn?
Oh, and Shawn and Dick.
He said he went to the Schvitz one time.
He went into the steam room and saw Milton Berle there and he thought he was with his son.
I don't know.
Maybe he was wearing lipstick or something.
You know what they used to say about Uncle Milton?
I heard that Jim Neighbors was the best.
The best pact.
He didn't have any children of his own.
It was just kind of a clone thing.
I don't know about that old character actor Arnold Stang.
He was a rock packer, man.
Arnold Stang, too?
Is that why you took that name?
Yeah, he was the Johnny Wad of his day.
What about Rodney Dangerfield?
What's his name?
Oh, you know, he was in all those B-horror movies.
Reagan.
No.
Yeah, he did some B-horror movies.
Reagan was castrated back before 1980.
We're talking about the meat.
The meat men of the B-horror movies.
And Reagan was not known for that especially.
Well, in many ways...
He did some early porno when he was a communist.
Until next week.
And that's your man on time.
You're back to the winning of the sack and the saddle.
Take care, folks.
Well, kids.
Poor old commies out there having to do porno films for a living.
To music like this.
Happy new year.
Although we're staying alive.
It's a time like any of this.
Wait.
It's diciendo la muerte.
With Obsec downtown this way.
B- forehead standing and the right.
MIKE CH aprender all door sor.
© BF-WATCH TV 2021