What, a problem?
Oh, why would you want a problem?
No, no, no, why would you ask that?
We're not having any kind of a problem at all.
No, no, no, a few, uh,
I've had to answer a little bit of extra e-mail perhaps lately,
and, well, the mail has been stacking up,
but, you know, I mean, people want to be chatty,
they have questions they need answered,
and, of course, after you answer them,
they always want to throw in a nice little joke return.
And, uh, a problem, no, no,
you're not a, of, of,
oh, getting a radio show put together
shouldn't be any problem at all.
No, I think we'll just,
no, no, no, no, don't worry about it.
We want to hear your phone calls.
We want you to call us and tell us
what's been happening in your life.
That's not a problem.
Oh, well, uh,
we have time to listen to the tapes,
I'm sure, sooner or later.
It's not a problem.
No, no, no problems here.
We're just doing just fucking fine!
Uh, pardon my language.
Uh, mm!
Uh, uh, yeah.
We've probably just, uh,
a few little technical setbacks here and there.
A few minor little, uh, things
on the personal side,
but, uh, maybe, uh, but, uh...
Oh.
Oh, cut.
Cut.
You don't know what it means
You live
You don't follow your dreams
You feel
You don't fall to your knees
You love
But you don't love me
I'm tired of waiting for my time to come
I'm tired of playing your games
I'm tired of watching my life slip away
Take me from this lonesome town
Too bad you don't love me no more, baby
Too bad your people are rolling down
Through the dark
Ooh
doesn't matter
I'm tired of playing your game
You live
Just doing what it takes
Just when every day
Seems a great day with a smile
Sounds about to fade in
I'm doing time
Oh, yes, friends, we're back with that wacky, funny, hilarious show.
The Subgenius Hour of Slack.
This is for everybody.
Slack, yes, Slack for everyone.
We're going to share our Slack with you, friends.
Because it was under the sea.
At first for food and later for other purposes that the Old Ones first created Earth life.
These viscous masses were without doubt what Abdul Alhazred whispered about as the Shoggoths in his frightful Necronomicon.
Although even that mad Arab had not hinted that any existed on Earth except in the dreams of those
when Shoggoths were born.
They were not only the first to eat a certain alkaloidal herb.
Oh, wait, wait a minute.
Oh, that's not, oh, that's not what, that wasn't the Slack we were going to share.
We were going to share with you the kind of Slack that we've been getting lately.
Now, um, let's see, how did that go?
Uh, um, hey, Stang, Stang, did you listen to my tape yet?
How come I haven't heard it on the show?
Hey, Stang, my man.
What?
I just don't answer it.
Duh.
Uh, but I have a question.
Um, uh, Stang, you didn't spell my name correctly on the website, and that picture of Reverend
Suzy the Floozy looks all grainy on my screen.
Uh, hey, Stang, I know you're busy, but you wouldn't believe what my dog did today.
Hey, hey, Stang, I just called to tell you.
I won the lottery, man.
Bob came through.
I'm going to be buying that Bob T-shirt.
shirt real soon now. I just wanted to let you know. So, uh, like, tell me how things are going, dude.
Mr. Stank, your internet access will return. We are working on the problem.
Expect your service to improve just as soon as our Dallas move is complete.
Please. Dear, you never spend any time with the family.
Hey, Stank dude! I haven't seen you in years! I'm in town and I'll be right over!
Dad, uh, somebody backed into the car today while I was driving it.
Uh, hey, uh, Stank, you got a minute? I know you're busy, but this won't take long.
I promise, this will only take you five minutes.
Five minutes, max!
Oh, Stank, have I got a deal for you!
I have this game for a, this, this, this great game idea, and all you have to do is write the proposal.
It'll be easy. You will all get rich, man. You want to get rich, don't you?
Well, Stank, uh, uh, I guess you just don't, uh, even care about us, uh, little people anymore.
Uh, I guess you're too, uh, busy partying with, uh, Gwar and, and fromping with movie stars.
Uh, Mr. Stank, um, I'm afraid we have some bad news about your dog's nose.
It, it is cancer.
Uh, well, uh, Mr., uh, Stank, we're not accepting applications at this time, and, well, we'd rather talk to people with college degrees.
Hey, Stank, about those pictures I said I'd scan for you.
Um, I, I can't find them.
Do you have any more spare copies of those you can send me?
Hey, hey, Stank, hey, this is Bob Dean, hey, hey, hey, the Canadian False Bob, hey, hey, hey, hey, guess what, hey, hey, I got interviewed again.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey, Rev, remember me?
We met at that DeVival in Austin in 1983, and I bought that Bob button from you.
Man, I lost it. Can you look, send me another one?
Dear Church of the Subgenius, I ordered a church video from you three weeks ago, and I have yet to see any such video in my mailbox.
I am alerting the Better Business Bureau.
I spend three hours a day listening to other people's problems, Stank.
Uh, uh, Reverend Stank, you must see this television special.
I taped about UFOs.
It's somewhere down near the middle of the tape.
Tell me what you think.
Reverend Stank, I'm sure you're too high and mighty for people like me, but I sent you five 90-minute tapes of me ranting, and if you don't even have the courtesy to respond, you can forget any future support from me.
You, sir, are a fascist.
Hey, Stank, I'm sorry.
Dang, dude, you're like working too hard on slack, man.
Why don't you slack off, Teed?
Get it? Slack off?
And where's the stark fist, dude?
Well, friends, now I know how the Omega Man felt.
You ever saw that movie?
But at least, you know, he got to go out killing them during the daytime.
Well, not necessarily.
Nice working, pensar.
Okay.
I'll tell you how you were removed from your family.
Your 74-year-extra has just awareness of commentations byarios перед dumb lambs of aology.
I'm so sick, so sick of you
Your face is gross, you eat my toast, you don't know what to do
And just your luck, you really suck, that's all I'm sick of you
Sick of you
I'm so sick, so sick of you
Sick, sick of you
Bring it down
I said bring it down
Thank you
Don't you know
It's not fair
I'm so sick, so sick you
Think you're sad
Think you do
Don't you know
I'm so sick of you
Think you're sad
Think you do
and know the things you do
See don't you know
Why you're still sick of you
And all the things you said
and all the things you do
Don't you know
That I'm sick of you
And all the things you do to me
See you next week.
The heresy within the church is that I've been listening all night long to all this fine talk about slack.
And I got to tell you, there are some people here that are working too god hard so y'all can have some slack.
But those who know Sister Melodia's chops know that I'm here.
not one to complain. No, I write songs and this is all about that hard work heresy.
Amazing face that's known as Bob. You promised slack to me.
I took your red light and I put my heart in your hands.
You took my advice and quit my job. Now I'll work twice as hard for thee.
Well, it's good to see you here tonight, but I got to say it's all not right.
Behind the scenes of the things you see is a lot of hard work heresy.
Now, Bob is great and Bob is good, but he don't slack me like I should.
He should be eating bonbons and lying in bed and busting ass at the smart bar instead.
Whoa, give me that!
Where do I go tonight?
I'm going to get my slack.
Say whoa, give me fun.
Knock another ranch and rave to run.
I went to a party that was wrong.
Cause everybody wants to hear Bob's song.
They kept me playing till my fingers bled.
With nothing paid and no one said no.
Give it back.
Where do I go to get my slack?
Say whoa, give me fun.
Knock another event to run.
I worked all night at another ranch.
I wanted to sleep, but they said you can't.
You got to pack up a room or two.
And put up the tables before you're through.
Whoa, give it back.
Where do I go to get my slack?
Say no.
Give me fun.
Knock another big event to run.
Why can't Bob just pass it on?
Without an event from dusk till dawn.
Why can't slack descend on me?
Without this hard work heresy?
Whoa, give it back.
Where do I go to get my slack?
Say whoa, give me fun.
Knock another big event to run.
So all you people, don't you.
Tend to them cause we are through.
Go out and find a world to save.
We're going to enjoy the rants and raves.
Say whoa, give it back.
Where do we go to get our slack?
Say no.
Give me fun.
Knock another event to run.
Say whoa, give it back.
Where do I go to get my slack?
Say whoa, give me fun.
Knock another event to run.
Knock another big event to run.
Knock another rants and raves to run.
Give it back.
I want it now.
Up to hell with you.
Okay, she's down to hell.
She dared to question Bob Zedek.
Lucky for her it's the sub-sum.
She's the sub-genius hell.
Lucky for Sister Melodia's chops.
It's the sub-genius hell, my friends.
And by the time you get to the sub-genius hell,
you'd be wishing to God that you'd made it to.
No, wait a minute.
Take two.
By the time you get to the Christian heaven, my friends,
you'll be wishing to God you'd made it to sub-genius hell.
But the great thing about sub-genius hell is,
oh man, what a party.
You have to go through it in order to be prepared to endure
the even greater pure slack fun of sub-genius heaven.
Oh, that must be where we are now, I guess.
I had it all mixed up.
I'm sorry, folks.
Just been under a little bit of pressure lately.
Just a little bit of a steam cooker, but I'm sure we can...
give some credits.
Yeah, that's it. Credits.
Well, of course, that song just now was by Sister Melodia's chops,
the lovely Sister Melodia's chops of Cleveland,
accompanied there by the lovely Princess Wiardo.
And what else have we been playing?
Well, this material in the background,
all of the background so far has been from a band,
a Cleveland band that we don't know,
nothing nepotistic this time,
called, um...
What are they called?
Oh, Only a Mother.
Yes, Only a Mother with their album Fetal Chicken.
They're very bull-dada, don't you think, really?
And, uh...
Well, they get wacky and quirky and then they get kinda sad like this.
But it's gonna be okay, man.
It's not a problem.
Um...
Uh, what we've heard...
Some of the Jimi Hendrix samples are from a group called...
Pardon me.
Beautiful People.
Uh, very technically adept at tape splicing and sampling there.
Well, now it's Sergio Leone.
Pretty soon they'll get to Nina Rota.
Um...
Eh...
Before that...
Oh, of course, um...
Sick of You.
That song by Gwar.
The gods from...
The elder gods, you might say, from beyond space.
Uh...
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da.
And a little media barrage there from sister...
Uh, Suzy the Floozy.
The...
Oh, Suzy.
Uh, Suzy did a show on her show in Atlanta,
on WREK.
A pain show.
And it has come in very handy, uh, to us here, because, uh, to tell the truth, it's...
Gah!
Get your hold on it, get your hold on it
Mind it, mind it, get your hold on it
You work
You don't know what it means
You live
You don't follow your dreams
You feel
You don't fall to your knees
You love
But you don't love me
I'm tired of waiting for my time to call
I'm tired of playing those games
I'm tired of watching my life slip away
Slip away
Oh, slip away
When my ship rolls in
I'll be face down in the sand
Burning in the sun
On this distant island shore
When my ship rolls in
The captain will come to save me
I'll gaze about his visage
And see whose face is mine
When my spaceship lands
I'll be kissed by a silver angel
Who will drag me all aboard
While the trappers bite my flesh
They'll take me to the moon
A beat of white light
I'll be to banish his fear
And see his face is mine
When I'm stranded
I'm crying for help
Everyone ignored me
They stood around in line
When my ship rolls in
To my aching isolation
I'll gaze above the captain
And see his face is mine
Freedom, freedom
I'll be free from the mask
Of the world
Feminism is a nation of your society
Freedom, freedom
Don't leave me
Feminism is a nation of your society
When my spaceship lands
I'll be kissed by a silver angel
Who will drag me all aboard
While the trappers bite my flesh
And see his face is mine
When I'm stranded
I'm crying for help
Everyone ignored me
They stood around in line
When my spaceship rolls in
To my aching isolation
I'll gaze above the captain
And see his face is mine
When my spaceship rolls in
To my aching isolation
I'll gaze above the captain
And see his face is mine
Freedom, freedom
Don't ignore me
Lau-lu-lalau la-la-la
We charge and burn
O motion in time
Whose ship is this
Our Зап 1200
guitar solo
Yes, yes, yes dear friends, the great,
the great Zug's Riff
with his song
When My Ship Rolls In.
I'd give you Zug's address
except that it got to him.
He quit, he quit the music business.
He even quit the wrestling business.
He quit the music business.
Yes, because it,
he got fed up.
He just got fed up with
the struggle.
And here's an important credit, friends.
That song
Tired of Waiting,
which I have interspersed throughout this whole show,
is by Mary McGuire
and her band Cosmic Dolly
and I'm going to give you their address
because you should send off
their CD or write them for information.
Cosmic Dolly at P.O. Box
Got that pencil ready?
P.O. Box
Royal Oak
Michigan
That's M.I.
I saw her perform
at the Underground Film Festival
in Chicago and
it was lots of fun.
And you know, friends,
it is a struggle.
One must keep
must keep hacking
and hacking and moving
in constant motion
straight ahead.
Until the tape runs out.
Because the tape
will run out, dear friends,
just as it did for Dr. Legume.
And we'll get to that
pretty soon.
I guess on side two of show.
Although first,
I think there's some other things
that we're going to stick on
this pain theme.
I just love this.
Why it's almost as good as the hate.
In fact, we may not even get to Dr. Legume
this show.
It may just all be pain
and hate.
And we might not even get to death
until the tape runs out.
Yes.
Sweet Susie.
She'll beat you
to death.
Sweet Susie.
From Ross Meyer,
the director who gave you
Vixen and Beyond the Valley of the Dolls.
For a taste of evil?
Sweet Susie.
A woman.
A woman too much for one man.
Sweet Susie.
The diary of a wicked lady.
The memoirs of a bad girl.
Sweet Susie.
No man escaped her island.
Or her whip.
Sweet Susie.
Slamming, crashing,
banging action from opening scene
to mind bending climax.
Sweet Susie.
She ain't no lady.
Whoa, yeah.
He knows what he's talking about.
Welcome, welcome
seekers of slack.
Welcome to WREK
Atlanta. Bob's
slack time funhouse.
Oh, I'm the right raving reverend
Susie the floozy, your genial
hostess. But let me
warn you, dear listeners.
The theme of my show
tonight isn't a pleasant one.
Last night, I had a close
encounter with Ross Meyer
and a 20 foot tall
Turris satana. And it
got me thinking about the nature of something
near and dear to my heart.
The only thing that cuts through my teflon
coating anymore. The only thing that
makes me sit bolt upright and take
notice. Pain!
Oh.
I don't mean the sharp twinges you get
when you slam your thumb in the car door
or stub your toe. I'm not bothering
with that penny ante piddling
ooh, I hurt myself crap here.
Oh no, I'm talking
about the brain twisting agony of
everyday existence. From that
first conscious breath you take in the morning
when you realize, no!
Damn it, I didn't die in my
sleep again!
Oh, until you eventually pass
out hours later from the excruciating
pressure and torment.
They call this going to
sleep. With me, it's like an
overloading agony circuit reaching
critical mass and then massive
systems shut down.
But maybe you're
different. Maybe you
think that there's a minimum of pain
in your life. Well,
think again, bucko! It's
there. And I'm gonna have to put you in touch
with it if you're going to achieve
Bobhead. And take it from me,
Bobhead is worth it.
So welcome to the house of
pain cakes. And
please feel free to scream.
It's music to
my ears.
.
Your problems, they will soon be gone
We soak up, soak up, soak up lots of pain, yeah
If life is a reflecting pool
Then we are like a sponge, yeah
It's all been dug up with the bad
We soak up, soak it up
So give me all your troubles
And baggage you can't handle, no
You gladly take it off your back
We soak up, soak up, soak up lots of pain, yeah
It's all been dug up with the bad
Everybody locks the doors
Strangers
Never mind, it's all been dug up
We soak up, soak up, soak up lots of pain, yeah
We soak up, soak up lots of pain, yeah
A poison girl
In a line
Come and get your big reward
It's not too late, just in time
Just put your hand on mine, your mind, your mind
Everybody has gone to bed
Get up late and watch TV
And soak up, soak up, soak up lots of pain, yeah
And take your big reward
Get up late and watch TV
There's no junior on the bus
There's no book by your side, yeah
Soak up, soak up lots of pain, yeah
You call the ever-missing bus
We soak up so much soda
We travel far, both monkey and me
By airplane, boat and train, yeah
Get up late and watch TV
We're here to eat up all your sins
I'm soaked up, soaked up, soaked up all your pain, yeah
Is it anyone's in now?
Everybody goes insane
Everybody locks the doors to keep out any stranger
Everybody's all fed up
Everybody's got your fuse
Getting ready to blow up, we're living so much danger
Boys and girls in a line
Come and get your big reward
You're not too late, just in time
Put your hands on mine, on mine, on mine
Boys and girls of every creed, yeah
Religion and persuasion, no
It's time to get up off your knees
Soak up
Soak it up
Open the door and let me in
Don't question who I am, no
Just shake my hand and give me your name
We soak up
Soak it up
Soak up
Now
, let's go
Soak it up
Soak up
I saw her walking by, and I sort of winked my eye, and she stopped dead.
Redhead, she had a cute way of walking. I had to get her talking. My heart bled.
I said, my knees are getting weak. Smile at me, speak, she said.
We'll return to The Painful Threshold after this message.
So the severity of the anal rectal pain or burning
is sometimes a clue to the diagnosis.
They may have difficulty voiding,
and they may have pain in the buttocks
and paresthesias in the buttock areas
and also paresthesias in the upper posterior thighs.
This is thought to be related to the virus infecting the sacral ganglia.
Oh!
Betty!
What's the matter, Coco?
My cooch!
Oh!
Ow!
Ha!
Your eyes cast a spell that bewitches
The last time I needed twenty stitches
To sew up the gash
You made one of my eyes
with your lash
As we dance
To the masochism tango
Bash in my brain
And make me scream with pain
Then kick me once again
And say we'll never part
I know too well
I'm underneath your spell
So darling, if you smell
Something burning, it's my heart
Excuse me.
Although they may be hitting the pain,
it's not affecting them through fear
as much as it would otherwise
because fear and pain
sort of act on one another.
In a way that the fear, plus the pain,
actually enhances the pain.
Mary never cries.
Smack her, pinch her, hurt her.
Not one tear will you get.
Ever.
Mary also never laughs.
I dare you to make her do either one.
In the midst of Gabbatha
was a huge stone, uh, a post.
They would bring a man to that post.
They would take his hands
and wrap him around the post
and pull him as tight as they possibly could
to stretch the skin very tight across the bank.
They would turn and take the length
and pull them around this huge stone
and tie that person down,
spitting their clothes.
On each side of that stone
was a basin filled with salt water.
In that salt water was a number of skirts.
Now, these skirts was a short-handled leather skirt.
They had nine strands that came down from the hands.
Each of the strands, I'm told, were tied in knots.
Little bits of bone were tied in each of the knots
in the strands that came down from that skirt
that was huge.
Oh, yes.
Oh, real pain to my sham friends
and sham pain to my foe.
Hell, real pain for everyone all around.
Oh.
Yeah, see, the Church of the Subgenius
isn't the only religion that wallows in a pain theme.
Look at the supposedly benign Christian cults
like the Baptists and the Catholics.
But this is a season that all Christians indulge
in lip-smacking Easter-time necro-porn.
Boy, they pack the pews like rubberneckers
at a multi-car fatality this time of year
because everybody likes to see somebody else get hurt.
Oh, how they relish pouring over the gory details,
thinking that somehow because somebody got staple gun
to a tree a couple millennia ago, they're off the hook.
Hey, I'd rather duel a masochist than Methodist any day.
Oh, those religious snuff perverts sicken me.
I'd rather cast my lot in with a cult
where there's some certainty that when you buy your salvation,
it stays bought.
Barring, of course, any clerical oversight.
But grab a pencil, seekers,
because I'm going to give you some advice here.
You can buy salvation
by saying,
sending a stamped, self-addressed envelope to Bob
at P.O. Box 140306,
Dallas, Texas 75214.
And get all the pain you've got coming
because with Bob, that pain you suffer daily
is a beautiful thing.
Bob's going to see to it that you not only feel the pain,
it becomes as a narcotic.
You actually jones for it if the torture...
ever stops.
Yes, you can use your pain like a magic strength tonic
to pump yourself up and spit the caustic fire
of your psychic agony out through your third nostril
enveloping this slackless world
in a sheet of Bob's scent flames.
Yes, the pain will keep your coat glossy.
But have you had enough pain yet?
I don't think so.
I'm alone
and I will always love you.
I will always love you.
Oh, even I'm not...
Let me show you something.
You will feel absolutely no pain at all.
How do you feel?
Fine, thank you.
Well, thank you, young lady.
We'll get back to removing the needles in just a few moments.
I wonder...
You don't care to hurt a person.
I am very sensitive to pain.
Okay.
Stand together.
Good.
I'm arrive.
Twoありがとうございました,
great to see you then.
I just have to start my experience.
I'll be on my way then.
Bye administrator.
Ok, there's still 1 day left.
Janice, goodbye.
I'm doing fine.
You're killing me.
Put me in the grave.
Try to set me aside.
Only be the grave.
You want to plunge a knife into my back and twist it.
Twist it round and round.
You want to plunge the knife into my back and twist it.
You're killing me.
Turn me inside out.
You think you don't see what we're all about.
I'm a phone on your side.
I'm a pain in your ass.
You want to see me die?
You want to see me pass?
You want to punch the knife into my back and twist it.
Twist it round and round.
You're killing me.
Put the sleep on good.
You want to die?
We can do you would.
You're killing me.
Put me in the grave.
Try to set me aside.
Only be the grave.
You want to punch the knife into my back and twist it.
Twist it round and round.
You're killing me.
Turn me inside out.
You think you don't see
what we're all about.
I'm a phone on your side
I'm a pain in your ass.
You want to see me die?
You want to see me pass?
You want to punch the knife into my back and twist it.
Twist it round and round.
You're killing me!
Alright. Get down.
Oh.
So this is how the world works.
Vibrations getting nasty.
Overload.
Trading on disaster.
Vibrations getting nasty. Overload. Trading on disaster.
Pain is no problem.
Pain is art.
Love is pain.
Why do you eat people?
Not people.
Brains.
Brains only?
Yeah.
Why?
The pain.
What about the pain?
The pain of being dead.
It hurts to be dead.
I thought I'd gone to the limits.
I hadn't.
The Cenobites gave me an experience beyond the limits.
Pain and pleasure.
Indivisible.
What does it mean if you don't beat anybody?
But I do. I beat their time.
Is that how you got cutie pie over there?
By beating some guy's time?
No.
You're not the type.
You're the all-American boy.
A safety first Clyde.
Are you trying to say something?
I never try anything.
I just do it.
Like I don't beat clocks.
Just people.
Want to try me?
Oh.
Oh, so you want more punishment, do you?
I just never seem to push you far enough.
Oh, yeah.
Sometimes my best efforts just don't seem to take.
You've sickened me with your hopeful, craven looks as you grovel on your hands and feet
for more.
Feel the lash and learn to kiss the whip.
And you Marietta kids had better get one of those.
You'll be hurting plenty tomorrow, so why don't you do it now and get it over with?
Screw you, Seekers.
I'm the one who really needs the pain.
If I had any nerve endings left, I'd be scourging myself.
This show is a curse, but it's not nearly the source of enough agony for me.
Sometimes this ministry grates on my last nerve like electrified tin foil on fillings.
And that rage somehow inspires me to fling myself into the fight to get you the slack
you need, to beat that slack into you, to tenderize you with Bob and Connie's special
blend of herbs and spices.
And then to grill you lightly until you're tender and ready to eat.
But sometimes you have to make your own slack.
You have to feel so much pain that it pushes you clear through the couch, through the space
of your life.
It springs like a sieve, catching all that clotted crap that's been backing up in your
system for so long.
And then you pop out on the other side, all wet and glistening.
Oh, and most of your hide stripped off your body, your flesh hanging in ribbons, and you
feel so good.
Yeah, that's what you need right there.
A good sucker punch from the stark fist of removal to knock you back through the rott
ed fabric of space and time.
Knocking that crud off you, blowing that carbon out of your pipes.
Oh, thank you, Bob.
Thank you.
You're there for me.
You've always been there.
You're there grinning with that pipe still clenched in your teeth and that smile is just
for me.
Oh, hurt me, Bob.
Make me feel something.
Make me feel it all.
And oh, see to it that the torture never stops.
Oh, man.
Oh, my gosh.
Hello friends and welcome.
The sermon tonight is entitled Life's Little Compromises.
Because, let's face it, life is full of little compromises.
So many of them, in fact, that we are often not aware when we're making them.
But hey, you gotta bend a little to get along.
You can't always get everything you want just the way you want it, right?
Well, allow me to respond to that common misconception with one word.
Corrupt.
You've heard about corrupt.
It means lacking in moral integrity.
To taint, infect, or spoil.
To change the original form or intent.
In other words, to compromise.
Now, most of us don't like the word corrupt.
It sounds too dirty, too sleazy.
We'd rather view ourselves as compromising.
That sounds so much more respectable.
But is there really any difference?
My friends?
Let me tell you a little story.
It's a story about a fine Christian widow going through some hard times.
She was still beautiful, but her husband had jumped out the window after a stock market crash,
leaving her family and herself without much money.
They had lived a very lavish lifestyle before, but now they were struggling.
Her only daughter was sick, and both her parents were old and feeble.
Still, she was a very proud woman, because she still had her integrity.
Until one day, when a wealthy old man came by and visited her.
He asked the old woman if she would sleep with him.
Of course, she flatly refused.
She was angry at the suggestion, but then he offered to marry her, restore the family fortune,
take care of her daughter, and provide for her parents in their old age.
At this point, she knew the man was a lecher, but marriage seemed a fair compromise.
So she agreed.
The man then offered her another compromise.
Why not skip the marriage altogether and just have sex for a hundred bucks?
She exploded in anger.
What did he think she was, some kind of whore?
Why, yes, the man replied.
We just established that fact.
Now we're negotiating price.
You see,
the old man was right.
The woman was always corrupt.
She was just living in denial.
She wasn't a bad woman.
She had many good qualities, but she had one fatal flaw.
She was willing to compromise for principles.
Now how many of us are in that same situation?
I don't mean widowed with a sick kid or older parents.
I mean willing to compromise for principles.
I mean willing to compromise our principles in order to get ahead.
After all, when the reward is big enough, it's not easy to resist giving in just once.
The problem, of course, is that it never is just once.
It's only the beginning of a long line of compromise.
It's always that first little compromise that's the hardest one to make.
But from there on out, it gets easier and easier.
My friends, even religion is not immune to this temptation.
Have you ever heard of a seeker church?
A seeker church is a non-denominational church designed by compromise.
Every principle that might offend or scare newcomers off is compromised away.
There is no loud, angry sermons.
There's no insistence on tithing.
There's no talk about the horrors of sin.
There's no hell.
Only the peace of heaven.
In fact, there's no controversy at all.
Just touchy-feely stuff to make you feel good so you'll come again next week.
These so-called seeker churches are the fastest growing churches in America today.
Many of them are mega churches built to literally hold thousands of customers.
I won't call them believers because they don't have anything to believe in.
Nothing they're not willing to compromise.
Because their church isn't built on a rock.
It's built on the shifting sands of compromise.
Alas, it's not just the seeker churches that are built on these changing foundations, my friends.
Religions from across the globe are compromising away their most fundamental beliefs,
their most fundamental principles, their most fundamental truths.
Oh, sure, it starts out small.
Some Jew eats pork.
Then some Catholic has an abortion.
The next thing you know, the Episcopalians perform homosexual marriages,
and the Hindus forbid women from climbing on their husbands' funeral fires.
I mean, really, what's the point of even having a religion if you're not going to play by the rules?
Do you think God is a God?
Is it going to know when you're cheating on Him?
Do you think God is going to turn a blind, omnipotent eye on your betrayal?
No, sir. No, sir.
He knows.
And if you betray God, why shouldn't God betray you?
Oh, it's your choice, all right.
Don't get me wrong there.
You can choose.
But stop a moment to consider this.
Who is going to suffer more?
In the long run?
God or you?
We've considered, and that's why we, the Church of the Subgenius,
are dedicated to not compromising.
That's why we, Bob's chosen few, refuse to give in to outside pressures to become more mainstream.
If you want mainstream, you can go to any one of those other milk-toast churches that litter the landscape
and refuse to pay taxes.
But don't come whining to us with your,
Gee, Bob, can you tone it down just a little bit attitude?
Because we're not interested in winning the Nielsen ratings.
We don't care if you're disgusted by Jane or launching decapitated heads from the stage with a nine iron.
We don't care if you're nauseated by the hardcore anti-Muzak of the swinging love corpses.
And we damn sure don't care if you're offended by my hate rats.
In other words,
we don't care about you at all.
Because this church isn't about you.
In fact, our church is probably the only product of the me generation that is not about you.
It's about Bob.
And if you don't like it, you can just go to hell.
Because that's where Bob sends those who compromise his church.
Hearing the word of Bob.
Unchanging, unamended, and uncompromised.
Praise Bob!
Amen.
Ah, yes dear friends, Father Joe Mama, the great Father Joe Mama, closing out the show.
And of course, dear friends, if you need more information about the Church of the Subgenius,
please write for free information from this address I'm about to give.
Got that pencil ready? That's Bob at Post Office Box.
Box 140306.
That's Box 140306.
140306.
Dallas, Texas 75214.
Oh, yes.
Yes, it's so purging.
So purging to do a show.
Us Fl bacterial tolls of about to make it from not flavourable to verifiable.