The gun is good.
The penis is evil.
The penis shoots seeds.
Jesus Christ, no, it's still coming.
It hasn't even been touched.
It's shooting lightning bolts from its eyes.
The flames are being blown from the sky one by one.
He can't make them shut up.
He'll never make them shut up.
Somebody gag the cowboy.
All right, here we go.
Five, four, three, two, one.
And now it's that time you've been waiting for, kids.
You're a hero.
That's right.
The awesome cowboy man just rode in on his automatic horse bucket.
Howdy, kids.
I had a terrible ride here tonight.
I was threatened and accosted by three young bullies,
one of whom had a rancid, arid eye that kept on staring downwards while he beat me for my boots.
After being stabbed and knifed several times about the head and buttocks area,
I began to scream and chased a 13RTA bus all the way down Chester Avenue.
I was so scared.
Once I got to the dumpster next to Mary Lou's, I had visions of her in my head.
Oh, Mary Lou.
I had visions of ski patrol and visions of French bunny girls wearing little parkas
and little teeny, teeny, teeny tiny critters you couldn't even call clothing.
Smart guy.
And it kept me going as the oil was slicking up around my feet
and the fires were raging, making the air on my ears.
The oil was slicking up around my ears.
All I could do was think of...
The Song of Jesus.
So you, uh, go to prostitutes, huh?
Uh, yes, dear friends.
This Hour of Slack number 927
is a rerun of Hour of Slack number 776
from our 77th.
Season.
Seriously.
Sexy is the title of this old show.
Hit me.
Stop it.
No.
Do it.
Stop it.
Hit me.
And I still can see blue velvet through my tears.
There it is.
You like it when I talk that way?
Mm-hmm.
Honey.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey.
Thousands of bottles of blue beer on the wall.
The kind of beer that'll make you a man today.
The kind of man that can fly our planes.
And knock out the Yaks and the Dingoes, too.
And the rest of the people trying to bring this country down on its knees where it truly belongs.
So stand up for America today if you can at all.
Are you a bad boy?
Are you a bad boy, Dave?
You mean it.
I was.
Do you want to do bad things?
You want to do bad things?
Are you a bad boy?
I took the toilet bowl brush.
What do you mean?
And answered it to where the sun would refuse to shine.
And I'm beginning to sing.
Do you want to do bad things, Dave?
Singing.
Stop.
I'm getting so excited.
You know, every time you get him sexually excited, his nuts go up inside him and he
gets that female voice.
Well, more like a little boy.
Yeah.
He's like little Dave.
He gets scared.
That's why he's so lonesome.
Haven't you ever heard the gelding sound, Stang?
That's different.
That's when a yearling is frightened by larger males of his own type or kind.
We call that the forgot-to-debeat-the-prairie-squid voice.
But a squid proboscis is more than just a proboscis.
It's a hiding place for a metaphor.
A metaphor for the pleasures of the universe.
Tuck it inside out and it works both ways.
Yes, Dr. Wang.
Take out the green scalp of nature.
Now that's a good idea.
So I heard, I'm going to take my clothes off.
I'm going to take my pants off.
I'm going to do this show with no pants on.
No pants on.
Friends, last night I was showing, somebody told me they found my gold plastic subgenius
minister's card at a party I'd been at last week.
And I was going through my wallet and going, oh yeah, it's gone.
I guess so.
And I found my universal life church preachers.
How many here are members of the universal life church?
Look at that.
I knew it.
Praise Bishop Hensley.
He was the man who decided that he didn't want to help subsidize religions he might
not believe in since religions didn't have to pay taxes.
So he started ordaining everyone he knew, much like the discordians do, ordaining popes
right and left.
So you're all ministers now.
You don't have to pay taxes.
But as I was going through that wallet, I also came upon my oldest original subgenius
membership card.
The person looking over my shoulder went, oh, they saw the universal life church card
and said, oh, I want one of those.
I said, oh, I'll send a self-addressed stamped envelope to Modesto, California.
But then she saw the subgenius membership card and said, oh, I don't want one of those.
Now, I woke up this morning thinking about that.
And I thought, okay, we know what she doesn't want.
What does this say she does want?
Friends!
When you say you don't want a subgenius membership card, you don't want to be a subgenius
minister doling out the slack of bobs.
What it says you do want is that you do want to take yourself seriously.
And friends, as a subgenius, I do not take myself seriously.
I don't take you seriously.
I don't take her seriously.
I don't even take that man J.R. Bob Dobbs seriously.
Seriously.
I take seriously is the one serious law that the Church of the subgenius has that Bob passed down and that one rule is
Fuck them if they can't take a joke. I see somebody's been reading their prescriptures here. I
Don't even take the news what you people call the news. I don't I take that least seriously of all
So you think you're in America?
Do you last time I checked well you're not you're in high school now take that thing and bury it where it belongs
Look at this thing
It wasn't even human. Do you think it's healthy for a 13 year old boy to imagine his teacher naked?
Absolutely mommy when do I get bread?
This is strange, but there are four people in the hospital who nearly suffocated in here
There has to be a reason for this. What do you think I'll run tests on all the main electrical circuits
I might find something there
You
Grew wearing black underwear
Did you go in there and write that on the mirror while I was taking a shower?
Yes, well enough is enough young man. Do I make myself clear like a plague or something?
people disappearing right and left old ladies
little girls young women
School boys. I don't call it a mendacity
I call it anti-slack. This is Ivan stanks version watch this. He started crying right here
It's running
for
I
am
Is he laughing there?
I
You
This
Herren
You
I
C Zukunft
Of
The
Millennium
Other
As
I
Touch
Close
I tryo
I footprints
I'm kind of pissed off that that ever came through.
Well, that's the thing.
Dr. Drummond, have you not heeded Bob's new word, build your own ship?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Bob's new word?
Is that like Bible with a little N?
Ain't quite the same as getting that eternity on the escape vessels.
Hey, you know, I'm a flexible guy.
You know, he changes the rules.
I can change.
I can move.
I can understand it.
You know, I understand the way that the upper management operates.
That's right.
After years of being in middle management in this cult,
I understand that, you know, upper management changes their mind at a whim,
and the whole strategic direction can change.
You know, it doesn't matter if 20 years you've been predicting that the Earth was going to end on 1998.
If Connie has a headache.
You know, yeah, if Connie has a headache,
four-fifths of the dogma suddenly goes away.
You know?
That's when I don't get it.
These bimbo...
Bimbos come in here.
They start changing the rules.
And, you know, Connie's the queen of them.
I'll say it right out loud in front of Bob and everybody.
She's the queen of the bimbos.
Oh, well, hey, is that...
So that's news?
So that's not news.
All right, all right.
I understand.
But I mean that in a...
The minute Bob was killed.
But I mean it in a malicious way.
I don't mean it in a loving way like most people do.
The minute Mr. Liberate the Women there shot Bob dead.
Yeah.
Yeah, I bet he's gay.
He's gay.
He's not gay.
I know he's not gay.
What's that?
He rue the day you shot Bob
because that was when them bitches took over.
I rule the day.
If you left Bob hanging and swinging,
why, it'd be as if Confucius had never come along.
Dr. Stang, have they upped your prescription of Halcyon?
Is that what's going on here?
No, no.
I started this diatribe into the bowels.
The bowels of the things that are wrong with the church.
The philosophy itself is like it's just...
So are you talking about church point two?
I didn't really mean to cast any dispersion on any of our previous dogmatic points
because they are still all valid, all still true.
As true as truth is, you know.
But perhaps I wandered too far into my own...
Oh, give me a break, Dr. Drummond.
You were the one that made it a...
Wanted it to be a men's club.
I still think it should be a men's club.
If only it had remained the way...
If only it had been the father church that I had promised to be.
It was a polygamous kingdom at one time.
The purity, the purity was there.
And now I feel like a stud on a stud farm with all those women I have to manage.
I don't know.
Retrovision?
What?
Yeah.
The savage revenge of Helen Keller in retrovision?
That is a real actual tract written by Dr. Mars, I believe.
It's a visionary piece.
It also involves performance and it is quite visionary
except for the fact that they duct tape your eyes shut.
And you're supposed to experience through your nasal cortex most of the experiences.
You express that so well.
The long knitting needles, believe me...
Express yourself.
It's a kind of a clean feeling you get, you know, like you've all been...
Clean yourself.
Clean.
Fresh.
Clean it out.
Wipe yourself.
Find refreshment where you...
Ream yourself.
You peppermint douche.
Begin.
In a clean...
Bust.
A brand new body.
Lighten up.
Man hole.
Yourself.
Grab a rock.
Now it's your several dollars.
It's for you.
It must be done by...
Stallions.
Bowie knife.
Brass cannonball.
Then a brick shithouse.
There he is.
And you just put this right on his head.
Oh my god.
I've never seen anything like that before.
He's got a head condom.
It's really fun.
Dave has just put a condom over his complete head.
He's ready to go.
He's ready to dive right in.
I can't breathe.
Oh my god.
That's obscene.
He's getting into it now.
Ladies and gentlemen, you should see what's going on in the studio.
I've never seen performance art quite like that.
Eat your heart out, Howard Stern.
Ow.
It's clean.
Calm, calm, calm.
Subjective.
Subgenius.com.
And it's a calm moment, friends.
A briefly calm moment.
Because...
Well, I was putting together last week's show and I suddenly realized that with the Amsterdam Subgenius field trip coming up,
I'm going to have to somehow crank out three shows in advance.
Because I ain't going to be around to do them damn shows.
Now, I could run some old reruns and things.
But...
But we don't have to do that yet, friends, because there's been so much going on.
There was a...
I have this wonderful recording of a KPFA Berkeley more than an hour, less than a show show.
The original The Show, by the way.
With a special guest, Dr. Philodrumon.
And host, Puzzling Evidence.
And caller, Phineas Narco.
I've got tons of recordings.
Recordings from Winterstar Symposium.
Sponsored by Ace, here in Cleveland.
You're hearing some of the recordings from that in the background.
Einstein's Secret Orchestra and Ron Slade.
But I preached there.
And maybe I can...
Maybe by...
At some point I can find some tapes of Robert Anton Wilson, who also preached there and was really funny.
Friends, of course, we always have tons of ESO Swamp Radio.
Originally broadcast live on WCSB in Cleveland on Thursday nights at 11 to 1 in the Eastern Time in the evenings.
And you can call that station at WCSB.org.
And call in. Hell, why not?
And friends, I've got this incredible recording of Booger 9000.
The legendary subgenius band, the super group, composed of Sphinx Drummond from the Swinging Love Corpses.
And...
President William Howard Taft from Homicidal Briefcase.
And yes, Joe Newman from the Rudy Schwartz Project.
An incredible recording from an Austin revival in the 90s captured by our friend Potter Nostril.
And friends, as always, every hour of Slack recently has been partly programmed by the artists of alt.binaries.slack.
Where...
Along with artwork, lately the Sabinis have been posting sounds.
And...
So we have all these little clips and bits and mixes from...
New Monet, Artemia Salina, Dr. Phineas Narco, Puzzling Primates for Bob, Jupiter Research, and Mr. Sister.
And friends, we got the Bran Flakes new album is in here.
We've got old Meteor Barrage stuff in here.
And we've got a little bit of the original
I've got the DeVival recordings coming in, better ones than I've had.
From Tucson DeVival.
And of course the sample, the Tampa C-Vival samples did have not hardly been touched.
Oh yes, friends.
And finally we, I may end up having to, you know, as I said, I have to do three shows in a week to get a catch up ahead.
And finally the final show, number 778, might be nothing but outtakes.
And I'm going to show you the final show, and you're going to have to watch the final show.
You know, my last show, I didn't have any of the other shows that we did with no explanations at all.
I don't know.
Because we've got to move in a hurry friends.
We've got to move fast.
Because this is the church of the subgenius.
And we know because of the word Bob that the end times are so, so very nigh.
The time is ripe for their arisal.
And X, X, X, X day is coming friends.
4X day.
We'll see you there at that campground, Brushwood.
In a couple weeks.
in Sherman, New York, come July 5th, 2001,
when the aliens shall meet with those who are worthy
and have achieved their ministershiphood in the church of the subgenius
under the slack master Bob.
Oh, yes, praise Bob.
We didn't want to play this gig,
but when Jesus told us we had to, we couldn't say no to that.
Do you want to hear some Schoenberg or some Neil Diamond?
Okay, I think it's pretty clear.
Everybody here would like a Neil Diamond.
Thanks, mate.
Thanks for coming.
You too.
You and you.
Racklin' Rosie, get on board.
We're going to ride till there ain't no more to go.
Taking it slow.
Lord, don't you know.
A happy time with a poor man's lady
Hitchin' on a twilight train
Ain't nothin' here that I'd care to take along
Maybe a song
To sing when I want
No need to say please to no man for a happy tune
Oh, I love my Rosie child
You and me, we're going in style
Racklin' Rosie, just an odd woman
But you make me sing like a guitar strummin'
Hang on to me, girl
The song keeps runnin'
Ah
Playin' now
My baby
Racklin' Rosie, make me smile
Girl, if it lasts for an hour
Well, that's alright
Ah
We got all night to set the world right.
Hang on to me and then fuck my asshole babe.
Oh, I love my rosy child.
She got the way to make me happy.
You and me, we're going in style.
Crackling rosy, the store-bought woman.
You make me sing like a guitar strumming.
Hang on to me, girl, the song keeps running.
Ah!
guitar solo
Alright, but I need something to play.
Yaw, yaw, yaw.
Lords of Acid is just...
about nothing but that kind of Richard and Kitty Cat.
Well, how about a pronuncement of earth-squagging impertinence?
Somebody told me that people have group sex
at Lords of Acid concerts.
I said, now, I've been to a 5X Days
and a Thrill Kill concert,
and I've seen them all just about,
but this young lady that was explaining this to me said,
well, I had my first three-way at a Lords of Acid concert.
Well, everybody had a three-way there,
but they're talking about long-sliking dogs.
They're talking about three-way hits.
No, I think they were talking about
three-way sexual activities with a prairie squid.
A man on one end, a woman on the other,
and a squid in the middle.
You better believe it, baby.
And sometimes you can get another guy or girl in there,
depending.
Depending on how, if it's a large enough
and willing enough squid.
Depending on how big the ink sac is on the squid.
That's right.
You can always use the ink sac once it's been de-inked.
Can you put them together like a little pioneer toy
when you were 75 years old?
We've got those de-inking suction cup pad machines
at Subgenius Foundation.
Huh?
Or, I mean, just if you had three squid.
Not three squids.
I'm, of course, an erudite person.
Three squid, could you just snap them together like blocks?
Yeah.
And they would serve the same purpose
of perhaps 100 just clear?
Army, the South American army squid will do that.
They will actually form bridges of their own bodies
across rivers so that their horny squid mates
can get across, you know, at the cost of thousands of lives,
yet thousands more will live.
That's the reason for the psychic experiments.
Look here.
The army squid are not only growing in size
through conjugating and multiplying,
but they have one mind.
One mind.
One hurt, one mind.
Much like you, Dr.
If you cut off the head,
it just grows another one.
One mind.
If you pull a beak, another beak tears.
If you shave an eyebrow, another thing laughs at you
and cries at you.
If you pull out its fangs, it grows twice as many.
If you pull its ears,
it wants you to rub its back.
If you pull its belly,
if you give it milk, it will suck your blood.
All these things and more can be yours
at Squid Town, Prairie Town, USA.
My, miles and miles of furrowed dirt
and squid flipping and undulating in each and every patch.
I thought I'd died and gone to heaven.
Yeah, rose, pond rose.
I never believed there could be such a squid
on a dead farm.
Ah, five.
Squids, as far as I can see.
They're sloppin' and sloppin'.
I think they're ready to be picked.
I got my Viagra.
I'm all greased up and ready to go.
Look, look, I got one of them fake beauty marks on my,
no, sorry, it's a melanoma, but look,
I got a tear in this tight, tight, tight pants.
I got a tight squid here.
Yeah.
I'm retired.
Little bit of that sorrel sausage sorcery there, eh?
That's right.
I'm not even talking about shaving it real thin.
I like to get down in them furrows and just plow,
you know what I mean?
Just plow my way.
Use one squid as a condom for use of another squid.
Yep.
And then a bigger, and then use a bigger one atop them.
We were the ones who invented them things back in the dole,
you know, back in the dome.
Well, back under them, you could take one of them,
and it would shave your eyebrow for you.
You wouldn't have to even sit in a chair.
You could just sit there and lecture it about anything that would
I tried to get a patent on those things,
but it turns out you can't patent a formula.
That's right.
But that didn't matter back in the day.
And that's all you really need to create that.
We just sit there wit-lidding and having the squid.
Wit-lidding and having.
Mammy didn't know nothing.
We did all kinds of songs.
Happy was none the wiser.
Remember the squid songs we used to sing?
We used to make up when we had nothing else to do
but just try and recharge our depleted accordion.
Knowing the squids.
Getting to know them real personal.
Loving the squid.
Having the squids.
Plowing the squid.
Squidding around on the squid.
Squid cake.
I like to just take it in my hand.
Squid soup.
Squid sandwiches.
Squid bed.
Screamin' squids.
Squid flags.
Squid pudding.
Squid beach furniture.
Squid primavera.
The hair is nothing like squid pudding though.
All that stuff is good.
Everybody's grandmother made squid pudding out of their own orifices.
And squid strudel is good too.
When you had a dry, dry old granny.
Not like the rest of us.
We used to dry out the grannies and remember that.
We'd take the grannies and we'd string them up.
Smoke them.
And for a long time.
And get them cured.
Two, three, four weeks.
We would be cured but we would never get high off of it.
Jerked granny.
Nope, wasn't right.
Besides, grandpa didn't like that.
No, he wanted to do his own jerkin'.
He walked 50 miles a day to go to a squid.
And then grandma, she walked until she quit squid.
She walked about 25 miles a day.
And they just keep telling the same story.
Everybody knows you took the squid bus.
Grandpa been jerkin' with that prairie squid murkin'.
I remember that old song.
Aliens comin' to Earth.
Earth to get our beef jerkin'.
Bob said it, so you better pick up on it.
If Bob says that traffic light is green but it looks red to you, floor it.
Floor that.
Close your eyes and gas it to the max.
Do what Bob said, not what your mind said.
Who do you trust, friends?
Who do you trust?
Your mind or Bob Dobbs?
Get that part straight first.
But people are afraid to trust.
You know, I don't blame them.
We've all been bad.
We've all been burned at one point because we trusted the conspiracy
or we wouldn't be so screwed up as we are.
We wouldn't be in this room right now.
But, you know, you go, well, if I can't trust Bob, who can I trust?
Friends, you cannot trust Bob to do what's right for you.
Okay?
That's in your hands.
That's entirely in your hands.
But you can trust Bob to do what's right for Bob.
Which you can't even trust yourself about.
So, friends, Bob is real and yet some people don't believe in Bob
because either he's too good to be true or they fear Bob.
You know, just as some people, normal humans, sometimes fear, well,
actually it's the old timey, I know a lot of old time subgeniuses
that fear computers and the Internet.
There's always resistance to anything new and Bob Dobbs,
is always new and improved.
So there's always going to be somebody scared of him.
Did you know that Hitler owned 8,960 acres of land in Colorado?
What?
Hitler?
No.
Yes, he did.
He owned 8,960 acres of land in Colorado.
Why, no American citizen would do business with Adolf Hitler.
I'm optimistic this can happen.
That's nothing though.
Mata Hari was making, you know how much she made?
$7,500 a throw.
That must have been some poon there, boy.
And so as we begin the work of healing our nation.
God's going to strike you down.
Who's healing our nation now?
In a big thunder storm.
Hey, something happened to that thing, Doug.
I'll feel up your pain.
You know, how the hell did you know that?
How did you ever survive the last seven years without your troinkin?
I'm sorry.
Well, what happens is if you've been around enough squid,
well, they get into you.
And they just start reproducing and hollering and carrying on.
Before you know it, you're just a vessel for squid intelligence.
And then you got to send them to college.
Exactly.
Start all over again.
You're going to get done with the little peckers.
Keep you young.
Keep you young and quick.
My feet have gone to sleep while we're talking about this.
And I think my hemorrhoids come back.
So if we could maybe change the subject a little bit.
No.
All right.
I know that's the only thing you ever want to really talk about in depth.
But for crying out loud, we've been talking about it for six weeks now.
I know.
I'm telling you now.
Hey, Wil appeared.
Will we fail?
No.
You do, because you're mine
There's nothing you can do
Oh, I can't stand
I can't stand
The roads around, I can't stand
The woods down, I put a spell on you
Because you're mine
I can't stand
The roads around, I can't stand
The woods down, I put a spell on you
Oh, because you're mine
Because you're mine
V knots
All nights
bad that he wanted to turn into a woman.
Then he wanted to make out
with, you know, the regular
guys that he had just been
you know, running around making explosives
shooting off bombs with.
That's all he was doing. Bomb making.
He was rocket butt sniffing.
As long as it can be distinguished
that man is man and woman
is woman. I think you're just a big bully.
What makes these men
one of their selves?
Sex can be changed. They're the easy ones.
What are those who so desperately
want to be of the opposite sex
yet can't change their sex?
We're ordinary people.
Girls have a penis.
Guys with limbs and
women. The classic
dude in a... One is a man
but you feel that you're really a woman.
Correct. And you are going through the process
of actually surgically becoming a woman.
Very good. We have a winner here.
I hope you don't freak out at the last second
when they get out the pinkie shears for you.
I don't care if you like us because we don't like you.
And we don't give a flying f***
what you think.
I thought you were trying to first kiss me.
Boys have a vagina.
Girls have a penis.
Man is woman and woman is man.
Guys with limbs
and women.
Hummin' a, humming a, humming a.
A woman pretending to be a man
pretending to be a woman? Ridiculous.
It's preposterous. In fact, it's so preposterous
no one would ever believe it.
There's gonna be hell. Medically impossible.
It's not really hard to believe.
It's just hard for you to accept.
Medically impossible.
God.
Castrate him.
Good heavens!
You can use me while I whip this out.
Guard.
Castrate him.
No!
We're gonna be on our own.
We're guards.
Castrate him.
This is not a haphazard maneuver.
Careful planning for it started months back.
I'm a blonde limbo.
Well, the joke's on you.
Beware.
I'm not even a real blonde.
Beware of the big green dragon
that sits on your doorstep.
He eats little boys.
Boys have a vagina.
I'm a dog's tail.
Oh!
Big, fat tail.
Connie's spewing too by Reverend Protectrix Amazonia.
Isn't a boy named he cannot leave the back of the EMS vehicle singing to the various and crippled
victims of the gerbling problems.
I guess we want to call them problems.
Somebody was clearly at fault
and didn't want to take
credit.
If you don't feed the gerbil, what do you think's
going to happen?
Soon, the gerbil
becomes very hungry.
As his belly becomes
hollow and his skin becomes slick,
as the hair falls out and his eyes
grow weak, he will bite at
anything. At the last minute,
I will substitute the
starving gerbil for the
healthy one.
The master
won't suspect until it's too
late. He's humiliated.
This is the only...
cutie. Hey, come here.
Did you hear what I said?
I said, come here.
Come here, daddy. You look so good.
I will go
through the girl.
She's loving the plant.
I know I cannot verify it. I feel that she will
understand.
There is no escape.
I have a mission to perform.
Even some more.
Very well.
I will recalculate.
I cannot.
But I cannot.
A human look is the
bringer of human life.
It must be an end to your race.
But I want to see the girl as...
the one who is not alone.
A beautiful face, monsieur.
Oh, yes, of course.
You remember her.
She drove everyone crazy.
Ah, the woman was for herself.
Oh, yeah.
She was at the oyster bar one time
and she was clipping the cathedral, as we used
to call it. She was making time
with a one-eyed man.
There they were.
exchanging spit in the middle of the barbecue
No man blinded me
She was no good
She was no bad, you know
She looks like one of the
Stepford Stepmothers
I bet you can see the Latin side of her
when you turn her upside down
I bet she's got one of those little fuzzy monkeys
Oh no, you shake her and
she goes all the way up to her belly button
Bob, you don't even know who he is
and you might miss it if you didn't have a real
good look at it, you wouldn't even know who he looked like
If you don't believe me, I'm sorry
I don't believe I'm Christ, do they?
Do you feel blamed?
Are you mad?
I will pull your goddamn tongue out of the roof
If you didn't have a real good look at it, you wouldn't even know who he looked like
You really haven't got an excuse, but I've done all kinds of things
I will pull your goddamn tongue out of the roof
There will be no excuse
Thank you very much
Bye
And do you remember when you were a little girl perhaps?
And your father gave you a beating
And get ready for a shock
The music
that they're planning to use
to crumble the morals of America
is this rotten, filthy, dirty
lewd, lascivious
junk called rock and roll
It isn't just the lyrics
It's the music
It's all Satan
Though they dwell among the stars
They make millions of trips to places
to the planet Earth daily
By an increase in swearing with language that would stand as failure's hand
on end
Psychiatrists and psychologists are no match for these ETs
Mob?
I think of Bob as a protean sex gland
Often when I think of myself ensconced in a little home
Little domicile on the pipe on the ring of Saturn's moon
I can see little flocks of pastures of green sheep floating by
And what do they call those?
Hillocks, like a little cottage with smoke curling out of it
And each one resembles a pipe
And I can see myself there with my own little Connie
A Connie of my own design perhaps
Hairy footed, perhaps with a face much bigger than the rest of her body
I thought you did and that's why I brought her up
She's been calling you again, Stang
That big head girl from space
She's been calling you, Stang
Oh
Didn't always call you that, Stang
I hear her
I see all I ever get is your machine
I know you've been thinking of me
I went back to the carnival again and went on the ferris wheel
And rode the merry-go-round and all I could do was think of you
Of course it was very hard to fit my head in
The merry-go-round was low ceiling
But still I was alone
And thought of you
I ate a half a loaf of bread
And then I played with the little girl on the street
And I thought of myself and cried again
Then I went on the ferris wheel
I had to be restrained because my head was disturbing the other passengers
And I thought of you again
I went down to the boardwalk and looked at the scene
And all I could see was
You, Reverend
Why you don't call me back sometime?
Well, it's maybe a huge little ice cream
Big head woman from space girl calling you back again
Hoping sometime you'll return my call
And I can't wait until the evening gets late
And I'm alone with you
Me
It's so strange
The perfume fills my head with stargates
You know they
For the night so blue
All those groupies
Yeah, I remember
All they needed to do was to just send their thirty dollars to Bob
And I know that's all they're trying to do is get close to Bob
They think I know Bob's phone number
And I do
You do
But they think I can give it to them
And I can't
I just can't
And instead of giving you their thirty dollars
I deny them Bob's essence
What do they do?
They come up to you and in time
They say something stupid
They play with your hairy feet
They talk backwards to you
Try and trick you
When time is right
Listen to the words
Time, yes
How many times does this happen at Divisible?
And then I go and swim all by myself
Every time
Every damn one
Something stupid like I love
I remember the last time I was playing with a lady
I told her it was nokr
Yeah, oh gosh
I only looked bad
Yeah, no, you were
Yeah, yeah, I wasn't
Yeah, I permanently
I don't think I ever saw the grave
You missed this one note.
I saw where you missed this note.
Yeah, it looks smart.
And there's a link on your website.
It's dead.
I wanted to make sure you knew about that.
You know what's wrong with those CDs?
That's where they go skipping.
No, man.
We don't want that.
That's a coding problem.
Hi.
How have you been?
I'm watching you tonight.
Are you all right?
Are you hungry?
Can I get you anything?
A cup of coffee, perhaps?
A sandwich?
A ham?
I'd like some guineas and some crackers.
A bee job?
Maybe some...
Knotted nylons?
Oh, yes, bees.
Yes.
I can bring you peas.
Would you like some peas, honey?
I can make honey for you.
No, they don't talk that way.
The hot Yoo-Hoo bottles?
No, they don't wear Hulu skirts.
They don't talk funny languages for our pleasure.
No, they just say, price Bob.
None of them have hair on their faces.
I found my copy of Book of the Subgenius for a dollar at the cutout bin.
Would you sign it?
Some of them do have the little lines, the dotted lines for the cranial implants
and the place where they took off the top of their...
Oh, yeah, I like that.
She's pretty, don't you think?
You creeped her out.
Actually, to be quite honest, there's been times when I've thought,
maybe this is going too far.
I would get frustrated with the sheer nerdliness of some subgeniuses, you know,
because it just seemed like,
God, I didn't know they were going to be so dysfunctional and messed up.
And, well, duh!
Duh!
It finally sunk in.
That is what this is!
That's what the Church of the Subgenius is all about.
Of course they're fucked up and dysfunctional,
because there really is a conspiracy of normal people sapping away their slack.
And, of course, they're fucked up.
And, of course, that's why Bob is their God.
Now, friends, when X-Day didn't happen in 1990,
we were so sad.
We're going, oh, man, we could have had a new government that was no government at all.
That, you know, that Bob would be the leader, and he never shows up.
We'd have a new church where you didn't have to get up at 7 in the morning.
You could worship it drunk until midnight Saturday night in bars.
We'd have a new coolness where, you know,
coolness was completely defined by each individual uncool weirdo.
Friends, so X-Day didn't happen.
What are we waiting for?
Do we really have to depend on some pipe-smoking dot-faced salesman,
or a bunch of aliens from outer space,
or a bunch of invisible monsters to make our own slack?
Hell no!
Friends, Bob is not the answer, and neither is anything else.
We must learn to think for ourselves, although only Bob can show us how.
And we must!
All of you had better!
You must question authority!
Why?
Or else, huh?
We got somebody here who's been reading their pre-scriptures.
There!
One who dares to really question authority.
And friends, really, honestly, I think that as bad as things are, if you can just...
The scientific basis of slack is this.
Fuck them if they can't take a joke!
Even if they help, fuck them if they can't tell a joke.
Yo, yeah, y'all know what time it is...
If you need more information about the Church of the Subgenius,
please write to this address I'm about to give.
That's B-B-B-B-BAAA!
That Post Office Box 140306, Dallas, Texas, 75214.
Once again, that's Box 140306.
Dallas, Texas 75214
www.subgenius.com
and praise the...
...to the side.
We just knew they were on the ride.
The sweetest squid you'll ever know.
Blow you right through the door.
They'll blow you right through the barburetor.
A 3D squid falling from the sky.
A 3D squid and they get through the water.
A 3D squid where they're falling on out.
A 3D squid.
I got a tentacle.
Oh no!
There's a tooth.
A great tentacle is everywhere.
A great tentacle.
Oh my God.
Look at this.
Little suction cups.
Oh my God.
The peel.
That's when they peel the suction cups off.
I like it so much.
Oh yeah.
Mm-hmm, baby.
Yeah.
So if you're ever out of your life.
Don't think you have to run high.
When you see some hair of pink-pink snow.
Falling down.
Oh no.
Hair of pink snow.
Falling down right from the sky.
From the sky.
Just pull the hardwood and the rock inside.
Pull on over.
Open your mouth.
And all the hairy squid with the best of its eyes.
And do some genius and enjoy the ride.
And then.
A 3D squid falling from the sky.
A 3D squid and they get through the salt.
A 3D squid where they're falling on out.
A 3D squid.
That's right.
The Lord.
A 3D squid.
83D squid.
They go from the sky in front of my car while I was driving down the I-90.
I pulled over.
I opened my car door.
And they were blowing my mind through the car door.
Placed all the hairy squid.
Ah yeah.
Ah.
You gotta make a stand.
Back in the day, there's a kid I played stick-em-up.