If I'm not getting it, then probably a lot of other people won't get it.
No, you're...
And he just keeps learning more and more.
This is gonna be your best birthday party ever, Bobby.
We still have a few more decorations to put up,
but your sister's finished her breakfast now, so it's time to go sit on the potty.
Okay.
Must we stand amidst the scum and get the idea across?
These days, perversion gets a bum rap
because it's being given a bad name by all the amateurs.
If you want to get the highbrow lowdown on all the subterranean hijinks
going on in the so-called real world you have to live in every day,
turn to us, the experts,
the unchained reverends of the subgenius hour of slack.
Wouldn't you like to teleport your debtors into limbo,
smooth out the wrinkles in your brain that contain all your childhood phobias,
and learn how to make your car run on sheer gall?
Well, sure you would.
And who, tell me who, is in a better position to do that
than the brighter...
than bright J.R. Bob Dobbs and his glow-in-the-dark henchman,
that most unspeakable Reverend Ivan Stang?
Why, no one but you,
after you've been exposed to an industrial storage tank
full of the subgenius hour of slack.
Every Sunday night at 9 on that sizzling source of nifty neutrons,
KNON, 89.3 FM,
and that runaway reactor of the great Midwest, Dallas, Texas.
There's a huge chasm between blazing truth and outright lies,
and you can learn to breakdance on the rope that stretches between them
by listening to the subgenius hour of slack.
You may have to...
You may have to get older, but you don't have to grow up.
Why, just look at what it's done for us.
Unimaginable wealth, girls, flying saucers,
and the best hip replacements money can buy.
Swap your oxygen bottle for some nitrous oxide,
and praise Bob!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Oh, nurse!
Nurse!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Some material contained on this tape may not be suitable for children.
Some material contained on this tape may not be suitable at all.
Do not waste time blocking your ears.
Do not waste time seeking a soundproof shelter.
Try to get as far away from the sonic source as possible.
Do not panic.
I am the first person to make this fabulous gesture.
But if you do not understand the force that protects you—
but if you must respond as you if you must respond in response to your
feedings and your children'sливоise military commands,
even if they areAKE ME!
If there is any hope today to ensure you can answer the wrong questions that를
member camp by heart, on your remote pretty?
Astronomers can describe in elaborate detail what happened in a billionth of a second after the Big Bang.
They cannot say at all what happened a billionth of a second before the Big Bang.
Something tiny exploded into the reality of everything large that exists in the universe today.
The thing that you see today is a universe which is expanding.
My dad is a 15-year-old boy.
Everything that is in the universe today is compressed into an extraordinarily small volume.
So, every little thing that is in the universe now is a journey of終γ descon largelasts gj
measurable point in a void.
Where did the point come from?
The Big Bang theory now has a stature
comparable to Darwin's theory of evolution,
which is not going to be refuted.
It's one of the fundamental facts of life.
I think we live in a Big Bang universe.
If it's right, and matter, it all began
when matter was concentrated in the size of a point.
How did it get that way?
Was there another Big Bang long before that?
Something tiny exploded into
the reality of evolution.
Everything large that exists in the universe today.
The thing that we see today
is a universe which is expanding.
The point is that 15 billion years ago,
everything that is in the universe today
was compressed into an extraordinary,
small volume.
Transcription by ESO. Translation by —
Subtitle by ESO. Translation by —
Subtitle by JS. Translation by —
quanto Scott Morrison.
Subtitle by ESO. Translation by —
the greatest story
science has ever told.
If it began
from that tiny,
little,
unmeasurable
point
in a void,
a void of the point
down there.
How did it get that way?
Was there another
Big Bang long
before that?
It's an amazing
philosophical puzzle,
isn't it?
Because you have to
try to imagine
what the universe
was like before
there was a universe.
Oh, yes, friends.
A properly
spacey
and beautiful
and, uh,
cosmic
piece
called
In Search Of
by our good friend
in Ohio,
Reverend Ray Sammartano
off of his, uh,
album
Peeling
the Big
Blue
Banana.
A properly
philosophical
puzzle,
a perfectly philosophical
pillow
upon which
to base
the ironies
to come.
Yes, we'll get
a little bit more
down to earth,
I'm afraid.
It's
potty time!
Not over here.
That way,
I'll see you.
Let's get that
diaper off.
I use my potty
when I have to pee.
Now I am learning
how.
Gangster,
computer god,
worldwide,
secret,
containment policy.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
See what I mean?
It gets worse
and worse
and worse.
Well,
it's so much
fun to,
you know,
here at the
Subgenius Foundation,
we've been
working on a new book
and for the last week
I've been, uh,
piecing together
the notes
for my very
favorite
chapter.
The chapter
about the hate.
The hate,
dear friend.
Friends of the
conspiracy.
All out hate
and paranoia
directed at
the normals.
Uh,
this chapter
will go into
explaining the
traits of the
subgenie
versus those
of the pinks.
The various
conspiracies,
uh,
political fundamentalists,
new age,
PC,
fashion,
et cetera.
Generally,
it's about the
the natural
inferiority
of the
human.
An entire chapter,
friends,
devoted to the
faults
of the pink
on what's
wrong with
them
and why we're
so much
better
than
him.
The pink.
And we were
thinking about,
uh,
titling the chapter
The Natural
Inferiority
of
the Pink.
Or we might
call it
Man and the
Subgenius.
Or we may call it
Revenge of the
Neanderthals.
But I think,
friends,
what we're probably
gonna more likely
call it is
The Difference.
Because that's
what we are
and that's,
uh,
what we can
certainly
hope
to make.
Oh,
uh,
hopefully I'll
do some sermons
from this chapter
and,
uh,
coming up.
It covers the crimes
of the conspiracy.
The types of pinks,
such as the,
the deep pink
versus the shallow pink
or the,
quote,
benign pink.
And the types of
subgeniuses,
yes,
and most important of all,
how to fight
the conspiracy.
Because, you know,
friends,
as, uh,
Pope Michael Flores
and a bunch of us
actually all said it once,
one,
uh,
the only thing
of the Lee Harvey
Oswalds
acted alone.
But,
moreover,
as Charles Baudelaire
said,
moreover,
to become serious
about a subject
that is as sad
as it is laughable,
is it not a really
stupefying thing
to see a nation,
several nations,
and presently all humanity,
say to its wise men,
its magicians,
I shall love you
and I shall make
you great
if you convince me
that we're all
progressing,
unconsciously,
inevitably,
while sleeping.
Rid us of responsibility.
Veil for us
the humiliation
of comparisons.
Turn history
into sophistries,
and you will be able
to call yourselves
the wisest
of the wise.
Or, as Charles Manson
once said,
the wise of the wise.
A free mind
creating thought
may seem
in raw form
to be mad.
Or, in the words
of our good compatriot,
Jaina Hyperpleet,
people laughed at me
as a prophet,
but many of the people
who laughed at me
yesterday
are not laughing
quite so loudly
today.
And many of the people
who are still
laughing at me today
perhaps will not be
laughing at me
quite so loudly
tomorrow.
When I was the skinniest
person in ninth grade,
many people chose
to laugh at me.
However, when I attended
the funerals
of these same men,
I found that the air
itself was burst
with the yetinsin
chorale
of modern
mocking,
braying,
sneering
laughter.
They used to push me
and shove me around,
but when Bob Dobbs
comes into power,
I will push and shove
them around
in box cars.
People used to smile
at me in point,
and they're still smiling,
for their flesh
is rotting back,
revealing the teeth
of the skull.
There are no frowning corpses.
Oh yes,
they're still smiling.
The only difference is
that now,
I am smiling
with them.
Uh, yes,
and friends,
as I said,
Bob's hierarchy
will pervert
the subgenius religion
just as Jesus's Peter
ruined Christianity.
And as our guru,
J.R. Bob Dobbs
said in 1954,
I am not a
fool,
forgive them first,
and then you can kill them.
And as some dumb idiot jerk said,
I hate them sub gum guys.
They said I was a dumb idiot jerk.
Or as my father,
Captain H.M. Stang said,
it's the bizarre idiots
that act smart.
And as Charles Fort
once said,
I think,
therefore,
I'm going to have breakfast.
And as Reverend Boxholder,
whoever he is,
once said,
what do you throw a pink
who's drowning in quicksand?
His wife and child.
And as an unknown subgenius,
said slavery under Dobbs
is preferable to freedom
under any government.
And as Reverend Mumbles
or Dennis Worden,
I think,
said,
have a nice day,
died for your sins.
And as bespoken by
the nihilist teen,
I am not,
therefore,
I don't think.
But as Bob Dobbs said
in Bobco's B-grade movie,
The Evilest Monk, 1959,
he was playing Rasputin.
He said,
if you have a pipe,
I will give you one.
If you do not,
I will take it away from you.
And as Master Control said,
any idiot can find something
wrong with anything.
That's what makes them idiots.
Because friends,
you know,
there's two kinds of people
in the world.
Number one,
there's those who say
that there's two kinds of people
in the world.
Those who say there's two kinds
of people in the world
and the other kind.
But friends,
the second type of person
is the ones who say,
Praise Bob!
Praise damn God!
Praise God, Bob!
Because you know how it is.
You look around and you wonder,
is everybody really that
shallow, stupid, ignorant,
and naive?
Or is it me?
Have I become something
so different, so twisted,
and warped by my lengthy sojourns
into my own interior landscape
that I'm no longer to empathize
or even communicate with most
of the human race?
Have I become such a mental mutant
that I alone know that I'm not
and feel this disgust,
even hatred for the pinks
who run our lives or try to,
and despair with those pink masses
who seem determined to be eternally dupes
of the shark boys?
Sometimes you think
it gets lonely in here,
but then I hear my fellow subgeniuses
agonizing over the same things
and I realize, yes, yes it is me,
and yes I am a mutant,
and yes they are all doomed,
and most of all,
I'm not alone in this way of thinking.
Other mutants exist.
And like Rob's dear friends,
it's the truth.
We're a shortcut in evolution.
That's what we are.
Let me make two points.
Number one,
the human race,
or Homo sapiens mediocritus,
has successfully halted
its own evolution
and is now working on its own extinction,
if not in body,
then in mind, spirit, and so forth.
Point number three,
the evolution of the semi-Yeti race,
that's us,
has been marred by ceaseless persecution
and repression
by these mongrel quasi-human race
anti-semi-Yetites
with their lightweight butt,
chicken-kissing code of normality,
or CON,
con.
Congratulations, humans.
You've managed to halt
your own evolution.
But what conspiracy are we talking about, friends?
Which conspiracy?
The conspiracy that we truly hate
is the overall conspiracy
of the normal.
The conspiracy that doesn't even know it's a conspiracy.
The confederacy of dunces
that is so vast and so broad
that it's the cause of all the lesser conspiracies.
And we can love those lesser conspiracies
because they're not quite big enough
to be worthy of our grandiose
and all-powering hate.
The JFK conspiracy,
the UFO bases,
Alternative 3,
fluoride in the water,
Iran-Contra,
the Republican conspiracy,
the Democrat conspiracy.
Those we can love in our hate
because we can get our hands on those.
They're apart from us.
They're not as constantly breathing down our necks
as the normworms
and the mere humes at large.
And then there's the liberal media conspiracy,
which is every bit as liberal as Westinghouse and GE,
which own the media.
So many, so many conspiracies,
and fanatics, my friends,
with their false explanations for reality.
False because they have explanations, period,
that they expect others to adhere to.
But, you know, whoever you are,
there's a conspiracy for you.
And what about those who killed
Jimmy, Janice, and Jim,
and John, and Malcolm,
and Martin,
and Jack,
and Uncle Sam?
And that's all just another tie-in
to the basic CIA conspiracy.
But then all the conspiracies are so interlocked
that when you talk about one,
you inevitably end up drifting into another one.
There should be a conspiracy for everybody
to sink their teeth into.
And the church provides this all-pervasive umbrella,
which will allow all of you misfits
to get together and compare notes.
There's certainly plenty of conspiracies to go around.
We've started hundreds.
We've got hundreds of them ourselves.
The important thing is,
don't keep this information to yourselves, friends.
Spread it around, because human politics
and the squabbling of nations
is only part of what the conspiracy manipulates.
It has no face.
We know it only by its desires.
The thousands of little conspiracies
within the big conspiracy are real enough,
but they themselves don't even know
who they're really working for.
Many of them even mean well.
But they're all just ravening mouths
for a vast hunger with no body,
with which the elder gods have infected the Earth.
Now, of course, this sounds like the product
of a diseased mind, but wouldn't it
if what we're saying is even remotely true?
And the conspiracy is also a great mirror
of disfigurement, friends,
reflecting what's wrong with all of us.
It's much bigger than Republicans and the Democrats
or presidents and interlocking corporate directorates.
It's everything from the school bully
to the wimp principal,
from zombie moms and embittered dads
to the Nazis who censor school textbooks
and to the subgeniuses,
who try to make this church
like all the others.
What you must remember, though,
is that more than anything else,
the conspiracy is an attitude, a fear,
an irrational distrust of anything unfamiliar.
This fear pervades our society,
and it's what lets the conspiracy
get away with real murder on a massive scale.
Oh, Americans love new things,
like Michael Jackson is new compared to The Beatles.
But if, say, a real Jesus were to show up,
why, it'd look just a bit too new
to be allowed to run loose for long.
Gangster computer god worldwide secret containment policy.
Made possible solely by worldwide computer god Frankenstein controls,
especially lifelong constant threshold brainwash radio.
Quiet and motionless, I can slightly hear it.
Repeatedly, this has saved my life on the streets.
Four billion worldwide population, all living,
have a computer god containment policy brain bank brain,
a real brain, in the brain bank cities
on the far side of the moon we never see.
Primarily based on your lifelong Frankenstein radio controls,
especially your eyesight TV,
sight and sound recorded by your brain,
your moon brain of the computer god
activates your Frankenstein threshold brainwash radio
lifelong, inculcating conformist propaganda,
even frightening you and mixing you up,
and the usual, don't worry about it,
for your setbacks, mistakes,
even when you receive deadly injuries.
This is the worldwide computer god secret containment policy.
Worldwide, as a Frankenstein slave,
usually at night, you go to a nearby hospital
or camouflage miniature hospital van trials,
you strip naked, lay on the operating table,
which slides into the sealed computer god robot operating cabinet.
Intravenous tubes are connected.
The slimy, vicious Jew doctor simply pushes the starting button.
Based upon your computer god brain on the moon,
which records progress in your systematic butchery,
your butchery is continued.
Exactly, systematically.
The computer god operating cabinet has many robot arms,
with electrical and laser beam knife robot arms,
with fly-eye TV cameras watching your whole body.
Every part of you is monitored,
even through your Frankenstein controls.
Synthetic blood, synthetic instant-sealing flesh and skin,
even synthetic electrical heartbeat to keep you alive
are some of the unbelievable computer god instant plastic surgery secrets.
You are the highest, most intelligent electrical machine in the universe.
Inevitability of gradualness.
Usually in a few years, you are made string-beam thin
or grotesquely deformed, crippled and ugly,
or even made over one foot shorter or one foot taller,
as the computer god sees fit.
Virtually all of the important instant plastic surgery
is done to you inside the computer god sealed robot operating cabinet.
Even unbelievable, impossible plastic surgery operations,
all impossible even for dozens of vicious kosher-bosher doctors
working around the clock for weeks.
The computer god sealed robot arm operating cabinet
can perform all of the above impossible plastic surgery operations overnight,
even dwarfing you over a foot or increasing your height by two feet.
This is possible because computer god robot operating cabinet
imitates your micro-miniature electrical current intelligence system in your body.
It even duplicates the micro-miniature electric currents
that soften your broken bones to create mending of them
and then creates stress either compressing the bones,
thereby shortening them, or stress to make the bones grow longer.
Spring 1984, Mr. Deck, lifelong would-be doctor and printer.
Insight to the worldwide computer god stratified closed society,
perfected by hospital birth, making possible lifelong Frankenstein controls,
and lifelong hampering human defense, containment policy.
Hospital birth lifelong gifts, example,
deformed, crippled, retarded, pox, hives, warts, moles, blindness, deafness, poor vision, etc.
Kosher-bosher containment policy work, good doctor's secret health example,
cataract, rheumatism, weak heart, damaged vision, epilepsy, fainting spells, paralysis,
loss of memory, trembling, gout, diabetes, many diseases.
The worldwide unbelievable lowest deadly gangster kosher-bosher
vicious medical profession, worldwide unbelievable instant plastic surgery
butchery of the body and brain, especially the face.
Wipe-on hormones and laser beam surgery causing instant ugly, deep, wrinkles, scars, age spots,
arthritis, freckles, blemishes, pimples, red, brown, black, or even sick white face and body.
Worldwide dark, negroidic colored male sex organs...
I use my body when I have to poop.
And I am earning.
Now...
It's OK if you don't need to go right now, Katy.
Just let me know when you do need to go to the party.
Ok... Ok...
On the floor.
Put it on the floor.
Gently.
Now just what could have happened to get such a piece of trifle?
You have no idea what I've gone through in the last three months.
And your conscious mind just doesn't see it.
Well, when they came out in 1956 with the subliminals,
there were two different people or types of people that went to Dr. Hal Becker right away
and wanted to use this subliminal.
And you can probably guess who they were.
They were preachers and they were politicians.
Because the preachers would love to get converts,
and the politicians would just love to get votes.
And a lot of politicians we would never vote for if we had any choice about it.
But they found if they used subliminals,
they could get votes from people who would never support them normally.
And the same thing with people teaching false religions.
That whole game, that whole game somewhere.
And the movies, the movies ain't doing but program your thing.
They say, put them all on dope.
And all the movies start glamorizing drugs.
Yeah, that's what Hollywood is about. Hollywood ain't about a trick.
Glamorize drugs.
The French Connection Academy Award winning.
And how many of y'all saw a movie called Midnight Express?
By the white boy over there and Turkey smuggling drugs and they caught him.
And the movie made the white drug smuggling the hero
and the Turks who caught him made them the pigs.
Grrr.
Later in the day.
Hey, wha-wha-whoa.
Bobby Worby sat in the wall.
Bobby Worby had a great fall.
A list of geniuses, horses, and men
couldn't put Bobby Worby back together again.
Grrr.
No graying and balding, even hairy buddy and furry buddy.
Mustached, bearded women, even wipe-on synthetic hormones causing cancerous growth.
Bloating, swelling, deformed big pickle nose, bulldog hanging cheeks and jowls.
From teenage gradual wipe-on, yellowing, browning and blackening of teeth.
And instant grinding and acids leaving hollow brown stumps.
So vocal cords are made raspy, aged.
Creating a wrinkled, ugly, gargoylic, clown booze face worldwide population by age 70.
Deformed, crippled, weak and brain damaged.
No, senile.
Lingering for inevitability of gradualness.
Extermination.
For your only hope for a future, do you know one word of pray for me, Francis E. Deck?
Computer God computerized brain thinking sealed robot operating arm surgery cabinet machine removal
of most of the frontal command lobe of the brain.
Gradually, during lifetime and overnight in all insane asylums,
after Computer God kosher-bosher one month probation period,
creating helpless, hopeless Computer God Frankenstein earphone radio parroting puppet brainless slaves.
Resulting in millions of hopeless, helpless, homeless, derelict,
and
In all Jerusalem, USA cities and Soviet slave work camps.
Something is implanted, an instinct, a blind compulsion to act for them.
But, Quatermass, if you're right, what's going to happen?
What's the ultimate object?
I hesitate to guess, Inspector.
First, a few of these things came here.
At random. Scattered. And then, expended themselves to a purpose. A year ago. Phase number two. The concentrated attack.
The concentrated attack.
The next rule of the Church of the Subgenius is that the Church of the Subgenius will help you pull the wool over your own eyes.
That's right, children. Pull the wool.
What do I mean by this, children?
Well, ever since you were a little, bitty baby, ever since you were a little girl or a little boy,
you've been sold your family's wool, your church's wool, your school's wool, your governor's wool.
This is our land.
A land of peace and of plenty.
A land of harmony and hope.
This is our land.
Oceania.
These are our people.
The workers. The strivers. The builders.
The builders of our world.
Struggling. Fighting.
That's us, friends. Struggling and fighting.
And it's time now for me to tell you what you've been listening to.
Gosh, at the very beginning of the show, there was a wonderful piece, the perversion intro by Hell Pope Huey.
He's been doing all these wonderful hour of slack promos.
A miscellaneous media brawl.
A collage material from my collection.
A lot of cuts from Saint Joe Riley here in Dallas.
A wonderful little potty time tape contributed by Saint J. Condom.
Oddly enough, ironically enough, the author of P-Dawg, among other great works.
And of course, Francis E. Deck.
The great, great ranter.
Perhaps one of the most intense ranters who has ever existed.
Just short of this one.
Papa Joe Mama.
Hello, friends.
And welcome.
The sermon tonight is entitled, The Last Chance.
Yes, friends, 1998 is fast approaching.
And a lot of people out there have come to expect the church to start singing a different tune about the judgment day.
They say, hey, did you hear the news?
The Berlin Wall has fallen.
Things are getting better.
We say, is that so?
They say, hey, did you read the paper?
The Russians are now our friends.
Things are getting better.
We say, is that so?
They say, hey, did you see it on CNN?
We won the war.
Things are getting better.
Is that so?
And now they come a running and a cheering.
Saying, roll out the barrel.
We now have a new president.
The Republicans are out.
The recession is over.
It's the year of the woman.
Everybody get naked.
You poor, pitiful little pinks.
Do you really think an eternity of sin can be erased so easily?
Are we now supposed to embrace the conspiracy and call off the excess invasion?
Do you actually believe you can defuse an entire revolution with a few scraps of conspiracy compromise?
Never.
These petty little sidelines that have a nice day news don't divert our attention from the news.
They're not even the real issue.
Not for a second.
Dateline, Washington.
New conspiracy president sworn into office.
Promises new conspiracy health care plan to keep worker drones healthy and make more capable of serving the state.
More to follow.
Dateline, New York.
U.N. meets for conspiracy roll call vote of conspiracy agenda for global conspiracy world domination.
Renegade nations refusing to conform to new world order will be penalized.
More to follow.
Dateline, planet Earth.
Conspiracy in last instance.
A ditch effort to avert bloody overthrow attempts to utilize all arms of conspiracy propaganda machine to convince subgenius rebel rousers world is now A-OK.
Member for conspiracy high command states, quote, conspiracy no longer hostile.
Conspiracy now friend of little guy, end quote.
Well, well, well, the world is getting better.
We should just call off the invasion before it's too late.
Wrong.
You can fool some of the subgenies some of the time.
But you can't fool any of them.
You can fool the overmen any of the time.
They're much too in tune to the wily ways of the wicked one.
I'm talking about you, Mr. Pink Boy.
Yes, you.
The one with the firm handshake and the easy smile.
You're not tricking anyone with your bold new vision or JFK idealism.
We in the church go by one credo.
Ask not what the conspiracy can do to you but what you can do to the conspiracy.
And come July 5th, 1998, we're going to put that motto into simultaneous global orchestration.
We're overthrowing the conspiracy and we're executing the ringleaders along with anyone else who tries to stop us.
Now, to some, this may seem a little extreme.
That's perfectly normal.
To the average man in the street, witnessing a public execution of a criminal may also appear extreme.
After all, chances are that the man is unfamiliar with the crimes of the criminal.
He was too busy making a living to notice what misdeeds the condemned perpetrated on society before being brought to justice.
Add to that the criminal's emotional last words, his pleas for mercy,
his insistence of his own innocence and his reciting of all the good deeds he ever accomplished.
Then imagine the prisoner's family stepping forth, begging for his life
and witnesses filing forward to testify to the innocence of this great man so wrongly accused.
It should be no surprise that even an intelligent but uninformed person
would find themselves feeling sorry for the poor soul and wishing him a pardon,
if restored.
Expected newspapers were produced and showed article after article supporting the accused.
Even the most skeptical in the crowd would likely become sympathetic.
Why? Because they would see in that individual before them
not a criminal guilty of crimes against humanity,
but themselves falsely accused and condemned to death for crimes they never committed.
By now, the executioner should be more worried about their lives than the prisoner should his.
The crowd might well demand clemency,
and if refused, storm the guards and free the prisoner by force.
If you were part of this intervention,
you would probably feel proud for the good deed you performed
and the terrible injustice you averted.
But if a few weeks later you learn that the prisoner you saved was an insane serial killer,
that the witnesses that testified were all paid actors,
and that the newspapers you believed were all frauds,
you would be more worried about your life.
You might start to regret having been so compassionate.
Then by some quirk of fate,
if you stumbled onto incontrovertible evidence that the man you freed
had devoted his life to destroying yours,
that his new obsession was to capture you,
torture you,
and sell your loved ones into slavery,
well, you'd probably start to feel anger.
Anger at yourself for being fooled.
Anger at the actors who tricked you
and the newspapers that lied to you.
And anger at the people who lied to you.
And anger at all the mental dweebs still running around out there
claiming the bastard is really reformed and just misunderstood.
This is how we at the church feel about the conspiracy.
Each and every one of us at one time or another believed the conspiracy.
Each and every one of us in one way or another served the conspiracy.
And every single one of us in no uncertain terms knows that the conspiracy,
is out to get us.
Every day it tries to capture us,
torture us,
and enslave our kind.
And every single time we get close to destroying the monster,
some well-meaning but ignorant bystander starts whining that we're being too severe,
too extreme.
They say that the conspiracy is actually innocent.
They say they know because they read all about it in the conspiracy newspapers,
or saw it all explained to them on conspiracy TV.
They say they think you know.
They insist that theyonymize the word up with its programmer.
They insist that our allegations are exaggerated.
That the conspiracy is getting better,
and that we should just mellow out.
They try to tell us that we are to give the conspiracy slack.
Dear, dear friends,
these poor misguided morons,
may be in the dark now, just as we were before.
And we may have acted back then just as stupid as they're acting now.
But that doesn't mean we don't have the right,
nay, the duty to destroy the conspiracy while we have the chance.
Do not be taken in by any last-minute media blitz
that tries to convince you that the conspiracy
has suddenly turned over a new leaf, because it hasn't.
The noose is around its neck.
What do you expect the conspiracy to say?
We deserve to die? Kill us?
No, the conspiracy will look and act nicer now than it ever has before.
So don't be fooled.
If you hesitate, even for a second,
you give the conspiracy a chance to win the crowd over.
And if that happens, you may find yourself on trial
with no more X's around to pull your fat from the firing squad.
There's only one X day, dear friends.
Don't blow it.
July 5th, 1998.
Kill the conspiracy.
Cut off its head and launch it through the cosmos.
Hearin' to the word of our praise, Bob.
Amen!
The builders of our world
Struggling.
Fighting.
Bleeding.
Dying.
On the streets of our cities and on the far-flung battlefields.
Fighting against the mutilation of our hopes and dreams.
I've accidentally raised the powers of darkness. Please come!
Oh, that's all right. Here, hold on, hold on.
We'll get to you, we'll get to you.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'm sorry it is against my religion to operate the heat and the temperature.
I'm fighting in the interior, my share.
Oh dear, it's that other boring collar.
But because we believe in the sanctity of all living things, we will let him come.
I cut my penis in a coke bottle and I can't get it off.
No, no, it wasn't a coke bottle, it was a can and it really happened.
It did not. Fanny Arbuckle was absolutely innocent.
No, it wasn't.
Eventual brain lobotomization of the entire world population
for the worldwide deadly gangster communist computer god overall plan.
Children, politics is a dead issue and let me explain to you why.
Why? Why?
You can go to Poland and vote, children, if you want to vote.
You can go to Chile and vote if you want to vote, children.
And the people that live there know what they're voting for.
And you know what they see as democratic freedom, children?
What do they see?
I'll tell you, you know what they want in Russia, children?
What do they want? What do they want?
They want Led Zeppelin albums and 501 blues, children.
The products of a free society are now mistaken for the society which had the freedom to produce them.
So nobody around the country, around the world is looking for politics, children.
They want ghetto blasters as big as El Dorado.
Big! Big!
For slack!
When you invest in pop culture, which is what you've been given,
as a substitute for politics, children,
you get bored in a hurry.
And you get bored in a hurry so that you'll go out and buy more pop culture.
More!
And you're so convinced that your taste in rock and roll or art or movies
is what defines you, children, that you buy and buy and buy to shore up that definition.
And you're playing right into the conspiracy's hands, children.
Right! Right!
But as it turns out, children, you're also playing into our hands, children,
because Bob is a savior designed for a consuming society.
Bob is a short duration personal savior.
That's right, children.
Bob wants you to take him into your heart, to take him into your mind,
to take him into your wallet, and then cast him out, children, and make your own church.
And children, when you look around at the shambles that the modern world has become, children,
don't blame Bob.
He doesn't make history. He just exploits it.
And if children, if you look at these subgeniuses, and you see how deep their devotion is,
and how truly they believe, and how much Bob means to them,
and you say, a joke is all that's left, children,
yes, that's true, children, but it's a joke you can believe in.
Can you say this was the eve of destruction?
Surely, my friend, you must have been blind.
I can see on the dawn of this morning
a new ray of hope for mankind.
And your dead men, they are marching,
in legions to end things,
the roads where the highways begun.
And your young people are leaving,
their candles like sunflowers,
in darkness to walk in the sun.
We are here tonight to talk about
to preach a word of hatred for normalcy, children.
Unlike the Namby Pamby Christians and the New Agers,
the subgenius is a religion of hate.
Now, we're not talking about just any old ordinary hate.
You can't just talk about some mealy-mouthed, wimpy little,
oh, I just hate President Reagan so much.
You know, I just hate this society.
Or, even worse,
you know, I just hate myself.
What we're talking about
when we say hate
is an all-encompassing,
an all-empressing,
an infinite hate.
Hate, hate,
I'm too busy hating.
Hate! Because it is our hate of the peep boys, the normals, that gives us our unruly psychic powers.
Yes, in the Church of the Sub-Jeez you can learn psychic powers.
Learn to psychic and read your own mind.
Predict the past and present.
Become master of the universe while losing weight.
Dominate yourself.
Reveal yourself.
Incorrect answers to questions you never would have thought of to ask anyway.
The infinity series. Collect them all.
But you might ask, who's this hate to wreck that, children?
There are some men whose level of hideousness, protest, repugnance,
reaches such levels that we have...
coined a special phrase for these men.
We call them idols of hate.
Kill me! Kill me somebody!
Can I get a witness?
Can I get a hate?
Can I get a kill me?
Kill me somebody! Kill me somebody!
Pull that one down and go, she ain't got no legs!
My legs are fire round!
Now who are some of these idols of hate?
I think you know who we're talking about.
Mr. Dishonest TV Evangelist, sir.
Mr. Top 40 Radio Programmer, sir.
Mr. Sleazebag Corporate Executive, sir.
Oh, you don't even know what I'm talking about.
You're just living through the channels.
But by God, you don't hear me now, sir.
Now what is another example of what we call...
an idol of hate?
Another example of an idol of hate is...
the guy we call Mr. Just His Way.
Oh, I'm sure you've met Mr. Just His Way.
Is he totally cruel and obnoxious?
Well, that's just his way.
Did he pound your face in with two concrete blocks?
Did he try to exterminate an entire race...
and enslave the entire earth?
Well, that's just the beer talking.
He's alright.
And I can get into that.
I think it's valid.
But this is just my way.
I'm just into making lampshades...
from the flesh of Mr. Just His Way.
I'm just into painting my kitchen...
with the blood of Mr. Just His Way.
Oh, I do like your kitchen.
Do you really?
Well, it's Central Arkansas redneck.
Do you think it's really me?
It's just the way I am, I guess.
Now they've got themselves a colony.
And all this went on for a year...
and nobody said anything?
But who knows how many infected people...
they've got in high places.
What about here?
Can you be sure of all your stuff?
I think so.
I'll step up security in the morning.
The next move is Hall's.
We've got to break this conspiracy.
The conspiracy of silence and secret orders.
Your young men heard follow your teachings
Now they know the wrongs you've done
And they've heard all your two-sided preachings
Now we know just what must be won
And the sweet wine of life
Flows freely and clearly
Come break the spell while you can
And form a great circle
That shall not be broken
Proclaiming the freedom of man
Now you listen to me.
I'll only say once.
We are not sick men.
No, not us, friends.
Thank you.
And, yeah, there's some marvelous subgenius preaching there from some of the greats,
the real greats, Pope David N. Meyer,
Pope of the Great Pacific Northwest, Idaho and New York,
preaching on the conspiracy of democracy products
and followed by St. Janer Hyperclete with the classic hate rant,
Mr. Just His Way from, I believe, the Boston Babylon of preaching and friends.
You know, you can learn more about that hate and where to pump your hate up
by writing for free information from the Church of the Subgenius.
And what happens when you do that is you get a little catalog.
Basically, it tells you how much.
Money you could spend later on.
On books, tapes, and so forth and so on.
And, friends, just write for that free information from Bob.
You can just address it to Bob.
You got that pencil ready?
That's old Bobby at Post Office Box 140306.
That's Box 140306.
In mighty Dallas, Texas.
Dallas, Texas, dear friends, 75214.
And we'll be looking forward to hearing from you so, so soon.
Bye.
That was good.
What you were about to see, you may find hard to believe.
A, B, C, D, E, F, G.
H, I, J, K, L, M, N, O, P.
Lizzie, before we leave for Bobby's party, you need to go to the potty.
Okay, Daddy.
You need any help?
No thanks, I can do it myself.
That's my girl.
First I put my book away, then we'll go to the party.
When I use the potty, Dad's so proud of me.
There they go.
We're really good at this, aren't we, Teddy?
On top of your potty, you're sailing to poop.
Oh, life is much better when your diapers don't work.
I'm glad it's true.
But you have to be patient.
Just sit there and smile.
But instead of waiting, why not read for a while?
I'm done, Daddy.
Okay.
Okay, don't forget to wipe, flush, and wash your hands.
How often do you engage in unorthodox sexual practices?
Come on now, break the silence.
It's a sex party.
It's an emotional breakdown.
Walking through revolving doors.
The system stays intact.
Climbing walls.
Your ass is mean.
Fingernails claw at my back.
Kagan forces cling to us as we slide in and out of time.
It's a sex party.
It's an emotional breakdown.
Listen to me.
It's all about the bias scared.
Do what you gotta do.
It only works if you let it.
I'm sure they'll finger snap you at your own small test.
Say it.
Now break the silence
Now, now, now
It's a sick party
It's that emotional breakdown