But let's leave things of this world behind and walk now down the path of Bob for this brief minute of slack from the Church of the Subgenius.
Ah yes, dear friends, this is Reverend Ivan Stang helping to answer the question, what is slack?
Now, alongside your normal everyday life, there's another life, one in which you have slack.
Man was born with original slack, yet most so-called civilized peoples don't believe in it, and their most learned scholars cannot even comprehend it.
And that, my friend, is why the idiot is closer to the divine.
Slack is something for nothing, that unreachable goal, that perfect hamburger towards which all seekers strive.
And to seek it, one must travel the path of least resistance and learn to try, never to try.
Now.
Now, my friend, slack can neither be created nor destroyed.
If you don't have slack, it's somewhere it shouldn't be.
Who's got it, friend?
If you don't know, then, my friend, your only sane move would be to repent, quit your job, and slack off before you're too far gone.
Praise Bob.
Help me, somebody.
Let there be slack.
It's chaotic.
It's chaos.
Chaos.
것처럼
the
yeah
Yeah, Old呂
You
Hey cats
Let's listen to me.
There's a place down in Texas where the hip people meet.
They got lots of slack.
Come along, you will see.
It's the place called the Church of the Subgenie.
Yeah.
That's right, ladies.
You want to live forever?
You gotta sleep with Bob.
But hey, after all, isn't there a little Bob in all of us?
The place called the Church of the Subgenie.
Bob.
Those other religions, they want 10% of your income right off the top.
They want you to provide for them in your will.
They want you to pressure your government for billion dollar contributions.
They want you to double your taxes so that they don't have to pay any.
And what does Bob ask for?
30 lousy bucks.
They're the ones with the extravagant cathedrals, the lush synagogues, the giant mosques.
And what do we have?
One hour a week on noncommercial radio.
One hour a week.
Now, forgive me if I go out on a limb here, but doesn't that sound just a little lopsided?
Of course not.
It sounds a lot lopsided.
But we got something they don't have.
It's called slack.
And I don't mean the artificial slack they try to market for a profit.
Hey, folks, play the lottery and win free slack.
Uh-uh.
I'm talking about real slack.
Internal slack.
Slack.
Slack from within.
The kind that feeds on itself like a breeder reactor.
It radiates a warm, fuzzy glow that lights up our lives.
It's an inner peace they will never know.
And therein lies the basic difference in our religious philosophies.
They stress pain, suffering, and sacrifice because on the outside they have everything,
but on the inside they have nothing.
They're morally bankrupt.
Empty shells.
Just poor, pathetic souls tormented by inner demons of guilt and self-loathing.
But we Sagini, we are the exact opposite.
While on the outside we have so little, on the inside we have everything.
And that's why we're smiling and Bob Dobbs is smirking.
Because we're rich with slack.
Slack.
And for all their money, it's not for sale.
Herein is the word of Bob.
Praise Bob.
Amen.
1, 2, 3, 4.
All the way up, man.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Take you up
It looks like Johnny's gonna give me up
Knocked down to the ground
And kicked in the dirt
You're a coward
And this is shit
Johnny Garland is still the guy
And that's the look the other way
Johnny Garland
Is still the guy
Johnny Garland is still the guy
And that's the look the other way
Johnny Garland
Is still the guy
This isn't a song about school children
It's not a song about Johnny
This is a song about a class struggle
This song is about the haves and the have-nots
You know, when you're a have-not
You rip off the haves with everything you can
And when you're a
When you're a have
A have
You exploit the have-nots for every
Lever you can get from them
For as little amount of money as possible
Yeah
That's it
That's why Johnny got robbed
That's why
Boys would be boys and boys can't be cruel
Johnny shouldn't take his valuables to school
Boys have hope and boys have heart
Johnny and his money gonna have to pound
Johnny's penis was with a cricket bat
Johnny's wallet was a little fat
Now his broken body lays on the ground
The Bible reads, you'll never find
Johnny Garland is still the guy
And that's the look the other way
The head has to look the other way
Johnny Garland in School Today
Johnny Garland
He's still there
Oh, my God.
The Swingin' Love Corpses, dear friends, live at Off-Broadway on May 11th, 1991.
Today, however, is October 18th, 2002.
And at least it is in my time here in recording past.
And this is Hour of Slack number 860.
Now, friends, before the Swingin' Love Corpses,
we heard Papa Joe Mama preaching.
And before that, a place called Church of the Subgenius.
And I can't remember who did that.
That and other pieces in this show are from ancient hours of Slack,
taped off the radio by Dr. Humdinger.
Praise Dr. Humdinger.
Taped them off the radio back in the day
and turned them into 13 CDs of his favorites,
which he gave me at X-Day,
which are easy for me to pull for this show,
instead of going back to the original master tapes,
which I don't even know which ones they are.
And this, friends, is what we call Subgenius Progress.
Suppose someone cried,
Halt!
Stop this progress!
Suppose I shouted to the world,
Make an end to this progress.
I could talk.
Talk.
Radio is everywhere.
This modern world is full of voices.
And a master craft is everywhere.
And I have the right to talk.
But will they listen to you?
They'll listen just then.
If I shout,
Arise!
Awake!
Stop this progress before it is too late!
You want all the marvels cause you're not supposed to be wrong.
Your ass will be in trouble when Big Daddy comes home.
You give them all to him, then how you want them back?
The guides of the master are performed by a hack.
Was it you who said to him that it was okay?
You bought yourself security by selling your rights away?
Was it you proclaiming there are only shades of gray?
What will you do now?
You think that you're in your own grave?
The life you took for granted, is there anything left to save?
You put it out of your mind, you chicken-cheeked tea-save,
That the fact of the matter is, A equals A.
Big Daddy's gonna drag you and beat you to the club.
The one that you gave him, saying, I don't need it, bub.
A heavy price to pay for an apartment and a meal.
What difference does it make if everything's unreal?
Was it you who said that he could kiss your ass?
Not if he's falling for the con, why not give it a try?
Now you find yourself kissing your own ass.
Goodbye!
Bon voyage!
Have a nice trip!
You were such a damn fool!
You lost your grip!
What the hell does it take,
To get you to awaken?
No matter what you say,
A equals A equals A equals A equals A!
Black is black, white is white, day is day, night is night.
Nature is what it is, regardless of what you would like.
Man, I'm sick of your nonsense.
Go take a hike!
And follow me!
This isn't the Christmas I brought in my life
And on this mountain did I go
Just to really get to know you
Never, ever time to ĩ
Stop talking too much!
guitar solo
ZOOGS RIFT
ZOOGS RIFT dear friends
starting with this show I'm going to play
every ZOOGS RIFT
song in alphabetical
order and that song was
A equals A
this is coming off of a
30th anniversary
2 CDR set
that has 175
ZOOGS RIFT
songs from 1971
to 2001
the great, great ZOOGS RIFT
and now friends a word
from Reverend Tesla Coyle
there is
concern and discussion this morning that
maybe hypnosis is a shorter range
weapon the Washington area
sniper may have used it in his last shooting
Monday night police may have used more
than one vehicle and or two shooters
in previous attacks but a
witness to the seven corner shootings is using
cult AR-15 or Ruger
Mini 14 what does it mean and
how does that whole scenario lay out to you
where's Tim Harvey
Mick Oswald when we
made him
I was trying to conflagute
those names together too where is
he though now that we truly need him
he's at sniper school
I think
don't
leg up
the suburban area that
no we can't do that can we you know Mr.
Sister pointed out that somebody gets
killed in Washington DC every
day on the average anyway
so why are they so upset
well they usually know who's doing it to them
and why right it's suburban
usually it's people who
people who live in the back
well anyone who lives around
crackheads it's like well sir is
you right for being poor
well sure of course people get shot there
well duh or living
in those neighborhoods trying to be multi
cultural actually what I wanted
to do is get poor and start
taking crack he said I
suspect what it is is there's a kind of a
bag limit
of about five or so
per well they've moved the bag limit
up to nine right now Predator that
movie Predator I didn't even think about it
that's what they're not telling us these
people are having their spines ripped
out their heads removed
mysteries of the
unexplained
drunk from cups of
scum
Bob
Bob the Predator
the trophy Hunter
Craven Bob the Hunter
Wes Crane the Hunter
Wes Crane
Bob Crane the Humper
Hey dude first rule of sniper club
don't talk about sniper club
right
you'll be dead
yeah that's what I said
won't change a thing
just go back to bed
it may happen as you're scrolling
down the street
it may happen in the middle of a blissful sleep
it may come after years and years and years of pain
it may hit you too quick to register in your brain
it may find you in a belly full of lead
but sooner or later
you will have to be dead
you'll be no more
oh what a bore
can watch TV
or even go to the store
you may find someone else's
political blaze
you may walk into a lethal dose of
cabarets
you may shoot up something that's a bit too pure
you might catch a disease that has no cure
you could have lots of comedy
if it's the ultimate war
but a man tries
to kill you
you'll be no more
80212-1707
littlefiodor
f y o d o r
littlefiodor yahoo.com
remember friends
you will die
while there are many dangers in the world
the threat from the most serious dangers
of our age
are controlled by a murderous tyrant
to kill thousands of people
and we do
by its past and present actions
by its technological capabilities
by the merciless nature of its regime
and its drive
toward an arsenal of terror
the United States is unique
this is ridiculous
and it only grows worse with time
so there's so much war
the war mongering
going on
it's really sad actually
it's more than ridiculous
it's totally horrific
to see so many people
nobody wants to have peace
and give peace a chance
and get along
and make love not war
everyone just wants to go to war
they love to hear those huffy words
I've heard it's a real peace nick
he's really into it
his two sons are too
they're really cool guys
to go party with
who's a peace nick
especially the older son I hear he's a gas out at the dinner table
who is this now you're talking about
oh the Hussain's
oh the Hussain's yeah they are
those guys are quite partiers
they are known for their party
they party across Europe
in Paris they know them as
anyway but I know Bush's daughter got 10 days
for doing a slammer and a stinky in a hole
I mean at least Jeb Bush's daughter
got 10 days did you hear about that
no they keep those bits of news
smothered pretty well
was it for cocaine
was it coke or smoke
what was it some sort of
I don't know she's a little dope head
I don't think so
he's probably smuggling it in from Cuba
yeah right
he's probably getting the good bud
they got the Miami mafia working for him already
don't you guys feel like our president
and his disgusting family
are in need of support
everyone does not want the war
I just heard broadcast
on Cleveland News today
that
35% of the
American people
want change in our government
I don't believe it I think they all want war
35% that's nothing
that's nobody everybody else is perfectly happy
when they would march the prisoners through the street
everyone else is being silent
they just want another football game
to root for
the fall of Baghdad
we're gonna run that back right now
you take a look here
it's like Cleveland Pittsburgh games
you know
it's what the US vs Baghdad
the ultimate rival
Washington vs Baghdad
keeps getting smaller and more elucidative
Super Bowl 2 coming up
next week it's the French
the week after that it's the pioneer huskies
from normal
and certainly
it'll be
also
I'd be on the color TV All my friends would be talking about it
I'd be a star, there's no doubt about it But my life's such a drag
I wanna be a football hero so bad
Well I'd be so highly respected For my football playing abilities
I'd get autographs and interviews And the stories in the newspaper about me
There's commercials on the television With running through albums just like O.J. Simpson
Oh I wanna be a football hero I wanna hear the crowds cheering for me
I wanna be a football hero I want to be on the color TV
All my friends would be talking about it I'd be a star, there's no doubt about it
But my life's such a drag
Well I'd be on the color TV All my friends would be talking about it
I wanna be a football hero so bad
Well the sound of the crowd is so enticing Oh the thrill of it all would be so exciting
I wanna be a football hero I wanna be on the color TV
Life's been so boring lately The days go by and they're all just the same
I go to work and I come home Just another faceless name
Life could be much more intriguing If I could just make it in the big leagues
Oh I wanna be a football hero I wanna hear the crowds cheering for me
I wanna be a football hero I wanna be on the color TV
All my friends would be talking about it I'd be a star, there's no doubt about it
But my life's such a drag I wanna be a football hero so bad
I wanna be a football hero so bad
I wanna be a football hero I wanna be on the color TV
It's been so boring lately This world I've always anything just with it
I wanna be on the color TV I wanna show what I can do
I could make it make me a star With no doubt in my life
BelgianIC все же 애 그럴 헤이드
No team that's done a shit As far as I care
doses I need my du assignments
Oh, Football Hero by the Pink Boys.
Led by Dr. X, one of the earliest subgeniuses.
Friends, ah, well, enough of, you know, this war stuff.
It just makes me want to hide and escape.
Don't worry about it.
The spirit of Bob Crane is speaking to your children.
Hey, no problem. Don't worry about it.
He is dancing in the pale moonlight.
You're not going to fight.
Don't worry about it.
Pointing to his hair and his glistening pubis as he sings in a high bird-like voice.
Just let them do what they want to do.
Don't worry about it.
Make your body a vessel of this great land.
Sign up.
Line up and enlist today.
You are needed for Uncle Sam's war machine.
Did you hear about, like, they used to do LSD experiments on the soldiers?
And I guess there's some secret Prozac experiments.
That's what happened to Elvish.
Yeah, and they didn't know what their proper dose was, so they were overdosing soldiers.
Well, they were also giving them, what do you call it?
They had to give them LSD.
Biological.
They had to break out the old stash of LSD to bring them back.
Yeah, so they could withstand the biological warfare experiments.
That's from that Prozac coma.
At first we doused them out of the tox.
Now we're going to give them some acid and see how they took to it.
Where do you think Dr. Legume came from?
I thought he was the spawn of hell and came out from under a rock.
That's what everybody says.
He was in those army experiments where they gave them these drugs that they thought might give them psychic powers
because the Russians were studying that and were way ahead of them.
He's telling the story of the fly.
Dr. Legume took psychic warfare.
You're going to flip and fly like one of the little god's children of the air.
Look at your feet.
They're already getting bigger like a pair of duck.
Unfortunately, the mutant power that Legume got was the ability to read guinea pigs' minds.
Yeah, and also read backwards.
And this is how he gleans the future from the mind of a guinea pig.
He actually reads people's minds.
Very, very arcane.
Very arcane.
Very real.
And only entrusted to a few mutated genes born into the...
War guinea pigs.
War pig.
The pigs.
Are you being fattened up to be a war pig, Private Pyle?
Are you going to wear those epaulettes like barbecue sauce?
Private Pyle.
You know, what are they going to do?
They can't...
It's kind of hard to bring the...
As kids, you don't have to worry about the draft coming back.
You just don't have to worry about the draft coming back.
Because this American Army and Navy, they all know that American children are a bunch of little fat asses.
They would never cut the training, you know.
It's got to be a volunteer force, you know.
It's got to be gung-ho people, you know, just do it, Nike, you know, shtick going.
But this is how the corporate state has sliced our freedom.
And the rest are all the little fat bodies.
Disgusting little fat bodies in front of television sets.
That's me.
Soaking up.
They don't want me.
Nestle Crunch Bars.
I'm a disgusting fat body.
Gray, flaccid skin.
I'll stay home.
Moistened by the pale light.
Forehead.
The artificial light beamed in from the great Centurion Pactor.
There they lie, eating television.
Either that or they're going to send the fat bodies over.
And don't give them guns, just give them knives and forks.
Yeah.
Yeah, give them silverware.
Just give them computers.
A wave of fat bodies rolling into Baghdad.
With knives and forks.
With silverware.
Getting ready to eat, you know.
Ring, ring, ring.
Fire at work.
We are not halal.
We are pigs.
The American, the attack of the American fat body.
Slurred.
Pigs.
Thork slurred.
Slurred.
Pigs.
Thork slurred.
Hey.
Pigs.
Thork slurred.
Slurred.
Pigs.
Thork slurred.
Shtick to your ribs.
Slurred.
Thork slurred.
Thork Slipped.
Pigs.
Thork Slurred.
Like lying with bloody demons.
Slurred.
Pigs.
Thork slurred.
Slurred.
Hey.
This is a car.
S-S-Slack Pigs.
Pork Slack.
By Heart Ignition.
And friends, uh, by the way, this music?
we've been hearing in the background throughout the show is by the flying ryan brothers and you
can get their new cd legacy legacy uh from well you can get the information from ryanetics.com
spells like uh dianetics.com r-y-a-n-e-t-i-c-s.com and you are listening to the subgenius radio
ministry hour of slack friends and you can always find us on the internet anywhere at
www.subgenius.com
imagine the letter o like a star like a sun like a blazing beacon of bobness
floating in the endless night of pink fear and pinker embarrassment and self-loathing
imagine the glorious letter o floating like a donaty bountiful beauteous beacon in that endless
darkest night imagine now another b a brave and bold letter b chasing around and around that o
until we have a blazing band of golden b slice across this band
glance
across this disc of b-ness into the heart of onis and emerge again and again into eternal b
attitude and dive across the disc of bob nice again and again first b then the eternal sea
oh orbanist and finally as firstly b on ending on beginning b o b b o b b o b b o b a b a b a b a
b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a b a
ababababababababababababa and indeed on ending on beginning to die but die before Ст melting dead and and under their
Now turn the record over.
Is there anything religion can do to help me find my friend?
Well, we could join together in prayer.
Uh-huh. But is there anything useful we can do?
No.
It is the subgenius sacrilege!
And yet, in the interest of open theological debate,
we will consider just this once the question of what if we're wrong.
Now, theoretically speaking, not that it is statistically probable,
but hypothetically imagine, if you can, a world come July 5th, 1998,
where there is no excess invasion.
Oh, it's painful. It's painful, dear friends, I understand.
But remember, this is only theoretical.
A planet that is not surrounded by an angry alien spacecraft
that is not surrounded by an angry alien spacecraft
A globe not littered, a globe not completely polluted
with the corpses of conspiracy dupes.
Oh, dear friends, it would be a sick society
still dominated by pinks and normals.
An earth where corporations, governments, and well-equipped armies
still loyal to the system continue to uphold the status quo.
They fight to maintain their tight totalitarianism.
Oh, it's a nightmarish vision, indeed, one that makes my head spin,
but one we will contemplate nonetheless in the interest of free and open debate.
Yes, dear friends, this dark future of Dobbsian defeat
and conspiracy conquest,
this desperate future where the last of genius forces
are holed up in the underground bunkers
awaiting the final onslaught by conspiracy mercenaries
is a vision we do not want to contemplate,
but will this one last time.
As the Kelvin bombs explode far above on the planetary surface,
staying in his subgenius generals huddled beneath a flickering light bulb,
pouring over maps of subgenius tunnels, subway tunnels, and underground sewers,
examining any and all possible attack routes,
they will be determined, determined to fight to death
and take the maximum number of normals with them.
Yes!
Why?
Because we hate you!
They will be dedicated to honoring Bob through a dignified Dobbsian death.
It is even, it is then that some weak of heart heretic will step forward,
probably some Bobby who always dreamed of being a real subgenius warrior for a long time,
but when the chips are down for Dobbs wants to cash out,
this week will be the day.
The skilled wannabe Bobby will show his first real courage
when he steps forward and whines,
but Reverend Stang,
BUNKER!
you promised we'd have something to show for our, for our membership fee.
The bunker will fall silent like a tomb.
The collected gas will cost the barrel of
Daniel Webster will proclaim the same answer I gave the Christian in the parking lot,
and that is
this.
Even in hell,
we'll have the one thing the conspiracy tried to deny from us all our living lives.
The one human right they'll never be able to take from us again,
no matter how much they lie about what we did or what they didn't do.
It's the one virtue Christians will never obtain,
no matter how much they beg, pray, or grovel to their God.
I'm talking about respect!
Selfishness!
Out of respect!
The only commodity that can't be bought, traded, negotiated, or stolen in any of the conspiracy marketplaces.
Appreciate it!
Hallelujah!
It's a concept foreign to all pinks and normals who serve the system.
They may have stolen our freedom, our slack, and even our lives,
but by virtue of our very default,
we've earned a self-respect they can't even pretend to want.
And you want to know why?
Why?
Because their religion is based on submission,
while ours is based on independence!
Yes!
Praise Bob!
Give me a praise Bob!
So that, dear friends, is our answer.
That's what we get even if we're wrong.
Come judgment day,
the honor and dignity of self-respect earned through a lifelong fight for independence and freedom.
Only the devil could possibly resent a man for wanting to be free.
Any God that wouldn't want his followers to be free is no savior,
but a tyrant,
an enslaver of souls,
a devil in disguise.
And that leads me to my question to the Christian.
It's terribly original, so brace yourself for it.
What if,
what if you're wrong?
Come judgment day!
Please think carefully before you answer, dear friends.
What if you're wrong?
Because remember, your very soul dangles in the balance.
And it is the word of God.
Praise Bob!
Amen!
Praise Father Joe Mama!
Oh yes, dear friends, praise Father Joe Mama!
Friends, what Father Joe Mama was saying about that one side of the conspiracy,
it makes you wonder,
it makes you wonder which side of the conspiracy is running things.
I started getting paranoid about,
well,
the, the, the masons, let's say.
Let's just say.
For all I know, I'm really worried about the Illuminati.
But, you know, it started with that America Online logo,
which is a triangle with a circle in the middle of it.
Looks just like the old eye in the pyramid,
or the eye above the pyramid.
You know? And, uh,
I mentioned that to my friend Emot.
And Emot said,
Oh, that's just the beginning of it.
Haven't you noticed those, uh, triangles and the eyeball shapes are just everywhere?
And in fact, they've even gotten quite obvious about the, the names of these businesses.
You guys ever notice the, the red arches,
the, that form a big M of the Sonic hamburgers?
Get it? Sonic?
Masonic?
I think I'll have Masonic Burger now.
Or, he goes,
Did you know that Philip Morris cigarettes and General Foods were both owned by this gigantic conglomerate,
Kraft Foods?
Kraft?
The, as in,
The Kraft?
Yes, friends.
And, not to mention, when they replaced that Popeyes, uh,
place next door with Church's fried chicken.
Uh-huh. But it doesn't stop there.
If you look around, next time you drive through town, friend,
just keep your eyeballs open.
You may see things you didn't want to see.
Buildings, one after another, that look like, well, like the Temple of Solomon.
With, if it's not the arches, it's that Temple of Solomon shape that you see etched onto Masonic aprons and symbols.
Uh, my old supermarket nearby here, Menards, I, he pointed out, looks just like that.
Wal, all of the Sam Walton stores, Walmart, Sam's, Hypermart,
they're in the grand Masonic design, my friends.
Uh, computer places, uh, Computer City, Discovery Zone,
the best, uh, Best Buy stores, all subtle Masonic symbols,
and go buy your local, uh, water pumping station.
The gas company, uh, the gas company in most small towns is in the same building as a Masonic lodge, my friends.
The electric company.
They all,
all,
all of them, my friends, are part of one conspiracy or another, you know, and,
but what do they, what, we, you try to talk about things like this and they call you, well, the polite term,
conspiracy researchers, or conspiracy buffs, or conspiracy nuts, or conspiracy coots, or conspiracy crackpots, my friends.
Those, those are the real polite terms for, uh, the folks who attempt merely to look.
They're the ones who try to lift the veils, peer under the rocks, and pry into the business of the, uh, authorities, uh, so-called.
What I want to know is, friends, how come the conspiracy researchers get worse pressed than some of the conspiracy perpetrators?
Heh, it must be a conspiracy.
Uh, and you know, I can wax as sarcastic as the next guy about some conspiracy theories.
I like to think I'm skeptical to the bone.
But, I actually do believe a large percentage of those conspiracy theories.
Heh, heh, heh.
And worse still, I believe in the conspiracy, yes, the plot, by ordinary, normal, everyday people to label conspiracy researchers as loonies, or as a part of a conspiracy.
Now, contrary to unpopular opinion, friends,
it's still possible to use mass media to expose mass media conspiracies,
but you have to couch your expose carefully.
You have to make it look like a, a satire, or a comic book, or a radio show,
like this one, which is pieced together from the dead parts of history books.
Heh, heh, heh, heh.
And of course, some conspiracy theories are just that.
They're just theories, improbable, paranoid, predicated on few facts.
Like the one about the Masons creating the Greys.
They've obviously got it mapped out.
Others are founded on pure coincidence.
And these, I would consider kooky, wouldn't you?
But then, you know, one man's a paranoid lunatic is the next man's dedicated researcher.
And, uh, you know, the problem is the domino effect, though.
There's those who see conspiracies everywhere, literally everywhere.
The crazy old bircher lady who fears commies under her bed isn't just a stereotype.
Nor is the religious nut who sees Satanists everywhere.
Nor the UFO cultist who mistakes something that could be cured with Prozac for messages from the Space Brothers.
But you know, there might be something to some of it.
And once you're fairly sure of one conspiracy theory, it starts to tie into neighboring conspiracy theories.
And pretty soon you'll believe in quite a few conspiracy theories.
And you start to sound like one of those nuts.
Unless you're selective about who you tell it to.
And that's one of the things that inclines you towards the conspiracy view of history.
It's the way the more trusting people around you respond to the very idea.
You know, try discussing the CIA's more heinous misdeeds in polite society.
People edge away.
You've got a friend in bar.
Just follow the pipe.
He'll take you there.
Two planets trending out somewhere.
Jump on the luck way.
And you'll find.
You'll leave the conspiracy.
Conspiracy nukes.
Far behind.
And if you think this is all just a scam.
You'll be wishing you believed when the sh** dissapeared.
As we kill you.
Pinks.
So gleefully.
You've got a friend in bar.
When the X's come out of the sky.
And all the media crevins start to die.
All you fools with your pathetic jobs.
Will wish they'd listen to the words.
And if you never said in your thirty bucks.
It's gonna look like you'll get royally fucked.
With a mole's in lead.
And a bar.
You've got a friend in bar.
Bar's revelations are the sign of its peak.
Reveals the subgenius.
Destiny.
Cast out false prophets.
Extra meditate.
So set thirty bucks.
Before it's too late.
For you've.
Got a friend in bar.
You've got a friend in bar.
July 5th, 1998.
Seven a.m. I can hardly wait.
The six goddesses will take me away.
I'll party down with Jesus and Jane.
Half-pain.
Sex hurt with the horn of a Babylon.
Front to the gills.
The party rages on.
Full of.
Eternity.
You've got a friend in bar.
Well, I heard the American military, especially in the special forces guys,
their likelihood of beating the crap out of their woman
and creating domestic violence is five times higher than the national average.
Wow.
Now, we're not very.
I can't believe there's that many uppity women around.
Yeah.
That's such a shame.
Especially on a military base like that where they ought to show their face and not their ace.
I mean, show their ace and not their face.
Well, they're just putting them through a little basic training.
That's all.
They got to learn how to tear that M16 apart and put it back together in five minutes.
They got to put the socks on the right drawer.
They got to put the socks on the right.
Five minutes?
You get five minutes?
Oh, I mean it's five seconds.
You're going to be dead in five minutes.
Yeah, you'll be dead in five minutes.
You'll be dead.
The whole state will be dead.
The whole north coast will be dead and wiped out by the time you get that gun put back together.
I think that's what's going to happen to America.
I can just see millions and billions of soldiers unable to use their guns or put them together
sitting around errantly going .
Oh, this is the wrong.
No, wait a minute.
I got to .
Geez.
No, that's just the reserves.
We have reserves?
Yeah.
We have the reserves.
The regular army, they don't know how to do it.
Private Lonesome, you make me sick.
You are the slowest soldier in this force.
Give me 25.
I'm going to cut your balls off so you can not infect the planet.
25 reach arounds right now.
Down on your knees, private.
Down on your face.
The mankind accordion of Lonesome Cowboy David placed on his duffer bag.
Fat body.
You're the oreo cookie in this room.
You're the circle jerk, private.
He knew enough to wear his helmet on his ass so the flak wouldn't come up through the
bottom of the helicopter and remove the top of his skull.
Like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like, like,
What kind of a sandbox is this?
I know.
I don't know if I feel comfortable in here anymore.
It is a stinky sandbox with very, very bad kitties.
This is like really, really, really out there, man.
The kitties ate all the lamb chops and all of the tuna.
I don't know.
And now it is coming out the wrong type.
I'm telling you, private.
Sir, five foot nine, sir.
Five foot nine.
I didn't know they stacked that high.
There is nothing more un-private than a private in the U.S. military.
You are about as public as they get.
We can always go back to this.
Private Dobbs, Ben Nolan's friend.
Pull that pipe out of there.
What have you got that pipe up in there for?
Would you get that pipe?
Let me take a look inside that box.
What do you got in there?
You got a big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big,
big, big, big, big.
I can't believe you wrote that in four and a half minutes.
Well, it is sad.
You got more than me.
Well, the shackles are going back on as time to fix some more road, to clear some to drain
some more deltoids.
I'm going to drain my deltoids all afternoon.
Come in there and drink water with me or something.
In that as well.
No, I'm not giving you any water until you finish your work.
Lord, give me a drink of water.
No, no, no.
And no candy until you finish spinning the road.
Who's that riding?
I don't know.
He wrote the book on the seventh sea.
You know Christ and 12.
I'm scared.
Every land away.
Say, watch with me when I walk.
Till I go yonder and pray.
Tell me who's that riding?
Who?
Who's that riding?
He wrote the book on the seventh sea.
Tell me who's that riding?
I don't know.
Who's that riding?
He wrote the book on the seventh sea.
Well, I wish we'd known him.
He called us in.
At least the sun.
Till next week.
Through the clouds.
And the dark clouds are rolling away.
Just as soon as that blue sky appears.
Keep your head on tight.
You're back to the wind in your sack.
You can see clearly.
From here.
From the end of the globe to another.
Your scope has grown.
Your eyes are bigger than those dishes.
Oh yeah.
It's full.
Oh ho ho ho ho.
That's right.
The magic disinformation.
The kind that makes your genes swell.
You're too fat.
You're too small.
You're too everything.
You're going to pray.
My brains of you.
God's a clean'tle.
Bye valey.
Bye.
Thank you for watching!