I am seeking information about Bob. Let us see what is on the radio.
You're listening to PR News.
No, I don't think I can accept that program.
Nor that one.
The subgenius. Power of...
Slack.
Hey, what's going on?
Along with Bob, the pursuit of Slack, and a conspiracy of pinks, the subgenius theology includes a vision of the apocalypse.
According to church doctrine, on July 5th, 1998, when the television signal of Amos and Andy reaches the men from Planet X,
the aliens will arrive.
They will unleash their wrath upon the Earth.
And the men from Planet X are going to come down and take over Earth. They're going to...
They will put us out of our misery unless Bob can explain to them in ways that they can understand that there is something on Earth worth saving.
And only the subgenii, the dues-paying, book-buying, receipt-in-the-pocket-paid-in-full-to-the-church subgenii, have the tiniest prayer of survival.
The rest of them?
It's a tough world, Jack.
That's right, friends.
A red-letter day is coming.
And it is July 5th, year 2001.
And there the gigantic flying saucers come down out of the blue sky to pick up the happy-go-lucky subgeniuses and their pets.
Bluebirds.
And all their worldly goods.
And swallows.
Because, friends, you can take it with you when you're a subgenius, sure.
A throne of gold can be yours.
You can take off and get it on with Ba-ah-ba-ah.
And Dave here, who will be your driver throughout Earth space.
Step in. Step in, please.
Stand clear of the closing door.
Step in, please.
Red line, please, only.
Blue line to the left.
Red line to the right.
Hey, hey.
Welcome, and we'll be embarking for, well, wherever these escape vessels escape to.
No one's ever asked, and we're not telling.
What's gonna happen to your children?
What's gonna happen to you when this society we've created, when this society we've created, air conditioners, air conditioners, station wagons with wooden sides, station wagons with wooden sides,
cautious indeed, a retired actor, orange hair, orange hair, orange hair,
What happens when that collapses?
What happens when your diary was a damn well?
That's when the man from Planet X-9, when the man from Planet X-9,
I'm down to save the members of the subgenius jerk.
But until that day, the power and wisdom of Bob can help us break their mind control by activating that mutant gland that we all have within us.
I don't know what I feel.
I don't know what I feel this way.
I don't know if it's right or wrong to laugh at misfortune.
Darkness can never last too long.
Every time I think I'm falling and there's nobody around to hold me up and it seems like the world has come to an end.
I look up for my husband, now the face is friendly.
And suddenly a photo comes up in the ground.
The bottom of the pool is a raging fire.
I try to jump above it but there's no way.
The next thing I know, I'm going down.
Does it hurt?
Oh, it really doesn't matter.
Does it burn?
Oh, I don't feel a thing.
Does it stink?
Oh yeah, it really doesn't matter.
Does it hurt?
Oh, I don't give a damn.
When I find myself falling and I hit the bottom, it only makes me laugh.
It only makes me laugh.
When I go down the pool and I hit the bottom.
The last time that I fell in love, the love was milk and honey but the milk turned sour.
The woman became a monster and everyone I knew had become a stranger.
And the room went black and my luck was spent.
The floor opened up, down I went.
Does it hurt?
Oh, it really doesn't matter.
Does it burn?
Oh, I don't feel a thing.
Does it stink?
Oh yeah, it really doesn't matter.
Does it hurt?
Oh, I don't give a damn.
When I find myself falling and I hit the bottom, it only makes me laugh.
It only makes me laugh.
When I go down the hole and I hit the bottom, it only makes me laugh.
It's coming at me like, it's coming at me like.
Just kick it out, kick it out.
Oh, and the ground doesn't hurt.
Oh, it really doesn't matter.
Does it burn?
Oh, I don't feel a thing.
I don't mind.
Just a little pain.
Oh yeah.
Oh.
I remember when I was a young man how everything seemed to turn against me.
I didn't know a soul was an alien place
The sun was coming by a dark cloud
No, I tried, I couldn't find a way to escape
The only way to go
Straight down
Does it hurt? Oh
Really doesn't matter, does it burn? Oh
I don't feel a thing, does it sting? Oh yeah
Really doesn't matter, does it hurt? Oh
Don't give a damn when I find myself falling
And I hit the bottom
It only makes me laugh
When I go down the hole and I hit the bottom
I don't know why I feel this way
I don't know if it's right or wrong
To laugh in this orchard
Darkness can never be
Never last too long
When you laugh in this space
Oh yeah
I don't know why I feel this way
I don't know if it's right or wrong
To laugh in this orchard
Darkness can never last too long
When you laugh in this space
It only makes me laugh
Then I combined memory with life
When I floor the Himalayas
This student said
My future dream is to have friends
Or sakthi
Or last night wanted to try
prison for harboring PR News in Washington. PR News, Washington. The alleged mastermind is still
at large. Oh yes, dear friends, thanks Lemur for news and titles. Praise good old Danny Elfman for
that song, Only Makes Me Laugh, and praise Pope of all New York, David N. Meyer, and Professor
Chaz Smith and Lonesome Cowboy Dave and G. Gordon Gordon for that media barrage set of clips there
about X-Day. Lots more of that old media barrage-y stuff to come. We recorded hours of fun at 23 X-Day,
or more properly the 25th X-Day drill, day in and day out for a week, because we were meeting
virtually for our end-of-the-world ritual.
party using the Zoom app, and the sound is weird and spotty and requires a lot of editing.
A lot of editing. In fact, it's kind of hard to imagine getting through it all.
But we tended to get strangely informal and maybe too inside. I've removed some tedious
and or interesting lecturing.
But I'm putting it elsewhere for internet-only download.
Buddy? I don't know if you can hear Buddy barking, but this music in the background is from Captain
Blackout. Cassie Overdose, he called her. We did some kind of controlled show type things with the
old guard early in 23 X-Day, but much more of it was open.
And we're gonna get into some of those things in a little bit.
And I think that it's going to be a lot of fun.
And we'll get into those recordings soon. But for now, it's the calm old guy stuff with Dr. Howell,
Uncle Onan Canabite, Dr. Philodrumond, Piss Baptist John Shirley, Moda Mack, and host Professor Pressure.
I've never seen that behavior before but that's always why I went to X-Day, you know? I always went there.
see people do this. I've never seen that
before. That's why I went
to X Day.
So now I can say
this was the X Day that I
saw Johnny. When I was a young boy
they said you should go to X Day
if you want to see that stuff.
Hey, did you ever hear about the Stark Fist?
Well, I got
something to tell you.
Yes.
Milo's granddad
told him all about subgenius.
The lush fist.
Look him out behind the woodshed.
The nice fist of approval.
Yeah.
The nice open palm of approval.
Which you cross
with silver.
And then you have to show to
buy and sell in the marketplace.
For the first time I realized
what the meat I had seen below
might be.
What else could it be?
Frightening as the thought may be,
it could happen.
The sun will become dark.
The moon blood red.
The stars of the heavens will fall.
There'll be two major earthquakes
that are going to be coming.
The islands and the mountains are shaken
out of their sockets.
And the second one, no island,
no mountain was found in the face of the earth.
It's all coming.
Yes, I'm ready now.
Then close your eyes and tap your heels together three times.
And think to yourself,
there's no place like Bob.
And in that ship there was a Bob.
A rare Bob, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Woo!
Bob!
With a bob on the ship, and the ship in the air,
and the air through the smoke, and the smoke from the prop,
and the frop in the pipe, and the pipe in the grin,
and the grin in the Bob.
Bob Dobbs in the Sosaro!
Woo!
Plan is to invade, to infest key men in government
and industry with some alien force from outer space
that
that seeps into the human body and takes over.
Is that more ancient literature of subgenius?
Yeah.
Yes.
Yeah, the only catalog.
Yep.
From a time when subgeniuses had to worry about who was eating
and who was being eaten.
It's always one or the other.
Eat or be eaten.
Our ancestors told us this truth.
Only the most advanced life forms get off that particular...
They unchained from the food chain.
Mm-hmm.
That's right.
I know who did before us were the giant cave bears,
who were far more intelligent than today's bears.
Oh, yes.
And some of them, it seems, died of natural causes,
so-called, peacefully surrounded by their loved ones.
Didn't get eaten at all.
Mm-hmm.
And they were the first to achieve this.
Just four hours ago, I murdered two lesser creatures,
and we ate them for lunch, lobsters.
We boiled them alive.
Oh, my God.
I hate that practice.
Mm-hmm.
They're known to be relatively intelligent and socially, you know, evolved.
They're also quite delicious with butter.
But you're going to terrify the kids on the kitchen floor.
Then you boil them alive.
But first...
Bobbies are delicious, but that's another story.
Yeah.
What if there is a form of life in space,
not on some planet, but just drifting?
Not life as we know it, with intelligence, yes,
but pure energy with no organic structure,
invisible.
Invisible?
Now, the rocket passed through its path.
It entered the rocket.
It found living specimens of our form of life.
Cell organisms, human.
Exactly.
Now, if even by accident it could enter one of those structures,
what a way to invade the Earth.
Now, look, sir, I'm not over-intelligent, but will you...
You saw the film, you know what happened.
Only God knows where and how far that rocket traveled.
Something got into that rocket, and it's found other forms of life.
The cactus.
Good.
Great.
You mean Kurozik?
The cactus.
He's now in the shell of a man being transformed.
If one of these cactus plants were subject to the same mutation,
there could be an affinity, a union between plant and animal,
with the ability to destroy,
and possess,
and multiply.
An alien cannot invade a dead man.
We're merely using this corpse for demonstration of placement.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm trying to murder former housing secretaries in several states,
and in Arizona, retiring Senator Paul Sarbanes plummeted to Earth.
Wall Street down 4 off 9.
This is PR News.
President Bush is calling on voters to intensify their resistance against the United States
after an unclaimed black-backberry pack spoke to PR News in Washington.
The Earth is a black hole.
America goes down
Here we are on X
Motherfucking eggs!!!
Eggs!
Eggs!!!
X LOL
※ bid é
EXPL passou
I don't think you want to record us but if you do want to,
I could bring my...
What should I call it?
Trisand.
I'm happy with not recording us.
Let's just audio record.
We can be seen by the people on Zoom.
They can see us.
We can see them.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Happy X Day.
Happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy.
Happy X Day, motherfuckers.
Happy X Day, subgenius.
Are you a subgenius?
Are you really?
Did you pay your dues this year?
So.
I want to know.
Got to pay that entry fee.
Got to pay that entry fee to the salsa ship.
To the salsa ship.
The salsa ship that's taking us away.
Taking us away.
Take me away.
Ha, ha.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ever-important.
Ya put these together.
And the preachyоС axes won't just tell you
I'll get you with it.
I was meant to say hello
like of class Boston.
I miss SSA.
Well, it was really good to do it with him.
You're welcome.
You love me.
I don't have one.
Speaker and budget.
meantime
in the meantime
we're gonna
rock out
until that
salsa ship
comes
and takes
us away
oh you can't
imagine how it
makes my old
ticker sore
like a hawk
to hear young
doctors doing
doctor music
like me and
Philo and our
buddies did
back in the
days of
Doctors for
Rotan
which was
inspired by
Doctors for
Bob in
Little Rock
where you just
turn on the
recorder and
go nuts
that was the
Sub G
Kids
the Sub G
my favorite
new doctor band
which is saying
something because
I normally
hate doctor
bands
we'll hear
lots more
new doctors
in the future
but for now
we must make
do with the
old doctors
still in the
first hour
of the first
day of the
first Zoom
X day on
July 1st
of the so
called
wherein we
refer to the
video things
that are
beloved radio
audience cannot
see
this scene in
the background
behind me now
is the way
real X days
are
is that it
does
I love how
you can
like you can
move the
image like a
curtain
it is a
either robot
in the center
can come out
from inside
the image
I love that
look at that
that's a great
effect by
itself
it's just so
simple and
obvious and
I'm sure it
beyond the
veil
on the veil
days in the
past that
looked a lot
like that
as I recall
yeah
now this
way it's
going to
look next
year
now of
course the
people listening
to this on
the radio
don't know
what next
year this
is the last
year
I was saying
earlier that
that contextually
this is so
apocalyptic
Al this
year that
this could
be the
year except
the problem
is the
saucers
will go to
the place
and you know
and we won't
be there
and so I've
left a message
for them to
they're going
to pick us
up with by
pincers which
will pull us
upward like
this
oh
and it will
be a little
painful but
it will be
worth it
greatens your
spine right
out
I just
heard it
make it
clear the
last terrestrial
year because
just like space
travelers
pretend for
days and
simulate
Earth's
wake and sleep
but periods
will have the
great solar
year
it'll actually
be the year
one yes
down here
this could be
the last
year in
fact and
truly is
the last
year of
man on
Earth
will there be
taxes
on the pleasure
saucers
there won't even
be in Texas
well I don't
know if
there might
be that
but it
depends on
how you
want to pay
and your
ability to
pay
yeah yeah
how you
organize the
things in the
pleasure saucers
but if they're
truly pleasure
saucers no
tax would be
necessary
there would be
you to
innately
utopian
effortlessly
there's a
heavy tax
for everyone
who wants
to pay
it
totally
voluntary
they have a
cussing jar
but if you're
hanging with
subgeniuses
you may find
it taxing
if you want
to hang up
a bob head
you have to
use tax
that's a
good point
yes
that's a
good point
Gatorade
there Philo
or is it
something else
yeah she
mysteriously
appeared and
vanished
it could be
a bottle of
green pea
or something
but I think
it is Gatorade
it's a
like a ghostly
apparition
endangered
species
oh
hey I did
want to
point out
if everyone
looks up
in the right
in the left
hand corner
there's a
little
icon that
says recording
and it's
red
so
if you see
that that
means that
the whole
thing is
being recorded
by them
of course
it is
we're on
zoom
which is
managed by
a corporation
it could
well be
you know
in the infinite
files somewhere
a chinese
corporation
am I
yeah
I'm doing
is it a
chinese
corporation
oh
uh
we
I have
nothing
against
the people
from
public
China
yeah
I add
that you
can make
a personal
recording
of this
if you
just look
down at
the bottom
the button
on the right
that says
record
you just
tap it
with your
cursor
every
subgenius
has a
team
of three
to five
conspiracy
agents
that follow
and record
everything
they do
and each
of those
in turn
have five
to eight
conspiracy
agents
that
how many
people
are now
around you
here
so that
means
the mystery
of the
beehive
exactly
so
the
the pyramid
the conspiracy
pyramid
is usually
accurately
portrayed
inverted
because the
subgenius
at the very
bottom
is the one
controlling
all of these
conspiracy
agents
by what
we say
and do
you mean
the
is actually
representing
the church
of the
subgenius
it might
be
according
to
the
masons
who
you know
you're
if we
we don't
have god
so we're
going to
make god
we're going
to build
this pyramid
we're going
to have
the eye
of god
there
who
favors
the beginnings
because without
you can't
get to
that particular
end
yes
it begins
with the
letter i
that's found
in jr
bob
dobbs
that's the
mystery
that you
have to
unfold
to get
to the
next
level
every
dot
has a
revelatory
message
for those
who will
but
assemble
them
correctly
we give
you the
dobbs
head
and you
then
disassemble
the dots
rebuild
it
into
the
uh
clinch
that makes
sense
to you
the super
message
yes
derive
their
information
from
their
relationship
to the
other
dots
in the
glyph
we're
all
extraterrestrials
on a cycle
that is
ancestral
we're off
to see
the wizard
on a
paradise
among
the stars
we're
off
to
see
the wizard
on a
world
among
the stars
you
know
that
scientists
have
said
that
the
earth
will
soon
be
dead
philosophers
have
told
us
long
ago
you
think
by now
we'd
all
be
in
the
know
we
must
get
off
we
must
see
the
fire
sweeping
our
very
streets
today
burn
like a
red
coal
carpet
mad
bull
has
lost
its
way
gone
,
it's
all
a
shot
away
it's
just
a
shot
away
it's
just
a
shot
away
thank
you
ESO
and all
media
barrage
CD
tracks
with the
phrase
X
day
in
the
file
I
don't
for
something
a bit
unusual
for
our
slack
but
some
listeners
may
have
noticed
that
some
of
us
sub
genes
mix
tapers
are
fans
of
classic
movie
scores
are
the
modern
equivalent
of
purely
instrumental
illustrative
classical
music
well
one of
the
greatest
just
boarded
the
saucers
Ennio
Morricone
the great
Italian
composer
in
years
past
I ripped
off his
scores
for
background
music
on my
very
most
heartfelt
rants
and I
owe
him
here's
one of
my
favorite
pieces
of music
ever
not
from a
movie
soundtrack
album
but
performed
by the
Danish
National
Symphony
Orchestra
you can
see the
amazing
performance
complete
with the
lady
singing
on
YouTube
which
is
where
I
got
this
Danish
National
Symphony
Orchestra
doing
ecstasy
of gold
from
the good
the bad
and the
ugly
art
my
life
art
¶¶
I'd like to make a point that these are the best kind of pretzels.
These are good pretzels.
Pretzels, eh?
Pretzels are good.
They're in the form of monks praying, but before that they were the pharaohic arms,
when the pharaoh would be laid to rest.
Oh, and now you can scare a vampire with them.
They're Egyptian.
This is Dobbshead.
Carrying the crook in flail.
Dobbshead made out of Dobbsheads.
No, it's made out of photographs of X-Day.
Oh my God.
Potter Nostril Divination.
I have a picture of this.
Unfortunately, it's not high res enough to be poster size.
But it's actually made of tiny photographs of X-Day made into a Dobbshead.
That was a wonderful thing.
What's the program he did that with?
I don't know.
You'd have to ask him.
Now, here's the funny thing.
In the other room, I have a Dobbshead about as big as that one made by Potter Nostril
from snapshots from the 1990s X-Days that he took.
They're cut out and put together manually, not by computer.
And it's huge.
It's the size of that thing.
It's from the early X-Days.
I have a different wife in those pictures.
I see you've got an original Knight of Slack poster back there.
Yeah. Yeah.
I don't know if it's there, but I needed something to hide that mail-out table.
It was kind of unsightly.
I don't always have the Bob masks on top of that.
Usually it's just boxes full of buttons and little...
People don't like looking at other people's mail stuff.
No.
I don't care about your mail stuff.
People don't want to see an inbox or an envelope or a stamp or anything like that.
I want to put my mail.
I want to put my mail in your inbox.
Make sure you put a stamp on it first.
Don't stamp on my mail!
Too late.
Oof.
I have this urge to cross my legs right now.
So is it 4.03 p.m. in Ohio?
Yes, Eastern Standard Time.
On the coast of Coromandel where the mangoes grow?
It's 4.03 all up and down the East Coast.
There's a...
We had an Australian guy...
Now it is 4.04.
It's exactly half of 8.08.
An Australian.
8.08 might be here later.
I know Giggle Puss was interested.
I've heard from dozens of people who asked me...
I mean, I'd say at least 50 people asked me for the passwords to this thing.
Did you give it up?
Some of them have jobs at this time of day.
Not safe for work.
There was a suggestion about jobs that I read in this pamphlet.
Jobs, jobs, jobs.
Well, this is...
I'm actually doing my job right now.
Yes.
This is the first edition pamphlet.
Oh, someone needs a pamphlet.
Well, I'll pull one of those out.
Oh, they need pamphlet number two also.
There's pamphlet number two.
Oh, there's pamphlet number two.
What you need is a permanent link to the...
...to your store, Stang.
Since there's no sacred swag shack here,
you need a way for anybody to click on your links
and buy stuff.
It looked like you devolved into a pig man or something.
I beg your pardon?
I'm talking to Philo.
He devolved into a pig man.
There's nothing so tricky you can do with these things.
I know pig man.
You've just given me memories of this young adult novel
that I read back in high school.
I think it was called The Pig Man.
The Pig Man?
Yes.
It was one of those young adult growing up type of novels.
Essentially about a teenager and girl and boy
who ended up...
Who ended up taking care of this older man
who had this obsession with the pig.
I mean ceramic pigs, model pigs, and so forth.
A lot of people do that.
They are to be pitied.
William Hope Hodgson Howell would have something to say about that.
The House of the Borderland warned us about the pig people.
No kidding, man.
That was one of the first books I ever read.
I was about 10 years old.
A terrifying book.
That blew my mind.
It's a mind blowing cosmic horror beyond cosmic horror.
Did you read The Boatman?
I read Love, The Land, and Everything.
I just stumbled upon House of the Borderland.
I've only read his Carnacki book also.
How about The Night Land?
The Night Land I found the prose unreadable.
I'm one of those people who cannot bear that stilted, fake old English he's using in that particular book.
Too bad because there are great monsters in that stilted, fake old English.
I know it must be there.
I just wish he had written it in some other way that was not such a conceit.
Well it's supposed to be from some reincarnated book.
I know.
I know it is.
But it's...
What about The Boats of the Glencarrig though?
I haven't read it.
I understand it's very...
Terrifying marine voyage with ghastly things coming out of the ocean.
What about The Map of Time and The Map of Space?
I don't remember the author's name but they're...
Can you hear me?
As if H.G. Wells...
Whoever said...
Can you hear me? Yes.
...invisible man and an invasion from outer space and time travelers.
And it's written in this
attempted,
florid, kind of quasi-Victorian...
H.G. Wells himself was pretty straightforward.
But this thing is written in this...
forced, fucking,
painful, fake Victorian way.
I'm surprised, John, that you haven't encountered them
just because they're so bad.
It's a modern writer, writes in his old style.
A modern writer pretending to write in
1890s.
You've got to watch out because the slightest usage
can trip you up.
It's always going to be threaded with anachronisms.
Not always, if you're a very careful creator.
A few people are.
In television, when they have historical things,
they're always having anachronistic terms.
They're always having anachronistic terms.
Robin Hood gets his arrow in the right place,
shoots the apple and goes,
Yes!
Yeah, exactly, stuff like that.
That was awesome, Robin Hood.
Yeah, that was awesome.
That's the kind of thing that you see in...
The story of Abraham sucks!
Awesome.
No, they don't research these things.
It sucks donkey.
You had that Kevin Costner Robin Hood movie
where they brought in gunpowder
so they could have explosions.
Anyway,
the
Robin Hood
legend is
permanent.
Yeah!
It's embedded in my mind in some form.
It is
impressed on me as a child
and it will never go.
And Errol Flynn is Robin Hood forever.
And so is Daffy Duck.
We will always remember Robin Hood Daffy.
Yes, that was also a Warner Brothers presentation
which included footage from the Errol Flynn movie
in the cartoon with Daffy.
I love that movie.
Yikes! And away!
Wham!
I remember that now.
That's interesting.
Bonus what?
Thank you for taking the time to watch.
Please take a look on the screen next.
If you are wondering why,
well,
in Japan,
the stream looks like this one.
from our normal levels of living.
But still,
classic Boron hymn
The Psychoskeletons
Who else? A piece called
Keep Current
But now, we must
lift off with
Chaz
Knowing her fate, Atlantis sent out
ships to all corners of the Earth
On board were the Twelve
The poet
The physician, the farmer
The scientist, the magician
And the other so-called gods
of our legends
Though gods they were
And as the elders of our time
choose to remain blind
Let us rejoice and let us
sing and dance
And there was much rejoicing and singing at X-Day
But we'll have to wait another year
Hail Atlantis
Hail the sex goddesses
Because they
They did show up at X-Day
A new day
Yeah, we went over the rainbow
Into the mitochondrial yeti DNA
Level C
Well, we're gonna have to go north and south
And east and west
And we gotta wait another year, yeah, but
But we're gonna fill up a new pipe
We're gonna wait for the sun to shine
We're gonna turn around and take our time
We're gonna break the seal to the other side
You know
From the valley
I hear the muffled cry
Of all them poor sheeple
That we left behind
And we're gonna take that next evolutionary step
Yeah, we're gonna climb on those rocket ships
We're gonna build the vessels if we have to
We're already testing the engines
We're already testing the systems needed for this trip
We're on the ride, yeah
Mitochondrial Eve
Thanks for the ride
We'll take it from here
Be part of the rally
She made it
To Nike
Lou's
Subtitles shot on Tuesday.
Please pikat to Kimber at Mexico City
I was riding down Main Street in my car, a 41 underslung coupe.
I was all decked out in my blue suede shoes and my hair was covered with goo.
I was listening to my radio and waving to all the chicks when the music stopped and the newsman said...
We interrupt this program to bring you a special news bulletin.
They destroyed the world, the entire Los Angeles area.
Already hospital facilities have begun to crack under the strain.
And civil defense authorities state that the situation is much the same across the entire country.
Martial law is now nationwide.
Our fellow countrymen are dying.
The very foundations of civilization are beginning to crumble under the dread assault of that horror long feared.
Mom?
Colorado Channel, this is a class one emergency.
All civilian traffic is barred from streets and highways.
Stay in your homes. Stay in your homes.
I got exactly what I wanted!
X day shall come sooner or later.
That X is nothing but...
A cross that's fallen over on its side and somebody jumped on it.
Banged it up.
There is hope. There shall be hope.
You know, we sit and worry, oh gosh, if only the X's had come.
We could have had a new government where Bob was the leader and since he's never around there'd be no laws and we can do anything we want.
We could have had a new church where instead of having to get up with a hangover on Sunday and watch boring crap...
You'd go to church Saturday.
And get drunk!
Drunk, my friend!
Oh, we could have had our own coolness where we invented the coolness, blah blah blah blah blah.
Friends, what are we waiting for?
Are we really waiting on some invisible monsters in the sky?
Or some space things?
Or some pipe smoking salesman with a good line?
Friends, I say, quit waiting, do it yourself!
Make your own slack!
Bob is not the answer.
And neither is anything else.
You must learn to think for yourself, but only Bob can show you how.
Question authority or else!
And fuck them if they can't take a joke!
Praise fucking Bob!
Oh, those were the days, friends.
Oh, listen to that energy.
And nowadays I'm too old and beat to edit anymore for this episode.
So I'll end it with this one.
This is edited by some utterly mysterious, probably much younger person or persons from the Cleveland area.
Going by the name of Sheridan.
Sheridan sent us stuff.
This is some.
It's a very laid back long collage piece called Adrift.
Even if you're driving right now.
Closed.
Close your eyes and slack off.
I'm coming.
I'll be right there.
Get some rest.
Go.
Take care, sir.
Good morning, senor.
Welcome aboard.
We've been expecting you.
You greet me with 11 gond.
The correct salute for El Supremo Capitan is 23 gond.
The king himself receives only 21.
That is why I always have 23.
Uh-oh.
I'll be right back.
20 minutes later, they stood on our deck.
Dark, ugly men with a great show of arrogance.
Just listen to this stomach of mine.
I mean the way it keeps growling and squealing, the way it sounds, you'd think I had a hyena
inside of me.
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to do this, but I'm going to do it.
I'm going to do it.
I have a dream that one day this nation will rise up and live out the true meaning of its
creed.
We hold these truths to ourselves.
We want to be self-evident that all men are created equal.
His kindness, his gentle wisdom, his humor, everything about him is so right.
We can never leave!
Isn't it wonderful?
Yada, yada, yada.
Well, miss, so far so good.
Can two women really be so distracting, Captain?
May I remind you, ma'am,
that my men have been continually at sea for more than seven months.
And you, sir, how long have you been at sea?
I was... I...
Ah!
I shan't complain, Mr. Ornott.
We have much to be thankful for.
Yeah, that's a fact, miss.
It's like they say, it ain't never so bad that it can't be worse.
Thank you.
His kindness, his gentle wisdom, his humor,
everything about him is so right.
I still have a dream.
Thank you.
You.
We're going to cut out their living guts
and use them to crease the treads of our tank.
Americans love a winner and will not tolerate a loser.
That's why Americans have never lost and will never lose a war.
So, Dr. Knudsen, I take it that everybody's now on the same page and they all agree
on something about climate change. It's all finished. The shouting's over, right?
No, hardly. Based on the panel discussion that we had
yesterday, I think it's all over.
In New Orleans, there's still quite a bit of disagreement on this issue.
Why is it such a hard issue to resolve?
Well, we're...
See it at all?
We're not going to resolve it.
That was the broadcast version.
This is the internet version.
So, an hour can really be two hours.
And I've got some news.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave is sick.
And he was in the hospital for a week.
he's in rehab now not the covid but his um i guess his congestive heart failure problem
kind of came back and well
he could use help the one of the best things you as a poor broke subgenius could do
would be to write dave a letter write dave a letter about how you think he's real funny and
clever and you always liked his hour of slack stuff dave's not on the internet by choice
i think he is afraid of it he's really old he's in his 70s um
i'm so glad that we have had him and we
will hopefully continue to but really this is a good time to send him a fan letter he doesn't get
the kind of feedback that the rest of us on the internet do so if you write him a letter you can
email it to me stang subgenius.com look at subgenius.com all the contact information stuff is
there um you can
text it to some of our facebook pages and i'll probably see it but tell dave
that you appreciate him he really could use the moral support right now and if you want to hit the
donation button on subgenius.com or go to the hour of slack section and you'll find the gofundme link
for dave
uh that would be great i i i'll forward anything you send me for him we're real old friends you know
um i want to do what i can friends uh thank you now what else was
oh yeah yeah um
this is the internet show it's the we can make it as long as we want who cares
uh and we recorded a lot of stuff in that first zoom show and it was maybe a lot
inside subgenius history and a little bit too much paleontology that not everybody in the world
would be interested in
uh my co-spouters were dr houston to demi Mun phrase uh he just said you know many magic hands
and John Shirley and other junior scientists and so I ended up talking about
rudists and how the first pamphlet number one and media well actually the
entire membership pack subgenius membership was first laid out in one
night back in the day subgenius history 101 I've got his brother yes Bob said
scar this is the original wow oh my god oh yeah this one looks a lot darker it's
receding cafe press can screw these things up the Bob on the other side is
rather swarthy also this is a
the first pamphlet I got you'll notice it's brown it's not on white paper it's
on brown paper yeah we made those out of those are paper sacks little Chinese
kids stitch those together here's a little piece that's not printed anymore
right in the in the gutter there's a line all about that guy who's a madman
cookie and
I like drumming first degree we're here yep that's not there any more dedicated
to mammy there's a dedication of my mother in there and there's a thanks to
a guy named Wade left which you snuck me into the D magazine office after hours
where I did all of the typesetting in the everything in the membership pack
and all the bumper stickers in one night
the pan's nuclear beer the what the hell do you think you're doing then the
forbidden sciences all the bumper stickers the card everything was typeset
in one night and I wasn't on speed you were spewing in a grand admission that
we
50 words a minute then that's the moment that you release it you see學沒 it it
the moment that you release it you see know it was it was a that was like your
a prepared there was a rough done on a typewriter so i knew what size things had to be because you
had to make those decisions right then and there i wasn't going to have a chance to do it over again
and uh wasn't any of this expanding and contracting like the sissy boys have now
but i wouldn't get another chance to get into that office all night again it was in between
computers and the demise of uh of hot hot hot pants hot toddies in between you know the uh
computer um computer graphics and uh and hot type setting oh yes they called it cold type
cold type composition i had to learn how to do that type setting in that same night
earlier subgeniuses just had to use those
press on letters one at a time and if you run out then you have to start making up words and that's where
abafrop zipulops came from that's just those were the letters that were left
there's a subgenius on the screen oh god i remember those i worked in underground newspapers and i
remember those letters zipitone oh yeah that's tight zipitone is a transfer screen
yeah we used it didn't they also offset press letters mimeographs it's called
press
type celio tech transfer lettering press type i remember the hand crank one that we used to
that we used to made back during elementary school i think that was my first experience
huffing the liquid that they used to uh adhere the ink to the papers when you hand crank those
copies out weren't they fragrant though nunca fragrant and uh yeah we used them
uh to make i've used them to make my first underground newspaper
and when always i reducing tvan op.au we're gonna go to this…?
was 12 and distributed it at the middle school and got into trouble instantly.
The 12 year olds had their own drug experiences. If you remember Robert
Williams painting of a kid dreaming as he puts together a model airplane and
he's huffing glue and the glue is all over the airplane and all over him but
in the thought balloon there's the deadly dog fight he's experienced.
And we've all been there I think. The glue, the toluene rushes up into
the sinuses and into the brain.
Dr. Howell I have a question for you real quick.
You see that this painting seen behind me?
I do. It looks like titanoboa is it not?
Well those things and also the barrels in the back there.
background are rudists, like nudists but with an R.
Are you familiar with rudists?
They were a type of marine animal that lived,
they're kind of like a cross between coral and mollusks.
They had tentacles.
No, no, those,
I see.
They're more like a clam, they're two pieces.
They can swing open,
there's probably little tiny tentacles
at the openings there at the joint.
Yeah, when you're swimming underwater,
don't touch anything.
Don't stand on the bottom,
don't touch anything that you see is a good way to go.
Well, my driveway is made of those things.
Of rudists?
Rudists, yes.
Wow, so you have like a,
you can walk from ring to ring down the driveway?
No, unfortunately the driveway was made of pulverized
rudists from a quarry.
Rudists during the Cretaceous,
the reason they're not better known is
they were only around during the Cretaceous,
which was a long time,
but they were, and some in the Jurassic,
but they were not around after the Cretaceous.
They went out with the dinosaurs pretty much,
but they were very common during that period in shallow,
shallow oceans.
And they grew in reefs.
There was apparently a quarry nearby here
that was basically just a big rudist reef.
And that's where our driveway gravel came from.
Now, did any of them make it out in whole and in one piece?
I'm sure somewhere there are some,
and I've seen some at the University of Texas
that are really,
and I have two really good examples of them downstairs.
I could actually show you.
Ah, you got the good ones.
How, how big are they?
They're boring creatures.
It's like all the fossils around here,
they're sea life that mostly hasn't changed much
from the ones you find on the seashore now.
They're just made of stone
because they're old versions of them.
But the rudists are different.
And Princess Wee and I kept finding these,
these curved things with a peculiar color to them.
And we just couldn't figure it out.
And it took me two years of, you know,
of studying fossil, Texas fossil books
and going to museums until we finally,
and quizzing paleontologists who were often stumped.
But I've been able to prove that our driveway
is in fact made of these rudest things,
they're curved, they're really only about this big.
At the large, never very big.
So your driveway is made out of crushed creatures
from the Paleolithic?
Yeah.
From the Cretaceous.
Yeah, it is.
There's a lot of other little crinkly.
How is that any better than a golden toilet?
You may have been thinking Paleozoic.
In a different world,
rudists would be as valuable as diamonds or gold.
It's because they're rare.
I've fooled around in Reverend Stang's screen.
What about Stang's screen?
Anyway, I'm gonna.
You're reaching, you're trying to reach.
Trying to get invisible hand.
And the rudest creep.
The invisible hand is going into Modak's ear right now.
It's on my screen, it looks like you're trying
to fist John Shirley.
Yeah, okay, everybody has them in different order.
That's right.
Yeah, it's like the Hollywood Squares
or the Brady Bunch here.
It's possible to have it in one band across the top
if I only knew how to do that.
Oh yeah, that's probably true.
I don't know.
I kind of want to go back to seeing you fist John Shirley.
That was pretty interesting.
Enter full screen.
Oh, is that a picture of a Cretaceous thing?
Yeah.
I believe in miracles you Cretaceous thing.
That's what rudists look like in life.
Oh wow, that's a great monster, Philo.
When this becomes a radio show, is this a radio show now?
No, it's a TV show now.
I'm recording audio.
I don't know if anybody's recording.
It may become a radio show and the people will have to look
at the eidetic imagery in their own brains.
Look at this, it's the rudest fossil, is it not?
Yeah, maybe I should just get rid of the background
because that green screen messes with stuff.
No.
Back to reality channel.
First we found these things, these curves, these strange curves.
And every now and then we'd find a tip.
Of course, one could lie and say, dinosaur teeth,
but no, they're rudest tips.
Then that, that's a good one.
That's half a rudest, that's pretty.
That is half.
It does superficially resemble a dinosaur.
A dinosaur phalangeal claw.
Yeah, it's not though.
It's not.
Then I found one, this is my favorite.
I think this is one.
Wow.
An ammonite.
It's mounted on a little platform and everything.
Is it an ammonite?
No, no, no, totally different.
It's a half of a rudest again?
Half a rudest, yeah, which is more like a combination between a clam
and a coral because they would grow.
They would grow close together and form reefs.
It's a shell, you know, with something soft inside.
Like a Christmas tree?
A mollusk.
It's basically a mollusk, but yeah, they're not like anything nowadays.
They were their own kind of critter and they're not well known
and now you know about them.
Now we know about them.
Yeah.
Did they have a bob?
It would be hard for us to distinguish it.
The very rude bob.
He was the rudest of them all.
Yes, yes, absolutely.
Not PC.
That was slack for them.
Remember, they're not decadent creatures living after the extinction
of dangerous life forms.
They're in the thick of it all the time with everybody trying to eat you
and get you.