and yes uh here we are back at your lounge chair please sit down and strap yourself in
you're about ready for another ride and remember when they come by uh please just don't be alarmed
they may be offering you something oh i paid extra for that part buddy sometimes it's
bring them on come on baby hour of slack sponsored by the church of the subgenius
the subgenius hour of slack that you are about to listen to is specially designed only to be
made on radio station and only in the city of
oh yes dear friends and this hour of slack number 928 is actually a rerun of hour of slack number
uh this is
a search for dave's brain on the high seas of hell from our 75th season about three and a half
four years ago
and you can hear this
this is a rock and roll party church this is a this is a church that is for sin don't come expecting
no performance art satire dear god please yeah that ain't gonna happen it's not going to be
moral majority takeoffs my friend this is not a joke this is the one true church the last church
after relaxing a little bit of time i'm going to go to the church where i'm going to be spending the night
on the lake, Bob's ready to have a great time entertaining his friends. Right, Bob? Bob? Bob?
Bob?
There's no business
like show business
like no business
I know
everything about it
is appealing
everything that traffic
will allow
nowhere could you get that
happy feeling when you
are stealing that
extra bow
Bob, what a relief. How are you
doing tonight? His name is Bob.
Bob is not the illegitimate
son of Michael Jackson.
Take it.
Take it with me.
Here you see, it's not Mr. Bob.
Come on, how many? Come on, Bob.
How many posts do you take to spin the light bulb?
Bob? Come on, Bob. Come on.
Will seven be enough, Bob?
Watch out.
The bob, it's loose.
It's coming this way. Back, back.
I created you. Back, back.
No!
It's later than
you think.
The terrible spitting vengeance of
Bob's mighty staff shall
scour clean this planet and the
all-pervading radioactive
pestanche of his boundless supernatural love.
Wake up. Open your heart.
Drop your pants. Close your mind
and bend over because he'll be
kicking and taking names.
Dear brothers and sisters,
he'll be struggling and gasping. His face
will turn blue. Then Bob will pitch over on the floor
in the grip of a massive
coronary thrombosis.
And we will be there to see that event
and to record it for you.
And that's the way we live.
Name of time.
Don't you see that he's dead?
Wait a minute, Bob.
They try to say
things.
Don't leave me here.
They try to make
me say things.
Don't leave me here.
Well, now, you can believe that you're
not going
to hell. As a subgenius,
you can believe that you're not going
to hell. But, my friend,
you've got to face the fact
that you are in hell now! In hell now! Are you not? Do you not have to slave your butt
off for a damn job of some kind? Do you not have to pay income tax? Do you not have to
get the common cold and worse things that come from fornication? But should naturally
be without disease. Hey, hey, my friend, yes, you're in hell now. Your marriage may be hell.
Your lifestyle may be hell. You may be needing to change your lifestyle and quit taking them
so much, but you just can't. You just can't. Well, Bob's been in your shoes. Bob, understand,
Bob ain't telling you that you've got to clean up or nothing.
Bob's just telling you to get your ass in gear, son. Enjoy life like Bob. Frankly, you
know, the church of the subgenius is nonsense. I mean, it's triviality. It has no significance
for anything that anybody's going to care about for any length of time. You know, it
may be lots of fun, and I don't mean to belittle it as such, but when you're faced with a serious
situation, you've got a world that's on the verge of nuclear holocaust and the all-democratic
institutions in this country that haven't already vanished are under severe attack,
and when all of a sudden, you've got a world that's on the verge of nuclear holocaust,
it's like the world you're in. And so when some people are in trouble, we're going to
we've got to deal with as a church of the subgenius. I think what comes to mind as the
church of the subgenius, I've got to think that's one of the reasons we're in the trouble
we're in. Well, just to try and put the church of the sub genius to rest, those of you who
are not familiar with it, the church of the subgenius is essentially a group that, and
I'm sure that people will argue with me on this, but it's essentially a sort of a comedy
routine. I mean, they may have a philosophical point, but it's based on humor. There are articles
about it in John Rubenstein's, John Carroll's column in the Chronicle and things of that nature.
It's more or less a sort of a comedy affiliate.
It's about as politically weighty or less politically weighty than, you know, Saturday morning kids TV.
So there's nothing to it.
Okay.
Thank you.
It was a themopod of the beginning, but then, yea and lo, it became an if-a-pod.
Yea, he cometh in, he turneth on with the right hand, and yea, he turneth off with the left hand.
Yeah, now it may sound ludicrous.
It may sound ridiculous to many unbelievers out there.
It may sound impossible.
Satan is real.
Working.
In spirit.
You can see him.
And hear him.
In this world.
Every day.
Satan is real.
Working.
With power.
He can tempt you.
And lead you astray.
I attended service at a little church in the country not long ago.
A prayer was led.
By an old country preacher who then raised his hands as everyone stood and sang,
My God is real.
A warm breeze through the open windows brought in the smell of new mown hay in a nearby field.
And the singing of birds could be heard in the moment of silence as the preacher opened his Bible to read.
And then a little old man stood up, bent with age, his hair thin and white, and said,
Preacher!
Tell them that Satan is real too.
You can hear him in songs that give praise to idols and sinful things of this world.
You can see him in the destruction of homes torn apart.
I know that Satan is real.
For once I had a happy home.
I was loved and respected by my family.
I was looked upon as a leader in my community.
And then Satan came into my life.
I grew selfish and unneighborly.
My friends turned against me.
And finally my home was broken apart.
My children took their paths into a world of sin.
Yes, preacher, it's sweet to know that God is real.
And to know that in him all things are possible.
And we know that heaven is a real place where joys shall never end.
But sinner friend, if you're here today, Satan is real too.
And hell is a real place.
A place of everlasting punishment.
For a long, long years, stole many a man's soul and faith.
I was around when Jesus Christ at his moment of doubt and faith.
Made them sure that Pilate washed his hands and sealed his fate.
And I was pleased to meet you.
Hope you guessed my name.
Cause what's possible in you is the nature of my game.
And is your soul clean?
When the devil comes by your door.
Are you ready to meet the devil at the crossroads, my friend?
All hands on deck!
Are you gonna have what he demands in the way of...
I seek out a gift.
Dick, that's far too many.
We'll have to call you the Centipede Man.
Now sit down here. You're not the first experiment to fail.
I was waiting to be hanged in the morning.
But I didn't care about that.
I opened the door.
And there was the captain and his first mate.
I swung the hatchet, splitting the captain's head wide open.
I turned and nearly chopped off the first mate's head at the neck.
There was blood and gore everywhere.
And I was glad for what I'd done.
Or captain, look what he's done!
He's dead!
Ha!
Stand to, men.
Men, you swabbies there, stand to.
Oh, yes, I...
Murder on the high seas is no more or less a...
It's a moral act!
Lieutenant Smith, could you start the...
Off with his head! And scoop it out and put a candle in it!
And on with his new face, thanks to luxuriant and the beautiful skin treatment you can wear like a hat.
I see she's a virgin.
Are you, uh, two?
Ah, she looks like a used virgin, Tash.
Quite used.
In fact, you can smell her a mile and a half off, three fathoms away.
She's as used as a dog in heat.
You could smell her three fathoms under.
Ah, yes, you are of a mind to smell things in Poseidon's locker.
If you wanted to go to where the frozen food locker is.
And his body hung from the yardarm at the neck, and he dangled in the wind for the rest of the trip to the Americas.
Is that an albatross, sir?
No, Ponch, it's not an albatross. Had we seen an albatross, it would be viewed as an omen of good fortune.
I personally believe that... I personally believe that this is a fetish burden.
A need of Central America. It wouldn't be far off from the Cammy Isle.
And, uh, friends, we'll be right back to the hellish trip to deep inside Dave's brain.
Here on the Hour of Slack, Slack for everyone but Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Oh, testiculoids and lactators, it's an ESO radio subgenius night.
Or timeless day.
For inside Dave's water-filled head, there is no time and less money.
Chaz Smith, friends, Lonesome Cowboy Dave, and we will continue with the Devil on the High Seas of Dave's brain.
But first, credits, friends. That Sympathy for the Devil version was by Tia Matt, and you will be hearing the rest of that.
Satan is real.
It was by the Lauvin Brothers, posted to all binary Slack by Magma3.
Usopods and Themopods is by... and the Bub Dubs radio, old radio.
Ancient KPFA Berkeley sub-show of Hal Robbins, Puzzling Evidence, Gary Gabroke-Frame, and Bob Nelson.
Let Me Play My Music is Frank Marino and Mahogany Rush.
You also heard Pope Meyer, Pope David N. Meyer, the Pope of all New York, and myself, Reverend Ivan Stang, on this show.
And Media Barrage 10 remix, a subgenius CD.
And Ghost Riders in the Sky was by Dick Dale, my friends.
The ESO show, which is most of what follows, is broadcast from WCSB Cleveland State University, friends, every Thursday at midnight on the net at WCSB.org.
With host Chaz Smith, Lonesome Cowboy Dave, and now this beefy message.
You like beef?
Mommy, I'm scared of the clown.
Beef on the hook.
Beef by the pound, by the ton, and by the honey bun.
We got beef for ya at Tim and Terry's Slaughterhouse.
Stop in and we'll smack them down and deliver it fresh and piping hot, or creamy smooth, the way it's supposed to have been.
Mommy, the clown scares me!
That's alright, son. They're supposed to scare you.
The clown makes us laugh.
Yes, the clown takes away our fear.
Because it reminds us of our own absurdity.
Our own mortality.
The clown makes us laugh.
But the tightrope walker...
...inspires us.
Yes, the tightrope walker makes us fear death. Makes us fear death.
Shining in their silver suit in the spotlight high above.
We can't all be tightrope walkers.
On the center of radio.
Most of us have to be clowns.
Top-eyed, tickled teeth and his amazing dangling unit.
There's more clowns than acrobats.
Even before more stunts with his oops don't be in the buff than you've ever seen available or possible to any human-born woman.
You won't believe that something this hideous could survive.
But it's real. It's here. It's only 50 cents.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave. See him. Hear him. Smell him.
It's alive. It's real. It's Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
See the freak. See the hideous subversion of God's nature.
Step behind the curtain and see the freak. Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
I'm afraid of fire, man. Stop flicking that lighter at me.
Hey lady.
Ha ha ha. Look at the freak.
Yeah. Well if I looked like you did then I would be one to be pointed.
Yeah. Where'd you get that rouge, you old bitch?
Yeah.
Hey. Ah ah ah. Oh man. Come on, man. I got a little psych or something.
I'm just here...
It's kind of a little funny. Look at уч.
Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak.
Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak. Freak.
It's alright.
Oh Dave, how could things have gone so terribly wrong?
Once you were a strapping, young lad, with a peachy, dark complexion and miles and miles of good humor.
Man, look at you now.
Your testicles are dragging on the ground.
Crawling in your own pits.
It was a lot of fun back then, wasn't it?
You're wearing like I'm a skater.
There ain't a lot of money in New York City.
Yeah, man.
Those were the days.
What do you think you're doing else?
Now you have a spong the size of an elephant's trunk.
Freak!
Those were the days, man.
I was hung like a horse.
Why?
Oh, man.
Am I ever going to get out of here?
It's not cool.
And so Dave curled up inside the dumpster behind the jack-in-the-box.
A hated cold rain.
With the rain pouring down on his shivering bones
as he waited for Bob to come and deliver.
Hey, that's my spot.
What the hell are you doing?
Get the freak out of here.
Cut off your eyes.
Hey, hey.
Taking the abuse of passerbys.
What the hell are you doing?
Oh, man.
I can't live like this anymore.
No, no.
It's horrendous.
What am I going to do?
Hey, lady.
What are you doing over here?
It's just, just passing by.
Don't talk to that freak, honey.
Come on.
Hey, lady.
Wait, don't go.
Please don't listen to that guy.
Back here.
Dave.
Back here behind the curtain.
Take a good look at him.
He's got a good looking eye.
Take this envelope.
Go down to the pier.
This is a passage to America.
Just shut up and go now.
What's in the envelope?
Just shut up and go.
Give it to the man on the board.
He was able to escape London
and made his way to America
where he was adopted
by a tribe of Iroquois
who took him
into the sacred cave
of the bear
droppings.
And they showed him there the paintings
which predicted
that someday a cowboy would come
alone.
Him here.
And no white cowboy arrived finally.
Prophecy come true.
Better known as
Lord Sun.
Made their way through Wolf Pass
and we had a great sight.
There's your grandpa there.
He was quite a figure.
Knock him down.
Bring out the women
that they might receive
the seed of the bear.
The day of the mass sting.
He was brave.
I can't go all the way back.
No, no.
I'm going far enough.
No, no, no.
Come on, come on.
You gotta see the rest of the exhibit, Dave.
Just hunker down.
He'll get through it.
It's not a matter of moments.
And hence when the first wood teachers
came to our land.
And here's about four or five of us
attacking about three hundred of them.
No way, Dave.
No, no, no.
The tribe took them in as a god.
They worshipped him
tied to their totem pole.
Bring out the burning pot.
Okay, you guys.
They decided to feed him to himself
as an act of sacrifice.
Okay, now,
once you get the papadum
and they danced around the pot.
And the papayas.
As the lonesome Dave ate.
He's on his own train.
And you guys can all join in too.
Once I get down to below my navel,
I don't know if I'm gonna stop.
And here came the ballerinas.
Popping like a little pork.
Hundreds and hundreds of ballerinas
in pink foofloos.
Oh my god, I've never seen such a display
of hirsute masculinity.
The lady in the farthest corner of your left eye.
They're all she-males.
Appears to be wearing a, uh,
wolf-man suit.
Oh my god, they have no underwear.
This is disgusting.
Some sign of a walnut costume.
Halloween day hat
wrapped in a neck to the back of her shoes.
And as we can see from bottom under top,
the off-camera shot shows her undulating with Pappy
in the bar room beforehand.
And isn't it wonderful how she can move
the lower thing there.
But slowly the drug began to wear off.
And lonesome slowly awoke from his peyote-induced
trance of wonderful ballerinas.
And looked around him to see an altogether different reality.
Oh my god, I'm back in that thing again.
Oh, shush, shush.
Look at the freak.
Oh, he's getting sass.
Beautiful ballerina.
And then...
Remove his arms.
Remain calm.
And let them repeat the lies.
And reattach them.
Now you're out of sync.
The process is about to begin.
Now he will remove his head.
And reattach it.
Notice how we are able to keep his head alive.
All by itself, hooked up to these pumps and bellows.
That's quite a sandwich right there.
It comes with a side of slowing.
And if you'll check closely, Dave's ears are actually paranormal.
That's what they used to call in the old country.
He can actually hear sights and sounds below his own vision.
That is if he's looking at anything at all.
Look at that Aaron stare.
Let's scoop it out and put a candle in it.
Look at the freak.
He's a geek.
Look.
He'll eat a live chicken or veggie.
Don't look at that.
Hey Dave.
Hey Dave, come on over here.
Get a little closer to the window.
Can you hear me?
I can hear you just fine, man.
I got a little proposition for you.
See these things I got in my hand?
They glow in the dark.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
See that three of these things?
You hold them together like this.
And you can do anything.
You could be out of here in a matter of minutes.
See, Dave?
We have brought you here to pass on the sacred orb.
Dave, listen.
I'm trying to make it go away.
You have passed all the tests.
No, I can't look at you.
I won't pay attention.
He has even passed the sacred stone on his kidney.
No, I have not.
I have.
I've passed the sacred stone.
Oh my God, a bloody wad of my own existence.
Now prepare to receive the orb.
This is what I was made to use.
This is what I was born for.
Bend over, human.
I can't even repulse with my own legs.
Thanks for your attention.
The daunt.
The protuberance appears to have been clipped off
in one of the frost addresses.
And if we could see here the colon area,
also nice and shiny and clean.
Nurse, suture.
The second team of remnants of the toxic material.
Scalpel.
It just scooped out like this.
Give the vacuum cleaner.
Vacuum.
Vacuum cleaner.
Vacuum nurse.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to interrupt you.
You were playing golf while I was scoping out the patient's brain.
I was on the clamped hold.
Yes, clamped.
Hold it for him.
Where is that handle?
Suction.
Right here.
Five slabs.
Clamp.
And a little bit of cappuccino for the whole group.
Well, it looks like he isn't going to make it.
I don't think so.
I'm glad to say that we've wasted our time.
Let's go ahead and drink the cappuccino before it gets cold.
What about the next patient?
Do we have any of the same ones?
Let's move this one out before he gets cold.
He's going to start stinking.
I think he's going to wind up stinking.
He was already cold when we were out.
Yeah, yeah.
What was his name?
Dave?
A so-called lonesome cowboy.
They called him Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
He lived thousands of years ago.
He was a playboy of the streets.
A man with only one good rancid eye that did the work of many.
Lonesome Bovine Boy.
His legend lives today.
Across the great plains of Ohio.
Scrawled upon bathroom walls across America.
Rest areas across the highways.
And a plastic cathedral of hair somewhere in Oval and Ohio.
Truckers still fill the citizens' banderaves with his name.
Late into the night, he's prepared to end his own life.
To further his biopulchral purportions.
Roll on.
Yes, Dave finally achieved fame.
But at what price?
At what price?
Well, we'll be back on Larry King Live, talking about what price?
Fame and fortune.
You're on the air with Larry King Live.
Human.
Shut up.
Humans.
Wow.
What a great show.
A quick check into the background.
This man reveals that not only has he probably a remnant of the Pleistocene era or some bygone era like that,
But he's also well, well underdeveloped to intake.
And in comparison with other Pleistocene man's or woman's of his same peer group and function.
Look at the size of his head.
Here we see his liver and spleen are filled with tiny pieces of roots and drawings by inarticulate women.
Sometimes when the moon is right, blue artifacts emerge from the top of his skull.
All hands on deck! All hands on deck!
All hands off my dick!
Have you seen the white whale in the trousers of the Daveman?
Eh? You snobs? Have you seen the white whale?
Never mind, Captain. You're getting a hernia.
Sit down. You're going to disturb the town.
We'll see the whale.
Never rest till I see the whale.
The whale turned belly up in the sea.
Uh, Captain, I'd like to remind you that we are sailing on a kind of a psychoplasmic sea, if you will,
and the whale is bound to eat you alive.
No way around it, because he's got control of your mind.
Oh, I'm well aware, mate, that the whale is but a metaphor for me.
Oh, I go, ah, a metaphor.
Ah, a metaphor.
But I'll, I'll, hand me that harpoon and I'll go for it.
Well, Captain, I'm afraid I'm going to have to hand you the metaphor.
A metaphoric harpoon, if you will, because the real harpoon resembles a large, large packing paper tube.
However, on the other hand, it is a fine, a silver, a sterling steel harpoon capable of taking down any metaphoric whale.
Bend over, human.
Friends, bend over for Lord God, Lord God.
Bend over!
For human, God is coming.
Bend over, human.
I stuck around St. Petersburg
When I saw it was a time for a change
I killed the Tsar and his ministers
Anastasia, spring in vain
I rolled a tank at the general
Demonstrate
C size
Sell it
I swear you, it's the nature of my game
I watched with glee while your kings and queens
Fought for ten decades for the gods they made
I shouted out who killed the canadians
When after all it was you and me
Let me please introduce myself
I'm a man of wealth and taste
I lay traps for troubadours
Who get killed before they reach Bombay
Pleased to meet you, hope you guess my name
Cause what's passing you is the nature of my game
Oh you're my name
Aha, stepped into your dark rancor
Pleased to meet you, this hall I've fram
Oh you're my name
You're my name
Satan is real too
And hell is a real place
A place of everlasting punishment
Satan is real
Working in spirit
You can see him and hear him
In this world every day
Satan is real
Working with power
He can tempt you and lead you astray
You can see him and hear him
In this world every day
Satan is real
He can tempt you and lead you astray
Your blood is wild
And oxygen flows
By opposing these fines
You can't live as though it's all a,-
A S A S A Z A
A Y E T
A L L
D I G H
G o Y o U
S K I M
A S C O U L
I knew I'd end up here if I kept doing it.
But I just couldn't stop.
And now look what happened.
What you see is a hallucination.
A hallucination of what could be considered the testicular problems.
I thought it was funny.
You know, make fun of religion.
And spray paint them dog's heads in them graveyards and stuff.
I mean, it was just a satire. It was all a joke.
I guess I must have messed up real bad.
I guess if Southern Baptist was right after all.
Don't leave a mess where you go.
Leave a mess where you've been.
What good is this $90 going to do me here?
No!
Money means nothing.
The soul means nothing.
It took salvation to triple your money back.
I thought hell was a big joke.
I thought it was a big joke.
Hell is an illusion.
All my friends are going to be there, I used to say.
Hey, all my friends are here.
Dave!
Chaz!
Princess Wee!
What are you guys doing here in Cleveland, Wisconsin?
For eternity.
Well, we're not really here.
We're just kind of like a figment of your imagination.
It's part of the Dave brain.
Oh, what do you mean it's not real?
It's like matrix to the tenth power.
Just part of the Dave.
No, you mean me, my whole life, all of reality was all, all along.
It was just part of Dave's imagination, not my own.
You mean Dave?
Dave was the one who was holding it all together all along, but now he's waking up?
That's right, Sting, baby.
He's waking up and he's got a problem.
He's grown 400 pounds in the last half an hour.
His hypothalamus is the size of a large tubular object you might call that bowling alley down there by your shoe.
And he's ready to sting like a bee and smoke like a smoke thing.
If you're not ready when he's ready, there's the door.
It's smoked.
Will the Dave ever wake up from the dream?
And void.
Or will the dream wake up from Dave?
Wow, man.
Well, I, it was 1942, I think it was.
Dave, inside of Dave's brain, it's beautiful.
It's like your journey to the center of the earth.
God.
Now look at those stalactites.
It's a whole other world.
It's sparkling.
Those waterfalls.
Those mushrooms.
Those sunsets.
I think it was.
It really was.
Yeah, it was in Ocahontas.
Those galaxies.
Those signals.
Those eggs and stars.
Look.
Those mountains.
Those palm trees.
I forget what the hell it was.
It's like a black light poster.
Only it's alive.
It's a couple hours.
Those time lapse clouds and roses opening.
It's just a sign.
Oh.
Well, I'd love to.
But I'm not a human being.
Thank you.
You're an amazing.
You'd call a human being.
Wow.
I'm not really human.
Dave's brain is beautiful after all.
I, it's nothing like the hell that I imagined it to be.
Oh, it's so shiny.
It's like the planet Zeron.
And it's, it's, it feels like home.
Oh my God.
Look at the little cherubim.
Look off the top of the mountain.
In the distance scampering naked women.
He's drooling, but it's beautiful.
It's like a fountain of cherry candy drops.
Little magicians and sorcerers running around.
They're trying to put a little pointed hat on his head right now, but they don't know
they're putting it on.
Shines from land somewhere.
Littering leprechauns and piranhas resting under the mushrooms.
The most beautiful thing I've ever seen.
Uh oh.
Oh shit.
Who unplugged?
Who unplugged the shit, man?
Man.
Somebody tripped on the cord.
What the hell's what's oh my God.
Oh, I'm sorry guys.
I, I think I, who are you?
I think I pulled the plug on Dave.
Who are you?
All these years he's been in a coma ever since he was seven years old and fell into the lake.
Thought he could swim along with his dog.
They pulled him out.
Now he's a 50 year old man.
Oh my God, Ted.
What have they done to him?
Oh my God.
What have we done?
But he's still there.
It's all right.
He's alive.
He's still there.
Somewhere inside that head is the Dave brain.
Dave, Dave, come back to us.
It's been 43 years.
Dave, we missed you.
Beautiful, beautiful, beautiful.
I don't ever want to go swimming again.
I know he'll come back.
Look at him like a seven year old.
Dancing to weird techno beat music and bothering me.
Call me Davey.
I know he'll come back to me.
There's a mountain of markers in my closet arguing with him.
Oh my God.
He's not a guy.
He's a toothless old mountain guy.
He's only got one eye and he's pointing at me.
It's okay, Dave.
Things are souring now.
You've clicked your heels three times.
It's all right.
We're going home.
You've done your part.
Don't, don't.
It's over, Dave.
It's over.
You're starting to smell a little bit, but it's okay.
You can stop now.
It's okay.
No, really.
There is no more.
No more rapid eye movement.
No arms.
Wake up now.
Peace is yours finally, Dave.
Your rest has come.
They'll make a religion around you that will last for thousands of years.
They'll think that you died back there on that yard arm, but it won't be true.
You get to go home now.
It's part of the protection program offered by the powers that be.
If you believe in Dave.
I do.
If you believe in Dave out there, pick your nose.
Pick your nose for Dave.
Everyone who can hear me now.
You can do it.
Everyone with the sound of our voices.
Who can hear, join us as we pick our nose.
Just reach down there and stick your finger up there and then just twist it around.
Dave will come back.
Just twist it out.
It's working.
Take the mucus out of your nose.
He's coming back.
He's working.
Look at kids.
I can see it.
It's nice and quivering.
Kids.
He's picking.
His lips are quivering.
His ears are quivering.
Oh, he's dead again.
Oh well.
Figures.
Well, how long can we go on reanimating the guy who died five times in the last half an
hour?
It's like when a cat plays with a little lizard it finds down in Arizona.
Everything seems fun and then suddenly the lizard just sort of starts twitching.
Oh, my God.
Sure.
The cat tries to keep playing with it like it's OK.
But yes, you can tell there's something very wrong.
Very, very wrong.
Thank you.
Many say that the heartsick dog sought refuge with a tiny, tiddling poodle.
She gave him comfort and sheltered him in a tree to rest safely until needed by the show once more.
Giant eel.
That is very nice, dancing around in my mouth.
One way or another, she's going to get you, Doc.
Giant eel.
The squid, the live ones, their livers are quite small.
And the squids were very small.
It makes them difficult to handle, you know.
Ah, I see.
I was scrambling like crazy.
Oh, so nice.
So nice.
Oh, my.
Oh, so nice.
And it wobbles in my mouth.
If I had a nice cold beer.
I thought it was going to be really greasy.
This is so good.
It's really good.
It's like jelly.
This is wonderful.
Look at the fat.
Lobster brains.
Oh, my.
And it wobbles in my mouth.
All kinds of different streaks.
This is wonderful.
Look at the fat.
Lobster brains.
Oh, so nice.
What is that?
He doesn't know what he's doing.
Oh, my.
Oh, so nice.
And it wobbles in my mouth.
And it wobbles.
And it.
I thought it was going to be really greasy.
And, friends, that was Thelonious Squid by, by Champion Jack Codini from Altbinaries Slack.
Thank ya'll.
And for more on that,
check www.subgenius.com.
Sub kokod nichts wait.
I love you.
Aware, F-3.
Damn, that hurts.
I don't know, that is real flavor.
ESO Beach Party?
The beach ball is filled with a sleck of hydrogen.
And each and every one Sunday,
Yanny Funny and Ned Funky Cheller
is down with everything else he's done.
It's a first and annual beach party bunkajunkie.
There is truly the rest of the grave.
I'll bring the beach balls if you bring the cornstarch.
I'll bring the...
I'll bring the Saturn boosters
if you bring the...
If you bring the ocean.
I'll bring the sodium nitride pellets.
I'll bring the Apollo spice capsule if you bring the sand.
I'll bring crashback if I get old again and die.
Can you please loan me it?
I'll bring lonesome cowboy Dave
if you'll just get out of my hair,
shut up and go die.
And I'll bring your hair back.
Time to get out of here.
One wave, my magic wand.
We gotta leave the Dave brain for another week.
Thank God.
But it'll be there.
Oh, I'm afraid it will.
Pulsing like a diamond.
You'll think it's not there.
I heard that Dave died on your show, man.
That guy's out there.
That guy is totally out there.
That guy's so...
Man, where does he get that stuff?
Where do you...
Man, what is that dude on?
Where do you find that thing?
Where did you find that Dave thing?
How'd you get that all the way up there?
How you gonna get that out of there?
Yeah, well, I guess you can't believe
he's got the whole thing in.
Oh, is that a foot?
What's hanging out of the...
Did you sit on somebody's whole body?
What's that bullet Dave thing?
That's an animal.
I thought it was a human foot.
It's as big as a human foot.
But vomit, that's not what that is.
Oh, look, it's growing again.
Yolly, yolly, yolly, yolly, yolly, yolly.
Yolly, yolly, yolly.
Yolly, yolly, yolly, yolly, yolly.
Until next week, keep your hat on tight.
You're back to the wind and you're sacking the saddle there.
There's always tomorrow for dreams to come true.
So believe in your dreams.
Come what may.
I read that right.
There's always tomorrow.
Come what may.
There's so much to do.
We have no highs.
And so little times.
You'll see with our minds.
We have no good nights.
We all pretend the rainbow has an end.
And you'll be there, my friend, someday.
There's always tomorrow for dreams to come true.
Tomorrow is not far away.
This never happened.
There's always tomorrow for dreams to come true.
So believe.
This never happened.
It's time for school.
We now return to your television set to you
until next week at this same time
when the control voice will take you to
The Self Genius Hour of Swag.
Friends, you are listening to
the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Swag.
Here's our address.
Got that pencil ready?
P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
That's where you send things to me to play.
The show, The Hour of Swag,
is the voice of the Church of the Subgenius.
More about that at www.subgenius.com,
which includes...
a catalog of books and other things.
Friends...
...
And the moon will be rich as well
As mayor of the Monskin City
In the county of the land of Oz
I welcome you most legally
But we've got to verify it legally
To see
If she
Is morally, ethically
Spiritually, physically
Positively, absolutely
Undeniably
And reliably
Is this podium twister?
I hate this moment
What I want to do is
Start the show with a prayer
Something about
A great big nose
They don't call it that
A poor, empty palm
On air
It only takes about a minute
Oh
Excuse me, Mr. Mayor
I've got a couple minutes
For your speech here
Go ahead