What does the phrase number one record mean to you?
The entertainment industry is about money.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to...
The self-genius.
So I cried.
See that?
Uh-huh.
That's when all of a sudden he had the difficulty in the third inning.
And those people over there are people who act like a fool when I...
A thousand right-wing talk show hosts in a row talking about how the right-wing talk show host is endangered by the liberal controlled media.
Owned by Westinghouse.
Well, you can get...
You can...
When you have a subgenius radio show, you can not only steam and bitch and piss about it.
You can go in there and type up some...
Nasty little bitter, hate-filled, absolutely awful just rant.
Then you can take it back.
Then you take a walk around the lake, have a froth stick or something.
Then you come back and make it funny, right?
You take out all the bitter...
Well, you take out the unfunny bitterness.
Let's put it that way.
And then you can...
Boy, you've got a soapbox.
It may be that nobody's listening at all.
But who cares as long as you think they do?
Faith is all that counts, friend.
It's just like Dr. Legumes.
He said, you know, when that spike is coming down towards your hand,
the faith is the only thing that counts.
In fact, when X-Day happens, this is a little-known piece of doctrine.
But, you know, people have asked us,
well, when the aliens come to rupture the subgeniuses up and destroy the pink world,
do...
You say it's at 7 a.m., July 5th, 1998.
Well, where does that start?
I mean, is it 7 a.m.?
7 a.m. is different times in different places.
I'm here to put your mind at ease.
It actually will start, according to Bob's memos,
at the International Date Line,
which happens to fall across the Pacific Ocean.
The first subgeniuses to be ruptured up will be the ones in Micronesia.
The Earth, the saucers will basically hover in place over the Earth,
and as the planet turns underneath it,
they'll zap up people as it hits 7 o'clock.
It eats.
Now, that means those of us in America can watch the Europeans getting ruptured and destroyed on television.
So far, so far...
Now, of course, people have said,
now, where are we going to have the big X-Day gathering for all the American subgeniuses?
You know, there's got to be a place.
Yeah, Ben, I think so far, Brushwood is the perfect place.
It means that a lot of us...
We just have to come from California.
You really are dangerous like you, baby.
I've got to admit it.
Sugar.
Mom.
Hey, Ben, watch out for that UFO.
Sugar.
Mom.
Sweet farm bird,
You're economist more expensive because you weren't
across country and culture
there.
You have never seen another because of very different reasons.
Uh huh.
Um, I also have the doctor's office to check on them.
Ah.
Right.
And lift your VE
Alien
Antoid
Succubus
Alien
Antoid
Succubus
Oh, Megan, you won't be able to tell the difference at all.
We cite goddesses partly because it sounds better to our primary market,
which I'm sorry, you know, it's pretty obvious.
But it's also because they only have one chromosome.
You could not call them male.
Female is the closest thing.
But they'll look like anything you want.
You could be sitting there.
Well, I wrote a 40-page essay about what my ideal experience on the escape vessels would be,
and my fellow editors made me cut it because it was too limiting.
It was too juvenile.
It was too ordinary.
It was like all the undergrads.
Underground comics, movies, you know, babes, whatever.
Food.
Actually, it was mainly food, now that I think about it.
That may have been part of the...
You know, as Bob said, give me slack or give me food.
Or kill me.
I'm starting to feel that way right about now.
Stop.
Stimulate my system.
Electronic erotica is only a fever away.
Sigou...
ber...
The magic that'll fill the ground
It's an orgasmic pleasure, keeps coming
Machines keep humming
As the time walks and dances
Into a dreamland of dreams
I love to be naked
The microtech jumps up the entire soundscape
For autonomy
Alien, android, succubus
I'm coming
Thank you, Thighmaster
Alien, android, succubus
You please
Hello
Arknights
Oh no
ättİ
Do you know the technology
Nope
Uh, yes, dear friends, hello!
That was Alien Android Succubus from OBE, Out of Band Experience.
And you can get more OBE.
What a pleasant, pleasant band they are, too.
By calling, in this case, you make a phone call to 1617-LICK-OBE.
That's 1617-LICK-OBE.
They've got CDs and cassettes and so forth.
You can get their free information from them about that.
And now it's time to go on with the rest of our subgenius show.
The Alien Android Succubus was intermixed there with the wacky
Ex-Day and Sex Goddesses rant from Starwood Radio.
So we're going to have a real wacky, crazy, nutty subgenius show,
just like we always do, and nobody will get hurt, we promise.
Ooh!
Here we are.
How does it look? Pretty good, huh?
It's the pause now.
I don't know why.
I feel so happy.
I think three of you are just what they are as sexual persons.
And by the way, before we start, I'd like to introduce you to a real expert on sex.
The guy who taught me everything I know.
My wife.
Jeanette.
He always introduces me as an expert.
What a babe!
But I don't claim to take any credit for this knowledge,
as I didn't know much either.
Anyway, I'm in the studio listening to what he has to say today.
And I hope his comments will help me to communicate.
Well, thanks, Jeanette.
And now that we've both established the fact that he really is an expert,
we can say any damn thing that we please without any experts contradicting us.
And so I'd like to start with a kind of a simple idea.
One that I think it took us all our lives to learn.
And this is that sexual intercourse is not what you do.
Sexual intercourse is not what you do.
It's not the things that you learn.
It doesn't have anything to do with techniques or positions or anything of this kind.
What?
Sexual intercourse has to do with what you are.
We have a journey.
I would like to give you the chance to know about our love.
I will treat you to that.
I will feel about your son.
I will feel about our child.
And how the kids are.
All of these things are part of what you are.
And all of these things come to bed with you
and make love with you every time that you leave.
I love you.
Oh, the happy moments.
Yeah, it goes to bed.
Yeah, we have our happy time down here.
Let's drink up that espresso.
It's a hap hap happy day.
You are here.
Whee!
While others may toil unrelentingly on publication projects.
Happy.
Yes.
So is here.
Yeah, it's, it's, yeah, right like you said.
I'm so happy.
Well, you could think of the show as an eager puppy.
I guess.
Why is it that these little crawlers are never satisfied with the content of the program
and you only command something.
I don't know if it's a favorite organ, but this is the happy segment.
Okay, begin happy segment now.
It's a happy day.
La la la la la la.
Pardon me.
Oh, I'll get it.
Can you get that?
Somebody get that.
The sun is shining.
It's a happy day show.
It's all about getting it.
I'm not here.
Everything's about to change.
Okay, I'm not here either.
Is the machine on?
The phone rings and you get it.
All right.
I think it, I think it stopped ringing.
I think it's okay.
I knew you'd get it in the end.
Hey, why don't you answer the phone, ma'am?
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry, I can't move out of my wheelchair.
That phone is, is tormenting me.
You should hear something.
It's like that, it's like that phone back in the knob, man.
Keep America ringing all day long.
Watch Truth Will Come a-Winging on a song.
I'm not here.
Smile while the phone is ding-dinging.
Carry, carry your car.
Keep the melody ringing and singing in your heart.
Hello.
Hi.
Hello there.
What's seeking?
Huh?
Hey, look.
Uh, you got that 30 pound codfish underneath the living room couch?
What's this?
Who's this?
You got the wrong number.
Oh, wait a minute.
Larry?
Huh?
Larry.
No, this, this is Larry.
This is Larry.
You got the wrong number.
Is this the Moose Dough residence?
No.
You got an American flag on your window?
I have a no.
I have a no American flag on my window.
Oh.
Well.
Uh, I got this 30 pound codfish, see?
And I'm looking to sell it.
You interested?
Well.
Strictly out of the county, you understand.
You just got the wrong number, mister.
You got a funny, what are you talking to?
Huh?
What?
What's going on?
You got...
You got the wrong number, mister.
You got a funny...
Hello?
Uh, hello?
Yeah?
Now, listen.
I only want to say this once.
We got your dog, and if you want him back, you'll put 25 dollars in a plain envelope and
leave it at Brigham's at 1145 tomorrow.
What?
Look.
Can I...
I don't want to say this any more than I have to.
Look, take the dog and stick it up your...
Hey, listen.
Listen.
You listen.
You want us to kill the dog?
Kill him.
You did it, bastard. Kill him.
Why?
Don't you want him?
You did it.
Listen.
You kill him.
That's what you do.
That dog is worth at least $100.
Well, good for you.
You sell him.
You want him killed?
Kill him, you'll do it.
You don't care about him?
Why don't you kill him?
Why should I?
Why shouldn't you?
Because you can't kill an animal like that.
Well, you want to kill him. You said you'd kill him.
I don't want to kill him. I want the money.
Yeah, well, you're not going to get neither.
Why not?
You're not going to get the money, all right?
$5?
You're not going to get anything.
I got to eat.
My kids have got to eat, right?
So you want to kill a dog, right?
You're a dog napper.
Look, man, I tried to get a job.
You're a dog napper, right?
I found him.
Come and work for me.
You want a job?
What?
You work for me. You want a job?
You give me a job?
Yeah, I give you a job.
Do what?
Meet me at the bar at the same place.
What do you give me?
A job to do.
What do you care?
You want to eat?
Your kids got to eat, right?
Well, wait.
I got to know what I'm going to do, you know?
What do you care if your kids got to eat?
You're still a dog.
Well, wait.
Is it going to be legal?
What?
I ain't got to kill nobody.
I don't.
I'm not worried about you killing nobody.
Then why can't you tell me what you want me to do?
What do you care as long as you get paid for it?
Well, I want to know.
Is it going to be...
I want to do decent work, you know?
You want to do decent work?
Yeah.
You didn't do a decent thing then, did you?
Well, maybe not.
Yeah.
Well, wait.
You're going to tell me you've never done anything indecent in your life?
No, I'm not going to tell you anything.
I'm going to tell you something.
The ringing of the bells.
Of the bells, bells, bells, bells, bells, pals.
Palsy of the ringing of the dinging of the bells.
You know, Richard Belzer is a good comedian.
Hear the horrid bells, alarum bells.
What a tale of tinge and abulation there.
Kiss the promise he does.
Is that phone fidelity?
Did I get that phone fidelity thing right?
Did I get that show fidelity thing right?
I got fidelity.
I went to a natural born cat.
Show us again.
Show infidelity.
Since you last called us?
Yeah.
I mean, I mean, Gobi called me at 4.30 in the morning our time to tell me that she had
seen that movie and it made her feel like going out and killing and she wanted to know
which kind of firearm I should, I kid you not.
Wow.
So I was impressed, but I doubt if I'll see it because I think it's just pedantic.
It's not just the good ones anymore.
It's not like Logan's run or anything.
Well, it's like watching news in MTV style.
Who cares?
Potato gun.
To work on such a project is wonderful.
To have a set watch.
No dogs in helicopters.
I think Mickey and Mal were used for Magnum, didn't they?
Project.
Magnum oatmeal.
Potatoes.
Magnum.
Drops.
Yeah, it's a cough drop, right?
Magnum, that mossy detective on TV.
Magnum cough drop.
Emil and das cough drop.
Okay, now we have.
We have an error in the first part of the show.
You got a buzzer too.
Oh, okay, go ahead.
They're all in there.
The dinosaurs are all in back of the pen.
Yes, there they are here on Dinosaur Island.
That whole scene at the beginning of Jurassic Park is so fake.
It doesn't take a lot of guys with rifles.
You just say over here and the dinosaurs get in the pen.
Slow people.
Here boy, jump up.
Jump up boy.
That's right.
Good boy.
You just need an island secure enough for them to jump because sometimes when 10 of those guys are jumping off the stools in the cage, man.
Yeah.
Well, sometimes.
Man, this is Oregon, man.
They do their best thinking there.
Between their two stools.
So did you get a volume four yet?
We haven't done a two stool show for a decade or so.
All the women.
What did you say?
Did you?
Phineas Narco has the floor, the microphone and part of the phone.
I believe the chair has the table.
The table has the floor.
Stop chewing on the end papers and come to your conclusion.
Well, I was wondering if Poe Wing heard my volume four yet.
No, you haven't sent it to me.
No, he didn't.
But Doug Smith did.
And he even created a show for his show called Aunt Bertha versus the Head, which has already been broadcast.
Oh, right.
All right, man.
Yes.
And listening there to the KPFA subgenius show in Berkeley with Dr. Howell and Puzzling Evidence.
And Phineas Narco.
Phineas Narco is the caller.
Interspersed there with a nice old classic prank call section.
We don't know who did it, who perpetrated it, called Dog Napper.
An unusual prank call in that there's not too much cussing in it that I had to remove.
We need your help in identifying a pedestrian killed on 285.
285.
Screw you.
Yeah, that's an unusual prank call in that the erstwhile victim of the pranker turns the tables and sort of wins the game.
285.
Now, what we're hearing in the background here is Silica Jell's piece, Master of the Game.
Between Old Dixie Highway and Connelly Drive.
Drive.
D selvice Exec for27.
Breathe to Doe Laveel-
Doe Laveel-
can get going. Oh, me getting going is always such a long shot. But I've been a little upset
about something lately, listeners. I mean, every TV news bite lately has been about D-Day. Hey,
what about X-Day? It's a little over four years away, kitties. Four years before the X's towards
come down to smear the human race off the face of the earth like a booger on a pants leg.
Oh, you'd think they'd care. You'd think they'd be concerned about the coming global apocalypse.
But no, they'd rather sit back on their withered butts and talk about how they defended freedom
and the cause of white bread values 50 years ago. And then they turn a blind eye to the near future
and the onrushing Holocaust.
Oh, from the signs in the current media retchings, you couldn't tell the doomsday clock has ticked out
another year in the 666 mile an hour demolition derby road race to human Armageddon. Well, honey,
I'm Armageddon excited just thinking about it. I can whiff a stench of fried pink flesh in the air
already. But let me let you in on something. A lifetime supply isn't that good a deal.
But the cosmic sweetness and light tone of the media's view of the future rings as hollow as a
politician's promises. Oh, sure. There was the stand a few weeks ago with its warmed over Vegas
set from that Limburger Lily cool world. But it sure wasn't like what Bob told us X day would be
like. I don't think X day is going to be a feel good Christian fundamentalist survivalist,
martyr pistol porn hug fest. And what an ineffectual Prince of Darkness they have. I mean, he couldn't
morph worth a damn cheesy effects. Only one crucified guy on a billboard to after a lot of build up. And
the big payoff sucked. We got treated to way too much of Stephen King's gerbil face good looks. You
know, at least we got to see Miguel Ferrer plug the scenery knowing Ray Walston in the gut with hot
lead. But
still, I was unsatisfied. The black and white plot line pointed out the limited vision of their theology. It's either good or it's evil. It's either God or it's Lucifer. I mean, where's Bob in their equation? Bob wasn't involved in the stand because he was setting himself up with a car carrying tithing subgeniuses on the escape vessels. Thank you.
Oh,
yeah, but the stand sure went over big with a family values types because every Bubba's boy sure could identify that armchair macho Frontier feeling. Oh, they can't wait till the end of the world as they know it to come so they can legally take pot shots at us in the name of their Lord. I say the more the pinker, the bigger the sphincter. This is what they're made of. They'll be easy prey when the excess mom down like spring wheat.
Too bad they won't be more of a challenge because they will be our entertainment.
Oh, yeah.
We'll be off with Bob watching this pink human worms duking it out to the crawling spasming near death even before they face the excess abattoirs up there for our pleasure on the big wall size view screens.
All in feely vision since around and every seat and Bob's theater has its own armrest fingertip burst. Oh pain control buttons. Oh, they'll be looking like the number two scrambled eggs and pork brain special at a greasy spoon diner.
Ha ha.
Oh, yes.
Oh, I feel so wonderful.
Vengeance is a beauty treatment.
Oh, and I'm in this fight for life or what's left of it at least.
And I'm going to see to it that you at least live before you die.
Oh, there'll be a certain percentage of unsafe subgeniuses who won't make it off planet.
Oh, of course.
That's just because they didn't think their lives were worth that measly membership fee.
Oh, and the rates will soon be going up too.
There's a postage increase and we're not a tax exempt church.
No, we stand for profits.
Even though we don't ever seem to be.
I'm not sure we'll be making any.
But still, with faith in Bob, I'll at least have a good time of it.
We'll see to it that you reap reams and reams of pure, easy, light slack.
Oh, would you rather be separated like a fool from his money or like the wheat from the chaff?
You can get more flies with honey than with vinegar.
Oh, but you can get all of the flies with slack.
If you lack slack.
Get it back, Jack, by writing to the Subgenius Ministries International Headquarters in the sprawling mega-burb of Dallas, Texas, where slack is more precious than ever.
Oh, the church is still thriving underground beneath their very repressive feet.
Yet still, the bonded federal employees are mindlessly delivering the mail to the sacred P.O. box like everything's okay.
They haven't got their orders.
They haven't got their orders to disrupt vital church communications.
But it's only a matter of time before they crush that vital lifeline.
Oh, so, sisters and brothers, hearken to my voice.
And before it's too late for you, write for more information on how you can save your ass from the coming Holocaust.
Grab a pencil or write in the dust of your shattered existence there the name Bob.
Oh.
P.O. box.
1-4-0-3-0-6.
Dallas, Texas.
75214.
Oh, send a stamped self-addressed envelope to the sacred P.O. box.
And before you know it, you'll be slurping up frop and Fritos on board the escape vessels of the P.O. box.
you'll than I am gorgeous around ghosts who sunbathe and
with all your new sub-genius friends.
Noooo amth рядом with rats.
Mo organize your storm to find occupational members of
Pardon me?
The pills?
Oh, you want those pills.
They always talk about it.
I heard about the Bob pills.
You never come down from one of those Bob pills.
You've got to be careful not to take too much the first time
because it's not going to wear off.
What's inside, and sometimes we have actually had
the fabled legendary bucket of pills at revivals.
Frankly, there wasn't enough of a budget for that at this one.
But we would, and have done this in the past,
we have a bucket of little gel caps, actually big gel caps,
and we cast them into the audience generously.
Now, what's inside those pills is the same thing
that's inside.
It's inside the head of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Oh, that's right.
We changed the dogma about what was inside his head.
Now we're going to have to put that horrible poison
inside those pills.
Oh.
Slack!
You slap yourself!
Slack me on your wildest dreams!
Buy now and slap!
You have the power to find slack!
Good something for nothing!
Credit cards are taken!
Slack!
Send cash!
I want more slack!
Send your money now!
Conspiracy denied me again!
Send your money!
I will have my slack!
Your slack's open and here!
Slack!
Not your money!
We use your slack!
You slack!
Is that good?
You're very old!
All sorts of slack!
Every time, slack imaginable!
You slack!
Is that good?
You're very old!
All sorts of slack!
You slack!
Every time, slack imaginable!
Slack!
Slack from the other side of the world!
Attack!
Slack from right next door!
Here you are, Slack town, my dear! Slack town, my lady!
You Slack, my dear, my now!
Use the Slack!
We have used the Slack!
I'll number three!
I want my Slack!
Who in Slack will find recognition with the fruit of order?
Use Slack!
Slack!
If you have the chance, you can have your Slack.
Money in Slack.
Something for nothing.
Slack is great!
Slack.
Slack is government control.
For your home.
protection. I want more slack. Slack is not for everyone. You cannot take my slack away.
Slack can be taken by prescription.
Yes, dear friends, used slack there. Some used slack left over from our good friends
out-of-band experience, or OBE, which you can reach by dialing.
If you're interested in their types and CDs, and you should be, you can call up old Reverend
Bill Miller at 1-617-LICK-OBE. Easy enough, right?
And other times, you know, it's like you've done that, right?
So, I guess the point of the subject is the matter of the speech, I suppose, but you're
damned if I know of, like, anything of pink.
Later on, I feel like you can sit there.
You're blue, right?
So, yeah, I guess, like, you know, I started feeling real good about myself again, you
know, because it's like, man, I got my car going again, and stuff is all right.
I felt like, you know, you know, screw it, man, if you don't like it, you know.
So, something...
Me, man.
Yeah, so something me.
Like, I don't care what it was.
Like, sue me or blow me, I don't care.
But, I do remember this.
Please, man.
I don't remember what I'm feeling now.
They're not really doing a very good job tonight, are they?
The whole thing was because they were, like, invaded by, like, this poisonous kind of thing.
It was a big pus ball.
I was going to Jacksonville to buy a green green bag for a friend of mine.
Now, y'all know the mystical components of a green green bag.
Green green green green green green green green green.
I love that song.
Black cat balls.
A lamp in our gym.
Four kinds of feelings.
And a magic mushroom.
You don't want to get it over here, do you?
All right, baby.
So, they said they'd take the old green green bag and put it on a man's doorstep after Epiphany Day.
You know what?
What's he doing?
If he don't come back and die the very next day, then it don't work and come back again.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave here.
And Chaz, I think, going on about the green green bag there.
On WCSB Cleveland.
It's the blues, my friend.
It's retarded.
I don't make noise.
Let's get them balls.
I'm going here.
I'm so going here.
Don't look back through the glass.
I don't know where you're going.
I'm out here.
Out here.
Then at the restaurant, there was crews packed in brief ice and they had to stop mice.
But that old green green bag must have not worked too good because the very next day, the cats come back and it was alive.
dale whoения
I'm gonna be the last man
And his spirit is stucked in that old Greek rib bag just to make one old woman die
Put a curse on me
Did one times three
Three times three
Got nine lives
But y'all gonna die
Three times three
And this reminds me of when we found my daughter's cat's skeleton this morning, yes
It's been, uh, this will be the third dead cat we've found on this radio show
Over an eight year period
We're all gonna die, friends
And end up little wads of wet fur on the ground
The only recognizable piece of a cat you can see is the skull
And the fur
It had been rained on a bit
We don't know what happened to Princess
But, well, we know she's dead
You know it could happen to you any time, my friend
You may tie your shoes this morning
But the Undertaker may tie them tonight
Are you ready to meet Bob?
Move here for my man
That's him
He's here
Here he comes
That's him
He's here now
The All-Knowing Big
The All-Knowing Bee
Let me tell you something.
Asked Bryce
The All-Knowing Bee
Ask Frank.
Call Frank.
Ask him.
Even facts, Frank.
We must ask.
I hear him now.
We must.
Ask Frank.
Call Frank.
Even facts, Frank.
Nah, don't mess with Frank, man.
He'll tell you.
Yeah, I think the thing to do is to ask R. Stevie more about the all-knowing Bean.
Bean.
And that's who that is.
That's R. Stevie Moore.
The famous first of the independent crazy men, one might say.
And you can write for those crazy rhythms from R. Stevie Moore's cassette club at...
Captain Beefheart.
What?
At...
Let's get this going up right here.
Yes, R. Stevie Moore.
At 429 Valley Road.
That's 429 Valley Road in Upper Montclair, New Jersey.
Yes, he's still there and still cranking it out.
At Upper Montclair, New Jersey, 07043.
429 Valley Road, 07043.
Gosh, this music is just so...
I don't know.
It's inspiring in some peculiar way.
And it just makes me...
I'm so happy-go-lucky, you know?
It's so...
It's some subgenius or something.
It's something like that.
Let's see what Dr. Howell and Puzzling Evidence have to say about Aunt Bertha and the nuclear war.
Thank y'all.
Uh, sure.
Billy.
Follow along in your script.
Billy and Timmy are poking through the nuclear rubble.
Looking for candy bars in the radioactive slant.
Billy and Timmy turn left on Central Street.
Aunt Bertha, blinded by the flash, uses them to guide her through the rubble.
Aunt Bertha's leg is pinned in PS-127's doorway, collapsing upon her during the blast.
Also, Aunt Bertha was a victim of a shower of glass from the windows of the school, which embedded itself in her elderly flesh.
The buzzer of the school continues to sound.
As Aunt Bertha...
Lies writhing on the ground pinned by the front species.
And the speaker says over and over again, today is August 12th, 2076.
Which is odd, because it's only 1996.
Wow.
So scary.
And you know, a coleopterist or beetle-like race will dwell in humanity's disused cities.
That beetle is a beetle.
Yes, these neotenous beetles.
Somebody get that phone.
They're fetal beetles, as our caller pointed out.
Oh, oh, just a moment.
We'll continue with our fetal-beetle recital in a moment.
At first.
Picture if you will.
A lone outcast spurned by his so-called peers, coddled by his fawning mother, berated by his masculine father, and lost in a world without slack or meaning.
His name, Doug Smith.
A lonely child in an average home in an average town on a lonely planet called Earth.
His fate, to be swept up in the pre-apocalyptic world of the mighty church of the subgenius.
None know why he alone is...
chosen.
For none can fathom the myriad plots of this most devious of cults.
But even the spawn of the...
normals...
must bow and bend beneath the moronic will of J.R.
Bob Dobbs.
In a story we are forced to call,
A Pink Boy Comes to Bobolon.
Last week, Doug realized his dream. He became a member of a worldwide religious cult.
More than that, he was gifted with an actual ordainment as a high priest.
And doctor of forbidden science.
Now he feels full of fervor and belonging as he sets out in a seemingly brighter world.
Armed with the word of J.R. Bob Dobbs and his lackey editor, Reverend Ivan Stang.
This week, episode four.
Now, upon this block, I'll found my church.
The scene? A dingy and damp strip mall in a seedy rundown portion of an average American town.
Too bad there's only three stores left open.
I...
I am the Bob man, Cuckoo Cachoo.
Join the Church of the Subgenius or face bubbling, icky, cosmic space vengeance, puny ones.
The world ends tomorrow and you may die if you don't give up Bob his props.
The Church of the Subgenius offers eternal salvation or triple your money back.
What do you say to that?
Damn! No one's here yet.
Hey, none of the stores are even open.
Oh yeah.
It's Sunday.
Uh, guess I'll go get a chili dog and wait.
Later that day, Doug returned, his heart full of fire and his stomach churning with indigestion.
Okay, now this place is open and jumping with the after church crowd.
All right.
Hear ye sinners! The hour of judgment is at hand.
Your only hope of salvation is me and Bob.
And do you know how you can be saved when the saucers come?
Well, here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna tell ya.
For just 20 bucks, that's right, 20 bucks, you'll save yourself from the end of the world.
That's right.
And if you donate now, we'll save your pet gerbil too.
After all, you gotta have some extra pleasure when the sex goddesses get boring.
Remember, just 20 bucks or triple your money back.
Do I hear an amen, brother?
Crap!
No one is paying any attention.
Uh, I'll switch to plan C.
Let's see, it's in my notes somewhere.
Uh, uh, uh, okay.
Yeah!
Ah!
You all burn in laser fire unless you give it up to Bob!
The true path to salvation is through slack and a small donation to this ministry.
It's all true.
Two weeks ago, it was a pathetic wimp, but Bob died with...
And now you're a pathetic crazy wimp!
I heard that.
I see you going into that dollar store.
You think plastic owls on your, on your lawn are, are gonna protect you when the, when the...
Uh, uh, when the saucers land?
Uh, uh, oh friends, be, be sore afraid at that which you see.
Uh, uh, uh, must come to pass, does come to pass because you'll be up the creek without a paddle.
Up your butt with a coconut!
You suck!
Uh, uh, you all wish you had a coconut up your butt when the aliens, uh, uh, um, this, this isn't working.
Uh, curse you, Bob, I'm closing my eyes.
And when I open them, I want a flock of followers to do my deviant bidding.
Praise Bob!
Ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay.
Woof!
Ah, nothing but a bunch of dogs.
Hey!
You look kind of friendly little fella.
Uh, uh, eww!
Yuck!
Over my leg, just like Dad.
Stupid, stupid dogs!
Woof!
You people, you stinking zombies!
You normals!
Woof!
Ow!
That's it, I'm getting another chili dog, uh, uh, and come back after the effects of their recent religious brain spew wears off.
Returning from his nitrate-filled repast, Doug repeats his previous promise.
He's a little bit of a failure, hoping for an act of GHVH1 to change the outcome.
Alright.
One more try.
Hey, people!
Look here.
I'm trying to save you, okay?
You and your stupid, pathetic souls.
You know what it's like to boil in your own fluids for all eternity?
Well, neither do I.
But I'm sure it's not fun, and for a measly 20 bucks, you don't have to worry about boiling in fluids.
After all, what good are fluids if you don't share them with someone else?
Yeah.
So, uh, for 40 dollars, I can let you soak in smegma with someone you love.
So, so how about it?
Come on, or I'll hit you with my chubby stick!
Hey, mister, your fly's open.
Huh?
Timmy, get over here.
That man's not right in the head.
That's right.
I'm crazy.
Crazy.
Mad.
Cuckoo for Cocoa Puffs with the power of, uh, uh, of, of, uh...
Excuse me?
What?
I was just wondering how your apocalyptic message ties in with what was foretold by the prophet.
Ezekiel.
Uh, um, uh, uh, come again?
The prophet Ezekiel.
And your message today.
How are they related?
Um, uh, I'm not sure what you mean.
Never mind, never mind.
How does your religion correlate with the anarcho-matriarchal societies of far-off and ancient Sumatra?
Um, uh, I think it's here in the stark fist.
Uh, uh, hold on, hold on.
Uh, uh, nope, not here.
Uh, nope, uh, sorry, nothing about Sumatra.
Lots about sex, Atlantis, and Tibet, though.
Then fear for your soul, unenlightened one.
I'm Jeff Smith.
I bid you peace.
Uh, what the hell was that all about?
Uh, I guess I'll go get another chili dog before they close.
Doug approached the sardonically simple Pinewood fast food stand where he has been consuming beef byproducts all day under the cruel, capricious sun.
Uh, one chili dog, please.
Uh, with extra relish.
Uh, you, uh, want onions with that, boy?
No.
How about some kraut?
Uh, sour that is.
No! All I want is a chili dog!
Ah, it's you!
What the hell are you doing here, Mr. Man in Black?
It's, I say, it's my shift.
Didn't you check out the sign?
Not too swill of dizzy folks.
Bob's Burger Barn? Wow, a franchise!
Yup. Yet another one of the stores in Bob's multinational conglomerate. Amalgamation, that is.
But that, I say, that's beside the point, boy.
You, uh, you suck.
Yeah, I couldn't do anything to get their, their, their stupid attention.
Those normals just are impossible to preach to.
Bullpucky, son. I can do it, boy.
Mind the store while I go open up a whole can of whoopin' hot dogs.
Oh, okay.
Tick, tock, tick, tock, tick, tock. Boring, isn't it?
Later, somewhere in the Crimean, oh, uh, uh, I mean, shopping mall.
Where is he? All I see is that kraut over there. Oh, here he comes!
See, son, it's not impossible. I got $117.54 and a whole mess of coupons.
Save me, Reverend! Save me!
Yeah, but you can do it. By the way, you owe me $4.25 for mine in the shop.
Okay, that's fine, son.
I, I got confused and can't find what I'm looking for in my notes, and, and, and, you know...
Notes?!
Now, no self-respecting subgenius uses notes by hand. Well, some of them do.
But, uh, hand over that paper before I ream you.
Paper! Ream! Ha, ha, that's a joke, son. I'm too fast for you, boy.
You're so funny, Reverend.
Back off, lady. I ain't got no time for no romance right now.
Listen here, son. Get yourself dirty.
I'll give you $13 and head on down to the book crevice.
And get you a copy of the book of the subgenius. Then memorize it.
And then forget it. Forget all about it.
Then it'll be imprinted on your subconscious mind, and that's all the notes you're ever gonna need, son.
But, but I don't have $13, and you still owe me that $4.25.
All right. Here's your $4.25 out of that. Uh, will you take, uh, ca-cappuccino coupons?
Teeth. Teeth. Uh, sorry, I ain't got no teeth right now. Lady, you got any teeth?
Reverend, let me get you...
Uh, here's a gold tooth there for you, son.
That's a tip. Thanks. I can give it back to Dad.
All right. Uh, I'll tell you what.
Get the rest of the money, and you get out there for Bob's sake, and you preach for your supper.
You got that? Get out there. Get this flock.
Yeah! Yeah! Get out there and preach.
Give your money to the Church of the Subgenius, or, or, or, or me.
Mell it, you stinking sinners. Uh, here comes Dougie.
Ah, ha, ha, ha, ha. Drop your purse. You're, you're done.
Tune in next week for the next exciting episode of...
the continuing story we are forced to call...
A Pink Boy Comes to Bob-a-lon.
Same Bob time, same Bob station.
Oh, man. Well, like I say, friends, I don't know what to think about this, uh, Pink Boy Goes to Bob-a-lon thing.
It's, it's so beautifully written, and yet so subgeniously performed.
You know what I mean, yeah?
Yes, and, uh...
I'm just 18 and I haven't got a worry.
They tell me get a job, but I figure what's the hurry?
I got three square meals and my roof is partly made for work.
I got a car, a PCR, well, you know I'll probably get more.
I'm living at home with my parents.
I really like it here.
I got a free ride.
I'm living at home with my parents.
I really like it here.
Because I couldn't make it outside.
I just don't care where my parents get the money.
They say I'm good.
I know someday, well, I'll be kind of funny.
Because I know all I need is a little piece of plastic.
But when they say you've got to work, now isn't that a little drastic?
Because I'm living for my parents.
I really like it here.
Living for my parents.
I've got to be right.
I really like it here.
Living for my parents.
Because I couldn't make it outside.
I really like it here.
I've been losing them.
My brain's going dead.
Well, I'll just stay in bed all day long.
And make up a solo.
A really cool solo.
A rock band can play in this song.
Lower lip hangers.
Noудard Walk story where I like of learning more than get long.
ä****æç***ä sugä***äавливä****ää ä***äölöööchü crawläœer dæä his Quando vged Äsujöëizer Shq picking up yü cannes
to do it
Behavior Haven street Telecommunicating.com Enfin beg forgot to tweet noding ress США
Have you ever been to California anyway?
I love you.
I'm living on my own now because I couldn't make it outside.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Living at Home with My Parents by Dr. Bizarro there.
And before that, of course, a little bit of KPFA.
Oh, no, there wasn't.
It was just A Pink Boy Goes to Babylon by John Ling
and his friends don't know much more about that particular one
and have conflicting feelings about it, but yet we share it with you.
We did hear some KPFA Berkeley subgenius show
with Dr. Howland puzzling evidence as usual.
And friends, you are, as usual, listening to the subgenius radio ministry
Hour of Slack broadcast here from Dallas, Texas,
by the Church of the Subgenius.
And if you want to write for some free information regarding...
Yeah, here it is.
You got that pencil ready?
You can get the free catalog by writing to...
Bob at Post Office Box 140306.
That's Bob at Box 140306.
In Dallas, Texas.
Beautiful Dallas, Texas.
Zip code 75214.
And it's slick, it's groovy, and it's sick,
and it's groovy, and...
It prays, Bob.
And it's drowsy, and it's drippy.
They hung up.
What a hangup they had.
They never wanted to go all the way down there into Dobstown.
You've heard about Dobstown, haven't you, son?
Yeah, I got off the boat in Dobstown to get some mangoes.
They call it subgenius land.
Right, that's right.
Yeah, that's right.
Where the mangoes grow in the mangrove groves.
And the sap is thick and green.
It drips down the trees.
Okay.
that you can smell it in the breeze and the air never smelt more clean as you walk in the sand
your every demand you'll find is satisfied and the grin of bob will do every job and salvage your
waning bride oh you're worthless
okay i was going to say you're waning pride but your worthless hide is is also also a factor
this is uh delta control are you reading me over um
without control for major tom uh you've really made the grade there's major pong's beauty lotion