Hey, well alright sir, here we go then, what are they gonna give for him?
AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH
That's the most incredible performance I've ever seen.
And look, the one with the sandwich hat thinks it's giving birth to something, I guess.
Ewwwww!
A thing with a sandwich hat!
A gift for you!
A gift for each and every one of you!
Hey, these slackers didn't even donate last week. What should we do about it?
They were slappers.
Oh really? This show didn't get much support?
No.
From the believers?
Wow.
Alright, there they are again. We get the most people on the internet.
Not one of them, not one of you people called in to donate to this show last week. Not one of you.
I've been a bit of a stalemate.
They're not only slackers, they're all like, you're all like slackers.
Not even Reverend Turin, I'm surprised.
None of them.
He always, he always used to donate.
Well the only way you can redeem yourself is to call up during business hours tomorrow and put in a donation.
But I'm, I'm disgusted with y'all actually.
Bob's calling me home. I'm going home my friend. I'm going home. Bob doesn't call me home.
He doesn't want to, he's not going to listen anymore to your garbage.
And that means we can't do any more of our garbage. If you ain't going to pay for it, you pay your garbage man.
Why don't you pay Lonesome Cowboy Dave to bring you garbage?
How about Mr. Egalitarian Fartbushel and some of those other people who have not connected with their dues for the last five year plans?
These people are not only remiss in their doodads, they're also completely and totally ungrateful.
They're useless as far as I'm concerned. They're useless.
You know they listen to this stuff as if air was free. As if somehow radio broadcasting was something that was done without any formal...
Do you think they're getting free radio waves in Afghanistan?
Oh it's as if you had unlimited brain cells Dave.
They think we have little tin cans and were yelling into the one part real hard...
Dave, these are little tin cans connected together by strings and we are yelling into the one part real hard.
And, friends, it's because Bob did call me home.
This is the subgenius radio ministry hour of Slack, dear friends.
Does it sound a little crappy this time?
Well, it's like this.
I was in my white tassel in the clouds in Cleveland in my slick sound studio
about to spend last week's hour of Slack
when I got a call from HQ that I was urgently needed back home in Texas.
Bob called me home immediately.
Four hours later, I was on a plane, friends, and now here I am in Texas,
in fact, on a remote cattle ranch way out in the boonies.
Now, my dire mission has been accomplished,
but now it's time.
It's time to finally get that hour of Slack done.
And what do I have to produce it with, my friends?
Why, I've got all of subgenius needs.
A bad cold, duct tape, bailing wire, twine, some popsicle sticks,
my mom's boom box, which is what I'm talking into right now,
some blank cassettes.
Remember those, friends?
Cassette tapes from Radio Shack.
As you can tell by the low noise that comes free with every Radio Shack tape.
It's the only kind of tape you can get out in the boonies.
But, my friends, I brought with me two uncut ESO Swamp radio shows
from WCSB Cleveland, and I've got my dad's CDs,
which include Hank Williams, Roy Acuff, Cab Calloway, and so forth.
So, bear with me, my dear friends, on this,
the very first hour of Slack.
Slack done the old way in two years.
Mixed and duplicated on cheap tape decks.
And for this one time only at the Dobbs Bar Sinister Ranch
in Stangsville, Texas.
The All Stang Family Special is this one, friends.
Co-starring ESO Swamp Radio from WCSB Cleveland.
Starring Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Mrs. Smith, Princess We Are Doe.
And yours, truly, Reverend Ivan Stang.
Friends, I can't edit very well on these decks,
and they probably won't sound all that great,
but by gobs, the word about doesn't have to sound that great.
So, let's go back.
¶¶
I heard the crash on the highway
But I didn't hear nobody pray
When I heard the crash on the highway
I knew what it was from the start
I went to the scene of destruction
And a picture was stamped on my heart
There was whiskey and blood all together
Mixed with glass where they lay
Death laid her hand in destruction
But I didn't hear nobody pray
I wish I could change this sad story
That I am now telling you
But there is no way I can change it
For somebody's life is now through
And I wish I could change this sad story
But there is no way I can change it
Their soul has been called by the master
They died in a crash on the way
And I heard the groans of the dying
But I didn't hear nobody pray
I didn't hear nobody pray
Yeah, brother, I didn't hear nobody pray
I heard the crash on the highway
But I didn't hear nobody pray
Dave, I heard they're broadcasting us on Radio Free Afghanistan.
Well, I heard the Northern Alliance...
That's to show how bad America is.
Yeah.
Well, they had one of those...
This is what they have to listen to in America.
They call themselves free, and they are free to listen to garbage!
It's Dave, Lone Cow Dave, man.
And free to correct themselves.
He and Bert, evil Bert, puppet devil.
And free to have those really awful one-night-a-pancake, three-nights-a-sausage dinners
that they're having at Pickelodeon Bill's or some of those other places.
This is where they're giving people regressive fametergy.
We evil doers, we hate freedom.
So do we.
We are evil doers.
Oh, you are evil doer, too?
Yes, I am.
Oh, let us be evil doers together.
Well, it takes more than one evil doer to make evil doers.
I know, let's have a war.
We can make a lot of money.
We'll make a big war.
Yes, yes.
Let's make a big war.
You be evil doer number one, I'll be evil doer number two.
And together we will be the evil doers.
We've had big fights.
We get rid of surpassed populations.
We sell tons of gunpowder.
And we get rid of all the soapstones.
And all of the alternative pizzas.
Yes, the psychic pizzas.
And then, of course, the...
Oh, this is fun and easy to be.
Evil doers.
What the hell are you guys talking about?
And they're 14.
And people want to know what you're talking about.
Look at this rocket launcher I've got.
Can you explain?
People, yeah, people, sure.
People want to know what you're talking about.
What are you talking about?
In the old days, back a long time ago,
before procreative girth was really invented,
people sprang into existence from underneath trees,
fully grown, with their hair and their hands
and the nails on their feet intact.
That's not explaining anything.
Yes, it is.
It's explaining the...
You're just getting to the good part, man.
Okay, this is the part that I...
What part did you not understand?
How can a...
Why does a...
Okay, you forgot.
When a mommy loves a daddy very, very much,
well, they get together and they feel very close.
And mommy's forehead looks kind of like a unicorn's foreskin.
It gets... His head gets actually bigger.
And then daddy's forehead actually...
You know, your hair shows up further breadth to it.
But really, why is a little bun still in fire?
You can imagine a small short what falls off the power supply
Once it's then directly pressed and thencićман starts to color theiin the applying it on.
uhm..
He is now learning more about entender own self and how to live bigger than part of your brain.
You couldn't help it.
Anytime it's the cake of your life.
the dex are still there for the winners.
Well, can you open up?
Your no, gosh.
There are some crazy amazing projects in the future.
So, can you sort them out?
It's not fair.
Mutated children again.
And it doesn't look like we're ever going to get rid of them.
They seem to be procreating like trees or some other small mammal.
And I don't know if I can stand this much longer than...
Now, that's the character Dave does that we can never figure out.
That is mean old lady.
Kind of like women, old lady.
But sometimes there's a gay character that's very close to it.
Deep down inside.
No, the gay character is completely different.
Is it?
Is that any relation to the French character?
The favorite is the southern gay character.
So that's what this is.
Dave would be institutionalized if he didn't have this venue for letting all those creatures and entities and personalities.
Well, he was a hairdresser in Memphis, Tennessee for about 14 years.
And just really got tired of the whole thing down there.
Just...
Others call it a serious multiple personality disorder.
Yes, it's a form of schism indeed.
But is it a real party schism or something?
We as members of the international subgenius...
You can help these multiple personality disorder character actors...
...by donating to help their medicinal needs.
Medicine can help their condition.
Give me the little small frozen monkey hand.
And put them in a box.
Are you getting tired of Dave's standard 57 personalities?
Don't you wish he had more like 250 or 1,000?
Send more frock to Lone Cow Dave.
At Admiral Corporation Box 757577.
New York, New York 11307.
Well, I thought you could buy that as an upgrade.
All the Lone Cow Dave.
You could boot it.
Nightmares and insecurities and...
Supposedly those can be good.
Those are very popular as compressed files on the internet.
Well, the horrific visions came as a separate disc.
I had to buy horrific visions separately.
Oh, you paid money for that?
Oh, man, that had a triple X disclaimer on it.
Well, I needed the manual.
I couldn't figure certain things out, so I needed the manual.
Oh, you can download the manual.
The whole manual?
From the Dave brain cell manual.
It's only one brain cell.
I thought there were three.
So it's not like it's a real long...
It's a real long...
File.
Complete discret...
Discrete?
Or whatever they call them and stuff.
They're the size of your thumbnail.
And when you had that whole set, you didn't have to worry about hanging on your forepaw.
Right.
Or like...
The instruction manual for you, Dave, is a lot more complicated than the brain cell itself.
I thought it had the two brain cells so you could rub them together.
Isn't that...
I thought that was the whole...
That's the missing Mrs. Dave.
The anti-Dave.
The receptacular Dave.
I remember Scott Loshley.
Dave Vest.
14 years ago, Scott Loshley.
And just tried to walk out...
Daveena.
In a pair of little pink booty socks.
And it wasn't the time of year to be walking around in the middle of a snowstorm in pink booty socks.
Especially if nearest highway was...
Popular cowgirl Dave.
Yeah, popular cowgirl Dave.
She only had 56 personnel.
If only her blood temperature was higher, she'd be here right now trying to suck on my booties.
But she just didn't quite get it.
You can't drink three pints of whiskey.
You can't walk around in the snow in your socks.
Pop cow Daveena.
Long cow Dave.
Me so milky.
Yes, yes.
She did come from the old country, I guess you'd call it nowadays.
She was a visa bride, all right.
But I didn't get to see her very much.
Came across the country on a Conestoga.
Yep.
She was wearing one of those weird Vietnamese bonnets.
Singing like...
Oh, I can't tell you this and that.
Ordered from a Russian mail-order bride website.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Have you checked out the Russian mail-order bride website?
No.
Latvia.
Oh, should I?
Yes, you should.
Latvia was so hot for you.
Yeah.
How much do they cost?
I don't know.
It depends.
They just want a new life over here, you know.
Then they divorce you and run off with some Russian guy that they had all planned.
And Mr. President, your stimulus package is in the other room, if you know what I mean.
Except genius and all slack.
Natasha, I guess, is her first name.
That's all you need to know.
Was saying that...
A friend of his had actually done that.
They'd gotten a picture of the Russian woman.
She was beautiful.
Hello, Mr. President.
And he went to Russia to meet her.
And strangely enough, all his friends were saying, no, man, it's going to be a lie, you know, when you get...
She was, just like in her picture, she was...
And she was an actress.
She wasn't a prostitute.
She was a singer.
But she was a schizo-screaming maniac.
Maybe that was lone...
Maybe that was Pop Cow Debina.
And why you think she only has two toes on each single...
So the guy had a leaf and he swore off...
He didn't marry her.
And she screamed at him the whole time.
The Russian mail-order bride screamed at him.
And she wasn't even a bride yet.
Then she sent him thousands of emails apologizing.
But it was too late.
The American millionaire had left.
She said she was an actress.
That's kind of like that Johnny Cash movie.
Johnny Cash on Teenage Queen.
Do you remember when he was on Morph...
He was on Acid, I think it was on...
Kill the Pop.
Remember Kill the Populous?
It was very popular around the Vietnam era.
Yeah, Johnny Cash was on Acid on Kill the Pop.
Remember Kill the Populous with Dick Cabbage?
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Okay, he was right in the middle of it.
And of course, they had the scene where like the union...
Ruth Buzzi was in that one.
Yeah, Ruth Buzzi.
She played the actually...
She played the parrot in the thing.
And she had the full headdress and everything like that.
And when they invite...
She was hot.
The members of the quote unquote Gaffer's Guild in there all help her...
Ruth Buzzi.
Stang's got a thing for Ruth Buzzi.
He does, he loved her.
She was in Far Out Space Nuts with Chuck McGann and Gilligan.
I think...
So you know they were fropping, man.
Well, you know what's going on in the internet now.
Yeah, right.
Maynard G. Krebs wasn't just allergic to work.
Yeah, they didn't call him Maynard.
He bobbed in for nothing.
The grim visage of Maynard G. Krebs as he lurks in your town.
No, he never went away.
He never died.
The program never went away in his mind.
Griselda was one of my role models growing up.
She was my first sexual encounter because Griselda, the witch, the evil witch of the
north, was it?
South?
No, I...
What were you talking about?
Dobie Gillis.
Oh, I thought you were talking about Hector Pelvis Cube or what?
What was that one guy?
No, the girl that was really, you know, bookish, the bookish girl.
Right, with the huge eyeballs and the weird like Dobie ears.
I always wanted Dobie to like her.
Right, but she was a pathetic laughing stock because she had glasses.
Do you remember watching Yogi...
Little Wrinkle Nose Girl?
Do you remember Yogi Satyananda?
Remember, remember, I think it was Morning Cube with Yogi Satyananda.
We would sit around in the regular morning cube.
Or a small circle, examining each other's navels.
We are a very social group.
We do not contemplate our own navels but the navels of our friends and families.
Now, some of the shows, if you play the tape back, they do make sense, then there's the
ones like this.
Some of the shows are evil.
Yes.
Yes, some of those shows are evil.
But some are good.
Those are ignored.
No one cares for them.
They only like the evil.
And now you can tell the difference with an amazing new...
Craft Go.
Some of the horror shows are evil doers.
Bandwidth generator.
Horror shows.
Play each song backwards till your heart's content
and then listen in forward and reverse modes.
You'll know the good from the bad in just a very short period of time.
All at once?
Craft Go.
So, perplexing the young.
You'll pay to know what you really think.
And now I'm like...
There's slackers out there listening in on the internet and all that.
You left us hung and dry last week, didn't you?
Yeah.
They don't care.
They don't love Bob the way they used to.
They did not call.
Not only did they not call, they did a pledge.
They refused to believe the truth to stand.
We needed that money.
We needed it.
We had to buy blood for our executive staff.
Keith, because they're here all the time.
You have to keep a blood supply on your tap for them.
Now we don't have that backup blood supply.
I gave.
Princess, we here gave.
We gave.
We gave a part of our time.
Sad, sad documentary.
And they...
We gave more.
Oh, look at so many beautiful tropical birds.
So many beasts.
So many birds.
Look, look, look.
There's another shape emerging from the top of my forehead.
Well, it's time to sit down now.
I think I've gone one foot further than I...
Throw that thing in a box.
God, that...
We're going to have to get another box soon.
Dave, can you do something about that forehead?
Get this...
Get this damn dog suit off me.
My knees are burning.
Turning my mic on.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I just thought...
I'm turning off.
I'm going to sit over here in the corner.
Turning on.
Off.
On.
I'm going to go sit in the corner.
I will no longer...
At the wall.
I will no longer sandbox.
I promise.
Put your mic back where it belongs.
And I promise I will not play bad.
Dave, look at these spiders over here.
The spiders are in your pocket, man.
Hey, I never saw this place before.
And I just...
What's under this couch?
I'm not going to get in there.
Don't touch that thing, Chaz!
Just take the one little knob off there.
Yeah, just so long as you've got some room to breathe.
A little bit of air to get in there.
Oh, man.
I think I ought to get out of here entirely.
Just leave the entire area.
I think...
I don't know.
I think it starts to collapse.
As Chaz enters the infrastructure of the building,
Rhodes Tower is built exactly like the World Trade Center's.
You can tell me, B.S. me.
Actually, Rhodes Tower does look...
It does look like the World Trade Center.
...like the Pyramids.
Kind of a miniature version of the World...
Well, what was the World Trade Center.
Yes, it was once at Giza.
Speaking of the World Trade Centers,
I hear that these movie stars are afraid to fly in airplanes.
Including Bruce Willis, it seems, refuses to fly in airplanes.
It seems that they want to stand up and go,
Oh, we want people to know that we care.
But they don't care enough to...
They aren't willing to die hard in real life.
No.
Only in movies.
Oh, yeah, that was a stuntman who died hard.
They just want everybody to watch their little award show
and watch them pat each other on the back.
Well, it's more than the back patting.
I think it's great.
I think if nobody goes to movies, good.
Yeah.
Knock them damn Hollywood people off that damn pedestal they're on.
I think the minister of home...
I think we should go see subgenius movies.
Yeah, and cartoons and midnight movies and old crazy stuff.
On the day after Thanksgiving,
the anti-world global conspiracy people,
say you should not buy anything.
And, of course, this is kind of a rough time to shake the economy.
Now, you must elaborate.
You should go.
I think you should go to...
Or, you know, you can also protest globalization by buying subgenius.
Making all the clothes.
Buy, but don't buy conspiracy.
Or by donating to this radio station.
Right.
Instead of buying that...
Donate radio station.
...Pootie and the Blowfish used CD...
Or that dozen donuts.
...to the...
WCSB.
Yeah, we could use the donuts.
Instead of going to see that Bruce Willis Hollywood movie,
go see that...
Crap.
...weird little art film that you heard might be good.
Oh, speaking of that...
It's only in one theater.
November 17th.
...the dreaming of pickerwoods with...
Speaking of weird little art movies...
Weird little art movies.
Speaking of weird little art movies.
November 17th.
Weird little art movies.
November 17th, Cobra Verity will be playing live music
at the Cleveland Cinematheque along with...
What's the name of that weird movie?
Sexual Thaumaturge.
The Andalusian Dog.
Yeah, your favorite dog.
The Salvador Dali and Louis Buñuel.
So this really crazy, surrealistic night out at the Cinematheque,
November 17th, with live music by Cobra Verity.
So, you know.
That should be a really artistic experience.
I'm going to wear, like, a Black Turtle-ish sweater.
I think the night before that,
I'm speaking at the Skeptics Society meeting.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
They wanted to have a believer in...
Welcome once again...
They're so used to skeptics, they wanted...
...to the foolhardy...
Skeptics in Assen, as we like to call ourselves.
The lovely Mr. and Mrs. Reverend Ivan Stang.
We...
Nothing...
I'm a believer.
...needs no more further...
I believe in this man, J.R. Bob Dogg.
The face of J.R. Bob Dogg.
I believe in this face.
This face!
This dot-be-speckled,
real-cream-be-shining,
hairdo-ed face!
This pipe-gripping...
Usually excitable.
...floats against the TV.
That's the weird thing.
He is my Messiah.
Bob's grin is a clenched grin,
yet he has a pipe attached to his mouth somehow.
How can this be?
Is he missing a tooth?
Is that how the pipe sticks through,
even though he's gripping?
Adios, man.
Before you go off, you know, I'm sorry.
Und...
Und das...
...lachmache...
Guido, silent, they leave the room.
Guido.
Now is the whole downtown circus and all the people with three eyes.
La comedia es finita.
La comedia dell'arte è finito.
La parola è fatta.
And now it's time for the...
Search your heart loop.
The stinky winter song, brought to you by Abel Cloggs and the Spider Chorus.
These small children here, after the latest onslaught of mutations,
have legs that resemble hairy little spider legs.
We want something good for everyone.
Not just foolhardy or the big and onion.
We want all God's childs to shine with that same effervescent smelly sound.
Okay kids, let's make good faces for the camera now.
One more time.
Oh they're so cute.
ESO Radio. Television for the blind.
Take one or two of them home.
Take them home and put them in a vat of salt water.
See how long it takes.
Stand back please. Stand back please.
Some of these children are dangerous.
So Dave, can you answer the eternal question?
Is masturbation really just a porn movie for the intelligent?
For the intelligent or perhaps for the extremely physically handicapped?
The emotional... Yes.
No, it's for the artist.
The only true artist, Bob said, is the jack-off artist.
That's the truest, most sincere form of creation.
Because the artist works for no one but him, his or herself.
He points his confused epithets skywards and hopes they land somewhere besides his own pillogs.
There's no concern over critics or audiences.
It's merely the creation for the pure joy of creation.
I hope DJA's on his way up.
Because I can't hang out all night tonight.
We'll just lock Dave up here in the studio.
Yeah.
We'll get Luis Bunwell.
Just leave all the microphones on and lock Dave in the main air studio until the sun comes up.
I bet Dave would figure out how to play record.
He's gonna play records on those turntables.
Yeah?
You know, if you push enough buttons, sooner or later, noise will start coming out of something.
Well, that's a hypothetical question, you guys.
What if you were to light up all these wax demons sitting out here at one time?
Well, it'd be great if this was a TV show, but...
They are lit up. Look, Dave.
No, no, there's still four or five.
Look, see, those are the important ones.
John Gold, Kibofrenia, Mr. Slap-Happy.
These are the...
Mr. Slap-Happy?
Is Mr. Snuggles here, too?
Yes. My favorite demon.
I liked it when Mr. Snuggles was here last week. That was Dr. Legume. He's Mr. Snuggles.
Yeah, I'm surprised he didn't call.
Cute little demons.
No one called.
Bleepo was supposed to call.
No one cares anymore. They didn't donate. They don't call.
Our mom's calling me.
What's the point?
He was going to call.
Who was?
Bleepo. Bleepo. Bleepo was going to call. He told me he was going to call.
Why?
He was caught in the most recent...
He had a big thing about Frank Sinatra. He was going to talk to us.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Bleepo has become... Frank Sinatra is his new short-duration personal savior.
Oh, well, that makes a lot of sense to a lot of people.
Yeah, well, blue eyes.
Nancy Sinatra was mine numerous times.
How many times a day, tops, say, age 13? You don't have to tell me.
Yeah, you're sort of putting me on the spot here.
Yeah, I know. That's like making you admit that you actually had her that many times.
You know, at all.
Yeah.
At the age of 13.
Now, how many times did you bother that old Amish lady again? Remember...
How about the cover of the...
Extremely Harry.
You're on a brass album...
Oh, okay.
...with the gal bathing in the shaving cream or just...
Yeah.
What about the galvanized fuzz holster that you got from the extra meditation labs, man?
Griselda.
Yeah, Griselda.
Well, would you be a Ginger or a Mary Ann?
Kathy or Patty.
Or a peyoteen.
I don't know.
We already did that one. That's right. We decided Mrs. Howell.
Yeah.
The rich one.
No, but we didn't decide on Kathy or Patty.
Kathy or Patty, you're talking about sandwiches or are you talking about actually the food?
Oh, the crepe suzettes or the hot dogs.
Yeah, yeah.
Kathy adores minuet, belly troop and crepe suzettes.
Well, Patty likes the rock and roll. A hot dog makes her lose control.
Think about the triple innuendo going on there.
Oh, there. Right.
The American or the classy British chick.
Patty was a slut.
She was. She was a schizophrenic slut. And that's why she had not only two sides.
So then the question is, Kathy or Patty?
Who was a male or a female cesspool you're backing up into?
Hmm, Dave?
I think it's a...
You got some kind of problem with your own genderality? Hmm, Dave? Hmm?
I place my gender talia on the altar of sacrifice every night and I talk to the plastic whistle.
My boss would be rich too. And you have boss too. And his boss. See that dame over there in the car?
Oh my God. They keep on breaking my heart.
If only we could get out of this vile top stock. If we could only burrow beneath the barbed wire.
If only these... these vessels could get us out of here. These tiny little boats.
The sponge raft. Perhaps we can fashion some sort of crew device.
And maybe if we flap our arms very, very hard, we will go...
I can help keep you boiled up old Davey.
Yes, yes.
You don't think?
I have some idea of something wild.
I've been listening to you since you got on this island.
Some kind of craft things that we can float on. I think I know what we can use. We'll make a... We'll make our own ship.
No, no, no, no. There's no chance.
Yeah, yeah. We'll make our own ship, yeah. We have some mailing tubes and... and all kinds of marshmallow cream and...
It... it will be good. It will work.
In order to sink, you have to lose your ship, my friend.
And in order to fly, you have to lose your little poo poo head.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Ben flies all around the world because he lost his little poo poo head.
They call this inappropriate laughter for those people confined in mental institutions.
Don't you know the walls around you have eyes and ears and nose and throat, doctors?
You must be aware that Dr. Ben no longer exists except for in your own febrile sexual organs.
You're contaminated.
The what? The Dr. Ben's no longer exist?
Then what do you call this?
He is contaminated.
And no one understands his point.
Then take him away.
Ah, yes, it is the most contaminated music of all.
Music made by doctors. True, enlightened doctors.
We're going to remove your hypothalamus with sound now.
Oh, now Dr. Philodrumon applies his saxophone to the patient's sacroiliac in this sacred act of love.
Yes, friends.
Surgery is a form of intimate love.
And the doctors of the airwaves will do this to your very ear mind and your ear brain.
Just trust the good doctor.
Now he's going to take out your spleen and your hava pancus.
He's going to replace the soles of those tired shoes with a brand new hardened belly button.
Just like the one you wanted to close.
I was scared, but then so was the doctor.
Sit down here on this barbed wire seat.
Don't worry.
Don't wink and knobble about those little winkings in your eyes.
Now they're just controlling your rapid eye movements.
Those doctors have powers you don't know about yet, but you're going to find out.
Oh, you'll find out soon enough, my good fellow.
My good little nurse girl.
Yes, come on into the operating room now.
The operating theater, we call it.
But on these rubber gloves.
Sit down, Dr. Clance.
Pour this alcohol into your lap and here, drink some of this.
And have some of this gas.
And take this pill.
And take this shot.
And then this night here, insert this deep into your chest cavity.
Now take these pencils and work them gradually into your ears.
Now put on these headphones and give me $20.
You notice the acrobatics we are doing now?
Look at me.
I am a monkey man.
Look at my strong forceps.
Look at my chin.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
I bet you wish you could imitate this, but no.
You need more, more, more sound cut.
More.
There will always be a need for more.
More slack.
And yet, more money, dear friends.
More money.
And how, how, you ask me, Reverend Stang?
You say, how should I get this money?
With what you speak.
Because it's true.
Sure, slack is what you make of your imaginary, your dream.
But let's face it, we need money.
We don't need a bunch of this hoo-ha, is it, damn?
A bunch of new age gobbledygook.
We need money.
We need money coming into this radio station.
We need money coming into this church.
We need money coming into this wallet.
The one I'm sitting on, on my butt.
Now I want you to get off your butt, my friends.
And get on down there to that sub.com thing.
And check out them.
Because this is a prosperity ministry.
We are not going to sit here and just hope that some magical monkey is going to start crapping money out of its butt.
We want you to start crapping that money out of your butt.
So get with it, baby.
Oh, if only you understood.
If you were one of the brilliant shining lights of humanity, you would know that you can crap that money out of your butt as easily as flying saucers make planets.
You know that you can create a better world for you and your mutant clones by simply following this.
Oh!
Oh, my God!
I expected it to be so.
It was moving very close to some place I didn't want to go.
My head was throbbing.
Sure, I had been knocked on the head three times by a bowling ball.
What would anybody expect?
And of course, the dame was no help either.
Sticking that strange substance down my pants and also trying to clip my gonads together with a safety belt.
Yeah, I wasn't complaining though because I could still walk.
Unlike so many other Joes that passed this way.
Yeah, not only could I still...
I could still...
Walking...
Hey, you!
Hey, you there!
Lean on the corner.
Yeah, no, no, you there.
Singing man.
Yeah, what do you want, buddy?
Hey, I need a little help.
You guys go ahead and keep singing.
I'll attend to this.
What are you, a cop?
No, no, I'm a private dickhead.
Listen, buddy, I've been out of the car for the last five weeks.
My pants are pretty shabby and, you know, I need a place to go if you catch my drift or...
Oh, you're looking for...
Huh?
You're seeking something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm seeking something.
I see.
Here, here, here.
Sit down.
Let me look into my crystal ball.
Thanks, I appreciate it, pal.
Close your eyes.
Let me look through this wallet of yours.
Oh, wow.
Hey, what you doing with my money?
I know, I see.
Hey, just leave the wallet alone.
Well, I tell you what we're going to do.
We're going to go see...
Thanks, sir.
Oh, we don't need to go see him at all.
Here he comes right now.
You're going to drink the water?
Here comes the man I wanted you to meet.
His name is Bob.
This is Christy.
And you're about to meet Cheyote Bob Dogg Sirself.
He looks like a...
Dave, here he is.
What a...
What a disgusting body.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to pass out from the fumes.
What a grotesque looking...
My pipe.
Where is my pipe?
Oh, my God.
Well, sure, it was the same pipe he's been smoking all along.
Of course, it was.
But Dr. Sue Man also knew that there was something special inside that pipe.
Something beside the usual habsopropolis that he had been smoking for the last five weeks.
Of course.
It was the demon sperm itself.
Inseminated by his archfiend rival, Lawrence...
Could you please...
Demon sperm, my friend.
Are you a victim?
Or are you a user of the demon sperm?
Bump into the pipe.
Are you addicted, my friend?
Are you lost in bondage to the demon's fur?
I'll send them down by the riverfront.
Come on, now, you can tell an old preacher.
They can't, and they can't do it, and they can't move their limbs anymore.
What about this demon?
They feed around disease.
Demon disease.
Most of them have eye problems.
Eye, eye, eye, eye, this.
You know, they're egocentric.
Of course, they are the old wino bums, but...
Aye, aye, sir.
We make good use of them.
So, Shanghai, Willie, Emily, I mean...
Shanghai Nelly.
Me?
That's right, you, Shanghai Nelly,
the girl in the frumpy suit and the 40-year-old haircut.
It's time for you to dance all night long
in the disc-shaped shack of your own design,
the most beautiful place you've ever seen in your life.
Can you imagine where this is?
I'm blushing right now.
It's on the Cabo de San Lucas,
here in Dobbstown, U.X.A.
It's party time!
I can't believe it!
Everybody get ready for the, uh,
for the swimsuit competition.
Marie...
Uh, Maria, what's your name, honey?
Al Damas.
Maria Damas?
Where did you get the hot sweatsuit?
Hot Damas.
Hot.
I'm talking about the bacon powder, baby.
Where'd you get the glands?
I made it myself.
That is certainly hotter than anything I can think of right now.
You want to take a little walk down the runway?
I'm a designer.
And they start...
Dolmus.
Dolly Dolmus.
Come on.
Yes.
The perfect time.
We're soаны
Crazy, are you?
We're still inT、
Cannot
Hey, don't you mind
Show to her
we didn't necessary
You sad
Okay,
So.
You don't have any
Only reason
to have
Can you come out of the closet?
Honey, come on.
No.
Get the contraption off your head.
You're not on the runway in Miami, honey.
No.
You're stuck in a closet back here in Cleveland.
Come on.
No.
We'll talk about it.
Okay, we won't talk about it.
We'll just pretend it didn't.
Please.
No.
Your mother's having a histrionic fit.
You know what happens to your mother when she has one of those?
Uh-huh.
The vesicles come exploding out of her ass.
Next thing she can't sleep for a month and a half.
Please, honey.
Peppy wants to play with you.
Come on.
Doggy wants to go salute.
Wang, wang, ding, dong outside.
Come on, honey.
Please.
I want to go play in the doghouse.
I'm going to have to call up Dr. Zane.
No.
No, don't call Dr. Zane.
All right.
I got that.
Me?!
You just let me amortize all this dog food stuff.
Smile.
I don't think I'm getting take.
Still look cool.
spiritual powers that you can uncork by using this magic uncorking device.
Oh very very interesting.
Eric
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
¶¶
Hey, hey, get your hands off the artificial wombat breast there.
Lung, chee-wim, whatever.
God don't care.
Just...
Uh-oh.
I think it's the old lady or something.
What's she doing here?
I didn't want to sacrilege your bums, sir.
I didn't want to recorrect your list of little habits
or the strange way you address the people around you.
I'm talking about your family connections.
The way you make your vowel sounds.
It's clear to me, as clear as chocolate pudding,
that you're one of my least remembered cousins from...
I think it was the tubular year or it was the bad bassoon era.
Oh.
I know you now.
You're a...
Bueller.
Ashton Bueller.
Yeah.
Named after a town.
Well, child, just sit over here on top of this vociferous lightning razor like me.
Ashton was my sister.
Ashton.
She was a fishy old woman, wasn't she?
Yeah.
Some menzies flowed like a river.
I remember your daddy.
Big box.
Size ears, didn't they?
Don't be talking about my papa like that.
Okay.
Well, at least I know you're related to someone who's almost related to me.
Can you...
Besides, you know in the Orient, the big ears, it means intelligence and wisdom, you know.
So come on now.
We're on the east side of this planet now.
Talk about my father that way.
Well, we call him figuratively a father.
At least when we put him up on a pedestal, he didn't wax the way we...
This man here now.
Could you come and help me put some of this cottage cheese here on my pantyhose, child?
I'm gonna touch nothing around there.
Child, you know, great, great uncle grandma woman thing here needs help.
Putting...
Hepatitis.
Help is here now.
Help is on its way.
Help is here and on its way.
Help is coming, friends.
In the form of a well-dressed businessman carrying a briefcase, smoking pipe,
and wearing a great big grin.
And a little bit of a smile on his face.
He's got something for you in that briefcase, my friend.
It's a little...
It's a little minister's card.
You never thought of yourself as minister, preacher, any kind of a religious person, did you?
In fact, the last...
Last thing you ever saw yourself as was some kind of a holy man or holy babe.
I tell you what.
Maybe...
Maybe this is a different kind of holy man.
A hole...
Hole in the head that we're talking about.
A hole in the head.
What's that little considering?
Well, it kind of starts with hoping that somebody régs on and beginssis to get the
So the calvary guy that the creepy guy that's calling the callings, says good building
It's just a guy out there.
Now he's nice.
So he doesn't realize, what exactly is going on with this guy here?
He's around.
Well.
What you see, nhs?
This is a major thing.
One, there's a lot to do.
That's aku?!
Yeah, sure, it's easy. Easy. Easy. That's why everybody's doing it.
Everybody's doing it right now. Everybody is doing it.
Except for you, right, buddy? Right, pal?
That's right. You're the only buddy, pal, right there.
You can't do it. You can't make it. You can't make it real.
You can build your own Instagram. You can build your own shit.
You can leave this planet. You can do it, man. You can do it.
If you don't like the band you're in, baby, move!
Hey, the magic moment of resolution.
Congratulations, buddy.
Everybody's doing it. Everybody's doing it.
You are waiting a moment of...
Doing it. Doing it.
Could you please put your hair just a little bit further to the left?
I can't. I'm using your spirit hand again.
That line puts you in a real, real electric hand.
Tastes like chicken.
It tastes like rattlesnake.
Smells sausage.
Yes, baby, we're going back in time.
In fact, we're going back in time to when this show ends.
And another show.
The show begins. This is ten years after.
Live at the Fillmore East in the background, friends.
And we're going to slowly groove on out of here.
But Chaz will be back next Chaz Week.
Chaz Time and Chaz Channel.
And Dave is still here.
We'll be back next week.
We'll be back in a lot better physical condition than we were next week.
We're going to come back from a therapist.
We're going to have to really solve some problems.
Not just diddling our time's weight.
Eating those weird cinnamon bites.
And hanging with that shit.
We're going to really find out what's making it tick.
And then, once we pronounce ourselves deaf,
we'll be ready to solve all the problems it's created for me.
The son of a bitch.
I wish I knew who my mind controller was.
I wish I knew who was pushing my click on the often clicking often button.
I wish I could get out of this.
I wish I could get out of this suitcase.
Bob dogs indeed.
I don't know how much longer I can take in Bob's suitcase.
It takes more time to ejaculate.
Roll up a spliff and throw the weighty-day.
With marijuana in your brain.
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
You smoke a...
Mmmmmmmmmmhhhhh
Mmmmmmmmmmhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
RAAAAAHHHHH
H è n t H atenẮ
Hear me knocking on your door
But you can't move no moak
You're st kans
LIKE 3
You
zig