Dear Hour of Slash, I'm standing outside of Ed Arroyo Auto Body Shop in San Francisco
waiting for puzzling evidence to come out of the taqueria where he's buying a Red Bull
because we're going to do a four hour show on Pirate Cat Radio with John Hell
and Pirate Cat Radio is located above Ed Arroyo's Auto Body Shop.
That's where the Pirate Radio station is, above the Auto Body Shop in San Francisco
and I guess we're going to go over there and do a long, long show
which will be this episode of Hour of Slash.
Give me the hammer, Bob.
The lunatic is in this room.
Shine the light on there, Bob.
Good night.
The Soul Genius Hour of Slash.
The champ is gone.
This way, Joe.
This way, this way, this way, this way.
Not only have I got it, I love it like a brother.
Good.
It should, Louie.
It should, it should.
The voice of the...
Bob howling for blood.
Oh, perhaps the world is sick and I'm well.
Who's on the big show tonight?
Listen, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Remember, Bob.
The Church of the Sixth Sense.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you, Norell.
And thank you, Fernandi Nandi, for the openings.
Ooh.
Ah.
Hey, friends, this 1136th Hour of Slash finds us in San Francisco for the whole show at
the Mongoloidapalooza Devival, the KPFA Puzzling Evidence Show, and John Hell's Season in Hell
Show from Pirate Cat Radio, all there in San Francisco.
And we'll hear plenty of Mongoloid, Hell, Hal, and Philo.
And Puzzling, and Gary Gebrogfran, and Philo's latest daughter, and Morrell, and Murrly Murr.
But first, there's this, well, there's this, uh, an outspoken concerned citizen named Frank
Chew in the San Francisco scene.
Frank could be called a colorful and beloved eccentric local character and friend to many.
Now, I didn't get to meet him, but, uh, he opened up the show at, uh, 12 Galaxies Nightclub,
which actually is named after part of his rant.
Uh, he opened that show there, the Devival of the Mongoloidapalooza, after being introduced,
as we hear now, by Dr. Hal.
Dr. Hal.
Some geniuses, humanoid and otherwise.
Welcome to this historic occasion.
The Church of the Subgenius will proudly feature Mongoloid.
And the first set will be Mongo Lounge.
But first, to inaugurate the festivities, the man whose words, after which 12 galaxies
is our name.
As you can see by the sign outside.
And the sign inside, held by Mr. Frank Chew.
Woo!
Well, uh, CBS Evening News, I met John Blackstone and, uh, Tom Brokaw that I met from NBC 90 News.
And the San Jose Mercury News, I was published by them.
So I was filmed of, uh, those populations at 12 Galaxies that were guilty with Bill
Clinton's.
And it was concerning myself.
It's that TV star.
That's the guy.
That movie star.
And it was also about those other rocket societies and the flying saucers and the space vacations.
They were across in outer space and, uh, the Pentagon and NASA keeping it all top secret.
And those other populations were across those other galaxies and they were also top secret,
too.
So, uh, 2009, I think I'll get improvement in Washington, D.C., too.
Thank you.
Yeah!
Woo!
Thank you.
19 Season's Scripture
So that's...
So, uh, that's not the beginning of compilation.
That's not the end of compilation.
The later.
The first part on the Ivy list.
Back to the Intro and the Part One.
hops on here.
Oh, no, we'll get a dopestack as soon as that's out.
We're printing into the radio.
And the big question here is kind of underwhelming right now.
I don't know.
Coming up!
So we've discussed the Onnit, uh, Se lyrics, and Tron, Celebration.
We're also showing the series team where there commitment, number three, Con Hanslund,
and the movie crew...
All right.
coming into the studio,
and Hal is going to introduce
a fabulous guest that we have here tonight.
Thank you, John Hill.
Yes, it is fabulous.
An incredible short space of time
has witnessed the burgeoning and efflorescence
of many different devivals in different lands.
Lastly, here in San Francisco
on the Twelve Galaxies stage.
And then, as now,
it was my deep and profound pleasure
to introduce Reverend Ivan Stang,
the sacred scribe of the Church of the Subgenius.
Why, there he is now,
delivering the sacred subgenius salute.
Thank you, Dr. Hal.
Man, what an inspiring evening that was.
It was so devolving.
It was devolutional, certainly.
And devotional.
Actually, you know, the term devolutional
is a misnomer because people don't really get devived.
They get revived.
It is a revival.
It just sounds cute to call it a devolvial.
Well, they have a life.
But the fact that it was also
like a devotional to the band Devo
in that respect,
then the devolvial thing certainly fits.
I suppose you call it a devolval or devolval.
Well, that would be...
It's not like a volvo.
It's a specific, I think.
A vulva?
A vulva.
That's what we do in Africa.
A devolva.
They would come in out of the cold for that one.
But most people have a life.
It is a mistaken life on the treadmill of the conspiracy
and a devival takes them out of that life
and into a mongoloid or subgenius life.
How do you feel about that?
Does that feel okay?
I'm kind of hurting just thinking about it personally.
But the microphone-age or the concept...
The concept.
It might be heartburn.
Sticking to the wall.
I don't know.
Well, John,
Hal is used to the style that I bring to the airwaves
since he and I have been the color commentators
at the Power Tool drag races numerous times.
There should be no surprise.
And how I've played the sort of Joan Rivers to Chicken John
at the Ask Dr. Hal show over the years.
That sounds terrifying.
And it is.
Well, we also have mongoloid, Lloyd Mongoloid,
as John Hal just said,
and this is a historic occasion.
He is here to report on the afterglow
of Saturday night's incredibly successful show.
That's right.
How'd it go?
I don't remember.
Well, there was a lot of wang-bang-a-langing
and speech-a-fying and sound effects.
My wang didn't get banged.
There's some ding-dang doodles going on.
You know, if you can remember it,
it means you were ripped off.
I'll buy that for a dollar.
You were cheated if you can remember it.
But if you can't,
then you know you must have had a great time.
No one was ripped off.
Everyone was satisfied.
No one remembers anything.
I woke up.
I woke up wearing somebody else's clothes,
so it must have been okay.
Is that my underwear?
Those must have been hard to get on.
I'll take it off my head later.
Not your size.
I woke up hurting all over
because I danced my fool head off.
Did they write things on your body again this time?
It makes me...
When I hear them Devo tunes,
I get all...
I feel like I'm young again and spry.
Man, notorious.
I get hopping around like a kid
in a punk rock festival or something.
Famous cyberpunk writer John Shirley
was also flinging himself about
down on the dance floor
as he was enraptured by the Mongo Lounge tunes
and all the tunes that followed.
We're lucky that there weren't heart attacks
among all the old-timers there.
Haven't been that juiced up
since the last time they saw the real Devo's.
I heard somebody in the crowd say that
as they walked in the room,
they could feel an entire culture
coming down upon them.
Well, it smelled funny, too.
Now we're all bored
Cause we're gonna
Go down
I'm making sales
And I'm on the grid
I got a bag of junk to sweep
Sweep it up
Sweep it back in
I am poor
And I don't remember
So let's let it slip
A little bit
Sweep it up
You never be here
You're pretty excited
Cause we're gonna
We are gonna
We're gonna
Go down
So it's really a Mongoloid show with
With Lloyd Mongoloid and the boys
and me, your Thanks, Mark.
Dr. Howland Owl.
You'll definitely see puzzling evidence there.
He'll be videoing up a storm.
And, of course, Reverend Dr. Supreme Commander Ivan Stang,
his exalted holiness, and a right nice guy.
But Princess We Are Doe, unfortunately, will not be able to attend festivity.
She is in the midst of other matters.
In her celestial city.
And can't come this time.
Where did, uh, I blew up the little doll of Ivan Stang and the little cute one here,
where'd they go?
We spoke of them.
They're floating around the station?
Beyond.
They're probably, they're pounding on the front door from at the last minute.
The Nuosphere.
Oh, all right, well, that's not really that important.
Oh, my gosh.
The Gary Brokham will not be able to attend either.
No, I'm very sorry.
He's running for a political office in another county.
He's going to be supervisor.
Of Stanafruz County.
Anti-freeze platform.
The reductive theocrats.
I'm going to let the Mormon come out of me this year, I think, in public office.
As significant in its way as the Mitt Romney Mormonism speech.
Yes, but I'm going to melt Romney.
How is that?
Well, I'm going to hold a match under him.
They say he has an icy heart.
Exhale.
Okay.
He has an icy heart.
He said he didn't inhale.
Well, I didn't.
Exhale.
And I don't have four wives either.
I used to be hail and hearty.
You could say I'm exhale.
Anybody know about any more screenings of this thing?
No, I don't know.
Well, oh.
Well, I've heard there will be.
There was one at the Grand Lake and I missed it.
I forgot it.
Oh, we believe it.
I hardly believe it now.
Dangishness.
Run!
Yes, ladies and gentlemen, his exalted excellency.
In the past of honor, file a drum of advice.
Reverend Dr. Commander Ivan Stang, one of the saintliest men ever.
What?
He's the greatest man on earth.
Cleveland, city of light, city of man.
Look at that cute little ponytail.
He's documenting everything with assiduous thoroughness.
The flickering flashing of the stroboscopic brightness of flash cubes is throwing everything
in the studio into dreadful relief as a thousand cameras pop off as the paparazzi convulse in
an orgasm of overkill.
Self-fuck, yes.
Self-fuck.
So, ladies and gentlemen.
I'm temporarily at a loss.
I don't know how to deal with this incredible incursion, but fairly soon, through the miracle
of radio hookup, they're going to get weird up.
And soon, you'll actually hear their voices and not just me talking about them.
I see Reverend Dr. Stang has brought the swag bag containing $40 million in...
Oh!
$40 million in prunes!
Yes, but they're very special prunes.
Yes, prunes.
They're not ordinary prunes.
Oh, my gosh.
You're an old man now, Stang.
This is the greatest medicine there's ever been.
You should see what Philo does.
And Dr. Philo Drummond.
I never thought I saw the day...
Agent of the 34th degree.
He also is here in the studio.
So, this is truly a turbo-philosophorum.
And if you believe that, I've got a radio show to tell you.
A convocation of subgenius savants.
What'd you pay for that glass?
That's a liquid scam.
They're darkening our towels.
They really are.
Darkening my bowels?
Hungry people from hell.
I would gladly give up my station.
Oh, well.
Yeah!
You're going to go around one!
You gotta switch that person!
You gotta grab that gun go!
You gotta get there first!
George favored in themiyor.
I think I heard that word pop that we used to hear.
Bymyrka.
Sure thing.
And you wanna know what he's done here?
I want to be West Versus King.
But also Wouldn'tId just be Isla?
First, have you ever noticed that,
the original game was именно based upon the app's game
fucking brains out on what we wanted to be working on. The concept of work has gotten a bad name
because it's not work, it's slavery. Most people don't like what they're doing. They're just trying
to pay the rent. You know, praise Bob if you can even do that nowadays. But no, we're not going to
tell you what slack is because that's for you to figure it out. All we're doing is giving you a
pep talk. That's all any goddamn religion is. It's a pep talk to remind you that that one time
that you were doing that thing, that hobby or that whatever it is that you like to do. Maybe it was
jacking off or even fucking someone. Maybe it was doing a crossword puzzle. Maybe it was launching
the bleeding head of Arnold Palmer. But whatever it was, suddenly you found yourself sort of in the
zone. Your mind was clear. You were concentrating on what you were doing and you were having a great
fucking time. Hold on to that.
That thought, because that's where the slack is. Because you actually, despite what appearances, you actually are
smart enough to make your own slack. And well, we can sell you plenty of false slack starting at that sales
table back there with those t-shirts, DVDs and CDs, which you can memorize like I have and then forget
them like I have.
Stir up your pure minds. Where is lust? The Lord is slack. Looking for? The Lord is slack. I want to speak to you this morning on
Dog is slack. Today, dog is slack. Slack but is long. Now let me just simply say and say very quickly and emphatically.
Pleasure. Pleasure. Dog is slack slack and coming again. Understand that dog is slack. Dog is slack slack.
Ch Bali's married andflanzenen at home.
fräôn
went ch
nh
i
r
theat
cessi
test啰
Dog is slack word.
Dog is slack.
Slack.
I want you to take this word today, and I want you to place it against your own heart.
I have the right to develop a point because I'm a creature, and I can do what I want.
Here's one in which he's slack.
Here's another one.
I don't know what I'm saying.
Yes!
Let it be so.
Slack.
The Lord perhaps can be slack.
Dog is slack.
Oh, see how good this fruit looks?
So?
Dog is slack.
Dog.
Is slack.
So what's this one about?
An analysis of teeth marks on pipe stems.
Dear me.
Fortunately, though, I've had news of him lately through my underworld grapevine.
He is reputed to have some connections with a new cult that calls themselves the Soul Genius.
Our house.
Splendid.
What on earth does that mean?
Oh, some newfangled cult.
Heathens, most likely.
By George, yes.
Well, it was quite a social event.
Many people came, and I guess you may have seen that Laughing Squid has posted some videos on its site, including Stang's complete oration.
Really?
Yes, and then the assiduous...
I hope it was okay.
...bug girl put up, like, a few seconds of me.
Actually, I think Laughing Squid put up a rather truncated version of your speech.
But it looks like John Hell's digital digits are uncovering that right now.
So you might be able to get a preview.
You know, the scary thing about the Internet is every dumb thing you ever did is still out there preserved.
Tell me about it.
Like a fossilized portrait of drunkenness.
Yes.
I started posting stuff to the Internet in the 90s, and it took me a couple of years to learn the lesson.
Never, ever, ever post after drinking a bunch of wine.
And with that...
Let's see how you...
It sounded after a little bit of wine.
Well, now, I stayed...
What?
Hold on, it's coming.
Here it comes.
You were on.
Straight from Laughing Squid.
For those of you who are not familiar with the word of J.R. Bob Dobbs, I don't want to preach to the same.
I love you, J.R.!
I will briefly explain everything you need to know.
There's only three things you need to know.
Bob.
Slack.
And...
The conspiracy!
The basics.
I get all upset when you mention the conspiracy.
I was fed on that growing up.
Yes, friends!
This man, J.R. Bob Dobbs...
Why is the Devo Lounge music on behind me?
It's supposed to be the theme from Abominable Snowman.
Well, we can't control every iota of the tech on stage and happening events.
...monster that has...
Uh...
...pretending to be God to many Earth cultures for thousands of years.
How's that war on God coming along?
...to beat Bob up and said to him,
Bob!
It's an ambitious project, isn't it?
One step at a time.
...normal people robbing away the slack of the abnormals.
And I command you, Bob, to found a church not based on a rock but on the shifting sandy beach of hypocrisy!
I've heard all this before.
How's the ratio with slack?
Back to sandy hypocrisy going.
Hypocrisy!
Where will any religion be like a...
Well, they go hand in hand if you're running a church.
...a...
...the song genius, our old...
...Squatchy!
Big, big, big, big...
Well, he was a pretty good sight.
How big was he?
Well, I took to...brought him home and...cleaned him and kneaded him.
Did you measure him?
Yeah, two inches long.
I was drunk.
I showed him all over the county. I reckon I did. I think I did.
A little bitty...a little bitty...but, uh...
...choked that head about three or four times. He just turned over on his side and just blow ball, blow ball, blow ball.
Yeah.
Well, stretching out. Straightened out, you know, sit. Stretching out.
When I jerked him, I thinks I'm hung. Didn't go nowhere when I jerked.
Well, didn't think nothing about it. I mean, good.
How often did you have him?
Three messes.
Well...
Oh...
I cannot hear anything.
Gentlemen, gentlemen, start your oysters.
First off...
We were too loud.
Now we're too soft.
Okay, you know what?
I listen to another show.
Yeah?
Bad girl.
It's worse than the other show.
It's more on KTFA.
94.1 FM.
It's called This is Hell.
And they have a chat.
You can chat with them while the show's going on.
Yes, hell is a chat room.
Listener participation, you know?
We don't allow that.
No, we don't like it.
What we do is we just spy on you while you're listening.
Yeah, we can see you right now.
That's all we've got.
How do you like it?
Hey, I just heard her click.
She just hung up on us.
She did.
Well, part of another click, you know?
There are so many of them out there.
We are going to be watching her very closely from now on.
She said we were childish.
The Department of Surveillance and Homeland Security.
It takes one to know one, Ivan.
It takes one to know one.
I have to listen to the...
It wouldn't be the music.
Maybe she meant childlike.
Childlike.
Oh, right, yeah.
Oh, yes.
It is childish.
Childlike.
Or maybe she meant youthful.
That's probably it.
Youthful.
Youthful and childlike.
It's like a...
That's what I was saying.
The show is like a playground all the time.
When I went over to your house last night or today, Dr. Drummond,
the only one that would talk to me was your tiny little daughter.
My child.
Yeah.
The two-year-old who doesn't really even talk yet.
Out of the mouth.
You couldn't...
Dr. Drummond and Mrs. Drummond had their brains locked on the TV.
And there was no one for me to talk to.
Scandalous.
Yeah.
We forced him to watch television programs.
And she read Dr. Seuss books to me.
Is this how a subgenius acts?
And that's good because she's only like 17 months.
Wow.
She couldn't talk, but she read Dr. Seuss books.
But she never threatens.
She never wheedles.
She never whines.
She can't.
She actually can talk.
It's just kind of part of that.
She never sounds desperate.
I noticed she didn't wheedle nor whine.
She never whine.
I came out here on the HMS Bob Dobbs.
What are those guys talking about?
This is great.
The salt spray in my face.
And the waves at 35.
Oh.
Did you see them spray in that guy's face?
Hey, they forgot to take down the ground.
Say it.
Don't spray it.
Look at those iguanas mating on those rocks.
Iguana.
Is Michael Pepp in there?
Those dodos.
The herds of dodos running across the plain.
Look at those presidential candidates mating on the White House lawn.
God's country.
And all I ask is a tall ship and a star to steer her by.
And a cup of coffee and a cigarette.
And a donut and a hard-boiled egg.
And loose shoes.
And a pint of milk.
And a warm place to defecate.
At DEF CON 4.
In this big world under the big open sky.
or in the forest
where the Pope and the Bears
and the little things.
Parking lot?
Yeah, they fill the parking lot with about four feet of water.
Parking lot, a motion picture.
Stage one, I mean, I'm sorry, it's like stage five or something.
It has the side of the wall where they drop a site.
Just when you thought it was safe to drive back in.
The cloudy day site or the stormy site
or the beautiful day site.
And then they have little model ships go across parking lot one
at Raleigh Studios.
And you get Raleigh cigarettes.
For movies like this, anyway.
Yes, it all happens,
but you've got to be there at the right place
at the right time.
If you can't surf the luck plane,
well, mister, it's just not for you.
You know, I turned up four years ago
to be an extra in this movie,
Chameleon, and they still haven't
given me lunch.
We'd give you lunch.
We had great craft services for that movie.
In fact, uh,
too much.
I waited and waited all night long
for them to call my name
and I thought I would,
be a monster.
But no.
We still have a lot of rehashing
of the Mongoloid
Mongoloid concert
to do before we put that topic
to rest.
And now we have K-Rob.
We're going to be here until midnight.
Yes, we are.
We have plenty of time
to get the details all hammered out.
And if you haven't guessed so far,
we have a cavalcade of crazy critters
here in the studio on a season in hell
with John Hell.
Dr. Hal is in the studio.
K-Rob has just shown up
to mix some fabulous sounds
in his own K-Rob style way.
Lloyd Mongoloid in the studio
puzzling evidence on his way back.
And Reverend Ivan Stang,
founder of the Church of the Subgenius,
following J.R. Bob Dobbs' doctrine.
Sweet.
No.
Ouch.
It's important that...
No, I'm not the founder.
J.R. Bob Dobbs founded the Church of the Subgenius.
Dr. Philo Drummond and I
were the first two clerks,
you might say.
Philo's a personal friend of Bob's.
I'd never get to go to those...
Philo made the primordial alignment with Dobbs.
Right.
There was no organized church
before Philo.
He has to babysit tonight.
Yes.
Well, he has a young subgenius
coming up.
The rising generation.
Bob's taking...
There he is now.
He's the biggest man in the world.
He's...
Well, this is the part where Jehovah One
has to fight the unforgiving minions.
Yes, the Yakatisma.
The creatures from beyond the stars.
The gateway to the doorway to doom.
And, friends, you can avoid these traps of the spirit.
You can avoid getting too sucked into
material things or spiritual things.
The trick is to avoid slack abuse
or false slack.
The conspiracy's gonna have you thinking
that the only way you can really relax
is to take a $10,000 ski trip
or buy as many video decks.
You should buy as many video decks as you can.
Well, those things are fun
and certainly we'll use them
to overthrow the conspiracy if we can.
But in the meantime,
if I were you,
I wouldn't worry about how you're spending your money
but how you're spending your time.
Are you getting slack on the job?
I think not.
I think many people out there
are sorely wanting.
They feel a need deep in their souls.
So, call in.
Call in.
Make a pledge.
.
Well, the final day of the convention
was Sunday, November 22nd.
The 18th anniversary of the assassination
of John F. Goodbrother.
This was hardly coincidence
that it rapidly became
on the Dallas Daily Plaza
for the final rites.
As to escape and escape from it,
Assassinologists popped in and out of manholes where additional hitmen supposedly hid and took acid on that fatal day long ago.
So when we talk about the computer, we're talking about everything from the mass to finally march past the assassin's site.
Well, David Rockefeller and his men used to...
The Nazi mob is the most...
So?
Yes.
Uh, yes?
What?
Oh, hi.
Do you...
Are you taking that stuff often?
Ah.
Yeah, it makes me remember back.
I was still so...
Yes, it's true.
Oh, and our ten-minute segment on Bob was scheduled for sometime in February on Showtime.
An HBO competitor in What's Up America.
Subgenius Dark from Madness will infiltrate an estimated five to eight million living rooms.
This summer.
We'll be able to...
I just think you'll know about it.
I'm just listening to this tape right now.
No, I'm not.
Carl, the goals...
Final answer.
The best of the best.
False prophets.
The conspirators.
The media creeps.
The stupid people and the malignants who beat down our mouths.
The abusive territorial urges.
Without ever dreaming that they were doing it.
The ones who have tried to...
They are the ones who have been the ones who have been the ones who have been the ones to remain our self-respect,
down through the centuries, by making slack and anti-predictability taboo in human culture.
They are the offensive ones.
And they brought this Buck Rogers monstrosity of microchips and inflation.
Nothing making sense anymore and everything costing too much.
The weather is weird, and why did they do it?
Don't they know they're begging for the flaming sword of retribution?
The space monsters aren't about to let us get away with this masturbatory industrialization much longer.
They watch our TV shows.
They know all about us.
They can snuff us out already with all...
It's all right.
All right.
And you can buy many tapes of former radio shows that we have done around the country with different doctors.
It's pop-up in time.
That's right.
These tapes are available for sale.
They're only $8 and 90 minutes long.
That's right, 90 minutes from the Church of the Subgenius.
And that address is?
That address is Church of the Subgenius, P.O. Box, 140306, Dallas, Texas, 75214.
And this planet will be sold down the river just as sure as Lee Harvey Oswald's clone.
What's that address?
That address is?
That address is.
P.O. Box.
1-8-1-4-1-7, Cleveland Heights, Ohio, 44118, www.subgenius.com.
Or you can tear tin cans open with your P.O. 6.
If the last of your fingers itching is not well pleased...
We must understand that Dallas is quite far away from California.
The thinking is different here.
You're wonderful to hear you in this part of the country thinking and calling.
But it's not.
We've had some...
The river shall shake.
The sky shall fall.
The space jump.
Pornators.
Hail the size of Cadillac.
Is there a call coming in?
Do we have a call in here?
Is this an actual contact?
Let me check on the computer.
Yes.
Okay.
Is Bob there?
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
No, he's not, but we are.
No.
As I say, Bob appeared to me this evening.
Did he really?
Yes.
Was it over the station or was that a different one than...
He has a gland on the radio.
No.
It wasn't over the station.
Would you...
Could you...
Sir, you were actually touched by Bob?
I'm touched by Bob.
Bob saved my life.
Bob.
What happened?
Um, I was about to be apprehended by the Oakland PD.
Uh-huh.
And Bob appeared over the horizon and guided my auto off.
And you...
You made an escape.
A miracle, friends.
A miracle in Oakland tonight through the radio power of Bob Dobbs.
And you've heard this living testimonial here on the telephone.
Hello, sir.
Yes, yes.
The Oakland PD was just going to nail me.
Well, what was your alleged crime, sir?
DUI.
Pardon me?
Could you spell that out for those of the listening audience who don't understand?
DUI.
I don't know what DUI is.
No, there are some who don't hear.
I do.
Driving under intoxication.
I've actually seen this happening myself.
Oh, trance driving is what it's known as in the church.
Yes, trance driving.
This is something...
It's an opportunity in my moment of need.
Yes, he did.
Did he do it...
Was your radio on?
Were you able to put hands on radio?
It was definitely hands on radio.
Okay.
That's probably how you guided your car to safety.
We have all been...
It was late at night.
I mean, we...
You know, I had the power.
Bob operates on the...
Oh, friends, put Bob in the driver's seat.
Well, I sure did.
And Bob took me...
Bob jams police radars with a single...
No, Bob just got me out of a tough situation.
And I'm here to tell anybody who's awake at this particular hour of the morning.
So...
To send money to these guys.
Yeah, definitely.
To everybody.
I think everybody should just send some money to everybody they know right now.
Immediately, even if they don't need it.
Just get out of bed.
Or wake up and get out of bed.
But I did see Bob.
And there he was with his pipe.
Well, sir, you are indeed blessed.
It is only the lucky few who actually...
The miracle that Bob has moved through this...
This man.
Bob has moved through the very bowels of this city.
The United States.
Bob definitely works in strange ways.
And fortuitous ones.
Yes, Bob specializes in strange and mysterious ways.
And it's almost never spelled out.
And as a matter of fact, the reason it's not spelled out is to...
To keep the unattuned...
The unsaved out.
There's sort of a built-in alienation factor.
From PR News in Washington.
I'm disturbing.
The Justice Department's Inspector General has rocked the region.
More than 20 U.S. attorneys across the country are vacant and empty.
On Wall Street 3, 13th, 8237.
A British court has ruled that this is British PR.
But behind.
Later this hour, congestion and delays.
Morons will address concerns about PR News.
And so, as for the night of mongoloid...
Mongoloid-odious...
That's a new word.
Mongoloid-ious music.
How was the set?
How did the hardcore set go for you?
Oh, that was great.
That was great.
We were trying to dig up all the old Devo tunes from back in the embryonic days of Devo.
Early 70s stuff.
And I wasn't sure how it was going to go over.
But we dug up that stuff and replayed it.
And all those Devo nuts went even nuttier.
How many songs were in that set?
We did about, oh, I don't know, eight songs.
Old school Devo.
Stripped down, really weird stuff.
Definitely a different taste from the stuff that's on the album.
That was pretty thorough.
Justice devolved.
It was good to begin with Mongoloid.
I think that put the crowd right in the right mood.
Agreed. Agreed.
And somebody commented to me that they saw the best Kentucky waterfall of the night.
And that belonged to you.
The way your hair was all splayed out.
It was quite wonderful.
My mullet?
Yeah.
Well, Michael Pepe calls it the Kentucky waterfall.
He should talk.
It's not really a true mullet.
You have to go to a real barber to get a proper mullet.
He's got a pair of Chester A. Arthurs that just won't quit.
It's a future comb-over is what it is.
I'm getting bald.
I'm going to have a lot to work with.
That's all right.
I can take it all the way over the top of my head, down the sides, and then form a little Amish-type beard with it.
And if an oil spill occurs, you can have it cut off and woven into a mat, which will absorb the oil.
Yeah.
You know, a lot of guys will, throughout their whole life, they'll wear their hair the way they wanted to in high school, but nobody would let them.
And that's the situation with me.
High school has such an effect.
Yeah.
Did you have the crew cut?
What, in high school?
Yeah.
I was at a school where they added a hair dress code.
We had to wear little suits.
They measure your sideburns?
I had to wear a suit and tie at school, and they called me Masta Stag.
It was a private school.
Masta Stag.
There were no girls in this school.
Only buck privates.
That's the kind of thing that can make a feller into a subgenius.
It's very frustrating.
Right there.
You already had ideas before you had ideas.
You see, you can mourn your lack of slack, but it could cause a rubbery response, a sort of a Newtonian boing in the other direction.
You could be being groomed for subgenius dumb and not even know it.
Well, that was the thing.
There weren't any girls in the school.
I was really frustrated, so I became a cult leader.
And now it's girls, girls, girls.
That's all it takes.
Want girls?
Start a cult.
Bob promised that you could have intercourse.
With a beautiful live girl or anything else.
And that's the important part.
And I was always interested in the anything else part.
And by golly, by gobs, it all came true.
His promise rings true, my friend.
His promise rung true for me, too.
True.
William Shatner as well.
Bob actually took away my slack for decades.
But when the rubber band was, it was like a slingshot being pulled back for 20 years.
That rascal.
And it finally was released.
It's been pure slack ever since.
Now, sooner or later, I'm bound to hit the wall or the glass window of the old mean man across the street,
which will set off some cosmic tirade of, you kids get off my lawn.
We'll be X day.
That's my word.
When the church, the little stone that is the church of the subgenius goes through the
plate glass window of the rich old man who is Jehovah.
Jehovah One, anyway.
President Grand Rapids Ford.
He died.
Uh, uh, uh, sex life, sex life is still kinda interesting.
But parted, parted, I, I, talk, talk, talk, talk, talk, talk, talk, long time, long time.
I'll tell you things.
Sexual addiction.
Famous dick, dick, dick, dick, dick.
I, I, but uh, but uh, I, I, I, I'm just touch that, touch that, uh, uh, touching, touching,
the, the, but, but, but, but, really weird guy, really weird guy.
Sex, sex, dirty sex, sex, dirty sex.
We, we, we, we.
We, we get along.
I was a little too worked up.
I'm a very troubled man.
Really weird guy.
You know what, you know what?
It's nothing.
I think it's something.
I, I fear.
I fear.
I, I, I, I fear.
Leave me alone!
Come on.
Agh!
The sons of God and man pale with the sun, but I speak only the truth and never in my
days have I heard the soundtrack of the British film version of Brag of the Subgenius.
Yeah, we saw that actually.
It was on the screen.
A company called Bolex Brothers did that.
They did The Secret Adventures of Tom Thumb.
That's a great film.
You know, that too is a YouTube video which is in close proximity to the videos recorded just the other night at the Mongoloid concert.
You can see the Bolex Brothers video because in searching out those other YouTube things,
I noticed that over on the right-hand side, there it was, and many other pertinent pieces of video.
If you type in subgenius on YouTube, you'll get quite an array of really awful material.
That's some real neat stuff.
Sting, are you doing some video work yourself?
Oh, yeah. I've always done that.
That's how I started out.
I was doing video.
I did video in the 50s before there was video.
He did film, ladies and gentlemen, with sprockets and photography and projectors and all that stuff.
Believe it or not.
Actually, so did I.
But he actually won awards, and then he went to other countries and made full-length motion pictures.
Yeah.
He went to Vietnam, and he made a film for them, the Vietnamese, the North Vietnamese, called The Coochie Tunnels.
Isn't that right?
Yeah.
As opposed...
As differentiated from The Coochie Girls, which was a different...
Well, they were all around, but then they usually...
And, folks, this continues.
You could probably purchase copies of the latest subgenius video iterations just from Ivan Stang at subgenius.com.
I saw Bob on night flight when I was eight years old, man, and I believed in you, but you let me down.
I was a little scared.
How about...
Sorry.
Such things as bug porn and Dobbs and Deliasticles.
Bob's Lunch Hour is now online.
That was a film that Philo Drummond and Dr. X and I started filming in 1977 and finished filming in 2007.
30 years in the making.
30 years in the making, starring Dr. Philo Drummond as Bob Dobbs, or a man named Bob Dobbs, although he doesn't...
He doesn't look anything like Bob.
And Bob's Lunch Hour, the lunch hour that lasted a thousand years...
A long lunch hour.
...actually cuts.
There's a wonderful moment when it cuts from the 1977 Philo, who looks like a 70s porno star, to the 2007 Philo, who looks like the mummy.
That crotchety old thing.
And, uh...
He looks like a 60s...
He looks like a 60s porno star.
He smells.
It's, uh, the longest lunch hour.
And it's only a ten-minute video.
Is it filling?
It hurts longer than ten minutes.
Does he feel good at the end?
Is it a good lunch hour?
No, he throws himself off the top of a building, dies, and then goes to heaven, only to find that in heaven his problem has been compounded a million-fold.
It is sad.
It's an ironic...
It's an ironic story.
That one caller that I thought was in New York was actually in Brooklyn.
What a mistake.
Brooklyn is in New York though, right?
It's a burrow.
Well, it's a burrow.
Cute little fella with long ears and a twitchy nose.
That's right.
Yeehaw!
Four hoofs.
It eats all the insects at your home.
Yeeow!
Including the ones you like.
Well, uh, I tried to ask you this while we were yakking, Stang, but, uh, did you see the mist yet?
I have to know.
The movie.
The mist.
Did you see it?
Stang.
Hello.
Ivan, can you hear?
Can you hear?
He's not here.
Oh, that's why he can't hear.
He disappeared.
He went up in a puff of smoke.
No, the mist got him.
That's right.
The mist got him again.
Well, they nearly missed him.
It was a near miss.
It was a near mist.
It was a close call.
But we need closure now.
You know, the weird thing is that we're not in the middle of the world.
The weird thing is that there's no, uh, Colonel Sphinx Drummond is not listening.
Just, you know.
Yeah.
Just.
Yeah, why?
Why?
A lot of people ask, why is Colonel Sphinx Drummond not listening to the show?
He's watching the laptop.
He's watching the home mail after me mail.
People want to know.
Yeah, what's the deal with that anyway, they say.
Why is he not?
It's his job to listen.
Why is it always the same music?
Well, out here in the hinterlands, mister, this is the kind of music we like.
Can't see him.
He has a lean and hungry look.
Now that's the show I remember.
Yeah.
Let's march out of here now.
Bold, adventurous, big, brawny and beautiful.
Somebody in Stockton is listening.
A huge, brawling, brawny, quiet.
Army.
It's an army and they're all running with scissors.
Oh, I see.
Yeah, yeah.
Out on Shattuck Avenue, trying to move the show down four blocks to the new studio.
Yep, the good old days.
Yeah, yeah.
And then on to Tokyo.
Off to Godfudd for a delicious snack.
Is that place still in business?
Yeah, just like the comic book store.
Gone.
Run by the same enthusiastic cadre of diehards and hold-ons.
Yes, a family of moonies who sold pornography for a living.
Boy, I gotta hand it to you, good beau-fram.
You know where all the bodies are buried.
How deep they are.
Yes, and how they taste.
I mean, excuse me.
He spent too much ghoulish time gooming in the graveyard.
He's gommed.
He's gomming.
Ah, he's a gore-blimey gummed them all.
Ever since his gobsnappers.
Gummed down on him.
Ground down.
Now, did you do any milking?
Get any butter while you were there?
Ghost butter?
Hey, could you give me a hand for a gummy ghouls while you were at the market?
I don't know.
Nay, thank ye.
Maybe there's something wrong with my telephone.
Gummy ghosts?
No, we hear you now.
We hear you.
Yes, we hear you.
Well, I think...
I'm just going to ask.
There's a listener in Brooklyn.
Yeah.
Maybe...
Yes.
If they're really bored and they don't have anything else to do...
Tired.
They can go to 4608 10th Avenue and throw eggs at the house.
That's a great idea.
But in Brooklyn right now, it's a quarter to eight.
This is a lot better than cash.
An egg store is actually open in 15 minutes.
So we've got remote egg products.
Here we go.
Are you sure you're free?
It's wise to egg them on that way.
If they were going to 46 10th Avenue...
Now, what was that address again?
4608.
4608 10th Avenue.
What's going on over there?
Pelt it with eggs right now.
Google it.
Make sure it's good and pelt it.
Would that work, caller?
That's silly.
You can't do that.
She's gone again.
On the northern center of California.
Oh, I see.
I see.
She's not here anymore.
She's left.
Dang.
I really like that caller.
Yeah.
Really, really like her a lot.
We like you.
Call back.
Or send one of your eggs here.
And other time.
Sit on it until it's hatched.
Speaking of events...
I can do that.
Is there something that we're supposed to...
See, I've been trying to talk about Mon-Loyne...
Due tomorrow?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's breakfast at the Brogue-France house at 830.
Some of us are just going to watch the show, but some of us are going to be in the show.
It's the big rumpus and wampus at 12 Galaxies, which is near Mission...
I mean, it's on Mission, actually, but it's near 22nd in San Francisco.
Isn't that some kind of a hideous matrix?
Yeah.
Is there a marketing of Devo and Subgenius?
Even so.
Something like that.
That's the advanced publicity.
But many people who are so distracted that they can't even read, but only skim emails,
think it actually is a Devo concert, and so you can expect the place to be mobbed.
Oh, really?
I've received inquiries about it.
All these people will be there hoping to see the Devos.
Hey, is Mother's Ball going to be at that Devo thing?
You know.
Yes.
Why don't you read the email that I send you instead of spending a second to...
cast your lazy eye over it before you call me, but...
I will be gossiping about Mark Mother's Ball on the stage.
Even John Shirley thought it was a Devo concert from his cursory glimpse at...
Yeah, their new name is Mongoloid.
So how is Mark Mother's Ball these days, anyway?
Actually, I haven't talked to him much.
Only a mother could love.
At the last devotional in Akron, I had dinner with Jerry Casale, and I asked him if his
Jihad Jerry thing was getting him much hateful.
And he said, yes!
From all angles.
Oh, bless his heart.
From the PC and the un-PC alike.
Bob Dobbs will cut him a lot of slack for that.
No, Bob actually has taken Devo for everything they were worth.
Devo was originally an experiment by J.R. Bob Dobbs, like the Monkees were another of
his experimental bands.
Jimi Hendrix, too, right?
Well, Hendrix was one that got away from it.
The guy that opened the door.
Oh, the Peaking Man.
And fled to England.
Heidelberg Man.
Devo wasn't so lucky.
Nebraska Man.
No, Devo fell for Bob Hookline and Sinker.
And Pilkda.
You can't hear the show?
Bob, in the end, he left Bob for everybody in about 16 minutes.
That'll be true.
Well, that's cruel.
They all had to get new jobs.
Better get a replacement DJ in here fast.
Is this happening to all the columns?
Can you get the choral show?
I want to hear the choral show.
No, it's saved.
Of thy bones are choral.
Yeah, it's definitely happening to all the columns.
He's back.
You can just sit here until Sunday morning and he comes in.
You can just sit here until you run.
No, no.
I just can't hear it.
You can spall your Sunday pants messing around.
I like that line.
Is this what happens to all the callers?
All the callers?
Is this how it's going to be from now on?
Yeah, honey.
I'm afraid so.
You made it with this.
From now on.
Failed to serve Bob in life.
And now, here in the afterlife.
You know, it's been honey and milk and milk and milk.
Forever and ever.
It's been a nice sweet creamery butter until now, but now it's going to be like pickles
that have been picked up off the floor and mayonnaise that's been sitting in the refrigerator
for over 21 years.
The afterlife just got a lot more interesting.
Yeah, really mushy avocados.
Just completely disgusting.
Ew.
Pass the caller into the lake of show.
But that's the way the show is.
Alligator pear.
What were you going to say?
The pizza's the size of a penny.
I was going to say...
Yes.
You were?
But then he decided not to.
Yeah.
He decided to pay for free a penny of poop.
By Robert Williams.
Yes.
All right.
Now, a trio, trio bite.
Yes.
Because they won't install a flash player.
My favorite comic book character.
Oh my God.
I'm glad she's back.
I'm just one of the ordinary ones here.
Really?
A new death experience?
What happened?
I just love it when she calls.
Me too.
So what was the new death experience?
I just love it when she does this.
I do too.
Now, you're listening to the radio, see, and that's 12 minutes ago.
Oh, oh, oh.
I think I can barely hear the show.
Barely.
Yeah, the 12 minute delay is a key to tough on listeners.
Better put something on, sweetheart, or I'm going to have a heart attack.
The show is sneaking up behind you.
Oh, maybe I can just hear something.
Yeah.
Remember, it's a ghost show, so it'll be, it'll feel kind of cold on your back.
Ghost show.
And the little short hairs will raise up because the show is so ghostly.
Are you allowed to half-dug?
Yeah.
Dugs?
No.
He's like a half-dug.
Where's my golden microphone?
I went skiing with half-dug last year.
I'm calling from another country too.
Now you can go see the Dugs, but you can't have them.
I'm calling from a country far away.
Yeah.
I remember when the Dugs were popular, but-
Are you in the far away country now?
That was before she was born.
She won't remember that time.
Yeah, she's in Oakland.
Far, far away.
Whatever happened to Dug Girl?
It's a nice country.
Fresno.
I like it here.
Dug Girl.
She dug her way up.
People that listen to KPFA don't like it.
Dug Girl died.
Yeah, people that listen to KPFA don't.
All the Dug Girls go away eventually.
Because no Dug Girl was ever called by a drug on a cell phone.
We don't talk about that country anymore because we don't want to draw their wrath.
They died of sorrow and a broken heart.
But there is, of course, a-
Dug Girls can't have cell phones.
Dug Girl on tape.
I know.
That's the problem.
It's sort of a conundrum.
The Dugs can't have cell phones and the Dug Girls die because they never called.
How come you can't hear Bishop Joey anymore?
I'm blowing up my Dug Girl doll.
What has happened to Bishop Joey?
We haven't heard from him in over half an hour.
He's blowing up his Dug Girl doll.
I'm blowing up my Dug Girl doll.
He's gone soft.
We call him Bishop Joey.
What about the ending of Bob himself?
The ending?
The death of Bob.
Oh.
Which one?
He's died many times.
That got me.
I'm going to be-puzzling evidence here, of course, was the first person to take, that
we know of, to take Bob at his command and kill him.
And he did.
And puzzling evidence.
I was there.
It happened a few feet away from me.
I'll never forget it.
I understand there were sightings of numerous gunmen.
Yes.
As always.
That's right.
But there was one that was clearly there.
And then Bob Black smashed him over the head with a bottle.
He was the Jack Ruby of the game.
Yeah.
It was all a terrible muddle and confusion.
And then Jayner hit Bob Black over the head.
And then Bucknacket hit Jayner over the head.
And then so on and so on.
Yes.
Tales of vanished, vanquished subgeniuses.
Looks like someone's calling in now.
Let's go to that caller.
Caller, you're on the air.
I just turned on this radio program.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I don't know what you guys are doing.
You're the audience.
We're the funny guys.
You tell us what's going on.
We don't really have much of a clue.
How does it seem to you?
I just want to know what's happening.
Okay, you play Pete Goldie.
What's happening over there?
Well, we did bring out the telescope earlier.
We were just looking at the stars.
We weren't doing anything else.
Yeah.
Now we're looking through the other end of the stars.
We are looking for a director of the program tonight.
Could you help us out?
Just give us some direction?
I don't know why I'm here.
Actually, you've won a prize tonight by calling in.
Yeah, a brand new sigmoidoscope.
Yeah, we're going to use it right now.
And we're going to look for the money to send Mongoloid out of the state.
I need a new outlet.
Well, let's facilitate your inward turning by asking you, since I have a feeling you
were at the concert, what your impression was.
I just turned the radio program on.
I don't know what you're talking about.
The really good part of the concert.
Oh, my God.
Oh, come on.
Well, then tell us the best part of the best concert you were at.
It was the Mongoloid concert.
Of course, we know that.
But what was the best part?
And the very last set was the best part.
Last set was the best?
Absolutely.
Yeah.
After the guy stang, stop talking.
Yeah, after the...
That made me stop talking.
That guy stang.
The big hook came out and grabbed him.
Yeah.
We weren't going to wait until...
But we just decided to go ahead on and prove to be a providential...
Yeah.
...provision.
I think every act should rush the stage and push away the prior act like history itself.
I agree.
Caller, can you...
That should be part of show business.
Please, caller, please, caller, turn up your radio.
Caller, please, we don't...
We need your radio louder, please.
No, no, it's not...
It's a...
No.
It hurts.
I know, I know, but it's a good thing.
We need the feedback, please, caller.
We need a loop.
We need an endless loop, please.
No, no, no.
I'm not going to help you.
This is like the opening shot of a apocalypse now.
No, no, no.
In your mind, though.
Leave me out of your little game you play.
Or as Dobbs is reputed to have said, believe me out of it.
I'm not going to go there.
I'm not going to come with you.
You are there.
We are there.
Yeah, exactly.
We are already there.
I'm counting on an updraft to make me taller.
I don't think we have a choice.
That's all I need in this world.
That's all I want, is to be taller.
Hey, Michael.
That booboo...
Michael, you're on the internet now, right?
This show is messing with my head, Matt.
What kind of show is this?
Ask him if he's on the internet, Matt.
Exactly what kind of sound effects were you recording?
Are you on the internet now, Matt?
I was telling somebody about that the other day.
Michael, you're on the internet now.
Yeah.
Just what sort of types were you?
You can hear me asking you, Mr. Whistle Radio.
Well, I'm listening to your radio.
I'm talking to your radio.
It's just show, officer.
But let me try to turn up my computer.
It's all right, officer.
It's supposed to be orange.
No, you don't turn up your nose at me, officer.
You're on the internet now, young man.
No, when you're on the internet...
And Earth has sent the force over.
No, I mean, he's not...
When I say, is he on the internet, he's off the air.
Is he on the internet to show you something?
Of course he's on the internet.
He's got an iMac.
He's got a little camera on there, and he wants to talk to all the girls that...
I like calling them talking head girls.
I've reached out to them.
I've reached out to them all, too.
The endless talking head girls.
You know talking head girls?
Yes.
They'll take you the rest of your life to talk to all the girls.
Didn't talking head girls do a song about you?
My favorite is one that does the...
She doesn't talk at all.
Okay, be careful.
And she pretends to be Japanese.
It looks like she's in Utah.
She's turning Japanese.
She is.
Bye-bye.
Michael Pepe, say goodbye.
Michael Pepe is going?
No.
And there are other Japanese women who pretend to be real, but they're...
Michael Pepe in our land.
It's a sad day.
Another Michael Pepe gone.
Michael, we hardly knew you.
We'll miss you when you're gone.
We'll miss you when you're awake.
No, no.
We'll miss you when you're good and bad.
I'm just going into the box.
Oh.
Oh, okay.
All right, let me turn down everything.
Okay, yeah.
You gotta turn down that box.
All right, here, you turn down that duty box, Mike.
The box is...
So, um, wait, can you see by any chance the...
Wait, what, Baron Von Traveler?
Wait, now they're saying-
Okay.
They have special subgenius names.
You know what?
I have...
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, Shane.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey, hey, oh, I know them bittersweet.