NAN NAN NAN NAN
NAN
NAN TAN NAN
Stop!
There's shit to pay for a kite!
x8
Time to rock.
Too much.
Too often.
Time to rock.
I'm in there and have to dig life with father, and I mean father slack.
Too much.
Hi, it's Pat Paulson.
I just want to say that I endorse Bob as my running mate in this year's election,
and this is the hour of slack in Dallas, Texas.
You know, I know where that is.
Coming up on your morning stream,
station it's the hour of slack drive by comedy hour once again your wacky hosts ivan stang and
lonesome cowboy dave help ease your morning commute with a fun-filled hour of classic rock
laughs and trivia where you can win fabulous prizes so stay tuned to your classic rock station
coming up right after this
goodbye earth good morning planet x
say your prayers little one don't forget my son to include everyone
i tuck you in warm within keep you free from sin
till the sun comes up and you're free to go
and then he comes
sleep with one eye open
gripping your pillow tight
eggs and lights
enter night
take my hand
we're off to never never land
that's all
for
sang
intense
grave
all
basically
time
ad
alarm
All your money back, all of the religions will be having a heart attack
A pipe full of froth equals what?
A lot of slack, no matter how you kill it, he always keeps coming back
Bob, I'm talking about Dobbs
Repent, quit your job and slack off
Get ready to blast off when Ed Stain comes
And all the geeks are on the run from Bob
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob
Pull the wool over your own eyes
Start to realize what till now has been disguised
Keep looking through the skies at the saucers flying by
And maybe by and by you will see the light at the end of the pipe that leads to Bob Dobbs
Bob Dobbs, talking about the salesman
To the gods, he's still a chap that coughed and bled
On a conspiracy of normality
Oh, who could it be but Bob?
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob
Ahhh, I'm rails
Boy, my, black, brown
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob
Billy Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob
Cracking into a Admiral
Bob, switch and you won't regret
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob
Grr
Now there is no difference between truth and lies
The rich became the beggar and the fool became the wise
Cause it's a way out, far out, psychedelic freak out
Took a hit of pop and I'm startin' to peak out
Geek out, my friends are gonna leak out
Look out everyone, here he comes, it's Bob
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob
You wish you could forget
You wish you could forget about Bob
Everybody up here is so crazy about Bob
Everybody up here is so crazy about Bob.
Ugh.
Oh, yeah.
You know what time it is.
All right, dude.
Well, time to rock, friends.
And the Bob rap were by this new guy, the great Neptune.
Yes, the great Neptune.
We're going to be playing tons more stuff by the great Neptune,
who is at www.neptune.itgo.com
or josephficus at yahoo.com, friends.
And we heard, well, this whole show is the show designed to drive you insane
and make you think somebody slipped you a Mickey.
Isn't that a pretty good meter?
And so we also heard Pat Boone and Modemac driving you crazy.
And upcoming, friends.
J.R. Bob Dobbs himself.
And in the background, we hear MC Kevrock with time control.
Come on, Bob.
Come on in.
And the worst thing was that I got a little angel baby hair in my spaghetti.
That was the worst thing.
I hate angel baby hair in my spaghetti.
Once I get to my spaghetti, I start to get a little noodley, you know.
I hate that.
I hate to feel noodley.
You know, once you run around here along the sun,
you can't have a little too long.
You just get noodley, you know.
You start to hang out a little too long.
And it's noodley.
The noodle starts to noodle. That's a sad day.
I hate it when my little doodly-doodle starts to fart along.
So I try to rub things on it.
And little tiny toes.
Little baby toes all over the tent too.
There's one right up there, Bob.
Right up on the sleeve of the shirt of the jacket of the tent.
On the sleeve of the shirt of the tangly, fangly...
Okay, and now I want you to gently feel your neighbor's nipple to your left and to your right.
Bob?
I ain't got it any younger and I gotta settle down.
Find a wife and make a move to the white-bred part of town.
Get a job and work it for the man when they don't really appreciate you.
I'll shiny go watch in the bed on the back when your hard years of labor are through.
Don't want no babies.
Don't want no wife.
Don't want no nine to five.
I want a life.
Don't want no babies.
Don't want no wife.
Don't want no nine to five.
I want a life.
People say that I gotta know a place.
I ain't got it any younger and I gotta settle down.
Find a wife and make me a move to the white-bred part of town.
Get a job and work it for the man when they don't really appreciate you.
I'll shiny go watch in the bed on the back when your hard years of labor are through.
And I don't want no babies.
Don't want no wife.
Don't want no nine to five.
I want a life.
Don't want no babies.
Don't want no wife.
Don't want no nine to five.
I want a life.
Cause I love to play music
Love to make money
Love to meet women
Is that so funny?
Love to play music
Love to make money
Love to meet whereby
Is that so funny?
No!
People say I gotta grow up, I ain't getting any younger
And I gotta settle down
Find a wife, make a move too
Walk islands
Get a job, working for the man
But they don't give a shit about you
I'll shiny go watch in the bed on the back
When your heart gets a labor of cruel
Well, don't want no babies
Don't want no wife
Don't want no nine to five
I want a life
Don't want no babies
Don't want no wife
Don't want no nine to five
I want a life
Cause I love to play music
Love to make money
Love to meet women
Is that so funny?
Love to play music
Love to make money
Love to meet women
Is that so funny?
No!
Yeah!
Gillas does that for you
du ee
I'm evenly separated
There's still more to show
Do they think we're just ordinary people
Yeah!
can do to avert this grim fate. This economic depression is far too great for any of us
to overcome, and there is nothing left for America to do but suffer. All is lost. The
situation is hopeless. Yes, we as a nation are doomed. Doomed, doomed, doomed.
Next song.
Ah yes, it took a little while until we found something that was, how shall I say, more
spiritually enlightening.
To our, to our generation.
To our atmosphere of new reality.
Uh, I don't know the title for this song. Andrew, I'm sure, will write it down on the
tape afterwards. But here we go.
I, I, I fear.
Hello?
Boys and girls and snuggles.
The floppy bunny.
How you like my ears?
They're really floppy, huh?
And really fuzzy.
Ha ha ha.
The floppy crowd.
Everywhere.
Oh look!
There's a thump.
Fuzzy bear.
Everybody be happy.
Or else.
Cotton candy and clowns.
Balloons flying in the sky.
Ha ha ha.
Everybody be happy.
Don t question how or why.
Happiness is gambitory.
Sadness is a sin .
Don't be ugly.
Be cute and snuggly.
Ha ha.
Be fuzzy, furries in love.
Fist is knuckles, you're coming down.
Real cuteness is what I want.
Must be cute, don't be scary.
Gotta be furry, don't be hairy.
Happiness is mandatory.
No sad ending to the story.
Do you feel cute?
Well, do you?
Do you feel punk?
Oh, look at my fluffy tail.
Oh, it's so fluffy and got me.
And everyone must be cute.
Everyone must be cute.
All cute people must be obeyed.
All uncute people must be destroyed.
The final solution to ugliness will be revealed by the cute.
Cute.
We must have big bright eyes.
We must all be cute.
We must all look up in the sky and see the white fluffy clouds.
I'm cute.
You're cute.
We're all cute.
Hello, Bob.
This is Father Guido Sarducci, formerly Pope Maurice of the People's Catholic Church,
and all of my fellow popes from the People's Catholic Church.
Salute to the Church of the Sabbath Genius.
Carry on.
Hail Mary, Hail...
Hail Mary...
Hail Mary.
The Nerve
Nerve
You don't deserve this phone abuse
So please just stay your wife
Work in a graveyard shift
From black to blue to white
I'm standing in white light
I have no clue to help me through
So please let's take the night
Work in a graveyard shift
More things in heaven and earth than in your books
I was working the graveyard shift late one Sunday night
Making sure all the trains were running smooth and uptight
Keeping a close eye on the back beat and 409
Making sure the trains were running on time
Then I lucked off into the cold distance
And what did I see?
Looked like one solitary headlight coming after me
One solitary headlight with his eyes on me
Come and take me away
Working a graveyard shift
Is life too weird?
to be funny.
I won't think so.
Do you?
Only you can save your soul.
You've got to get off the devil's payroll.
Get off the devil's payroll.
I stand before you a change man
Just the way the Lord had planned
Try as you can understand
If you get off the devil's payroll
Get off the devil's payroll
I hope you know these words ring true
The Lord he just has love for you
Let the spirit take you to
And you can get off the devil's payroll
Get off the devil's payroll
That's what mama said to me just
Trust the Lord he'll set you free
But only you can save your soul
You gotta get off the devil's payroll
Get off the devil's payroll
Heal to Bob
Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob
Bob is a rock
Bob is a tree
Bob is a bear
And Bob is a bee
Now this ain't all that deep
Well, do it, Godikat Godikat W BREATHES ALL OF THE B finans
And Bob is lies, Bob is cakes and fruits and pies.
Bob's my hassle, Bob's my watch, Bob's my sandwich, Bob's my crotch.
Bob's my toothpick, Bob's my brain, Bob's that ugly yellow stain.
Bob's a cactus, Bob's an itch, Bob is taking off every stitch.
Bob's my master, Bob's my slave, Bob will rob me, Bob will save.
Bob's my toaster, Bob's my fridge, Bob's my little sister Mitch.
Bob will cost you, Bob is free, Bob's the luck and Bob's the key.
In short, Bob Dobbs is the man who used your leg as a frying pan.
If your mind is a jar, you can pour down the same.
Bob, Bob is Bob, Bob's church, Bob's the most thing Bob liked.
Jump, jump up and down for Bob!
Cause Bob is the future!
Woo!
Come on you lazy ass, drag off and don't jump!
Bob!
You can see the future, it surrounds you and it surrounds the imagery in the church.
Bob is the industrial information and quantum revolution.
Bob is the color of the future.
What color is the future?
Bob is the bright refraction of the quantum field around us.
It's because Bob has slack.
Slack is the quantum field!
And that's why I'm on my knees praying now.
Praying here before Bob.
Because I am Bob.
You know, and that's the odd thing is because, you know, I don't know if my mom was raped by a
parathletic, uh, man with blonde hair.
Who was delivering milk, pounding the milk.
Getting a little hard, but, you know, but there it was.
And I just came.
And I just came again.
And I just keep coming.
I can't help, I can't help but come here, you know.
It's a special thing.
Hallelujah brother!
And Bob is going to lead us into the future.
Bob is going to be the next revolution.
Bob is going to be the nanotech revolution, the quantum revolution, the spiritual revolution!
Ah!
Woo!
All right, yeah.
All these dot coms that you see, there's only one dot com that matters.
And that is www.subgenius.com!
Woo!
So what does this all have to do with you?
Well, you guys, you're yetis.
You are the future.
You have to use that quantum field for your future.
You guys have to make the apocalypse happen.
The more you're yourself, the faster the apocalypse will come.
Ah!
Well, right!
Right!
Orhhh!?
Just like that?
Okay.
Okay, have a nice holiday.
Please…
Dreams of war, dreams of liars, dreams of dragon's fire and the things that would bite.
Sleep with one eye open, gripping your pillow tight.
Exit light, enter night.
Rain of sand, we're off to Never Never Land.
Hi, this is Pat Paulson. I'd like to endorse Bob as my running mate in this year's election.
Bob's a lot of, well, he's not fun.
But anyway, this is the Hour of Slack in Dallas, Texas.
One of my shoes got cow stuff on them.
It's the way conspiracy works, friends.
Conspiracy creeps into every human endeavor by nature of humanity.
That's why we just tried to say, well, screw you.
We're humans. We're subgeniuses. We're different.
Subgenius can be any age, any size, shape, color, from any background, any nationality, any damn planet or species.
We don't care as long as they have the fragment of Bob consciousness
and have sent $30 to P.O. Box 1436 Dallas, Texas, and my P.O.
Oh, yes, friends.
You can be saved even if it...
kills you.
And that's how much Bob loves you, friends.
He will kill you to save you.
Because, you know, once you're saved and Bob, you never really die.
You know, it's, you know, there's an old saying, what Bob offers, his most famous discovery.
Eternal salvation or triple your money back.
What other words it offers that, friends?
If you don't live forever, you get your money back.
A perfect, perfect formula for belief and love and, uh, slack.
Or slack, whatever that is.
Slack for me would be to shut up for a minute.
It's been a long day.
Someday the exes will come.
Bob's promise will come true.
Our alien benefactors will give us our own planets.
And we will be able to create the 25-hour day.
The 26-hour day.
The Martian pineslip.
The day that lasts forever.
The night that never ends, dear friends.
The night that smells like cinnamon for three days and then it smells like, uh, epoxy the next three days.
Any planet you want.
The most bizarre, outlandish things you can imagine could come physically, literally true.
You better hope you have a pure mind when that happens.
You better hope that you aren't thinking real paranoid bad thoughts in the back of your mind at the moment when every wish then come true.
You better hope that you really have some good wishes in your head.
And so you can't be constantly thinking about how you're gonna get back at that conspiracy bastard or so forth.
Friends, you gotta just learn to rise above it.
Time control is what Bob has been preaching all along.
And unfortunately, until we get the time machines working, the only true form of time control available to us is that boring virtue called patience.
And that's why you need to remember about the funny little monkeys.
Because otherwise, it's so easy to lose patience with them.
And God knows, only Bob stands between most of us and us becoming mad serial killers, machine gunning,
entire lives.
And we're gonna have to get our perfect dongs full of pink boys out of their smugness.
Kneel down.
You ain't what you're not.
So you see what you got.
You are what you is.
And that's all it is.
A foolish young man from a middle class family started singing the blues cause he thought it was manly.
Now he talk like a kingfish.
From a Amos and Andy.
And I'm gonna have to get my ass kicked.
Holy pockiness.
He tell you that chin lens.
Well, they taste just like candy.
He thinks that he's got the whole thing down.
From the Nibbley Ocean to the Royal Crown.
Do you know what you are?
You are what you is.
You is what you am.
A cow don't make ham.
You ain't what you're not.
So you see what you got.
You are what you is.
And that's all it is.
A foolish young man of the Negro persuasion.
Persuasion?
Did he say persuasions?
Devoted his life to become a Caucasian.
He stopped eating pork.
He stopped eating greens.
He traded his dashi again.
For some Jordache jeans.
He learned to play golf.
And he got a good score.
Now he said to himself.
I ain't no nigger no more.
Chika boom, chika boom.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I don't understand you, Boama Macumba.
Would you speak a little clearly, Mercedes Benz?
Mercedes Benz, hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
That's your mama, baby.
Who is who?
I don't know.
And what is what?
Something I just got to know.
And why is this?
Somebody tell me now.
Appropriate.
That's a funny pronunciation if I ever don't like.
But you don't like.
Where did you get that word?
But you have got.
You have got.
I spend my days.
Driving in the dirt, yeah.
And letting it rot.
I can smell it now.
Someone else.
Here they come, here they come, here they come.
The Shirley car.
I told you they were coming.
To pick it up.
To pick it up, yeah.
Because he wants some.
And she wanted for free.
And when one day.
And then one day.
You wonder who.
You used to was.
Who was it anyway.
And what you do.
I used to work at the post office.
You scratch your head.
I scratch my head.
And look around.
I don't want to, I don't want to do that.
But what you lost.
Just so you see.
Will not be found.
It just can't be found.
Do you know what you are?
I'm gonna buy me a Mercedes.
You are what you get.
I need a big red one now.
Here is what you have.
An Avalon 450 SLC.
It can't make hair.
Oh yeah.
You ain't what you know.
Some dark club sticking out of the truck.
So you see what you got.
I don't want down till it rakes my head.
You are what you live.
Do you want to see my grime?
I'm not gonna give you my grime.
You are what you live.
I'm high.
You are beautiful.
You are what you live.
This is some lumpy gravy you make here.
And that's all it is.
I look like a man to bongo.
You are what you live.
And your mama.
And that's all it is.
Give me a car with a head.
You are what you live.
I'm a boxer.
I'm sure of that.
And that's all it is.
I don't need no pancakes with my head.
You are what you live.
I know a fat old policeman.
He's always on our street.
A fat and jolly red-faced man he really is a treat.
He's dont quite born a policeman.
He's never known ast ground and everybody says he is the happiest man in town.
Hahahaha!!
Hehehehehe!
Hehehehehe!!
Hahahaha!!
Hehehehehehe!!
A overall in the うдщ joke of what can happen.
Finding a good seat to sit in.
He laughs upon pointy feet
He laughs upon his feet
He laughs at everybody when he's walking in the street
He never can stop laughing
He says he's never tried
But once he did arrest a man and laughed until he cried
His jolly face it wrinkled
And then he shut his eyes
He opened his great mouth
It was a wondrous sight
He laughed at everybody when he's walking in the street
He said I must arrest you
He didn't know what for
And then he started laughing
Until he dragged his jaw
So if you chance to meet him
When walking round the town
Just shake him by his fat old hand
And give him half a crown
His eyes will beam and sparkle
He'll gurgle with delight
And then you'll start him laughing
With all his blessed mind
Ha ha ha ha ha
Haha
He lit my ear
He wet his fingers
Ha ha ha ha ha
Ha ha ha
He wet PAW
He wet his fingers
Ha ha ha ha
Oh, you're just going to make me stare it out and think about love.
And you know what the bad thing about, the bad thing is about love is it's a subgenius love.
And you know what a subgenius love is?
Fire and burning and death.
Large holes.
Yeah, there's just not enough large holes, you know.
I really tried to make large holes with my potato cannons, but they just didn't quite reach.
You know, I pounded and pounded.
I pounded.
I've got a doodle in my noodle and his name is Minky Boodle.
Minky Boodle.
I got my mojo rising.
There's a poodle in my strudel.
Minky Boodle.
Cruddle doodle.
Goodle.
Poodle, poodle, poodle, zoodle.
I'm sick of this.
Minky Boodle.
Shut up, Brack.
No.
Stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it.
I got a doodle in my noodle and his name is Minky Boodle.
Stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it.
Be beautiful.
Stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it.
Crazin'.
Aw, Bob.
Yeah.
Get up, everything.
Work my life away
I break my back
I never get any slack
When next day comes
All you peeps better run
Cause the excess
Might blow up the sun
If life was what it used to be
Fuck them and they can't take a joke
A ton of particles
Oppenheimer's split
And as for Bob
Yeah, he cut the shit
When next day comes
All you peeps better run
Cause the excess
Might blow up the sun
If life was what it used to be
Fuck them and they can't take a joke
Bob's a rocker
If life's just a rocker
You just can't believe everything you believe
You just can't believe it at all
Oh, yes, Bob's Your Uncle by the Reverend LeChuck, delivered to alt-binary slack in mp3.form.
Before that, we heard Space Ghost with Minky Boodle and You Are What You Is.
That was The Persuasions doing Zappa from their album, Frankly Acapella.
And before that, we heard some preaching from the Puffer Dome at Starwood 2000 with Einstein's Secret Orchestra and yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang.
Friends, this is the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
And if you want more information about Bob, you just write to this post office box I'm about to give.
I'm giving it right now. Here it comes.
P.O. Box 14306, Dallas, Texas 7521.
Once again, that's Bob at Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
And we've got some special Brother Cleve remastered hymnification coming right up.
So stay tuned to www.subgenius.com.
This is Ego Plum with EbolaMusic.com in the background.
Ego Plum.
I know he can make it
Without him we can't take it
We'll lose the pieces of our minds
To the pink boys and the whims
Until the day that he comes back
It'll be a world without slack
Mom's a boy, oh
And he's coming again
Bob is my lord
If we don't want the answers upon us
Then we need Bob to be honest
Bob is my lord
And he's coming again
Great God, he's coming for me right now
Again
Wow.
Great Pope Bob.
This is an epistle from the Reverend David Lee Black.
Reverend Stank, you'll be the...
I don't believe this.
Read the first and last paragraph.
Dear fellow sub-geni,
The evil forces of anti-slack that prevent me from going to America
Are the very same ones that prevent me from being with my brothers and sisters of slack on X-Day in Brushwood.
Subsequently,
I think he meant consequently.
I must have my own X-Day in Kiel, Germany with my brothers and sisters of slack here.
There's nothing, I mean nothing,
That will stop me from getting on board the intergalactic love ships
On Wednesday, the 5th of July.
And being with the rest of you.
Not the DEA, not Janet Cujo-Reno, not Bill Clinton and his hordes of concubines.
Not customs, not even Mulder and Scully and the reanimated corpse of J. Edgar Hoover could
stop me when that platform lowers, the red carpet rolls out, and I'm carried on board
in a throne like an African chieftain by my leather-clad alien love slaves of the cosmos.
I had a dream the other night, which makes me believe this year it is.
This is the day.
The year.
One of the love goddesses came to me in a dream like a space cherub loved succubus.
She floated through the air and revealed to me a divine revelation, which I make known to you now.
On her right leg and left leg there were ten holes, and a piece in the middle, there were three.
And in the middle there were three holes.
She could suckle twenty-three.
Twenty.
Which is the number of the Illuminator.
She took my hand and we floated up to the heavens.
The pills are kicking in about this part in the epiphany.
A Barmageddon.
And anyway, he foresees a battle of Barmageddon where the demonic forces which you guys were
talking about which have enslaved the human race with the yoke of bad television and have
sold them sportswear, media-induced self-consciousness, landmines, and cheap adrenaline-producing
drugs to then herd their unwitting victims into soccer stadiums and then send them to
pop-star concert halls only to farm their pain and misery to feed its insatiable appetite
for hurt and suffering have finally realized that the exes know about their evil intentions
to make hostile bids for benign alien space corporations only to peddle their superficial
cheapness, Hollywood black magic, and sow space minds so they can create a hell in space.
The Intergalactic Federation of Alien Races, which currently live in peace and harmony,
will not tolerate their Universal Garden of Eden to be invaded by the evil monkey-snake
god of Earth.
The evil demon-monkey-snake god who will replace all the stars with poison apples and sell
fig leaves to the goddesses who have 23 holes.
This is so black I'll write it.
As I looked down into Earth, I saw the saucers hovering over Brushwood, Lemuria, and Kiel.
Yeah!
I'm so glad you're here.
I saw smaller craft hovering over several other locations where subgenius ministers
who are rich in slack but poor in human money supposedly reside.
I could see the masses of the illuminated with their suitcases of cool boarding the
saucers of love, hope, and happiness.
As they did, the armies of Earth scrambled to destroy the invading love ships of the
sex goddesses, the very threat to their existence.
Then it was the great and final war.
As the last space saucer, sex space saucer, lifted high into the heavens.
The great war began.
The navies and air armadas with their rapid response forces scrambling to attack.
I could hear the sirens of war around the planet wailing, heralding the inescapably
impending doom that awaited citizens of this sinking battleship of hate, war, and misery.
But the great armies of Earth didn't battle with the star cruisers of the love goddesses.
They battled with themselves.
They battled with each other for the right to battle with the invading saucers of slack.
Hovering up over the planet as it burned.
I was so glad.
I could hear the screams of billions of human souls who weren't lucky enough to get off
this planet with the chosen ones.
The alien sex goddesses took my hand again and floated with me back down to Earth, to
my bed, back to my alcoholic narcosa.
And so I awakened with this revelation I now give.
And with this revelation I also send the symbolic other half in the form of a cake.
I want Stang to have everyone laugh.
I want the lineup for this cake to be ritualistically served as communion of slack for all at Exday
in Brushwood.
Make sure Nikki Death Chick gets a big piece.
I want a lion's share of the ass whopping next time I see her.
How many minutes was purchase in adultery?
How many times have you been intentional sit box with your nose.
Make out, pipette?
Do us a favor and join me.
Our plans inよ minuti...
I'm sorry.
If we just get a grip on our man-to-hand relationship
Come to terms with truly how we feel
If we put our heads together
We'd just stay home forever, dear penis
I beg I like you after all
Oh, and Rodney, while you're shaving, shave my balls