This here's Tater Gumfries reminding you that X-Day's a-comin' July 5th,
and ain't nothin' you can do to slow it down nor stop it,
so you might as well get yourself down to the Brushwood Folklore Center in Sherman, New York,
and get ready to rupture.
Friends, we're at X-Day, or off-planet or something,
and therefore this hour of slack is not the one you were expecting,
but a rerun of number 951 from 7X-Day 2005.
We interrupt this program to activate the emergency...
Some genius hour of slack!
What?
Yarr!
Yes, friends.
Well, you know, according to subgenius prophecy,
the space monster, Jehovah One,
told mystic salesman J.R. Bob Dobbs
that the world would end for everybody except subgenius cult members
at 7 a.m. on July 5th.
Well, my friends, we still aren't really home yet
from the New York celebrations of X-Day.
Our minds aren't home yet.
So you might as well consider this a live X-Day show,
even though the event itself, July 5th, was weeks ago.
Friends, we're always behind after X-Day
because we've been doing a lot of work.
We're going to blow everything off,
assuming that our guru, J.R. Bob Dobbs,
is going to be right this time.
We weren't harvested,
but yet we harvested lots of recordings,
such as this of Acid Corpse performing at Brushwood,
and we harvested many subgenius' radio shows,
such as the KPFA Berkeley show,
the WREK show in Atlanta,
Bob's Lifetime Funhouse,
and, uh,
the WCSB show in Cleveland,
and Dr. Sinister's.
And we'll start with the KPFA Puzzling Evidence show, friends,
with Dr. Howell at Puzzling Evidence
and Philo Drummond's X-Day Report.
Yes, everyone's somewhat world-weary here.
Because you know what?
These fine young folks have just returned from X-Day
and they're coming back in their triumphant post-X-Day parade now.
Yeah.
We had pictures.
because all we do is advance straightforwardly.
We're going to have an X-Day parade from this little Tuesday,
Somewhat bedraggled and debauched,
what marvelous sights one sees at X Day.
But one thing we did see, of course,
is when we assembled at 7 o'clock a.m.
We're trying to talk to Philodrumon down on the field.
He is there, and we will be connecting with Philodrumon momentarily.
It was at X Day that we gathered at 7 a.m.
on July 5th, 2004.
And as we waited in the shade of the main pavilion,
a band played, and then all eyes went to the zenith of the sky
where a huge, round, glittering shape rapidly lowered down,
expanding in size and blotting out the light
with an enormous metallic humming like the ringing of a glass.
Or the buzzing of innumerable bees.
Long, telescoping legs extended and...
Hear that bee in the background? He was just buzzing, buzzing.
Well, you know, the main theme now is for the whole of the audience
is they want to know what happened at X Day.
Well, I'm telling you.
Well, a lot of people want to know what happened at X Day.
They keep asking that question.
Now, next up on Monday, July 5th,
at 7 a.m. Eastern Daylight Time,
our Earth will be at athelion,
which means that it will be at its farthest point away from our sun for the entire year.
Almost 3 million miles farther away
than it was when it was at perihelion, its closest, last January 4th.
And then, get ready for a super goodie.
All right, Atlanta.
Perhaps we have something for you here.
Yes, perhaps. Who knows?
It's one of those things that, like this church, it's wild and unpredictable.
We are going to attempt to...
We are going to attempt to get a live update from X Day.
From Brushwood, from Ground Zero.
Ground Zero, 7 a.m., July 5th.
That's where the smoking's going to start.
It'll spread outward from there.
All right, well, let's try to punch them in.
Let's see if this thing's working.
Hello, do we have Brushwood?
Atlanta to Brushwood, over.
I think we're being jammed at the source.
Uh-oh.
Oh, my God.
You don't think they did it at Jonestown already?
There's something.
Oh, my God.
Suzy, I don't know if you can hear me, but here at X Day number 7, it is a complete catastrophe.
I am watching the fire eat away at the very heavens right now.
It was a terrible tragedy, the pipe of fog that we had in the fire circle whenever the burning cross finally fell.
Oh, what the fuck?
It disgorged a little gift for all of humanity.
And it's currently burning.
It's burning down everything that we ever loved.
I knew it was going to be good.
And yet we somehow feel much more cleansed for it.
And now, with more details, is the Reverend Ivan Singh on site.
Oh, no, that crummy bitch.
It's a perfect success if death and destruction is...
Suzy, are you there?
Yes, yes, I'm here, but you can't hear me.
It's a nightmare, and yet it's like heaven.
It's like a Jack Chick comic come to life.
It's what every X Day is supposed to be.
Surely the saucers will be here.
Oh, damn it!
Damn it!
What?
Oh, my God, it's silent.
The police are coming.
We're going to have to...
We may not be able to be on for long.
Hold it!
Hold on.
What?
Suzy, hold on just one second.
No, don't get away from me!
You goddamn...
I don't know!
I don't know what to do!
You can't stop!
Ow!
Oh!
Oh, well, there goes our connection.
I'm afraid we've lost them.
Have we lost them?
Hello? Hello?
Uh-oh.
Okay, so that's what's going on at Brushwood.
I knew they'd be having a great time without me there.
Damn it, it sounded like they were all bleeding pretty good.
I think that term would be hemorrhaging.
They were hemorrhaging slack.
And it was such a hemorrhage of slack that they couldn't hear our unslacked voices.
And, man, I really need that sort of stuff to bathe in.
I can't find virgins anymore.
Oh, no, you can't find a good virgin these days.
Well, virgin on the ridiculous, but they don't go for the technical virgins.
Ah, it's starting.
The floppy boot.
Okay, now we started.
Then the X-Day Parade kicked off.
This is inspirational.
To be here at the X-Day Parade.
At the 2000.
2004 X-Day Celebration.
While we wait for the saucer to descend.
And we also are on our...
Clear sky.
No sign of a saucer yet, but we're all hoping and waiting.
Except, of course, for Philo Drummond, who decided to stay at home in his bed,
reading the National Review.
But the rest of us are...
Wait a minute.
Is that something that we see up there in the sky?
A glittering brown?
It is.
It's the saucer.
It's coming down.
Oh, this is just great.
The crowd is really reacting.
Look at there.
The enthusiasm.
And the saucer now makes its way through the float parade.
Look at those great little cutout characters of space aliens on top of the saucer.
Those aren't cutouts.
I believe they're made out of roses.
They're actually razor-thin aliens.
Razor-thin and razor-sharp, I might add.
That's right.
You wouldn't want them to make a...
You don't want to stroke those aliens on the edge.
You don't want to cut your hands.
I don't want to stroke those aliens at all, Philo,
but it may be that I'll have to.
It may be that we'll all have to.
You'll have to.
We all have to stroke the aliens.
Since it's going to be a new day and a new world
since we've been visited by our visitors from afar.
You have to stroke the aliens sometime.
You can depend on me, darling.
Well, I better the aliens have a stroke.
I do depend on you to help me stroke the alien.
All right.
I think we've stroked this alien thing for all it's worth.
Isn't that a dance like Shock the Monkey that somebody did?
Stroke the alien.
Okay, if you say so.
Wasn't it Cha-Cha-Cha?
I hope they have nice cities.
No, it wasn't.
Yeah, well, they do have nice cities.
It's hard enough to do these dance moves.
They're half underground, half above ground.
Yeah, this is when the saucers show up over you guys' heads.
I was strolling through the park one night
And oh, I felt so blue
When I heard a little voice say
I'm so lonely
Then I turned around to look
And to my surprise
A little space girl said
They're crying right before my eyes
Stepping up a little closer
To see what I could see
She said
Mr. Earthman, will you please marry me?
I said, why, no, I couldn't do that
Well, that just wouldn't happen
Couldn't be right
Cause you and me
And me and you
We don't even look alike
Cause you've got four arms
The better to hold you
Three lips
The better to kiss you
Three eyes
All the better to see
I can really rock and swing
Cause I've got more of everything
Oh, Mr. Earthman, will you marry me?
Then I said, what will people think
When we go strolling by?
Why, they not only laughed at us
They lay right down and died
Then they'd put you and me in jail
There we would be
And the people, they'd come from miles around
Just to look at you and me
Cause you've got four arms
The better to hold you
Three lips
The better to kiss you
Three eyes
All the better to see
I can really rock and swing
Cause I've got more of everything
Oh, Mr. Earthman, will you marry me?
I said, this ain't gone far enough
I've had enough of it
She said, please, Mr. Earthman
Just one little kiss
I said, okay, okay
Okay, okay, but then you go away. But when I finished kissing her, I had this to say. Oh, you've got four arms. The better to hold you. Three lips. The better to kiss you. Three eyes. Oh, the better to see.
I can really rock and swing. Cause I've got more of everything. Oh, Mr. Earthman, will you marry me?
Why, sure.
A thanks to Artemia Salina for sending that one in. And now, Reverend Carter LeBlanc, live at Brushwood.
So, it's X Day. It's almost X Day. It's, uh, let's see, how far are we? Anybody got a countdown calendar going?
How many more minutes till the end of the world? No, I didn't think so.
Nobody really even seems to be paying attention. I think everybody is kind of suspecting the same things that I'm kind of expecting.
Which is, uh, we got sold out, you know? I mean, we really, we really kind of got screwed, you know?
We were told saucers 1998. They make up all these excuses that seem to justify, you know, the absence of saucers.
But the simple truth is, the saucers seem to have passed us by.
Okay.
There were people after 1998 that came to Stang, and they were, I think, really upset about that.
And, uh, and a lot of those people, a lot of people didn't come back, actually.
Which is fine, because really, maybe those are the people that got ruptured.
They got, uh, you know, they got taken away.
Because if there's one thing that we really don't need here in the Church of the Subgenius, it's a true believer.
I mean, you know, we don't really need any, uh, I mean, we don't really need any true unbelievers either.
Because, I mean, belief and disbelief both mean pretty much the same thing.
You no longer are accepting new ideas about a certain issue.
And, uh, so, so what I'm seeing here is that something special has been given to those people that lost faith.
You know, those people have been given.
A gift.
A gift called suspicion and disbelief.
You know, anytime any of those people that have walked away from the Church of the Subgenius,
anytime they go to another, another religion, or another spirituality, or another, another form of self-indulgent, uh, you know, self-gratification,
that, that we, we like to think of as religion, but it's just really justification for our actions.
Anytime somebody goes somewhere else to find...
something else somewhere inside their mind, they're gonna be thinking, they're gonna be thinking,
Is this just another scam?
Is this just somebody else making money off of me?
Is somebody else getting rich off of me?
Just like, just like when I gave all that money to the Church of the Subgenius?
Those people have been given a gift.
It's called disbelief.
You know, the conspiracy pays you.
What?
Well, probably.
I mean, compared to how well the Church of the Subgenius pays you.
Uh, I've, I have worked for both, and I can tell you that the conspiracy pays you real well
to do work that is guaranteed to be forgettable.
That's what it's all about.
And so you, you're faced with the problem of do you want the pay,
or do you want to do the work that is useful and will be remembered?
And, uh, uh, friends,
what we'd really like to do,
is, you know, neither one.
Why, why, why do we have to do either one?
Bob said we should be rich without, equally rich, without working.
Boy, that would be fair, wouldn't it?
Wouldn't that be so fair if everybody was equally rich without working?
Well, friends, you have to make that choice.
Are you enough of a subgenius to, to, to declare July 5th, Monday, normally a working day,
as your religious holiday?
As your religious holiday?
Earned by the blood of Bob on that stage as he bled for it.
Well, he didn't bleed for you, actually.
He bled for the insurance money.
We must get off Earth.
We must get off...
No, Bob.
I'm bleeding.
Please gotta get off Bob.
Bob.
Oh, man.
Oh, it ain't X Day yet, but it looks like I'm just ahead of the clock radio.
Okay, this is it.
This is it.
Okay.
10...
9...
7...
8...
5...
3...
4...
2...
1...
Oh, man, Bob, not again!
Ah!
Ah, hell.
Oh, at least I'm getting used to it by now.
Okay.
Well, I guess the next step is the inevitable vicious taunting at the hands of evil Susie.
Yeah, that's the way it always plays out.
Ah, jeez, Louise, I can actually hear that heartless bitch warming up that abrasive cackle-roos.
All right, you cow, come on, let me have it.
No, no, no!
You're in my pill stash!
You're in this right, Louise.
Why do you have to stash them under the toilet?
They're all tangy.
Spit them out!
Come on, some of that's for an actual emergency.
Let me go.
I don't want to live anymore.
Oh, God, get your head out of my damn mouth.
Oh, God.
Oh, man.
Oh, what gives?
Does Freaky Friday fall on a Monday this year?
This post-X-Day Suicide Blues thing is my shit, dude.
Bite me.
What fools we were to think that we would get to go on some divine killing spree and
crush all the pink boys with our alien powers.
Well, we believed Stang.
We did believe Stang.
That's what he said.
I bought into it.
I sent in my money.
Well, so you really bought into it.
Like, literally.
The only kind of bot that counts, baby.
All right, baby.
Not to Bob.
We were young, dumb, and full of...
Fun.
Yeah, that's what we were.
We were bright-eyed, and I can't spoil the end.
You all know what happened.
What do you think?
But about, just listen in, in about 10 minutes, we'll be back.
10 minutes before X-Day, we actually started alibi-ing.
All right, fine.
Yes, I'm a little bitter.
Yes, I understand that the conspiracy made the calendar, and it's not 2003.
Who knows what year it is?
It could be 1005.
Well, how do we know they got July 5th right?
And X-Day could be at any second.
I'm aware of that.
Does Ted Man make an appearance on the telephone during the show?
Of course he does.
Oh, that's wonderful.
I don't think you people have enough Ted Man in your lives.
He has a...
He's calling us from the observatory.
Right.
Oh, he sees the alien who wants to be his friend, and I think they have sex.
I believe they do.
Oh, that's wonderful.
And there's some people who got some science guys, but hey, you're going to hear it.
This show has been Stalinized for quality.
WCSB, you're on the air.
I got lost on the way to the station.
You got lost on the way to the station?
Oh, no, that's right.
We already did that show.
Yeah, you already did that show, man.
Only we didn't get to do that show, but we did that other show.
We need help on the next airport, because I'll be tumbling.
We got lost in the station.
We got lost on the way to Planet X, man.
Yeah.
Tables, they will turn around.
Planet X will soon be found.
How could you get in a place...
How could you get lost in a place so plainly and so clearly formatted, right in front of
you?
The holograms are everywhere.
If you get lost, all you have to do is wave your fingers in front of your eyes.
Bobbies know they're yeti pests.
Pink boys, they're all guests.
I think basically we meant that right.
He's the slack man.
That's why their armpits are so hot.
It's so sad that when you...
You expect to be...
To be ruptured and evaporated up into the escape vessels, but it doesn't happen for
another year.
So you go home, and in spite, you start up your lawnmower and rupture your grass.
If I had a million little grass souls that my excess pleasure saucer played by my lawnmower,
I'd spend all morning sucking those little souls up so that they're...
Into that escape vessel.
Hold for a second.
Now they're on their way to the city dump, which will double as Planet X for them.
Pink boys, listen, we gotta take a break here.
I hope you guys hold the line for just a moment.
The wind break.
All right.
This isn't over the edge.
No, but it's over the line.
You crossed that line.
Man, can't we just go back to have things like they used to be?
Can't we all just get along?
That was cool back then.
Yeah, no, we can't, man, because the world's gone.
The world ended, man.
Like I heard last week, the world ended, man.
And you died, man.
Yeah.
Well, it didn't actually end.
We thought it was going to.
The big UFOs came.
We thought it would, but something happened and prevented it from ending.
No, it actually did.
We all received a mental block later, a piece of forced conditioning, which we all took.
Whenever you see this picture.
Ah, yes.
You see this particular picture, it brings one out of the trance of oblivion.
What picture is that?
I can't see the monitor from over here.
Show it.
Is that the X Day picture?
It's a stereoscopic picture of what happened.
I already made a CD that made a million bucks off what you guys were doing last week.
Wow, invasion.
Invasion of Earth.
But it's really too late to do anything about it, so I don't even really want to get in trouble by talking about it.
Now, what was the other highlight of your experience at X Day, Dr. Howell?
The other highlight?
Other than, you know, the beautiful naked women.
Come on, man, don't step on the Rice Krispies.
That was just one of the many highlights, of course.
Don't step on the Rice Krispies thing!
Oh, God, they hurt.
Here it comes.
Actually, I enjoyed the easy camaraderie of my comrades in arms in the barracks.
That was just Al getting into the hot water.
Blah, blah, blah.
The man must know that he hath broken his code.
The other one's pretty sure they're the God of the Covenant.
And ye shall soil thy loincloth with the fear of Jehovah.
For Jehovah is the God of wrath!
Step away then from the bowling ball.
I think I saw the staying person light the fuse for the end of the world.
Light the fuse.
I think I saw it.
A mulberry.
That's what you say you saw?
Well, he bent over...
and something came out of him.
And then everything started shaking
and he was running past me away from this area.
That was just his psyche that came out of him.
Why would anyone want to leave beautiful...
Uh-oh, he's releasing foul gases.
Yeah, something like that.
And then we were running.
Apparently, Bob came and did something to all of us.
There's Reverend Stang.
Something did come out of him.
He changed us somehow.
I don't know what he did.
What are you doing up so early, Reverend Stang?
Oh, somebody burned the whole campground down.
Oh, no.
Yeah, I tried to...
Jesus!
But we were already gone, so what difference does it make?
Well, I was trying to go back there.
For the love and peace that happens at Brushwood.
And the whole campground had been burned down by the subgeniuses who dropped glass.
All the trees were denuded and blackened ash.
Once again, the subgenius bobbies have ruined everything else.
Well, you know what that was?
You guys didn't listen to me years ago.
That's what we would have called prop wash from the UFOs.
Those landing brakes they have just scorch everything, including the little non-normals.
Right, and they don't care.
They're just aliens, you know.
They don't even...
I'm not wearing any pants.
Well, why would you have to?
Exactly.
In these modern times, no one needs to call themselves a scepter in strange ideas.
Especially not on the radio.
Oh, tell that to my sunburn, Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Yeah, I got a little sunburned at X-Day, too, actually.
I don't think it was the sunburn.
I think it was the...
It wasn't the sun.
It was the saucers hovering overhead.
And when you get in the path of that afterburner of theirs, which is a special...
It's a special...
Graviton emission...
There's protons and stuff.
Well, it's got a couple different principles working in the saucer, the things that keep the saucers aloft.
One, of course, is the graviton emission.
Right.
You can get a sunburn.
Why is there a lot of pain in the buttocks?
The other one, of course, is the...
You also got a multiple contusion going on in your skin.
Pastor Pressure was showing off a sunburn in the shape of Jesus.
It was an anti-sunburn.
It was like the Jesus was formed by little spots that weren't burned.
It was a...
It was a reverse Jesus sunburn.
I think it had gone to a body cursing parlor, a biker place, before he attended the festivities.
And that's about it, Stang.
I think you're kind of ruminating over what might have been.
There were a lot of people who had actual saucer burn on the buttocks.
I mean, not...
Maybe 700.
That's a lot, right?
Well, we had a little bucket of hell and a little bucket of heaven, so you could put your feet in either one at the same time.
Get a bucket of heaven.
But, yes, after the drag...
What did we do after the drag king, queen...
The drag queen and king balls.
Weren't there a million psych-a-freak-a rock-and-roll rock-out rock bands?
That's right.
We had a great...
It was the Acid Corpse played...
I guess that was the first night of band nights.
But what about the Swinging Louve Corpse?
Well, that's their name.
That was their name.
We had the Swinging Love Corpses.
Three members of the Swinging Love Corpses.
It was melded with four members of the Amino Acids.
So the Amino Acids provided the bass and the drums and the tenor.
I don't forget what kind of...
It wasn't a tenor, but it was maybe a baritone guitar that that one guy had.
And then we played sax and guitar and trumpet and violent things.
Yeah.
Ooh.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 52, 53, 54, 56, 57, 58, 59, 52, 56, 57, 58, 59, 59, 60.
You said oh baby
And then I said oh baby
And then ever so gently
Ever so gently
And then...
You had so many sexual overtones
You looked over at me and you said
Baby
And I do right there
That's when I knew
This is the way you said baby
This is the way you said fade
Not so much the B-part but the B-part
It's the way you say, baby.
Bye bye.
You couldn't just say baby, you had to say bye bye.
What is that? What's that, bye bye?
I'm sorry.
Here is the power.
Power.
That's a little number we've been working on called Bye Bye.
We was on drugs.
It felt good.
So then after the Acid Corpse played,
and we played for an hour and 45 minutes which only seemed like 20 minutes to me.
It was just like being in heaven.
It was such great anti-music and wonderful mystery jazz and great sort of like space bug surf jam stuff.
Space.
Surf jam.
Everybody, it's gonna be a surf jam.
So after that, let's see, I guess after that we just partied till like it was 1999 till about, you know, 2 or 3.30 in the morning.
4.30 maybe and then we'd go to bed.
And then we would toss and turn fitfully as the three most thunderous snorers.
Suicide man wants to know something.
Oh, I just wanted to know if the show was still on.
No, we're not on the air anymore.
Hey, what happened to you, suicide man?
Are you on drugs or something?
I feel a little strange.
You feel a little slowed down to me.
Okay, concentrate on the reality we're throwing out to you.
Look out!
Hey man, get out of the way!
You gotta get out of the way.
Come on.
The reality will run you down.
It's like a tank.
Let me dust you off.
It's like a fast tank.
It's a fast tank with wheels instead of tracks.
Listen up, buddy, I'm just gonna tell you what.
Straighten up or fly right.
You can lead a horse to water.
You can't make him drink.
So what's your point, dude?
You're sitting on your point, right?
You're sitting on it right now.
Admit it.
We were just discussing a strange fellow who claimed to have died but is still alive
to plague us today.
You have never seen such sights.
Your heart has never felt such emotion, such sorrow, such joy.
You will be uplifted.
And never have you seen such freaks of nature.
One look at them will tell you more than a thousand words of mine.
Come and see, see little Theodore and...
...Habaluska!
I just sit here watching squirrels.
They have much more fun than me.
Sometimes they run around all day in circles.
They fight and squabble, then they lick their wounds.
At least they seem to have a purpose.
My mind's always clogged with leaves.
Like silly, stupid advertising jingles.
And themes on TV shows I do not like.
I must not go out the front door.
I could get hit by a car.
Just like the squirrels when a dog is growling.
There's perfect safety high up in the tree.
I know I'm bad to just sit here.
I should not be so afraid.
But once outside I'd have to choose a direction.
It might be the wrong one so I'll stay here.
I'm not afraid of the squirrels.
They tell me of self-improvement.
And someday could even have a job.
Then I would have become just like the squirrels.
I don't see how I could accomplish that.
First I'd have to choose a direction.
Like which tree I should start to climb.
They all seem to be up to the challenge.
I just take whatever's given me.
I'm not afraid of the squirrels.
So I'm okay here just watching squirrels.
Though the soundtrack could be much improved.
Those silly, stupid advertising jingles.
And themes on TV shows I do not like.
And...
I kind of regain some easily of the role of a squirrel.
I don't see the sense of propriety There's no respite in that.
A bit trashy, a lot of Dog resting up towards the sun.
And aific okay price really better.
I kind of think my voice may have scale where I live.
But all the truth isucha disc a life adjust and poetry stick.
Weil-w
You know, I like him.
He's silly.
The audience doesn't think that's very funny.
I mean, they do think that's very funny.
They're laughing their heads off.
Look, they love it.
Old rape-a-man.
See, I know people that say it's impossible and completely antithetical to the concept to think that a man could be raped.
That he wouldn't do it willingly and enjoyingly.
Joyfully celebrating the conubial...
This is the effect of X-Day, folks.
This is what happens to the mind once it's brainwashed.
Yes, thank you, thank you.
You want to spend your entire time in the bachelor's cabin with the conubial.
That's not my job.
We did manage to spend some time at the Frop...
At Dr. Frop's...
We used to just call it...
Oh, so yeah, what was the entertainment like?
We just called it Frop's Place.
What about all the bands that play?
All the bands were excellent.
Well, there was the amino...
The amino...
Amino acids.
Zuck.
benovaance.com
Where are you?
Ahahaaaa!
guitar solo
But the amino acids were actually
almost shut
you know, not shut down, but
And there was little
Theodore. The first act. Really? Oh, great.
Yeah, little Theodore was there.
So why were they almost shut down?
Why were they pretend shut down?
Oh, I was just saying they were almost blown away
by the band the previous night.
They were blown away!
The jam band kicked
literally kicked the posteriors
of all the individual
subs in their family.
Boy, were they sore. Was it with a big leather boot?
With a big leather boot
with red straps.
Big leather
hobnail boot with red straps.
Well, now, would you like to say
for our listening audience
just who were some of the famous
subgeniuses present at this
earth-shaking event?
Well, let's see.
We did have
well, we had you. You were there.
Well, you're right. I was there.
And not only that, I think I saw
Reverend Two Beans there.
Yeah, Two Beans was there.
Let's see who else was there. There was
Doc Frop and Sister Dexter.
And Dr. Pissed.
Dr. Pissed.
Sister Decadence.
Magdalene and Jesus, of course.
Yes, and thousands
of other famous
and semi-famous.
Where did all these bobbies come from?
And yet to be famous.
Bob Toberfest.
What they do is they cut their hair
and then dye their heads purple.
Having something to do with attracting the sun for Bob.
Hey, I think that's a good idea,
Reverend Howell.
Maybe we should have a
Bob Toberfest.
Oh, yeah.
I get it.
Bob Toberfest.
Would you come, Caller?
That'd be awesome.
Can we have some beer there?
Would you come, Caller?
We could find...
Could you bring some women?
Yeah.
Okay, good.
Sounds like you have a lot there.
You know, they're like smaller versions of us.
What notes do we play on this song?
Okay, this is Betty Blows.
Betty Blows, part one.
This is a little symphony we've been working on for a while.
Well...
guitar solo
blah blah blah
and they bringeth the
light stone, blam
the whore virgin brain
the guilt finder and smiter
the very mark of the
covenant and she is the eye
of the father, she shall
will thee and overcome the mark
of the beast and shall give thee
fornication and the true
sons of Israel shall be
snatched up, behold
my servant shall prosper
he shall be exalted and
lifted up and shall be very
high, he who knoweth
the fools who prophesy
from me shall be made over men
many will be astonished
at him for his appearance is
so marred, non-human
semblance and his form
beyond that of the sons of man
those who are over
men who have followed my
almighty word shall
be the minister of the angelic
host, they shall speak
for them and my prophet
who smiles shall be
among them and shall advise
them. Well I'm sorry
to have to call you on a normal phone
from somewhere else on earth
and I'm sorry that you're there on earth
to call. Yeah, how does it look from up there?
I'm sorry Bob
let us down. I'm
sorry, okay, I'm sorry!
Yeah, but you get to be on the ship. You don't have to
be sorry, we're going to do it again next year.
Hey by the way, were you number one in line?
Like your ticket says every year
at the gate?
I'm number one in line.
We use a double because
I'm the one filming the line.
There's always a sacred
filmer and they always think
that the sacred filmer is not really an artist.
That's right.
It's both a blessing and a liability.
Have you looked at any of the footage yet?
Yes. Yes
and the bashing
of the Christ, not to be
confused with the mashing of the Christ
by negative plan, but
our competition
for their short subject
should be, should really
look good. We got plenty of footage. We
really hurt Jesus bad.
Did you kill him like
a little George? He's still alive being a
Merovingian and we
so basically everything
that way is great for next year we'll have another
Jesus, the campground will
grow back, the
pagans will recuperate
and the subgeniuses will return everything
they've stolen once again.
Wow, is the little fake Bob okay?
Yeah, that's the funny thing.
This was the X day when
the thieves returned what they
had stolen. Great.
And asked me to thank them
expecting me to go, oh thank you for
doing that for three years.
That is a strange phenomenon.
But the thing is back where you are on that
planet, they return them. Here they
just keep them forever and gloat
in their living rooms with their two friends.
Yes, yes.
We all know about that.
Ghosts and ghouls
and wearing
black.
The crows are
nowhere there to
come back.
Eternal
global
drifting slack.
I've
looked at death
this way.
But now it's
just a
boring pain.
You get
all stiff.
You've lost the game.
And to think
it's your
best chance for fame.
When it does you no damn
good.
I've looked at death
from both sides now.
From cool and blue.
And still somehow
it's death's illusions
I recall.
Hah!
I really don't know
death!
Oh yes,
little fear
does not
matter.
I've
got a
bit of
fear
in me.
I've
got
a
fear
in me.
I've
got a
fear in me.
I've
got a
fear
in me.
I've
got
a
fear
in me.
I've
got
fear
in me.
I've
got
fear
in me.
I've
got
fear
in me.
I've
got
fear
in me.
I've
got
fear
I've
in me.
And
I've
lost
all
my
desire
You can download copies of the Puzzling Evidence Show from this address.
Get that pencil tape recorder ready.
That's matrix.c-s-u-s-t-a-n.e-d-u slash negative without the e.
Oh, again, friends, this is the Hour of Slack Radio Ministry, Church of the Subgenius, episode number 951.
This show has been done more to educate the denizens of Northern California and the world
on the Puzzling Evidence Show.
Dozens of myths that have pervaded Masonic lore.
It's about saying what's got to be said.
Fascinating. Fascinating.
Horrible, but fascinating.
Sit down, relax.
So, are you glad to be home now, Reverend Stagg?
Well, I'd rather be on my, you know, my home in outer space, my own escape vessel planet.
In your special space ranch.
In your special yacht with Elrond.
The yacht catisma.
Yeah.
Actually, I was more looking forward to seeing Herf Applewhite, previously known as Doe,
and David Koresh.
Yes, they'll be there in the afterlife waiting with open eyes.
And all those young eunuchs.
And Robert Kelton.
All the great famous Texas evangelists are waiting for me aboard the escape vessel.
And what about the Nike-wearing eunuchs?
The Nike-wearing eunuchs.
The Dobbshead shirt-wearing eunuchs.
Yep.
The swinging lorries.
The Love Corp. fanboy eunuchs.
Yeah, that's what happened is the people who did the first Dobbs shooting parody also talked
about the various heavens that famous people would go to.
And there they are.
All the famous people.
And each person gets to go to his kind of famous person heaven.
But then you're stuck there with people of your own gener.
There's Lon Chaney Janer.
There's Lon Chaney Senior.
Lon Chaney Janer.
There's Della Lugosi.
There's all the great celebrities.
Ed Wood.
I got a telephone.
They're all there on board the escape vessel.
Which is what we cover with this radio program, Coast to Coast AM.
I'm Art Bells.
All right.
The saucer last weekend.
The saucer.
Remember that?
Too good to be true.
I said so at the time.
Well, sure enough.
The good news is it's there.
It really is exactly there.
It's exactly where the photograph said it was.
The bad news?
It seems to be an elaborate construction by a member of the Church of the Subgenius.
A gag mail order crossy religion that worships a clip art face named J.R. Bob Dobbs.
For lack of a better explanation.
The old abandoned saucer home also known as a pleasure saucer.
Where many a subgenius divival has no doubt been held.
Can be seen in detail and it gives a fine URL.
But it's the same photograph we have.
So it really is there.
I knew it.
They'll pay to know what they really think.
Well, Mr. Zhang, it was an almost foolproof plan.
Because I love Bob and I'm happy.
Why don't you Dugs go over to Pirate Cat Radio and do your show over there?
We're zero listeners.
Yeah.
Yeah, man.
Uh-oh, I didn't realize what time it was.
Uh-oh.
I did. I could tell.
But the show is getting so foggy and hard to hear.
I figured it must be ending.
It's murky.
We'd like to add the murkiness at the end to help murkify it a little bit.
It seemed like it has about a fog of fog at set at about six and the murk is moving up.
It's weird.
It's almost ten.
Well, the murk is moving in and as you know, it's getting closer to that time in the schedule
when puzzling evidence has to shut the special Captain Fox and say,
How does America handle a headache?
I'm proud to be on a murkin' place.
Well, that's true.
And so are we all.
As we stand on that spotty flag after our long history and our climb up from the primordial
ooze to our present eminence as prominent American subgeniuses.
Yeah, I'm going back to the ooze, man.
You should go back to bed.
You're gonna go up to your special chamber and say,
My oozing bag.
The subgenius.
Ew.
I'm gonna climb back in my oozing bag and go back to sleep.
Good night, Dr. Stang.
Kill them all.
I'll let Bob sort them out.
For in his sorting is not the high E-polly.
That's the most arbitrary of judges.
Oh, my.
So here are the engines of the oncoming ships.
Finally, they're landing.
No.
Oh, no.
That was another, another drill.
Damn.
Well, we'll certainly have one.
You know the drill.
I only got here.
Okay.
It's the guy.
Christ, Bob.
Hello?
Is Bob Dobbs there?
I'm the little guy who lives in the corner.
Bob Dobbs, you there?
Hello?
Oh, you bastard.
I'm gonna kill you one day.
Beep.
We'll be right back.