Time for Pastor David Epley, your Good Shepherd prayer partner and your personal friend.
In the next 13 or 14 minutes, something good, good, good is coming your way.
So don't leave this radio station. Let's have a good time together.
He's all I need.
Ah, yes.
And now, the S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S-S of Genius Hour of Slack.
I think this is about the sickest, sickest, sickest thing I've ever heard on KFJZ and since I've been listening to it.
End of the break.
The very door of the day of the wrath of God is at hand.
And that if you plan to get saved, you'd better do it now.
In this temple lodge of the Church of the Subgenius of Little Rock,
and before we begin this sacred spouting,
I think that we should all bow our heads and let's all have a minute of noise.
Ah!
Knowing that God has given us charge,
and we're going to take charge of that home right now
in the name of Jesus Christ of Nazareth.
I send the angel of the Lord.
I send right now power, the very glory of God into that home.
I move back the foul spirits of opposition,
the lying spirits, the binding spirits,
I speak authority to you in the name of Jesus Christ.
Don't ask any questions. Just do as I say. All right?
There's, I mean, the teaching of Jesus Christ,
the authority, the commandments,
to strap a bomb to your chest, to abuse children,
to go and kill anyone, to blow yourself up,
but that's what we're here on earth to do.
And once we get a hold of the peace that is in that,
oh, folks.
Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus.
Jesus.
Jesus Christ, we've got to get this cleaned up.
Look at the...
Someone called Jesus?
Yes.
Yeah, we called him, but he couldn't come and help us clean
the splatter from the stain.
Oh, no, Jesus is gone now.
He's gone. He can't help us.
No, he's living with the sissies.
Oh, but look who's here, Sissy Man!
Oh, here he comes.
Where did you get that silly suit?
And how did you get that silly attitude?
Wait, you're not a man at all?
You're a...
Now, let's just see you drop them pants.
I've never seen anything so ridiculous in all my life.
You're a sissy boy, ain't you?
Ain't you?
Yeah, it's all right.
I'm a silly boy.
I'm not that.
I've one time seen a sissy tortured by the Cheyenne.
He never screamed at once.
He was a sissy, but as they cut pieces of his flesh off,
he never cried out.
He was a strong man, that sissy was.
Yeah.
He had taken the Sundance.
He had done the Sundance ritual and had his breasts impaled with the tusks of a dog.
And in the after hours, he enjoyed a martini and perhaps whipping up some lettuce and throwing at his children.
Little Big Sissy.
Big Little Sissy.
Good evening. I'm Adele Arakawa.
I'm Jim Bannerman.
9 News reporter Ginger Delgado has meth labs like that fellow.
Yes, Jim.
It's a job that is so dangerous,
it could eventually explode, cause fires or worse, cause life.
And because of that, he has decided to share his cancer.
He will not reveal Bob since he was 12, since 17.
I think if an person first introduced it to me, it would be really good.
Why?
Because I'm brown.
Today, Bob is dying of his teeth.
In short, an explosion has ruined his life.
He now says the quick high he got was worth it.
You know, it's fun for a minute.
No one should say.
He wants to keep making the same fatal mistake.
And his meth labs growing at an alarming rate.
Authorities in 31 drug labs.
The next year.
This year.
Authorities say this year.
And last year, here in Colorado.
Uh, yes, dear friends.
News of Bob's cancer, cut up by Fernanda Nande-Lee Murr,
preceded by some of the new remastering of our old collage album,
Media Barrage No. 4.
Media Barrage No. 5.
The old school sub-tape by puzzling evidence.
Byron Werner, Yours Truly, Lies, Glass Madness, Doctors for Bob, Dr. Philodrumon,
and G. Gordon Gordon with more coming up.
Friends, I've finished recutting Media Barrage No. 5.
And this show, this hour of slack number 849, will be a mix-up of the last third of that show
with miscellaneous news.
A new or newish stuff that has also accumulated.
We'll even be hearing from subgeni who foreswore Bob and forsook the church.
Such as the subgenius-hating Reverend Buck Naked.
And even the original pre-non-fame Saint Janer Hypercletes.
The prototypical subgenius saint.
We're pretty sure he's a psychopath now.
How do we spell it?
Spot him.
Well, if he's wearing a Napoleon hat, it's easy.
Otherwise, they come in all sizes and shapes.
From 11-year-old girls to 80-year-old men.
And they all look perfectly normal.
I keep telling y'all, this is a sick and perverted nation.
All tired.
And nobody wants to listen to me.
Nobody wants to hear about Bob.
Nobody...
I try to tell everybody what's going on.
They won't listen to me.
Well, to tell you the truth, I can't stand it anymore.
Bob.
Bob, take care of me.
Just do away with them all.
I don't want them anymore.
They hold a problem and illusion in my mind after all.
They don't love you, Bob.
They don't love you like I do.
.
It's not just the wars and awards that win them,
it's not just a dull and empty distaste for a smothered culture
that expires all around you in pools of its own wastes.
It's not just the terminal foals of Nunu.
It's not just the child zombies that murdered their mediocrity and parents
and then cruise the streets with bloody feet.
It's not just those starry old becks on the park benches
and you know what's going on
their faces like those who shuffled out of the boxcars of Belsen and Auschwitz.
It's not just the anesthesiologist for knee-deep.
It's not just the heaving pink meat masses that grope and clutch all around you.
It's not just the dino bones for Wotan.
It's not just the broken headlights, snapped antennae, and human excrement on your car
hood.
It's not just that the old ways were best.
It's not just the bastardization and perversion of every honest means of self-expression.
It's not just the killer shit ganja from the dark side of the bush.
It's not just the penoid snipers locking and loading on every high-rise rooftop.
It's not just the wide-screen technicolor corporate daisy chain that has defiled the
entire planet.
It's not just the...
It's not just Mongo in the Congo with fa-fa-fas the size of basketballs.
It's not just the prophets crying lonely and alone in the wilderness.
It's not just the indignity of having to work for some bland, nun-entity son-of-a-bitch
who thinks workers are property.
It's not just the blueness of the wound cleansed by evil.
It's not just the battling eco-freaks who want to go back to nature without realizing
that nature is an open-ditch latrine and no one can get out of it.
It's not just the
that gets stuck in midsummer.
It's not just some asshole with a pipe and a shit-eating I-know-more-than-you-do-dog-grin
all over his homogenized face.
It's not just the horrible feeling of being entrapped inside a regimented, devolving world that you certainly never made
It's not just the doorway to doom
It's not just wanting to know what the hell is really going on
It's not just the missing H's or the stolen alpha-beta-max
No, dear friends, there is more to it all than that
Bob ain't no nickel-dime bum show
I put it to you, he's on the square and a corking fine business proposition
He's the grandest thing yet, and don't you forget it
Shot salvation and fighting Jesus, you don't need to rise precious early
You sinner there, if you want to diddle the almighty Bob
No, he's got cough mixture with a punch on it for you, my friend
In his back pocket, just you try it
I'm just a clump of mud
Bob's tape recorder
Bob is things that don't always run
Bob is masking tape
Bob is a ballpoint pen
Bob is a rooster
And Bob is a hen
Bob!
Where's Bob? We want Bob!
Right now! We want Bob!
Okay.
Bob's probably not gonna be here
in physical man's station.
Oh,
where is Bob?
He's everywhere.
Check yourself and feel of your Bob
gland and make sure it's overactive
like it's supposed to be.
This is the headquarters for the
Church of the Subgenius.
I represent a group of scientists
who work with but one purpose,
to put an end to war.
Naturally, such a goal can't be attained without
experts of superior ability.
Men of vision,
men such as you, Doctor, gathered here
exchanging information daily,
putting aside all thoughts of personal
success. We hope to
achieve exciting new techniques,
leap years ahead of the others.
I don't think I need tell you how effective
our voices will be when the world learns of our
achievements. Well,
there you have it.
Nothing new, perhaps, but then,
what is?
However, let me assure you, Doctor, that we are dedicated
men and women, and as such,
we can accomplish wonders.
Back any other church! Back any other church!
The Church of the Subgenius! The Church has divine
tenets! Has divine tenets!
Divine rules! Divine rules!
Divine orders! Divine orders!
First rule of the Subgenius! First rule of the
Subgenius! Too much!
Too much! It's always better than not enough!
Can I get it too much?
Is it always better than?!
Is it always better than?! Praise Bob!
Praise Bob!
Bob, Bob...
Bob?
But let's leave things of this world behind
and walk now down the path of Bob for this brief minute of slack
from the Church of the Subgenius.
Friend, the devil is tearing the family apart.
But what the devil uses to do it with is nine to five jobs.
Conspiracy, corporate, pink situations
where mommy and daddy get up in the morning and go to work
and they kiss the kids goodbye.
It's the first time they see them during the day, kiss them goodbye.
Kind of a simultaneous goodbye and hello.
Then they get home about seven o'clock,
ticked off, to use a polite term,
after a long drive back out to the suburbs.
They get home, they kiss their kids hello and goodnight,
and they go to bed.
And the other churchgoers,
I just dare to say the breakdown of the family
is because the kids see a little tittering stupid sexy gags on television
or because of the new permissiveness
where men are allowed to do things with other men.
That's a bunch of holy hooey, I say, my friend.
I say, why not legalize pornography and ban work?
Work is what takes the parents away from the kids.
Most of these kids these days grow up, they don't have parents.
They got some kind of robot scarecrows.
Oh, friend, let there be slack.
I'm not gonna lie, I think I'm gonna have to go to the bathroom.
I'm gonna have to go to the bathroom.
Great unwashed, the hoi polloi,
venom, the conspiracy, the mediocretins,
the bootlifts, the sames, the conformers,
mall people, bankers, wankers, and blankers,
hires and smilers, credit heads, and the slackless ones.
In short,
the remnants of man.
The witless principles who are the false prophets.
Smith, I'll get us a contract we'll never forget.
Wild thing, man.
Single guy.
I know that Bob, I know that Bob is a good cause.
Bob took me inside his heart.
And I accepted him into my life.
And I'm here to testify, friends, what that man has done for me.
If you can really call him a man.
Many people say he's almost like a god.
I don't think so.
Of course, I don't know Bob, but I do know Bob in certain ways.
And I think you understand what I'm talking about.
Yes, Bob, he filled me with a sort of a spirit.
A spirit I never knew I had.
I knew it wasn't coming from him.
It was coming from inside me.
Bob was giving it to me.
He was laying hands on me from afar.
He might have been up in that great big jet plane.
Or he might have been down on Skid Row giving some bum a haircut.
But all I know is, it was Bob.
It was Bob.
Bob.
Yeah, he's smiling.
You never see Bob frown.
You know that behind that amazing smile there lies a mind like a steel trap.
I'm sure he makes mistakes like what he did with those young women that time.
But I think the newspapers exaggerated that.
I know that Bob will do.
All of us fine in the long run.
In fact, I think I know that we really need Bob in our lives.
In our lives.
In 1981.
And in 1984.
Hi little brother.
And in 1991.
And in 1995.
When they bring the conspiracy to its heels.
And in that wondrous year that we know is going to come all too soon upon us.
And we'll leave our earthly things behind.
And we'll go and join the exes from God only knows what strange planet they come from.
If they really even come from a planet at all.
And not some energy star beaming away in the darkness.
Lighting our lives with the technology.
And the spirituality.
And the mentality.
Of planet X.
Planet X coming down to take care of us subgeniuses.
And see that there's a place for us in the world.
And give us our rightful seat at the right hand of Bob or the left hand of Bob.
Depending on whether we're rewardians or mediocrities.
But I don't want to get lost in the dogma.
I want to tell you something that blesses my heart.
And it's Bob.
Bob.
Yeah I can hear him.
I can hear him talking off there in the distance saying.
Doug's right Virgil.
We are different.
Soon everyone will be a superior biospecies.
Even Doug Smith.
It's the good news son.
Ah yes dear friends.
Those are the things I want to tell you about today.
The very many things.
The things that Bob knows.
The things that you know and when you know.
That you know it.
Because everybody does have that gland.
That mystical Bob gland in their feet.
That one that tells them what to do if they don't even think with it.
But somewhere along in the past.
Man got confused.
And decided to start thinking with his brain.
And when that happened.
Ah dear friends.
That was a very sad time in the history of man.
Because when man stands on his brain and thinks with his feet.
Then he'll know exactly which way to go and how to find Bob.
You got to massage that foot gland.
And the only way to massage it is to walk on it.
Yes sir.
Ah dear friends.
You got to walk on the foot glands for Bob.
Because when you're walking.
And Bob's a talking.
Then you'll know.
All you need to know about what to do after the holocaust.
After the aliens come and take us.
And give us all the information.
And all them giant pills.
And all them fantastic machines that's supposed to run our lives.
And that big white stone that everybody's going to know personally.
In their very own home.
Ah yes dear friends.
That stone.
That's the stone.
That's the stone that you think you might know.
And you think might help you.
But by God dear friends.
That's the stone that's going to ruin your very life.
That's the stone that's going to make you think that niggie.
Is on your side this time.
Because that stone is going to rule all things.
You think you know who big brother is.
Dear friends.
I want to tell you tonight.
You don't know.
You don't know nothing.
I know.
And.
Among other things.
Bob.
I'm doing pretty well.
With those pills you sent.
Pretty well.
But.
But I can always use more.
And.
It's because.
Of Ohio.
And red trucks.
And they're all gone.
Bob.
But that's okay.
I know.
Yes.
Ah yes.
Oh no Kim can.
Can stand.
Up to the mighty fifth of Bob.
I've seen him walk through construction sites.
Banging the shit out of them old.
Chemical toilets.
Throwing them down saying.
You're God damn workmen.
You're men.
You don't have to God damn shit in the closet.
In a smelly hole.
Why don't you fucking just.
Pull down your pants and take a dump.
Right here on the damn construction site.
Feed the damn worms.
Yes.
Friend.
Bob is a natural man.
And he's made the car.
Directly in front of me.
Have a flat tire.
A blowout.
And say wait a minute devil.
I'm sick and tired of you always pushing me around.
I'm sick and tired of being sick and tired.
Nobody else wants to do it.
But I'm gonna do it.
Because I feel like I can.
Listen let me tell you something.
The devil may say you can't.
And people may say you can't.
But yes you can.
You can.
You can defeat your enemies.
You can defeat your giants.
That's why we miss it so many times concerning the things of God is because we want to see
it before we believe it.
See someone has made the statement well seeing is believing.
No I want to turn that around you see according to the Bible believing is seeing.
Now see the world system just exactly 180 degrees opposite from God's system.
God says believing is seeing.
Speak.
6A take one.
Roll camera.
Slate it.
Bob sometimes it gets so hard to talk Bob.
It gets so hard.
Scene 7 take one.
Camera.
Blur.
Roll.
Feet.
Choke.
Follow.
Feet.
Roll.
Profits.
Help.
Know.
Is there a tutti on duplicated ball?
Bob Triple.
Joe Glass.
AndAss 이러ch b attractorou.
F carta fr cattdgo.
Drop the zag in um ar surprise after a sharedo, but the
snag video is coughing right now.
Bye Mad Hatter.
Big bang on the inside of my head, Bob.
And, you know, and look at me.
Real red, Bob.
This man has something to say.
When I come up here this morning, I knew that Bob was straight.
Bob.
You see now, Bob, I'm feeling fine.
It's too hard to deal with you.
The reality, Bob, is real hard.
Bob.
I can't get out.
I'm stuck inside.
I have to stop.
I'm stuck in my brain.
I'm holding my mind.
I'm at myself holding nothing to find.
I'm in.
I'm a bad guy, Bob.
Bob.
I'm stuck inside.
I feel like I want to deal with these things.
Bob.
I need it.
Send someone to kill Bob.
Bob.
Paul, who are those humanoids that are out in the truck area?
Those?
Yes.
That's the team from Dallas.
There's big guys there in the jerseys.
They have big X's on them.
Oh I see, yes.
They seem to be getting creamed as they say.
Oh, there's the funeral.
There's the church bells signaling the toll of the dead for this portion of today's feature entertainment game.
Oh I see. And who is this young man singing these awful songs?
Looking around this town for Bob Dobbs. Looking around the sky.
Been so out of luck and money I've been waiting to die.
Looking around this town for Bob Dobbs. Hoping he'll help me out.
I've been down and confused so long now.
I just wanna shout Bob Dobbs! Bob Dobbs! Bob Dobbs! Where are you Bob Dobbs?
We were at the Hall High School library today and we put lots of subgenius literature in all of the books.
Bob can stop the aliens from coming.
Bob can stop the aliens from killing me.
Bob can save me, but will he?
Well, don't count on it, Buck.
Hey Bob.
Hey there.
What's the matter?
Oh, we can sit here and talk about this.
You know, it's Henry.
It's Bob.
That's why you need to send us money.
We're here at the Septian Church.
Church.
Bob, keep working miracles in your life.
Bring us in the Lord.
Amen.
Love,
Jesus.
Crying and singing and praying for Bob Dobbs,
hoping he'll lend me a hand.
I've been down, confused, and broke for so long,
I can barely stand.
I'm screaming, Bob Dobbs!
Help me out, old Bob Dobbs!
Hear me shout out, Bob Dobbs!
There were like long lines of people like weeping and glistening in the rain.
That's because they were carving onions!
That's because their sores were opening!
That's the way we want our music.
We want the third nostrils to open.
We want everyone's pores and their nervous glands
to open simultaneously.
Yes, I know.
If you can, okay, can you get with it, baby?
I'm getting with it now.
Okay, it's like a rhythmic thing.
It's not a melodic thing.
It's not a tonal thing.
Okay, I'm sinking up right now.
Okay, sink in because it's gonna flatten your cracky, woman.
And it's gonna make you dance like you've never,
well, I don't know if you've never danced before.
But you're gonna dance all over Stang's tail.
You're gonna pull his neck off.
You're gonna, I forgot what you're gonna do after that.
Well, I'll just wing it.
How's that?
Yeah.
Um, I feel that it's, uh,
people like me are not represented.
I'm very disturbed by-
You are very disturbed,
and I'm gonna recommend that you get some help
for your problem.
You are very disturbed.
Ah, you bitch!
You're very disturbed.
You're disturbed too, you bitch!
How dare you trick me like that!
All right.
Now go ahead and say what you want to say about drugs.
What are you gonna do, everyone?
I say you're gonna play these cheap little tricks.
Well, ma'am, it's not a cheap trick.
Everyone listening to you knows you're very disturbed.
How do you know?
You ain't the one who told me you're very disturbed.
Well, ma'am, all I know about you is that you sit here
and you scream all these epithets,
and you're, you get way out.
You must be on something yourself.
I started to talk, and you said talk,
and the minute I said I'm disturbed about drugs,
I...
Well, ma'am, go ahead and tell me
what you want to say about drugs.
Drugs?
What, what did you want to say about drugs?
Well, you're not gonna write me.
Ma'am, you've called me every name under the book,
and you're still on the air.
I didn't call you every name.
Well, just about.
Well, you've been doing the same to me.
Uh, I have not at all, ma'am.
Go right ahead and say what you want to say about drugs.
I'm disturbed about...
You certainly are.
Me.
Can I say anything?
You're gonna, every time I say I'm disturbed,
you're gonna say you certainly are.
Well, go right ahead and tell me
what you want to say about drugs.
How can I?
There's tremendous resistance I'm to get.
No, ma'am, go right ahead.
I haven't resisted anything you've said thus far.
You're still on the air.
You're playing games.
Yeah, I'm on the air, and I...
Well, that's true, and so go right ahead
and tell me what you want to say about drugs.
I have to keep fighting with you,
and you're not giving me an instant
to say what I want to plan to say.
Well, ma'am, uh, I...
If what you've said is not something
that you planned to say, then I feel sorry for you.
You really need help.
You need help, too, you son of a bitch.
You want to be kicked off the air.
All right, fine.
Now that you've gotten that out of your system,
tell me what you want to say about drugs.
Tell me.
All right, what do you want to say about drugs?
I'm very disturbed.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, thank God.
I'm very disturbed by the fact that people like me
are not included in...
all the statistics.
Uh, and, uh, who's a person like you?
Someone that gets on and calls people names
and cusses at them?
Is that the kind of person you are?
I've done it.
You've cut me off many times.
This is the first time.
Well, is, is, is...
What do you mean?
Is that the type of person you are?
Is that...
I don't have control.
Well, you're damn right you don't have control.
You don't have control of your faculties.
You don't have control of your senses.
So do you.
And, ma'am, what you need to do
is go out and get some help.
But at least I gave you an opportunity,
and all you did was cuss and swear
and carry on.
Uh, I feel sorry for you,
but go out and get some help.
Call Carla Perez.
Perhaps, uh, Carla is expert enough
to give you some help.
What?
Riverland Rivers.
Lord God.
Man.
Garden.
Tree.
An oligonevil.
Man.
Helper.
Ground.
God.
Animal.
Field.
Bird.
Guy.
Man.
Creature.
Name.
Man.
Names.
Cattle.
Birds.
Way.
Serpent.
Animal.
Field.
Woman.
Tree.
Garden.
Woman.
Serpent.
Fruit.
Tree.
Garden.
Fruit.
Tree.
Mist.
Garden.
Serpent.
Woman.
Date.
It.
Eyes.
God.
Good.
Evil.
Woman.
Tree.
Food.
Eyes.
Tree.
Fruit.
Husband.
Eyes.
Pig.
Lee.
고.
Zivo.
notamment There is a lot of
dar podemos talk about on the
the protein on the
People of America are
an intést菁isha
and we also need some
Pot
myself with a baseball
Hey, Carl.
Yeah, Grave-a?
Look at Barry back there.
He's playing those drums like a crazy Mennonite.
Yeah, for that, he was surely burning hell.
Yeah!
Hey, Grave-a, that guitar sure sounds great.
Yeah, thanks, Carl.
I carved it from our old back door.
Those knobs are kind of shiny, though.
Yeah, don't tell the person.
Okay.
Out in the field for 40 days.
Plowing and planting and raking the hay.
My mule Ezra is pulling the plow.
I got him from Carl for some eggs and a cow.
I work all day out in the sun.
But after the meal, we start to have some fun, I say.
Come on, Greta, and light the lamps.
We're making lots of noise, but we don't got no amp.
We are an Amish band.
We'll help you build a barn.
We just don't give a...
We don't give a damn.
We are an Amish band.
You know, it's because I'm too lazy to get out of bed
and actually go into the living room and use my regular phone.
Oh, okay, you're on the cellphone, huh?
Yeah, because I'm too lazy.
Wow, that's cool.
All America's on a cellphone because you're too lazy.
That laziness, I think, is very, very...
Cellphones have changed everything.
It's kind of provocative.
Who reads my phone calls...
Provocative.
You know, slackers are attracted to that level of laziness.
What the heck is he trying to get?
So weird happening out there.
Not that I'm a slacker.
I'm actually...
I'm slacking just for you.
What's that?
Okay, good, good.
Well, I'm really just a slack abuser.
It's really nice.
Not a slacker, per se. It's just that when I find slack, I try to use it to its fullest extent.
I just want to tell her when she turns her suit toward the...
When you turn your suit toward the command center, the signal comes in better.
Yeah.
That's what it is.
You're lying on your back. You should be on your side.
Then you can look out over the top of the...
Then we can hear the phone better.
Cockpit.
And see the Earth below us.
How do you guys know these things?
Because we're right up above you.
High above Berkeley. In the crack.
Because we're on the internet, you know, and you can find anybody on the internet now.
And folks, remember, we are going to find the end of the internet on this show.
I looked for like four hours.
Yeah.
To try to find the show?
She was looking for the end of the internet for four hours.
Imagine that. She used up four hours of her life.
She'll never get back.
Oh, you were looking for the website that you can download the show from?
Oh, that was... Okay, you ready again?
Mm-hmm.
All right, it's matrix.csustan.edu
forward slash
negative
n-e-g-a-t-i-v
without the e
If you go there,
you should be able to find
quite a few of the
more recent shows.
And Don's shows
are there too.
Over the Edge. Much to his chagrin.
But don't tell him, because he doesn't like that.
Well, when you tell him,
just say comma and their mp3 files.
Just remember...
Yeah. You know, so...
He's kind of a perfectionist in this stuff.
Does it have a w-w-w
in front of matrix?
No. It's just http
colon
forward slash forward slash matrix
dot c-s-u-stan
dot e-d-u slash
forward slash one forward slash
negative n-e-g-a-t-i-v
I wonder when
they're gonna make the flash obsolete.
Well, I mean, they already
have aliases that you can,
you know, obtain
through various
commercial methodologies.
Puzzling evidence,
Dr. Philo Drummond,
who's also heard in the background here,
the Swingin' Love Corpses did this music
and the music heard earlier
in the background.
And Dr. Halberg from KPFA
Berkeley. We heard a bunch of
clips from movies that were posted
by Udnu Monet
and Tesla Coil
and probably other members
of alt.binaries.slack
that I can't remember. That drugs,
the cut-up drugs thing
was from the National Cynical
Network,
nationalcynical.com, and the
Amish band thing
was from the Electric
Amish at
electricamish.com.
I don't know who
did the
peanut butter and
jelly thing.
Hello, Paul. Welcome to the
End Times.
In today's
End Time essay,
we will be covering the difference between
the Wolfram
and the Bloodyhead Blanca Society
itself.
As seen here in our first slide,
the Bloodyhead Blanca Society
goes on forever.
There is no end, and there's
no use resisting.
Look at those heads
fall in slow motion.
Just beautiful.
...down the celestial stairs.
...within my house.
The only way to get it there,
by God, is with Bob Dobbs.
They tell you in the
first paragraph.
...so I say to people,
fourth, an Arnold Palmer's
head shall materialize in the space
above your sleeping parlor,
and it shall indeed be bloody.
It shall be dripping
with the residual blood
formed earlier in the day
when he was
without the word of Bob.
What are we gonna do about
the Bloodyhead of Arnold Palmer?
What the hell are we
gonna do about the Bloodyhead of Arnold Palmer?
That's what I wanna know.
His crimson head.
I've seen it in my nightmares.
I've been seeing
omens and signs.
We've gotta do something
about the Bloodyhead of Arnold Palmer.
These guys are
talking bad on Bob.
Neither them or the Christians
we gotta start with.
We gotta do something
bad
to make up.
Oh my God.
Shit.
...that they can keep awake and be under your bed
and inside the water and shoot in the waves
and rays up at you all the time.
But those UFOs, they're flying all over your house.
That's right, then they know about Bob.
And they're gonna be dropping it.
Doctor
for Bob.
For Bob.
How well do you play
your game? How well could you play?
Chances are you'll never know
unless you're fitted with the proper equipment.
Proper equipment
now provided by
Lemur in the form of this
lever.
Finally I did what I should have done in the first place.
I got acne.
Lever
Starring Barbara Beaumont
Hugh Billingsley
Tony Billingsley
and
and Gerry the Beaver
Oh, uh...
I uh...
What?
Honestly?
Uh...
Hey Wally, guess what?
Beaver, you got dropping again?
I didn't say you had to
It's just that he should do something to repay it
There's no rule against my school
Yes Wally, gee Wally
Yes, yes, gee, gee
Okay, I
Hey Dave, what's the number?
3-2-5-3-2-5-9-5-2-3-8
Hello?
2-3-2-5-9-5-2-3-8
Hello? 2-3-2-5-9-5-9-5-2-3-8
Hello? 2-3-2-5-9-5-9-5-8
Hello, Julie?
Yeah
This is Wally
Yeah, well, um, you know, Julie, uh, Wally Cleaver
Well, um, well, uh
Yeah, well, um, um, well, uh, uh, or something
Oh, man, what?
Shh, shh, shh, shh
What?
I mean, oh, yeah
This is cool
No girl in the world is gonna settle for a liquid diet
That's a gentlemanly thing
Yeah
Okay
Can't, yeah
Hello? Hello?
Hello?
Oh, yes
Ah, I get it
I can, I can do this
While I'mstore
I have the advice
Ah, don't let this California
Have the awe
I mean, men
I'm so, so nervous
I'm giving it my all
We prob now
I think there's a
You here, baby?
What tell?
I'll tell you
clearly stated that he was a Libra, is often found quite earnestly inquiring about it with a last shake from another planet.
A billion light-years from that very location, in a place called boundary virtue, is the joint trench of spot for active meditation.
Very full of life and stents, more deep, high floors are disgusting for the finer merits of the most recent patch of Saint Seiya episodes.
As an escortian non-Freudian, he's made the rouses of the trench again, and mocked the fridge again,
a retrograded, not-so-human jellyfish was four inches deep in his small dish,
which, like the cafeteria bacteria, is selected, collected, and piled high in a petri dish.
Five minutes from now, nowhere near the trench, a captain priest in a French,
a professional food with a doubt his mind and a whole list of truths,
suddenly set his dog aloof, so he went through, yelling through his boots and pears like a freak hailing Ernst,
while the jellyfish man does what he can to get a coup off his pubes.
A cross-faced, another, and completely underrated,
a savage is the willing aim, a poor, of an octopus with a cucumber wrapped in duck tape.
Meanwhile, in his oiled briscoe, on sausage,
tears ruin the perfectly good mascara of a drag queen named Sonia,
whose friends used to call him Fred back in ROTC.
As the cylindrical midget made him class two,
who was often seen to stand in sunshine steel
and scream at the top of his little midget lungs
as the wrong man had done in the disasters yet to come.
Just that second in Washington, a beaten-line for Linux
was giving a horribly boring speech to a group of teens,
one of whom was well-to-do, a certain group of women,
I am online, by breaking Bushmere's face,
didn't know how to steer away from the cool of the tone of Sunday.
Around the corner on the dark side of the moon,
in an oblong room, a genius-lily named Tuesday,
tuned in joystick-friendly,
a slice of pizza with an amazingly well-to-do white guy named Go-Di.
I'm going to go to bed.
Ah, my good friends.
Well, that was the El Queso All-Stars.
You can find out more about the El Queso All-Stars
at mp3.com, www.mp3.com, slash,
Enterbulator.
That's spelled E-N-T-U-R.
Bulator.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
And I heard my mama.
I heard my mama say.
What's she saying?
I heard my, I heard my mama say.
Talk to your mama.
Oh, I heard my mama.
Tell me, mama.
She said, Jess, get off of the bathroom.
That's the tense time today.
.
Let's go outside.
We can go downtown.
We'll make that thing you like that.
I'm actually trying.
It makes the world gonna wonder.
Deja vu.
So you're here to save the world?
I know you're out there,
I can feel you now.
I know that you're afraid.
You're afraid of us.
You're afraid of change.
I don't know the future.
I didn't come here to tell you
how this is going to end.
I came here...
to tell you how it's going to begin.
I'm going to hang up this phone,
and then I'm going to show these people
what you don't want them to see.
A world without you.
A world without rules and controls, without borders or boundaries.
A world where anything is possible.
Where we go from there is a choice I leave to you.
A world without you.
I'll fuck this place.
For your meal, I'd give three chickens and my best black sundae pants.
For your meal, I'd let you do-si-do my wife at der square dance.
For your meal, I'd give you eggs and cheese.
I would get down on my knees.
I would do all of these.
Come on, mister, pretty please!
For your meal...
For your beauty
I can talk about Bob.
Bob can do anything for you.
He can do anything for anybody.
There's only one problem.
If you're having a problem with your cash flow,
if you're having a problem with your spiritual life,
if you're having a problem with your car,
how about sex?
If you're having a problem with sex,
if you're having a problem with your car,
if you're having a problem like we had today
where the tire went flat,
and there's a problem, there's a debt,
a hole that needs to be filled in your life,
there's only one thing that you can do.
That's reach for your wallet, reach for your checkbook,
and send the money to P.O. Watts,
140306.
140306!
Dallas, Texas,
7,
7, 5, 2, 1, 4!
This will all come to you
if you send a dollar to the church
of the subgenius
P.O. Box
Dallas, Texas,
75214.
This will enable us
to continue with the marvelous operations
which we've known about
and we've done.
We've tried to spread throughout
the western hemisphere
and change this
CFR,
trilateralist-oriented
goal-reachers
of the beyond-noids
getting here in this.
Send,
you will get sex,
this is a subliminal message
brought to you in care
of the Subliminal Message Corporation.
Sex,
money, Bob,
these three concepts
will always be linked in your mind.
Sex, money, Bob.
Yes, this is a continuation
of the flow spew
that the doctors of feel-good-ice now got for us here.
You would have been told
which Bob to tune to in your area.
And this is not a burned-out radio station.
It is a plant-oriented call, ladies and gentlemen.
This is a spouting of spewing
and thumping of graven images.
This is a spouting of spewing and thumping of graven images.
Spewn-eyed,
blood-y umped,
nortonese mule-word.
Nortonese Mule-word.
You're listening
to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
Sponsored by
the Church of the Subgenius.
For more information
about the Church of the Subgenius,
of genius, write to Bob at the O-Box, 204-206, Austin, Texas, 78720, or visit the SoGenius
website at SoGenius.com.
Thank you for listening, and praise Bob.
See you next time.
Living creatures, cattle, creeping things, animals, the earth, the animals, cattle, everything,
heaps, man, fish, sea, birds, sky, and cattle, the earth, creeping thing, the earth, man,
image, them, them, the earth, fish, birds, sky, living thing, the earth, herb, seed,
tree, fruit, seed, food, animal, the earth, bird, guy, thing, food, thing, made, heavens,
the host, God, generation, heaven, earth, day, God, earth, heavens, planet, earth, herb,
a field, rain, man, ground, mist, surface, ground, man, dust, ground, nostrils, life,
man, soul, garden, man, ground, tree, site.
Food, tree, light, mist, garden, tree, good, evil, river, water, garden, there, heads, first,
and gold, gold, good, crescent, onyx, stone, river,
Shut up!
Black-throated green warbler.
One.
And do you know what happened?
Again, that...