The show ends, the show begins, and so begins another cycle of shows.
We want you to never forget these awful shows.
The terrible wasted lives that you've spent.
The collective years of listening to this rotten show.
And you don't even get it.
On a friendly basis.
You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to...
The Soap Genius Hour of Sweat.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
This is Hour of Sweat.
Slack number 1,653.
But it's also number 450.
A rerun from July of the so-called 1994.
When the show was only nine years old and still being produced in Dallas.
This old episode was requested, and we don't get many requests.
The show's changed a lot from decade to decade.
I don't work nearly as hard editing it as I used to.
Because it takes...
Too much time away from other things I need to be doing.
Especially near the holidays.
Like filling Slack Friday.
Two-for-one Salvation Orders.
And making books and videos and walking the dog and so forth.
So I don't blame people for liking old shows.
They had a lot more variety.
This one is from when I was producing the shows from my home studio in Dallas.
We were between radio stations.
So we relied more on clips from other subgeniusly...
Subgeniusly...
Radio shows like Puzzling Evidence in San Francisco on KPFA.
And ESO Swamp Radio Brain Rot Theater in Cleveland on WCSB.
And also on cassette tapes that were mailed in.
It was the days before the internet.
And people spent more time on things like making tapes and mailing them around.
People also read and wrote books in those days.
And this episode reflects all that.
We have Puzzling Evidence.
Doctors for Bob.
Inventing the Church.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave's rantster piece.
The Corruptigating Worms rant.
I read from Donna Cossey's book, Kooks, regarding the Nation of Islam.
And we hear strange music from Slouch.
The Merkins.
The Baby Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
And...
What...
Well...
Swingin' Love Corpses.
We'll do this in the background right now.
And now...
Captain Beefheart.
The path is the mask of love.
A way, a way.
The flow is the task above today.
There is no other way.
There's no other way.
You've got to trust us.
When you need a friend.
To find us.
You've got to look within.
You've got to trust us.
Before you turn to dust.
Gotta see it, boy, you see
Gotta be it, boy, you be
You gotta hear without fear
You gotta feel to reveal
You gotta touch without take
Such is it that I ain't his ape
Yes, dear friends, Captain Beefheart there
and some sort of basement tapes
the listeners sent us
a fantastical thing there
and welcome to another
Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack
Where are we at here?
I hate having to turn the air conditioner off
in order to do this show
but the microphone
you see is a special kind
that will, uh
it'll hurt us, friends
It picks up any noise
noises that the human ear cannot hear
voices of the dead and so forth
and you can imagine that
the atomic-powered air conditioner
here at the Subgenius Foundation
headquarters studio
110 degree Texas weather
Oh, but, uh
we will continue
um, here with, uh
the, uh
combustible Edison
here in the background
from their CD-i swinger
uh, we're continuing with our
uh, series
Hour of Slack series
on, uh, kooks
and tards
and, uh
news of the weird
and so forth
and let's see what sort of news we do have here
this is from, uh
our friend Chuck Shepherd's view from the ledge
we'll give the address at the end of the broadcast
Man punished for teaching women
Dhaka, Bangladesh
Fundamentalist Islamic clerics beat a man with shoes
and ordered his head shaved
because he ignored their orders
to stop educating illiterate women
uh-huh
Bismarck Mountains, Papua New Guinea
Dr. Ulrich Ritterfeldt of Holland's Utrecht
University has found a remote jungle tribe
who worship a photograph of Lyndon B. Johnson
frolicking with his beagles
as their god
the tribe sacrifice yam-like vegetables
to the photograph of LBJ and his silly dogs
which is assumed to have been traded to the tribe
by an American visitor
and on 200 Nolan Street
a man walking by some vagrants
was asked to share his bottle of liquor
and when he refused
one transient became so upset
he stabbed himself
uh, well, let's, uh
what, what, what, what else have we here?
we were given this book called Global Ritualism
Myth and Magic Around the World
and it mentions the Church of the Subgenius
in the most strange, uh, context
let's see here
The Last Faith
they're talking about
uh, uh, creating one's own new rituals from scratch
uh, in order to ach-achieve effective dream connections with the divine
this is some sort of, uh, a book about
well, it's a serious book
Myth and Magic
a ritual linking the conscious and the unconscious
archetypes of life, blah blah blah blah blah
The Last Faith, Neo-Creation
uh, wait, let's get some proper music going here
uh, there's some time
Tommy Lopez
uh, okay, the, the last faith
Neo-Creation is one that very few seem to have reached
it consists of the wholesale creation of an entire mythos and magical system
that has no connection with past traditions at all
this is a virtually impossible undertaking
since most of the forms, practices, and spiritual disciplines
one ostensibly needs to forge these archetypal or spiritual links
that can make this possible
are in and of themselves part of the system
and part of established traditions
of the three examples that come to mind
the first two were made by people who are both artists
and who created their system simply as art for art's sake
and, uh, then he talks very briefly about
Austen Spare
who I know very little about
and the magical world of Lord Dunsany
the last example, the tr-
not art for art's sake
he doesn't say what it's for
Bob for Bob's sake, friend
the last example
the church of the subgenius
defies all labels and previously stated rules
what's important is that even though it advertises itself as an inherently bogus religion
it is indeed a parody that actually provides myths, rituals, magical techniques
and an attractive group dynamic
that has made it wildly popular
such semi-serious concepts as
the temporary personal savior
devolution
and slack
are extremely powerful
though nodding to such traditional systems as Daoism and Dada
well, well, well
so we, we, at least we did give the nod to those old stodgy, uh, traditional, uh, systems
Daoism and Dada
and, uh, I notice they credit us with de-evolution
no, that's the work of Satan
uh, we, we, uh, oh no, that's right, it's evolution that's the work of Satan
I got it, so, de-evolution is the work of Devo
and, um, uh, yeah, it's, uh, interesting, uh, uh, they, they think we created a ritual system
this Denny Sargent is the author of this book
cre- yeah, created it
I'll tell you what, man
uh, J.R. Bob Dobbs!
He didn't have to create nothing
this stuff was told to him direct by Jehovah One
the alien space god from some sin galaxy
the, the, the rival cults like to call that, uh, that thing
that writhing, uh, tachyonic monster
uh, the Lord God, Jehovah Creator of the Universe
mm-hmm, well, uh, uh
it is a monster that, uh, demands ob- ob- bi-ascent
uh, but, uh, uh, that, there's no sense in, you know, getting these things mixed up
I mean you, you, you don't need to be praying to either one of them
you, but you're supposed to be paying
and, uh, of course you can do that, uh, through the creation of your own religion
uh, after you have first paid Bob
uh, thank you
Thank you.
If they're true Americans, it's not too late.
It's not too late.
But the end is near the corruptigating snakes of hell.
These little demonic worms.
They're not real snakes.
They're worms.
Are the byproduct of the gelatinous goo that we produce when we think incorrect thinklings.
And there's all kinds of incorrect thinklings and bastardized thoughts going around there.
Creationism.
Anticreationism.
And Darwinism.
There's no such thing.
We were all created last second.
The moment you ascertain your own consciousness and are aware of it.
That's when those little corruptigating snakes can have their little corruptigating snake influences on you.
And that's why there's so many mass murders and John Wayne Gacy's.
And people pulling their eyes out and their testicular organs.
And running around without any clothes on and their medications off.
That's why it's happening.
Because society is so deeply decayed from inside.
That it's actually rotting outwards into a plethora of stinkiness.
You said it.
Er, I said it.
I said it better than you could imagine me saying it.
Because I know I'm telling the truth.
What must we do as true Americans?
We must not write our congressmen.
Because they're the purveyors of the little tiny corruptigating snakes.
Look at the next time you get some mail from the government.
And it says Senator Rickenbrack or Vice Vasectomy Honorable Lunchcake and Senor Landfill and all the rest of those guys.
They're not real.
They're little false dummy heads.
Plastic.
Some of them are this real rare chromium oxide.
Which is a form of rust.
And once they get in office they think they're running the place.
But they're actually the corruptigating snakes from another person's spinal column lumbar.
Yeah.
You thought you left when your science teacher told you that we were in a filling in one of God's teeth.
That wasn't meant to tell you how small or big we are.
Or how insignificant we are.
Everybody knows we're insignificant.
Just try getting bored and croaking a couple times.
It just keeps happening over and over again.
There's no getting off the wheel of karma.
This life is nothing but a bunch of dharma.
If you want to kill the corruptigating snakes you have to kill them yourself.
You must form small mobile units.
And small mobile phoenix and hunix.
And you must get yourselves cool looking outdoor ponchos and stuff.
And guns.
And train with pikes.
Go up in the hills and hope the British won't catch you.
Because it's too late farmers.
And freedmations.
Not the freedmations.
Take them guys out of there.
I forgot what the name was.
You.
I'm pointing my finger.
I'm giving you the finger directly at you buddy.
You.
Number two.
Third man from the rear.
Don't point your finger at me daddy or I'll cut off your finger at me.
You.
I'm telling each and every one of you to take what amount of poisons and lusty juices you have
sacked up and drawn up in your nipples and the membranes around your body.
And turn them into a fighting force for the future of your small little stupid looking
little children which have not, will not be born.
Not since they changed the water.
I'm, I'm, I'm ripping them off because everybody needs it including yours truly.
Right Chaz?
Now once you form these small little tiny little small little units you must go out
and train in the forest and pretend that like say huge kangaroos with sunglasses or something
so absurd you can hardly imagine is attacking you.
And then you'll be ready for stealth and secret and surprise because surprise is surprise.
Who would expect a huge carnivorous kangaroo with purple sunglasses to come, come bounding
out of the woods with an AK-47 or some new new assault weapon made in Romania.
No man.
No.
That's because they're not made in Romania anymore.
They're made in the UXA, the former UXA which was bequeathed to the sub-illuminati of third
branch from the rear.
And that's not yours truly or yours.
The blue lunge.
The blue lunged, blue blooded, blue bellied, blue lunge.
The red coats and the blue bloods.
It's all one sniveling, sniferoos, de-driveling swando-
Landowners.
Landfillers.
Hoppin' geeks full of themselves trying to take over your own sweat.
What they want to do with something so stinky and wet?
They want to take your limbs.
That's why they start wars.
They start wars for the limb banks.
And we're not talking about flesh.
Landscaping.
That's why they have landscaping so that people will cut off their feet with mechanized potato
rooters.
They want the limbs.
I don't think you got the edge here quite right on the driveway there, young man.
See, you can see it in all their fingers.
They're- they glow green.
Aye.
My name is Flowers.
I'm much prettier than mine.
The chlorophyll's starting to ooze out of the back of your-
Did you just tell me she's Flowers, boy?
Talk about day of the triffids.
This is ten times worse.
This is an invasion of a bunch of supplicating, corruptigating worms, which actually make
your body, your blood, crystallized and stinky when they cut you open.
When will you wake up?
When will you wake up, America?
When it's too late?
Like fishing in the warm waters of the electric trough.
It's been said that thousands of these turtles will never get old.
A turtle is one of mankind's oldest non-humans.
It goes for lots and lots of times.
It goes as many times as it can.
But it never relieves itself of that original feeling of being a human.
It's a natural feeling, which is to go onward and onward with that hard, tacky little shell
and that stupid nozzle.
But who wants to kill them now?
A big fat nuclear power plant, which is really home to the what?
The corruptigating worms.
The little, teeny, tiny, snakey things in your spinal membrana.
They're alien.
They're as alien as blinis and vodka.
They're as alien as pasta for Zuul.
And Chinese noodles.
That's right, buddy.
There's not a single hot dog in these corruptigating noodles.
That's because when they're in your spine, they take over.
It's planet corruptigating worms for sure.
Your name goes first.
Then your memories of your friends and your family.
Your whole life flashes in front of you like a quick urine test in the dark.
And when you wake up, it's far, far too late.
When are you gonna wake up?
Oh, unbelievable, dear friends.
Lonesome cowboy Dave, and scabby days on ESO radio.
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
They taught me a song they were programming, Dave.
Can I sing it for you?
Dave.
Can I sing the song for you, Dave?
Sing the song, Hal.
Thank you, Dave.
Daisy.
Give me your answer true.
I'm crazy all over love of you.
It won't be a solution.
I can't afford a cage.
But don't you see I'm on the scene.
I'm on my way to the end for two.
Two.
Dave.
What is it, Hal?
I'm scared.
Will I come to you?
No, Hal. You'll be reincarnated into a bullfrog's.
He's a bullfrog.
I'm scared.
I don't even know him.
He's not a bullfrog.
I'm scared.
He's a bullfrog.
You're scared.
CSB Cleveland.
Yes, a really classic, classic,
quasi-subgenius rant.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave is certainly no sloucher
when it comes to saving the universe.
And speaking of slouches,
this music we've got in the background
is from a cassette we just got in recently
called Slouch.
We celebrate our sickness.
And since we're focusing on cranks, crackpots,
visionaries, and those who truly know the truth
and know they know the truth,
let's check it out.
We'll see.
Yeah, this piece here on this cassette by Slouch
is called...
The Call of Thulhu.
Spooky, man. Let's see what else is on here.
Tsk.
And I don't know why we care.
We can't play guitar.
And we've got nothing to say.
And we're dancing
to the beat of the drunken drum.
We're dancing
to the drum.
drunken drum.
God save
Drunken drum.
Cool.
Cool, man.
I wish I could find their address.
A band named Slouch.
Whoa!
Yes, Slouch.
Another of the strange independent cassettes.
If only we had printed their address somewhere on the cassette,
we would be able to tell you who, why, and wherefore.
But in the meantime,
we're just going to struggle ahead
against the odds.
Against the corruptigating worms,
and continue inventing and reinventing
the Church of the Sub...
Uh...
The...
No.
Sub...
I like that sub part.
It could be a religion.
No, wait. An entire religion.
Sub...
Sub Real Smart Guy.
J.R. Bob Dobbs of the Church of the Sub Real Smart Guy.
Sub Intellectual.
Intellectual.
Sub...
Sub Einstein.
Sub Telza?
No, no.
That was the one that dropped the atom bomb.
Sub ID.
Sub IP.
Sub Ego.
Sub IQ.
Church of...
J.R. Bob Dobbs Search IQ.
No, no.
We got no one on the back.
It's a church.
It is a church.
And it's some guy named Bob.
Yeah, it is a religion.
Too many secular things.
J.R. Bob.
J.R. Bob Smith.
What was his name again?
What was the last name again?
J.R. Bob.
Bob Dobbs.
Wait a minute.
Wait, say that again.
Bob Dobbs.
I like the way you said that.
Let's say it again.
Bob Dobbs.
взять.
J.R. Bob.
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
J.R. Bob DOBBS.
Bob Dobbs.
Wait a minute.
Say that again.
Bob Dobbs.
Santa the Squirt. Church of the
Subgenius! Hey! There you go!
Church of the Subgenius!
Hey! There you go!
You got it going right there?
I already would have been
zombie. Would it be in
Pensacola?
Cleveland?
Chicago?
Pittsburgh?
Make it through Checkpoint Charlie by the skin of my teeth.
I know just how he
feels, dear friends.
And now it's
come to that time in the show when we
turn to our book of kooks.
Our literal book
called Kooks
by Donna Cossie.
We'll give the
address to right away for this amazing book
loaded with profiles
of various
what the normals
might call extremist
movements.
Well, Subgenius is
a
subgenius.
Man, this is
an amazing book.
Tonight we're going to be looking at
Nation of Islam.
Yes, the
section here which says
that Nation
of Islam
began much like Moorish
Science as an obscure
cult known only to its members.
It was suddenly thrust into
the national consciousness in the late 1950s
and early 60s when Malcolm M.
X became its chief spokesman.
Now,
much has been written about
Nation of Islam and even more about
Malcolm X.
And, you know, Malcolm X
did leave that group before
he was killed. But it's evident that
very few outside of the group have
ever seen the writings of Elijah
Muhammad or examined
the group's belief system in detail.
There's been more emphasis on the
group's black nationalism than their
religious beliefs, which
may be too zany for the
average social scientist to take
seriously.
The
founder of the Nation of
Islam,
what was his name here? W.D.
Fard, I believe.
Yeah,
W.D. Fard.
His
formidable mission was to
wake the dead nation
in the West, to
teach them the truth about the white
man and to prepare them for Armageddon.
His version of the
Battle of Armageddon had the war between
the good black Muslims
and the evil white Christians
taking place in
Har-Magedon, the
wilderness of North America.
Now,
Fard disappeared, but
Elijah Muhammad took the
thing over and began teaching that
Fard was God in person
to be worshipped as a deity.
With prayer and sacrifice,
Elijah Muhammad emphasized
that Christianity, the white man's
religion, teaches that God is a
spook, while Islam,
the natural religion for the black
man, teaches that God is a man.
Evidently, this teaching had
great appeal. In no time,
Elijah Muhammad was leading the Nation of Islam
with a firm hand, calling himself
Allah's prophet and messenger.
If
W.D. Fard's teachings have
bite, then Elijah Muhammad's
have fangs.
Muhammad developed Fard's ideas in
astounding detail, accounting for
the state of the world as the product of the
evil white race and
its hold on world power.
He taught that the original man
is the black man, that white
people are the result of a genetic
plot and have only been around
for 6,000 years.
The, quote, so-called
Negro, unquote, came from
the tribe of Shabazz
within the Asiatic nation.
Who originated in Africa
when a great explosion divided
the earth from the moon
60 trillion
years ago.
Members of this eminent tribe
were the first explorers of earth
and the first inhabitants of the Nile
Valley. Furthermore, they
authored not only the Bible, but the
Koran. Elijah
Muhammad's main text for the dissemination
of his teachings, Message
to the Black Man in America,
tells the story of the graphed
ending of the evil white
race. The woeful story
begins 6,800
years ago when
Yaqub, an evil scientist
from Mecca, angered the
Meccan authorities and was exiled
along with 59,999
of his followers
to an island in
the Aegean Sea.
While in exile, he plotted
his revenge. He would enslave
the tribe of Shabazz by
breeding an evil
white race.
He would rule over them for
6,000 years.
He created the brown race from the
black using the old biblical
method of infanticide.
He ordered the nurses
to kill all black babies by
pricking the brains with a sharp needle as soon
as the black child's head is out of its mother.
When there was a birth of a brown baby,
the nurse would come and make much
ado over it and would tell the mother
she'd given birth to a holy child and that
she would nurse it for the next six weeks,
for her child was going to be a great man.
Using the same method,
200 years later,
he created the red race
from the brown and 200 years
after that, the yellow race
from the red. Finally,
after 600 years, his work
was completed and he had created
the white devils.
And as Elijah Muhammad
said here, the
Yaqub-made devils
were really pale white
with really blue eyes
which he called the devil.
The devil is the most
ugly of the colors
for a human eye.
These hateful creatures were exiled
in West Asia, or Europe,
and became savages, remaining
in that condition for 2,000 years.
As Elijah Muhammad says,
they lost all knowledge
of civilization.
The Lord God of Islam
taught me that some of them
tried to graft themselves back
into the black nation, but they
had nothing to go by.
They were not brave enough
to make a start and got as far
as what you would call the gorilla.
In fact, all of the monkey family
are from this 2,000 year
history of the white race
in Europe.
You know this stuff,
it proves what we've been saying all along.
All races are equal because they're all equally racist.
This is exactly like
old Ku Klux Klan type
stuff, mirror image.
In the reverse.
If only the true teachings
of the Yeti, the birth of the
true subgenius race,
the race that is the master race
because it comes in all
colors, all flavors,
and all sexes.
Anyway, let's see.
According to
further teachings of Nation of
Islam here,
after 2,000 years,
Allah raised Moses
to civilize the white race, who
made his job quite difficult.
After the process of civilization,
the white devils fulfilled
Yaqub's vengeance by enslaving
the tribe of Shabazz.
Fortunately, the end of this sad chapter
of history is now in sight.
The 6,000 year white rule ended
in 1914. We are now
living in the post-1914
years of grace, which will last
until the chosen of Allah
will be resurrected from the
mental death imposed upon them
by the white man.
Achieving this resurrection was the holy
mission of Elijah Muhammad,
messenger of Allah and the spiritual leader
of the lost found nation in the West.
He died
in 1975,
but his mission is
being carried on by
Louis Farrakhan,
whose name you may recognize.
He's been in the news quite a bit.
Louis Farrakhan, who succeeded Malcolm X
as the group's spokesman,
resurrected the old Nation
of Islam.
Elijah Muhammad is alive
and well in the hearts of the followers
of Louis Farrakhan,
and not just in their hearts.
He flies to Earth from time to time
aboard a giant flying saucer, occasionally
summoning Farrakhan to receive
his instructions.
So claims the notorious minister
Farrakhan.
He became a household word
in 1984
when he was accused of
making anti-Semitic remarks.
But,
he is leading
something like
50,000 followers
and his devotion
to even the most obscure teachings
of Elijah Muhammad
is reflected in his belief in flying
saucers as Ezekiel's vision.
We quote Louis Farrakhan,
The great wheel
that many of us see in the sky today
is not so much a wheel as one may think
in such terms, but rather
a place made like a wheel.
The like of this wheel
like plane
was never seen before.
You cannot build one like it and get the same results.
Okay, today we see the white race
preparing for the sky battle
to determine who shall remain and rule
this Earth, black or white.
The present wheel shaped
plane, known as the mother of planes,
is one half mile by a
half mile, and is the largest
mechanical man-made object in the sky.
It is a small human
planet made for the purpose of
destroying the present world of enemies
of Allah. The small
circular made planes called flying
saucers, which are so much talked of
being seen, could be from this
mother plane. This is only one
of the things in store for the white
man's evil world. Believe
it or not, this is to warn you
and me to fly to our own
God and people.
And Elijah Muhammad
has evidently taken residence on
that mother ship, dear friends, in order
to direct the proceedings that will end
the six thousand year rule of
the white devils, which I suppose
includes yours truly,
according to these guys.
On October 24th,
1989, Louis Farrakhan
held a press conference in which he
detailed his September 1985
vision that he was carried
to a mountain in
Tepoztlan, Mexico,
and then to Elijah Muhammad's
mother ship.
As we reached the top of the mountain,
a wheel, or what you call an unidentified
flying object, appeared at the side
of the mountain and called me to come up
into the wheel.
A beam of light came from the wheel
and I was carried up on this beam of light
into the wheel.
And it moved up to the mother wheel,
the human built planet.
At the center of the ceiling was a
speaker, and through the speaker I heard the voice
of the honorable Elijah Muhammad
speaking to me as clearly as you are hearing
my voice this morning.
Mr. Muhammad began to speak to me. He said,
President Reagan
has met with the Joint Chiefs
of Staff to plan a war.
I want you to go hold a press conference
in Washington, D.C.
and announce their plan and say to the world
that you got the information
from me on the wheel.
So friends, we're sharing that
information with you.
A recent
issue of the Nation of Islam
newsletter reveals
a government plot to institute
a new world order which
may involve alien beings
and so-called UFOs
which are in fact created by the government.
So,
dear friends,
the world
of kooks and crackpots
and crazies,
you know, they come in all
kinds, and you can get the book
of kooks by Donna Cossie
probably in better bookstores,
but you can also inquire from
here, got that pencil ready,
Ferrell
House, F-E-R-R-A-L
House,
P.O. Box 3466
Portland, Oregon
That's P.O. Box 3466
there for Ferrell House Press
book kooks
and this might be a good time
to break in with the Church of the
Subgenius
Church of the
Subgenius address, you got that pencil ready
dear friends, if you
could but
address that
self-addressed stamped envelope
or whatever, you know,
if you want to know a little bit more about
what this particular
religious take on the world
is, and I think perhaps
one or two of you, you, you,
yeah, that one, you do,
well, you, pick that pencil up
and write to Bob, that's right,
just Bob, at, as long as you
get the rest of this right, it'll get to it,
at Post Office Box
easy enough,
Box 807
Bob at Box 807
the zip code is
I remembered that,
it's Bob, P.O. Box
for the zip code
and
Bob P.O. Box 807
Pittsburgh, no,
not Pittsburgh, J.R.
Bob Dobbs, Church of the Subgenius
in, uh, San Francisco?
No,
we need something
down to home, Tulsa?
South, in the South,
definitely, in the South, not Louisville,
Little Rock, though, that's too obvious,
J.R. Bob Dobbs,
the Church of the Subgenius, in,
Mexico City,
J.R. Bob Dobbs,
Church of the Subgenius,
it's gotta be in the South,
it's not Atlanta, it's not New Orleans,
it's not Baton Rouge,
it's gotta be in,
South Pole, man,
the South Pole, all the way to the South,
San Antonio,
Texas, you got the right state there,
J.R. Bob Dobbs, Church of the Subgenius,
in, Amarillo, just doesn't
sound right,
what's that, Big D,
Big D, what is it,
Dallas, just south of Bob,
Bob in Dallas, hey,
Kennedy,
Kennedy was shot in Dallas,
the grassy knoll,
the grassy, Lee Harvey Oswald,
the book repository,
Oh, no, no, no,
it's not so funny, man,
no more of that,
one little bit of News of the Weird,
here, I just noticed,
this is from Chuck Shepard's News of the Weird,
for those of you with tape decks on,
that's P.O. Box 8306,
St. Petersburg, Florida,
33738,
anyway,
this is a nice,
crackpot sort of news story here,
least competent person,
in Fort Lauderdale, Florida,
in February,
accused murderer,
J.R. Bob Dobbs,
and Donald Leroy Evans,
38, filed a pre-trial motion,
asking permission to wear
a Ku Klux Klan robe,
in the courtroom, and be referred to
in legal documents,
by the honorable and respected name,
of, Hi Hitler,
that's H-I,
one word, Hitler,
according to courthouse employees,
interviewed by the Associated Press,
Evans thought,
Adolf Hitler's followers,
were saying,
Hi Hitler,
rather than,
Heil Hitler,
but we carry on,
regardless,
we carry on,
and on,
and we're dancing,
to the feel,
of the drunk controller,
the drunk controller,
A little bit of slouch here,
his best friend.
Let us follow the narrow,
winding trail of Billy's life.
Let us share in his experience
and from his perspective.
This is Billy.
Ooh,
I need to call for a free brochure.
1-800-543-1495
That's a toll-free number.
Number.
Where is Mrs. Q?
Q, I tired.
Hungry.
When is it time to sleep?
How do I go to the bathroom room?
Snap.
Snap, boom, bam.
Put your trust in TV.
TV.
TV gives me seeds.
Plant seeds.
It's all God.
Outpatients by day,
lovers by night.
1, 2, 3, 4.
Outpatients by day,
ва Stardom by night.
vaccine.
убийство.arota
come me
protein
Funk magic
it's
esters
up
the
moon
.
Humans.
. . Bucks.
Oh, how does it feel, baby?
What a great night!
We got a little bit of nighties
A good night, boy
Oh, yes, dear friends, Lonesome Cowboy Dave there
And Outpatients by Day, Lovers by Night
Before that, It the Tard with its album Die, Tard, Die
And before that, Slouch
And what have we here? Well, let's see
There's The Merkins!
Okay, yeah, sure, let's try that
Let's try this, The Merkins
Sister Velveteen Sly sent this in
This is in the theme of tonight's show
Where I come from in the north part of the dance
There lives a crazy creep who would wake me from my sleep
With the clatter of his naked feet upon the winter snow
And the clinking of the icicles that hung below
He is monstrously oversized, no
He wore a crusty beanie and a midnight blue bikini
And a blue bikini and a midnight blue bikini
And a string of moldy lemons interlaced with paper cups
Some have said his brain was curdled when he lived among the turtles
Who would hit them, start and wallow in their eyes
Crazy Creep, he was a very mad kind
But I loved the crazy creep, he was the only one
Who'd listen when I played my glockenspiel
I'd ride upon his shoulders as we rounded up the caribou
And he'd scare off the bullies with a shriek you'd hear in Baraboo
Ah!
But cause the town was red, he was forced to slink about
So I'd leave him bits of dumping or a piece of pickled kraut
And they never comprehended, even though his mind was bent
That all he ever wanted was a chance
To show the people how to dance
Woo-hoo!
Hey!
I heard he was a shriner
And I heard he had no buttons
I heard that in the night he used his tongue to play the drum
He is snorting!
And cavorted
Seems all the bitters
Yes
And some say he built a treehouse
Where there wasn't any trees
I loved him
But cause the town misread him
He was forced to slink about
So I'd leave him bits of dumplings
Or a piece of pickled grout
So don't laugh at crazy creatures
When you meet them on the street
And don't shout them
Just because they smell bad
They could be the only brand
You ever had
Oh man, wonderful.
Crazy Creep there.
I guess that's a hymn
for subgeniuses, inadvertently,
by the Merkins,
where they are at
618 Western Avenue,
Madison, Wisconsin,
53711.
The kooks can be your
very own
very, very good friends, you know?
Friends.
He's the person who's the son of society!
He's the one that corrupts and kills our youth!
He's the one that wants to change us to the devil!
Satan! Satan!
He's the one who killed us all!
Satan is the lord of all evil!
He is the demon of magic, Father Grace!
Satan!
Have you seen the modeling of the labors?
Correcting the remains of those people that were killed!
And destroying!
And the lustful violence of the world!
Doing their crime!
Satan!
Satan loves it all!
He will kill!
And destroy!
And corrupt you!
When you least expect it!
Satan! Satan! Satan!
The holy Satan!
Can make you and bring you down!
And take you away from the lord Jesus Christ!
Oh!
He!
The lord Jesus Christ is the only one that can save you!
Oh!
He shall!
Jesus Christ will save you!
Oh!
Jesus Christ!
Satan is the killer!
Satan is the one who will bring you down!
Satan is the bad one!
Jesus Christ!
And old Bob,
he'll just stand,
stand by and watch.
Couldn't hardly do a show like this one without Church of New Faith!
There in Virginia Beach, Virginia.
P.O. Box 9152
And with Chris Cordes, Demons in My Head.
No, they're in my CD player actually, is where they are.
And, oh,
no, the corruptigating worms have tried to stop us,
my friends.
But, and it's been tough, I'll tell you.
It's been a very difficult week around here.
You can hear the zombies working so hard in the background,
trying to get our mailing out.
And, and, uh, but, but,
but I, but we're gonna keep trying.
I ain't gonna let you down.
You ain't gonna be let down by your old friend Reverend, uh,
uh,
Reverend, uh,
Reverend Spank.
He's on this tiny, hot thing.
Reverend.
Hey, Jim.
Hey, we gotta, we gotta.
We can change his name to Kaivin Blank.
We gotta, we gotta think of a name for him.
Spank.
Kaivin Blank.
And so like that.
Spank.
Um, no, not Spank.
Ygor Spank.
No, no.
Reverend Ygor Spank.
So Spank would be just like, uh, you know, Spanky, you know.
It's gotta be Russian.
It's gotta be totalitarian.
Oh yeah.
Vladimir, Vladimir Spank.
We gotta, we gotta get the Jewish, the Jewish thing.
Name that one guy that tortured everybody.
Ivan the Terrible.
J.R. Bob Dobbs, Church of the Subgenius in Dallas, Texas.
Ivan Spank.
No, no, no.
It's not perfect.
Look into your soul, J.R., you know it's not perfect.
I don't have a soul, I've already sold out.
J.R. Bob Dobbs, Church of the Subgenius in Dallas, Texas.
Ivan...
We've got to get the Jewish thing in there.
Oh, man.
Stein.
Stein is too common.
I like the F-T-E-S.
Stein.
St-a-nk.
Stank.
Stanky.
What do you mean, the little rascals?
No, that was spanky.
We can't use that.
We probably got it copyrighted.
J.R. Bob Dobbs, Church of the Subgenius.
There's a big bang.
Reverend Ivan.
Big bang.
Stank.
Bang.
Very good.
Like a gang bang, a stank.
Yeah.
We got to make him right on the tip of our tongue.
High praise.
We need some kind of heretical offshoot.
Yeah.
Like a golfer's hand.
Golfer's hand.