The Stone King of our Love!
仲介綝 priest
I'm dreaming of a white Christmas
Just like the ones I used to know
Where the treetops glisten
And kitties listen to the air
Sleigh bells in the snow
Ooh, oh
I'm
I's
Diana
Es
Yes
Stop
Drop
I
Merry Christmas and be white.
Merry Christmas.
May your two days be merry and bright
And may all your Christmases be white
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
And may all your Christmases be white
We must buy our toys!
We have to buy some marketing scheme for children's toys.
It will empower us to resist them.
You will use your church as a vehicle to bring these toys before the power.
It will be a lot of fun.
But for kids, do we understand and accept?
For the usual, plus expenses.
Good.
Okay, I think for the girls, we'll have the strawberry rainbow hearts.
And for the boys, little tiny Transformers.
Robots will change into dollar bills and back again.
Yes, but how about...
That will of good against evil be represented in your marketing schemes, human?
Good at what, the muscle?
Good.
Good!
The primitive Earth societies should accept this value judgment.
Good will have free physical attributes according to human desires.
Sexual desires.
Latent in children.
Children brought out through the vehicle of this so-called...
So far, we're told these boys have church.
Batteries not included.
Yes.
The old subgenius toy marketing scheme.
Recorded there at Dockstock 1984.
And me and Palmer Veedies.
Angels we have heard on high.
It was by the Philistines.
The collage called All the Money You've Got is from the great Obtuse Christmas collage album,
which you can get for free.
Get this.
Check out this website, obtuse.iuma.com.
That's obtuse...
Excuse me.
Some of these subgeniuses.
That's obtuse.iuma.
dot com.
Free.
The obtuse thing.
And before that, jingle bells from the Mill Valley Taters.
Oh, and this background music is Christmas Gas.
14 blasted holiday carols with Slim Spinkter.
Now, his name is not spelled Stinktor, but Spinkter.
www.slimspinkter.com has...
Or you can write to slim at...
Slim Spinkter.
But that's S-P-I-N-C-T-E-R.
Slimspinkter.com.
Ah, yes.
And next up, the real story of Christmas by Michael Shelley.
S-P-I-N-C-T-E-R.
He wanted to play the drums and be the little drummer boy, but he couldn't.
He wanted 10s and 20s.
10s and 20s.
And he got McDonald's gift certificates and he got Zuzu's pedals.
And that's the real story of Christmas.
Dave.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
A lot of people don't know this, but Lonesome Cowboy Dave
was the original producer of the album.
original Mr. Jingling.
That was so long
ago, Chaz. That was another
life, and that was another lifestyle.
I lived then with a very,
very, very dear friend of mine,
still to this day,
Mr. Horace Joris Nobo
Monkey, and he and I
were the best.
Those were the days, weren't they?
I don't know. The sun never came
up, but we still called them days.
We were feisty
people then. The glass was always
half full, and we were always happy.
Wasn't that when you originally met Bob
was when you were the original Mr.
Jingling, and you were hanging out down
in the Greenwich Village? Everything had
tassels that year. I think it was
19... That's true.
What bar did you run into him at? Was it Santa Claus?
You? I think it was
Bob. We were looking for records at
Bleeker Bob's one day, and I was wearing the tutu,
and he recognized me as
Swingin' Sam, also better known as
Mr. Jingling here in Cleveland Town.
He could tell by my little elf
tassels and the fact that I had
the... We were on all of that.
How did that paternity suit ever turn out
between Dobbs and Santa?
And who? His dad.
Santa Dog. I don't know.
You know, and I don't think it was...
Yes, but St. Nicholas, this is fact,
St. Nicholas punched
another bishop in the nose
and bloodied his nose.
And sucked him. Really? The historical
St. Nicholas?
Over the trinity of God.
The original St. Nicholas?
Nicholas in Turkey?
I swear upon Bob.
Who the hell is God?
The heart of the country.
I could tell he said God.
Who the hell is God?
Ask Dobbs one day.
That's the question we should be asking.
Suddenly, a lightning bolt
struck from nowhere on that
bright, sunny day.
Bob did a backflip, and from that day
on, he too was a believer.
And from the snow...
A little child bearing flowers
emerged.
Chip, what else was on the table?
Each one a dirty flower.
The historical
Santa Claus is
originally lived
as the caller knows
as a bishop in
was it Constantinople?
Yeah, like one of those
It was in ancient Byzantium.
Yeah, Asia Minor
in general, yeah.
Yes, and he was
he was known for
sneaking into the rooms
of young women and leaving
gifts.
Light-sized lumps of coal, complete with a fake beard
and a CIA Wall Street credit card.
A saint he was,
the girl said.
St. Nicholas invented the CIA.
You got it, brother.
He snuck into people's houses through the chimney.
He knew when they were awake.
You got it, brother.
But like the CIA, he was...
He was protecting them.
St. Nick was a creeping, stinking
spy. He knows when you've been
sleeping. He knows what you've been
eating. Hey, man, my kids still believe
in St. Nicholas.
And who keeps that belief alive in their
fevered, sick little brain?
Madison Avenue, of course.
No, the surveillance community
under your direction.
And the Reynolds Tobacco Company.
Miller Bear, you know.
If you're bad, he punishes you.
If you're good, he rewards you.
He's probably the closest...
closest thing to Jesus walking the Earth.
He's the closest thing to Big Brother there is.
He rewards those who knows when they are smiling
when they're awake.
I think, really, if you want to make a deal,
you have to do it with, you know...
Could Dr. Claus, in fact, be
the wandering, quote,
milkman rumored to have
fathered our savior,
J.R. Bob Dobbs?
Well, we find it a very likely possibility
from the falsified documents
we have here.
And also the fluffy beard that often grew on Bob Dobbs.
And the sperm count
with the glowing red nose.
What could this mean?
Listen, if you're going to say
Indiana had flying saucers
out in Minneapolis 15,000 years ago
and my damn God,
it was for sure the beard, the fake beard.
And I want one of them new robots
with the real intestinal bacteria.
Yeah, what about...
And one of those robots
with a fish brain for a brain.
They're sold out.
Their Toys R Us has no more.
They're on the shelves.
Can't get them from Amazon.com.
Can't get them anywhere in time.
Too late for Christmas.
Have yourself
a merry little Christmas.
a merry little S igenness.
Have yourself a merry little s ます
Have yourself a merry little Christmas.
Have yourself a merry little cinema Seriously,
Okay!
It all worked.
Christmas
Let your side
be light
From the water
troubles will be
outside
Have yourself
a merry little
song
From the
water
miles away
Once a day
as in olden
say
happy golden
be miles
away
Let your heart
be out of sight
light
miles away
have yourself
a merry little
Christmas
night
Oh, my God.
Together, if the fates allow, I'm a shining star upon the highest bough.
And have yourself a merry little Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas, friends.
Have yourself a merry little Christmas by No-L.
No-L.
Before that, some year-old ESO and Michael Shelley did that real story of Christmas
from the Tarkin Records All-Star Holiday Extravaganza.
I'm playing a lot from that.
So check out www.triage.com for that one also.
The Tarkin Records is also on www.
www.triage.com.
And now, the Jeff Rose.
Go.
Yeah!
That rice is such good food.
The we're bobs and I'm those who have the psychosis that convinces them that they are the Santa Bob or that they're Santa Bob by night.
And they go shuffling through the snow on their nameless, hideous errands.
The grin of Bob and the beard of Santa Claus and the pipe of the Lord stuck on their face.
They stop using the locks of their doors and they just kind of float into the keyhole.
Oh, friends, it's tough.
It's tough. And, you know, you just just going to church ain't enough.
You got to send your money to the Santa Bob.
As a matter of fact, the people across the street from me told their kids that that Santa Claus bills them for the toys he brings.
Can you believe that?
They asked the kids were asking if their parents, if maybe Santa Claus will bring us to He-Man erector sets.
And the mom said, no, no, he won't, because he bills.
We can't afford that.
Santa Claus sends us a bill after Christmas.
Yeah, but at least he totes the note.
Every Christmas Eve, children nestled in their beds dream of Santa and the presents they hope he.
Hey, wait a second.
That's no kid.
All right, everyone, use your sideways.
Say.
All right.
It's not Santa's workshop.
It's Santa Claus.
Don't worry.
I'm almost there.
See, that's where Santa lives.
All right.
Jinx Jinx.
Is that Santa Claus?
What's going on?
Jinx is psyching and projecting his story into our minds.
Holy zombie Jesus.
Is that Santa Claus?
Merry Christmas, Santa Claus.
Merry Christmas.
A season for miracles.
Oh, thanks, Wappers.
Don't forget Santa Claus.
And Jinx, too.
It's snowing.
Looks like we're going to have a white Christmas.
It's not you.
Advanced Dogmatic Studies, dear friends.
Also known as Electric Elf at loop.com.
How the Jinx Stole Christmas.
From their collection, Have Yourself an Advanced Dogmatic Christmas.
That's Advanced Dogmatic Studies.
Did I say studios?
Studios.
At, um.
Well, you can email information about that whole album,
which is available, the Advanced Dogmatic Christmas Album,
from electricelf at loop.com.
Go to him.
But I have no gift to bring.
Go. Look upon the newborn king.
Go. Go. Go. GO!
And they told me a rum pum pum pum
The newborn king said see the rum pum pum
or a Sell the barn ado
Yes we may
Hey?
I swear to give a f***
A rock-a-bum-bum
Yeah, I'll play for you
On my drum
I swear to give a f***
A rock-a-bum-bum
Yeah, I'll play for you
I swear to give a f***
both
lee
I
And
And amazing.
More from Corporal Blossom.
I am really impressed by their editing work.
And that's on Corporal Blossom and the Mutated Christmas is on the Illegal Art label.
That's www.detritus.net slash illegal art.
www.detritus.net slash illegal art.
And now more Jethro's.
Jethro.
And whose birth do we celebrate with this new century?
Who was nailed on that great manger cradle but Satan Claus?
Oh, my God.
whose father, Paul Bunyan, and whose mother, Big Sister, created the conspiracy.
Before there were malls, there was no such thing as Christmas.
Yes, there was a down-home Norman Rockwell-style, it's-a-wonderful-life type of Christmas.
It was a kite-flying, Coca-Cola-drinking Christmas, not a crack-smoking, rubber-snapping Christmas.
It was a-when your little brother broke through the hole, fell through a hole in the ice sling, and you went and saved him.
You didn't laugh at him and huff some more glue.
It was a wonderful life back then.
When Uncle Bud would come in with the candles, like most people have Christmas candles,
I mean, at birthday camp, why can't I just eat the little wieners all over again?
It was dangerous.
Strange lights appear in the skies all over the world.
The wife of a carpenter experiences virgin birth,
and a baby is born with a head that glows like a fluorescent lamp.
Dare I ask it?
Yes.
Was the infant Jesus neither man nor God, but merely one of the countless aliens that visit the earth each and every day?
The answer?
Yes, definitely.
Take that, and shove it up the tube, mark certainty, in the fuzzy place called the Twilight Zone.
Friends, try to imagine.
God and save...
Somewhere in the snowy north, the Santibob trudging mindlessly through the Himalayan snows,
driven by strange forces to complete his nameless errand,
and he may show up at your house, my friend, if you've been a bad subgenius,
or a halfway subgenius, or if we keep getting tangled up in these other shows and having strange microphones.
Oh, shit, this is a situation.
Down in the workshop, all the elves were making toys
For the good gentile girls and the good gentile boys
When the boss busted in, nearly scared them half to death
Had a rifle in his hands, and cheap whiskey on his breath
From his beard to his boots, he was covered with ammo
Like a big fat drunk disgruntled Yuletide Rambo
And he smiled as he said, with a twinkle in his eye
Merry Christmas to all, now you're all gonna die!
The night Santa went crazy
The night Saint Nick went insane
Realized he'd been getting the wrong deal
Something finally was still snapped in his brain
Well, the workshop is gone now, he decided to bomb it
Everywhere you'll find pieces of Cupid and Comet
And he tied up his helpers, and he held the elves hostage
And he ground up poor Rudolph into reindeer sausage
He got desert Francer with an old German Luger
And he slashed up Dasher just like Freddy Krueger
And he picked up a flamethrower, and he barbecued Linssen
And he took a big bite, and said it tastes just like chicken
The night Santa went crazy
The night Kris Kringle went nuts
Now you can hardly walk around the North Pole
Without stepping in reindeer guts
There's a National Guard and the FBI
There's a van from the Eyewitness News
And helicopters circling round in the sky
And the bullets are flying, the bodyguards rising
And everyone's dying to know who's Santa why
My, my, my, my, my, my
You used to be such a jolly guy
Yes, Virginia, now Santa's doing time
In a federal prison for his infamous crime
Hey little friend now, don't you cry no more tears
He'll be out with good behavior in 700 more years
But now make sense in therapy!
And Donna's still nervous
And the elf all got jobs working for the local service
And they say Mrs. Claus, she's on the phone every night
With her lawyer negotiating the movie rights they're talking about
The night Santa went crazy
The night Saint Nicholas slipped
Broke his back for some milk and cookies
Sounds to me like he was tired of getting shit, whoa-oh-oh
The night Santa went crazy
The night Saint Nick went insane
Realized he's been getting the wrong deal
Something finally must have snapped in his brain, whoa-oh-oh
Something finally must have snapped in his brain, tell ya
Something finally must have snapped
In his brain
You better watch out
You better not cry
You better not pout
I'm telling you why
Santa Claus is coming to town
He's making a list
He's checking it twice
He's going to find out who's naughty or nice
Santa Claus is coming to town
He knows when you're sleeping
He knows when you're awake
He knows when you've been found or good
So be good for goodness sake
You better watch out
You better not cry
You better not pout
I'm telling you why
Santa Claus is coming to town
Have yourself an advanced Dogmatic Christmas song thing called Santa is Coming by F. Gillespie and F. J. Jones.
And you can find it on the YouTube channel of the
Electric Elf at loop.com
Can tell you more about that
But now the greatest scary Christmas song ever friends from his new album
Don't Trust Whitey
James Kochalka Superstar
Jingle, jangle, jingle
We're on a sleigh ride to heck
Santa and his reindeer
Are really wicked
Wrapped in wrapping paper
We're gonna break our necks
Got a rocket in my pocket
On a sleigh ride to heck
Sleigh ride to heck
The elves are full of cheer
The kids are tucked in bed
Santa is coming
Santa ain't coming
We're on a sleigh ride to heck
Their dreams are filled with toys
But they're out of luck
Cause Satan's taking Santa
On a sleigh ride to fuck
Sleigh ride to heck
Sleigh ride to...
...heck
Sleigh ride to heck
It's almostlat teensing time
...heck
Sleigh ride to...
Again, I'm Tony rebellious, and as your host from the same channel,
I can't seem to accommodate all my loads 130bars,
the vocational part more disturbingly equal
now brown-enhanced
and there will be
light watching
Thank you.
Oh scary.
man, totally scary, scary
broke friend with his new nameless
album and nameless song
about, well I call it
Gary's X Day song
before that, Saint Anne
and Helena Handbasket with
Welcome to Hell from
their CD by the same name which you can get
from www.minitrue.org
www.minitrue.org
Minitrue has no E
in it, it's M-I-N-I
T-R-U dot org
The Sleigh Ride to Heck
of course was the great James Kochalka
from his new album
and that's also on
www.tryedgemusic.com
or
Indie World
with a Y
www.indieworld.com
slash Kochalka
with a bunch of K's
Oh and the Jethro's
friends, here's their address
2-1-2 and a half
Miller Avenue
this is the Jethro's
2-1-2 and a half
this is a strange number
2-12 and a half
Miller Avenue
New Hampshire
N-H that is
Portsmouth
0-3-8-0-1
and of course the subgenius
Post Office Box
1-4-0-3-0-6
Dallas, Texas
7-5-2-1-4
for free information
or my address is
Box
1-8-1-4-1-7
Cleveland Heights
Ohio
it's all at
www.subgenius.com
and at the very bitter end
after the rants
shall be
Reverend Mark Mothersbaugh
a silent night
oh thank you
Slim Sphincter
after all these friendly calls
I got one call from some
some
somebody who
who said
what are y'all
the usual thing
the usual question
what are y'all trying to do
and I go
we're trying to give you
some slack okay
you know
they go who's Bob
I said well
give me your address
I'll send you some information
or whatever you know
I'll give the number
at the end of the broadcast
and they
and this person
you know I knew
there was something
that they weren't saying
and finally
he goes
well
I just hope that
it was something like
you know
you can get right with Jesus
or something like that
and just hung up
he hung up
that was the key point
he said he didn't want to hear
what I had to say back
about that
because
you know see
a subgenius has so much faith
that he not only can accept
somebody making fun of Bob
stomping on a picture of Bob
he'll do it himself
he has so much trust
and faith in Bob
Bob is such a good friend
that he can insult Bob
now we subgeni
I hate to get on my soap
but I hate to get on my soap
Bob's in the middle
of a bunch of entertaining tapes
but we subgeni
may be bad
but our way of bad
is holy
compared to the evil
of so
not all
by any means
but so many
American fundamentalists
charismatics
evangelicals
etc.
in general
of course
they and their corresponding types
in Iran
Russia
Libya
South Africa
etc.
if you ask me
are actually the ace
up the devil's sleeve
wolves and animals
and sheep's clothing friends
just like Jesus warned about
we're
Jesus and Bob
like we say
our old drinking buddies
got nothing against Jesus
it's just his fan club
and now
we aren't saying that Bob
is the ace up God's sleeve
he's more like the smear
on God's handkerchief
just like you or me
but the uptight rival cults
they don't think God
has a handkerchief
uh uh no
cause God's perfect
he doesn't even sneeze
we're made in his image
except that
we have all these nasty parts
attached to us
and we have to go in the
the secret room
the bathroom
to do awful things
but God
oh he's clean and pure
according to them
oh and he's male
but he doesn't excrete juices
and sweat
and smelly stuff
out of him like we do
cause we sin
oh yeah
we all sin
we're bad
we're worthless
we're no good to God
unless we sign a contract
with his agent
well friend
Jesus himself
outed just about
as many great punchlines
as Bob
probably more
but and this is true
this is historical fact
the very early
mainstream Christian church
methodically censored
about half
of the existing gospels
about Jesus
and this is
I'm not kidding
you can go to
any real bookstore
and pick up
the censored gospels
that they finally
found years later
they took out the parts
where Jesus specifically said
that every person
had equal access
to the Lord
and that you didn't need
no preacher
between you and him
that in fact
was probably his main point
now lost in antiquity
that you
were the son
or daughter
of God
just as much as Jesus was
or Bob
see
but that's too humanistic
for the conspiracy Christians
so they
they wiped out
the subgenius
Gnostic Christians
anyway
I'm gonna get off
my soapbox
we'll get into the
hideous theological discussions
coming up next week
as we attack
the bobbies
we interrupt this program
for a special promotional announcement
we turn
hey Bob
and the bastards of the universe
will be back after this message
thank you
a new young people
listen to me today
quit playing games
with Christmas trees
Silent night
Holy night
All is calm
All is bright
Round yon virgin
Kinder and mild
Holy night
Mother
and child
Although they fixing out
on reception
Youay
Wong
Niners
or at least
a little bit today
I don't have any Christmas trees.
Quit playing games with Christmas trees.
Christmas trees.