Hey you! Get gone!
I need help, all the help I can get.
We cannot take your souls for minds or bodies.
How do you know? What do you mean? How do we know they're nuts?
And I wouldn't know it.
I'm going to call out some words.
And I want you to respond with the first word that comes to mind.
Window. Grass. Candy. Money. Desk. Mother. Steel. Paper. School. Park. Car. Nail. Tooth. Flower. Letter. Red. Friend.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Water.
Shit.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Toy.
Ass.
Truth.
Lie.
Toy.
Shit.
Home.
Fuck, fuck.
Worry.
Motherfucker.
Why do you suppose you use mother so much?
God damn.
The temptation was too great.
Fuck you.
And it exhibits itself in devious ways.
Motherfucker.
Do you understand?
Fuck you.
And, uh, and if you are in fact a motherfucker,
you've come to...
You've come to the right place.
And this might even be the church,
the religious church for you.
You notice that we're not in a cathedral,
and it's not Sunday morning,
and you're not wearing a necktie,
and you're not trying to hold in your farts.
At a subgenius church meeting,
you can go ahead and fart.
Bob doesn't care.
Bob does not care.
Because he's not here, and he won't smell your goddamn farts.
I am, but I'm up on stage,
and I won't smell them for a few more minutes yet.
I am up on stage.
The First Amendment gives you the right to choose what you hear,
what you say, and what you think.
Now, how much money do you think you're gonna make out of this?
Neil doesn't give a fuck.
Oh, I don't know.
I don't know.
Money, talk, and bullshit, walk.
No, I didn't say about that.
I don't give a fuck.
It's time to grow up and take some responsibility.
So what?
Why shouldn't they be offended?
Because they've done that they shouldn't be offended.
Uhhhhhh, what was that?
Who gives a fuck?
Funny, talk, and bullshit walk.
I don't give a fuck either.
Could you state that as a question, please?
Who gives a fuck?
But Bill doesn't give a fuck.
Funny, talk, and bullshit walk.
How do you feel about that?
Ha! I don't give a fuck.
I don't give a fuck.
I just give a fuck.
Censorship is never going to accomplish anything.
As long as there are a few four-letter words in the album,
it will always sell an extra million copies.
We want people to make up their own minds.
I don't give a fuck.
The first amendment gives you the right to choose what you hear, what you say, and what you think.
Funny, talk, and bullshit walk.
Please, state that as a question, please.
Have you been told?
Screw it.
No, I'm not.
I'm not going to say anything.
I don't give a fuck.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
That was Bill T. Miller, the king of slack.
.com, if you want to get more of that.
With I don't give a fuck.
Yes, baby.
And before that, we heard some stuff from Fernanda Ndelemer.
From Reverend Norrell Preff.
Reverend James Smurker, all the way over in Australica.
And yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang.
Yes, an X day is coming.
The end of the world is coming.
Who cares what the fuck happens?
Because I'm slacking off, dear friends.
This particular show, X-Rated Hour of Slack No. 7,
is strictly for the Internet.
And underground stations.
It's all the cussful and naughtyful material that piles up
at the labs here, built out of time control.
And then finally, every X day or so, erupts like an infected boy.
For us to live any other way was nuts.
Plus those goody good people who worked shitty jobs for bum paychecks
and took the subway to work every day, worried about their bills, were dead.
And they were suckers.
They had no...
No balls.
If we wanted something, we just took it.
If anyone complained twice, they got hit so bad, believe me, they never complained again.
It was just all routine and you didn't even think about it.
You can never hit a number.
Hey, sit out here.
Watch. Watch this, Jenny Lee.
Watch this. Look at this.
Great.
Will you say hello to our audience, Mr. Boomer?
Hello.
Now tell me, sir.
When did you first realize that you...
You were proficient enough to take a shot at the Empire Championship?
Well, ever since I was a little nipper, I liked to fart.
I remember I used to make my mother and father laugh their bleeding heads off
when I used to let one go in church during the announcement of the ladies' eighth.
Excuse me, Mr. Boomer.
On the radio, we call it crepitating.
Now look here, copper.
What I always says is a fart's a fart.
Whether you raise up on one cheek and sneak,
or whether you give it a full blast like I do.
Very well.
I personally find the four-letter word much easier to say
and more descriptive than the longer and more academic crepitating.
Thank you.
That brings us up to speed.
And, um...
Yeah.
Valfen, oh, Valfen, you're from the Vestiniskis.
Visit number to call.
And, uh, you know, I already kind of stated what it would take
for you to get in my good graces this week.
Very special, uh...
theme we're talking about this week.
As you may or may not know,
July 5th is coming up on us very quickly.
Very, very quickly indeed.
And July 5th is an important day on the calendar because...
Well, if the conspiracy hadn't been messing with our calendar for so long,
then, um, you know, July 5th would be for sure the day that Bob comes down
in the saucers.
But that could happen any day, really.
I mean, it could happen tomorrow.
The world ends tomorrow.
You may die.
But X-Day, my friends, X-Day.
It's the big day.
Um, for all you Bobbies out there, and that is coming up July 5th.
What is going on?
This is bullshit, Bob!
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bop...
Bop!
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
What is going on?
This is bullshit, Bob.
This adorable lullaby is another slow one for you lovers.
What the fuck am I supposed to be if I'm not supposed to be what I am?
What the fuck am I supposed to do if I'm not supposed to do what I do?
What the fuck am I supposed to say if I'm not supposed to say what I say?
What the fuck am I supposed to fuck if I'm not supposed to do what I say?
to fuck what I fuck
And the only booze on Sunday
is the blood of Christ
God damn the Christians
Thank you!
That is all!
That was Man Incorporated, dear friends
You can get a lot more of Man
at beerforman.com
That's beerforman.com
What you just heard was actually recorded live by us
at the Subgenius Devival in Cleveland
at the Beachland
Uh...
And before that
and also next
some Norrell Pref
of which you can get more
at heavyconfetti.com
And then we'll play some censored
Team America
from their soundtrack
Oh, yes
Motherfucking cocksucker
Motherfucking shit fucker
What am I doing?
I don't know what I'm doing
You rock!
You floss or masturbate
that could be the key to your entire reality
You see a lot of people in here
who claim they want to know the ultimate truth about reality
They want to peer under the surface of the big everything
But this can be a very painful process full of surprises
that can dismantle the world as you know it
That's why most people prefer to remain on the surface of things
Have you ever transcended space and time?
Beat it, you little pussy
pussy
Fuck it!
Nothing matters
How can I matter?
I don't know if nothing matters
Something that matters or something that matters.
I'm trying to figure that out and I want you to help me.
You use petroleum, you're a murderer. That's a fact.
Killing the ozone and all the creatures that it's hurting.
Killing Arabs and oil producing dictatorships.
Where everybody is poor.
That's cruelty.
Nothing's connected.
It doesn't matter what you do.
You can drive a car.
You can burn up gas.
Which would explain the way things actually are.
Where people do destructive things like it doesn't even matter.
This is the truth.
Okay?
Little girls like you, they have to work in dark factories.
Where they go blind for $1.60 a month.
Just to make money.
Is it possible for anybody in this world to work together to make it better?
I don't think so.
To see an image is always better.
You've got to reach people quick.
The situation was not created by nature like the drought or the olives or any of that.
It was created by people, and this is by facts.
It was created by people who act like nothing's happening.
And that's causing all the problems.
No, no, no.
Why?
Because people only ask themselves deep questions until something really bad happens.
How come people are self-destructive?
If the forms of this world die, which is more real?
The me that dies or the me that's in front?
Can I trust my habitual mind or do I need to learn to look beneath those things?
You say you're Christians living by Jesus' principles, but are you?
Yeah, of course we are.
Jesus is never mad at us if we live with him in our hearts.
I hate to break it to you, but he is.
He most definitely is.
If Hitler were alive, he'd tell you not to think about oil.
But how did Sudan happen, ma'am?
Could it possibly be related to dictatorships that we support for some stupid reason?
You shut up. You get out.
Shut up. You get out.
Looks like you saw some truth.
What'd you see?
Well, the interconnection thing is definitely for real.
It is! I didn't think it was!
I can't believe it. It's so fantastic!
I know.
But it's also nothing special.
Yeah, because it grows from the manure of human trouble.
You see, the detectives, they just wanted to gloss right over that.
But in fact, no manure, no magic.
Wake up, pretty girl!
The joke's on you!
The joke is on you!
Don't look at me like that!
Fuckabees!
Fred Lee.
She said fuckabees.
I'm just gonna accept my loneliness, and I'm gonna go to an even darker place of nothingness.
From an even farther, more extreme nothingness on my own.
But what's so great about depression?
Nothing.
How am I not myself?
I SAID GET AWAY FROM ME!
I'm completely lost!
I've hit rock bottom.
Easy, easy, whoa, you gotta calm down there, Chuck.
I hurt people.
I'm a dick.
Oh, being a dick ain't so bad.
See, there's three kinds of people.
Dicks, pussies, and assholes.
Pussies think everyone can get along, and dicks just wanna fuck all the time without thinking it through.
But then you got your assholes, Chuck.
And all the assholes want us to shit all over everything.
So pussies may get mad at dicks once in a while, because pussies get fucked by dicks.
But dicks also fuck assholes, Chuck.
And if they didn't fuck the assholes, you know what you'd get?
You'd get your dick and your pussy all covered in shit!
Alright, that does it. Get out of here, you drunk lowlife!
You gave up on life, didn't you?
I'm not a dick.
I'm a dick.
Space, the final frontier.
Specimen gathering mission on planet Alpha 177.
Mr. Spock is much stronger than the ordinary human being.
Aroused, his great physical strength could kill.
But it's a risk I'll have to take.
Something bother you, Mr. Spock?
May I say that I have not thoroughly enjoyed serving with humans.
I find their illogic and foolish emotions a constant irritant.
Unlike you, we humans are full of unpredictable emotions.
Love. Tenderness.
Yes, yes.
If I seem insensitive to what you're going through, Captain,
understand, it's the way I am.
Don't be afraid.
Here's my hand.
Hold on.
You are beautiful.
More beautiful than any dream of beauty I've ever known.
What is your point, Mr. Spock?
I love you.
I can love you.
Kiss me.
You're out of your mind.
The prospect appeared quite attractive to you a moment ago.
You don't really want to hurt me, do you?
Put that thing away.
No, I don't think so.
No!
I can't.
It's painless and quick.
Aaaaaah!
Entry made by Second Officer Spock.
Possible we may have hit the wrong entry point.
Yes.
Very well, Captain.
Try again.
If it pleases you.
What are you waiting for?
Hurry!
If you'll excuse the intrusion, Captain.
Aaaaaah!
Bury the hatchet.
An appropriate choice of terms, Captain.
Aaaaaah!
Shhh!
I'm not going to let you get away with this.
Keep your fuckin' hands off.
Just keep away, you green-blooded half-breed!
Scotty, no!
Wait!
Are you all right, Captain?
It's all right.
I'm just a little busy.
I have to take him back.
I can't survive without him.
I don't want to take him back.
He's like an animal.
A thoughtless, brutal animal.
Here, let me give you a hand.
This thing can go anywhere!
You've not yet explained the nature of this thing.
She's a projectile at one-nine.
Get below.
I'm going to get you.
Take command.
Ice out.
Your beauty!
I won't fight you anymore.
I feel so weak.
I'll be glad when this is over.
This is impossible.
I'm a Vulcan.
What can you expect from a simpering devil-eared freak?
His father was a computer and his mother an encyclopedia.
You can't beat the game.
I'm behaving disgracefully.
I had eaten animal flesh and I've enjoyed it.
Believe me, Mr. Spock.
It was painful in more ways than one.
I thought...
Captain's log, supplement.
I've seen a part of myself no man should ever see.
I don't know why I have not been infected.
Thank you, Mr. Spock.
From both of us.
Everybody's fucking.
So many people fucking.
I bet they're glad that I'm not.
But I'm not.
Glad that I'm not.
Fucking.
Everybody's fucking.
So many people fucking.
I bet they're glad that I'm not.
But I'm not.
Glad that I'm not.
Fucking.
Oh, shit.
Little Theodore and Babushka.
At 7X Day, friends at Brushwood.
Recorded last X Day.
We've got 8X Day coming up.
You can contact Little Theodore at
littletheodoreatyahoo.com
That name is spelled F-Y-O-D.
B-O-R.
Little Theodore at yahoo.com.
And now, Nowrel.
The past is a foreign country.
They do things differently there.
Go to your pleasure of the bad fountain of life, honey.
Go to your pleasure of the bad fountain of life, honey, bad flower.
The giving and the receiving of bad pleasure.
Ecstasy.
Bad pleasure.
A longing for money, fame, and influence.
Love.
Theory.
And even harder to maintain.
The story of our quest for sexual love.
And we may fail.
Call me at the rear of...
Are you so sure?
But how about up and down?
Call me at the rear of...
Not exactly.
Alice was beginning to get very, very sleepy and stupid.
Curiouser and curiouser.
Oh dear, what nonsense I'm talking.
Digging everything.
Because the only people for me are the mad ones.
Desirous of everything at the same time.
Come on, man.
Those girls won't wait. Make it fast.
Flunky.
Nauseating.
Ascent and smoke and sweat, greed and fear.
Fear and nervous tension.
James Bond suddenly knew that he was...
Flunky.
Ironical, brutal, and cold.
Bond was not amused.
The prospect of working with her stimulated him.
At the same time, he felt a disquiet.
On an impulse, he touched wood.
Good news.
DJ Good News.
DJ Good News!
DJ Good News, you see?
Yeah, it's...
Flunky.
Amazing!
I've never met anyone like Good News.
Flunky.
Good News is...
It can be hard to figure out what has meaning and what doesn't.
Say, will you be washed in Jesus' cup?
Will you be ready?
When Jesus comes, one shall come.
America again.
To save the motherfucking day.
Yeah, America.
America again.
Freedom is the only way to erase your game, Mr.
Now you have to answer to...
America again.
America
Fuck yeah
Coming again to save the motherfucking day
America
Fuck yeah
Freedom is the only way
Terrorists your game is through
Cause now you have to answer to
America
Fuck yeah
So lick my butt and suck on my balls
America
Fuck yeah
What you gonna do when we come for you now
It's the dream that we all share
It's the hope for tomorrow
Fuck yeah
We got us
Walmart
Fuck yeah
The Gap
Baseball
Fuck yeah
NFL
Rock and roll
Fuck yeah
The internet
Slavery
Fuck yeah
Starbucks
Disney World
Fuck yeah
Porno
Valium
Fuck yeah
Reebok
Fake tits
Fuck yeah
Sushi
Taco Bell
Fuck yeah
Rodeos
Black Bath and Beyond
Fuck yeah
Liberty
Whiteslip
Fuck yeah
The Alamo
Band-Aids
Fuck yeah
Las Vegas
Christmas
Fuck yeah
Immigrants
Popeye
Fuck yeah
Democrat
The Barbicans
Fuck yeah
Spongebob
Books
Spider-Man
Tim America
Dear friends
Great Troy Parker
I guess wrote that
And now
This psychedelic band
From Michigan
Which we saw
At the Detroit Revival
They do an incredible
Video and live show
The L.S. Dudes
And now
We're going to
So, it begins.
Are you ready?
Take out the jams, motherfuckers!
Getting away with murder.
Thanks, drugs.
Pissing on America, fucking up the music.
Get it done.
Look at this shit music.
Those goddamn nigga-loving hippies, they even fucked up the music.
Get it done.
I mean, what is that like in extra meditation, you know, when you're in a trance and there's peach pits pushing their way slowly out your asshole?
It's really not that much of a problem.
Sometimes, if you're not really...
It seems like they give you real weird visions.
If you're not maintaining a high dissipation level, well then...
What?
Dissipation level.
That's where you dissipate all thoughts, doing extra meditation.
If you're not maintaining that high level, well then they'll come out just ripping your asshole open.
Otherwise, they're just no problem at all.
Well, how exactly do you mount that special head like it says in that little book?
Mount the head?
Uh-huh.
It says that in that little book.
You just put a nail in the wall and hang it up?
Yeah.
You know, it's no problem.
I thought it...
Or you can get you a picture hanger, something like that.
I thought it meant I was supposed to jack off every time I went to the bathroom.
Well, that too.
Jack off and also...
No, I didn't mean that.
Oh, okay.
Your unworthy servant has the power to confront this cruel demon.
Ah!
Hi, anything I can do for you?
I want my pills.
Know anything about pills?
Yes.
Pills, please.
Pills?
My pills.
My what?
Pills.
Oh, uh, my pills.
I come looking for my pills.
Bad, bad pills.
Here you are.
Thank you.
For the truth is that Team America fights for the billion dollar corporation.
They are just as bad.
Enemies they fight.
Oh, no, we aren't.
We're dicks.
We're reckless, arrogant, stupid dicks.
And the Film Actors Guild are pussies.
And Kim Jong-il...
What?
Is an asshole.
Pussies don't like dicks.
Because pussies get fucked by dicks.
But dicks also fuck assholes.
Assholes who just want to shit on everything.
Pussies may think they can deal with assholes their way.
But the only thing that can fuck an asshole is a dick with some balls.
The problem with dicks...
Is that they're not just a dick.
Is that sometimes they fuck too much.
Or fuck when it isn't appropriate.
Yes, Gary.
Yes.
And it takes a pussy to show them that.
But sometimes pussies get so full of shit that they become assholes themselves.
Because pussies are only an inch and a half away from assholes.
I don't know much in this crazy, crazy world.
But I do know...
That if you don't let us fuck this asshole...
We are gonna have our dicks and our pussies...
All covered in shit.
Lisa, I'm crazy about you.
Will you please forgive me if I can...
Shh.
You had me at dicks fuck assholes.
Attention.
Attention, everyone.
All you in the audience should go to your homes now.
Your countries need you.
But the world will be safe thanks to a brilliant actor named Gary Johnston.
Let me explain to you the kind of man Gary is.
He's a man who knows that when you put another man's cock in your mouth, you make a pact.
And that is the kind of man that Gary is.
A bond that cannot be broken
He's a man so dedicated
That he will get down on his knees
And put that cock right in his mouth
Well then let's go show the bad guys
The police are back in force
Fuck yeah
America
Freedom is in free
No there's a hefty fucking thing
And if you don't throw in your buckle five
Who will
Who will buckle fast
Freedom costs a buckle fast
Only a woman
Can brighten up my day
Can touch me the right way
Only a woman
Is allowed to touch me then
All I ask is that you're a woman
You gotta watch out  my Steel
Iuv Jim
You should knock my Man
You got it
tremble
you
It's broke
It's hurt
But it's enough
for a thot
Right
Come right here
just do it
causes some shit
ncia
Due to a congenital birth defect which caused me to be born with double anus vaginas,
I am a charter member of the Double Vaginal Double Anal Society.
I want to join.
There's a $14.95 registration fee.
It goes entirely toward funding the gentle stroking of my anus.
A message from Reverend Error.
And before that, the toilet song by Reverend Ed Fred.
And Team America before that.
And now, Norell.
Thank you all for coming.
I even take the position that sexual orgies eliminate social tensions and ought to be encouraged.
I've had this before.
Let's do a quick reality check.
Let's make love.
Great to be with you.
My opponent uses rumor and innuendo.
I use rumor and innuendo.
And of course.
Some very personal items.
When it goes through your fingers, you get to...
It's sticky.
It sticks to the fingers.
A plague descended upon the world.
It depends on what your definition of the word is is.
It really depends on your definition of the word.
Cruising toward an iceberg.
That's a very interesting point.
That will take.
The president believes it too.
Voodoo economics.
Heavily, heavily monitored by the government.
Thank you all for coming.
Don't go away.
How much would you cough up?
On Marilyn Monroe.
In 2001.
Cock 2042 BC.
But what is indisputably true, it seems to me, is that...
I gotta go back and have First Lady Laura Bush.
And I can't wait.
Cock Bush.
Bush.
Cock.
Great to be with you.
Cock 2018.
Great to be with you, Keith.
Closing social security.
Thank you all for coming.
Again, great thanks for coming in.
Thank you, Keith.
Great talk.
Today our topic is cock.
And why a person would want to sell cock.
Cock is probably...
Cock is making some changes.
Strong.
Passion.
So, I will stress, it's going to break down.
It's not going to work when you need it to.
We can't underestimate cock's strength.
I like cock.
From PR News in Washington, I'm doing a poor job of human trafficking.
Meanwhile, ask us.
Ask us.
In stocks to 1046161.
PR's bad.
PR's guess.
Ask.
Some analysts say...
The State Department has added more cunts to its list of governments that it says are
combating PR News in Washington.
You're still too far back.
What is...
Are you afraid?
That's sad.
Blow things up!
Kick out the jams, motherfucker!
Two more days!
I'm in!
Turn on!
Jack off!
Masturbate constantly!
If you don't touch yourself, Bob sure as fuck won't!
Why not live orgasmically?
Fuck all the time!
Why are there girls here that are not kissing guys?
I want to rock and roll all night!
And fight the cops!
And run every day!
Turn on your friends!
Turn off the TV!
The cop wants you to know more about the cast of Friends than you do about your own fucking
neighbors!
What the fuck!
Fuck crime thinking.
Try just plain thinking for once.
Steal a book and read it.
Take a piss in public.
Take a walk.
Write a song.
Make a baby.
Ride a skateboard.
Rip a heart.
Kiss your lover.
Laugh about it.
Daydream!
Just don't give in!
Don't fucking give in!
It is not an alternative.
Don't give in.
Death is mediocrity and mediocrity is fucking boring.
Oh, oh, but Wally, why should you tell us what to do?
Who are you to say how we should live?
Wally, why should you tell us what to do?
Now you're fucking thinking!
Do it every day!
Apply it to your everyday life!
Must see TV!
The real world will seem way more fucking evil that way.
Do it.
So yeah, fuck me!
Doubt me!
Question me!
Fuck me!
I'm an asshole!
I don't know what I'm talking about.
Think!
Fuck me!
Fuck me, please!
Ladies?
No!
But most of all, fuck Bob Dobbs.
Fuck him.
Fuck the pipe out of his mouth.
Grab that gritting face by the ears and shove it in your crotch.
Fuck Bob Dobbs.
Fuck him!
Or kill me!
Who the hell is this guy?
A Pope Wally, dear friends.
Pope Wally.
A Pope Wally.
At the 2005 Detroit Revival.
I hope to see Pope Wally at 8X Day.
But now, Onan Canobite, Uncle Dr. Onan Canobite, on the road.
Earth is the fourth planet from the sun.
This planet is Mars.
And it has been since 1953.
Well, maybe 1957.
Or maybe 1953.
It was during that time that the former Earth, which was the third planet from the sun, switched
places with the fourth planet from the sun, which had been Mars.
This planet is Mars.
That planet is Earth.
And that planet, the fourth planet from the sun, is the planet the X's landed on.
The fourth planet is Earth.
It sounds outlandish. What evidence do you have for that, Uncle Ronan?
Some of you are faxing that in even now.
Well, I'll tell you.
Have you ever felt a little alienated?
Well, how can you be an alien on your home planet?
The fact that you don't fit in proves that this is Mars.
The fact that all those science fiction movies you grew up with don't agree about what the aliens are like proves this is Mars.
Some of them, and the way that you feel about them, supplements that proof.
Some of the movies show Mars as a planet of destruction.
A planet of war, one might say.
And they come...
Some of them come to destroy this planet.
Others show them as saviors.
How could those both be?
They contradict.
But in fact, if you make this planet Mars and that planet Earth, they all agree.
They fall into place like a zipper.
The zipper you pull down as you expose yourself to dobs and join the church of the subgenius.
The church of the subgenius is like...
Having a pet you can fuck.
Bob would never touch a bible.
He would burn his hand and he needs that to run the adding machine, jack off the rubes,
pull cards from the bottom of the deck when dealing with other dimensional demons, diddle
the giggly girls, yank people's chains, pull stang's string again, and hand out the slack.
This ongoing polemic is a panoply of puckers.
However, I still enjoy it.
Here, have another canap and a glass of nectar.
You have real promise.
Why, add a little astroglide and you could become an actual doctor.
Princess Wee and I were talking about the Jewish tradition of the Sabbath.
You know, starting Friday afternoon.
Those guys, if they're orthodox, they can't even lift a finger to get more slack almost.
They have to pay a non-Jew to do it for them.
And it's for...
And they're real serious about it.
And for an entire day there, up until Saturday night, it's enforced slack.
You can't work.
In fact, if you picked up a stick and threw it in the fire, you could be stoned to death
according to the true righteous law of Jehovah One, which so many have forgotten.
But we're not here to preach a fundamentalist Judaism.
But their Sabbath idea was great.
But it's limited.
Why must we...
Can't we learn from their mistakes?
They did it for one day a week.
Why can't we do it seven days a week?
The endless Sabbath.
Like getting off...
Well, I'll tell you why.
Because the conspiracy will take your house away and throw you in debtor's prison.
And it's just not fair.
So that's why we have to pray and wait for aliens, I guess.
God damn it.
I don't know where that was from, friends.
Maybe Detroit.
But before that, Help-O-Q-E.
And now, and 80s, it's a genius classic by Doctors for Bob.
And this one's like 14 minutes long, friends.
But bear with it.
Doctors for Bob, recorded in Little Rock, Arkansas in the 80s.
And this one's called...
Huh!
The Pretty Song.
Yeah.
That's right.
Play it.
Play it just right, because I got a tale to tell.
This is a story about...
What?
Huh!
Being the primal sound of that which has been called the squirting universe.
Oh, there's people who'll try to deny it.
There's people who'll try to tell you the primal sound of the universe is oh, or amen,
or some kind of crap like that.
But these are all life is a bowl of cherries.
Sweetness and light, love burgers.
They know not the glories of the squirting universe.
For the primal sound of the boring, laid-back meditation universe might indeed be old.
But the primal sound of the bobble-thumping, black-eyed peen.
Back to the old stuff.
Squirting universe is huh!
For they know not the glories of that which has been called the squirting universe.
For you must ask yourself, my friends, are you still living in the testicles?
Or have you crossed over that mighty river Jordan?
Are you squirting out the head yet?
Huh!
For the purpose of life is not happiness, peace, or happiness.
Or even truth.
But the purpose of the universe is to squirt.
For 50% of the universe that is.
For slightly over 50%, the purpose of the universe is to ooze.
But the story of huh!
Is an all-encompassing tale.
Which tells of the,
the utter tragedy of the universe.
The transformation of the universe in the final days.
As was written in,
Huh!
Ecclesians 5, 17.
For in the end times there shall be the one world religion predicted in the Bible.
And that shall be called the church of the subgenius.
And there shall be a band.
A band which shall,
which will,
was,
and shall be known as the Doctors for Bob.
And lo!
Huh!
Doctors for Bob was the very hand, the very tool of God.
So to speak.
And that which was called the squirt universe.
Huh!
For the true purpose of Doctors for Bob.
Which could finally be revealed at last.
Is to squirt.
To speak.
Every word.
To sing every song.
To make every sound.
Every noise.
Melodic or un-melodic.
Possible in all infinite variations of the universe.
We're not bound by any laws of quality or good.
Our songs don't have to be good.
Because it is our duty.
To write every song that is left.
To utter every syllable.
So that every name of God shall be uttered.
So that the universe might end.
Yes friends we are here to see that the universe ends for the proper reasons.
For in 1998.
Slightly before the arrival of the universe.
The arrival of the exes.
Our mission will have been fulfilled.
We shall be.
We shall have uttered.
Every syllable.
Spoken every possible name of God.
Or Jehovah One.
Or Ram.
Or Allah.
Whichever name of God you call him.
It shall be at Doc Stock 17.
The Doc Stock 17.
The Doctors for Bob.
Shall be.
Performing.
What people little suspect.
Is their last performance.
And at the exact precise correct moment.
Snavely echoing.
The mighty, mighty saxophone player for Doctors for Bob.
Shall hit a wrong note.
Which low.
Who, who, who.
Lo and behold shall be.
In fact in actuality the right note.
And as he hits that note.
wrong note it will be a note so wrong that the entire universe shall start to
crumble all energy of all universes of all dimensions of all time frames of all
realities shall be channeled through the chief amplifiers of Dr. Survive yes the
universe shall be destroyed by amplification equipment bought on credit
at Boyd's Music Center yay lo and behold
and as all energy of all known universes begins to be channeled through their
amplifiers a new and heretofore unknown force shall be created a force which shall be known as anti-sound
and you thought anti-music was sound
you thought anti-music was sound
The cause of the world's statewide
sound is so that you'll have some type of reference point. But anti-sound has nothing
to do with sound. These waves, these rays, these forces of anti-sound shall vibrate,
or anti-vibrate, I might say, through the entire universe. And the entire universe will
lose its form. It shall be destroyed. Every molecule shall be demagnetized from every
other molecule. Every electron demagnetized from every other electron. Every proton demagnetized
from every other proton. Every atom shall be repelled from every other atom. The universe
shall lose its form as we know it today. Born to lose, and now I'm losing universal form.
Hypercletes shall quip.
Breaking off one last one-liner before the universe loses its form. But lo and behold,
nothing is ever destroyed, for the universe is eternal. Thus, matter cannot be created
or destroyed. It is only and merely transformed. And it shall be low transformed in the following
manner.
As all matter in the universe shall be magnetized to one particular point in the universe.
And all matter in the universe shall come together to form one gigantic universe. And
all of the elier things
and legislations ...
Melan gradient, and the
Will appear according to the laws of the universe in duvant baseline by means of two quadrangle
funz nouveats universe.
Preum ...
at the other diametrically opposite end of the universe.
And then, specially trained heliopters
shall transport the giant white penis
ever closer and closer to the giant black vagina.
And in a billion million eons,
depending on how hard to get the giant black vagina plays it,
the universe shall achieve penetration.
It shall be the ultimate meeting of the yin-yang.
It shall be a meeting of all offices of the universe.
Quiet shall meet black.
Matter shall meet energy.
Male shall meet female.
And it will all transpire into the giant fuck.
The giant fuck of which every stroke will take ten billion eons.
And we shall all be there, friends.
We shall all participate in the glorious, the mighty giant fuck.
Praise Bob.
Hell, I'm not going to participate if Smith's in on it, Jones.
Quips.
I ain't no queer.
Forget Jones and Smith.
Every stroke shall take ten billion eons.
This will be the ultimate pleasure.
For ten billion eons,
we will totally, with complete consciousness,
feel the power,
blow the mighty power of the giant fuck.
Deeper and deeper shall penetrate.
Harder and longer the giant white dick will become.
Wetter and hotter the giant black vagina will become.
Wider and wider it will open.
Tighter and tighter it shall squeeze.
In and out, in and out.
For ten billion times longer than this universe has even existed,
shall the giant squirt go on.
The giant fuck shall go on.
Excuse me.
And then,
At the end of this longest time period which has ever been,
there shall occur,
the squirt.
The giant squirt.
I'm not just talking about any squirt.
I'm talking about the squirt you dreamed about.
I'm talking about the squirt you always wanted to have,
but were too inhibited to have.
This will be the no holes barn.
The three billion naked girls at once squirt.
Or the three billion naked men at once squirt if you're female.
Or the ooze.
The ooze if you're female.
And lo and behold,
and hoo, the hoo sound,
shall reign across the universe.
But this is not the end for the giant squirt.
The giant squirt shall impregnate the giant vagina and uterus.
And shall give birth, lo, and behold,
to a new universe.
A perfect universe, friends.
A universe of peace, harmony, and slack.
In which transcendental love shall reign over all.
And you will be able to get a seat on the subway.
And minimum wage will be enough
so that every man, woman, and child will be able to live as millionaires.
And you won't,
kids won't throw chewing gum on the sidewalk
to where you can step on it
and get it on the bottom of your shoe.
And this is the prophecy, friends.
The prophecy.
The final prophecy.
As hinted about
and told the judge.
But here described in its more true fashion.
The slack universe.
If you'd like to see this happen,
if you'd like to see peace and harmony reign forever,
all you need to do,
get your money into Doctors for Bob
or the Church of the Sub-Genius.
Come to Doctors for Bob concerts,
buy Doctors for Bob records, tapes,
t-shirts, buttons,
paraphernalia.
You will be saved.
The universe shall live in perfect slack,
perfect harmony.
This is the plan.
This is the mighty master plan.
Predicted by the prophets for billions of years.
It approaches, friends, it approaches in 1998.
Help me, somebody.
Help us see this vision through.
Hoo!
I can hear it coming.
I can hear what it means,
O-o-o-o-o...
I can hear what it means...
You must due XX times.
Doctors for Bob, friends, Little Rock, Arkansas in the 80s,
and you're listening to the Hour of Slack 7th X-Rated 8X Day Show.
For more information about the Church of the Subgenius
and anything we've been playing on the show,
check out subgenius.com.
And we'll let Artemia Salina take us away now.
Thank you.