The
Bob show. And here he is.
Ja, ja, ga, Bob.
Bob. Oh, Bob.
Please, Bob. Listen, Bob.
I think they mean ja, ja,
ga, Bob. I said ja, ja, ga, Bob.
Uh, it says ja, ja,
ga, Bob. Oh, now there's a dish
to capture the imagination.
It's some kind
of forecaster, and it shows
the future of anyone the operator thinks about.
Well, darling, that's
witchcraft. No, it isn't.
It's some kind of
forecaster, and it shows the
future of anyone the operator thinks about.
There are ancient powers
gathering in this place.
Powers beyond the comprehension of unbelievers.
See?
That was nothing.
But that's how it always begins.
Very small.
Pray for these people.
We all need to love and pray for these people
as they continue to spread
life through the community.
They have passed out,
containing many lives,
and attacking the church and Christians.
They are şithere thought feelings as well.
From each guide,
there's a달â stra對啊
and other thoughts about their own life.
anauvan craio stri,
anam iran,
ned bsgêl e bilug,
ts bizêdz parna,
y fragâniw râ siê Çâdoрачiêr
What's the name of the woman,
who has almost become sl 따 in her heart?
It's the modern age.
È l'età moderna.
Excuse me a second.
Hello.
The electronics department, please.
Hey, how you doing?
You're a sound effects man, always fooling around with electronic devices.
Fooling around with electronic devices.
Tell me, do you suppose robots would enjoy listening to music?
Oh, all right.
It's the modern age.
Elevator, yeah.
Elevator, elevator, go down.
It's a one way.
Anything new?
Not quite.
Nothing new.
Your telephone is out of order.
Pachy, pachy, pachy, pachy, pachy, pachy.
You're remote.
Within a month, lo and behold, a miracle had occurred.
Within a month, within a month.
The sky is low.
The ground is flat.
The sky is high.
They meet together in the sky.
Dirt in the clouds, clouds in the ground.
Pork in the store sold by the pound.
I lie awake at night.
And poke my finger in my eye.
Your telephone is out of order.
The sky is low.
The ground is high.
They meet together in the sky.
Dirt in the clouds, clouds in the ground.
Pork in the store sold by the pound.
What do real estate agents do?
Have you found the men's phone?
Come.
To them they're alone
Within a month, lo and behold, a miracle had occurred.
Shining new hair had started to grow on his patchy bald areas.
And his itching and scratching decreased significantly.
Within a month, within a month.
The sky is low, the ground is high.
They meet together in the sky.
Like dirt in the clouds, clouds in the ground.
Pork in the store, soy by the pound.
They pretend they're selling houses.
Closing the deals on cellular farms.
The
silver
apart
a
tire
It broke
apart
și
and
so
You know about the, uh, suppressed transmission, of course.
This is a songbook.
Just think.
All we have to do is read the words in the book,
learn the music,
and then sing the songs.
Oh, impossible.
I have never sung a song before.
No way.
It's weird, huh?
We can do anything once we set our minds to it.
Whatever you say.
I'll count to three.
And then we'll start playing them.
One, two, three.
Oh, was that music?
I don't think so.
Let's try again.
I don't think that's the way it's supposed to sound.
From PR News in Washington, I'm still denouncing PR.
Stang has died.
Stang says he died of pneumonia over the weekend in the jungles of southern Massachusetts.
Stang says he was kidnapped from his home late yesterday.
Stang was also the voice of PR News.
Well, it turns out it was too good to be true.
Yes, it was a little too good to be true, my friends.
But don't fret.
I'm sure there's an answer.
Somewhere.
And that answer lies within.
And boy, does it lie.
And lies and lies and lies.
And what we just heard.
The PR News, of course, was by the great Fernandes Lee Murr.
And before, he also did the case of the missing sense.
And the very first cuts at the beginning of this show.
Which is hour of slack number 1,239.
Live, in this case.
On 1-10-10.
Before Fernandes and Andy Stang.
We're actually this whole show.
We're playing music by our friends tonight.
And now that we're back.
Our previous friends there.
That mixed up music.
That.
Ended with the phrase.
Was that music?
Is from Rural War Room's latest CD.
Called The Flaming Yawn.
We'll be.
We outplayed some other Rural War Room earlier.
That was the one called It's the Modern Age.
It may be hard for you to tell some of these pieces apart.
Before Rural War Room, we had a little.
A short, simple march.
Called March of the E-Class Workers.
From Gadgeto's new CD.
Called Crystal Radio.
I think that's the name of it.
He's from Gadgeto.com.
Gadgeto is spelled G-A-D-G-E-T-T-O.
Gadgeto.
Rural War Room is at RuralWarRoom.com.
But we also heard something from what you might call.
Mark Hosler's solo album.
Negative Land presents Thick Mo Tackle.
Thick Mo Tactic.
Thick Mo Tactic is mostly Mark Hosler.
With a couple of other friends.
He did that song song.
With Lofty Music.
Called Pork in the Store.
From the Thick Mo Tactic album.
From Negative Land.com.
Negative Land, by the way, does not have an E in negative.
In case you ever wondered about that.
Only at the beginning, not at the end.
That's right.
And we had Reverend Sweetness McGee.
Gave us a little collage there.
As did Gadgeto with Pray for These People.
And we have a new collage, yes.
Called Local Color.
We got a couple of EPs from this person.
Don Music of Local Color.
He did the.
Well, we'll hear more of that in upcoming shows.
But you can find Local Color at.
This is a nice website URL.
Brainpanlitterbox.com.
This music in the background, by the way, is also rural war room.
And will probably be followed by some more music from Thick Mo Tactic.
Which is Reverend Mark Hosler of Negative Land.
And I think that covers it.
Lee Murr.
Gadgeto.
Sweetness McGee.
Rural War Room.
Mark Hosler.
And, yes.
I think that's it.
That's it?
That's the whole gang.
And Princess We is here.
The beautiful Princess We.
In fact, she's always here.
From now on.
Hi there.
She's never going to have to leave.
She can do anything she wants from now on.
Because.
Friends.
Princess We.
Our doe.
Queen of all the UFOs.
Retired.
She quit.
She repented.
Quit her job.
Of 30 years.
And slapped off.
Actually, it was one week shy of 30 years.
But they gave her three years for free.
Just for being her.
And when I'm not giddy.
I just have to wipe this silly grin off my face.
That just creeps up out of nowhere.
Wonderful.
So, friends.
It's.
We don't know what it's going to be like.
I mean.
For her, of course.
It's great.
And for me it will be great.
But.
I've been wondering about my career.
Because it's like.
If Princess We is home.
That means it's Saturday.
Well, if she's always home, that means it's the eternal Saturday.
And indeed.
We haven't been in the station here.
Because we've been on the eternal vacation.
We left.
For Stang Ranch in Stang County, Texas.
So, I just wanted to say thank you.
just before Existlessnessmas
and had an Existlessness vacation.
Flew from oddly warm Ohio to Texas
where it was 73 degrees the first day
and then it was a blizzard the next day.
Yes, friends, strange, strange weather.
You aren't supposed to have to shovel snow in North Texas.
Certainly not in Stang County
where there's always supposed to be a drought
according to the ancient Indian curse.
But instead we had snowstorms twice
while in sunny Texas.
Very, very strange.
Very strange.
Some might call these signs of the end times.
And we came home
and then we shoveled our driveway
and then we filled orders.
And all of those things took three days.
And we had to take pills
to...
to ease our pain from the...
But just regular pills,
not the kind...
not Bob's kind...
not them kind pills, Bob.
Not them kind pills, Bob.
Matter over mind.
That's what it is, friends.
If you take them kind pills,
it's...
you change the way your mind is working
by swallowing some matter.
In this case, ibuprofen, I think.
Probably would cut it.
Aspirin. Yes, aspirin.
Yeah, we've...
I guess...
And once we get this hour of slack done,
then I can answer my email
from the last three weeks.
See, we got our priorities right.
Joy!
We fill the orders
and send people their ordainments
or their books
or whatever they needed
that they ordered three weeks ago.
Those are all on the way.
It's in the mail.
It's in the mail, just like Bob said.
Oh, and we have other news.
Let's see.
Subgenius Devival coming up at Winterstar,
which is February 14th weekend, right?
That's right.
Valentine's Day weekend.
The only way to know about
the Winterstar Symposium
is to go to
roseandcomet.com
That's not Rose-in,
but roseandcomet.com
or just Google
Winterstar Symposium, I suppose.
Or Starwood Festival,
and you can get there that way, too.
That's right.
We're still trying to figure out
where Starwood's going to be.
In fact,
they're probably
hammering that out
right as we speak.
That is true.
This very, very moment.
Yeah, at this moment,
they're probably deciding
which of several places
to hold Starwood at,
but that will be for the first time.
That'll be the week after X-Day,
and X-Day is the week of July 5th.
Actually, X-Day ends July 5th.
It starts, and the world ends July 5th
at 7 in the morning.
It's that simple.
Indeed.
So I don't know why we're worried about Starwood,
but X-Day will be at the same old, same place
as always,
and you can look that up at subgenius.com,
although I think I have to get
the numbers going.
I see a little, I mean the web page.
I have to fix that web page.
I see a blinking square light.
What have I got here?
Is it the blinking of day?
Is it Dave?
The steamroller bowling bag was, wasn't it?
It was the psychic bowling bag.
Or the steamroller, either one.
Those are the ones I remember.
Okay, sure.
Back when I lived in Onion Town,
right next to Dobstown.
Little Hamlet, not too far.
Beautiful place.
That's that Cipriano onion, right?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, they made them,
they double caramelized them
and whipped them up on the children.
Mm-mm.
Onion.
Children.
The bulb of Dobstown.
A little bulb hanging off.
You peel one layer away
and you still peel it.
Mm-mm.
Skin it back, friends.
That's for those of you with a five-kid.
Hold on to it while we run water through it.
That's what Bob said.
Bob's brain is like a sieve.
It holds only the spaghetti that it needs to hold.
Or whatever material.
Well, you pour, it's like a computer.
It's a box that you pry open.
And pour money into every month or so.
And everything else passes out,
but it holds the money.
It retains.
The Dob's brain retains the money.
In other ways, it's quite retarded.
Quite slow to pick up the beat.
The brain holds on to very few things
that don't have to do with finance
or the buskick artifacts.
So take care of your brain, friends.
Or it'll take care of you.
Take care of your brain's friends.
Those are all the other organs
that are contiguous with it.
If you don't take care of your brain,
someone else will take care of your brain for you.
Your mouth is directly connected to the brain,
so you have to brush your teeth,
shove that toothbrush way back in there,
and you can get the root of the brain.
The nose is a direct pathway to the brain.
And be careful when you're cleaning that out.
If you grab any of those long hairs
and pull too hard for too long,
you can uproot.
Again, you're uprooting part of the brain
because a long, slimy string
still connected to the brain,
as the swinging love corpse has described,
the booger.
And while you're there visiting the booger brain,
stop off at the Pineal Sands Rest Home and Vista Resort.
It's a beautiful place to take a look at what's happened
and what's going on.
What's going to happen in your head?
I'm afraid that's the only place it's going to happen.
Right.
In our minds.
In our mind's eye.
We're going to see all kinds of things.
We're going to see Big Sister get fatter,
with a P spelled P-H-A-T-T-E-R,
you know, like she's passing some meat, fatter.
And we're going to see everybody else on the land
become much leaner and more full of beans.
But that's the way of El Mondo, or El Mundo.
El Mondo, El Mundo.
The music we just heard there was Mark Osler,
or Thigmotactic.
It took me, I had to practice a while
to be able to say the name of his new solo band,
Thigmotactic.
It's tricky.
Does it have an arcane meaning, Thigmotactic?
Yeah, it does.
It's not a made-up word.
He found it in a book.
So, he found it somewhere,
and in context, I think it meant protecting oneself
or something along those lines.
I don't know.
But it was actually some pretty music.
It's funny how these olden bands that I used to know
back before they knew how to play music,
back when they were famous,
like the Devos and the Negative Lands,
over the years, and the Swingin' Love Corpses,
over the years, they...
They learn how to play.
That's horrible when that happens.
It's pretty, but it's different.
It is different.
They used to say that's what destroyed punk.
Not different.
Different.
Well, okay.
This is Speed Cave in the background
from our Friends of the Divergent.
Oh, Speed Cave?
Is emotional?
Beneferent?
I thought they were more just like a,
kind of a psychic pie you shove into your,
uh,
hypothalamus and just let it cook.
Or so you said once.
Oh, I can smell that pie cooking right now.
Call in to me.
Come and take a chance, sonny boy.
There's plenty of steaming hot pie in here.
The kind that made America great.
Enjoy.
Feast on my brain.
Oh.
And you have to take care of your heart, too, friends.
And your heart.
And I'm gonna take care of it.
Dr. Legume could tell you about that
if he wasn't in the hospital right now.
That's some more news for many of you subgeniuses.
If you don't know Dr. Legume,
you're probably safer that way.
But many of you do know Dr. Legume
and many thousands more know of the fearsome Dr. Legume,
generally regarded as the, uh,
the subgenius tough guy, you might say.
The hulking man.
Oh, a mountain.
Yeah, Dr. Katahdin Legume.
Uh, he's such a mighty man
that he had over, on New Year's Day,
or New Year's Eve, I don't know which,
he had three heart attacks.
Yes, but not only did he survive them,
he survived the subsequent five, count them,
five heart bypass surgeries.
Good Lord.
And we talked to him just yesterday.
He was, uh, feeling, uh,
he sounded a bit ragged around the edges.
Uh, but, um, uh, he informed us that,
just as I suspected,
it wasn't that he was out partying like a crazy man
on New Year's and gave himself three heart attacks
by doing all manner of drugs and staying up too late.
No.
As a matter of fact, uh,
he said that he hasn't smoked or drank anything,
not cigarettes, not nothing,
since the last time he saw us here in Cleveland,
which was Monday.
That's a month ago.
And because of that,
because of his, his New Year resolution
to be a healthful person,
he was probably out taking a nice healthful walk
like I do all the time.
Drinking vegetable juice at the same time.
Yeah.
Pure abstinence.
That's what gave him three, not one,
three heart attacks.
In other words, as he put it,
he almost died of nothing.
And that's, now, that's the subgenius for you.
We've, as subgeni, we must remember to pollute our health,
to continue to eat the foods that make us sick,
to continue to smoke three to four packs of cigarettes a day,
albeit with chronic bronchitis and a bad eye.
We must continue to shave our heads,
even though there's nothing but skull remaining.
It keeps us alive and going somewhere.
I have no idea where, but...
Strength through disfigurement, friends,
is the name of that, uh, doctrine.
You stick to the subgenius industrial diet,
uh, which includes a little bit of everything,
and I mean literally everything.
Heavy metals included.
Uh, and, uh, and that's,
it kind of builds up your immunities.
That's the idea.
You know, just don't restrain yourself from pleasure.
But, uh, attack yourself with it.
Beat yourself over the head with your pleasures
and build up an immunity.
And then free yourself from the need, the desire, you see.
All life is, uh, unsatisfied desire,
so you just free yourself from that
by fulfilling every sick, twisted, meh, desire.
As long as it's, uh, consensual, of course.
Uh...
Death.
They believe that in, uh, good, liberal doses,
that one should enjoy oneself.
Party to life!
Tiffulist.
Kill yourself with life!
Laugh yourself to death for crying out loud.
Live yourself to death!
Leave those droopy eyelids at home
and come on into the sanctuary of Bob.
Bob will comfort you like a large, sweaty womb
and will make you give birth to something unholy.
So come on by.
Ah.
Sometimes.
He does smell like a large, sweaty womb sometimes.
Well, you tried to get that effect,
and you succeeded.
I told you it wouldn't work.
We told you it probably maybe could work sometimes,
but probably wouldn't.
But you had to go ahead with the idea
of wombifying practically every artifact left in Dodge Town.
So...
there you go.
And, uh...
we all go.
We are here to go.
Oh.
Oh, by the way, Dr. Legume mentioned that, uh...
Now, this may come as a surprise,
but heart attacks hurt.
He said that the pain was enough to make you not want bacon.
Now, think of that!
Actually, we all...
You can imagine not being able to eat bacon
because you had a heart attack
and you don't need any more cholesterol.
But imagine it hurting so much that you don't even want it.
Or as...
Dr. Legume put it,
I've become bacon queer.
That was his way of putting it.
BQ is much shorter than Q.
Yeah, yeah.
So, you know, friends...
There's a lot of pork queers around,
I get around, too.
There's a lot of ham queers and whatnot.
Pork is sold in stores.
And not stored in any soul,
as the...
You know.
That's how the subgenius advertisement goes.
That was pretty.
So, uh...
So what else?
Well, you see, it's...
We're not concerned with health.
And we're not concerned with intelligence,
as the name subgenius shows.
But with something far more important
and far more slippery, which is sanity.
And $30.
Well, that's where you know we're sane
because we ain't giving it away.
You know we're not crazy
Well, actually, we are.
We're giving it away right here on this radio.
We're giving away the clues and the hints
that will lead you to do the right thing
for your local radio station.
Yes, despite the fact that the airwaves
are bought and sold by the fascist imperialists
from Zoran.
Not all airwaves,
and certainly not to all internetery.
Some of the internetery is still free,
although increasingly you have to know where and how
to look.
I say search for the hard nipples.
You know the phrase in advertising?
When you look what gooses people's bumps,
that's where you're gonna know the money's gonna be made
and the airwaves are gonna be slopped and sold
like a slimy, slithering thing.
Well, I can tell you what greases people's bumps
is stupid stuff.
Because that's what's the most popular
and that's what they go for.
Now, of course, I say stupid.
Now, how can a subgenius call something else stupid?
Well, it's easy.
It's not that we're that much smarter.
It's that we're simply better.
Not prettier, not taller, not richer,
not more educated, not smarter, not more correct.
Just simply better.
And only because we've got Bob
and that subgenius minister's card in our wallets.
That's all it takes to be better.
Yeah.
Not smart.
Well, parts might be bigger.
The tongue, the ego, the other tools of the preacher
will swell with exercise.
And that's why we're preaching exercise.
Exercise your sanity like Dave here does.
He's a good example to follow.
I'm at a loss to figure out how I'm exercising sanity,
but didn't you want me to...
Pump it!
Pump it up!
Ah.
Like a big fat balloon.
Stretch it out.
Like an over...
A bladder that you held too long.
Like an incestuous...
Oh, never mind.
That was something else.
Hey, Dave, when was the last time you dropped?
While Princess and I were on vacation,
we dropped almost every day.
You did?
Yeah.
Yeah, most people say you can't drop,
but it's like...
But maybe every four days or so,
because you're just wasting it.
But every day, we took a drop of water
and dropped it on a slide
and looked at the tiny monsters in there.
You could never burn out doing that.
Through the microscope.
Well, we were in Texas out on the goat ranch.
And so we had availed to us slime and slime waters
that you can't find in frozen northern Ohio.
Cow tanks with...
Cows swimming around in them.
The big giant aquariums.
Stock ponds.
We found those things are full of evil seed.
Fresh, juicy slime.
Oh, the juiciest slime.
Ostracods and diatoms rolling around in there.
And a giant stomach-turning blob.
And I filmed it!
Dave, Dave, Dave, this is the most wonderful thing.
We discovered that we could actually shoot videos
through the microscope hole of the microscope.
Just sticking the damn thing up against the damn thing.
Yeah, so I can put this stuff, once I edit this down,
I can put some of it on YouTube.
But I've been filming the frolicking and raping
of the microbes that I look at under my microscope.
When I say a stomach-turning blob,
I mean a blob in whose body
you can visibly see the stomach rotating
and swirl around wildly.
And the strings of blob rotifer fecal matter.
In fact, I think this thing used its spinning stomach
to propel itself.
Well, there are animals or hypoplods down there
with third nostrils.
I would think that there's a number of things
that are echoed, if not perfectly mirrored,
in the subgenius world.
When you say you can see something's stomach
inside on the outside while it's rotting its materials away,
Yeah, yeah.
we can, by use of certain third nostril techniques,
see humans on the bus, on the street, at the grocery store.
We can watch their intestines.
And they don't even know that's the good part.
And that's why, you know, when you get slack,
it's kind of like an in-joke.
You walk out chuckling, and you realize
you've just seen 240 people's stomachs.
I mean, the internal parts of their stomachs.
And they just had no idea that you were,
why you were looking at them down there.
Like that, laughing at what they had for dinner last night.
I don't know. It's a wonderful world.
Wondrous world.
Well, at any subgenius gathering,
that's what you'll see.
An orgy of stomach pumping.
And as above, so below.
There are, just as you see things down there
in the microscopic world that perfectly coincide with things.
They correlate to things in the larger world
that we're dealing with.
For instance, there's a type of rotifer down there
that looks just like a child's drawing of a kitty cat.
Only it moves.
But it looks like a very simple,
you know, a kid can draw a little circle
on top of a big circle,
and it draws two little ears and a little tail.
And that's a kitty cat, right?
Well, there are things that really look like that,
that are alive.
And chasing tiny little mice
that look like a child's drawing of a mouse.
And little stick figure men
that look sort of like a man,
except they have no arms or legs,
or faces.
But otherwise, they're like little people
running around down there, raping and killing,
just like real people.
What we must come to understand and realize
is that in the microscopic world,
there's also a mirror of the world above,
which is the world we live in,
and above us,
in huge, grand scope and fashion.
People, not people,
but whatever may encompass a galaxy,
going around, wiping and stomping
even large kitty cats
drawn by even larger children.
Right, right.
We're the equivalent of a child's,
an elder god child's drawing
of an elder god.
We humans are.
And the elder gods are the equivalent
of a child's drawing,
a child,
an ancient,
ancient,
or I don't even know what goes past the elder gods.
Maybe just...
The Ancient of Days.
All right.
That's, you know,
that's in the pre-week,
the pre-Seven-Day-Week format.
It's hard to tell how many days
the Ancient of Days was,
but he was pretty old.
I know what's even older,
Bible Man.
We were staying with Doc Frop
and Sister Decadence,
and somebody as a joke gave Sister Decadence
a Bible Man action figure.
Well, this was new to us.
Actually, it was a Bible Man's villain
whose name was Cipher.
But we got to looking at it,
it was like,
Bible Man,
what franchise is this?
And there was a BibleMan.com
advertised on the box
of this stupid action toy.
So we looked at BibleMan.com
and that was like
the floodgates of stupidity
poured open upon us.
It was fabulous.
It turns out Bible Man is the hero
who fights evil with the Bible,
and there's a Bible girl
who's kind of cute,
probably an ex-porn star,
and they've made a couple of DVDs
that must be so bad
that I swear to God,
on BibleMan.com it says,
free DVDs, only $17.
And I quote.
And you, if you don't believe me,
go to BibleMan.com,
and look around a little bit,
and you will see that those Christians
are selling things free for $17.
And I thought,
well, we need to do that.
Actually, I believe that we have done that
now that I think about it.
I think that that's an old subgenius.
But the difference is
we did it on purpose.
Free, only $30, you know.
I think that the Christians
are doing it on purpose too,
Mr. Englewell.
I think that...
No, I don't think they were that self-hypermodernating.
You mean intelligent?
I wouldn't say.
Let's not dress it in those terms.
You mean them stump-dumping Bible readers
was too dumb to know that free and $17
didn't go together somehow?
Probably it was a web page,
and probably they add,
first it was free,
and then they added,
they let it be free for a while,
and then they added the price,
but they kind of forgot to take out the free part.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Because that was artwork,
and the free was a GIF graphic or something.
Sure, Stanga.
And the person designing the website got fired,
I know how that happened.
and a new person designing a new website
inadvertently left free in there
when they put $17 in there.
See, that can't happen at a subgenius website
because nobody can get fired from it
because I'm the only one who does it,
which is why it hasn't been changed much
except for weekly hours of Slack every now and then.
But I'll get to that.
And the occasional schizoid personality jumps and leaps,
which any schizophrenic will do,
they will become another person for a while.
No, that's different.
That's alt.slack,
which is not the same as subgenius.com.
Subgenius.com is controlled totally by yours truly.
And the conspiracy.
And it's really,
it's like a fly frozen in amber.
But, no, the conspiracy
doesn't really control subgenius.com.
Well, yeah, sort of.
I've had to take down a couple of them
and a couple of Scientology secret documents
that we had inadvertently published.
I mean, I didn't even know they were on there.
But they were actual literature.
Now, for the uncensored,
completely free subgenius land,
you can look at alt.slack.
You would have to Google alt.slack
to find it, most of you.
Because to most of you,
the internet is your browser.
In fact, it's not even your browser.
It's Yahoo or Google.
To you, that's the internet.
Google or Yahoo and a browser.
Because there's no other way
of doing the internet for you.
Because you're young and hip.
Think of the, what a browser really means.
I'm old.
I'm old and I'm an old geek
who works under the hood.
An old tool user.
Yep, I've been napping.
I used to nap code.
I'd take a chunk of flint
and nap out me some code
for like a gallery,
our graphics gallery or some such thing,
or a podcast.
That's the way we used to do it.
Kids can't do that now.
They just click on things.
But real old people can't even click on things.
My father, Pappy, actually said to me,
you people can click on links.
I can't do that.
Nobody ever taught me how to click on a link.
Nobody ever taught me how to click on it.
But the sad thing is, well, actually,
all of us had taught Pappy how to click on a link.
He just, he has trouble with the click twice business.
Well, he thinks, maybe he thought
that a click on link had some sort of secret meaning.
Like browser.
When we think of the word browser,
what is a browser really?
It's a person who errantly goes from shop to shop.
Look at this.
Looking for things to perhaps buy one day.
It has to do with procurement
and the evil of material necessity gone wild
or something like that.
So perhaps when he said click on links,
he thought you had to do more than just go to the part
where it said links and click on it.
Well, he doesn't need to know that stuff
because he's Pappy.
I think if you were Pappy,
you wouldn't even know how to click on a link anyway.
People would click on them for you.
Yeah.
And that's the way it works.
Well, you think of me that way.
You think of me.
Huh?
Well, no, I was just going to say,
you think of me that way.
As an itinerant Pappy, I'm able to click on links.
But just the other day, I showed a person of my,
even younger than my own age group,
that all they would have to do is scroll down there
and click on it.
And they were going, oh, okay, what do I do now?
And I felt like I was literally staying with Dave.
Wow, that's really pathetic.
I felt like I was some sort of computer.
Computer whiz banger.
Well, Princess, we felt like that at her old workplace.
Now, when she's home with me, she's the Dave and I'm the Stang.
But when she goes to work, she's the Stang and they're the Daves
that don't know how to click on things.
Abso-clickingly.
You know, so it's all relative.
Now, that person that you were helping, I just don't know.
I just don't know.
Well, click technology helps.
I'll pray for them.
I'm going to pray for that person.
Don't tell me who they are.
I'll just pray in general for all those people.
And they'll probably die because I don't think God listens to my prayers.
I think some evil monster listens to my prayers.
I'm pretty sure of that, too.
That's why I don't pray much.
You know, I think it is an evil monster.
But remember, if you want to light a candle in the window for this person
or any group of people, try not to light the drapes on fire.
That's an important part of that.
And when you pray, try not to, you know,
use those magic negative evil incantations.
Try and wish or pray something positive on them.
Well, think how many smarty pants subgeniuses there are out there
that know how to click on the link,
but they don't know how to not set their drapes on fire.
They're sitting there kicking away on their links
while their drapes are burning away
and they're setting their ceiling on fire.
Soon they're going to be burned up.
Their face will literally be on fire
like that guy at the end of Crank 2.
High voltage.
And spilt milk will be flaming all over their floor.
Right. They'll be watching spilt milk burn,
just like Bob told them not to do.
But they can still click on links, boy,
and they can write code.
Hmm.
Phooey.
Phooey on them.
We learned many things on our trip down south to Texas.
Besides about Bible Man.
We learned about a TV show and a whole network for men.
The network is called Spike.
I did not know such a thing existed.
It turns out that there's networks just for women
and networks for gay homosexuals
and networks for all kinds of...
and for people who like to see animals get cut apart.
That's Princess Wee's mom's favorite.
And the autopsy network.
All kinds of...
I didn't know this because I don't...
you know, nobody ever showed me how to click...
how to change a channel.
Oh, it's been...
I can click on links,
but I'm not big with channel changing.
It's just like Fireside Theater predicted.
Yes, it is.
It exactly and most certainly is.
I remember the first time I saw an operating table
and an operating theater with medical students
as they disrupted a cadaver's eternal schlep
with... on television on channel 332,
which is a long channel.
I'm telling you, man, it's...
it's...
it is, you know?
We found a show that has got...
I guess you might say it was...
it's the dumbest thing I've ever seen on television,
short of my favorite show, Owl My Balls,
which doesn't really exist yet,
but is on its way, obviously,
because this show we saw called Mansers.
It's Answers for Men on the Men channel.
Mansers.
Mm-hmm.
I was blinking in disbelief.
For, like, three episodes of it,
I sat there going,
I can't believe anybody watches this
for three episodes in a row.
You'd have to be unbelievably stupid
or else new to television
to watch three of these things in a row.
But every five seconds,
there was a jiggling bikini girl,
and they would answer questions
that concern all men.
Like, can you flatulate enough
to blow your...
to explode your scrotum?
That was a serious question asked
in not such lofty language,
in much more vulgar language.
That was one.
Another one was,
what animal is best at self-abuse?
What food in my refrigerator?
Which, the answer, by the way,
is the elephant,
because he is prehensile nose and...
elephant...
membar.
The...
What food would be best for me
to make love to
that I would find in my refrigerator?
The answer is veal,
because it has more collagen.
These...
Oh, how...
How's the best way to get a lesbian
to make love to a man?
I remember seeing that one.
And the answer to that one was
to wear the urine of a pregnant female.
Mmm.
Now, this was...
The way I'm outlining this show
is so vastly different
and vastly more sophisticated-sounding
than the way they actually talk on this show,
because this is a nice radio station
for families, you know.
I'm sure there's lots of children
listening right now, and...
Oh, certainly.
So we don't want to be like
the Mansers show.
It was like jackass or something,
only, believe it or not,
jackass style, you might say.
But it did have a jiggling bikini girl
every five seconds,
whether they were talking about women,
whether she had anything to do
with the show or not.
It was Al My Ball's come to life.
Right, and that's what...
I was just thinking that
if the Church of Subgenius
had any of those balls,
that's the first thing they would do
would be start their own
replicant channel on 300...
Or 953.
Well, we are...
We do have a start.
Called Al My Balls,
and really do Al My Balls.
And I would say get far more specific
than the concept of Al My Balls.
Bob's.
No, that's stupid.
Well, if they look like Bob,
then why not?
Damn the torpedoes full speed ahead.
I've got one that looks like Bob
with a little tiny pipe.
Well, you're not unusual in that respect.
So many of us do nowadays.
Well, when you get the surgery at Dobstown,
but not many people can afford that.
I got mine for free.
Well, not free.
I paid, but...
Not with money.
Paid with blood and sweat and urine and...
Yeah.
Mine.
Blown out areas.
Well, I would like to say that in the trades,
what is it when they blur things
when you're going through the airport?
I had no idea that the father
of the underpants bomber
has close ties with the oil industry
and the banking industry and even Mossad.
Isn't that weird?
Oh, the most recent bomber?
Yeah.
Oh, no, I didn't know that.
Where did you...
I didn't know that.
But see, I'm just one of the sheeple.
I don't believe anything I read on the internet.
Oh, you can't believe also sheeple
how many of the right wing talk show hosts
have taken to calling anybody
who doesn't agree with what they say
a sheeple now.
Yes, I know.
And they think they invented that.
That was my...
I know.
That was my point.
And everyone knows that I invented it.
That's right.
Well, in fact, I'm pretty sure
that we could probably find an ancient ESO show
or Swamp Radio or Brain Rot or something
which predates, which uses that term,
predating dating itself.
But as we know...
Because back in those days,
all you had to date was sheep.
You people really were sheeple
because they love their little sheep out there.
And they would say,
what's wrong with Herm?
And we'd say,
it's ew.
But I remember when we first used those phrases incorrectly,
there was a crazy guy in Texas.
I'm pretty sure it's nobody that you know
who was one of these like militia type guys
who called everyone sheeple.
Are you talking about Alex Jones?
No, this is pre-Alex Jones.
Remember, Alex Jones was pre-Alex Jones
when he was in Texas.
He was a guy in Texas
that drove around in his pickup truck.
hollering through a bullhorn.
Now he hollers through his podcast.
I think he's nuts myself
because he's not a man of Bob.
I looked on the membership on the Book of Life
and I didn't see the name Alex Jones in there.
There is none.
Well, there is another Alex Jones
from Topeka, Kansas who is a...
Oh, that one's saved.
That one's saved, sure.
He's what the first Alex Jones would call a sheeple.
And yet he paid.
Oh, my God.
He's a subgenius ordained minister
and so he's going to go to heaven
and Alex Jones ain't.
Alex Jones is going to die
with the rest of the pinks
and the quote sheeple.
Me.
Unquote.
If you don't mind.
If you don't mind me putting it that way.
If you don't mind me being so bold
as to intimate
that perhaps somebody that didn't get behind J.R. Bob Dobbs
and memorized Book of the Subgenius
might be a dumbass.
I wouldn't mean to.
Intimate such a...
I wouldn't want to imply something harsh like that.
How you're bald.
You're so brash and brassy.
Oh, God.
And here's another thing.
This is how I know there's a conspiracy.
You can't buy ranch-style beans up here in Ohio.
I looked.
I checked.
I can't find ranch-style beans.
Now, I went down to Texas.
I bought seven cases of them
and had them shipped up here.
So I'm fine.
I'm set.
My friends and listeners down in Texas
don't need to send me any more cases of ranch-style beans.
But can you believe they don't?
Well, you never even heard of them, have you, Dave?
No, I have bought them at Ohio stores,
not only in Cleveland,
but out here in the far-flung sticks of Cleveland.
You have?
Yes.
They're not a, you know, everyday Boston-baked or pork.
And they're kind of slightly specialty items right now.
Now, this is ranch-style brand.
I don't mean ranch-style flavor.
Sure, sure.
But Bush's has ranch-style, chili-style beans and stuff.
No, this is a brand in Texas.
It used to, it had a very distinctive can
that had a drawing of a cowboy on it,
and it said,
Husband Pleasing.
Well, wouldn't you know,
around towards the end of the 70s,
suddenly it changed to
Appetite Pleasing.
Because apparently it's wrong to please a husband.
Especially if he's not your husband,
Unless you mention also pleasing the wife,
or then, well, you might be implying that marriage
is somehow supposed to be a man or a woman.
And of course, that's against the law now to intimate.
I'm starting to sound like my dad now.
You don't want mommy in the kitchen all day,
doing the mommy stuff all day.
Man gotta be a man.
I'm trying to get in there, helping out once in a while,
while he's rustling down the couch.
While I was on vacation,
I read a, somebody on the subgenius news group,
alt.slack, was, it was some,
a new person calling itself Negative Guy.
And Negative Guy said that he hated happy people,
especially families,
because happy people didn't know how utterly screwed we are.
And that made me jealous.
I got to where I was thinking,
I'm kind of jealous of all those unhappy people
who hate everything.
The hate-filled people.
I've lost my hate.
I've got a family.
I don't know how completely screwed we are, apparently.
And now I feel like I'm missing something,
not being unhappy and full of hate anymore.
I vaguely remember being unhappy and full of hate, but,
I remember, it's not the same.
If you're, you know, it's kind of like LSD.
You're either, you're on the bus or you're off the bus.
You're on your brain and drugs,
or you're off the brain and the drugs.
You can't describe it.
And I can't, I can't,
I'm having trouble remembering extreme unhappiness.
Maybe you can help me.
Oh, you mean me personally or we or the audience?
Oh, anybody, somebody.
Well, then.
Can help to make me remember what it's like,
to be, to really hate everybody.
Well, as a young high he popped of the church,
I have seen your early videos and you definitely
were filled with a vile, vituperous,
Oh, yeah, yeah.
and a shining form of hatred.
Yeah.
A kind of luminescent, incandescent hatred,
which burst through the screen like a photon beam
and right into the brain of the viewer, making them go,
Yeah, I hate them suckers too.
Yeah.
You know, and that's what got me going on it.
And so I am literally heart wrenched to hear that you've lost a great deal.
I know, man.
All I've got left is slack.
Comely hatred.
God, if only I could get rid of this slack and get my unhappiness back.
Oh, wait, wait.
I started to get it.
I started to get it just then.
I've lost it.
I hear Princess We Laugh and my heart flies like a hawk and I can't.
Shores like an eagle.
I need to think about what I'm missing out on.
All that hate, that juicy, glorious, mouth-watering hate.
Oh, and feeling sorry for oneself.
That's a juicy emotion.
You can really milk that.
Oh, look at where we're stopped here.
You can milk hate.
And you can milk self-pity.
The two go together pretty well.
When you're all hate-filled, then you feel bad, though.
You don't like feeling bad, do you?
Don't you like to feel good?
Well, I do feel bad that I feel like I'm, like I said, all those unhappy people.
I'm jealous.
I'm missing it.
I just don't, I'm so confused.
I could see your house from here.
Oh, my God.
Oh, the Ferris Wheel of emotion.
It goes with this music so inappropriately.
I looked down below and...
It's this music by Speed Cave of speedcave.com.
Look, there's a few...
Look, wait, wait.
We're coming up to the top again.
I can see more Speed Cavers running away.
Something, something, a bomb just went off.
Holy crutch.
Oh, man.
Oh, the Ferris Wheel stopped.
I hate, I love, I have, nappy, shappy.
That's pretty good.
I'm going to make a loop of that noise there.
I hate, I love, I have, nappy, shappy.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
I hope that guy gets down.
See, Dave, you just started to launch into a kind of an improv skit.
Now, back when I was a hateman, I used to be able to jump into those skits right along
with you.
and now I'm just, it's like I'm too sane or sold out, pink, rational, normal.
Stan, I must tell you, from the yogic point of view...
Is slack bad? Is slack wrong?
From the yogic point of view, slack is not wrong,
but you must have an indifference to anger.
You must have an indifference to evil.
The conspiracy must make you go, oh, instead of,
I'm going to kill him, wait, the exes are going to kill him,
and I'm going to sit by and laugh.
Hey, you know what I just realized?
We have to go. The show's over now,
and if I go on for another two seconds, that's the end of it.
Friends, you've been listening to The Hour of Slack
from the Church of the Subgenius.
For more information about the Church of the Subgenius,
you can look at subgenius.com,
or you can write to P.O. Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio, 44118.
And, uh...
Thank you, Lonesome Cowboy Dave, for calling in.
Thank you, WCSB, for being here to let us do this.
Thank you, Princess Wee, for being Princess Wee.
And thank you, kind listeners, for listening to us.
And all of our...
And, uh...
So with that, I take my leave.
Mal.
Evacuate the building.
Evacuate the site.
Please leave the building.
This is Phil Proctor.
And David Osman.
Of the Firesign Theater.
And we're enjoying listening to The Hour of Slack.
I'm slacking off myself.