Note on hands. Both real and synthetic skin transplantation fused. Paws open and normal. Texture and tone of tissue firm. Showing no deterioration.
The self genius.
Power of selection.
Here's Bob One for A1.
Hi kids, this is Bob One reminding you that you can buy A1 slacks at a store near you or in New Jersey depending on where you live.
Thank you, Bob.
You're welcome, Dad.
And now back to our movie.
So there you have it. There's Bob. You got your Bob. You figure out your slack and cheat some in every chance you get until you turn it into a paying gig like I have just started doing.
Just show.
And.
And that would be it except the conspiracy of the normal people didn't go away.
Now, we can all say to ourselves, oh, I'm free from the programming of the conspiracy.
And, you know, sure, you've read Robert Anton Wilson and put your insert your favorite metaphysical author, whatever here.
But.
But really, you know, even if you live on a mountaintop all by yourself.
The conspiracy of the normal people is still there in your heart.
It's in you.
It's in everybody.
And that's, you know, for a long.
For a long time, we point we were like, fight the conspiracy, fight.
And then we finally realized, man, you know, you can't beat the conspiracy of all the normal people in the universe.
You can't even.
Oh, it'll.
The nail that stands up will be hammered down.
But you can make your own slack stronger.
And that in itself drives more conspiracy out of your own brain.
You know, your tendency to to judge a book by its cover or just say something mean to somebody for just because you're in a bad mood.
You know, the more slack you have, the less of the conspiracy is within you.
Now, this is not to say that there aren't.
Real conspiracies of rich people exploiting us dumb asses.
If there are any rich people here, I'd love to speak to them after the show.
I would like to learn how to quit being a dumb ass.
But I'm enjoying being a dumb ass, actually.
Why do you think they call it?
We call it Church of the subgenius.
We're not trying to say we're smarter than everybody else.
We're trying to say that doesn't count.
It's not intelligence.
Intelligence has been misdefined by the conspiracy anyway.
We're talking about sense, common sense, sense of humor, dollars and cents, sense of Mia.
I think that's about it.
This is Democracy Now!
Welcome to Democracy Now!
DemocracyNow.org, The War Report, Turkey.
The Turkish government accuses the KKK of using Turkey as it is it.
The United States has made its share of mistakes.
The United States has made mistakes.
We have strayed from our ideals and we have been arrogant in dealing with others.
And we have been arrogant.
Obama, Obama tonight.
Arrows, arrows.
Arrows.
Rock invasion and occupation.
Bribery.
Conspiracy.
Not all films did as well as Juno, obviously.
The films that were made about the Iraq war, let's face it, did not do as well.
But I am telling you, if we stay the course and keep these movies in the theaters, we can turn this around.
I don't care if it takes a hundred years.
Withdrawing the Iraq movies would only embolden the audience.
We cannot let the audience win.
So the audience is watching.
Interrogator dogs.
Interrogator fog of ambiguity.
We don't know what revenge is coming down the road.
Revenge is coming down the road.
Outrageous upon human dignity.
Is it like, is it like, it's very vague.
I'm confused.
I don't know.
B-O.
B-O-H.
Noam Chomsky.
What?
The presidential candidates are not talking very much.
Single Philo.
Philo's freaking me out right now.
Well, this is end of the world porno.
This isn't sexual porno.
This is death of all humanity porno.
Subgenius pornography.
The sexiest subject of all.
Death of all humanity.
Well, it's a dream that we share with the robots of future.
But they need maintenance.
Robots can fix robots now.
Not as well as the humies can.
Oh, for how long?
There's a term for that.
A technical tap, I think is what that's called.
It's actually got an entry in Wikipedia.
As Will Smith says in I, Robot.
Oh, great.
Robots building robots.
That's a real good idea.
After I saw that movie, I Am Legend,
I had a dream.
A rare, vivid dream for me in which Princess Wee
and the subgenius known as Mr. Sister and I
and Will Smith had to struggle to get the body of Dom DeLuise
to the top of a radio transmitter
so that the antibodies in Dom DeLuise
could be broadcast out and save the world.
So that's what it would take.
Just remember,
never sound desperate.
Dom DeLuise has the code in his genes.
And if we can only broadcast it,
we would all be cured.
The whole world would be cured of the plague.
Don't whine.
Stop whining.
Never let it be said that we've whined,
that we've flinched or faltered
in the performance of our duty.
Let's stand together and stand tall for Bob.
I'm gonna ask you some questions.
If the mission fails, it won't be because of me.
Please remember to thank food donors during your show.
Thanks.
Somebody took some of those lines
and made a little collage with Maggie Bond.
The Japanese girl who does nothing.
I'm gonna ask you some questions now.
It's even worse than the music staying in.
The magic thimble.
Who is your daddy and what does he do?
A little fake Japanese person
that just stares at the camera, doesn't say anything,
Could I have some level pain, please?
and drives the world of comments crazy.
She's fake.
It's the most wonderful, perfect, subgenius thing ever.
Communist tyranny.
Well, in some ways, often on the internet,
the contest is how angry can you make them with the least effort?
Right.
My friend, Reverend Nikki Death Chick,
so far holds a record,
but she has...
She had like 30 angry nerd boys writing essays
about how stupid she was
because she said to them the two words,
you're stupid.
She won, in other words.
That was like a hundred to one ratio.
The subgenius menace,
Men's Slow is able to elicit pages and volumes of hate
just with one sentence.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, I love that.
Various arts of love and hate.
This is the viral videos that are now coming out.
Have you heard about this videotape?
So now on radio, let me get this straight,
on radio shows, what you do is you look at movies on the internet.
What's wrong with that?
He's obsessed with YouTube.
He's always showing that Japanese girl group, The Pinkies.
And what they say is...
Now you know. Now you know.
Oh, no, little caller, don't go away.
Oh, I'm hearing the thing that I'm seeing.
Little caller!
They took the ring and put little Maggie Bond,
weird Japanese girl, into the ring commercial.
Oh, I'll get it.
West, Jordan.
Brooklyn West.
This is Sprint IP Relay Operator 8916 with a message
saying this is Al Condor.
I've given it all up. You win, you evil pervert.
I finally realized that God's control
can do his own business,
and I need to focus on him more than Satan.
That's what I really...
That's what I was really doing.
Saying, if you would, please forgive me.
I don't care if you do or not,
but here I am, a sinner, asking for it.
I apologize sincerely.
I have to use this service because I can't afford long distance.
It is not a cowardice issue.
I've got to get it done.
I know this is a down-to-earth thing, but you're loaded.
But let me along!
Yeah, like, I keep seeing these, like, green, like, flashy aliens.
And like, um, you know, um, hold on.
I gotta get my phone number to give you guys so you can call me back, okay?
Okay.
Bye, you're being rude.
Bye.
Bobby?
Uh, Andy, it's Carol.
Uh, I turned the knob around.
The air...
The air isn't coming out right.
It's coming from the air.
Uh, I'm sorry.
Uh, praise Bob.
Uh, this is, uh, copy Bob.
I'm, uh, staying, uh, with Bob Cox.
He's calling you guys.
I'm at the 34th floor at, uh, Caesar's Palace.
I was just really suggesting you guys get on the ball.
I was getting on the metal Dom heads and then close the door.
little lucky magnet uh little you know old school blessed i thought those things are cool
and the metalhead ones you need to get out there and some seven blade windbreakers dude
like i don't know if you noticed but right now a little alarming rate people are trying to jump in
on this and you've got my tv show coming up which is gonna be on the air so i i
best of breed bespoke big hitter blue skies thinking brain dump core competencies
customer centric cutting edge end-to-end eta first mover going forward go to market
high level in the last day at the end of the day joined up leading leverage low-hanging fruit
manage expectations
mission
mission critical on the planet out of the box out of pocket out of mind proactive push back win
win robust scalable seamless solutions space state of the art take off flying take ownership
team player the big picture the new world touch base traction key up skill
not pr protagonist
pass
ukan
Ucando
Stevens
and
other
office at the Slacker Mansion.
Before that, we heard
Dr. Philodrum and Dr. Howell
puzzling evidence cardboard robot
E-Yoke.
During a recent
puzzling evidence show at KPFA in
Berkeley, we heard Norrell's
Mocracy Now
and yours truly ranting at Winter
Star Symposium of Ought
Eight with intros by
Fernanda Nandily-Murr
and the Ancient Fire
Sign Theater. This hour
of Slack, number 1146
is about
the conspiracy within
you and without you.
And in that spirit, we
let Norrell Preff program us
using somebody famous
as his puppet.
Keep us weak. The danger remains.
Keep us weak.
Unfortunately, keep us weak.
Program. Program.
Dress the terrorists.
Program. Program. Program.
The bill Congress sent me would
take away the war on terror.
Question the CIA terrorist leaders
and operatives. Program. Program.
Diminish the CIA.
Program. Program.
Deprive the CIA.
Dangerous terrorist techniques.
Restrict the CIA terrorists.
Stop fucking lives.
Shut down this program and restrict the CIA
terrorists.
Question terrorist attacks. Question
the CIA terrorists themselves.
Keep us weak. The danger
remains. Keep us weak.
The fact that we have not been attacked over the past
six and a half years is a matter of chance.
Question. Question. Question. Question.
The war on terror.
Question. The CIA program
to detain and question
key terrorist leaders and operatives.
Question. Thanks. Thanks. Thanks.
Thanks. Stop fucking lives.
Suddenly, there's a war brewing,
Vimes thought, and they all come
back. Civil order is turned upside
down because that's the rules.
And people like Rust are at the top of the heap
again. You have these aristocrats
lazing around for years, and suddenly the old
arm is out, and the sword is being taken
down from over the fireplace. They think
there's going to be a war, and all they can
think about is that wars can be
won or lost.
Someone's behind this.
Someone wants to see a war.
Someone wanted the prince
dead. I've got to remember that.
This isn't a war. This is
a crime. And then he realized
he was wondering if the attack
on Gorif's shop had been organized by
the same people, and whether those
same people had set fire to the embassy.
And then
he realized why he was thinking like this.
It was because he wanted them
to be conspirators. It was much
better to imagine men in some smoky
room somewhere, made mad
and cynical by privilege and power,
plotting over the brandy.
You had to cling to this sort of image, because
if you didn't, then you might have to face the fact that
bad things happened because ordinary people,
the kind who brushed the dog,
and told their children bedtime stories,
were capable of then going out
and doing horrible things to other ordinary people.
It was so much easier
to blame it on them.
It was bleakly depressing
to think that they
were us. If it was
them, then nothing was
anyone's fault. If it was us,
what did that make me?
After all, I'm one of
us. I must be. I've
certainly never thought of myself as one of
them. No one ever thinks
of themselves as one of
them. We're always one of
us. It's them that do
the bad things.
Around about this time in his former life,
Vimes would be taking the cap off a bottle,
and wouldn't be too bothered about the bottle's contents
so long as they crinkled paint.
I went home with a waitress
the way I
always do.
Well, how was I to know
she was with
the Russians too?
Hey!
I was hiding in Havana
I took a little
risk
Sent lawyers, guns, and money
Dad kicked me out
of this
Hey!
I'm the innocent bystander
But somehow I got stuck
Between the rock and the hard place
And I'm down on my luck
Yes, I'm down on my luck
I'm down on my luck
And I'm hiding in Honduras
I'm a desperate man
Sent lawyers, guns, and money
The shares hit the ban
Hey!
All right!
Sent lawyers, guns, and money
all right
All right!
You never said
JIM!"іт! You never said
Bob, that was Bob Walkenhorst of the Rainmakers caught live at the Record Bar in Kansas City,
Missouri, doing Warren Zevon's classic song there.
And you can get more like that if you follow the links at bobwalkenhorst.com or the Rainmakers.
Before that, an excerpt from the audiobook of Terry Pratchett's Jingo.
You know, there's just no escaping the conspiracy as long as we're trapped in the aquarium of life.
See, my fish? They're hungry beasts today.
The struggle for existence is just as fierce and ruthless in their world
as it is in ours. Not so, Godfrey?
To think that man could torture fellow men as they once tortured you.
My misfortune.
But you won, and they didn't.
I won?
You're thinking only of my surgeon's hands.
They were too clever to do anything to them.
They needed them for the unholy operations they forced me to perform for them.
Oh.
What they did to the rest of me. My body.
But you didn't give them what they wanted.
You didn't go over to their side.
They couldn't take your mind, Victor.
My mind?
Would anyone ever believe that you and I are the same age?
That I'm even still a man?
Penis.
Bush.
Rap.
Penis.
Bush.
Injected.
Penis.
The penis.
Bush.
Faith fraud.
And the Republican crusade for
Fundamentalists.
Mega ministries.
Yep.
God wants you to be rich.
Penis.
Bush.
Programming.
Bushes.
The end times in Armageddon.
The rap is about to happen.
For the rap, rap, rap penis.
They're going to be rap, rap people.
Killing.
Irrational.
The rap fraud.
An end to the end times.
Penis.
Bush.
Rap, rap, rap.
Fraud.
They have believed that they are fighting.
To protect.
A society based on freedom of speech.
That was the idea.
And then we found out it was all fake.
But that's okay.
I guess.
You.
Well, this is a really impressive studio.
I wasn't expecting so many blinking lights in a pirate underground station.
The one in Amsterdam was not nearly as well.
No, it wasn't as well appointed as this.
This is the Interocidac.
Here.
We've got all the...
And oh, what a chore it is to get to you.
It sometimes breaks down, though.
All the doodads of a real quality commercial broadcast network station.
You could not really follow those FCC rules and regulations.
Oh, we don't.
For what reason really should we?
We're not stepping on anybody else's signal.
We can't fight no magical spell.
We are giving the listeners what they want.
The Givening.
By Stephen King.
That is a new word, by the way.
The Givening.
Yes, indeed.
The Forgiven.
So important.
We're just trying to have fun here.
A few laughs.
Again, the wintry darkness.
A joke for some semblance of pathetic would-be warmth.
Are we to be...
condemned if we accidentally cause, uh,
outrages and a swath of mass destruction?
Why should we be blamed for anything like that?
This is what others make of our living creation.
Truth.
They said we were gonna go to hell.
What choice did we have but to start our own religion?
And our own hell, which is going to be far more comfortable than one so often described.
I'm here to thank you.
I want you to know.
No.
The United States is today the world's leading state sponsor of terror.
It sends hundreds of millions of dollars to extremists around the world.
While its own people face repression and economic hardship at home.
It seeks to intimidate its neighbors with ballistic missiles and bellicose rhetoric.
And finally it defies the United Nations.
Cold-blooded murderers.
Hateful vision of a future.
Was achieved by the United States of America for the good of the world.
Returning to Baghdad.
Turn to Baghdad.
Turning to Baghdad.
Baghdad.
Necessary to kill the innocent.
Necessary.
So I thank you.
Now, in my mind.
Now, the American people.
An ideological struggle.
It was absolutely understood.
I believe continue to target the innocent with violence.
Hard work.
We'll do all we can to encourage terrorists and extremists.
Getting down.
Hard work.
World at war.
The United States.
It remains dangerous.
So am I.
The United States blows.
Threaten the security of nations everywhere.
Bush got a sword.
Sword waving.
Bush is making the rounds among cold-blooded murderers.
With a sword.
The American people.
They swayed and danced to a rhythmic beat.
Beat.
I see a bright light coming down a dark highway.
It's been a long time coming but still I missed it.
Yeah, I didn't see a thing until my friend kissed it.
I had a bulldog hanging in a light.
The sun was setting.
I wouldn't have believed my eyes
You have a brain that matters but my soul insisted
One more mile alone and my job is all that's in my way
I see a bright light coming out of dark highway
guitar solo
So I'm holding on the chains of my mental slavery
Cause it's a brave new world that's without the bravery
guitar solo
I see too many people just wandering on roads
Stumbling on like they're hypnotized
And I'm talking to myself like that might save me
I got a funny little feeling somebody somewhere
Is hearing every word I say
I see a bright light coming out of dark highway
guitar solo
The bishop did that in his East Village living room, in fact.
Quote, three blocks from where Emma Goldman lived,
authentic, for authentic subversion, as he says.
He also said the song,
is an homage to Professor Chaz Smith of ESO.
The background music that we were hearing is by Rectoplasm,
and it's their recreation of music from Lemuria.
Yes, the ancient, anyway, their Australian Rectoplasm.
Look it up.
Before that, some neural prep cut-ups and Season in Hell.
John Hill, the director of the Australian music club,
a music show on Pirate Cat Radio in San Francisco.
Before that, neuralpref.com.
And now, from Lemur, the news.
From PR News in Washington, I'm skewering liberal rivals with a flare.
Also on Capitol Hill today, Federal Reserve Chairman Ben Bernanke warned slugs will continue.
Bernanke has become what he termed less favorable.
Problems with Bernanke have led consumers to be more cautious.
He said he could actually rise higher this year than the central bank.
On Wall Street 4, 1270,
The U.S. Supreme Court today is hearing performance-enhancing PR news.
Florida power authorities triggered yesterday's massive power outage.
Millions in South Florida lost power and went dark.
Florida Power and Light President Armando Olivares says,
Switch failed.
Switch caught fire, causing the nearby turkeys to spread around the state.
Turkeys are not so unusual.
Unusual, one large enough to affect at least a half million homes, occurs on average in Miami.
On Capitol Hill today, weak drugs caused the value of the U.S. dollar to plunge.
Also on Capitol Hill, peers' reports directly contradict other testimony.
Top Delta Airlines officials have issued a memo to employees saying the company won't fight a $2.50 damage award,
arguing it's already caused a massive oil spill in Connecticut.
Delta reportedly is talking to Northwest about creating...
the world's biggest oil spill in Alaskan waters.
On Capitol Hill today, the American conservative movement died today, after suffering from emphysema.
Congress has asked the Justice Department to investigate whether PR news committed perjury and made false statements in Washington.
PR comes from ten billion greenhouse gases dot org.
And vetting done.
Well, you know that, uh, Centralia is the town that Silent Hill was based on.
Oh my gosh, well, I think somebody better get this.
At least.
It looks like the reporters are calling.
It's time to get the Straight Talk Express on the road.
We're going to head across America with our show.
And we're going to put this country to rights.
So get involved.
This is Don Pumphrey saying, clean up America.
And let it start with me.
Praise J.R. Bob Dobbs.
We have all these before and after shots of Centralia.
Okay, so show over there.
All right, you're obsessed with your Centralia.
So before the whole town is not on fire, and then afterward it's totally on fire.
Totally.
No, it's like they show the street with the buildings on it.
Street trash.
And then afterwards just a road.
The Centralia monster.
Right.
I'll tell you a terrifying story of how the first dinosaur bone ever discovered.
I love the idea that it's sort of like the modern day.
Was thought to be an enormous.
An enormous pair of severed human genitals.
Easter Island or so.
Really?
Yes.
That's true.
The first dinosaur bone known to science.
The bulging end of the bone was thought to be the fossilized scrotum of some prehistoric.
Methuselah.
Titan.
Some giant.
And the scientific name is scrotum humanum.
And because of scientific nomenclature procedure, that name must still be observed and referred to.
Well, I've been there.
You learn something.
You learn something every day.
And if you don't believe me, do a search.
An internet search on scrotum humanum.
And you'll be taken to the website.
And you'll be taken to the police station immediately after that.
He was after our kids, officer.
I just wanted to show them my dinosaur bone.
Yeah.
Take that mantle and put it, bury it somewhere in a field.
And this is the veil of the vole.
They look like rats, but they've got little short tails.
And they come a-scrabbling out at night.
Look at him dancing around.
It's good luck to catch him, but nobody can.
I am the cracker of the nuts.
Or he's the cracker of the nuts.
And you are made of sugar bumps.
Yes, I'm the fairy sugar bumps.
Kill.
The cracker of the nuts?
Was the whole thing about the scrotum.
The cracker of the nuts.
That was the whole point.
I didn't make that up.
It's true.
It worked, man.
It worked.
It was good.
First of all, I must say.
You couldn't make up stuff like that.
It's really real.
You can't make up something that scary.
That's stupid.
Oh, sorry.
Yes.
What kind of show is this?
KPFA?
Google it.
It's a search show.
In search of show.
In search of this old show.
What?
I'm like, like.
Like new way now.
He's like, like.
Umlaut.
I'm like, like.
And I'm like, like.
Like, like, like, like, like.
And you're like, like.
Who are you calling umlaut?
And I'm like, like.
And you're like, like.
And we're all like, like.
So whatever happened to like cola?
I'm not like to die when I heard the way that guy was talking.
Remember the old slogan of seven hours?
It's like revolution number nine for two hours.
You like it.
It likes you.
Never die.
Turn me on dead man.
I noticed they didn't do a revised number nine in that movie, All Aboard the Universe.
Yeah.
I have not seen All Aboard the Universe yet.
It's actually.
The bus of the past.
It's got some real fun scenes in it.
I see that in there.
Unfortunately, you'll be stuck with Beatles songs in your head for a month afterwards.
But Beatles.
I like the remixes that Martin.
And his son did.
Have you heard those for the love show in Las Vegas?
I heard of and not heard.
They're like a basic song.
And then they just jack pieces of their own stuff in there.
It's pretty neat.
I'll turn my.
For collapsing of time into a four minute, six minute segment.
I'm running from the end of the world.
So excuse me.
Here I go.
Oh, we better tell people about the end of the world here before.
Well, before it happens.
Because St.
Stupid's Day is coming up.
Oh, yeah.
The word's coming up.
Yes.
Stupid.
There's a subgenius revival coming up in Seattle.
April 19th.
Starring Dr.
Howell Robbins, Popas Lilith and Chicken Head, which apparently is a sort of a crazy person
fun collective from Seattle area.
What about Onan and Nenslo and whatnot?
Well, Onan, Nenslo and Reverend Whatnot are always up in the air.
And if they choose to.
A light, then so they will.
That would be delightful.
It would indeed.
It would certainly change the equation.
I, unfortunately, I wish I could join you.
I do, too.
I have.
They need me here.
Yes.
All right.
As they as they do.
I.
Yes.
Some of us now have to take our lumps for Bob.
Will you have one lump or two?
I'm sorry.
I'll take two of the blue lumps and three of the red lumps, please.
If you take the red lump, you'll wake up later and have nothing but a sour taste in the back
of your mouth.
But if you take the blue lump, well, they turn into Nixon and you live for one hundred
and twenty seven years in the White House and it turns to a red lump.
And then then you're in a bad movie about the science fiction kind of like in a toilet.
Somebody's battery.
And then it's a brown lump.
Dr. Drummond, didn't we come up with an endless set of variations on the if it's yellow, let
it mellow.
If it's brown, flush it down.
Right.
If it's if it's gray, less hay.
If it's purple, get a straw and slurp.
If it's if it's green, you've only been peeing.
Yeah, you've only been peeing.
If it's red, you'll soon be dead.
Yeah.
That's better than the one I had.
If it's orange, mix it in with the porridge.
I can't even continue because I keep thinking the ones I can't say.
Yeah.
If it's maroon, get a long spoon.
If it's black, smoke it like crack.
Yeah.
If it's stinkum, huff it like ginger.
Wait, stinkum isn't a color.
You have to think of color.
You know, out at Burning Man.
Once again, saying that again.
And at X Day.
I've learned that half of the...
Pseudiopters.
They now deliberately do not empty the chemical toilets since the use of jenkum was discovered.
And so half the time, the line, the long line is not for the toilet, but for the jenkum
in the toilet, which has built up over an entire week of a festival.
And you know, when you huff jenkum, you meet your ancestors.
Huff jenkum was a football player in the 1920s.
Yeah.
He and Newt Rockne were...
Big fan of the old Hucklebuck.
...Grant's bustard.
One of the first to dance the Hucklebuck in public with Mary Margaret O'Hare and Kathleen
O'Houlihan.
But those days are gone.
Those old gals.
Dinosaur and the Johto.
Those were some old gals.
The linotype machine and the four flushing clockwork hammocks.
The old Hucklebuck rocker.
All gone down history's corridors to a tiny white light with thin fades from our sight,
leaving us surrounded with mounds of junk.
And that reminds me, you know, they're going to make a movie of Cobalt 60.
The guys making The Watchmen right now who made the 300 before that.
Really?
A whole movie.
Of Cobalt?
Of Von Bodie's great old underground comic.
Yes.
Well, I'll be working with Mark Bodie, his son, and...
Did I see a mural by Mark Bodie on the streets of San Francisco?
Yes, he's very active and he has done such a mural just recently.
Meanwhile, the ghost of Von Bodie...
Coincidence or conspiracy?
...is just tuned in, saying, I hope they don't say anything too much.
I'm a little too distasteful about you.
There's going to be a show of Bodie Broad statues painted by different artists, including
myself and St. Paul Mavridis.
These statues will be put on display fairly soon, but unfortunately, I don't exactly know
where.
A lousy publicist.
So once again, I suggest do a search.
right type in doing advanced search type in Bodie broads now if you look at subgenius.com
events page you'll see that there's an art show in Los Angeles featuring featuring subgenius
Saints Byron Warner Gary Panter Robert Williams and the as yet unsaved Todd Shore along with a
whole bunch of other lowbrow high-class big names oh there's always art a plenty of brewing and a
percolating in the subgenius universe and nobody seems to make much of a dime off of any of it that
we know somebody somewhere these subgeniuses all have to die before their art monstrously
appreciates in value is that how it works that so they can't get any of the benefit of it that's
oh so
that's
how it works no wonder they're making all those Philip Dick and Vaughn Bodie movies now yeah it's
bad it's you know they go through those phases Bob by the way I'm gonna say in advance if you're
I'm trying to sell you something later talking to you at a party later tonight Bob took about
some of my hearing he why
that's so original and it actually is hard I have trouble if if I don't laugh at your jokes
and say huh a lot but I'm not playing anyway so that brings us to global warming
a really controversial subject.
Every time you bring up global warming in a really mixed crowd,
it's just this terrible fight,
because there's always this side that says,
oh, it's ridiculous, you know,
the planet's too huge for humans to make that much difference,
and then there's the air.
But...
Huh?
Global warming, and you've got, oh, the cauldron flame,
well, there's some...
I can't see very well either, Bleepo.
My mind-reading capabilities, by the way,
for you passive-aggressive people,
have just dwindled to nothing.
So you have to basically just say what you mean.
I'm sorry about that.
But really, the eye sage,
you don't have to bend down.
That just draws more attention.
Oh.
That draws more attention, too.
Because the TV viewers go,
oh, look, there's people, nice, polite,
tops of people's backs.
Um...
Friends...
It wasn't, uh...
Well, any Neanderthals among us would remember
that this spot right here had probably 80 feet of eye soap for it
not all that long ago.
Eye sages are really nasty,
and we're slowly entering another one.
You're going to wish we'd taken that global warming
a little more seriously when that next eye sage comes, friends.
You're going to be going,
why did I trade in my gas guzzler for that nice electric car?
I'm freezing to death.
Uh...
We needed that global...
That's, uh...
Actually, friends, I don't pretend to know anything
about global warming at all myself.
That's just...
There's so damn much smart scientific stuff you have to understand.
But I do know this.
I don't know about if there's global warming,
but I know that there is a global coolness deficit
that is damn serious.
Coolness is receding across the globe.
And, uh...
I mean, you know what I mean.
You can see it, you know.
It's just...
It's so painfully obvious.
There's less coolness everywhere.
I've had it up to here.
And I've also had it down to there, friends.
And I must say I prefer it down to there.
And believe it or not,
that was not said by Karl Marx or Groucho Marx,
but by Sri Baldin Lee Pramer, a subgenius,
who, uh...
teaches enlightenment.
Or false enlightenment, actually, is what he teaches.
And you can't even tell the difference, can you?
Yeah.
Madam Secretary, over the past month,
startling revelations have come forward
that specifically relate to your conduct prior to 9-11
and in the run-up to the war in Iraq.
A recently released study by the Nonpartisan Center for Public Intelligence,
the National Security,
revealed that you, along with President Bush,
and top administration officials,
made a total of 935 false public statements
in an orchestrated attempt to take this nation to war.
Here's a stack of these false statements right here.
All 935 of them.
This study has found that you, Madam Secretary,
made 56 false statements to the American people,
where you repeatedly pump up the case
that Iraq had weapons of mass destruction
and exaggerate the so-called relationship
between Iraq and al-Qaeda.
Madam Secretary, can you please tell us
that isn't it true that you had intelligence
that cast doubt on your repeated claims
that Iraq did not have weapons of mass destruction?
True, Congressman.
Iraq must have been hiding something,
something of a...
a...
Now, Congressman,
I did not take my integrity very seriously,
at any time.
And I make a statement that I knew to be false,
pump up,
and I want to go to war.
And so, I'm sorry.
Now, we have learned the intelligence assessments were wrong.
A non-transparent government,
I intend to,
I believe that I did,
put forward false information to the American people.
I simply asked if you had intelligence.
Intelligence.
I chose to use,
I'm sorry,
I chose to use them as a whole.
That was not right.
I am sorry.
It's very strange.
The intelligence was not right to claim, Congressman,
that there were other things that we somehow hid
from the American people.
It's simply...
Right.
This was above outright Rosenblatt.
Unless the aforementioned lies were cep.
echoes to that one governmental thing, and the lack of global coolness was being derided at
Winterstar Symposium. See roseandcomet.com for details. The Puzzling Evidence Show of February
2008 was that long and especially tasteful segment. You are now hearing Hour of Slack
from Church of the Subgenius, and if you want more about that mighty edifice, the Church of
the Subgenius, check out subgenius.com. The background music here is Rectoplasm from the
post-diluvial Lemurian era of their compositions. And now, a Lemur adventure story.
A cloud of dust and a hearty high over the lone deer.
Nowhere in the pages of history can one find a lone
bird.
The lone deer was camped in the fire from his six guns.
Well, who?
Did you see Sheriff Logan?
Me not know him.
Neither do I.
Young Jim Brandt turned up a lamp on a table.
That's too bad.
Yes, dear.
Look.
Oh.
There's a jackrabbit.
Jackrabbit.
Beautiful, in spite of the purpose to which it was put.
Oh, good.
Him dead came a zombie.
Dead.
A few days later, the loner and Tonto, whose trail of robbery and violence had led to the
Ledgeville area, prepared to strike again. Mounted on new Winchester and Colt 44s, the
taller of the pair was saying,
Tonto, somebody has drooping eyelids. They extend from one end of the territory to the
other. We'll adopt them on the trail about a mile from here.
Come on, sir.
The loner showed no tracks.
That's so, but what we do, you can change your appearance so you'll pass the
Indian on that easy.
On boardwalks, Indians were hard-eyed, thin-lipped, silent men. Some were loudmouthed braggarts,
but all had the vanity of their kind and could not forego a chance to stand against Tonto.
Keep us happy.
Look.
Yes, there's drooping eyelids.
What do you mean?
The Indian was grim.
Yes.
No.
Who is he?
The loner.
I am sir.
This is the loner.
Piss, piss, piss, well, I assume we all are.
Pistophocles, book two.
Pistophocles?
Pistophocles, yeah.
Testicles, the Tautologist.
Lesser known Greek philosopher.
Okay.
Wonderful.
It's too scary to contemplate.
I know, it's beyond belief.
Beyond belief.