Hey everybody!
Huh?
Moment of truth is here.
Really?
Yes.
No.
The Self Genius Power of Swag.
I'm gonna be sick.
Well how about that?
Oh god.
I've let us all down.
Wow.
My lighter went out and I thought I could frantically find one.
Your lighter?
My lighter.
Your lighter went out.
My soul mind, it's the Ikram Atman lighter.
How can you possibly combust the frop if you have no lighter?
I'd have to use my hoary breath, spelled H-O-A-R-A-E-Y, and then pronounce it slightly
sparingly.
I mean.
Well it's not a lisp but it's kind of close enough to pass mustard.
You can light that little pipe with your breath?
Yes.
And I can do all kinds of tricks.
I was thinking of joining the circus.
You know?
Why hide all this?
What would your act be?
Well that would be it.
It would be like a kind of surrealist thing where people would be compelled to wonder
what the hell is he doing?
It doesn't make any sense at all, you know?
And then I come out at the very end of it and I just ignite a bunch of extreme inflation
and leave the stage for permanently.
Dave, a lot of our friends and us have been doing that for years and we never managed
to make a living at it.
Sod Show marvels.
It just.
It used to pay back before they outlawed it.
But it's kind of hard to pay.
It's hard to get by on a Sideshow Marvels salary now.
I remember the days.
Last I heard.
I remember those not too distant days when you would like chew up a light bulb and a
banana and expect everything to come out correctly without singeing your posterior parts and
look where we've gone today.
Just like when Hitler was born.
I think you've got me confused with Andrew.
Well, my mentor, Andrew the Impaled.
Well, tell me.
See, mentor to me is a place near Cleveland.
It's kind of a high buck neighborhood, isn't it?
They wouldn't let us live there.
No, probably not.
But you're paying Cleveland High property.
No, I was talking about my mentor in light bulb eating, Andrew the Impaled.
Oh, he's from Pittsburgh.
Yeah, right.
And it's true.
If you eat a banana.
Before and after you eat the light bulb glass.
You might not die.
Yeah, you probably won't die.
It'll all just smoothly banana out.
Kind of a glassy little banana shaped thing will emerge.
Your son or daughter, as it were.
Whichever.
Oh, you're calling the the the flotation device that emerges after the massacre.
After the meal.
Yeah.
After the meal is either your mommy or your daddy.
My son.
My son hated when I would.
I'd come out of the bathroom and go, I just passed another one of your little brown brothers.
My kid hated that too.
He did not like that.
He didn't think it was funny.
When my old man said it to me, I didn't think it was funny either.
I hated him for it.
Just think, Stang.
You're calling your.
I have a phone line.
You're saying your brother to a manure wagon.
It's a German word.
No.
Misquoting.
Now what?
Schopenhauer.
Oh, Schopenhauer.
I've been trying to study Schopenhauer.
You know, the German philosopher was real difficult.
Schopenhauer.
Well, actually, I'm kind of confused.
Now, who's the 12 tone German composer who does anti music?
Well.
I thought that was Stoppenhouser or Schopenhouser or Wolfenstein.
Schopenhauer.
Yeah.
One of those.
Was there two of them?
Was one of them a philosopher and the other one Schopenhauer?
For all I know, they're both the same.
I don't know.
I don't know anything.
I'm all mixed up.
Dave, I think I'm losing it, man.
Honestly.
You've already lost it.
I've been cooped up.
I'm not.
I'm just so long and so dark here.
Everything's so old.
You're in the closet with the light turned off and that's why it's so dark where you
are.
It has nothing to do with the exterior shape of the universe at large.
I'm penned in.
I'm trapped, man.
I can't get out into the universe.
I'm stuck.
Being a penned in has no excuse for any other kind of articulation if you ask me.
I want to live, man.
I want to get loose.
I want to move.
I want to fly.
I want to fly away.
I'm very—
Bad chance of that, Stangy.
Well, because I have to just—
All moan on all you must and all you may.
Nothing's going to change me in any way.
Everything's just going to grind us into the dirt like a lowly sack of smoke.
My guru—
It's going to pound us and pound us and pound us until we no longer exist.
Really?
Really.
I hope not, but that's what I've been doing all this time.
been warned of the last 25 years i think we we've been warned of and we've both been warning of for
the last i'm afraid it's more like 40 years dave maybe 50 oh god man i keep reading these magazine
articles in the uh uh retired person's journal about great rock stars and movie stars and they
their career has spanned 50 years and i think to myself wait a minute that they didn't even come
out with their first album till i was 30 what are they telling me they're trying to tell you things
that are not good for your health that's the first thing you have to remember is
all these messages from other people because it's not going to be good because people complain all
the time i don't give a shit anymore yeah yeah yeah so i think there's that that's true
um i think i have no idea what i'm watching bruce look it's awesome usually you get 17
films a year that uh co-writer kim scott amazing and you see how busy he is
at videotape last year yeah
if i was editing a horror movie eh
it was good
i'm kind of carefully
he had the
time
and
from the Crimea.
So she's hot to detect her surface valve.
Right.
Probably not my type.
The Playboy type, not my type.
No, not my type.
The dumpy, bespectacled, middle-aged ones, my type.
My type too.
Well, I mean, let's be realistic.
We're in our 60s or something like that.
Let's just be realistic.
Anyway, I don't want to be accused of some kind of Me Too thing.
I didn't do it.
I didn't do any of it.
I never even thought about it.
Well, I thought about it.
Yeah.
But I didn't do any of it.
I was always too polite.
And my friends kept telling my male friends, said,
Stang, don't you get it?
No doesn't mean no.
No means keep going.
Until I say, well, just keep going.
And I thought, well, you know what?
That just doesn't seem right.
Yeah.
I sort of halfway tried it once.
I said, okay, I'll give you a ride if you give me a kiss.
And the girl looked at me like I was the most disgusting pervert she'd ever seen.
And I don't blame her a bit.
But honest to God, I was just, I was doing what?
What my male peer group was telling me was okay.
And I went to the same kind of school as Brett Kavanaugh.
So I really, I didn't go to the same kind of school as Brett Kavanaugh.
But I had an interesting thing happen to me in the liquor store.
There's a, there's a liquor store lady there.
And she's rather attractive, but I'm not, you know, trying to get into her
gumshoes or her Bollywink or any of those other private parts.
But anyway, I'd noticed I'd seen her in my neighborhood.
I said, oh, do you live near me?
And I went on about paranoid look on her face.
Like, why do you want to know where I live?
And I got the baddest vibe from that.
I've had, you were just being friendly, but she got the wrong idea.
I was like drooling around the corner, you know, where you go, which
house is yours and made me cry.
Well, it's a tender.
Young.
Babe.
It's a tricky, tricky situation.
I remember one time my, my good buddy and over man, Dr.
Philo Drummond.
Uh, he w he came to an X day drill one time and just like a werewolf.
Uh, well, he went driving around with his video camera poking out the window
because this was fun.
It was being, well, it still is being held at this hippie campgrounds and
there's.
Colorful tents and colorful artwork and stuff.
And he was just driving randomly drunk with a, did you hear my dog?
Bart just in or shake his collar.
Anyway, Philo Philo, uh, was just randomly videotaping the scenery.
Well, suddenly the campground gets called from a hideous old woman who
says this man been videotaped me because I was walking around with topless with my.
Things.
My, my, uh, pendulous is out.
Right.
Her pendulum.
Yeah.
And, and this man, I saw a car just drive by with video cameras.
You need to sue him and arrest him and kick him out.
She was so vain that she thought he even saw her.
And, you know, I swear, I think that same person complained later on at a
starwood or something, because I was walking around with the camera.
Uh,
at one of Chaz's crazy sex orgy parties.
And she was thinking, oh, the only reason that man's got cameras
to film me with my pendulous.
My 59 year old giant pendulous.
We just, well, in the south of Spain and other places where we come from,
we just call them gigantic basoons.
And everybody seems to know.
The zoom.
Yeah.
And there are Broncos also because they are related to an
exterior.
Form of lung, like a block, like broccoli is.
So this is, they can get your vegetables 10 times a day, each and every way.
If you just suckle like a young babe to a mother's breast.
See today, I met two women who were both breastfeeding, like it was very
important and they got, they have things now like, well, the one lady who quit
to get a cheaper job, but she was still more friendlier than the other people
and stuff like that every day at 10 o'clock and at two o'clock, she would go
to a special room.
And collect her milk from her bosom.
And that's what they fulfill her child's Bubba with was mother's milk.
And it's been two years now.
And she's still doing the mother's milk routine.
I'm wondering if it's all right.
Don't interfere with parenting.
That's something I learned that the don't, even if I know people, I knew a lady who
was breastfeeding her six year old.
Okay.
She happened to be a, yes I did.
She happened to be a very traditional Lakota native woman.
I hope I'm using the correct terminology.
Very sweet.
Gave my wife and I a star blanket that she made.
And a wonderful milk cake.
I guess she thought we were nice, but she, no, she didn't give us any of her milk, but
she, yeah, her kid was upright and running around and shooting play guns and he was
still getting, you know, breastfed.
Now I thought that was a little weird, but as a parent, I've learned that you don't
tell parents how to parent.
You just don't, they're going to do it their way, no matter what.
And no one knows what goes on behind her.
They're going to close doors.
They could anger and obsequiously come and anger on you and enjoy the rump diminish slash
you like a dog.
Oh, people, people, people that have never been parents blame parents for their kids.
They're the most opinionated.
The ones who haven't had kids.
No kidding.
Yeah.
The ones who never had kids.
They know exactly how to.
They know everything about it and why there should be or should not be abortion.
You noticed that.
They probably never even had sex to begin with and wonder what to do afterwards.
You noticed that, did you?
As a father.
I noticed that guy I was telling you about earlier today who was in a diner usually calling
people bad names and stuff like that.
Yeah.
You told me that.
Well, I just forgot the rest of the story, which was even funnier.
Well, it was a fellow customer of a diner that you frequent and he was loudly and belligerently,
uh, yeah.
He was, uh, proclaiming the N word about black people and he was loudly and belligerently
even insulting your ethnicity, the Italians talking about dagos and wops and, uh, so forth.
Pardon my language.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You got that right.
Where I come from, we didn't have Italians, so we didn't have any slur names for them.
So you made soup instead.
Yeah.
Well, we picked on everybody that we had around here.
Germans, Mexicans, of course, uh, and needless to say, black people.
When I was growing up.
Oh, I know what the fifties were like and I know what the early sixties were like and
I'm very, very sorry that our present government is trying to return us to that time.
It does seem like it.
It does indeed.
It seems like they're trying to return us to around 1939 and not this country.
But another highly technically advanced country in Europe.
That's why he's been lately, he's been forced to calling himself hair chancellor.
Now what the hell does that mean?
I mean, is that an American word or is that too feisty for a hair chancellor?
Does it have something to do with his haircut or?
It doesn't matter.
That's the horrible nightmarish thing.
It doesn't matter what he does, whatever he does.
They love it.
They eat it up.
They bend over, unzip their pants, pull them down and say, come on and give me more.
I'm sorry, but that's, that's the way I see it.
That's the story today.
I just heard something.
Somebody say, well, if he lies every day, what, what lie did he say today?
And I couldn't remember.
He had me on his stump.
You know what I mean?
There was surrounded by searchlights and Nazi soldiers, everything.
There's too many.
Even it was like, well, which one do I land on?
I'm a self made millionaire.
I made my own.
I'm I'm not, I wasn't just some, some, uh, fund kid.
I, I, I made my way on my own.
Well, do you hear he's, he's, he's friends with Prince, Prince Zalman.
Is that the one who has a real bad dementia?
Somebody in the, Prince Valiant with the bad haircut.
That's what they used to call him Prince Valium sometimes.
Cause he was scared.
Now who, what?
Prince Valium.
He was a, he was a sore begotten son who never learned to trot and so on and so forth.
Forever.
He was just no good.
That's the only way around it.
But I was talking about something else.
Yeah.
So was I.
How do we even, how do we even know what the show is about, Dave?
How do we.
How do we focus.
Focus.
If we can't take a joke.
Oh my God.
I heard the most horrible, horrible subgenius joke today.
Let's hear it or see it.
See what's coming next.
I can't say it at all on the broadcast radio because it's a variation of our church's, the church of the subgeniuses, most sacred motto.
The one that has the F word in it.
Yes, blank them if they can't.
Right, blank them if they can't take a joke.
It's a variation on that.
And of course, I'm really polite.
So it's hard for me.
And the minute I heard it, I said, don't ever say that on your radio show because it was the younger subgeniuses with their younger podcast radio shows.
It was Reverend Fid Chooley and Reverend Fox and Reverend Cat Feather with the Time for the Show show.
And he, Fid, I think, uttered the phrase, F word them if they can't escape.
We were thinking about the Kavanaugh hearings and so forth.
But it was one that, and see, Daryl went and did it.
I just went and uttered that phrase.
And.
But that's not where we're coming from.
That's not what we mean, friends.
Really?
We want freedom and peace for everyone.
For every living being.
Not necessarily beings like pork and beans.
Human beings.
Yeah, human beings.
Like French style.
French style beans.
Or Szechuan style.
That's another flavor we could have too.
We could have five different flavors.
Think of it, Stang.
And of course, we'll have natural chocolate.
Every day of the week, it'll be available.
And any other times during the lunar holidays, we'll come down and have our own festival.
You know?
I dream of those days to come.
You mean you're dreaming of the future?
Halcyon, Halleycon days to come.
However you say that.
Why is this fast forward button?
How do you say that?
Say Halcyon or Halcyon or Halcyon.
I guess.
I don't listen to the radio or watch TV, so I don't know how things are pronounced.
I just read stuff.
For five years when I was a kid, I thought the word examine was examine.
I read flighty, highbrow books by H.G. Wells and Jules Verne when I was 10 years old.
And they were always examining.
I think I was probably 13 before I realized what they meant was examine.
Yeah, I had similar things.
I read the classics at an early age and all that stuff, too.
And I always had one particular pet word.
I don't know.
Somebody might have even told you I get obsessive compulsive thing when I'm typing or writing or something like that.
I'll misspell something.
I know I misspelled it.
No way.
And tell myself that the next time around, I won't misspell it.
And I keep misspelling it over and over again the same way.
Now, that's a sure sign that somebody's not minding the store.
Your mind is not minding the story.
My mind is not my mind.
Not if mine.
Those were the days, my friend.
I thought you'd stop saying that once in a while, but instead you have to keep on reminding us.
My mind is not my mind.
It's not my own.
It's a really old subgenius saying.
I have no mind.
My mind is not my mind.
Cast off the imperial brains of normalcy.
What?
My mind is not my own?
My mind is not my mind.
Ha ha.
See, now that has a little bit more kind of like a silly twist to it.
I don't know if you'd call it a post-nuptial entrail device.
It has to be said in a high voice.
My mind is not my mind.
And then there would be an answer like a choral, like apostrophe or whatever his name was, or antipasto.
Like in those Greek plays about the frogs and stuff like that.
That would be the chorus.
It would answer back, my mind is not my mind.
Like that.
And everybody.
We'd get real goosebumps and quivers running up and down their spines.
My mind is not my mind.
See, now you sound like Dostoevsky or Schoenberg.
Schoenberg.
That's the poet of magnificence of the 12-tone music.
Yeah, not Stockhausen or Schoenberg or Schopenhauer.
Schopenhauer.
Philosopher.
You're a nine-to-five man.
He was my favorite fly character back in the days
when I used to dress up like a pimp and soul.
Man, the girls would see me coming.
They'd just rush to my arms and say stuff to me and everything.
I couldn't often understand what the hell they were talking about.
But boy, I made quite an impression.
And just think of today's modern days.
I'm taking all kinds of selfies of myself,
and I'm JPG-ing them right back home.
Immediately.
Oh, I can hear that little froggy right now.
Yeah, I hear it too.
Now, what's that?
Is that a Buddhist gong bell?
It's very faint.
I think it's a frog.
Well, I hope it's like a Rastafari set or one of them guys.
I'm trying to get my...
That's quite a melodic.
That's quite a melodic frog.
There we go.
Oh, my God.
There's the frog.
For the last five minutes, I have to admit to you, Dave,
I've been half listening, half participating in the show,
and half trying to operate this DVD player to run my background CDs.
And it's not cooperating with me.
It just keeps sticking on this...
I don't know what this background...
You can't hear it.
But it was Captain Beefheart Instrumentals.
I had 20 minutes of Captain Beefheart Instrumentals
followed by a five-minute recording of my little new pit bull dog, Claudia,
licking her fundament.
It was just a really unique sound,
and I wanted to share that with the audience.
Okay.
I can always do that in editing, I suppose.
But it's distressing to me that I've lost control of my faculties here
at Tarzan's radio station,
my home studio,
where I can only take one caller,
and it's you.
I've been thinking...
Why do you call it Tarzan, anyway?
I'm trying to figure that out.
That doesn't make a lot of sense to me.
Well, Dave,
you've seen it.
It's like this 20-year-old radio shack mixer
and microphones that have windscreens
that are eaten away by disease.
The foam rubber is just, you know...
It's coming out.
It's putting pox in them.
And, yeah, it's all analog.
It's not digital.
And it's old.
And we're...
Even older.
Much, much older than any of this equipment.
Which just is so sad.
But, hey, most people don't live as long as we have.
It seems like.
Oh, my God.
Dave, I've got yet more of my old friends
who are coming down with the horrible cancers
and the diseases and all the crap
that...
That...
That afflicts large mammals.
Not just people.
I've never licked a large mammal in my whole life.
It's a miracle that we're still alive.
It is a damn miracle.
Yeah, but I don't understand why you said
I had to lick an animal and I never did.
You know I never did.
No, you misunderstood.
I'm saying I wish...
I wish you'd had the opportunity
to lick an animal like I have.
And the audacity to think of it beforehand.
Oh, my God.
You know, when a dog licks your neck, you just want to lick her back.
Well, if it's a girl dog, you wouldn't want to do that with a boy dog.
If you're a boy, unless you're gay, then you're probably having more fun than anybody.
I wish I knew, but it's too late for me.
I wish you did, too.
Maybe in subgenius heaven, we'll find out how fun it is to be bisexual, for instance.
Because I don't really have any way of knowing that in this life.
I'm just old. I'm just old. I'm stuck in my ways. I'm stuck.
Then there was quadrosexuals. I can't remember.
I can't either.
I can't even begin. How do you even approach that?
You didn't dally around. You were like me.
You believed in medium relationships, much like a steak.
I was so square. Oh, my God.
I was this long-haired hippie, and I was so much more square and reserved
than any of my employers who were burr-cut Texans
that were...
Cheating on their wives and bragging about it and showing us Polaroids of it.
And I just...
Everything is upside down.
I don't think the Baptists are always that honest.
I just don't know how to put it.
That could be what they say in the Me Too movement.
They used to say, you know, take a man and hang him upside down.
It all looks like the same thing.
No, wait a minute.
Did I say that right?
No. I'm not sure. I don't know.
But...
It was hashtag...
Once dot, dot, dot, enough.
That's kind of like our guiding light.
We didn't want to procreate and flat slate with every other abnormal person there is that walks the earth.
Oh, I did.
When I was younger. Oh, my God.
Oh, when I was younger, yeah.
I feel like now that I'm so old that I've lost most of my chemicals,
it's like I've surfaced from a swamp.
I've been...
I've been living in a dim, dark swamp underwater my whole life.
And I...
You know, all I could think about was, you know.
And then I guess my testosterone levels dropped a lot.
And it's as if I'm a brilliant mathematician by comparison now, you know.
But have no numbers to deal with, right?
Well, sure, I can deal with anything.
I don't have the poison of the doonads anymore.
I was poisoned for most of my life.
You sound like some famous 19th century yogi.
If we do too much doodledoodle, we will not be able to fly.
Right.
If you live in lust, you will not be free.
You have to free yourself from desire to truly rise above and all that.
Well, I don't have any choice.
I would just as soon wallow in the earth plane and the mud and the sex.
But I've just gotten so damn old, I don't think about it as much.
Me too.
I kind of miss it.
But at the same time, I feel like I've finally achieved a slightly higher level of intelligence.
Because the poison...
The poison of the flunads is no longer affecting me like it used to.
It's not dictating how I direct my attention.
It's sad.
Once again, Dave, here we are, a couple of old guys talking about our physical limitations
on a show called The Hour of Slack that's supposed to make everybody feel like slack.
Well, the old ones...
Probably do.
Because they're going, well, I sure hear you, buddy.
And they're a lot of our audience because baby boomers are in the majority for a short time here.
Wow, you certainly said a mouthful.
I have no idea what the hell you're talking about.
But that was a lot of words jumbled up together.
Well, what I was saying is us old people got to stick together.
But at the same time, I have to hope that the young people are...
gleaning some tiny bit of warning about what is to come.
And the true message is live your life to the fullest as much as you can while you've still got it.
Because it's going to dwindle away and you're going to shrivel up.
So go for the gusto.
Don't get locked into some slave job where that's...
That's...
All your best energy is locked into serving some other master.
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
I don't know how to tell people to do that.
I had to serve masters in nine to five jobs for most of my career.
But you never know when some crazy thing you did when you were a kid might catch on.
And pay the rent in a crappy apartment for one person.
But what's important, you know?
Slack or things?
Why not both, of course?
We must say, why not both?
I'd love to have Slack and things.
But that equals $1,000.
I mean, that's how I get...
You know, we're doing this radio show that at least 1,000 people download every month.
That's not very big numbers.
But...
Well, I wish they would go and get Neighbor World by Dave.
I wish they would, too.
We're doing it on equipment that costs a total of $40.
And...
Neighbor World was done on equipment that cost a total of $5.
That means it's even better.
So, friends, you need to get out and think about Dave's book, Neighbor World.
By the way, my sister has Neighbor World.
She just got her...
I ordered it for her.
And she's finishing up Neal Stephenson's Baroque trilogy.
Which she loved.
And the next thing she's going to read is Neighbor World.
Well, that's nice.
And she'll probably like it.
Most people do.
Well, if they can read.
That cuts out about two-thirds of our audience, at least.
Some people have their eyeballs and their ear balls disconnected,
so they can only hear things that other people can normally see.
Why not both?
If only we could all do both.
That's synergy.
Synesthesia.
Like our friend Dr. Sinister named his shows.
You mix up your...
You take enough LSD or have enough post-traumatic stress syndrome,
and you develop an ability or a disability to...
Actually, disability.
To mix up sound.
Sight.
Smell.
And feeling.
So that you smell colors and hear pain.
That's the way you want it.
That's the way you'll get it every time.
Guaranteed.
There's no round-the-block roofers.
There's no engine capacitors.
There's nobody trying to get away with nothing.
Nobody.
This is the real, real, real, real, real...
Real, real, real, real...
Oh, man.
Yeah, that.
Yeah.
That.
There.
Hey, can you hear my dogs?
No.
Yeah.
Yeah, they sound like they're in heat already.
I've been...
I've been sitting here with background music on,
but Buddy and Claudia want to play fight,
and they're dueling.
They're doing that thing where they pretend,
okay, I'm going to bite your face.
No, you're not.
Yes, I am.
And then they go chasing around.
Okay, listen.
Well, that's very playful and puppish
and quite exuberant.
As I told you last week, Dave,
I've been talking to the dogs.
It's just...
They're my...
I've been having long conversations
with these animals that can't answer me
and don't understand a word I'm saying.
I think they're like that.
Much like our audience, probably.
Well, they understand a lot more than you think.
Well, they feel the vibes of friends.
Right.
We start right off with the vibes.
They're much better at that than we are anyway.
Yeah.
We can hardly, hardly imagine
how far they can go with vibes.
Oh.
They can probably smell a difference in your skin
when you're uptight or nervous or frightened
or something like that.
I swear to God,
I think they can tell from the smell of my skin
whether I'm planning to go to the fight.
or do something fun.
Yeah, it's weird how they read your mind
and smell you at the same time.
Yeah, they really do.
Don't you wish we could do that as human...
as subgeniuses?
If we could just get on the bus
and when a guy says,
$0.50, please,
you just go...
and you can tell this guy's lying
to you it's really $1.27
or some other...
You know, we can imagine all kinds of...
And then you lift your leg
and pee on the thing where you put your coins in.
Right, and you make a face like you're chuckling,
like...
Then they kick you off the bus
and you have to walk to your job.
Yeah.
That's the problem.
It's fascism, man.
Fascism is coming back.
They're screwing us up.
They're taking away all our freedoms
in the name of freedom.
The name of the American flag in the Bible
and freedom,
they're wrecking our freedoms.
To not have babies, for instance.
Yeah, who wants them anyway?
Everybody's got special babies.
Lots of people want babies.
I love babies.
I want the subgeniuses to have a lot more babies.
If they're ready for it.
I'm not trying to tell every millennial
that they should do the thing
that they're going to be terrible at
because of the destruction to their instincts,
but...
the ones who still have instincts,
we need to stick together.
Somebody's got to keep the human race going
besides the idiocracy people.
Yeah, because they're saying
that most of the men's testosterone levels
are extremely low.
We could have whole bamboos and fortresses
and forests full of people that have no...
get up and go, if you know what I'm saying.
That would be a horrible thing
because that...
I don't know why it would be a horrible thing
because I personally could use less human beings around me.
But that's just my own personal thing.
I'm not one of those people
who want to push calling the herd
or calling the herd
or down anybody's throat
because I don't believe in that kind of stuff
because I'd be one of the first ones that they'd call.
Right.
And it wouldn't be on a telephone either.
No, we'd be...
Yeah, they'd take us in the...
Well, not the first sweep.
Probably the third sweep.
There's people with much higher profile.
They'd take us.
And us, they'd take first.
Yeah, their names are...
We'd probably actually...
We'd be more like in the 18th sweep.
Yeah.
We'd be thinking we were going to be okay.
Oh, good.
They only took the Jews and the queers
and the registered Democrats this time.
But any minute now, it's going to be us.
Yep.
The undefinables.
Okay, next sweep.
Those who didn't fit into any category.
Killed them all.
Or at least, you know, put them to work in Trump's stop.
Yeah.
I think I'd trade a cholera blanket.
I don't think we'd merit...
I'd trade a cholera blanket for that.
We probably wouldn't merit execution
in the New World Order, but...
But who can tell?
You know we'd be in the re-education camps.
Yeah.
For all the law.
I don't want to be re-educated
because I don't like being educated to begin with.
So harmful.
It made me feel...
The punishment permeated my entire body.
I know.
Like, I'd get there in the morning,
8.30, 7 o'clock in the afternoon,
or whatever number it was,
and I'd just, like, feel like
they were like these slingy bats
and other things.
All kinds of congruent creatures
hanging around me,
trying to square me up
and freak me out and stuff.
If you had never educated yourself so well, Dave,
you'd probably be happy to show up at work at 8.30.
It would make sense.
It would all add up.
It would be a simple answer
to a complicated question.
I'd feel happy for a half hour
after getting paid
and then go back to feeling like crap again,
and that would be wonderful.
Just simply wonderful.
Yeah, but you're doomed.
Because you know too much, Dave.
You know too much.
You're like a sub-genius.
It may not all be right,
but there's a lot of it that you know.
Yep.
It's just like Stephen Kavanaugh's notebook
or his catalog,
whatever he was keeping there.
His calendar.
Don't forget to pinch Betty on the rectum
and give her a kiss.
diciendo Duet.
Get into a tic baccharge.
an argument with her father
about being physical,
you know,
remind us like that,
like ooh, my head's not screwed on right.
I hate when they do that.
Especially when they have a role
like Russian egg baskets
that just keep getting
smaller and smaller the more resume.
The sad thing is,
I have a calendar kind of like Cavanagh's
from my high school years, my college years.
I kept my calendars, and I did keep some rudimentary notes,
and a lot of them are kind of like his.
They were like, how much drugs did I take that weekend?
How high did I get?
How much beer or alcohol of whatever?
How stupid did I get?
Yet I even filmed some of it sort of in Super 8 film,
and all I can think is, thank God the Internet wasn't around then.
Thank God.
Thank God and Bob and Gobs and all of the euphemisms I can think of to thank.
Thank the euphemisms.
The fates, luck, and everything.
The Internet didn't get invented
until I was a kid.
I was in my 30s.
Thank the euphemisms for that.
Man, because otherwise I'd be guilty, guilty, guilty.
So would you, Dave.
You would have splurted out wrong things.
I know.
I have for a long time.
I made a 16-millimeter, 45-minute movie when I was in college.
It's the most.
It's the most un-PC thing hippies ever saw.
It was kind of influenced by underground comics and punk.
It was just pre-punk.
But in some ways it was a rebellion against the peace and love stuff
because I saw the flaws in the peace and love philosophy,
which is that the war and hate won't go away.
You can't wish it away.
And I,
I had a vision of the future as an 18-year-old
that I articulated,
I must say, fairly well in an underground movie
before I quit trying to make movies
because they're too expensive for me.
Well, I did it.
When I was about the same age and the same period of time,
I wrote me a play, too,
and it was actually performed.
And the teacher thought,
Oh, that's very imaginative, Dave.
Yeah.
I got that.
Same reaction.
And some of the names that I thought were like monster names
and were real mean and everything,
I thought I dreamed up people.
It's common usage now,
and a bunch of that stuff is, too,
especially the part I stole from you.
Ahead of your time, Dave.
Ahead of your time.
It's like Bob himself.
He's a head,
a single, floating, disembodied head
of his time.
Lucky for Bob,
he's timeless.
You and me,
we're 65 and older.
Yeah.
And doing our best.
We have to sit in a special choo-choo closet
where they have the raising nets.
Oh, we're going to have coffee at 7 o'clock in the morning
because we never sleep anymore.
Just sit around waiting for the old examiner to come by
and scythe them asunder.
You know what I mean?
No.
Oh, I ain't got nothing to live for.
This is the old,
old woman died,
and I just have to go and have coffee
with the railroad guys every morning at 10.
Well, yeah.
Actually, I can understand that.
They never get enough pi, either.
Even if it is square.
You know, like the number...
Is there ever enough pi?
Can there ever be enough pi?
R squared.
That's the root number
that everybody's so fondled of.
Pi R squared.
Oh, my God.
While we were doing this show...
The dog urinated on your shoe.
Yeah, he kind of did.
He ate the fancy doggy bed
that my son gave us.
My son had a giant dog.
It died.
His new dog didn't want to sleep on the dead dog's bed,
and we ended up with this giant...
dog bed in the house.
It's great, but...
I see you...
Buddy just disemboweled it
while I was doing this stupid show.
Right behind me.
I mean, right behind me he was doing that
because I had music...
Background music was up, see?
I didn't hear anything.
I'm like deaf.
I'm like...
Bud, knock it off, man.
Yeah.
I hope I haven't been torturing you here.
It's too much because...
No, no, it's not...
I have the phone...
No.
Not right now, it's not,
but earlier I could hear...
Oh, listen.
In the background.
You can't hear it, Dave.
But what the audience was hearing...
For a second there.
It's gone now.
What the audience was hearing
was the licking of the fundament
of the pit bull by the pit bull.
Oh, that is great stuff, man.
It was urgently...
licking its exit wound
last night.
The sound was so vivid
that I felt like I had to record it.
I put my phone cam down there.
It was just a dark picture.
But you can hear the licking
and the urgent grunting.
Because don't you wish
you could do that, Dave?
Yes, I can.
I was doing an imitation of many dogs
that I've known in my pretty nature.
Yeah, that was actually
a pretty good copy.
But see, because I can't control my...
After the lick, you know,
you get a lick in there
and then you get a little chew.
Oh, there we go.
Now I got it back.
Well, I told you
that was going to happen
if you continued to bother her
about, you know what, you know...
The audience, but not you,
can hear the licking of the...
of the dog's own...
Imperfection.
...itchy part, I guess.
Itchy part.
Well, if that doesn't sound
like a sign out of me,
I don't know what...
Well, you can...
Yeah, it is kind of.
You can hear a faint grunting.
It's a good thing.
She grunts in the most faint and...
I can hear...
I could hear some licking there
for a while right now.
There's no way you can hear
what I'm playing in the background.
Is it going like
click, click, click, click, click, click?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I can hear that.
You must have the monitor up too loud.
Can you hear any music
when I play music?
I just heard some music just before
and as you said that,
it was...
No, I can't hear that.
Oh, but damn.
Well, you know,
they updated the iPhone.
Maybe it changed something.
Anyway, yes, you're right, Dave.
We've actually been talking
for not quite a full hour
and that means we're free.
We could be free
from Bob's slavery
once again for a little while
if we want.
Yeah.
If we want to be.
Well, I think I'm just going to go
and sit my posterior down
and take a relaxing break.
Perhaps you can get this
frop whistle to work.
You know, my problem is
once we finish recording
one of these things,
I can't...
I always think...
I always think,
well, that was pretty bad.
And then I get home
and listen back to it
and go,
oh, that's not so bad.
No, it's usually...
It's not...
No.
What?
Did I say that?
I don't remember that.
Well, that's pretty good.
If I listen to Dave,
I thought he was making nonsense
when he was doing it in real time.
Now when I play the tape back,
he sounds like James Joyce
doing beautiful word splicing
and cross juxtaposition of meaning.
Yeah.
Like Fireside Theater
or Monty Python
just off the top of his head.
I am Fireside Monty Python
and all them guys.
You know, Monty Python's
been around for 50 years today.
Yep.
50 years.
I seem to remember
seeing him when I was 20.
What does that say about me?
We're old, man.
Just think of the cheese shop
and the guys playing...
and the bouzouki in there.
One of these days,
we're going to have
our own little cheese shop.
Just like Mom wanted us to.
She'd look,
well, you're good old John
and I want you to own
the whole store.
We got all kinds of Philly Bertons
and Scrammin' Bears
and all kinds of wonderful cheese
for you to enjoy
along with that shiplick,
slap it,
let's call it,
your wife.
Yeah, except the store
is always out of all those things.
Well,
that's because, you know,
they just don't want to obey
our beloved leader.
That's why we have a beloved leader
is so that we can obey him or her.
I thought it was so
we could disobey him.
We can neither disobey
nor disallow the leader.
We can only accept the leader
as our leader.
And his name is Bob
in quotes.
Quote, B-O-B, unquote, Bob.
Capital B.
Not like, not like.
There you go, capital B.
But not all caps.
It's not,
he's not the Facebook Bob
who's just B-O-B in all caps.
That's the idiot Bob.
That's the pink Bob.
The true Bob is,
quote,
Big B, little O, little B,
end quotes.
That's it.
Yep.
There's no other way
and anything else is fake.
That's sub...
And what else could you want?
Everything's right there
in that solemn package
right for you.
There it is.
You don't need anything
more than that face.
It's a face-based religion.
The face of Bob.
There but for the face
of Bob Goy.
See, the Goy is another part.
Have you ever noticed, like,
if you look into Bob's eyes
for long enough
and you go,
hey, I, I, I, I, I.
If you look in Bob's eyes
long enough,
you see your own death.
You see how you're gonna die.
So don't do it.
It's too heavy for me, man.
I didn't want to say that
because, you know.
You don't want to do it.
Well...
I did.
I know you didn't,
but you couldn't speak
coherently for weeks afterwards.
Those were our best shows.
Yeah, but from what
I heard from Wheeler,
you were kind of hard
to be around.
You had your hair
frazzled out like Einstein.
That's normal.
You had like...
Yeah, to whom?
Her.
Oh.
Yeah, I forgot that part.
I guess it's not important.
I miss her so much.
She still has to be in Ohio
and I have to be here in Texas
until she finishes her job
and I finish mine,
whichever comes first.
I miss our mom.
Our old mom.
She was like a guiding,
positive beacon.
A beacon of positivity.
And we used to call her
Sweet Mammy Jane
or something like that.
Well, we still do.
She's still alive,
but she's 88
and I want her back here.
I need to go back there first,
pack up a moving van
with what's left of our stuff,
which actually includes
the cassette tapes
of all hours of slack
that were done on cassette
for 20 years.
And then bring...
Them and that
and all that stuff back here
with the dogs.
And then everything will be fine.
I just know it will.
I know it will once that happens.
But in the meantime,
it's just...
Where's the...
The hour of slack
just isn't the same
without Princess Wee's
lilting laughter
in the background.
Right?
Or the foreground either.
Normally, we would have her...
She'd be cackling.
And we have no laugh track.
Or we would say something
so oblique
that neither one of us would be like,
wow.
Man, it just ain't fair.
It ain't...
It is.
It's all so oblique.
What is fair, Stang?
There's no fairness anywhere
in the doctrine
of today's modern agendas.
That's my...
There's no fairness.
Everything is skiltered
and quandered
and stranded in one direction
for the ruling class.
The 1%.
The ones who...
Not the petty...
Very bourgeoisie.
But the acclimated clamboats
at the very, very top of the heap.
Yeah, and that's who
the poor people vote for.
Well, because they're all
so much alike.
Like, just think,
when you were three years old,
you already had $200,000
in the bank.
By the time you were 21,
you already had $200,000
in the bank.
What are they talking about?
Or maybe I got those figures wrong.
No, you're...
I was just reading
similar figures
for...
for our president
who worked his way up
from his bootstraps
with $100,000
when he was five years old
and a million dollars
when he was eight
and so forth
because tax fraud
and...
Yeah, that's...
Okay.
And with that, friends,
it's the end
of another hour of Slack,
I guess,
of subgenius.com.
That's the only thing
you need to remember,
but you need to remember
that subgenius
is spelled without an O.
subgenius.com.
The show is the hour of Slack.
There are other subgenius shows,
so don't get hooked on this one.
And...
Yeah, you could get sick
pretty easy.
You don't watch...
Look at us.
Just look at us.
Just mirror hundreds of him.
Yeah, just look at us.
Mirror shadows
for shadowiness.
Yeah.
Previous incantations.
Shadows for former shadowiness.
You...
Hey, you damn kids.
Get off my lawn.
You're gonna...
You'll find out if you're lucky
to live long enough
to be measurable.
You kids...
Damn kids.
Okay, Dave.
Okay, I'll go check some squids now.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
I know what I'm gonna do.
Whip that dog for biting up his...
eating his own bed.
Okay, Dave.
See you later.
Okay, you got it.
Mm.
Wow, he hung up.