You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to...
The subgenius.
Hour of sweat.
What?
Actually, the cattle mutilation, according to Tom Warner,
were done by the same two old guys who did all the crop circles.
The 13,000 crop circles.
Praise the old guys.
They practiced.
Praise the two old British farts.
They practiced in the U.S. on their vacations doing the 20,000 cattle mutilation.
And all they used was a board and a piece of string.
Back to the full hell of riotous radio picnic.
Back to your tangent mouth, doctor.
They already talked about liquid chicken in the last three hours.
Well, you know, chicken gristle.
Chicken gristle is the...
The important cornerstone of today's financial markets.
But something more important historically should be discussed.
This is the 23rd of January.
And, of course, on the 22nd of January,
the Bourbon King Louis XVI was executed in what is now the Place de la Concorde.
And in 1984, on that date, that same date,
J.R. Bob Dobbs was assassinated at the Victoria Theatre in San Francisco.
This is the anniversary of these important historical events.
Wasn't it a big news day today?
Yes.
Yes, so much news that one's cranium felt tightly congested with it all.
And now you're operated.
And you have the Pope in Cuba and you have the Unabomber in San Diego.
The Unabomber was at the last game show.
And the Reverend Unabomber will be at the final X-Day celebration, July 5th, 1998.
We're starting to talk about events coming up, friends, on this show.
I'm going to let Dr. Howell and Puzzling Evidence and Phineas Narco explain the upcoming very large devivals,
the last devivals in Portland, Oregon, and Seattle, Washington, and other things.
So, have you got a question for us today?
Because we've got a big show and a lot of stuff, so don't hold us up.
State short question, please.
Just exactly.
Government.
State short question.
We've got...
Don't know.
Phineas Narco's injecting himself with amphetamines.
What are these new blue buttons?
Don't touch those.
Those are collar-alert blue buttons.
You've heard of Star 69.
Well, this will bring the collar right into your living room.
Don't hit the star sign.
And especially don't hit the pound sign.
I do.
Or you'll pick up an extra pound each time, and the poundage can be stifling.
The poundage can be foreboding.
It can weigh you down.
Not if you can make it to May 15th.
Oh, I'll hit somebody.
Get that pound.
I'll get it.
Hello?
What's on May 15th?
I don't know.
I'm on.
Oh, I'm sorry.
March 15th.
What's on March 15th?
It's getting...
It just got a month closer.
What's on March 22nd?
Two months.
No, no, no.
March 15th.
March 22nd.
Yeah, and it won't be here.
It'll be up in Seattle.
Well, you know, February 5th, there's the Aerial Act run by John Law, and I, Dr. Helen
Dowling, will be there to comment on the proceedings and to bask in the adulation of...
And where is that?
You should tell everyone.
Well, I would, except I had the little card with all the info on it.
But I think I left it in the car, or maybe they used it to roll up a...
Whoops, I shouldn't have.
Hey, wait a minute.
I'm on the radio.
Roll a T-shirt, I think you meant.
Yes, exactly.
Just so.
And so...
Roll some coffee.
Coffee?
Oh, if I only had coffee in a roll.
Oh, just wish you...
A little collar coffee.
Well, yeah.
Which is pretty good.
It goes through the filter here.
Collar coffee is all right.
And then it turns into the...
It needs to be filtered with all the filth that they...
Oh.
Now, Doug, can we turn it here?
Be completely serious.
Okay, I'm...
Okay.
Somebody can be completely serious on the show.
Did you really assassinate Bob Dox?
Yes, I really did assassinate Bob Dox.
And as Hal said...
How long ago was that?
It was on this evening.
It was in 1984.
It was in...
Oh, my gosh.
So long ago.
We're so old now.
Not today.
This is the morning after that day.
The morning after.
That day was the 22nd of January in 1984.
At the Victoria Theater, right across from now the lab.
That was 13 years ago, and the prophecy was that 13 years from the death of the E-pop,
the E-pop...
30Xs would arrive, as foretold.
Only now...
So where will you be on X Day, Connor?
I don't know yet.
July...
You don't know yet?
Time is coming up fast here.
It sure is, and you'll be making any points after that.
You always make anything...
Nice kid back in 1998 at 7 o'clock AM.
Well, I'm going to be outside.
I think you know...
Outside, well it's a good idea.
Might as well be outside.
Yeah.
Can't hide by going inside.
Avoid shards of flying glass and...
Can't hide?
...giant timbers blowing past.
asymptotic recording
So much...
You might as well get in the bed and pull the covers up right over your head.
That's a good idea, too.
Well, they're not powerful.
your bed will go with you to the pleasure saucer and you'll be ready. You might enjoy having a bed
there because it's hard and the metallic adamantine metal from far away that those saucers are made of.
We're not kidding either. Yeah. We've been having great arguments actually. It's a lot like
some of the other religions where all of the church fathers have been getting together lately,
Hal, myself, Philo, Ivan Stang, everybody, arguing about just what will happen. Will it just be a
world in which only the subgeniuses disappear, giving more jobs to other people? Oh, but the
subgeniuses are the ones who go on to the better world. Of course, but I mean this mortal
shuffled coil that's been shuffled so many times, I think would be turned into black dark ash.
I'm sorry. Well, you know, with that you have the same problem as in the Christian
revelation because even though there's supposed to be this total destruction,
afterwards there's a thousand years of peace. Now that means there has to be something left
unless it's the peace of pure oblivion. And I can see that. I can see all the pinks and
normals sinking back into peace after all the sub-gum-demeys are gone. They'll be bang like sheep
lining up for the slaughter. As we subgeniuses, oh yes, don't say nay because they are going to,
they're going to move into special pens. Is this your room? Even though they make
themselves, there's some hope. All these guys are moving equipment into my room here.
It's all the food from the last three hours is all being moved into my room.
I'm going to throw it around too and then show Hal the tape.
Yeah, well, we have to go over those tapes in special session.
So there won't be a show after X-Day?
No, there won't be a show after X-Day because both of us will be gone off to the...
We are talking about, there's a practice for this happening in Seattle in March.
Seattle? Is that an athletic study?
Well, there's another different Portland aspect of it too.
Actually, we'll be looking at Portland on Saturday.
That'll be March the 14th.
That's Saturday, March the 14th in Portland.
And we will be looking at Sunday, March the 15th.
We wanted to secure a date for...
This is in Seattle, Washington.
You mean you can't secure a date, you poor fellow.
Well, we looked at Friday the 13th, but we thought we'd give a revival, a proper day of Sunday.
Good idea.
Sunday, Sunday, Sunday.
We'll be there.
Sunday, Dr. Hal.
We will.
Phineas Narco will be involved.
Phineas Narco?
Reverend Ivan Stang.
Okay.
He's a real...
Sternodocs.
Sternodocs will be there.
Oh, I will.
I think Tyler may have to return to that.
Three of the...
Jayner will be there?
Three of the original Doctors for Bob will be performing.
Oh, Doctors for Bob.
We have to get Jayner to come in.
Only traditionally, you must make Jayner travel by bus to Seattle.
Yes, yes, yes.
We were thinking of packing him under the bus.
In the Greyhound area.
An interesting bus.
He has to sleep on the bare floor of somebody's hallway for the whole week.
Actually, he has his own secret lab deep within the confines of a Greyhound bus.
We have to make him sleep in somebody's kitchen.
In the morning, when they come to throw the wet coffee grounds into the wastebasket, they hit his head.
And Grey is Bob, it's not my kitchen.
He will leave unidentified spoo in the shower.
Yeah, well, not get into that, which is actually true, and therefore liable us to mention that.
Yeah, no, it's true, though, and it's been saved by people who own that shower, and it's been put into a sealed bag, and we should auction it off.
We're going to do a kind of Jurassic Park kind of thing in...
Oh, darn.
Grey's future generation.
Well, come out of my output.
You're not plugged in here.
Future generation.
Look, there's so many things going on.
This life of radio gods stuff is neat.
Some of the genetic samples represented by the Janer spoo, and the Janer spoo contains the complete DNA sequence, which will allow us to recreate an entire new generation.
Oh, my God, quick.
We've got to figure out a way to kill this stuff.
Well, uh...
You're saying this on the first episode, don't you?
I know, I know.
See, the more Hal says, the more it becomes true.
It's the hundred-headed Hydra.
Up off one beetle head, two beetle heads grows, and then...
Too many heads!
There are so many heads in here, I'm going to have to stop.
I'm going to disconnect temporarily and just see if I can get to the bottom of this.
Eight heads is a pair.
Okay.
Is everything all right?
There's only...
Let's talk about the pair.
We might have to...
Well, we could...
No, no.
You know what happens?
The not recording...
That's a very subgenius rule.
Last week, we had...
We had Reverend Kirk Steiner on here.
What were you saying?
An amazing rant.
Half-hour rant he had.
It was not recorded.
Reverend Kirk Steiner.
Which Ivan Stang pointed out to me at a Doc's Doc in 1981.
He said that it was his experience that the best stuff never gets recorded.
The best stuff never gets recorded.
And I had to admit, last weekend that happened.
Hey, this could be a really good show if we didn't record it.
You know, speaking of recording, at the pre-X Day drill,
I know that Popus Lilith Von Frumensch in Seattle, Washington,
did record the entire event and has put together a six-tape compilation.
Oh, I'd like to see that.
That you can order.
It's a six-tape compilation.
What I'm going to do over the air, right?
Right now, and this is the Reverend Otis F. Otter from the Mobile Outreach Ministry.
I'm going to give you that address where you can order all these tapes.
All right, folks, get ready to take it down.
Get ready and get your pen and paper ready.
Get your winky-dink crayon.
And winky-dink.
Tiddly-winks.
And you're going to draw this address on the TV now.
Yes, you are.
And here is the address for you people out there.
Help little winky escape from the pirates.
This is at Fool's Press, 1122 East Pike Street, number 769, Seattle, Washington, 98122.
That's Fool's Press, 1122 East Pike, number 769, Seattle, Washington, 98122.
And what you need to do is write to the popess and ask her for copies of these tapes.
Just take a deep sniff of that healthy mountain air.
Everybody's looking for a pair of dentures that got knocked onto the floor.
I'm sure they're all right.
We wouldn't step on them.
Not knowingly.
At any rate.
It just requires a brisk scouring with some steel wool to get those carpet fibers out from between the incisors.
Well, we seem to have driven out our compatriots completely.
It's a rather touching situation.
Ooh.
Ooh la la.
Dr. Howell getting touched.
Mmm.
It's a beautiful thing.
But, but, but.
Oh, oh, oh.
You've got to hear this.
I mean, Bob is prominent all over the earth.
And what you're doing is exactly what Bob would want you to do.
You have the name of Bob and you're ministering in his name and you're helping people.
That's the subgenius helping out right now.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm ministering in the name of Jesus Christ.
Yeah, but you don't know.
You're covering it up as Jesus Christ.
But really, subconsciously, you haven't been awakened to this subgenius level yet.
You don't know it, but you really are ministering in the name of the subgenius.
You know, I'll bet.
If you and the people of the Partridge family temple ever got together along with the Electric Hellfire Club,
you people could eat cotton candy and hostess Twinkies all day long and really party down.
Well, yeah, that sounds fun.
Not.
Retardation is an airborne mental virus.
It travels from the infected brain out of the flesh and into the receptors of the unsuspecting victim.
Retardation is more dangerous.
Than any other virus known to man for several reasons.
One, it has quantum properties and can therefore be transmitted through devices such as television, radio, and even through our precious computers.
Two, the retardation virus is seductive and will use everything in its arsenal to infect you.
Money, power, sex, drugs, love, while not exclusively the property of the disease,
are often used as bait by the retardation virus to lure you into itself.
The retardation virus is a
The retardation virus has created the world's biggest evil, a program known as organization.
These are traps laid by groups of retardation viruses in order to recruit fresh brains and incorporate them, much like the Borg, into their collective.
The virus uses a basic pyramid scheme ripped off from the ancient Egyptians and refused to accept criticism of their retardation from anyone below them in the Matrix, as to preserve prior accomplishments and to inhibit the destruction of the human race.
Et cetera.
the program, by those who are wise to its process.
From STEVILLE, the Center for Advanced Research, this explains everything.
Then you can hear all the
Yeah, well, you know at least here on our station we are not censored and we are completely free if we want even to use such words as
Or even
Well, I'm not sure that you can say
But what we usually say we get around that we have a softer way
just don't say
Yes exactly just like that so
uh without refuge from the specter of censorship they're also evil spirit that uh more of a little
speaking dance dishrag over the proceedings oh how horrible look at it yes they may not
have ectoplasm you can see right through it oh yes here's a speaking device ah yes the things
ow oh that one really jeremy jimmy jones don't worry about it
you should be worshiping jesus instead of performing this evil pagan ritual
i sent craig baldwin the the aunt bertha snuff tape what you did with claiming that you did it
right no no no i didn't do that no what aunt bertha snuff tape you know where billy pushes
aunt bertha into the giant when we did the show over at the gate or something they punished for
that one yeah yeah i've got a tape of that too
yes well not one of the brighter moments in the history of the human race when
billy pushed his wheelchair-bound aunt bertha into that horrible pit full of monsters
cut my belly open and show you the black stuff inside why would i put you in black stuff inside
inside what would ever possess me to want to show my disavow myself
show the black stuff i'll show you
well doesn't she always wear trousers does she or doesn't she
they wear her dancing dancing
i beg your pardon you're listening then are you yeah we always listen we never speak we
we listen we just listen all the way nobody listen on the frontier listening listening to you
glistening listeners out there nevertheless
up there she goes down the radio nothing more to see shows over
whoa yeah we'll tase them and amaze them we'll shock them you are perfectly right
well of course we are it's july 5th 1998. where are we
you man the divine this is it is the image of perfection surely the image of the divine creator
what's in it for me with the dawn of marriage i have to work that day
i don't know if i can get that day off together facing the terrors of nature
those early brothers understand why people don't want to run quicker to progress of course after
x-day the bobbies not the bobbies but the pinks will just keep keep going to their jobs even
though their jobs are nothing burnt out husks well you see examples of this even today isn't
it awful when you read the story about some schmuck who suddenly inherited a billion dollars
but he decides to keep going to work
just to collect his paycheck and hang around with his fellow workers
they wouldn't know what else to do and all those checks get put in the drawer where i can't get them
and uh it's a terrible thing no it's not a dream i wish to high heaven it were a dream
but it's real all too real you'll have to lock him up again
hello you read it in that paper all the time you read it in yesterday's newspaper
yeah we could tell you what station this is but you have to wait another 22 minutes for that
or i'll tell you right now no don't you just ruin the evening see she doesn't really want to know
she wants to know what station 21 minutes program i want to know what station is in maybe she wants
to dial in she's having trouble uh the train's coming through we might have some difficulty uh
did you say soft machine i said it before and i'll say it again
these guys never could protect a dinosaur and they never will they can't protect you
ever and they can't protect your siblings
have done it twice we all have done it we all done it once
it
we all
forgot something important
to hands with water
instead of sky
uh no it's not wfmu i i'm sure radio station of curiosity if you saw a creature of some kind
we will take your deposition you know you just can't make any money doing radio shows like like
these that you hear you know i just i don't know i want to do a radio show like this but they won't
pay me candy oh candy no dance what
wait a minute radio shows like this are you implying that these things are as common as
corn cobs why this is the most unique uh station sir a unique uh station and unique program in
every way even if it's i who say so yes indeed we are proud of our contribution to the culture here
and we stand boldly on the rim of our achievement whoa nearly falling in
thank you she just bought a yugo oh no i thought she wanted to stop one drop someone named
hugo he moved out of here in 1914. he goes home yeah he used to live down the street from victor
he goes home well yes victor he he goes home where he wrote ladies and then of course the
poor old bob nelson well he never did make it home did he he's going to be we're going to be
taking him to burning man next year are you kidding me no we'll all pay for it because he
that's where he escaped to that's where burning man will be well as long as he has a nice uh
wreck to be in with the ice cold lemonade and vacuum cleaners burning man is a great place to live
Man, it's sold out, man.
Man, yeah.
Burning things suck!
Just like that subgenius church.
All those churches sell out.
Now, now, let's keep these sentiments to ourselves.
They used to be cool, man.
And then they raised their price from $10 to $20 to $30 for membership.
I can't even afford that.
Well, if you were one of the elite archons, you needn't pay a penny.
Indeed, they pay you.
There goes Hal's sedan chair off at high speed.
Watch how I can open this baby up.
I'll make these fellows run for their money.
Hey, go, bobbies, go!
That's one of the best parts about being a subgenius lower archie is the eight bobby sedan chairs we have.
These little starveling, sniffling bobbies need someone to feed them up.
I'd get to wear all these clothes that have feathers on them.
Yes, and buttons.
And my youthful hose, well saved, is stocking.
Boy, you know, that'll be quite a gathering of the old clan there.
But what are these blue buttons?
Not since 1984.
Knocking at your door.
Oh, there it is now.
And now, ladies and gentlemen, tonight's hymn from one of the truly great preachers of all time, Mr. Johnny Cash.
Mr. Johnny Cash.
Bad luck wind been blowing at my back.
I was born to bring trouble to wherever I'm at.
Got the number 13 tattooed on my neck.
When the ink starts to itch, then the black will turn to red.
I was born in the soul of misery.
Never had me a name.
They just gave me the number when I was young.
Got a long line of heartache.
I carry it well.
The list of the things I've done.
lives I've broken reach from here to hell. Bad luck wind been blowing at my back. I pray
you don't look at me. I pray I don't look back. I was born in the soul of misery. Never
had me a name. They just gave me the number when I was young. I was born in the soul of
misery. Never had me a name. They just gave me the number when I was young. They just
gave me the number when I was young.
Gave me the number when I was young
Oh, we all done it there, friends.
I know you.
I've seen you.
I've been bird-logging that stuff.
I know about that stuff.
And your mother, all I wanted was a lousy drink of water.
I wasn't asking for that wallet.
I said water.
A lousy drink of water.
Sorry, Dave.
It was just a misunderstanding.
Well, friends, I want to tell you who done it.
Who has been doing what you've been listening to?
Oh, where's my back?
Background music tape.
There's DK Jones in the background.
And a whole bunch of KPFA subgenius show.
The show, actually, more than an hour, less than a show.
A very recent one from this year, January 23rd.
In fact, with Dr. Howell, Puzzling Evidence, Phineas Narco,
and Reverend Otis Otter as a guest.
We.
We've.
With bits and pieces dropped, dribbled and drabbled in from Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
There'll be quite a bit more of that coming up with Lonesome Cowboy Dave and Chaz Smith
and Princess We Are Doe that night from WCSB in Cleveland.
A Johnny Cash song there was actually taken from Reverend Ed Strange's Prozac Free Radio.
What?
Yes, that did it.
It's all right when I hear the music.
Since you're undoubtedly going to hear the music,
I doubt if you're going to be all right.
Uh, yeah.
Cool.
You can't run from your own bunghole.
Um, the Swingin' Love Corpses from the Chicago Subcon in 1992.
Live recording, doing their classic downbeat riffs in a minor key.
We've got coming up, Melba comes alive.
Some telephone sociological experimentation done by,
uh, Brother Russell from, uh, his CD Melba Comes Alive.
Um, we heard a little bit of, uh, Bob Larson and we'll hear more.
Oh my gosh, the phone's ringing.
Hold on just a second.
Huh?
What?
Um, I didn't do anything bad after that phone call came in.
Um, okay, what else?
What other, um, I guess that's it, friends.
I guess that's, uh, it's, this is, uh, an all other subgenius show, show.
Oh, on side two of show, we'll hear quite a bit of the, uh, Bob's Slack Time Funhouse
show from WREK with, uh, a real good rant about the luck plane by Dr. P. Ellis and,
um, uh, some, some more wonderful speculation about X Day.
It's so exciting, you know, as to the time I, at this speaking, I think it's about 130
some odd days, uh, till X Day.
I, I haven't, uh, it, oh man, man, it's, it, it's kind of scary in a way, you know, it's
gonna be a big change, a big change.
Are we gonna be able to handle the pleasure, we the subgeniuses, are we gonna, and you
know, we have to practice.
That's why we have the X Day.
Dr. P. Ellis.
That's why we have the divivals.
That's why we have the parties, friends.
It's practice because otherwise, the escape vessels, the purity of the pleasure could
be so overwhelming as to drive a, a person mad.
You know, there were sultans who were driven mad by pleasure.
And, uh, friends, it's a, you know, you wanna be able to appreciate the most intense pleasure
in the universe, so you have to kind of prepare your, toughen your mind up for it, you know
what I mean?
by pleasure right now here on Earth.
You know, what if an asteroid
crashed on your city tomorrow?
What if the world for you ended tomorrow?
Are you ready?
Think about that, friend.
Bob at Post Office Box
Dallas, Texas 75214
Once again, I'll give that Post Office
Box number again.
Free information. How to survive
the coming end times.
Survive?
Hell, how to?
Eternal Salvation or triple your money back.
Bob at Post Office Box
Dallas, Texas
Email
slack at
subgenius.com
or check out
www.subgenius.com
Subgenius, by the way, is spelled
without an O
for you subgeniuses out there.
Let's listen to this
beautiful
DJ Jones music for a while
as he takes us out to eat.
Mm-hmm.
¶¶
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
I thought you were going to pack it with old lesbians.
That's another old idea from S.K.
With them rotating warp drives.
That's also another rotating idea that keeps on recurring.
That's an amazing ship you'd have there.
You'd be the envy.
Every girl in the galaxy would want to fly in your ship.
That's for sure.
Well, wasn't that a sexual illusion back in the medieval times?
The little old man in the spaceship.
Yeah.
And if you can get a Farfisa console for it.
And if you can get close enough to that in the Middle Ages.
They're not that good, but they're nostalgic as hell.
So, you know.
So, what else?
The spaceships are everything else.
Especially what you just said.
I'm sorry.
I just glanced down there and lay one eye at the floor.
I'm sorry I didn't pick up the pen.
I'm going to go back and sit down with Donovan for a while.
We're about to start messing with your minds.
Pay us no attention.
We're about to start.
And just listen to what we're feeding into your hand.
Ah, that's so much better.
Hello, patients.
This is Dr. Ellis.
Occasionally, the body or brain or whichever will build an immunity to the pills that facilitate our lives.
I can only assume that this is...
This is exactly what has come to pass by the inordinate amount of whining and moaning that have been hampering experimentation lately.
I must emphasize the importance...
Blah, blah.
Cultural ebb and flow.
Yada, yada.
Okay, this is something legal put in.
All right.
Well, let me tell you something.
Kids, you know make worky.
You know get slacky.
Clear?
Six, eight, four, three.
Maybe if we stop tweaking those voices, they might persuade you to come back to the fold, huh?
Group two.
We sent the insects away, and we can bring the insects back.
And they've been gone all this time.
They must be...
Ravenous.
How would any of you like it, huh?
I see you on the screens.
I see you all.
You saunter so smugly up to the dispensing station and pass your token to the chimp.
I see some of you giggling like little girls when your self-actualized cousin slides your daily dose back through.
Well, I'll cut you off.
All of you.
There'll be no sleeping.
There'll be no going to the bathroom.
There'll be no laughing.
And there'll be no asking questions.
Don't make me scrap this operation.
I don't want to, but I'll turn this program around right now.
Some fricasseed hobos in the ashes of a condemned warehouse.
Sound familiar?
A few zombies wander onto a few Greyhound buses and die in the night between Tyler and Killeen.
Are you getting the idea?
I'm not.
I mean, uh...
Well, anyway...
I guess I can tide you over, okay?
All right, let's see here.
Five-Forty-Eight wants to know...
Why do the Thing always bad?
And then it meanders off on some daisy talk.
All right, Five-Forty-Eight.
I'm a doctor, so I think I can make some sense out of your gibberish.
Uh, counterbalancing the luck plane.
That's what you want to know.
All right.
The fabric sags, and you're knee deep in your own soil.
Well...
Well, the first thing you need to do is locate the fulcrum of the immediate luck plane.
Simple machines, we've been over this.
Alright, examples. Okay, okay.
I know you guys don't get out much, but, well, frankly, I can't relate to you showdins.
Okay, example.
I'm in the car, late for something, and catching every red light.
Alright, we need counterbalance.
What I'll do is I'll throw my miniature nicotine delivery systems into the back seat.
Okay, now I can't reach them unless I hit a red light.
Well, that doesn't do it. I'm still hitting red lights.
Okay, pitch the tape you're listening to.
Chuck your portafropper back there.
Sunglasses, your works.
Keep in mind that the stuff in the back seat is not the fulcrum.
It is the counterbalance.
The fulcrum is your desire for the stuff in the back seat.
The lever, of course, is always present.
Eventually, depending on the inclination of your tilt,
all the crap you need in the back seat will tilt the plane
and ensure that you do not hit any red lights
to give you an opportunity to grab your stuff.
I must stress that you must leave the counterbalance in place.
In other words, don't grab the stuff back if you do happen to hit a red light.
Unless, of course, you now need the stuff in the back seat
more than you need to get where you're going.
In which case, well, you're out of luck.
Alright, now that better hold you.
We'll work on switching out the pills, but until then, shut up!
We'd like to welcome our listening audience tonight.
Listen to Bob Sighton Funhouse,
the local Atlanta subgenius radio ministry hour.
Welcome our cohorts tonight.
Reverend Dr. P. Ellis, Reverend Dr. Bugletter,
and the other people we have.
Please introduce yourself.
Tell us who we have tonight.
Hi, I'm the doctor's patient, Ted Mann,
and I'm still incapacitated and all.
Why do you have rotator room by the remote?
Nobody finds this anywhere.
Hey, what can you say, you know?
You're cool like that.
And we have Dr. Frank Quintley in the house.
I think I see him over there.
Hello, Frank, would you like to say something?
No, that's okay.
Thank you very much.
Doing research in the corner.
Agents active.
All recall civilization death.
From you, partner.
It's the River of Unfinished Time.
Please, shut up.
My son's family and I went to Disney World in Orlando two years ago.
Yeah.
And we didn't realize it, but the day that we went down there,
I found out later.
They call it gay day.
Oh, no.
Encourage the homosexuals.
You were there, Melba?
I was there on that day, and it was the worst experience of my life.
Can you tell me what you saw?
I mean, some of this you probably can't describe on a family show.
Well, that's true.
We saw several things that just were shocking.
But the worst part of it was, besides just, you know,
it was like these people would kiss openly, you know, and embrace.
But if we gave them a funny look, they would say rude things to us.
So when they were kissing, they're the ones doing the weird things.
Right.
But if you look at them funny, then they get mad at you.
Oh, yes.
They were very hateful.
And the worst part of it was, I have a nephew who is a teenager.
He went off and rode the rides and things.
He rode the rides and things by himself all day long.
Yeah.
When we met him back there at the pavilion and we all got back together,
he had a little friend with him, a boy a year or two older.
And this young boy, he said, I met a new friend here.
And this boy was very, you know, effeminate.
And he had like a pastel-colored triangle button on his...
Well, that's the story.
That's the gay rights symbol.
Well...
Melba, how old was this child?
18.
So this other boy was gay.
At 18, he was already homosexual and proud of it.
We found that out later, Bob, see.
And the horrible thing was that we...
Apparently, his daddy works for the Disney company.
Oh, my goodness.
We felt like Disney people were sending their kids to try to recruit.
Right.
And the boy was gay.
And it was a little...
I don't know.
Because they were on...
They kept riding the same ride over and over.
Uh-oh.
It's a small world ride.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So that kid was after your son.
I mean, that gay boy was after your son.
I think so.
And ever since...
Now, Stefan doesn't see him.
But I understand that they ride back and forth.
Uh-oh.
Because this boy lives in California.
And...
Melba, you got to put a stop to that somehow.
Oh, Stefan.
He often uses, and I won't say anything nasty, you know,
but he keeps referring to weird expressions like bonus eggs and felching and things,
and we don't know what he means.
Well, you don't want to know, and I don't want to tell you.
And that boy that he was with, I'm telling you, his voice was higher than yours is, Bob.
He was such a sissy.
Oh, it was horrible.
Yeah, and he had the little pink triangle on.
Yeah.
Okay, I'll tell you what, Melba, I want to do right now.
All right.
Your child has come under the influence of the evil spirits of seducing homosexuality
that were surrounding this other young lad.
Yes.
And I want to pray with you right now.
Oh, please do, Bob.
In the name of Jesus to break that hold.
Okay, Melba?
In the name of Jesus.
All right, now, Melba.
I believe it.
I want you to say, I'm Melba.
I'm Melba.
I, Melba.
As the mother.
Of my child.
Have the authority.
According to the word of God.
Over my child.
God gives me authority.
And I also.
Have authority.
any demon in hell.
Over any demon in hell.
That tries to steal my child.
That tries to steal my
child. Lord Jesus.
Lord Jesus. I raised my son right.
I raised my son right.
I raised him to be a man. I raised
him to be a man. Not a homosexual.
Not a homosexual. And I'm
not going to allow. I'm
not going to allow. The devil.
The devil. To steal my son.
To steal my son.
In the name of Jesus. And the
the name of Jesus. Spirits of perversion. Spirits of perversion. Take your hands. Take your hands.
Off my son. Off my son. Now. Go. Go. You go. Go. You go. In the name of Jesus. In the name of Jesus.
Set my son free. Set him free. In Jesus' name. Oh, thank you, Jesus. In Jesus' name.
Oh, you're getting a little blessed and happy there, Melba. Okay, now. Melba? Melba?
Give me the four bar religion. Add it to the other three.
Give me the four bar religion.
Add it to the other three.
Well, it's good to learn some reading and arithmetic and writing, but you gotta have
our religion. Add it to the other three.
You know what? I've just, I've prayed long and hard about this, and I've come to the
point where I don't want to go to public schools. I really do think that God's judgment,
you know, is on our nation, and those public schools being run, you know, by the government,
more or less, God's judgment is on those schools.
When the teachers can't teach, and the kids get profanity and drugs and no God and paganism
and the teachers living in sin and the profanity and all of this, you know, what's wrong with
this picture, you know? Jeremiah chapter 10 and verse 2 tells, God says, learn not the
way of the heathen. Learn not the way of the heathen.
Is that what we're not doing when we send them to the schools? And I think right now,
and I appreciate your empathy and your reasoning here, Robert, we ought to pray for Yvonne
Gonzalez. We ought to pray for that schoolboy. We ought to pray for the NAACP. We ought to
pray for Dallas and say, hey, God, please lend a hand to this because we are lost in
a fog on this thing, man.
Absolutely. And, you know, you were talking about the issue of trying to witness. I believe
someone called earlier, talked about trying to...
Yeah.
...share a pro-life message with some of these young people.
Yeah. Yeah.
Now, things have just...just in the last 10 years, things have just changed. Even up to
the mid-'80s, you know, I was able to go to the public schools and share with some of
the young people at high school, junior high.
Uh-huh.
And, you know, I try to do it now. They're trying to say that, you know, trying to drum
up a bunch of business that...saying I'm just talking to the teenage girls for some kind
of ulterior motive and things like that. But just...
Yeah.
...it's just utterly ridiculous, you know. But you're out there trying to share the message
with all the young people. And they just, you know, just because of one or two things
that might have happened or, you know, relationships that might develop, you know, out of that,
they want to make that into a big thing, you know. But, you know, most of the women in
the Bible, my goodness, were 12, 13, 14 years old when they married. I say if there's grass
on the field, go ahead and play ball.
Yeah.
And, you know, that's always been what I say.
Robert, I'll tell you something. Let me tell you what my take is here. If in 20 to
30 years, we're going to look back at today in America and say we have lost our mind.
We've gone to madness, to the killing of infants, the genocide, the infanticide.
I read about, I read about a fallen pilot swearing death.
And no one's there.
And no one's there, nobody there.
They stole their tail, their friends and friends.
But since they've been down there, God was on their side.
We can see the way they're looking.
Hello.
How long have you been waiting?
My son.
You're late.
How long have you been waiting, my son?
It is his.
His.
His later.
Later.
That.
You.
Y.
Think.
It's all yours, Lee.
It's all yours, Chuckie.
Chuckie, what he bought.
It's all yours, Lee.
It's all ours.
From the moment we laid our fish, John, at the first day we came across here to this big, small tiny place we're standing on,
to the day that we clenched down into the ground and lifted the dirt up to our eyes and said,
look at this stuff we've got.
It's dirt, and it's hard dirt.
And this land, which is our land, which we are on right now,
since the days when we first came here, we've been all out of caves.
In what we call the wellspring in the first cave,
which is actually not a real place, but a psycho-spiritual area.
We jumped out with hardly a stitch of clothes on and did the chicken dance all night long.
Till two in the morning we plucked and strutted and we fried ourselves in lard and sang the blues
and drank a pig, a knucklehead of pork wine and a beer, a whole bottle of wine.
Wow.
But now we're here, we're back to let you know
that jazz life is a little bit different.
Lucky, if you want to dance this dance,
you've got to do this dance with me.
Or if you don't do this dance,
then we don't dance.
Then you're not going to dance with...
You know what he means.
The pantheon.
Yes, we are the gods.
We're here to mess with your hands.
Can you dance with the gods?
And we're talking about Nick.
They dance quick.
Elvis.
Perturbo.
Areva.
Perduabo.
James.
Jimmy.
St. Dimfnath.
The Innocent Deadly.
Jim.
All the people of the Bizarre Shack.
Living and Dead.
Yeah.
Sunhouse.
Little Sun.
Yeah.
Big Sun.
Big Bill.
Big Bill Brunzi.
Muddy.
Little Bill Brunzi.
Dirtbag.
Mike Luther King.
JFK.
Hans Fielder.
Lex Luther.
Popeye the Rat.
He was actually a sailor man, but he was confused.
Yeah.
Jimmy Hoffa.
The Green Hornet.
Huck Sampson and Delilah.
They owned a barbecue shop down from my house where they both burned up that one night.
And Kato.
And Anne Rice.
She doesn't know it yet.
She's a vampire.
Zombies.
He's Booker, man.
We gotta be Booker in two.
There's only a scant 12 minutes until we have to be careless.
But we're gonna be bumping and grinding.
We're gonna get to a different tune.
We're gonna go weightless in 12 minutes.
Yeah.
We're zapping off, man.
You see these like normal, earthly coil type feet we got on here?
We're gonna shuffle off them and we're gonna zap out into the fourth dimension where we
can not only see the past and future, but the human kindness is a bowl of franken-beans
for your own list and then a blazer and your listless barbecue.
And a Rice Krispie treat that's been sitting on the mantle for four months.
That's what we've all been waiting for.
Mom's a Rice Krispie treat.
Yeah.
Sometimes she would melt down her fingernails and put them in them with the marshmallows.
Other times she would smell her own clothing and yell at me for no reason in a different language.
We didn't know what it was.
It was the softener.
He wouldn't have put the softener in the treats.
I don't think the cats would have liked them.
The dogs wouldn't like them.
They were all particular.
They were all protected by the soft machine, sir.
The dinosaurs certainly wouldn't like them.
And speaking of the dinosaurs, 150 million years is no guarantee of survival.
But they were all protected by the soft machine, too, sir.
How can you complain?
Did you say soft machine?
Yeah, Lord, Lordy.
Oh.
Woo.
Wow.
What's good.
Well, duddy?
Want me to dry, you sure?
No problem.
Would you like to give George some coffee to Tharion Barrow?
What?
Yes, yes, please, please.
No, thanks.
Down both allowances.
Yeah.
Can't you see the two neurons just ain't right
They'll have to worry
As long as we ain't turning
The key to the lock on the door of illusion
Yeah, yeah
Well, submission
Won't help the world's conditioning
Nothing done too long
I'm saying I'm trying, I'm dying
The way it starts to line
How long we got it on
I heard that men were created for love
But it seems there's some more than most
As long as fear remains undemouched
They'll have to worry
Cause the one we turn
The key to the lock on the door of illusion
Yeah, yeah, yeah
All right
Yeah
One
We'll let it go
Even if we don't break
It's this one
Yeah
It's nothing like
What we thought
Yeah
But tread with me
Broke
guitar solo
And that's Frank Marino
and Mahogany Rush, friends, from
an old album.
Praise God.