Climb inside.
On the way to
if you climb inside.
Climb inside my little people.
I've returned.
Here in the West,
I'm called Christ.
I've been sent by my father Lucifer
as a divine agent of intervention
to save you from a nuclear holocaust
and the destruction of the human race.
Be not afraid.
The great disappearance that has just occurred
is all part of the plan.
These people that were removed
were highly concerned.
They were crystallized in their thought patterns.
They would have been unable to accept
the new age of Satanism.
And now the old is gone
and it's time to bring in the new.
I come to bring you all to God.
All religions have strayed
from the cosmic truth of God
and the universe.
Now I will show you all
the simple path to God
and you shall see all of yourselves
as the divine beings that you truly are.
All one.
In the vast synchronicity of the cosmos.
You will understand the great law of karma
and you will learn to live in peace and harmony
and brotherhood among all of mankind.
Together we can eliminate all war,
suffering, disease, hunger, and injustice.
Love and light can fill the earth
and we shall seal the door
where evil dwells forever
and the great plan can be fulfilled.
The perfection of the Aryan root race.
Follow me,
brothers and sisters,
and we shall create a new world.
Today,
the kingdom of God has come upon you.
May the force be with you all.
My friends,
that was a direct reading
from a so-called radio broadcast.
It was done last week.
I didn't want to play.
I didn't have a tape of the original,
but that's the exact words of a broadcast.
I'm afraid that what I'm going to say to you
will shock you.
It will disturb your sleep.
It will make you worry for your loved ones.
It will give you nightmares of disaster,
plague, and horrible death.
It will make you rethink the priorities of your life.
It will change the way that you look at yourself
and the world.
There is a killer loose in the land.
This killer cuts down all that he touches.
If he touches you,
you will die.
If he touches your child,
your child will die.
His victims die a slow, horrible death.
They waste away.
They drown in their own body fluids.
They lose control of their mouth.
They lose their memory.
They become demented.
They die in agony.
There is nothing that can be done to save them.
The killer's name is J.R. Bob Dogs,
or Bob for short.
When he starts talking,
he says,
to kill you,
it is said that you are slackless,
an insensate,
mean puppet with no soul,
an occupant of an earth ship
rocketing headlong into Armageddon.
This killer and his cult of followers
first emerged on the American scene in the 1950s,
rising like an angel of printing death
from out of the oozing rivers of body fluids
that spilled like fettish waterfalls
into the streets of our beloved,
America.
From the sick and sleazy pleasure houses
of the killer Bob and his twisted subgeniuses.
And yet, despite this heinous assault
on all of the good and pure and virtuous traditions
that made America a shining beacon of freedom
to all the world,
the authorities have done nothing to stop this terror
from washing over this great land
like a sea of evil blood.
In fact, the leaders that you elected
are able to save you.
They are the ones that are leading
and abetting their cause,
claiming these evil subgeniuses
have the same rights as ordinary people.
Our elected officials are daring to let these freaks
and perverts hide behind the protection
of the Constitution of the United States.
It has been well documented that the tremendous power
of organized militant groups such as
the Subgenius Liberation Army Corps, or SLAC,
SLAC,
have its slimy tendrils deep into the White House,
the United Nations, and possibly even to the Vatican
and the Council on Foreign Relations.
These swine hold most of our craven and criminal politicians
in thrall, either through threats and blackmail,
or else through the politicians' own naked lust
for the pleasures that Bob's world offers.
You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery
which reaches from the inner mind to...
The Subgenius Hour of SLAC!
He was an average sort of guy, the image of a song.
How can I say this?
There was good in Larry and there was evil.
The evil part broke through, took hold.
He was an average sort of guy, the image of a song.
I'm a reporter, not a mystic, Linda.
If what's happened has made this all clear,
well, then, perhaps it makes sense after all.
And in all men.
When I first heard of Larry and Sarah,
We are...
Ain't got no car
Ain't got no wife
In fact, I got killed
Coming over here tonight
I am a dead man
I'm laying on the floor
I am deceased
And once more, I am a dead man
Yes, I have discontinued living
I have given up on cash
Wine and women
I ain't got no money
I ain't got no shoes
I guess it ain't funny
That is why I have the blues
I am so dead that I feel like a stiff
If you don't believe it
I am a dead man
Just take a sniff
Sniff me
Ain't got no job
Cause I won't need it anymore
Can't hit the time clock
Cause I can't get up no more
I'm on a permanent vacation
With no pay
Don't ask me what I think
Cause I got nothing to say
I tell you I am dead
That's why I have the blues
Yes, that's what I said
Now I'm telling you the news
I am a dead man
As quick as I can be
If you don't believe it, just touch me
I am a dead man
I have paid the ultimate price
That's why I'm qualified
To give you this advice
I'm a dead man
D-E-A-D
I am dead
That's what I said
Oh, yes, dear friends
And it's true
It's, uh, John Bartles there
A fine, fine performer
But, uh, it, uh
And we'll get back to more
From the fine Mr. Bartles
As soon as we can
But, you know, the power
The power of organized perversion
Is a factor in the suppression
Of the truth about this bomb
And it is certainly a fact
That these deviants
Are a part of the media's push
To destroy America
If the uncensored truth about Bob
Were released to the American people
It would have the potential
Of permanently derailing the plan
To submerge America
Into a multicultural new world order
It would have the potential
Of waking up the sleeping American people
And our masters in Washington
New York and Dobstown, Bolivia
Cannot allow that to happen
And so, uh, I'm going to
Tell you a little bit more
We're repeatedly told
By the controlled media
That the Church of the Subgenius
Is a joke
A bunch of crackpots
Boking a little fun
At our sacred American heritage
But that simply is not true
In fact, they are
An extremist paramilitary organization
Highly trained in the art
Of mind control
Trained by who?
By our own CIA
That's who
The Church of the Subgenius
Infiltrated our most secret organization
In 1953
When a letter signed by J. Edgar Hoover
Recommended that a young man
Named J.R. Bob Dobbs
Be placed in charge of the U.S. Air Force's
Project Blue Book
Investigating the phenomenon
Known as UFOs
In later years
He befriended a young agent
Named George Bush
And a soldier named
Lee Harvey Oswald
Yes, it is some great joke
Isn't it?
Let's hope that the rest of us
Survive long enough
To make it to the punchline
When Dobbs left the government payroll
In late 1970s
He had by then left a long trail
Of twisted minds behind him
Key government officials
Converted into practicing occultists
In the surface of the killer bob
It has been speculated
That between 80 and 95 percent
Of children that disappear
From our homes due to kidnapping
Are converted to the subgenius faith
By means of drugs, torture, and starvation
These children are smuggled out of the country
And sent to one of the cult's
Overseas slave labor camps
Cruel sweatshops
Where the children are forced to spend
16 hours a day
Making fake miracle trinkets
Which their false prophet leader
Bob
Peddles to his followers
Making over 17 million dollars
In 1993
Many of the children are sent to Thailand
To stalk Bob's
Many brothers
Some are sent to one of the 13
Dobbs town training centers
To be indoctrinated
To learn the dark secrets of the cult
And to work in their jungle laboratories
Manufacturing a designer drug
Called Gabrogfran
In 1983
Three subgeniuses were arrested
For covertly attempting to poison
The Philadelphia water supply
With a 50 gallon dose
Of this potent hallucinogen
The children are sent to the
Military hospital
Where charges were dropped
And the information suppressed
By order of the department of defense
Because it seems that this
Gabrogfran drug
Was developed by the military
As a weapon under orders of
CIA head George Bush
During the Carter administration
How many innocents must die
So that the sick sex games
Of the pervert subgeniuses can continue
How long must we wait
Before the police and the military
Take matters into their own hands?
And stop this madness
What can you do to save your family
And your country from this deadly menace?
There's a lot you can do
Avoid contact with known subgeniuses
If there is a known subgenius district
In your area, avoid it
Do not go there
Avoid the trendy or fashionable part of town
Whenever possible
This is often where subgeniuses are to be found
If you live in a rural area
Or subgenius district
In a small town that has preserved
Traditional American values
Stay there
Watch your family for signs of disobedience
Or strange behavior
Stay away from the television
It has become infested with subliminal messages
That lure you and your loved ones
Into the cult
Do not go to airports alone
If you must go however
Be sure not to drink anything
Bring bottled water
Many airport water supplies
Are tainted by the Gabrogfran drug
Teams of subgeniuses
Work at every airport in America
Waiting for the drug to take effect
And loading their helpless victims
Into waiting planes
While airport officials and the FAA do nothing
Make your children stay at home after school
If they try to sneak out
Beat them severely
This is very important
As this blood cult of evil targets
Places where teens congregate
Shopping malls are among the best recruiting grounds
For young people to be lured into Dobbs evil web
If you would like to be a part
Of the
The path is the mask of love
A way, a way
The flow is the task of love
Above today
There is no other way
You gotta trust us
When you need a friend
To find us
You gotta look within
You gotta trust us
Before you turn to dust
You gotta see it before you see
You gotta hear
Without fear
You gotta feel
To reveal
You gotta touch
Without doubt
Such is ill and I hate it, hey
Well, for you, of you, with you, more of you, just of you
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
problem for the future youth force. They just get on their communicators and call the police,
and a heavily armed super-trained SWAT team will be called in. They will easily drive the
Christians out with tear gas, stun grenades, and their M-16s and shotguns. If the Christians do
not come out from the tear gas, they will come in after them. Ten-gauge shotguns and explosively
charged battering rams can knock down any door. Plastic explosives can smash giant holes in any
walls. But what happens when a few Christians are heavily armed with, and this is a core-ish part,
bulletproof vests, tear gas masks, automatic weapons, and high-powered rifles? No problem.
You just use the Philadelphia Plan. Invented by Mayor Wilson Good, you drop an incendiary bomb
by helicopter and blow the house apart in flames. And if the Christians don't run out,
they burn to death. And if they do run out shooting, they will be blown away by police
snipers. If they run out of flame, they will either be allowed to burn to death or splashed
with fire extinguishers and led off to prisons, tossed into the death chambers. No doubt they will
be stripped naked and kept in handcuffs so they cannot resist what is to come later on. They will
probably be fed nothing nor given any fresh water. And they will be thrown into the fire.
They will have to lay in their own feces and urine. Possibly stale bread will be thrown onto the floor
and possibly water will be sprayed in with hoses so that they are forced to lap it up as dogs
amidst the urine, waste and blood from injuries and mnestration, as it says here. But who will be
the future prison guards? Why, the most sadistic, sick, and savage ex-prisoners become the new prison
guards. Of course, the subgeniuses.
The most brutal rapists, murderers, and perverts will be assigned to take care of the Christians.
No doubt Christians will be selected for daily beatings and tortures. Select girls, boys, and
women will be chosen for sexual rapes. In front of all, pregnant women will no doubt be booted
several times in the stomachs to prevent the birth of another Christian.
This is the end of the video. If you liked it, please subscribe, like, and leave a comment. Thank you. See you next time. Bye.
This is all, once again, my friends, from a Christian book called The Answer to Raptures, available at any good American supermarket.
And, let's see, oh, the Christians will be led to their deaths in giant sports stadiums and complexes of the world,
such as the Los Angeles Coliseum, the Houston Astronome, all naked and handcuffed, beaten and abused,
and before the Luciferic juries and the field stadiums.
Christians will be given their last chance to worship Satan as God, or be put to death.
And the method of death will be decapitation, beheading. We are told in Revelation chapter 20, why beheading?
Because it is the bloodiest and most terrifying and most systematic death, death ever to face.
When the carteroid arteries in your neck are severed, the blood literally spurts out everywhere.
And sometimes...
Sometimes your head is alive for up to 10 to 15 seconds looking about at a stadium, a satanic stadium, cheering madly, and then you are gone.
This terrifying form of death is purposely designed to terrify the Christian.
And no doubt, as they are led to slaughter in these giant sports stadiums and complexes,
the rock bands will be blaring away some satanic tune.
Possibly the old Rolling Stones classic, Sympathy for the Devil,
Led Zeppelin's Whole Lotta Love,
the ELP classic, Jerusalem,
Atlantis by Donovan,
or possibly even Pat Benatar's We Are Invincible.
Maybe they will even slice or chop the heads off of Christians in synchronicity to the beat of the rock bands.
Ho ho ho ho, oh dear friends, it's a scary, scary world a-comin', according to...
uh, these fine, fine preachers, and according to this fine background music by, uh, Saint Tommy Lopez.
Oh, what have we here? What other things have we? There's...
all, not all that many tapes, but...
but there is...
Oh, oh, I should mention that, um, that grinning evil death rant that I was doing earlier,
uh, about the evil of killer Bob Dobbs and so forth.
That, that...
Dr. Legume actually created that from an AIDS pamphlet that he found.
You know, most of the stuff we do is based on real, uh, non-Dobbs-ful things.
And, and here's Dr. Legume's letter that came with that rant.
Here's my latest still warm from the devil's hip pocket pamphlet.
I'm gonna pass out a buttload of them to foolish toady Christians this Saturday at the Peter Popoff Miracle Crusade.
You'll notice I included the sacred P.O. box, so the stink trail will lead back to you.
Joy, joy.
Says...
evil...
Dr. Legume.
And, well, meh, I don't know what, we've got lots of lovely, sarcastic music here to play,
and letters from the followers, and some news about the pilgrimage,
the subgenius universal pilgrimage coming up.
Oh, yes.
Ahem.
And, uh...
Uh...
What do you say to this?
Oh, my friend, how far have you progressed from the Stone Age?
How far have we advanced from the ooze and the slime?
Are the present doctors really miracle men of medicine?
What have they cured?
What have they controlled?
In the next few minutes, you will be shown a special example.
My friend, this is not the 10th century, but the 20th century.
I firmly suggest that if you are squeamish, please keep your eyes closed,
or better yet, leave the room.
I do not advise that children hear this.
But for you of the strong stomach and the open of mind,
I predict that there is one enemy we have not conquered,
and in our lifetime we never will conquer,
and that is leprosy.
Leprosy.
Leprosy, yes, leprosy.
The curse of the ancients.
The blemish of the present and the scar on the festering face of the future.
Leprosy inhabits the bodies of the damned.
Leprosy is highly contagious.
The Chinese know that even a look from a leper can bring you down
with this dreaded disease.
Leprosy is called the walking death.
Leprosy, the indwelling devil.
Leprosy, the result of yesterday's sin, tomorrow.
Oh, my friend,
we talk about this just for you to show you the karma of the 20th century.
These poor unfortunate souls exist under the same sun,
the same moon, and the same stars as you and I.
But we are so much more fortunate.
This spreads to the face, leaving it puckered and thickened.
The eyesight dims and is soon gone.
The voice goes to a heavy whisper and then stops.
The nerve vanishes.
The bones of the fingers,
rot,
decay,
also the toes and drop away.
And then you stumble into the pits of death.
Close the quote.
So says the good Dr. Joseph Mealy Hopkins.
Now...
Oh, thank you, Doc.
I can't break this.
Break this.
What we need is someone to take this church off our hands is what we need.
Okay, what's your church and what's your name?
First Church of the Good Discount, House of Faith.
Hey, that's my church.
That's your church?
Hello?
This is a true story.
You're giving the church away?
No, we're actually...
You're man enough to take it.
Oh, well, what if you give it away?
What are you people gonna do?
Well, we're gonna do something fun.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, we're gonna quit working for God.
We're gonna go to Green Hill and get glanscating.
That's right.
It's part of the plan.
They'll come up and there will be the sickening and the healing.
What happened to all the doctors?
What happened to the exploding golf ball?
Yes, who are the doctors?
Who are the doctors?
The ones that caught fire on the table.
This is Reverend Terrence Austin Tritt.
Well, listen, the phones are ringing off the wall and we'd like to help you out, but honestly,
we're just gonna have to turn your tape off because...
President Nixon is on line three, Doctor Puzzling Evidence, and please pick up line three.
Okay.
Well, thank you.
Hello, this is Dan White.
Can I come to your convention and get my head launched?
Yes, sir.
Oh, it's just a funny show.
Yes, it's a funny show.
Hello, tiny little caller.
Hello.
Wow, I don't believe it.
This is actually a live show.
No, it's just a tape.
It is a live show.
I thought it's all taped.
Oh, my God.
The tape's set at the wrong speed.
Thank you.
Here you come, the crazy.
What do you mean you called in without finding out what you were calling?
Oh, I knew it was the Church of the Subgenius because I'm a member, but...
You were a member?
You were a member.
I wasn't...
Oh, you've changed the name.
Oh, right.
Okay, go ahead.
Yes, well, it's a new church and it's a whole new story and...
You're not the white-haired guy that's on all the time.
And before that, it gets weird because then there comes the age of giant underwater scorpions
and wiggly, oogly things wiggling through the primeval muck.
Boy, we pass them on with the show.
Because we don't get up on that chart without enough of them.
In fact, any subgenius can chew up any denomination money and pass what he wants onto the show.
And they often do.
Yes, they do.
In places you've never imagined.
And with things that you can't believe.
But it's scary.
Well, we know where we usually pass things from, don't we?
Yes, we do.
Yes, from Bob and...
This is the church.
I want to go explain something.
I tuned in my radio a few minutes ago and I...
And sign here.
...tuned in to KPSA and there you go.
Sign here, please.
We're signing papers.
Okay, here I go.
Well, do you want the church?
And sign over here, please.
Okay, that's right.
We have to sign things.
Sign.
We've got somebody that's signed.
Yeah, okay.
We've got somebody here that takes at least two rooms...
Keep the pen in his hand.
...I'll keep the...
I'll be all right.
I exist because the world's in my...
In my telephone, yeah.
Well, actually, the church only exists because we have the paperwork on it right here and
the health works, therefore I am.
Well, I think I'm going to go out and stoke up the old wood fire.
I'll be back in just a few minutes with some tips on your future...
Yeah, let's be putting on some bogus live stuff and go out on the roof, boy.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying, huh?
Kilns fired in edible 24-calorie silver.
Never before in human history...
Mm-mm, wish I was there now.
Never, never before in human history has the Pope, McKinley, Harding, Coolidge,
Dobbs, Mint, not a U.S. government body, commissioned such a rarity.
Delicious and crackling with a cooked scallop.
A chicken of prepared edible material.
I think about it.
I think I'll have one right now.
Well, I'll bet you have.
And they grow into the same kind of animal as I do.
He says he knows you, Doctor.
Well, let's tune in on the monitor over here and see exactly who that is that's calling.
Can you see me?
Yes, yes, we see you and it's disgusting.
And I'm bringing the mirror close to my nose.
Oh, it's that doctor.
Do you know who you're listening to?
Yes.
Which is the new voice?
The new voice is the last voice that I heard.
Have human babies.
That doesn't sound right.
It does make sense.
There's the new voice again.
Must be one of those sub-dini hierarchical figures.
He knows all the passwords and the secret jokes, so let's send him a new cartoon by
Stang and Stanislaw.
Which one?
It's either, I think it's, I'm going to take a wild guess.
It's Pope Meyer.
That's pretty wild.
That's too wild.
South, south, go south.
Go south, go south.
It's Terry Thornley.
No, not, farther south.
Farther south.
Farther south and out of the country.
Oh.
Oh, that's a good one.
Oh, it's Robert Desco?
Yes.
For the info.
You know, the same people.
Go to the London Grill.
We'll be doing our show from there if you know.
You will?
Yeah, we're going to have to do it.
Yeah.
It's going to be on Friday night.
Your show's going to be from there?
Yeah, it's going to be from the London Grill in Santa Cruz on Friday night.
It's going to be a remote.
And you'll really like it.
This is my show.
If I go all the way down there and you guys aren't there, I'll laugh just as much as
you did.
I guarantee, I guarantee you find the London Grill in Santa Cruz.
We will be broadcasting from there on Friday night.
Then don't you do anything but watch the show.
I guarantee you find the show.
In fact, you would bow your head and kiss your panty that you even know about it.
You've got that little white stuff you put on your nose so it doesn't chip here.
Are you people pro-capital punishment?
What's the white stuff you put in your nose?
I want the white stuff you put on your nose.
We are capital punishment, dear friends.
And yeah, there was a nice little classic old stretch of very old show, the old KPFA
show.
from the subgeniuses of Berkeley.
And that was a pact when it was G. Gordon Gordon
and Glass Madness guesting
with the great Gary Gbrok friend, Puzzling Evidence,
and Dr. Howell.
That show's been howling away for many a year now.
It's gone through a lot of changes,
and there's infinite amounts of old, old tape
of old, old, old men we can always whip out on you.
Hey.
Hey, there.
So you come out, and you draw, and you say,
bam, bam, stop, and a guy doesn't stop.
Then you move up to the head, and you put one right there,
and that's usually final.
Get that spear away from me.
Get it away.
It exploded.
It hit people that had not known.
It's been hit in months.
Some began to dance in the spirit.
Others threw up their hands in exclamations of praise.
Others began to dance up and down the aisles.
Others fell like they'd been hit by a proverbial chainsaw.
I was in pain.
Others tuned in to the subgenius radio ministry
hour of slack.
And, uh...
What's going on now?
Well, I want...
I found some cool songs.
Now, last week, we were doing our opinionated thang,
really, really hating,
hating the conservative fundamentalist-type people.
And, of course, you know J.R. Bob Dobbs
with our doctrine of patriotic, psychotic, and narco-materialism.
We insist on equal hate for pretty much both sides.
Yes.
And so, in the interest of...
In the interest of equal time,
we're going to let the disgusting liberals be trashed as well.
This particular cut is off of a new one we found right here at the station
by our good friend, Reverend Mojo Nixon,
and his good friend, Reverend Jello Biafra,
with this song, which is...
Let's hope we have it queued up just right here,
called, Love Me, I'm a Liberal.
I cried when they shot John Lennon
Tears ran down my spine
And I cried when I saw JFK
As though I'd lost a father of mine
But Malcolm X and Ice-T had it coming
They got what they wanted to get me for
They asked for this time
So love me, love me, love me
I'm a liberal
I go to pro-choice rallies
Recycle my cans and jars
I'll honk if you love the dead
Hope those funny crunched-ass dumb stars
But don't talk about revolution
That's going a little bit too far
So love me, love me, love me
I'm a liberal
I cheered when Clinton was chosen
My faith in us was only born
I'll do anything
To save our schools
If my taxes ain't too much more
And I love blacks and jays and Latinos
As long as they don't restore
So love me, love me, love me
I'm a liberal
Rush Limbaugh and the LAPD
Should all hang their heads in shame
I can't understand where they're at
Arsenio should set them straight
But if Neighborhood Watch doesn't know you
I hope the cops take down your name
So love me, love me, love me
I'm a liberal
I'm the whitest person that ever did the funky chicken
I read The New Republic
Rolling Stone and Mother Jones, too
If I vote it's a Democrat
With a sensible inside view
But when it comes to terrorist tariffs
There's no one more red, white, and blue
So love me, love me, love me
I'm a big road
Once I was young and had an attitude
Stickers covered the car I drove in
Even went on some direct actions
When there weren't rental cops to be seen
But now it's grown older, wiser
And that's why I'm turning you in
So love me, love me, love me
Love me, love me, love me
I'm a liberal
Liberal
acre
fon
I am a liberal
re
I am politically correct
Hypocritical, you bet
I am pro-gay
But I wouldn't want my own kids to turn out that way
I am pro-abortion
And for gun control
I'm for balancing the budget
And for financing overseas wars
I am pro-small business
And for capital punishment
And I think we're more controlled
By the federal government
Now I'm for plenty of changes
Even though I don't know what they are
I'm for helping out Detroit
But I drive a foreign car
I do believe in God
But I promote humanism
I don't believe in war
But I'm for wiping out communism
Now I believe everything
That I hear on the news
And I can't figure out
Why the Arabs hate the Jews
I am an American
American hypocrite
Hey I'm a Jew
And I'm really proud of that
It don't bother me a bit
I can't believe the US government
Would ever lie to me
I'm an American hypocrite
Can't you see?
An American hypocrite
Now my TV sets on
Day and night
Turn into shows on violent crime
And I can't understand
Why my kids got a gun
And I'm drugged most of the time
I'm an American
An American hypocrite
And I'm really proud of that
It don't bother me
Not one bit
I'm an American
An American hypocrite
Oh yes dear friends
John Bartels the amazing
John Bartels there
And before that
Jello Biafra
And Mojo Nixon and
I should give some addresses now I think friends
I need you to get your pencils ready
One of them is a correction from a couple of weeks ago
We've been playing a lot of material by Rudy Schwartz Project
Also known as Joe Newman
And I gave his address over the air a couple of shows back
And apparently I did it wrong
I left a number out of his street address
So any of you who wrote for him
Information on Joe Newman's tapes
Here is the correct address for Rudy Schwartz Project
And a Joe Newman
That's Joe Newman
At the post office box 4542
Box 4542 in Austin, Texas
And while we're at it
I guess we ought to be giving our own post office box number
Yes the post office box number of
The Church of the Subgenius
That church who's
One of whose radio shows you are listening to right now
For better or for worse
So get that pencil ready
And be ready to just send for free information from
Bob
That's right
Or our slack or subgenius foundation
At
Here it is
The post office box
That's box 1403 06
Dallas, Texas
We'd love to hear from you
And send you catalogs about all the tapes books and what not
and death, horror, and fun, free pills, drugs, and evilness, music.
And let's listen to yet one other old subgenius show.
Well, actually, this would be a new subgenius show coming up in just a couple of minutes.
Reverend Susie the Floozy's show, which is broadcast, originates, shall we say,
at WREK in Atlanta, Georgia.
Stay tuned for Reverend Susie the Floozy, who's unfortunately had to get,
well, you'll hear the sad, sad tale.
¶¶
machine remember that the most unique gift ideas for all year at baskets and things they're in the
kenwood plaza just behind herschides give a gift of love from baskets and things at the kenwood
plaza and at northgate baskets and things wishes everybody a merry easter and a happy memorial day
the preceding commercial was seasonally updated for broadcast at this time
we're still working on what to do with the fourth of july
oh welcome let's see if we can get some sound up here
i'm gonna be real slack tonight because it's a frazzled night for the blues
listeners
it's good saturday and welcome to bob's
slack
time fun house number 13 lucky 13.
oh i'm your slack sister and polymorphously perverse prayer partner reverend susie the floozy but
oh i feel the need to make confession unto you dear friends i am stinky with sin oh purge me
oh pop this red aching boil of guilt and regret that feels like it's got its roots in my brain
oh either
reverend went out last week and
got a job
oh here i am in the belly of the feast and those digestive fluids are serving to eat away all that
tarnish and crud that's been building up on my survival skills i had become a little complacent
the sad fact is i needed the money the big problem was in the past few years i've been used to having free wills
Oh, that's a concept. They don't take much trucking in the corporate life.
Any kind of will.
Oh, sapped will. Oh, they love that.
Oh, but free will, or even will-a-dogs, who did an excellent show tonight.
Oh, they couldn't take that.
So, dear friends, by the virtue of my ministry,
and the auspices here at WREK Atlanta,
I need to make confession.
Oh, yeah, I got a job.
And even though it's not exactly a felch-level position,
I just feel so filthy.
Oh, I'm just passing a normal everyday life,
so you can imagine the amount of passing.
That's the last thing I've got to do to fit into a neo-corporate anti-existence.
Oh, there's one way to do it,
and it's like treating the whole thing as if I'm on a mission.
A mission to bring you the slack that you so desperately need.
And if that involves getting down on my knees in the muddy stinking trenches
to find out what the lack of slack is like,
so be it!
This is war!
I'm wallowing in the tar pits alongside my Yeti sisters and brothers.
I'm suffering, sweating, bleeding,
and bleeding in the workplace with you.
But here's a little workers' compensation coming your way right now.
I want you to feel that slack flowing out of the speakers and into your cerebral cortex,
massaging you with healing, stinging waves of Bob-given slack.
It's coating you like Bactine with aloe vera gel.
Dear friend, if you're so genius,
you know what it is to be a spy.
You know what it is to have your life on the line
every time you say the wrong thing or do the wrong thing
and get found out that you're not one of them.
So come on.
Let's slide into our trench coats,
pull our slouch hats down low over our ray-bands,
and slip into spy versus spy mode.
Let's go to it.
And if you're caught or captured,
this secretary will disavow any knowledge of your actions.
It's enough.
First of all, don't rush.
And here it goes.
They want you in the protection for a good time.
Good work.
Yeah.
Bye.
We're so glad you can all be here
And when life gets cold, oh so hard
You make it all the while
Scream yourself a laugh
And then a wild hit like a smile
This is getting heated too
Our friends across the world
You're the best, most loyalist
And that's for sure
When life gets cold, so push me
You make it all the while
Gonna have some fun tonight
Feel free to be alive
Scream yourself a laugh
And then a wild hit like a smile
It's gonna be happy
You're the only ones who understand
It's gonna be okay
It's gonna be alright
It's gonna be happy
You're the only ones who understand
That's what it is about this year
All is very well, CJ is here
And I can see the spells fall apart
Please give me today
It's the year I know you're gonna be
You're gonna find yourself a baby
It's gonna be okay
It's gonna be alright
It's gonna be happy
You're the only ones who understand
It's gonna be okay
It's gonna be alright
It's gonna be happy
You're the only ones who understand
It's gonna be alright
It's gonna be okay
It's gonna be happy
You're the only ones who understand
It's gonna be okay
It's gonna be happy
You're the only ones who understand
You understand
It's gonna be okay
It's gonna be alright
I asked you a pro capital punishment or amateur capital punishment.
We're amateur capital punishment or kill me.
Do you think capitals ought to be punished, Dr. Cabrog for him?
Not so much, but I guess it's a start.
Well, you can always get your parents to call in.
Miniature puterine reproductions authenticated by the world court at The Hague
and sent to you in moisture-resistant styrofoam chests
of the front door letter slots of the subgenius 36 most beloved characters.
Don't blow into the microphone, young man, if you wish to receive a beautiful Hummel figurine
which revolves on its ceramic base and plays the immortal Lara theme from Dr. Zhivago.
Yes, a special blue rivet advisory panel will ensure that the Foundation's Council
is certificated and inscribed insignia as approved by Dobbs, Master of Heralds,
before the application deadline.
No way.
What is your point to me?
Is it a potential?
Well, we are the potential guests.
So wait a minute.
What we've got to do is concentrate on those potential guests,
and you can stay with us for right now.
Now, Doctor, I think we should return to the basic finances of the church
and just who owns the church and what we can do with what's left of the church.
Right.
Well, Ivan Stang no longer owns the church.
Bob still has the Foundation, but we've got papers on that.
All right.
Hold on here.
Hold on.
Wait a minute.
What we also can talk about, of course, is what we can do with the church
now that what's left is still here and breathing.
Well, we can give it away, or we can just let someone take the church for a spin.
See, what I think is that people don't realize that the church...
The church takes two rooms to keep and grow in your house.
At least two.
And the maintenance involved takes up most of the week anyway.
And it does not run on unleaded.
I'm sorry.
So...
You've made a big noise about wanting to know the truth.
I'm calling in and saying you want the church.
If you don't have at least two good-sized rooms in your house...
Yes, at least two good-sized rooms and a lot of money.
And a lot of...
And neighbors that don't mind Wotan showing up in the middle of the night.
Right, and you need stamps and gummage.
Get the idea?
Or kill me!
Now!
And, uh...
The guy...
It got to the point where the guy he was bothering pulled out a .32 and let him have it.
And at which point, the bullet hit him square in the chest and went through his lung and came out his back.
But instead of falling on the ground, he walked back in the bar and ordered a drink.
Get the idea?
Or kill me!
Now!
Let's have a body count!
No!
None dead!
It's a miracle!
Friends, it's a miracle!
Bob!
Praise Bob!
Stamps and gummage.
Yes, lots of stamps and gummage.
Would you sign here, please?
Okay, sign here.
I don't have any stamps and gummage.
Wait a minute.
Wait, wait.
Ah!
Thank you very much.
The world is over now.
You can return to your bed.
Wow!
We're trying.
Well, we're not trying hard enough.
Well, it's certainly very trying.
Send us more money.
Yeah, more money.
More money?
How much would you like?
Uh, uh, fifty thousand, would you say that would do it?
Uh, checks in the mail.
All right, thank you.
You're welcome.
You can expect your...
Next caller, please.
We'll put on the automatic Bob Nelson.
We'll put the automatic Bob Nelson on.
Here, turn myself off.
Yes, okay.
Where's my thesaurus?
Ricky, Lucy, Phil...
Here, Bob, here's your hat.
Put this part on.
Here, here we go.
Here.
Now, give, give it up.
Drive this station down Shattuck Avenue.