Can you feel the slack emanating?
Vibrating?
You're relaxing now.
Who knows what evil lurks in the...
The genius, powerful, swanky!
Dobbs, can I speak to Dobbs directly through this radio show, for once?
He's listening.
How could I stop you?
Okay, all right, look, Bob...
And then suddenly...
You said it a long time ago.
You said that it was going to take a whole lot longer.
Bob happens.
Longer and stronger.
Yeah, Bob happens all over, busting out all over like June.
Only in July.
Only...
It's the end of June and everything else.
The end of the world.
And it was incredible when the giant gleaming, glittering saucers
came out of the sky.
Came down to whisk Ivan's dang and his rag-tag band of followers
off to a planet of pulsating pleasures.
Yeah, we left, and now we're gone.
Once blind, but now we see.
Off into the sky.
Yep, X-Day happened, folks.
The world's over, and you're not listening to anything.
And you missed it.
We're not here.
We're already up there having...
Having the illicit sexual practices with...
You can call 849.
See you.
...space aliens.
You can call as the Yakatisma will yak to you.
And, um, you know, we actually pre-recorded this show
knowing that we would be gone from this terraqueous globe,
this ball of dung, planet mudball.
Hey, quit stepping on my ball.
I'm talking about this run-down sack of sheep shite,
which we call Earth.
Hey, don't...
Don't look at my face when you say sheep shite like that.
All right, I...
I was...
Perhaps, uh, a little bit harsh on the old place.
After all, born and raised here myself under one terrestrial gravity,
uh, right in the temperate zone of this dear little planet.
And I must say, uh, it's an honor.
But, uh, there is a time when one has to move out of the backyard,
leave one's tiny, backward, introverted, and inbred peasant village,
and go to the big city, the big yard,
where all sorts of...
wonderful things happen.
They start churning up the, uh, succotash, the goulash, and the molasses.
I went down to Brushwood on X Day
Dreamin' about that saucer day
And he who has the holy luck
Good Bob, show me the way
Oh, Bobbies, let's go to the big yard,
and slow down
Hello.
Well, this is a group of twelve people from, uh, Russia
who want to visit the festival, X Day Festival, tomorrow.
Uh, we will try to call you back, uh, early again,
and find out how we can manage with it.
Thank you.
You are at peace with the world.
You are at peace with yourself.
Can you feel the slack emanating?
Can you feel the slack vibrating?
You have no worries.
You have no pain.
You are at peace with yourself.
It's biofeedback.
Slack biofeedback.
Relax.
Breathe deep.
Speak up, Dave.
Everything's all right.
Folks, this is the live hour of Slack here at X Day...
Which one is this?
Number nine.
Nine X Day.
Three times three.
It is the number.
The number is nine.
Nine.
Nighan.
Vise ya to X Day nine.
Now, this...
The recorder's machines can't hear you.
I just dreamed...
Speak into the rectifier.
...the bottom of the swimming pool.
The little barbed pool noodles surrounding my body like the squid.
I was fattened.
And I couldn't...
No longer move.
I could feel they were starting to become part of my body.
My body was absorbing the barb-pool noodles.
And I was fatter, and soggy, and I couldn't get out.
But then you surely must have realized...
...every time you've been sick, your body's getting weaker and weaker.
Everything was all right.
If you would only give in and allow yourself to be sucked down into the abyss of Bob.
Step into the vacuum.
Fall into the abyss.
Fathom after fathom into the inky darkness.
Now, if I could just get my right arm splashed and dried here just correctly.
I can fly.
This pipe.
I can fly with this pipe.
In terror and woe, he flung his right arm to the left.
His left arm to the right.
And his feet stamped the nether abyss in trembling and howling in dismay.
And cry.
What have I lost?
What have I gained?
And when are we going to get something to eat?
I think the sandwiches are on their way.
Here comes the sandwich boy now.
The sandwich encompasses the entire earth.
The wasteful desert.
It's not a sandwich.
It's a gun.
Some kind of weapon.
Guns or sandwiches.
Which shall it be?
Hello, you're on the air.
Oh, hi, Dr. Sinister.
Welcome, Reverend Stang.
How are you?
Let me turn down my time-controlled machine there in the background.
Now you're experiencing everything six seconds in the future.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, it's easier here in the future.
Yeah.
Everything hurts, though.
I'm recuperating from X-Day, which was very physically strained.
It's been continuous.
Just from having to put up the displays and everything on the stage there and take it
down?
Yeah, I had to pack everything and then unpack it all and then pack it all up and
then unpack it and so forth.
I was expecting to get a new body.
And so I kind of misused the one I had.
Well, they're sending us refurbished bodies, obviously.
Well, the one I'm using is getting refurbished right now, I think.
It's in the shop?
Sort of.
Slowly but surely.
Oh, me?
Oh, my.
Who the hell is in this club?
I never felt this way.
I think I like to stay.
It's given me excitement.
It's given me damn right.
It's given me so much more.
It's a slack orgasm.
Yes, it's a slack orgasm.
What?
Not that.
I can't believe you thought of that.
It feels so fascinating.
Oh, wow.
Oh.
Woo!
It's very titillating.
It's a slack orgasm.
Oh! It's a slack orgasm!
Oh!
It's a slack orgasm!
Oh my god!
Faster.
Harder.
Give me more!
Master.
It's a slack orgasm!
Oh my god!
NONE YET!
NO DON'T STOP!
OH IT'S A SLACK OR NASTER!
Oh yay!
Dear friends that was Princess Pisces singing at the 9X Day Drill
Improvising the words which she did for like two hours on Sunday night
With Reverend Carter LeBlanc on bass
Reverend Phil on drums
Reverend 2Beams on synthesizer
And Reverend Angry Larry on the guitar
And the amino acids are heard in the background
There's lots more where all of that came from
...of a great and powerful civilization
Yeah
Let us prepare for our world-est
Cool
Friends we're also going to be hearing some amazing talk and music from Dr. Howell
This is Hour of Slack number 1055
The first of at least four shows scavenging the holy recordings from the World Subgenius Festival
Plus
Other radio shows
Such as
A Dr. Sinister's Radio Synesthesia on WCSB in Cleveland
And also
A puzzling evidence from KPFA in Berkeley with Dr. Philodrummon and Dr. Howell
To which we can now return if you are man enough
I'm man enough for both of us
And now she's going straight up into the UFO
But I'm woman enough for all
It is like Independence Day
It's all cream and porcelain
There go all the little sub gum beans
There they go
Into the little hole in the bottom of the UFO
Streaming like particles into the solar wind
Ah yes carrying their little pencils and pens where they take notes in heaven
Is that what those are?
Ringing like wind chimes as they disappear through apertures into the black ether
Look they tickle her as they go by
And he prophesieth not
Yeah it feels kind of nice doesn't it?
For on the fields of Moab did Paul speak of unbelief
Oh no
Unbelief
That means he had it and then he undid it
He was a tax collector
And yea though I say unto ye the spirits of Moab leaketh not unto thine face
Ew
You know tax collector
Sounds like him
A tax collector invented the Doberman Tenture
Oh yeah
Yeah to help collect taxes
Giveth no place to the devil
Oh oh
Put not by the devil
I have seen my fingers under the armpits of another one
Say thanks my friend
I lift a maggot from his cloven hook
I have seen my uncles and aunts put their fingers under the armpits of another person and lift
By levitation of the Holy Spirit
Here we go folks I was trying to keep it on end state
The end of the world happened
And these are the semi-demigods of the church right here
Witnesses to the end of the world
They were actually there
My dear Jesus Christ
Yes, X-Day continues. The spectacle, the human triumph of X-Day.
They started as humble primates, simple humans. It's turned way too high up, I think.
And then, in the fullness of time, over millions of years of evolution, these shambling pre-humans acquired a better posture and less shuffling gait and more responsibility and a job and a place in the corporate state.
No more shambling through the veldt, chasing the exhausted world.
Or vice versa for Homus Novo, the new man, salary man, on his way to his job at Beetlebrow Industries.
But the workaday world must go on, whether of capitalism or communism or any system.
But it's lucky for us, for you and everyone, that we, members of the Church of the Subcontinent,
are able to pervert that productive impulse into performing these services, obsequies and ceremonies.
That's X-Day, folks.
All I can say is, well, there'll be another one next year.
Yet another X-Day.
The next.
And the end of the world happens again and again and again.
Well, until we get it right, dadgummit.
Well, or, yeah.
And I wrote a song about it.
Was that a pigeon?
Uh, no, it was a, uh...
Did I just hear a pigeon?
I actually did perform it with two members of the amino acids, uh, on stage.
Seriously, am I hallucinating?
And Princess Wee harmonizing, harmonization, harmoni...
Princess Wee was singing along on the chorus.
Could be a morning dove, maybe.
The subgenius hymn, for in the midst of life, the subgenius gene will suddenly activate.
Destroying red blood cells with an embarrassing noise.
Friends!
Intellectual stimulation has not ended.
The amino acids is not the last band standing.
Oh my fucking God!
On the way here, uh, Dr. Howland Owl, our esteemed guest, the toast of San Francisco.
He was delayed on a plane for, uh, 48 hours.
He'd have to circle around the world.
He's from Philadelphia, and he spent that time writing a song, which is 48 hours long.
However, uh, he and Princess Wee are going to perform an excerpt from this song, an ex-day song.
I have not heard it. I don't know anything about it.
And most importantly, I am not responsible.
Dr. Howl and Princess Wee, praise Bob Hilkamp.
Woo!
I have to get my lyrics.
Thank you!
Hello, friends.
You know, I did have a terrible amount of trouble getting here,
because I was opposed by the demons of the air, the powers of darkness.
And yet, uh, for all their formidable power, here I stand.
I managed to make it among you.
And so, as a final expression of triumph
over these inchoate, uh, entities of, uh, evil and chaos,
uh, Princess Wee is going to assist me in, uh, singing this ex-day song, which I wrote.
You may consider this, uh, an irritating imposition,
or you may consider it a moment of subgenius history in the making or on the hoof.
The choice is yours.
Yay!
Ex-day is here.
The mountains fall.
I cringe and hide my head.
I never send in my thirty bucks.
My soul is filled with dread.
Oh, Bob, just let me live.
And all that is mine.
I most surely will give.
Oh, lift me away on your bright saucer ship
to my subgenius home.
Oh, bear me away on your bright shining ship
I laughed at Bob.
Ah, woe is me.
I thirst for slack.
I'm back in vain.
Now he still grins and smokes his pipe.
I must have been insane.
Oh, Bob, just let me live.
And all that is mine.
I most surely will give.
Oh, lift me away on your bright saucer ship
to my subgenius home.
Oh, bear me away on your bright shining ship
I saw the pigs and normals flee.
The dreadful harvest from the sky.
They perish by the melting snow.
Yet not a one knows why.
Oh, Bob, just let me live.
And all that is mine.
I most surely will give.
Oh, lift me away on your bright saucer ship
to my subgenius home.
Oh, bear me away on your bright shining ship
The towers of the proud did fall.
There was no shelter from that storm.
While far above the subgeniuses watched
in comfort, safe and warm.
Oh, Bob, just let me live.
And all that is mine.
I most surely will give.
Oh, lift me away on your bright saucer ship
to my subgenius home.
Oh, bear me away on your bright shining ship
base
to James
Allィ
Wilson
toíp
t
m
spring
Co
Bo
and
Wednesday
Bo
du
You know, there's a thin, thin line between subgenius and complete idiot fuckhead, and
sometimes I cross that line.
In fact, what frightens me the most is how frequently I find myself doing something so
stupid, I can barely believe it or forgive myself, and yet I do, because I'm then always
reminded, the next guy's probably even worse.
That is the horror of today's modern world.
As dumb as the subgenius is, his neighbor is even dumber.
And right now we're listening to a baby bellowing on a bullhorn, folks.
Just one of the many ambient sounds you can hear at Camp Nake of the Woods, hideaway.
Oh, here's a little...
I came up with a dumb...
dumbness rant, speaking of dumbness, my own dumbness and that of others.
Nikki had reported that she had almost gotten killed by a...
and yet was saved by dumbassery.
A dumbass almost killed her, but the reason...
in a truck.
But the reason she wasn't killed by the truck is because she'd been held up in the ATM line
by another dumbass.
Held up, you say, in the ATM line?
Well, so to speak.
And I was prompted to say...
that I was really glad she wasn't killed, because then we'd have to cancel X-Day and so forth.
And speaking of helpless, mewling crybabies, that that's what I'd be without her and...
Reverend artist formerly known as Magdalene to do the stuff that they do, because I don't even know what it is.
But the... but the point was, I do not envy you lovely younger people.
You're 20 years or more younger than I am, so you'll probably live 20 years further into the future.
And that just means you'll see 20 years...
worth more of the devolution.
Everybody is getting dumber.
The dumbest reproduce fastest, and because of that, death becomes a blessing for the old.
And for everybody else, since people often get dumber as they grow old.
You can't imagine how painful it is to watch people getting dumber and dumber.
Some of them dumber even than me.
And knowing that it's only gonna get worse and worse.
Only a truly species-threatening crisis like X-Day...
or a massive asteroid strike or war or disease...
could cause human intelligence to start evolving upwards again.
Oh sure, somebody may come up with an intelligence drug...
that lets nerds remember pointless facts and figures better.
But that's not quite the same as 10,000 years of hard knocks...
and furtive illicit fucks behind bushes when the silverback isn't looking.
You're probably gonna have to watch humans get 20 years dumber than I will.
Unless you do get hit by a truck or something.
And you probably can't dumb yourself down to whatever is the current lowest common denominator...
in order to accept it all better.
I tried for years, but I found I just could not keep up with the Joneses, so to speak.
Self-dummification-wise.
I had to give up.
I couldn't wipe out brain cells fast enough to keep pace with the younger people or the older people.
Most of them don't even need drugs to become dumber.
It happens for those lucky stiffs automatically.
So said Reverend Ivan Stang that one day.
Amen.
That is my rant.
Yes, Reverend Ivan Stang.
That is my testimony.
And so there.
And a goodly rant it was.
Listen to that massive applause here in Carnegie Hall.
This well of applause attests the sincerity of the belief of the audience...
in all the principles you have espoused here today.
Here on Tarzan's radio station.
Which, by the way, sounds so much better in these headphones...
than it does through my son's hand-me-down speakers.
And anyone who ever wanted to donate speakers to the Subgenius Foundation...
we're begging.
Help us articulate our message.
There was a lot encoded in that noise I just made.
If you can have the decompression codec...
Yes, you need good stereo equipment to decrypt it.
And that we are unable, ethically and legally, to provide.
You have to supply this high-tech equipment yourself.
Or make your ears a lot better.
But we can't make you smarter, as Nenslow said.
So shut up, as Nenslow said.
You can lead a horse to water.
But you can't make him drink.
You know, that's another one of those old wise-sounding sayings...
that probably isn't true and makes no sense.
Oh yeah, you think you can make him drink?
You think you can make that horse drink?
It depends on the horse. It depends on the master.
Bob could make that horse drink, you know.
Bob could make him drink.
But the horse, if it drinks, then it was its idea.
Not necessarily yours.
I see you're missing some keys on your pad here.
But bravely we soldier on.
Though we may be sleep-deprived.
Brain buzzed and a few bats shy of a belfry.
We're still able to handle the tremendous, titanic, organizational mass of duties, devotions, and events at X-Day.
Like hiding from the rain and lightning.
And we never get to see a song.
I'm sure you've heard of it.
It's called a dance.
Dance!
It's a slack disco
Slack go-go
Start bouncing!
My brain is empty!
I can't see clearly!
It seems something's happened to me?
Things are strange.
They're not quite the same.
Something's emanating.
My breathing.
It's flowing through me.
It's kinda groovy.
It's getting stronger.
I can't take it any longer!
You couldn't do it if you hadn't played.
Shake it!
I'm gonna feed myself!
No I can't!
Was too much!
No, you were too much!
Do something!
You give me a break.
and by drugs I mean
hugging
and coffee
and beer
there was beer
and even hugging
if that's what you said
did you say hugging?
let's all cuddle
not exactly
come on you know you'd be into it
is there a big bowl full of cornstarch
and orange pulp
there was some sort of thing that I missed
involving naked women sliding
downhill on a plastic slide
slip and slide?
yes that's it exactly
oh yay
once again
Ragnar's girlfriend was a participant
and she claimed about
the bruising she received
also the bruising she received
at the naked uluhuk contest
which did indeed
produce bruises on her waist
which everyone was looking at
is she anemic?
not at all
more full blooded I should say
so
then
we had the body painting contest
you got that girl because of Bob
and we covered each other's bodies
with beloved subgenius icons
meanwhile Susie the floozy was leaving
tiny tattooed turrets of angels
around the campsite
and she also made special new insignia
for the subgeniuses
of an eyeball supported by wings
sort of like a fascist
Nazi eyeball subgenius thing
that we wore on our clothes
and our equipment
and some of us made new friendships
over and over again
yes
and now
now what about swingers?
is there a subgenius swinger community out there?
are you kidding?
there's yeah I mean there's a
I'm actually not part of it
because I'm an old square and I'm so
I'm an old square and I'm so
happy to be so happily married now
I don't want to shake it up
but there's a
I almost think that the square types
are outnumbered by the swingers
there's quite a bit of that going on out there
during X day and also
Starwood of course features
a lot of members of the church of all worlds
which is an overtly swinging and swapping cult
kind of fat old gray haired hippies
but hey if you're a fat old gray-haired hippie
that's hot action
yeah I think that's the problem
that a lot of the younger Bobby's
you know had is that you know those who
those who are available tend to be
a bit older
and not that there's anything wrong with getting old
it's just that
oh I don't know from what I hear
the kids nowadays are all practically
practically doing
in elementary school the kinds of things you know
that I was just starting to learn about in college.
Well, keep in mind...
Of course, that was in the previous century.
Well, keep in mind they're arresting the teachers
responsible for that as fast as they can,
you know, and the priests as well, you know.
And plus, bragging ultimately isn't the bragging
more important than the sex itself.
That certainly seems the way it is.
I don't know about that.
The amount of bragging I've heard
versus the amount of actual sex that I have heard
I mean, there's just no comparison.
And I think there are some people that...
Well, I don't know.
It's the only way they can hurt other people's feelings
is to brag about who they've done.
Whereas others, the only way that...
The best way they can hurt other people's feelings
is to brag about who they declined to do.
And I don't want to hurt anybody's feelings,
so I'm going to...
I'm going to shut up.
Before you do that, Reverend, saying,
well, first, to beg Jonathan,
thanks for the role of confidence.
Second, I have a question for you
about how many subgeniuses would you say are not white?
What?
Are not white?
Yeah.
I have no idea.
I mean, I don't know...
We don't even know how many subgeniuses there are.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, no sense.
If you looked around next day,
if you looked at the stage,
the stage...
The subgenius church is about a fifth black.
But that was just the stage.
Yeah, if you look at the audience, it's pretty pasty.
Yeah.
In fact, if you count the living dead,
they're whiter than white.
Yeah.
I was...
To tell the truth,
it's not just white people
because there were a whole lot of Italians
and Puerto Ricans, subgeniuses that were there.
And even, I dare say, I suspect,
there may even have been one or two Jewish people.
Then there was Rasna.
Well, Rasna is an alien.
He's from another world.
Rasna doesn't count either way.
Yeah, I don't think...
In subgenius land, none of those things matter.
Exactly.
You know, we're...
Pinkness is not a color.
It's an attitude.
We're all descended from the Yeti.
You know, not all of us look alike.
Some of us look pretty different from now on.
But the point is, you know,
there's the Yeti race
and then there's the rest of you.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh!
Oh, Bob!
What?
Yeah, you can do it there.
You're a dirty little Bob.
Meow.
Not too hard, Bob.
It's Charlie and his orchestra.
Yeah, they should have played that during certain intervals.
Big videos and some big projector over the hot tub or something.
Oh, at X Day?
Yes.
No, they did not.
No, they didn't.
In fact, that has never been tried.
It could be done inside the bathhouse.
There's probably enough room for a throw.
But you'd ruin your equipment and get it wet, which you don't want to do.
Well, no, you put it outside and have it.
To perform the baptism in the pool, I wore the fez.
And that's all, right?
No, I wore complete outfit, pants, T-shirts.
I'm not going to be naked.
I'm an official.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
I forgot.
I did.
That's like me.
I'm never naked.
Use my hands.
I'm just never naked, ever.
Well, first of all, whenever I get naked, I embarrass all the guys.
It's true.
But that's because...
You want another cup of my rum martini?
My job was to make sure that people who sang pushed under the water came back up.
Just have one more.
It'll make you feel better.
My job was to hold them underwater by the ankles.
I got to say this because he has...
You're passing out?
I have another one, sweetheart.
It's night, ain't it?
You're passing out again.
That's why he says I can't hold my...
Well, folks, we're trying to get the new talent here.
He has my...
I got your back.
I got my...
Shut up.
Oh, the backseat of the show.
There she goes.
That's going to be hard to clean up.
Ah, yes.
Just right on time.
Well, Santa was...
You guys just gave so much...
You know, Santa...
Hold on still.
When you and Santa were close...
...at one time.
Yeah.
Yeah, that was just like...
Do you think it was the cough syrup?
It was the cough syrup.
Or the liquid slime.
Oh, Robitussin.
Just because Santa gives you Robitussin for Christmas
doesn't mean you have to drink it.
Here is my...
...tussin.
The...
Brought to you by the Church of the Subgenius.
Dallas, Texas.
J.R. Bob Dunn.
No longer in Dallas, Texas.
Now operates from an all-new Cleveland, Ohio address.
Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
Pretending like it was an oldster thing.
Cleveland's flats and St. Louis' clapper alley.
Boston's north end.
Beware, beware.
Subs are everywhere.
But, anyway, that's all right.
From each according to his means
to each according to his needs.
What?
That's not Dobbsian.
No, that was Chairman Mao Zedong.
Yeah, that's...
Bob's no commie.
But when dealing with Philo,
you have to use...
Whatever system can catch his slippery essence.
From each according to his means to Bob.
From everybody to Bob.
That's the direction everything ultimately flows
in the great vortex,
which makes him the center of the luck point.
Which is the ball of the pipe.
Right.
The vortex point.
The maelstrom.
The singularity.
In the bunch bowl.
Yeah, singularity in the punch bowl, friends.
Well...
Are you ready?
When your cup dips up...
We must gird our loins
and put on our spiritual armor.
Strap on our buckler
and sharpen our sword
for the reaping of the horrible harvest is nigh.
We'll stand, oh we'll stand
hand in hand
when the trumpet calls
extending
in a brother and sister band
while they blow the world away.
We shall have paradise
subgenie of the world
united.
Alien sex
every night.
Subgenie of the world.
Unite.
Fly, Dagi!
Come on, cockpit.
Now, we are among the hyenas...
...in an army of dinosaurs.
to the fr Clinica reader.
atura,
lerde grisal,
Not пер путahrè ordam
gray.
no body can do
manufactured
wings?
We shall have paradise, so dreamy of the world you'll die
And I'll search for happiness, so dreamy of the world, so dreamy of the world, so dreamy of the world you'll die
Are you alone or died? Not sure you're all away
Such a long life, they all in one must die
We shall have paradise, so dreamy of the world you'll die
Every night, so dreamy of the world, so dreamy of the world, so dreamy of the world
you'll die
Every man with a trumpet for his dear
Doesn't sit still and doesn't throw the wood away
We shall have paradise, so dreamy of the world you'll die
Every night, so dreamy of the world you'll die
And I'll search every night, so dreamy of the world, so dreamy of the world, so dreamy of the world you'll die
YAY!
Thank you Dr. Drummond.
The malarkey's not over yet!
Well, of course.
I got a little malarkey.
Alright, let's continue with the malarkey then.
Oh no, not more malarkey.
I got my malarkey coat on.
Oh yeah.
Oh.
Yeah, it's right here actually.
Just a few, a few quick words for you before you all go to bed, because I know you're going directly to sleep tonight because we all have to go to church in the morning.
Yeah, funny, joke.
I kid, I kid.
Regardless, I have to just say this.
Just to speak to you very quickly on a topic, a topic that's dear to my heart.
I need to talk to you about, well the general topic of my conversation can be summed up in one word.
Evolution.
Now those of you that know me will know that I do dabble in a bit of the old anthropology.
I may have fiddled with some genetic material here, a few archeological remnants there, some bones, some fossils, some australopithecines, and some, you know, various, various devices and creatures of the, of the distant and near future.
And I'm not going to go into that.
But I need to talk to you about the topic of evolution.
But before I do that, I'm going to cast your memory back.
I don't know if you remember the early 90s.
I remember the early 90s pretty well.
It was a formative time of my life.
It was, it was a wonderful time.
It was heady.
It was, it was exotic.
There was a lot of fun things happening.
There were, there were, well I don't know if you remember that the alien motif had become fairly strong.
You couldn't turn, you couldn't turn a corner without seeing an alien head somewhere.
Or somebody's X-Files poster somewhere.
Or a conspiracy theory.
We had these great movies like JFK.
Great conspiracy movie.
These other, you know, shows like Millennium and these dark sinister references to the conspiracy.
The conspiracy, the conspiracy that we all know so well.
And these things were so strong they were ever present.
They were, they were, it was like a rich and varied tapestry that we could, we could pull from.
We could pull these, these crazy magazines.
I don't know if you remember.
Myles.
The Condo 2000.
What a great magazine.
All sorts of freaky articles.
And things like, well, things like, well, 2600 which still publishes.
But what a great magazine.
These, these rich and, and fertile counter cultural moments that we had to enjoy.
And, and, and you, you, you got to watch these things and see these things happen.
And the conspiracy was in the air.
You, people were taught, people were aware of it.
People knew.
Aliens.
Area 51.
Conspiracy theories.
Yetis.
Alien abduction.
You know.
The, all these exciting things.
It was great.
It was fantastic.
And, and, and if you notice, these things have faded into the background.
I mean, for those of us that are, are still willing to look, they're still there.
They haven't gone away.
But we don't hear about them.
They don't make movies about these things.
Yeah.
They don't, they don't talk about these things.
And conspiracy theories.
Oh, ha, ha, ha.
9-11 conspiracy theories.
They're so funny.
Oh, as if anybody would do anything like that.
But you know, the thing is, is the conspiracy theorists themselves have become ridiculous
attention hounds.
And, and, and all this, when, when did this change?
Oh, September 11.
No, it didn't change.
I'll tell you exactly when it changed.
It changed on July 5th, 1998.
Do you remember what happened after July 5th, 1998?
It all went to hell.
Yes.
Now, I want to bring you back to that thought.
Because.
I'm going to tell you something very interesting about the aliens.
The greys.
You know, everybody knows about the greys.
We've all seen the pictures.
We've looked at them.
We've thought about them.
Alien abductions.
Ooh, what are the greys?
Where are they from?
What do they do?
Why are they here?
Who are they working for?
Well, let me tell you something.
The alien greys are us in the future coming back to try and secure their own existence.
But they only one path.
There is a path.
There is another path.
It's another one we haven't heard a whole lot about lately.
The other path.
This is divergent evolution.
See, evolution conducts itself in a fashion known as punctuated equilibrium.
And let me tell you, the subgenius is the punctuation in that equilibrium.
If you're a Bavarian, well, then it's a question mark.
And if you're an emergenteal, it's an exclamation point.
But regardless, the subgenius is the punctuation in punctuated equilibrium.
And let me tell you, the equilibrium is about to be punctuated.
Praise God!
Thank you.
And let me tell you why.
Because we are at a point where we can decide what direction we want to go in.
And when we're thinking about the greys, that possibility becomes more real and more
potential.
But let me tell you something else about the greys.
You don't want to be a part of it.
You don't want to become like they are.
Because they are only one possibility.
They don't eat.
They smear decomposed, rotting cow parts that they have dipped in acid until it's retained
its sole biogenic qualities.
And they paint it on their skin and absorb it.
They don't enjoy food.
They don't drink beer.
They don't fuck.
They don't taste.
They don't even have fucking teeth.
You want to keep your teeth, don't you?
You don't want to keep your teeth.
You don't want to become like them.
What's in the other direction?
Because if you look at evolution, you move in one direction, you get less teeth.
Because you become specialized.
This is something that Darwin figured out.
He said specialization.
You discard these unnecessary characteristics.
Unnecessary characteristics.
I like my teeth.
I like my functioning genitalia.
I like my sense of taste.
I like my ability to process alcohol and other alcohol.
You got to call me up on a date.
Listen.
I don't have any of that.
How can I you?
Your video clip shows my eyes.
I miss the Levitis.
I make my eyes look like ecstell procure and gloves on!
The idea of getting rid of the balloon is awesome, but it didn't like these snobbish
That was the idea, baby.
You just have to understand 엉
Let's try that again.
Or even at your place, why don't the fools from the
their house throw me out there?
Because he wants to remove me?
How does that hurt?
My whole, whole body hurts.
Man, there's no pain.
Change the mileage day.
we don't want to become like those sterile
saucer crashing
motherfuckers
those abducting anal probers
that have no life
they have no slack
they are grey
they aren't even pink
but let me tell you
we're not hearing about them
and we're not hearing about the yetis
why? because both
possibilities seem to be
fading and receding
and we're at a crossroads
we're at a crossroads
we can go this way or we can go this way
well I don't know if you've ever been at a crossroads
there are four directions
at every crossroad
and we're at that crossroad
and one direction
leads towards certain death
for all of us
extinction for the homo sapien
sapien
and I'll talk about pinks
a little bit
but I tell you
biogenic structuralism indicates
that the religious
ecstatic experience
is hardwired into every single human being
we all have the potential
to be a subgenius
but let me tell you
not everybody's going to use it
there's two kinds of monkeys
on this planet
there's the dumb monkeys
and there's the stupid monkeys
and thank Bob I'm a dumb monkey
but I ain't no stupid monkey
yeah
but I
will be static
just throw me a drink
or a glass of toast
with my drink
do I have to slow my ding dung down
just
got to
at
go
yeah
right now.
Yeah!
Ow!
Is that your direction?
No, okay.
But one direction
leads towards the
greys, and one direction
leads towards the yeti.
And I know what direction I'm moving in.
I want more hair on my body,
not less.
I want functioning genitalia.
I want a sense of taste, smell,
touch, hearing.
I don't want to fucking hear what's in your brain.
I don't give a shit about telepathy.
I can see what's
on your mind by looking at
your face and smelling
the pheromones that come
out of your skin.
And that's what
subgeniuses do. The ooze
squirt is something
a grey will never understand.
And let me tell you,
the conspiracy loves the
idea of the greys
because they're all the same.
But the subgenius
is irreplaceable.
Every single subgenius is irreplaceable.
How many Janers do we have here tonight?
I'm a Janer!
Woo!
You're an Alex, bitch!
And I know it.
And you should never be anything
but, because you're
fucking awesome.
But Janer told me I was a Janer!
That's because he's Janer, and he says those things.
But there's only one
Ivan Stang.
He's the only one
that's going to be here tonight.
There's only one Princess Wee.
There's only one single...
Every time we lose a subgenius,
that subgenius is gone.
Gone. Irreplaceable.
Every single one of you
represents a unique,
evolutionary perspective.
And we need to preserve that.
We need to preserve that.
Like I said, we're at the crossroads.
It's going to get really ugly up ahead.
And y'all better be ready.
And you better be ready to move in
the direction that's going to give your life flavor.
The direction that's going to give your life substance.
The direction that's going to give you
good, squishy, ooze, squirt, and sex hurt.
The direction that's going to give you SLACK!
Can I get a praise, Bob?
Praise Bob!
Woo!
Yes, David!
Yeah, baby!
E-Y-I! E-Y-I!
That was, of course, the Reverend
Carter LeBlanc, ladies and gentlemen.
Let's hear it for him once more.
Praise Carter LeBlanc!
You have been hearing the
subgenius radio ministry, Hour of SLACK.
The song before
Reverend Carter's incredible rant
there was Lonesome Cowboy Dave
jamming with Princess Leigh and
basically the two of the Amino
Acids. Who are also heard
in the background playing at 9XD
and of which more can be had at
theaminoacids.com
For more information
on Church of the Subgenius
see www.subgenius.com
or write to
P.O. Box 181
417 Cleveland Heights,
Ohio 44118
Praise Bob!
So that's your next
big thing now, right Hal?
You're going to get ready for the man?
Yeah, I guess I'm going to have to,
but I'll tell you this, I'd be surprised
if I had as much delight and pleasure
at the man as I have just had it
right at X Day.
Aww, you had a good time last year, right?
Last time I had an okay time, yeah sure.
Last time I had a pretty good time,
but this year I was extremely...
The man's just a lot of work now.
There's no SLACK at the man anymore.
Well, now you're talking about
um, um, yeah... You can't get
SLACK at the man. You're talking about Vernon Mann now.
I've gotten SLACK at Vernon Mann.
It's X Day though, that's the place
that's designed for SLACK.
It's designed for SLACK, man.
Designed for Hagar SLACK.
Sammy Hagar.
So what are you drawing pictures of?
I see those diagrams you have in front of you there.
So, X Day,
actually it's the lyric sheet
for my song, but I think
it does contain irrelevant
drawings that have nothing
whatever to do with the lyrics.
Electronic mail flying around
for almost a whole weekend.
But I can explain this to you
if you would like.
Yes, I would like.
What you have is an iron bar
and it's drawn up this ramp by a magnet.
As it moves up the ramp...