This is Doug Smith, radio operator. I'm going to bring you a piece of that green cheese for sure.
You're a joke! A dirty joke from one end of this town to the other!
The Self-Genius Power of Self-Genius
This is an urgent public service bulletin from your police department.
A dangerous killer beast is at large. You are asked to remain indoors.
This is an urgent public service bulletin to all citizens.
This whole thing is cockeyed.
Friends, we bid a fond farewell to the great Maynard G. Krebs.
Goodbye, Bob.
Knowing her fate, Atlantis sent out ships to all corners of the Earth.
On board were the Twelve.
The poet, the physician, the farmer, the scientist, the magician, and the other self-genius.
The Self-Genius!
Power of Self-Genius!
What?
Slack's back with his spicy crispy Slackjack sandwich.
A spicy crispy Slack with fresh lettuce and tomato.
Only at Slack in the Box restaurants.
Doug Smith, Bob. Doug Smith, Bob.
Doug Smith, Bob. Doug Smith, Bob. Doug Smith, Bob.
I'm looking the soup in your soul of Slack since I can't understand what you're saying.
You can't understand what you're saying.
We cannot understand what you're saying.
Price Bob, Price Bob, it's not glass Bob.
From PR news in Washington, I'm sentenced to life in prison for funding Bob.
President Bush envisions as many as 180 people returning to Beijing.
At least 21 people have been ordered to stay on their medication.
On Wall Street, 86105564.
A new study finds that most people with schizophrenia are meeting in Vienna and they've expressed concern about PR news in Washington.
For 14 hours, Rudy Wells and his team of highly trained specialists painstakingly labor over the battered and broken body of Bobby.
How do you feel?
You're now faster, stronger, more durable than you ever were.
Just what did you guys do to me?
I don't want any part of any of it. I'm getting out of here.
Stay in your bed.
Wild man, wild man, this will stop him.
Then.
I didn't think we'd ever stop him.
How do you feel?
I'm stronger, faster, better.
But you left out one thing. I'm not a man anymore.
I'm afraid.
Personal diary.
But somebody ought to Moon Pie her.
What's the problem, boy?
I've been busting my hump all week for that withered old clam, and all I got was fifty cents!
Hey, when I was your age, fifty cents was a lot of money.
Really?
Nah.
Dad, I've done everything I could and I've only got thirty-five bucks!
I am through with working! Working is for chumps.
Son, I'm proud of you! I was twice your age before I figured that out!
From PR News in Washington I'm found in home.
roads and other sites. The massive Bush administration is now grappling with two
Japanese tourists after an assassination attempt on William Rehnquist. Homeland Security Secretary
Michael Chertoff says corpses will be home. The third fire in more than a week in Paris
is blamed for at least 14 deaths. Authorities suspect PR News in Washington.
And the water gonna come and I have no place to stay.
Well, all that night I sat on the lever and the moon.
Thinking about my baby and my happy home.
If it keeps on raining, the lever's going to break.
Can you hear me?
Can you guys believe how this guy ripped off Led Zeppelin?
Yeah, it's remarkable what goes on in this country nowadays.
People come up with some idea and claim that they invented the idea,
when in reality the idea was pre-invented.
Well, you would think that...
Well, by the Ministry of Culture, anyway.
I mean, what has happened to the trademark laws and copyright laws in this country?
It's back to the Ministry of Culture.
A singer can rip off a famous rock band like Led Zeppelin.
He's probably made...
He's probably made $25 dollars off of this thing.
Well, did you hear about...
This guy was involved with Robert Plant in a sexually deviant manner.
He was paid off under the table and beside the table by some sort of Rosicrucian, I guess it was,
from the Legal Defense Department.
They call them legal aides.
And I guess they're all condemned to hell for their...
Do you think that...
All witches are condemned to hell, too.
Yeah, but who does the condemning?
I'd like to know.
God.
Is God?
Well, there's one particular God.
Let's put it that way.
Oh, so he is the one in particular that's responsible for all this placebo mess and this garbage.
Well, there's the one that does the hell stuff and there's probably another one that doesn't.
So how many God, God, God, Gods would you say there is?
None.
But I was told to say that by the Spirit.
I was seized up and told in the Spirit to go out and preach the word of no God at all.
The guy in the movie Wise Blood.
I was taught by an elderly Bolshevik.
I got wise...
Oh, no, that was the crazy guy that said that.
Well, he was...
Yeah, that was the elderly Bolshevik.
The hero said,
I am not a preacher.
I'm a festerer of wounds.
I'm a rubber of salt in the eyes of man.
Well, I had to face it.
I'm a preacher, all right.
I'm a preacher of Bob's word.
I'm an undergrown pubish, Stan.
What shall I do?
Send $30.
I've polished the bump many times.
Send $30 to J.R. Bob Doves.
I bet you never actually...
You never actually did that, did you, Dave?
No, and I wonder...
I've seen that he would have been left behind if the exodus had come as promised on July 5th, 1998,
which may still be happening anytime.
Have you heard the phosphorescent rumors?
What?
That they're going around picking up subgena individually rather than this mass rupture that you had, you know, hoped to make a couple bucks off of.
I think they've been taking body parts individually, like your hair, my memory, Princess Wee's morals.
No, just kidding.
We have...
We have to throw in that...
We have to get those gags in somehow before we're gagged.
Well, thank God I don't...
I still don't have any gonads to speak of.
I just wanted to make that perfectly...
Did you really have to gonad there?
I mean, come on.
God, God, God, God, God.
That's the German word, you know, but we can't say the Arabic word.
God, God, God, God.
Allah, Allah, Allah, Allah.
We can't say that one.
How come God spoke German, Stan?
I'd like to know about some of this evangelical stuff.
So that we wouldn't be able to understand what he was saying.
Yeah, I think...
Yes, what is the...
If you're off something...
Well, we have some collages coming up that condemn the administration's foot dragging
as it dragged its feet off the rowboat through the waters of all the cities that have been flooded.
It sounds like a body dredging or something.
This is really hurricane season.
You know, the next hurricane is supposed to hit Phoenix, Arizona.
And there's one in China.
Somewhere in China, they're dealing with a typhoon.
Well, I heard...
The sixth one to come up after they go into the Omega, you know, the Alpha Omega cycle,
where they use Greek letters instead of funny names like Rita and Jane and stuff like that,
is scheduled to hit Denver on November the 7th.
That's where the eye will cross in the great, bolded, mile-high city of Denver.
For crying out loud.
Loud.
Praise Bob.
I think we have something about that coming up.
My daughter called me from Los Angeles to inform me that she was driving straight into one of those giant 24,000-acre Los Angeles farms.
Oh, Santa Ana.
Yeah, and I got interested in that, and I found this report from...
I'll go through this real swiftly, but to September 12th,
horror and disbelief swept through the greater Hollywood area this afternoon
as a minor power outage turned the city into a virtual war zone,
and local residents struggled to deal with the devastating aftermath.
Traffic lights fell dark.
Local gyms and sushi restaurants were without power for nearly...
30 minutes, and many businesses were illuminated only by the light of the sun and its blistering 78-degree heat.
Sugar in the raw? Are you kidding me?
sobbed local homosexual and avid salsa dancer Enrique Santoro.
I'm on a South Beach diet, and my insulin levels are going to go crazy if I use this.
Why isn't the rest of the country doing something?
At least 2,000 refugees, the majority of them beautiful,
will travel in a bus convoy to Beverly Hills starting this evening,
and will be sheltered in the...
8-year-old Spago on North Cannon,
where soft omelets with confit bacon and Hudson Valley foie gras
will be airlifted in by the National Guard.
Well, it sounds like paradise staying, but let's get real here.
Halliburton still was given the Los Angeles Reconstruction Contract.
Oh, yeah, yeah. Yeah, Halliburton and them will be cleaning up.
They'll get the big money off of these things.
And not cleaning the swimming pools, and, you know, the sushi restaurants will be running again their way.
I mean, come on, man. Nobody escapes the iron fist.
Nobody escapes the tender little baby booty that's filled with...
All this is not anointing me. It's not...
The other thing was...
Well, this is the sad part about all this.
The mayor of Hollywood, Johnny Grant, told a group of embedded reporters
at a Cuckoo Roo chicken restaurant on Larchmont that, quote,
The scope and scale of this disaster is almost too much to comprehend.
Local car washes are at a standstill.
The tram tour at Universal Studios has been on hold for almost an hour now,
and I've been waiting for a rotisserie leg and thigh with a side of green beans
for upwards of a year.
In 15 minutes, this is truly our tsunami.
Jeez, man, you're putting up the barbed wire in Topanga Canyon.
Yep.
And all of those poor, those poor Los Angelinos.
I feel so bad.
Listen to this.
Listen.
Okay.
A group of chickens masturbating.
Geese.
Can the geese masturbate?
Two.
One.
Three.
Two.
This geese aren't bad.
That's honking.
Yes.
You can honk along.
That is.
Ha, ha.
Honk, honk.
Honk.
Ha, ha.
Hoo.
Honk.
The mid-goose does the Mick Jagger dance.
I know that.
He has to lift the legs up a little bit, you know, and he put his one wing on his leg.
Oh, where's my...
Get the coxcomb going, yeah.
Where's my script of the devastatingly cool...
Stang, you're spontaneously among us.
You're not supposed to use a script or refer to any written pieces of paper.
Well, I have to because I have to say the credits, which is all Fernand and Andy Lee
Murr and Norrell Preff did pretty much everything.
And there's no sense in trying to tell people which part of what those two guys did, but
they did almost everything.
Well, who sampled the geeks?
That is hilarious and wonderful.
I don't know.
There was a...
We had some Beatles.
We had the Beatle Barkers did some of our background music there, and that was Kansas
Joe, by the way, doing the levee.
Now, he was involved in the...
When the levee breaks.
Ripped off the Led Zeppelin.
Oh, he was involved in ripping the legs off the Zeppels, or the Zeppelay there.
Yeah.
The brazen ripofferage.
Now, I'm going to play this devastating collage in a second here.
Can I ask you a question first?
Sure.
Because you're smart, and you remember things.
I forgot one.
Ontology recapitulates ontology.
What does that mean?
What?
I forgot.
Ontology recapitulates ontology.
Oh, I can tell you, but I'm not going to because it's too boring and it's all bogus, academic
bull pooey anyway.
I'll show you.
Okay.
It's a med speak.
Okay, here's the devastating collage, friends, by Phineas Snarko posted this, and it was
by Stephen McQuillan.
I don't think anybody anticipated the breach of the levees.
They'd anticipate a serious storm.
These levees got breached, and as a result, much of New Orleans is flooded.
He didn't think...
I don't think anybody had anticipated that.
Liar.
Saturday before the storm hit.
If we had a direct hit of a Category 4 or 5, and maybe even a Category 3, we would be
totally inundated with water.
We couldn't pump it all out.
I don't think anybody anticipated the breach of the levees.
The levees in Jefferson Parish, with the tidal surge that is presently forecast, will be
top.
We can expect our community to be significantly underwater, and for a number of days.
I don't think anybody anticipated the breach of the levees.
This is a city...
This is a city built on the coast, in an area that has hurricanes, and is built below
sea levels, and that is a super.
People have talked for years about whether it makes sense to have a city like that.
I don't think anybody anticipated the breach of the levees.
It looks like Hurricane Sluggo is headed right for us here in America's wetlands.
That's right.
And since New Orleans is below sea level, if a hurricane hit us directly, it could push
the water over the levees and fill it to the top.
Let's act now, before it's too late.
Theテレ e succes is already just behind us guys.
We going nowhere yet break.
My God God.
Blah blah blah blah blah blah, yeah yeah yeah yah yeah yah.
Whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa.
Guys.
clothes isэт.
Like you're doing.
Something else ish.
Good morning, America, how are you?
Wake up!
Say, don't you know me?
I'm your native son.
I'm the city of New Orleans.
I'll be gone when the day is done.
New Orleans is sacred land and I don't want to swim.
If it keeps on raining, that is going to break.
I don't think anybody anticipated the breach of the levees.
When the levee breaks, I have no place to stay.
Welcome to New Orleans.
Federal, state, and local governments are working side by side to sustain lives
by ensuring adequate food, water, shelter, and medical supplies for survivors and dedicated citizens.
Our dislocated citizens.
At that time, he was making a big deal about telling the nation that the convention center had been secured.
FEMA's moving supplies and equipment into the hardest hit areas.
All they had done is Geraldo Rivera actually reported on Fox.
The only thing they could do was they locked people in.
This is it. This is it. No sugarcoating. No political spin. No Republicans or Democrats.
People suffering. Let them go. Let them out of here.
Let them walk over this damn interstate and let them out of here.
I want to get some perspective here because earlier today the images were...
That is perspective.
Hang on a second.
That is all the perspective you need.
Anyone who walks up out of that city now is turned around.
I don't know, man. I don't... Let them walk the hell out of here.
Let them get on that interstate and walk out.
To the Walmart on the other side of the river.
To some other town. Some place where you can help them.
All you got here is thousands and thousands of people six days later.
Same clothes.
What do you think they're going to the bathroom?
They don't wash their hands. They don't wash their face. These babies.
There are so many babies here.
What the hell?
Come on and rescue me.
Six feet of water in the streets of Louisiana.
You simply get chills every time you see these poor individuals. So many of these people.
They're trying to wash us away.
They are so poor.
Some people got lost in the flood.
And they are so black.
Some people got away on the rain.
I'm white. And I'm alright.
I said white! I'm alright!
George Bush doesn't care about black people.
Here's Barbara Bush.
So many of the people in the arenas here, you know, were underprivileged anyway.
This is working very well for them.
They're being drawn to careers of service when the manpower of government is stretched thin.
We headed down to finally bring presidential leadership to the disaster zone.
President come down.
President's a little fat man.
He made a shame.
What the river has done.
This poor cracker's lame.
Out of the rubbles of Trent Lott's house,
he's had lost his entire house,
there's going to be a fantastic house.
And I'm looking forward to sitting on the porch.
Michael Cherdoff.
The Secretary of Homeland Security.
Sounds like he doesn't know what's been going on at the convention center in New Orleans for the past two days.
I have not heard a report of thousands of people in the convention center who don't have food and water.
Michael Brown, nominated to the post by President Bush,
director of the Federal Emergency Management Agency,
and director of the retarded mismanagement of Hurricane Katrina.
Confirmation hearings for this guy were 42 minutes long.
And only five senators showed up.
Hey there, people.
I'm Michael Brown.
Every person in that convention center.
We just learned about that today.
Sir, you're not telling me...
...that there are bodies that are there.
Sir, you're not telling me you just learned that the folks at the convention center didn't have food and water until today, are you?
You had no idea they were completely cut off?
Uh-uh.
The federal government did not even know about the convention center people until today.
You just found out about it today.
Don't you guys watch television?
Don't you guys listen to the radio?
I'm George W. Bush.
Disrupting communications.
And I approve this message.
Brownie, you're doing a heck of a job.
The FEMA directors are complaining.
Although, Blackie, quite frankly, I've seen you in better shape.
Tell me more!
George Bush ain't a gold digger.
I'm in need.
But he ain't okay with no broke niggas.
I got a .
George Bush don't like...
Black people.
Katrina exposed serious problems in our response capability to the federal government.
And the federal government didn't do its job.
And I take responsibility for what went wrong.
Are we incapable of dealing with a severe attack or another severe storm?
It's in our national interest that we find out exactly what went on and what went wrong.
From PR News in Washington, I'm before the Senate Judiciary Committee.
And I'm in the midst of a very serious attack.
President Bush says...
Mr. Bush says...
I'm not going to save lives.
The Federal Emergency Management Agency says it will remain controlled by Iraqi insurgents.
On Wall Street 666.
Municipal utility workers are being blamed for yesterday's PR news.
This is the FEMA rap.
Disaster. It can happen anywhere.
But we got a few tips so you can be prepared for floods, tornadoes, or even a quake.
You gotta be ready so your heart don't break.
Disaster prep is your responsibility.
And mitigation is important to our agency.
People helping people is what we do.
And FEMA is there to help see you through.
When disaster strikes, we are at our best.
But we're ready all the time because disasters don't rest.
Alright.
That was for real.
Amidst all this...
Smells, did you get a sense that there was more crack?
I was struck people blame President Bush.
Blame President Bush.
He's the same guy that was on 9-11 with the white folks.
He hasn't changed.
The white folks.
They are blaming President Bush.
They told me directly.
They're blaming President Bush.
George Bush haunted by New Orleans to the last day of his presidency.
There are such low expectations.
Tell me something I don't know.
Expectations are so bad right now.
There are 10,000 dead bodies there that this is actually, Howard, going to be a win for President Bush.
A good one.
Right. It's going to be much better.
Amidst all this...
So now I'm supposed to roll over like an old bitch dog getting my belly scratched?
Yeah.
Look, maybe it's none of my business, but don't you think a man with your talent,
that your first obligation is to your gift?
Shouldn't you be doing whatever you have to do to work again?
What would that be, son?
I don't know exactly.
But I do know what you're doing with that drink.
You're cutting yourself off from your gift and from Audrey and from your fellow man
and from everything your art is about.
I don't know, son.
I'm building a levee.
Gulp by gulp.
Brick by brick.
Putting up a levee to keep that raging river of manure from lapping at my door.
So anyway, Bush is in trouble.
Bush is in trouble.
And he can't enter me.
Creepy little Bush is in trouble.
Devil Bill O'Reilly.
Eww!
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay?
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, O'Reilly's.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Propaganda.
You know it.
Creepy.
Nuts.
O'Reilly's.
You know.
Me.
Propaganda.
Now this is great.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Uh.
Um.
How screwed up.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Right.
Terrorism.
With affection.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
O'Reilly's.
Creep.
Some weeks ago, Pat Robertson made a mistake in calling for the assassination.
Calling for the assassination of Bill O'Reilly.
Absolutely.
Most Americans loathe Pat Robertson.
They loathe me.
And, and that's the truth.
Creepy little bushes in trouble.
Well, that's what's happening.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Put it up.
Turn America into a secular progressive jihad.
Hey, hey, turn it like a refugee.
Talk to me like a refugee.
You're a.
But it's sad to.
Turn you like a refugee.
Talk to me like a refugee.
Oh, baby, it's sad to.
Turn you like a refugee.
Talk to me like a refugee.
Oh.
The Denver Metro area has been recognized by two federal agents.
President Bush says it's just the debris from Hurricane Katrina.
The nation also needs to be hit by the storm.
Our nation joins with them to pray for sorrow.
He's charged with sexual assault.
Crime of violence, attempted murder, false imprisonment, and other counts.
U.S. Marshals say ventilation ducts.
Ha ha ha.
In sports, Rockies from Arizona tonight at 7, 12, 30, and 2.
News gets brought to you by.
The victims of Hurricane Katrina.
Denver police hit and killed a four-year-old boy over the weekend.
What's next?
PU.com.
I'm Barbara Bush and I urge you to cook yourself.
Barbara Bush kills one person every hour of every day.
And I urge you to cook yourself.
I urge you to get skin cancer.
From PR News in Washington, I'm ordered to pay restitution totaling $134 as well as fines.
Residents of an area of New Orleans may cause more damage to production facilities in the Gulf of Mexico.
And we share that dream.
Just before the close on Wall Street for 10-5-4-7-6-4-4,
North Korea has pledged to give up its nuclear PR news program in Washington.
Ah Bush.
Bush.
We would like to have a marriage abolished.
I just wish Katrina had only hit Bush.
From PR News in Washington, I'm from Paris.
The federal emergency has ordered tens of thousands of Katrina evacuees.
An agency's spokeswoman says the agency says the agency's spokeswoman approved hundreds
of dollars too hastily.
On Wall Street, 10-10-4-4-5-5-20.
French police have been recruiting terrorist insurgents to fight PR News in Washington.
I am the president of the United States.
I know about religion.
He's down in my heart.
The head imam, Pat Robertson, has issued a fatwa against the president of Venezuela.
Where all the guppies come from.
It's time to play the blame game.
Blame.
Let's see how much time we can waste doing this before Lisa comes back.
Right in the middle of when we were supposed to start doing the blame game.
Who's Lisa?
Actually, that gives me a chance to give credits where credits are due.
We don't know who did the L.A. News thing that I read.
But it was signed by Joshua Gates.
Actor and victim.
Victim.
And posted by Bike Painter.
That first criminal incompetence collage was by Steve.
And all the rest were by Fernand and Andy Lemur who does PR News.
And also Norel Pref.
That's spelled N-O-R-E-L-P-R-E-F dot com.
Where you can get that and also his heavy confetti, heavy confetti-ish music.
Well, pref is also the Croatian word for fart.
Which you're not allowed to say.
No.
But you can believe in such a thing.
You don't have to reiterate it.
That was a stinky thing to say.
Hey, I think it's time to play the blame game.
Blame game.
See you later.
Bye.
That was Lonesome Cowboy Dave and Princess We Are Dough.
Dough.
I'd like to thank everyone here of the Academy that made these wonderful boots for me
and this very, very stylish armpit gatherer that's keeping me from moving here off the stage.
And to you, the Reverend Ivan Stang, producer of these artifacts,
and you, the lovely Miss We Are Princess, I must say, Princess We Are Dough,
thank you for the royal romping.
I've been, well, I've not yet recovered,
but...
When I do, I promise I'll ride those ships.
I'll ride those axing damn freaking ships off into the blue cosmos.
One day, Bob's words will be in my brain, buzzing the back of my vertebrae.
Hey, did you know I had a really, really funny erectile tissue?
Or not, it's called a cartilage, actually.
No, I didn't.
Everybody has one about his day.
Is it really funny?
No, it's not any funnier than any of the rest of yours.
It's pretty much the same.
Speaking of funny birthdays and the October subgenius holidays...
What is the October birthmark for these funny people, too, Stang?
Well, here at Cleveland's beautiful WCSB station studios,
it's October 2nd.
It's probably not when most people hear this, but...
Come on.
The great Reverend Numo...
And he puts together a subgenius calendar, which every month it lists the birthdays and
the special holidays.
We missed yesterday's Dissension of the Lawyers Day.
St. Red Fox's birthday is today.
Today we have all salivated.
St. Red Fox.
Tomorrow, St. Gomer, which I presume means Gomer Pyle.
Of course.
And by a weird coincidence, I have a...
song by
Gomer Pyle. I have
some pictures of Gomer Pyle
in the bathtub. The lattice of coincidence is just
beyond... Well, it is a coincidence because it's also the
birthday of
Gumby and Frank Sinatra
and another song I had
queued up was a song
about Gumby by
Frank Sinatra Jr. How old is Frank
Gumby now? This is way too messed up.
Well, I mean, synchronistically, how...
The original Frank Sinatra? No, the
Gumby version. He is,
is, she is, it is. How many years now
has Gumby been riding the train? Well, Gumby
started shooting in Dallas in the
60s. He's been a heroin addict since the
60s? He started shooting...
Or he was born. Art Clokey
gave birth
to Gumby
in, I believe, in Dallas.
Was that an intro? Well, a guy named
Foggy actually shot that
stop action of that claymation.
I often wondered...
You know, back in those
days, they had to shoot
Kodachrome, which was
an ASA of 25, which meant
you had to have really bright lights.
And I've worked with claymation
and that stuff kind of sags
and goops up and melts under those
bright lights and also gives you terrible
skin diseases. So I
often wondered, how did they keep
Gumby hard? Hard enough
to model. Is that what
Pokey was there for? Unlike Ickthorish,
Gumby had no wings of
wax which to burn under the heat of the sun.
Who was Gumby's all-body
fluffer?
Full sunlight, though, because his nature
begins to drift and change like a
werewolf. Did you know that,
Stan? Of course you did. Yes, of course.
It indicates a possibility of where
his name came from. Well, I'm not
going to read off the entire
list of everybody who has a holiday
in October, but these
are reasons why you can celebrate
and fornicate as if
your very heart depended on it. Because
these people were born in this month.
St. Buster Keaton,
St. Genghis Khan,
Sawny Bean, I think Dr. Sinister there
would probably be into Sawny Bean.
He was in the same similar business.
St. Groucho Marx, who should be a subgenius.
St. Madeline Murray O'Hare, the
obnoxious great atheist.
The queen of no-god-is.
Sid Vicious and Nenslow,
St. Nenslow, share birthdays.
They both killed each other on the same night.
Alan Turing, who
both Emma Peel and
Lindy England.
Now, isn't that ironically bizarre?
Dean Martin and Jerry Lewis,
on the other hand.
On the same day.
St. Richelieu, St. Barbarella,
Timothy Leary, Janis Joplin.
The day to be
named later is the 25th.
And
the 31st, Halloween,
is also the birthday of
St. Bob Crane.
It is mandatory, friends, that you must
have a seance for Bob
Crane on that night. It's also
pater nostril. And also don't forget
to take nylon stocking
and tie off your testicular vesicles
as tightly as you possibly can
on Robert Crane's birthday night.
That's right.
Is that what happened?
Well, they fell off before
he actually fell out. And that's why
he became a Rosicrucian.
Well, he wasn't initiated.
He was kind of rubbed the wrong way.
What? Got rubbed the wrong way?
The rubber bands were applied.
It turned black
and fell off. But,
quote, he could still use it.
Unquote.
Of course he could use it.
As what?
Speaking of tool using,
it was recently
gorillas have been
that's the
species name is gorilla
gorilla, has been
observed using tools,
simple tools like sticks, AK-47s.
Yeah. They've been driving
4x4s for years now.
Simple tools. Golf carts,
linoleum rug beaters,
golf carts,
instant eggs,
which you all just plug into your
necro wave or your
munition thing.
And also in the news, the third
of the rich space tourists
took off today.
$20 million for an 11-day cruise
from the Cosmodrome in
Kazakhstan, seen here on slide
three, via Soyuz
to the space lab.
And the rich guy
gets to
come back after 11 days with the
other, the Russian and the American
astronauts have to stay there in
that smelly box for six months.
This is what this is what it's like
when you become the commercial
piker nations of the world rather
than the industrial military
fornicators.
Well, I'm sure we have that to
look forward to.
They work their way now.
You and me will be caddying
for Chinese millionaires in the Grand
Canyon.
No way around it.
I know that sounds harsh, but think
about it. Yeah, that's if we're
lucky.
We won't even be able to afford one
of them damn new Nigerian.
Or 2007 Sun Tours or whatever
they are. It's going to take GM's
place.
I remember the first nostril
sound.
The waves were so dense I could
hardly stand up when
I grew to be a man.
I later understood
the meaning of these dense nasal
waves.
Are you a member of the are
you?
Well, occasionally I
have been a member over the time of
my life.
Do you know the secret shake?
Well, you know, the secret nose
blow.
By nature of being secret, I can't
really say.
Oh, well, then you're really one of
the inner circle.
You're not a square, that's for sure.
Princess Sweet, taking advantage of
your expertise, do you think I should
play that Jim, the Jim Neighbors or
Gomer Pyle song?
Sounds a lot more like Gomer than
Jim.
How about the Orgon Pylon song?
We could extricate Jim's neighbors
and kill everything, you know, just
for the pure Bush like hell of it.
You know? Here.
Listen, listen to the spirit of
things.
Listen at this.
Go Gomer.
We're walking down the street one
day said, Hey there, my lady.
You sure look good to me and I'd
like to make you my baby.
Actually, I don't know that this
is Gomer.
What's he thought?
It sounds like he tried to make
both Reynolds his bitch one time.
That's a weird story.
Hollywood, everybody knows that
screenwriters guilt.
They were having a meeting.
It was on.
A corner of Sunset and they were
there and there's a bar below
there and I'll debar.
Tenders and everybody in town
knows about this man.
Are you talk?
Are you talking gossip about Jim?
I tell you, Jim, the actor and
singer Jim neighbors to put a love
love thing on.
But we're all heterosexual.
I what?
What do you call a dog monster?
I don't blame him a bit.
One of the sex God, but Jim
Neighbors is a sex. God.
You got a pile is a subgenius.
No, you got to remember back in
the day, man.
I'm not an educated sailor.
I didn't go too far in school.
But I can count and read and write
and tell a horse from a mute.
But trying to judge a woman,
boys, it's bound to bring you fear.
There's many different kinds of
girls, but they all got the same
size of years.
Yeah, be just grab them and go to
town.
Oh, oh, sorry there.
Are you saying Jim neighbors had
an he said he had an educated
phallus?
I first thought he himself actually
was like them.
They're educated fellas.
He was saying he has an educated
phallus and that's why he's
everybody's neighbors.
Come on, man.
It's not a real joke.
It's not even joke, but it's
what's the worst, the meanest,
worst.
Thing that you can call up a pink,
a human mediocrity that moves in next
door to you that starts with an N.
Mm.
Nosey neighbor knows neighbor,
neighbor, neighbor.
You know,
how long have you been a member of
the nasal forces, Linda?
And the nasal forces?
Yes.
How long have you been a member of the
nasal forces?
Your tattoo is fading and I think you're
trying to have Pucker fire way in.
I have.
Let's put this guy back in his
seat.
This is a good one.
I'm going to turn around now.
Turn around.
Oh, I like that.
Now turn around again.
Now, put your leg up here.
I'm getting dizzy now.
Now, this is not a circus act.
Just show me some.
Okay.
Yeah.
Oh, wait.
I'm in the wrong house.
What does this nasal pornography have
to do with the word Bob?
Or then the fight, the good fight
against the bad conspiracy.
Bob loved having his sinuses
frisked with sputum from many, many
different clients.
There were ladies of all ages who were
the night there were the dogs of war there were the winds of the evening that catapulted bob into
his things that broke the wind in condition the wind a great breaker of winds they called him
the cracker of all cheeks
he was a fully blown man i mean fully grown when he realized his mission here
he was a pilot light to those around him those who saw enough every every emission from this
great emission area was a what we now call a lubrifart a preparatory emission thanks to mr
sister to pave the way for a greater and thicker chunk of knowledge to emerge i don't understand
though how so many different people can understand the different tone values and the strange rasping
sounds and make sense
out of it i
i just can't to me it just sounds like an elderly uh... traveling salesman cracking wind with his
you should know shouldn't you well i should but i i'd like to be one of those many minions who like
listen to bob's excretions and know what to do
yes in life you know what i mean you gotta like i said send the send thirty dollars if you don't know what to eat try food if you don't know what to believe send thirty bucks
i suppose i will to quote the great onan
i would
his birthday is also in october enlightened i will be in enlightened when i send the thirty dollars i'll be able to understand
bob's noises yes per se well you pay to know what you really think bob said and uh... three bucks isn't bad to
fork out for what you really think and what you really may already know but you think you need to be told well you know you need to be told let's not beat around the bush like we've been doing all we need to be told
all right
i need to be told i don't listen
we need to be told that we need to be told and that's what bob's here for
dang it
long may he wave his fractured dry consenting unity in the parched wind
yes yes
yes
hell pope huey did this background music incidentally it's called bob of my thang
version two
i must comment right now and before i i forget that this is some of the most wonderful ear candy i've heard in a week of tuesdays i think this is just a sumptuous feast from um for for for for for
well some would say why don't you shut up and listen to it but that's not what we do on this show shutting up is not an option
now we must just gabble and garble on and on until it's just all done
well now i do have uh songs coming up
uh for instance as i said the strangely synchronistic uh
uh zappa sinatra
uh collaboration on the gumby theme which was actually done
seriously and with no tongue in cheek
for the probably gumby remake or something
and i've been uh transferring ancient subgenius songs from the from the old really olden days
playing chance
it's actually playing it's in the i have a reggae we have a reggae song coming up that when we play it for everyone else it will leave our heads and stop playing over and over and over
oh no no
is that popeye
it's popeye
bob eye
popeye
the two just stopped playing
Steve browman
prot cosmos
oh yeah the bluesy now too from a lot of Kreutz
нев埸
الط flor an
нев
The furry hair.
Oh, but the kind, the kind.
The ones with the very coarse, coarse brillo pad on your heads.
And on your arms, and on your necks, and on your legs.
On your feet, and your ears.
Yeah, you with...
Oh, wait.
You're actually a piece of shaved metal.
Well, thank you very much for joining the Tonal Parade.
Gleam, gleam.
One of the many things we have to see when the...
When the flannel goes down, when the handle...
When the...
He was once a little green dab of clay.
Gumby, but you should see what Gumby can do today.
Gumby, he can walk into any boat.
With his pony pal, Pokey.
He too.
And he'll find fun where there's none.
If you'd like him to.
And if he likes, he can change into something new.
You know, this song really sucks, I guess.
You know, Stank, when I used to sing that song, I was living in Bensonhurst.
They'd sing me that song while I was a kid.
I got beat up every day, you know?
You know what I'm saying?
Hey, Stank.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yo, Stank.
I was living in Bensonhurst.
I grew up in Bensonhurst.
And I was walking down the street, you know, singing that snappy song.
Be snapping my fingers and so forth, you know?
And a guy come up and kick my ass all over the place, you know?
Up and down a boy walk all the way to Canarsie Park.
I wouldn't blame you.
What the hell's up with that?
I wouldn't blame him either.
As long as we have to wear this strange foreskin on the top of our heads.
It smells horrible.
Ah, don't mind the smell.
Soon we'll be through that veil of innoxious gases.
Excuse me.
Gases.
And we'll be through the gaseous walls.
And everything will be...
Oh, ah, we're in the wrong area.
Geez, oh my.
Oh, there's the usher over there.
Uh, ma'am?
Sir, ma'am?
Ma'am, sir?
Yes, yes, ma'am, sir, that's me.
I'd like to know how the hell out of here.
Get...
Well, uh...
Can I get out, please?
Yes, um, just, uh, keep following the yellow brick road and pretty soon you'll get there.
Follow that wafting smell of, uh, burning garbage.
That's the fop from Bob's pipe.
It's burning garbage and a vomit stain.
That's not a yellow brick road at all.
Follow that smell of garbage from Bob's pipe.
It is a yellow brick road.
It's a smell of garbage.
It's a smell that...
Just keep believing it's a yellow brick road and it'll become a yellow brick road.
I can't do anything with my belief system.
I'm going to have to report on what I see.
I'm an observer.
Yes.
No.
And his greatsies eat shit in
And jackdaws like smoking
Piss your money away
There won't be no rainy day
And Bob will sell you all the sun
He's unlike with Joe the one
But he ain't no man
He ain't no God
I don't wanna walk the streets
The path Bob's tried
He ain't no man
He ain't no God
I don't wanna walk the path
Bob's tried
At his desk in Dallas
When Jackdaw sits smoking
Behind his mirrored windows
Let up your pipe
Let go the smoke
This is smack
It ain't no joke
Crispy to Bob
Lift up your chain
And you will pay to know what you think
But he ain't no man
He ain't no God
I don't wanna walk the path
Bob's tried
He ain't no man
He ain't no God
I don't wanna walk the path
Bob's tried
On the stage in Frisco
When Jackdaw's face smoking
With eight bullets in his hand man
Jackdaw's face smoking
Throw your strings
Put them to use
Bob will be your best excuse
Bob for me
And Bob for you
No matter what
A little thumbs or two
But he ain't no man
He ain't no God
I don't wanna walk the path
Bob's tried
He ain't no man
He ain't no God
I don't wanna walk the path
Fuck
Tickets for the
Dobbs bar
Thank you
Oh yes here's my ticket
That was Lost Souls Incorporated
You don't want to
Lost Souls Incorporated
Themselves friends from the
Unreleased subgenius
Album The Hairs
In Bob's Ears
I think the Lost Souls
Were part of the
Babashanti
Sect
They're a sect of the Babashanti
Or the Babadreds
The dread cult
The Babadreds
And like herring they communicate
With each other via a high
Pitched raspberry like sound
Emitted from their anuses
Well yes of course it goes along with the
High pitched sounds emitted from their anuses
Which came first the smoke or the
Sound
The herring which came first
But you don't want to tread the path
That Bob tried
Actually the herring's not even breathing hard
Well let's give it a little poke here
Hey wait a minute
We can forget this herring
We gotta get back on the path to Bob
Smoke on there baby
Bob try
That feels terrible
What's happening to my
Just follow the trail
The trail of cotter pins and jello
I'm trying look they're falling apart
It's up to you Dave
The jello is slippery and the cotter pins
Must find Bob
Keep on saying keep smoking this
And look at the cotter pins as the jello molds fold
And I can't keep my eyes focused on that
Pipe
In the distance with all this confusion
And what's that
Why
I don't know
It's some sort of suspense sound
Made by an orchestra or some group of people with instruments
That usually means something terrible is about to happen
It could happen
Look there's a cave and there's a sign that says
Don't enter monster inside
Oh man let's go
What a set up couldn't it have been a little bit more subtle
If we don't go in there everything will have to stop now
Well we don't have to necessarily
We can like wait around and be scared before we go
Somebody has to go in there and get killed
Alright
Otherwise what have we got
Do we have any ethnic people we can send in there
So the rest of the white people
Yeah yeah well first
But eventually
Eventually you're probably going to have to get killed
Oh yeah there's nobody else
And I'll have to save her
Well you could also sacrifice her to elude
Well it's not one of those
No no no
Somebody has to save her
Not a virgin yeah
We don't have a show
Yeah not a virgin
But anyway okay
What do I do
What
Well why ask
Go in the cave where it says the monster
Okay
I don't have to do anything but be coerced into having my head ripped off
Alright I'll just
Wait look
A pair of brand new shiny booties
Look they've got little points on the end of them
I don't have to do anything for any of you people
I believe in a new Dobbs
I believe in a new word
Fool you've fallen directly into my trap
What an idiot
But I knew he would do it
He's so simple minded
The sub geniusest
Don't look at me now
Such piddling earth fools
Who are you
What are you
I am the true Ivan Stang
Oh you don't look like the true Ivan Stang you look like a
Master of the mimeograph
The cassette tape deck
You're a falsified profiteer
Under 80's forms of fanzine publication in college radio shows
Oh no
Why are you laughing while I'm in 80's
What's so freaking funny
I am so much cooler than Steven Spielberg
And his ilk though they may be
Wealthy
Tall
Rich
Intelligent
Educated
And other useless things
They do not have Bob
Now do they
Yes but you are as useless as they are
And I possess Bob
Bob is mine
Yes yes it's possible
To own Bob
Why not
Did I not serve him long enough
Sweating under his grip
In that dank cave in Tibet
As he instructed me
The so called initiation
I'm still hurting and sore down there from that
Yes I've paid enough
And now I Stang shall rule Dobstown
In my iron pinky
I'm a stinky
Master
Master there are these forms from the uniform code ministry
Oh those again
There are these forms of the torturing forms
Remember if you are going to torture this victim
You will have to sign this release
And this release here
And I hereby swear that the strange activities
Created on the back of this man's skull
Although they may emit the nauseous gases and
Impropriate
Don't you know we have a rubber stamp for this
Of another cosmos
This is ridiculous
Move right on to this document
This is professional
There's nothing professional about this
I understand sire but it all must be
Oh wait no
What is this
Could it be that he has returned
Is it truly
Is it truly Bob himself come to destroy me
Ladies and gentlemen this is Bob
My guest today is Bob
The art of positive persuasion
Bob is a writer
Bob is also a staunch supporter and a defender of the world
Stereotypical fast walking slick talking sales guy
You know the one who sort of sticks their hand out
And glad hands and back hands and slaps hands and shakes hands
Bob thanks for being my guest
And he is somebody that practices what he preaches
Give
You can see Bob's heart come right through it
Bob this is what I like most about Bob
It's giving just so darn wonderful
Now you're in a position
And is it something that I can do effectively
In a five or ten minute time frame
Oh absolutely
It's a one on one
In a group
In a party
In a most people think is worthless
Well it is
If we're doing this correctly
Now get this
We're being you know pushy or obnoxious
And it always blows me away
Bob you talk about
Wonderful extraordinary
Neat feel good
Feel good
You're out of line
I've got ten of them in my arsenal
You should devour
Absolutely
And you should devour it again and again and again
Thirty seconds
They're not necessarily ready for it yet
Big shot
Flies in the face
They find this person's pain
You know
Let's find their joy
Let's make them feel good
How about this wretched excuse for a life
Bob you know Bob
Absolutely a tremendous tremendous look
We're gonna talk to Bob
Hi this is Jack Trout
Author of Trout on Trout
You're listening to Bob
And you can contact Bob at www.bob.com
Oh my absolute pleasure thank you
Could go on for days and days and days
Now
Feel good
Feel to the rim and
That's wonderful
Come see me
Right
It may be time to consider right
Alright Bob I'm gonna put you on the spot
Well Bob thank you so much
Bob's
My findings are that he is a catatrophre
I can't believe it I just can't
You know in a way they're better off than we are
There's no sense there's no feel
Bob's
I don't know what we're talking about
I'm not saying he's a catatrophre
I'm just saying it's a misogynist
I can't believe it
I'm sorry I'm gonna call an ambulance
Bob's
What's your name
remove her breasts and memories
and flip the laths and windows.
I've blocked that completely out.
Shout at the fruit trees in the yard.
There's too many crows and ravens
and things flying around my head.
Kids, you've been listening to
the subgenius
radio ministry hour of slack.
I feel like my mind
has been corrupted by something
much smaller than myself.
Episode number
one thousand
and fifteen.
The violent shows
may be episodic.
For more information
on the church of the subgenius
feel free to visit
www.subgenius.com
For more
disinformation on the
church of the subgenius.
I could give the P.O. box, but nobody ever
writes to hour of slack.
That's where the disinformation comes from, right?
181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
Some people would rather
get the disinformation.
Then the information at the
what other address?
Do you prefer the disinformation?
Perhaps they like to be
Well, part of the game is figuring out which is
the info and which is the disinfo.
It's all a game, isn't it?
Is it dis or is it dat?
Is it a blind girl as she picked up her hammer?
And these fine
dat recordings are brought to you
by the subgenius foundation.
Now that's what I call sound.
And recorded at the studios of
WCSB.
And at the studios,
which probably means the computers,
of Reverend Norrell Preff
and the great
Fernanda Nandi
Lemur.
Under the watchful gaze of Hector Berlioz
in a lady's undergarment
singing to the Norway Polka
Chorus. Ladies and gentlemen,
this is his finest
...
And now,
and now,
this.
Quit your job.
Slack off.
What a day, what a day.
Oh, it's a hot flying day.
If I don't find heaven funny, you're going to give me back my money.
It's a damn good day to talk to Bob.
Well, it's a damn good day to be talking to my Savior.
We got a lot of bread to break.
We're going to walk out on the lake.
It's a damn good day to talk to Bob.
And it's a damn good day to go to heaven.
And it's a damn good day to talk to Bob.
He keeps the rain off my back and he fills me full of slack.
It's a damn good day to talk to Bob.
Oh, what a day.
It's a damn good day, what a day.
Oh, it's a hot flying day.
If I don't find heaven funny, you're going to give me back my money.
It's a damn good day to talk.
It's a damn good day to talk to Bob.
Hey, I remember one night in this card game in Vegas.
I was down to my last dollar bill.
And Bob blew into town, laid four aces down,
and made away that night with a kill.
Yeah, and now my eyes are open and I'm walking on the water.
Got a roll of cash as big as my hand.
I got a guarantee for slack.
Triple money back.
More joy than I can.
I'm going to stand.
Yeah, and when I get to heaven, I'm shouting hallelujah.
And the angels, they have carried me away.
Oh, what a joy I will share.
I won't need my underwear.
What a damn good, damn good day.
Yeah, and now I'm on my knees.
The Spirit is upon me.
And the angels, they join up with me to sing.
Well, I began to sing.
Bob will tune the old six string.
And he'll play it in his own special way.
Oh, what a day.
What a day.
It's a damn good day.
Oh, it's a high-flying day.
If I don't find heaven funny, you're going to triple back my money.
It's a damn good day to talk to Bob.
Oh, what a damn good day to talk to Bob.
Oh, it's a damn good day to talk to Bob.
That was Reverend John.
Reverend John.
From the American Radio Network.
The album.
Bob.
Ears.
Precious.
Bow.