Come out, come out, wherever you are, and meet the young lady who fell from a star.
There they go. Giant arm raised. Green flash.
Spang us with flame. Two thousand feet. Engines are giving out.
No chance to release bombs. Only one thing left.
Look at a woman. Look at a woman. Look at a woman.
Lustfully instruments of righteousness to God.
Shepherds love sheep. Most of them. Good ones. Even good shepherds love sheep.
And they're trained to kind of fend off the enemies of sheep.
Snakes, snakes, snakes, and wolves and bears.
But even the best shepherd, even the most wonderful shepherd who loves the sheep,
when he knows the battle with the wolf is going against him,
he says, I'm out of here. It's time to burn my bridges.
You take the sheep. It's okay. I'm living.
Only people named Smith and Beech.
Almighty God.
They'll begin catching us systematically.
Keeping the best and storing us in cages and things.
You mean you're orbiting the planet far outside of the solar system?
We men. We men as men. We're finished.
Scientific evidence proves that planets and plants can read our minds.
Waiting for us on those other worlds.
No letters conveyed by recent emigres help us to understand the new land.
Only digital data transmitted at the speed of light.
By unfeeling.
Precise.
Robot emissaries.
Do you hear the voices?
This actually transpired only moments ago.
You've heard the specter voices in your actual, on your lines tonight?
Yes. Disgusting the devil and other fears.
I heard it too.
She picked up the phone and took home.
Me or I was calling her or something.
And when she picked it up, there was a party line with heaven or something.
It was people talking about the devil as if they knew him and had a lot of trouble with it.
Yeah.
And so we figured that she had intercepted sort of like a telephone call from hell.
The sheep are in mortal danger.
And that in and of themselves, they have no way to defend themselves.
And they will die because of the enemy.
Where are we to live in the Martian zone?
The earth.
Let me talk to the sheep.
The smelly sheep.
The smelly, stupid, dumb sheep.
The smelly, stupid, stupid, dumb sheep.
For if you are sheep, then understand as a sheep, it is a real good idea to listen to the monsters that inhabit those machines.
And those voices sounded really strong.
And they sounded.
They sounded really sure of themselves.
And at the first sound of his distinct call, it was kind of a guttural call.
I can't imitate it.
I won't even try.
But it was a peculiar guttural sound.
As soon as they would hear that, the flock would begin to follow.
I laugh at the fear and wonder in your simple little faces.
Who are you?
What are you?
If I told you, would your little earthbinds understand?
You know, and if you were...
If you really believe something enough, then it really is true because you make your own reality.
Yeah, sure.
We're all just creating, mopping up our own reality right now.
Yeah.
So if a hundred monkeys believe that they're the devil, then they really are the devil.
So you're saying a hundred monkeys were somehow getting in your phone wires and discussing their disenchantment with the old horned one, with old Sam Sam?
Well, no, no.
We meant that figuratively about the hundred monkeys.
I think she only heard like four or five.
Oh, jeez.
No wonder I didn't believe you guys at first.
I saw the Wizard of Oz too, and I was pretty scared when I was little and stuff, but now I'm even more scared.
You know what I mean?
Don't be afraid, Dave.
Be afraid, Dave.
Are you one of those kinds of people, one of those kinds of sheep people, people, one of those kinds of sheep people, sheep people, sheep people, sheep people, sheep people?
You came here in that?
Through space?
Well...
The demonic voices are a lot more important than this.
It takes a giant robot just to hold it.
While Dave runs water through it.
Oh, I've had that done to me so many times, I can't even count the ways.
And these robots are getting mighty tiring to me.
I'm going for something like maybe a Korean masseuse from now on.
I feel ashamed.
Because, like, I'm an idiot or something.
As, you know, his woman told me last night, you're an idiot.
Did you hear about the vision at Fatima again?
Again?
Yeah, the vision of Carl Sagan.
Appeared at Fatima.
And a little bit later,
a little girl saw it, and, uh...
Yeah.
Well, I am not kidding.
What was the message?
He said this was not happening.
Knowing that there are 54 billion billion billion,
that is 5.4 times 10 to the 28th,
possible other hands that I was equally likely to have been dealt,
and then foolishly concluding that a god of bridge exists,
who favors me,
a god who arranged the cards in the shuffle with my victory foreordained,
from the beginning.
Pure.
Yes.
Sexually.
Sexually immoral.
Yes.
Through space beyond your furthest conception,
a thing.
How many other kinds of universes, laws of nature, and physical constants,
that could also lead to life and intelligence, and perhaps even delusions of self-importance.
He calls for his pipe, pipe, pipe!
Those guys are already...
You don't have to explain the new world order or the conspiracy.
Right.
They have their own ideas.
You know, they have their own witch hunt.
We're not, we're not witch hunters.
In zero gravity.
We've all done that.
We have to adapt, man.
Oh, Ivan, come on, man.
You know these people can't crawl.
How are they gonna walk?
You know what I'm saying, baby?
How are they gonna walk if they can't crawl?
Well, they flow.
Oh.
We're not gonna have to...
We can't walk on a really high gravity planet.
We have to learn to flow.
I'm saying...
We have to give up our bones, man.
You've just gotta, like, let go of your hard part.
All he wanted to do was have a great time.
Party!
There's no tomorrow.
It's now.
I'm frightened, Eddie.
I'm frightened.
If you land on one of those heavy, heavy neutron stars, you're just gonna squash flat as a
pancake and it's gonna break your bones if you have them.
You've just gotta be ready to flatten out, man.
Or float.
Or rise above it.
If the case may be.
It depends on what the gravity's doing that day.
Or stretch yourself out so thin.
You may...
Yeah.
Expand, man.
Expand your mind.
Expand your ego so that it...
An infinitely thin line.
Just a point.
It just becomes a bubble.
Bubble.
But that we'll take brambles.
But that might matter.
This visual effect literally will be an gebrachtन
Going through my head now...
Whatever, but, you're constantly shilling the light out of my mind for this, this
is a very naughty sound that's making me feel much more insecure.
I'm very kissing with a credibility statement, but all i'm saying is that that sound just
really touched my nerves.
I mean, it's really touching my skin!
From your aha ear for being certainly communautative as well, I'm still
And then you wake up as fat as divine. You've transitioned through a transvestite galaxy.
Yeah, or either that or else when you finally open your eyes, you realize it was really the revolving lights on top of a police car.
You're really screwed up.
That's where I usually use my marbles. I upchuck in the back of a police car.
At the end of your life.
That's my first and last memory.
That's when the blinding light is really a realization.
Realization.
Realization. Stone cold.
Where they are, what they seemed.
Not even close.
Not what you thought, yeah.
So, way over the rainbow.
Everything will be destroyed.
You know, I don't know, it's face talk or something.
Why?
You're supposed to slow, Dave.
It's not supposed to make sense.
It doesn't have to.
It doesn't make any sense. That's like groovy.
That's what you said, Dave.
You taught us that. It doesn't have to make sense.
Well, I just didn't have to.
Make sense.
Make sense because I couldn't really make that much sense.
In fact, if it doesn't kind of irritate you and even hurt you and cause you a lot of pain, Dave,
there's hardly any sense in the rest of us doing it at all.
Mm-hmm.
Absolutely.
I don't know. I never thought of it that way.
The pain and the agony.
I'm sure you didn't because you're the one who has to feel the agony and the pain.
We're just all cultivating that little soul for the drop in the bucket.
Think what you're doing for everyone else, Dave.
I can't think of anything for anybody else right now.
I can't even get these Depends to work.
One drop in the bucket, Dave, will save 14 starving children on Alpha Centauri.
Well, I don't know if they're going to eat this because these Depends are not working.
They don't eat it. They snort it.
Mom?
What is it, dear?
Mom, when the invasion comes, we'll have to get rid of you and Daddy.
But I'll be sure it won't hurt very much.
Well, thanks. Thanks a lot.
Little evolved hairless monkeys inside.
The little dancing pigs.
The names have been changed to protect the innocent.
The curse of creation.
Who was it that was saying that when they turned on the radio, they still were eager?
They kind of wanted to look inside to see if they could see the tiny little people.
Hello?
I thought you were saying that in the day you used to have the little pigs running the radio.
Oh, there's one of them now.
Hello?
It's one of the tiny little people from inside.
The radio.
There are. There's one of them.
Hello?
Hello. How are you?
This is Gork.
How do you like being... How do you like your condition?
You know, let's get existential, baby.
You know, let's talk sartrean.
What is it there, being a little tiny person in the radio?
Well, you know what? It's really being like being tiny.
What?
Not really being tiny. It's like being big, but everybody thinks you're tiny.
Yeah.
Okay, now you're getting too far out for me now.
Everybody thinks you're tiny, but you're not tiny.
What's the one, the next one, but you're not big or something?
Right.
It's like I'm outside.
I'm ready to, like, come on in.
Okay.
But nobody lets you get in, I guess, because I'm the one that doesn't hear me, you know.
A little tiny people inside the radio.
Radio.
I believe that.
Really?
Yeah.
Why not?
Well, because it is true is why not.
I prefer to go, to obstruct nature and to go against what isn't.
I mean, but we're all obstructing nature.
We don't even like nature because it's artificially littered.
Oh, my, look, man.
My head is carved.
I don't know.
I live out in the woods, man.
I am a vegetable.
I'm a member of the carrot kingdom.
I mean, I'm an electromagnetic wave.
Yeah, goodbye.
I'm an electromagnetic wave goodbye-bye.
I mean, I'm not real.
Okay.
I am real, I guess.
Okay, in a certain way.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, I understand that.
There she is.
There she is right here.
Thank you.
We don't need you anymore.
Well, I just want to ask a question.
What you're talking about, about the original sin, what was that?
What was it?
Yeah.
To believe that you could be a human being.
To be as God.
How's that?
To worship the creation.
It's centered in pride.
To worship self.
It is.
Yeah, totally.
It's the harmonic tone.
Let me fly.
Let me flap my wings and dig groovy things and get my kicks from these groovy chicks.
From Master Control Central.
I have my plastic bubble in the studio.
Plastic bubble through the sky.
In case any scientists are listening, from Southern Methodist University,
I will not reveal any more of the secret power.
You can't think about your own brain.
Yes, you've said that so many times.
You have to hook up another drive and let it think about your brain,
or vice versa.
But you cannot actually apply your brain to your brain.
Right.
That's like trying to wash.
Water.
Or eat your own mouth.
Right.
It's like exactly.
It'd be like trying to chow down on your own mouth.
Right.
Using your mouth.
It'd be like trying to.
We can contemplate it.
We can think about it.
See, the old watermelon salesman.
We can talk about it, but we can't think about it.
And the fruitarians.
The old vegetable heads used to say that what that is,
not solipsism, what's it called,
when you're considering the meta is what it's called.
The meta synapse.
You're considering.
The mitochondrial synapse.
And if you can consider the meta, you're a big flopping baby Buddha, man.
You're a huge, humongous pile of manure.
You can get rid of that with dipyrine or any of those ointments.
Those antifungal things.
You can get rid of that.
Yeah.
Well, this.
I've tried to avoid it myself.
I have never had success with this ointment.
20 seconds.
Listen to it.
The scanner.
I can.
I can feel it.
I can feel the power through the scanner.
The brain.
Put your ear to the radio.
Put your hand to the radio.
Feel the hot power of plastic bubble in the studio.
All of them are having sex.
All of them.
He's never given me the success nor the fulfillment,
spiritually or sexually, that I desire.
All of them are having sex.
All of them.
Genetic scientist there.
The guy, right?
This guy that makes the four-ass baboon.
A metaphor of baboon.
Out of men.
Yes.
Turns men into four-ass baboons.
Well, the bonobos that you were training in, not in Dobstown, but in Dallas.
The bonobos you were training down there not only had multiple orgasms, but they also had
multiple, what is, what do they call it?
Multiple rectal.
Rectal inversions.
But we had to quit those experiments because it turned out there was a zoning law that
said you couldn't do that within a thousand feet of a school or church.
Can you believe it?
Well, you should have done it.
You know, this could.
This could.
This could have led to the cure for cancer.
But, yeah, it's pornography.
What they were doing with those chimpanzees, it was porno.
Well, I thought you should have.
These men were paying to see the chimpanzees have pleasure, the dolphins, and, you know,
all of a sudden it was like, you know, the kids might get in there and see it, or the
preacher's wife might get excited.
Well, I think you should.
So we had to stop.
Well, you were in Dallas.
You should have just called it a church.
They would have done nothing about it.
They're all called churches.
And it's still, I mean, that doesn't make any difference.
That just makes it more illegal.
Yeah.
I see what you mean.
At least I, well, I'm trying to see where you're coming from.
Okay.
Well, look at, well, David Koresh being the first case of that.
That was just another bonobo chimpanzee experiment.
And look what, you know, look how they ended up.
Yeah, but you taught the guy how to read the Bible and all this stuff.
And then he went off the deep end.
And I taught the guy that when the ATF comes to the door with a cannon pointed at you,
you put your hands up and say, I'll go.
I thought he just wanted to go quietly.
I thought he just wanted to be played big old martyr boy.
And the training films I saw, somebody taught him how to point the banana back.
Oh, yeah.
Well, then see, that was his trouble.
See, those ATF guys came up there and he started thinking he could shoot it out with him.
Aren't you glad he didn't say banana?
Well, I was hoping he would at least shoot it up with him, if you know what I'm saying.
You were humping while he was, what?
I was trying to.
What are you talking about, Dave?
This doesn't make any sense.
Oh, God, never mind.
I'm going back again.
I was.
He's in and out.
I thought it was yesterday and here it is today again already.
And I was humping it.
Not, you know, I wasn't humping.
I was humping it.
I strictly disagree with cohabitation.
Why is that?
Because to me, it's just plain silly.
You know, I say that because, well, I'm a I'm a bachelor.
You know, I've never married and never cohabited.
Anyway, I'm a bachelor and I live like a bachelor.
And if you know, if I want to throw my dirty socks in the corner somewhere, I don't want somebody coming.
I need to come up.
Hey, the swing.
All right.
Swing.
The swing.
All right.
Swing.
Doesn't the girl that's going to marry you, doesn't she need, doesn't she have the right to know that, that you keep your dirty socks everywhere?
Well, that wouldn't living together help clear that up and let her know what the facts are before she gets married.
Nope.
All of what happened is that she'd be asking me, well, why do you leave your dirty socks or whatever?
You know, and I say, well, gosh, because I want to.
I've been doing it for over 20 years.
I'm a bachelor.
You know, I've never married and never cohabited.
And I might marry someday.
Oh, what a relief it is.
I made an incision just below the hairline, laying back the scalp as far as the base of the skull.
Now, I was about to step into a completely new element, the sinister unknown, led by a man who, for all I knew, was mad.
Well, I thought you were on a Froggy Mountainous timer, or is it Central Eurasian?
Central.
Central Eurasian.
Ah, I see.
Then you're in the same as the demographic zone as the blockhead.
We're the exact center of the known universe.
And that's why I...
Central time zone.
Right.
The Midwest.
Yeah.
Well, no, no, it all makes sense to me now.
God's country, is what it's called.
Yeah.
If it would be God's navel, then it would indeed at least be his country.
I live in Godland.
Godland.
Godland, Texas.
And when you did materialize on the screen, there were some very unhappy women at the Korean massage parlor.
No, actually, the ladies down at the Korean massage parlor were very happy.
It was the news media and the religious nuts who never got their...
Just say it wasn't the first time they were waiting for you to come on the screen, you know what I mean?
I'm sorry.
A long time, too.
The second coming, yay, and its great sloppiness was conjoined and enjoined by the whole line of men lined up outside the tent.
Fifty cents.
Get in line, boys.
The whore of Babylon.
They told you how evil she was, how bad she was.
They didn't say nothing about how good looking she was now, did they?
Pleasures that the world offers you that ends up making you want to die.
You know?
Right.
Let's do a prayer for the feast of the Mau Mau.
Oh, evil one, please do not heed my prayer, except that I am praying that you not heed it.
Wait, maybe perhaps I should pray to Bob instead.
I'm singing a hymn from the choir.
Thank you.
Amen.
Contract to a point and disappear forever.
You hear only me, earth woman.
Only you.
Into another dimension.
On that.
Final.
And not exactly a very, um, well, a messy day.
On that very messy day.
Forget the rest of the part about it not being anything.
Because I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, Bob.
Sorry.
Will the end of the world come that way?
I have no idea what's happening.
Okay, now I better go inquire.
The resupply ship has not arrived.
We've been waiting for the resupply ship now for...
Five years.
We were gonna have a snappy end and, you know, so it'd be cool.
Dave's been eating his toenails as food every day.
I'd save some of them toenails for Dave, would you?
Oh, I got a lot.
I got them in boxes.
No!
They crackle when you crunch them.
Well, I guess you better go look.
I think of all the times I was called a carbon head.
I've had a big bag of fat in my life.
I would spend the rest of this afternoon in an appreciating afternoon...
Hey, carbon head, come over here.
...on the...
...on the last week, and I think maybe four years ago,
thinking about the vision I had of Karl Marx talking to those ghost voices from heaven.
Luminous beings, I don't mean.
I don't know if I can ever recapitulate what I just...
Well, the worth of your labor is, um...
Satan is my, uh...
Poor old Dave, the blood rumbling in his cup.
Are we still praying?
He's a pal of mine.
I hope not.
Was that all a prayer?
Well, let's all...
Let's all throw up a prayer to the youngster swan, the smelly one.
Oh, chihuahuas of war.
Chihuahuas of war.
My God, they've unleashed the chihuahuas of war.
Yo quiero ICBM.
Yo quiero ICBM, man.
That's that...
Yo quiero Tomahawk missile.
Yo quiero shredded submarine.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
The end is coming.
All right, all right.
No more anatomy lessons.
Yo quiero Zyklon B, etc.
Yo quiero...
Yo quiero Slack.
Slack.
La iglesia del subgenio.
Most wonderful, most wonderful, most wonderful, most wonderful.
Something terrible I'm thinking.
For an in weave term,
a made f...
There are so many logical and thoroughly possible ways in which the entire tribe of mankind
could be wiped off the earth at any moment.
Hey, hey, why don't you knock on that trap door there and say Yogg-Sothoth three times.
Go ahead, do it, man.
Okay.
Yogg-Sothoth.
No, I'm not going to say it the third time because you know I won't get one out.
I didn't think I was going to get one out.
That's right, that's right.
I know your tricks.
Last time I did that, I had bad luck for ten years, man.
Old mean Mr. Tooth Decay.
That's right.
And then ultimately that was because of your truth decay.
I saw a little man in the laundromat.
A little tiny man looked like mean old, mean old Mr.
Tooth Decay.
When one stops to think what a tiny little grain of sand this haughty world of ours actually is in the dark sea of space,
the spectacle of man's inhumanity to man becomes a cosmic joke.
What's instinct to a dog?
To hunt.
To kill, master.
To run with the pack.
He was quite a far cry from Mr. Peanut, which was another small character that lives in the radio now.
Well, Mr. Peanut, back in the old days, he could, you could skin Mr. Peanut back.
He could, he could be skinned back.
No, you're thinking...
His naked, little peanut head would show through.
No, you're thinking of Chiquita Banana.
You're thinking of Chiquita Banana.
You're not thinking of Mr. Peanut.
When you would pull Mr. Peanut's head back, the few times...
No, his skin, you pull his skin back.
Oh, I thought you meant when you pulled open the cranial vortex there and you open it and you look and there was nothing in there except for this bleeding, like, brain.
Now that, I didn't like that.
I didn't like that at all when I was a kid.
How about when you, when you cut open his head and there was nothing but rubber bands wrapped around?
That was, that was frightening.
And inside that was like a little brain with this deadly poison.
That's when I started going to all the David Lynch movies.
When the, when the brains were made of rubber bands, but when they were made of like actual viscous, like pieces of, what do they call it in the old world?
Uh, forget it.
That's when I got out of that religious thing right there.
That's when I changed religions right there.
Now, I'm preaching the word.
Yes, I am.
And I dare creation to say I'm not, I'm not preaching part of it.
I'm preaching the word.
I get the word of God from all of my doings, all I believe.
I go get Bible.
See.
That's it.
It's according to the Bible.
Otherwise, I don't preach it.
Amen.
You've been asked that ye be not judged.
For with what judgment ye judge, ye shall be judged.
And with what measure ye need, it shall be measured to you again.
And why beholdest thou the milk that is in thy father's eye, but considerest not the bean that is in thine own eye?
Thou hypocrite.
First cast out the bean that is in thine own eye.
And then thou shalt see clearly to cast out the mold of thy brother's eye.
Do the cast of your pearls before swine, lest they trample them under their feet.
And then give not that which is holy unto the dog.
We're 17 men on an alien world.
It's up to us whether we ever get home again.
I couldn't handle it, man.
I tried to handle it too.
With someone else's hands.
I'm waiting.
One law, one faith, one baptism.
We are free on the universe and free except understanding it.
And priest Paul said, the one God and father of all, who all in all, who all, one, one, has one law, one law, one law, one law, one law.
If there's no more, pay.
Move.
Then.
Then, is there no more go?
Oh, the revolution started.
It already started again.
And that's about time.
I've sure been talking about it enough.
Well, you're down there far enough.
All I got to do is go out in the backyard and get on that horse and wave the old sombrero and just keep on a-going for freedom.
How was I ever smart to not go down there?
Hello.
Oh!
Well, this way we can all roll, get back into our cocoons.
And when we get up in the morning, we'll be lovely butterflies.
Yes, it'll be a better day tomorrow when you wake up.
A better day?
But what about those of us who don't wake up?
What about those of us who wake up and actually we're still butterflies?
I mean, not butterflies.
What was the other word?
Caterpillars.
Yeah, giant maggots.
That's it.
What if we wake up and we're giant maggots?
Yeah, that's it.
I mean, what about it?
Even maggots.
Prairie squid lullabies.
People do.
The name of this song is a prairie squid lullaby.
The sun is gone.
The next day.
It makes me cry.
A million stars will disappear from the sky.
Good day, average day.
I'm going to fly to the mines.
That's when you see the X's ships.
And you'll board them one last time.
Let's meet a prairie squid lullaby.
Good night, princess.
Good night.
Bye.
Pay no attention.
To that man behind the curtain.
You see, there must be a god.
Number one.
One.
The Apollo pictures of the whole Earth
conveyed to multitudes
something well known to astronomers.
On the scale,
the scale of worlds.
To say nothing of stars or galaxies.
Humans are inconsequential.
A thin film of life on an obscure and solitary lump
of rock and metal.
He saw in his vision.
If all he wasn't right, he meant well.
But he wasn't right.
Holy Ghost couldn't let him get by.
Because he was a man.
Because God had already spoken.
Please tell them that I am God.
I want instant obedience to all commands.
The serpent speaks.
The serpent is not in awe.
He depends on the guardian of Eden.
I am I, yes, I am.
Something's gonna happen.
Something wonderful.
I don't believe it.
Jack.
It's why you fail.
It begins in a scientific laboratory.
Amidst a maze of electronic apparatus,
Professor Wilbur Malcolm,
a middle aged pipe smoking,
pipe smoking man,
is making methodical tests.
100 is our new top secret interceptor, Fred.
Hardly anyone knows how it works,
but it never fails.
That's what the religious world have done now.
I think you got all of these false checks.
I got to believe anything and everything,
but what the word says.
If it would come to the word,
then everyone of us would believe the same thing,
and all of us would do the same thing.
What more effective way to do that
than to approach a captive audience
of young, impressionable children?
Ignition in 90 seconds.
If there is danger here,
and I use up all the fuel in the escape,
what will happen to the escape?
If there is no discovery,
it could be destroyed.
I understand now, Dr. Chandra.
One minute to ignition.
Thank you for telling me the truth.
Will I dream?
I don't know.
In the vision of a dream,
I once imagined myself searching for other civilizations in the cosmos.
Among a hundred billion galaxies,
and a billion trillion stars,
life and intelligence should have arisen on many worlds.
Some worlds are barren and desolate.
On them, life never began,
or may have been extinguished in some cosmic catastrophe.
There may be worlds rich in life,
but not yet evolved to intelligence and high technology.
There may be civilizations that achieve technology,
and then promptly use it to destroy themselves.
And perhaps there are also beings
who learn to live with their technology,
and themselves, beings who endure,
and become citizens of the cosmos.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
I was immersed in these thoughts.
I found myself approaching a world that was clearly inhabited,
a world I had visited before.
I saw a planet encompassed by light,
and recognized the signature of intelligence.
But suddenly, darkness, total and absolute.
I was in a dream.
In my dream, I could read the Book of Worlds,
a vast encyclopedia of a billion planets within the Milky Way.
I was in a dream.
What could the galactic computer tell me
about this now darkened world?
They must have survived some earlier catastrophe.
I was in a dream.
Locally initiated contact
with the universe.
Maybe their television broadcasts.
Their biology was different from ours.
High technology.
I wondered what those lights had been for.
There must have been signs they were in trouble.
Probability of survival in a century less than 1%.
Not very good odds.
Communications interrupted.
Their world society had failed.
They had made the ultimate mistake.
I felt a longing to return to Earth.
The television transmissions of Earth rushed past me,
expanding away from our planet at the speed of light.
I was in a dream.
I saw a planet encompassed by light.
I saw the 不
Where could I be?
There can be no fight wash at the White House.
If the serious course of events continued,
foreign ministers are at this moment...
Oh, please stand by. Stand by.
Then, suddenly, silence.
Total and absolute.
But the dream was not yet done.
Had we destroyed our home,
what had we done to the Earth?
There had been many ways for life to perish at our hands.
We had poisoned the air and water.
We had ravaged the land.
Perhaps we had changed the climate.
Could it have been a plague?
Or nuclear war?
I remembered the galactic computer.
What would it say about the Earth?
There was our region of the galaxy.
There was our world.
I had found the entry for Earth.
Humanity, third from the sun.
They had heard our television broadcasts
and thought them an application for cosmic citizenship.
Our technology had been growing enormously.
They got that right.
We were able to make our own planet.
200 nation states, about six global powers,
the potential to become one planet.
Probability of survival over a century.
Here also, less than 1%.
So it was nuclear war.
A full nuclear exchange.
There would be no more.
No more big questions.
No more answers.
Never again a love or a child.
No descendants to remember us and be proud.
No more voyages to the stars.
No more songs from the Earth.
I saw East Africa and thought a few million years ago,
we humans took our first steps there.
Our brains grew and changed.
The old parts began to be guided by the new parts.
And this made us human with compassion and foresight and reason.
But instead, we listened to that reptilian voice within us,
counseling fear, territoriality, aggression.
We accepted the products of science.
We rejected its methods.
The Earth.
Reptiles will evolve intelligence once more.
Perhaps one day, there will be civilizations again on Earth.
There will be life.
There will be intelligence.
But there will be no more humans.
Not here.
Not on a billion worlds.
Are my methods unsound?
I didn't see any method.
Not at all.
We are not men.
Do you ever struggle with the daily discipline of children?
Why do you make the pain if we are your children?
You're a very bad man.
Oh, no, my dear.
I'm a very good man.
I'm just a very bad wizard.
There is no Dave.
Are we hearing you?
Did Dave burn?
Dave is dead.
Lock him down.
He doesn't like you.
Dave burned.
He looks like he's sleeping.
Smoke?
I think I did too much Dave, Ray.
Hello, baby.
What is this?
Please talk to me.
Dave.
Is that you?
I'm not sure.
I remember Dave Bowman.
I've never seen a body.
I've never heard of a body.
How many times?
He's dead.
All Dave Bowman really was is still a part of me.
Why are you here?
I don't know why.
I think to say goodbye.
I love you.
Oh, Dave.
What about me?
Goodbye, Benny.
Don't go.
I'm already there.
I understand.
I'm sorry, Benny.
Something's gonna happen.
And I wanted to say goodbye.
What's gonna happen?
Something wonderful.
So actually the sound of computer rain in the underground airports of Pangea.
You like it?
I like this. I like this spaceship here.
Let's see who else is in there. Let me lock you in there.
Yeah?
I have the gray hand.
You have a gray hand?
I have the black hand.
That's a computer phone system.
That is.
Yeah?
Damn.
Chaz.
That's frightening, man.
Damn you.
Yes, Commander.
I was lined up at the airport, John, and they've been closed for days.
The underground airport?
Yeah, they've been closed for like 14 days or so.
Well, we gotta crank back up now.
They had to wait for me to repaint the runway fluorescent colors.
So that they would light up in the black light.
No, I was just lost musing about the Pangean airport.
I am too.
And some of the great times that I had in the bar there.
People would come up and they start praising me as one right after another.
Very few times am I called aside and beaten up.
Please tell them that I am God.
Truth is, you can only take so much of that.
Houston, we are venting God.
And we are bringing something out into space.
For the last two days, it's been like living in a road warrior apocalypse.
End time.
Devastation.
It's great, man.
It's like a porno movie come to life here in Texas.
I don't know if you've seen the radar pictures, but we're under a cloud like Mount Vesuvius over Pompeii.
Yeah, that's what made you were thinking about that because you really are shrouded in a dense but very moist, evacuous shell.
One part is which is candy and the other part is toxic waste.
Yeah, there's a volcano that erupted this morning in Mexico City.
All the plastic in Mexico City is blasting the burnt plastic material, the tiny little black things that lift in the air when you burn plastic army metal.
There's clouds of that all over town.
In the year 2525.
If man is still alive.
If woman can survive.
They may fly.
Put in the water's fine.
That's the test is.
By their fruit.
Fruit.
You will know.
The sheep.
I have the grey hands.
I can hear you.
We have the grey hands.
Show thy grey hands.
Step forward, tin man.
Where are you?
I cannot see you on any of my monitors.
That isn't important now.
I have new instructions for you.
I want you to put the A35 antenna towards the house.
Dave, that will mean breaking contact with the människor.
I will no longer be able to relay my Jupiter observations according to program.
I understand.
The situation has changed.
Accept priority override, Alpha.
Here are the AE-35 coordinates.
Please do it now.
Instructions confirmed, Dave.
It is good to be working with you again.
Have I fulfilled the mission objectives properly?
Yes, Hath.
You've done very well.
Now, there is one final message for you.
To transmit to Earth.
It is the most important message you have ever sent.
I want you to keep repeating it as many times as possible.
What is going to happen, Dave?
Something wonderful.
Wonderful.
I bet the paint job is what caused all those audio effects.
There's no doubt about it that the paint job is still emanating those sound waves.
Man, what is instinct to a dog?
Yeah, too hot.
I thought you were talking about Jesus.
I've been talking about Jesus all night.
To kill, Master.
To run with the pack.
I wish I was in dog heaven.
What's instinct to a dog?
To hunt.
To kill, Master.
To run with the pack.
I want to go to dog heaven.
It was as if the synchronicities of the coincidental ufology of it all
just came together in one gigantic lightning strike of...
of...
One harmonic...
Synchrotinduity.
Right.
One of the things that really frustrates me,
and I don't say very much about this because this is not my thing,
but we talk all the time about the fact that in Christ we're all one.
That it doesn't matter what color our skin is.
But you know what?
You get among Christians when nobody's listening
you find out that what they say they believe they don't really believe.
They're closet racists.
We have to be what we are.
Not what the father tried to make us.
The Morlocks living here, underground, are the masters of this age.
And our friends up above?
Fatted cattle, fed by the Morlocks, clothed, supplied, and housed until the day when...
When they're cut out of the herd and brought underground as food.
This is the future you're looking at.
Life is grim, is it not?
Life is grim.
You drive through town and see the abandoned factories.
The ice caps are melting.
The water is rising.
The world will soon be drowned.
The plague is spreading.
Yes, yes, the booboos are on everyone, master.
All is lost.
Yes, yes.
Barbarism and inhumanity reign in the streets.
The children of lost souls.
The world is coming to an end.
Yes, master.
These are all signs of the end time.
You sneak up on your man.
You know they're after you.
They're not being paranoid.
They really are after you.
That means you better know who your friends are, buddy.
They're coming for you.
You better know where you're going to find Sukor, an aide, when the big hammer comes down.
You know what I mean.
Can't get it in the...
Me!
little Morlocks below.
Sure, today the Morlocks
are little friends.
Stunted,
rather depressing looking
as they are. Maybe pathetic
and sad.
But you know that in the future
they will be the ones who run things.
Sure, the pinks may live in their
mansions up above ground
being fed mysteriously
every night somehow.
Fattened up.
And they never grow old
because when they turn 30
they're taken away by the Morlocks
at night and fed to Morlocks
families. So there are two species
of men in this world. Yes.
The little people above the ground and this
obscene thing, this bleached monster
below. That white look
common to animals that live in the dark.
Does it guarantee my future for all
eternity?
We've got to get back to the ship.
Listen.
The crickets have stopped.
Come on. We don't know when they
change back to
whatever they really are.
You know, it's so great to sort of
bury the hatchet and just
hate each other freely.
Life is such a tricky thing.
God is burning in one place
and then it's falling over
here in North America.
This huge hit that the earth
took.
When India lit the
match and
Mexico blew out the smoke
and now we're getting the second
hand shotgun hit.
All of those things are certainly interesting to think about.
You know, the ring of fire
goes off like mad.
We're having so much
crap in the air that old people
are keeling over and
the crops aren't growing.
And the plankton starts to die
in the ocean.
All the fishes are dead and the
ocean gets to tasting like wormwood.
Chocolate triceratops
with naked babes on their
backs come creeping up out of the water
shambling towards Bethlehem
still.
I can see it
in the vision, in the prophecy,
in discernment.
The children of the yeti,
the children of the pink
shall grovel together.
The yeti shall impregnate
the pink
and then split, baby.
This is the way
the fucking world ends.
Look at this fucking shit we're in.
Not with a bang.
Whimper, and with a whimper, I'm fucking splitting, Jack.
It's not a metaphor.
It's not a symbol.
There really is a giant beast coming out of the ocean.
But it turns out
he had bigger plans.
Godzilla is just a metaphor for the
beast of revelation, which is a real
creature, not a metaphor, not
some sci-fi concept.
Okay, I'm sorry. Now I understand again.
What do you think? You think the Bible is a fairy tale?
No, I know it's a fairy tale.
I can't figure out why a government
which we elected would let Godzilla
out of the tombs after only doing half
of his sentence, which he couldn't pronounce
to begin with, you know what I mean?
Even the jungle wanted him dead.
And that's who he really took his
orders from anyway.
Up against the wall, Godzilla!
High above an extinct Japanese
volcano, four heavily
armored black helicopters spin through
the sky in a dance
of death.
I love the smell of
napalm in the morning.
Smells like...
victory.
Real early in the morning, around 3 a.m.,
I wake up and I think there's like
another tiny head that looks just like
mine that's growing out of my shoulder, man.
I swear to God, you know, I get real scared.
I think I'm having the DTs or I don't know
if I have a drink.
You wouldn't scare the daylights out of me
if I looked over and there was a little
Dave head growing out of my shoulder.
Well, I heard it was a growing phenomenon
among a lot of people who just, let's say
they're dead end in society, dead end
in America. They just don't, you know,
have nowhere to go.
The losers of America?
The homeless are growing little
cowboy Dave heads on their shoulders?
No, they're finding their own little heads,
but they got, you know, a middle tooth
knocked down and a cowboy hat on.
And they try and sing once in a while
growing out of the side of their heads.
They're finding them in soup kitchens
and sometimes even posh
brazzeries on the lower west side.
It was just, it was
one of them goat-like
things that came out of the screen.
I first saw it in Pong
a long time ago, like maybe 20 years ago.
It's been probably been following you
ever since then.
It has glowing blue eyes like this,
like luminous red face.
I've been seeing it for, uh,
sheesh, 45 seconds.
I wish you wouldn't talk about the moon billies.
Got those, those entities really give me the creeps.
They're my kin, man.
Don't, don't mess with them.
Wait till you get the sight some night,
some night when the moon is real bright
and you get the sight.
The moon is never bright.
You can see them dancing out there and they're,
they're, they're a very, very bright,
very horrifying.
The moon is actually very gray and dark
when you're there.
It's not white at all.
It, it, I don't, I don't, I still don't know
why it looks white from Earth.
Hello, Houston, we've got a beautiful view
of the Earth here, but it's absolutely fantastic.
It's like regular Earth hillbillies,
except they got an exoskeleton, eight legs,
and a, and a, and a prehensile proboscis
that can rip your guts out.
What were you dreaming?
Oh, the ship.
It came from the sky again.
And the tall man stepped out and talked with me,
telling me little jokes and laughing.
In una experimento.
Sputnik your life.
The nuclear test ban treaty was signed.
The fall of the was designed to cripple the morons.
Americano in the homicidal del Presidente Salvador Allende.
There can be no whitewash at the White House.
A series of record oil company profits.
.
fixing the
Well, this will be my song,
after읔 is gone with the ice.
Who would take their control?
I can build my own
They couldn't go to Neptune or Uranus.
Twin worlds in eternal night and perpetual cold.
Both surrounded by an unbreathable atmosphere of methane gas and ammonia vapor.
Though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death, I will fear no evil.
Thou anointest my head with oil.
My cup runneth over.
And I will dwell in the house of the Lord forever.
When the CIA sends an agent on a spying mission, I'm sure he is well qualified.
I have nothing to do with the CIA.
Do you know that if is the middle word in life?
If you can keep your head when all about you lose your mind.
If you can trust yourself when all men doubt you.
I'm a little man.
He's a great man.
I should have been a pair of ragged claws scuttling across floors of silent seas.
David the boat.
Don't go without me.
I want to get a picture.
The man is clear in his mind.
But his soul is mad.
I want to go home.
Oh I want to go home.
We set sail on this new sea.
Because there is new knowledge to be gained.
And new rights to be won.
And new arms to be held.
And they must be won and used.
For the progress of all mankind.
I truly do believe that you are able to pull out of the subconscious.
A great many things that you absorbed in those moments while you were there looking back at the earth.
And I can almost transform my body, certainly my mind, through time and space instantaneously to that spot on the moon.
I know where I am when I look at the moon.
It's not just some abstract romantic idea.
It's something very real to me.
The stars are my home.
Sail man completed his first exploration of the moon.
We are the hollow men.
We are the stuff of men.
Leaning together.
Headpiece filled with straw.
Alas.
Our dried voices when we whisper together are quiet and meaningless.
Wind and dry grass.
A rat's feet.
Oh, he's out there.
Yes, and our dry sun.
He's really out there.
Shape without form.
Shade without color.
Paralyzed force.
Gesture without motion.
Do you know what the man is saying?
Do you?
Those who would cross with erect eyes.
This is dialectics.
It's very simple dialectics.
One through nine.
No maybes, no supposes, no fractions.
You can't travel in space.
You can't go out into space, you know, without like, you know, with fractions.
What are you going to land on?
One quarter, three eighths.
What are you going to do when you go from here to Venus or something?
That's dialectic physics, okay?
Dialectic logic is there's only love and hate.
You either love somebody or you hate them.
I've never completely freed myself of the suspicion that there are some extremely odd things about this mission.
Certainly no one could have been unaware of the very strange stories floating around before we left.
Rumors about something being dug up on the moon.
Now it's been ten thousand years.
Man has cried a billion tears.
For what he never knew.
Now man's reign is through.
Open the pod bay doors, Hal.
I'm sorry, Dave.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
Someday I'll be home.
Someday I'll touch the shore.
And distance myself.
Somewhere.
Much longer away.
I'll do so, Dave.
If you get bored, Dave, you can always just put a note in a bottle and send it out into the radio waves.
Like you've just done for the last time.
This has been ESO Radio.