What makes Bob holler?
When I asked Bob, he explained this way
And he said, well, when a little sweetie pie
In a misker twirls by
And rolls those big blue eyes
Oh, I holler
And when some pretty chick
Says she loves my fiddle legs
Well, now then, that can do the trick
Oh, I holler
The Self Genius Hour of Slack
Bob?
Well, I went on down
To the top of the hill
To my girlfriend's shack
To see how they did hang
When I got there
Her cupboard was bare
I couldn't ignite a thing
There was no shard
No bone, no twig
I brought my comic book collection
Was about this big, yeah
Well, Frop Without Slack
Is like Slack without Frop
But where the hell else
Am I going to cop?
I found my dog food collection
About to go to sleep
About five o'clock
But all that food was stale
Thought I'd call that rip-off schmuck
Forgot he was in jail
Ended up killing a porcupine
Just to see if I could smoke his rhyme
Oh, Frop Without Slack
Is like Slack without Frop
But where the hell else
Am I going to cop?
Yeah, Frop Without Slack
Is like Slack without Frop
But where the hell else
Am I going to cop?
I just know that
This here trip ain't through
And fisses me off
And I can't keep myself
Staying one night
In my diffuse
Fрейette pare
I just gotta stay
Just stayin' with fear
There like never-ending
Trash МУЗЫКА
F先生 Disco
Slack, Slack, without FROP.
Don't cop from that guy there.
Where the hell else am I going to cop?
Oh, stay away from that.
Slack, Slack, without FROP.
Uh-huh.
Where the hell else am I going to cop?
No way.
No, no, no.
No, don't bother.
That was Reverend Bleepo Abernathy with...
FROP without Slack.
Thank you, Reverend Bleepo Abernathy.
In digital sound now.
But it'll be slightly different for those of you with lights of change.
This Saturday, August 12th.
About uncertainty.
Blind Lemon Cleveland.
Chaz, can I ask you...
I'll see you there, young lady.
You've been bad, ain't you?
You've been bad?
You've been bad, little girl.
I'll see you there.
Bob will see you there.
He'll still be bad right there.
Little girl.
What's the Heisenpecker uncertainty?
Uh-huh.
Oh, yeah.
That's what I was going to ask.
I see you there.
I see you, young lady.
Young college student.
I'm in the vision.
I'm seeing her.
She's been bad.
And she wants to...
She doesn't want to be good, but she does want to be punished.
Oh, honey.
I've got a tongue lashing for you.
Oh, I've got some punishment.
You like it.
When you get what good?
We know what you're thinking.
The men don't know, but the little girls understand.
Praise Bob.
And the knees must be shaved.
Oh, yeah.
This is very, very, very...
Hey, you, them choir singers.
They know.
Brother, you bring your wife to church this Saturday night.
We don't make you.
This ain't the kind of church we have to get up at 7 o'clock on Sunday morning.
No, sir.
This ain't the kind of church where you come to our church.
You get drunk.
You drink beer.
You drink wine.
You drink mixed drinks.
You get drunk, buddy, at our church.
And you sleep well.
Late on Sunday morning, you pick up some creature and take it home and have intense physical love with that thing.
And then you wake up in the morning and you just deal with it.
But praise Bob, at least his promise rang true, Bob said.
Have intercourse with a beautiful live girl or anything else you want.
Does that go for that digital player right over there by your neck muscle?
Ignore the digital device.
How about that reel-to-reel player over there?
The one we're going to give you in the next few hours, maybe not, maybe longer, maybe the next few years.
Do I have to say it again?
You can make love with appliances.
You can do what you're called for.
Anything you want.
Anything you need to do.
You can have long lives.
Bob loves you.
And he wants to feel you up.
He wants to shake your hand, mister.
And he'd like to shake your money maker, honey.
Bob's out there.
Bob's real.
Don't you doubt that.
And that stark fist of removal, it's real.
And it's going to remove us from the air right about now.
Bob is not the illegitimate son.
Michael Jackson, take it from me.
más
Why?
I get up in the rain
The sun has yet to rise
I shake the webs and clear my head
Put on my doggy
I get eyes
Brown boots and brown fields
Brown is all I see
But the red spot on my middle stick
Is all I really need
On my ride there's many sides
And the bandit's on my tail
Another target in the eyes
Of midnight's growing pale
From morning mist I rise
To help them greet the day
With little silver sunbeams
And little light
In for rays
I paint the house
I paint the dog
I paint the chicken coop
And when they come out
To see the show
I turn and paint them too
On my ride there's many sides
Bandit's on my tail
Another target in the eyes
Of midnight's growing pale
They'll never know
They'll never see
Before the hit I'm gone
Back into the dragon's breath
To sing the twinkle of a star
To sing the dragon's song
Back home folks think what I do
I do to keep them free
And no one knows my secret
No one knows I fly for me
On my ride there's many sides
Bandit's on my tail
Another target in the eyes
Of midnight's growing pale
On their percentile
It's me is what I'm worth
I'm the one who'll airplanes
On their scrolling
Suspects areUL
So why not
When they see their side
My bold 갈
And instruction my fates
Studios,defots,imports qui-
Ooh, midnight's growing.
Ooh.
Hey, who's on the line there?
I can hear the foam coming through the other side of the line.
Ida.
Ida who?
Ida, would you like to say something?
You'd like to say something?
Say it on.
Well, I just wanted to ask Stank.
Stank, okay, like if we sell our souls to the devil,
assuming we can't sell our souls, like our souls are our own possessions now.
As far as I know, the devil and Bob are the only ones who will actually pay for souls.
I have seen the devil in my microscope.
We can like buy our way out of hell.
Does the devil know you can buy that?
With that like extra $30,000.
You can only see it.
That's why the devil hates Bob.
Because Bob gives him money.
You can only see the money that Bob's getting.
Because our triple your money back guarantee.
I think it's a very long legal process you have to go through.
You have to go through an apostate court.
Signed and blood.
And then you have to stand naked in front of a large tribunal.
You know, it might scare you just the sheer size of it.
And so, you know, before you even get down to get your reparations and repayment,
before being sent to hell and you could buy your way out,
you'd have to sue.
In other words, you'd have to sue the devil.
Or, you know, not the devil in car.
Or the incarnate, but the concept of the devil.
Which I guess we all have to do on a daily basis.
That was actually the egg lady.
Thank you so much for that.
Actually, I was actually contemplating that thing this very day.
Buying your way back out of hell.
Yes, exactly.
Well, that's what they go to staying for, you know.
You see, but that's not the only thing that you can do.
You see, what you also have to do, if you are going to sell your soul to the devil,
which you should have a lawyer present when you sign that contract.
How are you going to sell your soul to the devil?
You have to find the devil.
You've got to look in your microscope.
You've got to look at your DNA.
The devil has a tiresome connection of genes.
You have to look at your DNA and then you see the devil.
And trace it back, right on back to your reptilian complex.
Horny little helixes.
Yeah, little lizards.
Snapping the heads off of other little lizards.
Little red capes.
My intention is to root out the devil.
Evolution is the devil, Chaz. You just said it.
In your most retarded, elucidated moment.
What, evolution is the devil?
Why, because it's survival of the fittest?
I mean, nature.
Is that somehow devilish?
That's natural law.
Is natural law evil?
Whoever leaves more offspring survives?
That's evil? That's the devil?
There is no life without death.
There is no pleasure without pain.
How can that be?
There's no pickle spears without
mounds of potatoes out.
I can't see a world in such opposition.
I was wrong, I'm sorry.
You're right.
Right hemisphere, wrong planet.
Susie the floozy said.
And that pretty much sums it up.
Let's play devil's advocate here.
No pun intended.
You're C-B-4, you're an object figure.
But if the devil was DNA and evolution and natural selection, what then would God be?
Yeah, some never-ending state of sameness would somehow maybe reflect a differentness without moving or something.
Stasis.
Stasisism.
Then we must all be Luciferians because we worship the light and quick movement.
Well, I see that's all right.
You can't go talking about, you can't go saying,
well, I know about what God's gonna think about that.
I know about God,
because I know God real well.
I know what he'd think about that.
And he'd agree with me, not you.
Well, maybe God was before the Big Bang.
The moment before the Big Bang.
That infinitely eternal moment before the Big Bang.
Like that was God.
And then the devil took over when the Big Bang.
So the Big Bang was the devil.
Now, there's many who subscribe to that particular.
The Big Bang was the devil?
Okay, how many of our, like, prophets?
And the Big Bang was the beginning of civilization.
Satan.
That's right.
And the beginning of all, you know, 15 billion years.
We are the legacy of 15 billion years of evolution.
Satan owns this world!
Well, think of all those prophets all the way from Enosh down to Enoch.
So that means then we are the devil.
Any atomic vibration slower than light is satanic.
If you wanna talk about moral objectives and where do we go in our classrooms and how many times can we go there, you know?
But then what is...
Think of like Moses being bent over a log and being, you know, burned to death.
But then what is love then?
The death of Satan.
What is love in the universe?
I think love is gravity.
It's a mild form of hatred.
I think love is just gravity.
You know, gravity makes the earth goes around the sun.
That means the earth loves the sun.
Gravity is a mild form of hatred.
Yeah.
Well, I used to do art. Lots of weird shit.
But I gave it all up.
Cause it was too much work.
And it didn't pay.
And it was really just a big pit in the ass.
Anyway.
What the fuck?
What the fuck? What the fuck? What the fuck?
So now I ski
And watch TV
Cause that's a lot more fun
And relaxing
And it's what I really want to do with my time
Art gets old
When no one pays you
Or even understands
So what's the point?
Unless I was going to do it
Just for me
But to tell you the truth
I'd really rather just ski
And watch TV
Cause that's what's a lot more fun for me
And I might as well have fun
Cause that's what life's for, you know
Rap for all the gusto and all that
And I'm alive now
But someday
I'll have to die
And then
I'll be dead
For a long time
For a long, long time
For a long, long, long, long time
For a fucking forever in fact
So I might as well ski
And watch TV
Now while I have the chance
Don't have time to waste on art
And I'm sick of torturing myself
And of wondering if it's done yet
And I'm sick of
Hanging out with all those lazy flakes
Who think they're so smart
And now that I'm free of them
I might as well just listen
To the music that I grew up with
That's the only music that ever really moved me
That new stuff's just gone
Just a trend, it's not real
And now
I can get all those old great songs again
On CD
And then
I can download them all again
On MP3
Cause that's the ultimate technology
Can you see?
Oh I'm so glad to be alive
In this modern age
So much so that
I really don't wanna die
But there's not a whole lot
I can do about that now
So I'm gonna go to the church
And pay my $30 to the church of the subgenius
And eat more vegetables
And I think I better marry my girlfriend
Because it's such a risk nowadays
Even though I'm not one of those people
So I'm probably safe
But you can never be too sure
And so we'll marry
So we can ski
And watch TV together
And feel free and happy
Without having to worry about art
What a pain
Glad I'm through with all that shit
But now I've got all
That I could ever really reasonably
Expect to ever get out of life
Anyway
What the fuck
Fuck, am I so pissed off right now?
Why?
I'll tell you why.
Because I've been reading that book for years.
And I've been reading and not intentionally memorizing, but absorbing the word of Bob.
And for a decade and a half, I had completely ignored that one line in all things.
Slack must come first.
And that is why I am so motherfucking pissed off right now.
I am pissed off for ignoring the plain and obvious truth that Bob has presented to us.
But if Slack must come first, then why am I still pissed off about it?
Well, it's very simple, friends.
Whenever I find myself starting to get pissed off, I ask myself, is there Slack to be had?
And is there Slack to be had in being pissed off?
Well, dear friends, BRAVE FUCKING BOB, I AM PISSED OFF.
You know an effort by my attractin' friend didn't even hurt the guy's reputation.
That's why I am so freaking pissed off.
But one day, I'll get an answer, and I'll translate it to me in full.
Will you polls up or swap me for a lower ability?
You're the 추igan to every crush on You hammering German boys, too.
So take a deep breath, and don't hesitate.
¶¶
hate that crap. Boom!
No more goddamn
God, Bob, Buddha, Jesus on a pogo stick,
rabbis, Robertson, popes, hell popes,
dervishes, doom criers, fakirs,
fakers, Falwells, imams, seers, soothsayers,
stangs, prophets, fucking
door-to-door missionaries, medicine
men or airport Krishnas. Hurry this
you saffron fuck, I'll torture Totnot.
Boom!
No more Frenchmen. Boom!
No more $40 gourmet
Italian restaurant meals that taste like
they were eaten once before they ladled it onto your
plate. Boom!
No more turd-gobbling, piss-spraying
bosses who need to be knocked down and kicked
in the cossacks until all they can do is twitch and
shit themselves. Boom!
And speaking of twitching and
shitting yourself, no more craptastic
current former or wannabe sub-peñas,
Dick's Cordian, or fill-in-the-blank self-styled
faux-intellectual lizard lickers
who don't know a round peg from a square hole from the
pot most of them don't have the aim to piss in properly.
Boom!
No more racist black radicals,
rednecks, no-necks, feminist chicken chokers,
termites, F-marts, pollsters,
butt-suckers, butt-kickers, techno-dweebs,
tax-diddlers, former bouncers who think they're
platinum turds, finger-sniffers
finger-sniffers or foaming hysterical
pontificators with dingleberry-bedeck fruity
pink hats writing shitty, sputtering little
PCs to the mental health of others. Boom!
Boom!
No more ball-twisting student loans,
ovary-rotting junk mail, or
triple goddamn fucking Ed McMahon.
Oh, may I have another? Yes, you may,
you flatulent Tim Breckham. You can have one
nuke after another until they can see your
ass blowing from Bluto. Boom!
Boom!
No more enraging
emails from commercial e-rapists telling
me about how they're gonna make me rich.
Fuck that! Nuke them!
Boom!
And no more Duke Nukem. In fact, triple
goddamn Duke Nukem because I paid six dollars
for a plastic octobrine and the goddamn fucking
tentacles fell off within the first week. Nuke them
twice! Boom!
You all sicken me.
You jest about killing the normals, but I
wanna nuke the Super Bowl and stack the skulls
into a new tower of babbles so high
I can climb to the top and scream at God
for his shitty handiwork.
How dare he create us
and then hinge us in the middle so we have to go
through life bent over just waiting for the next big
butt missile.
If it weren't for that mole
masturbator Jim Baker getting a load of
karma right up his duchess, I'd wanna shoot
the Almighty up his eternal sphincter with a
a cobalt 40s impository.
Boom!
Now, some mewling skanks
will probably blanch in horror
at my proposal.
These pathetic pansies
see life as a precious gift
instead of the planetary skin disease
most of it represents.
They think I'd like people better
and couldn't bear to shoot them
in their drooling sucker-rim faces
if I got a glimpse of a snapshot
featuring their wretched offspring
and pooting grannies.
Bah!
Guess what?
Boom!
Yeah!
If I got to know them personally
I'd have to fend off their nasty breath
listen to their interminable droning stories
and scratch the rashes
that inevitably develop
when I'm exposed to their
violently offensive normalcy.
I don't care.
I say nuke them
until even the goddamn roaches
turn to one another and say
Maya, it's certainly hot in here
isn't it Chauncey?
Boom!
Go nukes!
I'm not gonna be happy
until they're flying around
like goddamn gnats in a rainforest.
Never mind, fuck you.
I say nuke you
and stop wasting your tick-picking time
with mere insults and guns.
I want to see nukes a-poppin'
in numbers that rival
the number of times
Richard Simmons has played
Rump Rangers of the Old Wild West
with every bodybuilder
in the tri-state area
who fell asleep on the bench.
Boom!
Go nukes!
And go speed racer
but don't go country
at least have a little reserve.
Goddamn you.
I'm just kidding.
Oh no I'm not!
A goddamn cock ripping,
blood dripping,
baby on a spit,
gobble shit,
tit splitting,
leech hurling,
colon twirling,
eyeball puncturing,
old church lady punching,
bone spitting,
scattering,
soul splattering,
cat sodomizing,
poodle clubbing,
fuck to you all!
Except for Friday,
Susie and Sister Decadence.
Hi.
So how you doing?
I'm just trying to
Go nukes t-shirts
available for me
so I can build a working
prototype in the backyard
and use it to nuke
all of your goddamn asses
and it won't be a dry heat either!
Praise Bob!
Thank you very kindly.
Thank you very much.
Help, hope,
better call me Huwet!
This is Bill homosexual
Everybody come on out
stop that
Stop following Ralph
Help both you and
First time,
Thank you.
Before the before life
He was my special friend
Always watching out for me
And he'll be there waiting
After my living end
So I'll get into eternity
Believe in Bob
Bobbie Bobbie Bobbie Bob
Bob Bob Bob
Into my heart he stole
Bob
Bobbie Bobbie Bobbie
I'm no longer in control
Bob
Bobbie Bobbie Bobbie
He's the man who sold
my soul
He's the one who made me whole
He explained my cosmic role
He's the man who sold my soul
Yes, dear friends,
the man who sold my soul,
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
That song was done by
St. Kenneth,
Hughie,
and Reverend Bunny Boy.
Friends,
and before that,
we heard some preaching
from XXX Day
with Einstein's
Secret Orchestra
in the background.
And that song about
on your grave
in the fog
and the dew
was Rudy Schwartz Project.
We heard Hell Pope Hughie
doing that boom rant
and the November 22nd
Kennedy assassination thing
was by Pope S. Lilith
who also did
that pissed off rant.
And anyway,
I'm not going to say
that this is a good song
but it was
Little Theodore
and
Midnight Growing Pale
if you didn't figure that out
was by Einstein's
Secret Orchestra.
In the background,
we are hearing
Electro Slat Treatment
by Lamprey Systems
and we're about to hear
some Jehovah Hates Fred
and some more
Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
So hang on, friends.
In fact,
I know you're going to hang on
because you have to
because you love
Bob.
Hey!
Keep those mutilated cattle rolling.
Here comes 9 billion,
200 billion more Zarkons
for the alien empire.
And why they call them doggies?
They're not doggies.
That's a cow, man.
It's a maca.
Up that saucer rant
for Bobbies.
Right up.
That's not a slaughterhouse door.
It's a saucer rant.
Throw them in that saucer.
That's it.
Thanks for the money.
Praise Bob.
So you think
you've discovered
the final secret, do you?
We've been good.
I think you've got
all the answers solved
and all the questions
well posed.
Now, by the time
you pick yourself up
from that basement floor
and you screw the light bulb
back in your head
while you belong,
it won't be long
before you understand
you've been mistaken.
I'm kind of a rattlesnake
picking,
kicking,
scratching,
cactus wiping,
old Brandon Iron
chuck wagon feller.
I'm kind of a Marlboro man,
I just say,
and I like to boss
them little weaklings
and sissies
and city boys around.
That's me.
I'm a subgenius minister
and I've got a whole flock
of dumbass Bobbies
that do anything.
I say,
and you know what?
You could do the same thing.
You're buddies with Bob.
Now, all it takes me
buddies with Bob
is just that membership
to his friends
to join up.
Church of the Subgenius.
Praise Bob.
It won't go.
So much.
Much for American made products.
This, this,
there was an advertisement
for moon pants
that made cow sound
and when you press it,
it makes
the appropriate cow sound.
It's ladies night here
down at the farm.
Don't ask too many questions.
The moonlight is
twanging over the post hill.
Tom and Marvin,
Maria and Slim,
all the rest of the people
down at the Double Z,
all taking a nap.
Chickens,
cows,
the beefalo,
the mighty pig,
have all decided
to throw a party
for yours truly.
And nothing's truer
than this.
Let me tell you
a tale
of the old Spanish trail.
She and I
She was a puerca
si pasera
down the old Spanish trail.
It's easy, little pig,
but I love her so much.
She and I
She wore red shoes.
Everybody said
she would make
very good jamón,
but I think maybe
we're gonna fall in love
sometime.
So we talked
of a June honeymoon
on the old Spanish trail.
Oh, yeah.
But then I started
getting a little bit hungrier
and we're still about
four hours from the museum.
Ah, slack.
Because that's where
we gotta go
because that's the nearest place
to the end of the year.
Slack.
Ah, yes,
dear friends.
Einstein's
Secret Orchestra
on the radio.
ESO's
Swamp Radio.
Broadcast originally
from WCSB
in Cleveland.
New home
of the hour of slack.
Though not of
the church
of the subgenius
which is still at
Cleveland Heights,
Ohio.
Where you
can learn more
about the Bible.
The Bible.
If you will just write
to the number I'm about to give
for free information
that's
at
post office
box
Cleveland Heights
Ohio
Once again
Cleveland Heights
Ohio
www.subgenius.com
www.subgenius.org
Well, it was like
a cheap psychedelic
Martha日
Chess
There were
street
world
place
your
by
town
walk through that airlock right now.
What would he think?
He should display his image,
his graven image,
like some of that
volatilist statue
with the worshippers
raining down the fort.
Bob would say,
hell no, what's wrong with you people?
You're acting like a bunch of
religious nuts.
What are you doing in this room,
though?
You should be out there
running through that field
partying.
Live it up.
Hell, this is Starwood, baby.
Maybe the world ends tomorrow
and you may die.
You should be
doing whatever the hell
you would be doing
if tomorrow was the last day on Earth
or if you had all the time
in the world.
That's what old Bobby
likes you to do.
Either live life just as if
this was the last day of it
or as if it was never,
ever going to end
because if you go to threaten,
who knows if it was
the great,
or great forefather,
Ken Kesey
of the Mary Planksters
who said,
the only sin
is fretting.
Ah, yes.
The only sin
is fretting.
And of course,
it's hard not to fret
and worry in this
miserable world.
Well, it ain't so miserable,
actually,
if you quit reading
the newspaper.
That's what I did, friends.
It's strange,
as you may see.
There was a time
not even a year ago
that I was a news junkie
just like so many others.
I kept reading
and reading every bit
of the newspaper
from the back.
Even the obituaries
where I was starting
to see my friends' names.
And friends,
I quit.
I quit reading the news.
It's been a year since
I've seen it.
I don't know why.
There'll be some news
on the TV
or some newspaper headline.
And by God,
it's exactly the same
as it was the month before.
And it's the same
as it was a year before.
And it's always
the same damn game.
Keeping you distracted
from your own business.
God Almighty,
just listen to my friends.
There's enough bad news
to fill a whole life line.
So I decided
I can't do a goddamn thing
about all those poor,
wretched people
in those countries
starving,
fighting,
or the poor,
wretched people
in my own country.
There's nothing I can do
immediately
except to keep
my own sanity
and keep my handle
on some slack.
Because friends,
if you don't have slack,
you sure as hell
cannot share it.
And once you do have slack,
you've got enough
to go around
because there's no end
to real slack.
Real slack, friends.
But once again,
this ain't no religion.
It's not even
giving you the slightest
chance to get
a message of a hint
as to what real slack
might mean to you.
Because it's up to you.
It's always going to be
a deal between you
and J.R. Bob Dobbs
or Connie Dobbs
if that's who you talk to
late at night.
You know,
we all do it.
Either Bob or Connie,
you've got to serve somebody.
Ah, yes.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
Or your pet dog,
Rover.
Ah, yes.
Bidding starts at a quarter.
Yeah, bidding starts at a quarter.
A mere quarter.
Do I hear a quarter?
We got a quarter.
What's your song, sir?
What's my song?
What's your word?
Give me a word.
Just a word?
Just a word.
Any word.
Sausage.
Lord, I love my sausage.
It's brown and fatty.
Unsung, like some guy named Matty two years ago who we had the misfortune to meet.
Matty liked sausage and Matty liked a lot of other things.
And he also liked to make trouble.
Well, he often talked about his sausage to anyone who'd give him a chance to listen.
And then Matty took out his sausage, started waving it around, got down with the ground.
But he was a jerk.
He just waved at them.
And then he said,
That nasty brown sausage had put him in a swing.
Didn't like the way that he acted.
Always asking questions.
Such as, you know, you guys aren't really all that abnormal.
You some genius.
Aw, you guys do.
Nothing but sit around.
Then he whipped out his sausage.
Woo-hoo!
And we pummeled him to the ground.
But, Matty, where have you gone?
Where have you gone?
Far away.
Now my song is gone.
Thank you.
That was Sausage.
Rum this is strange too.
Just know that if I sweetshad it out, then you'd even like it here.
No, not nice.
The regular sacrificer won't come out of what he split his start.
I think it looks just normal.
Not everything goes as he pleases.
I'm an industry snitch like you.
lit
What?
CRUNCH!
Suddenly a haze descended over the crowd
And they could feel the pee-pees between their knees
But they could not convert it to the necessary juices
With which to transport themselves away
The day unfolds from lamp-lit steams
The asphalt shimmers like blackened streams
And all about I feel and smell and sense your presence near
The lines have drawn the wrong direction and I am aware
No words are needed
No words in books here
Have a look there's something in the air
And measurements of time
Crumble and climb for Jaguar, Knight and White
Yeah!
Living in jungles of radio waves
Never now or ever or yesterday
And just now in the road
The wind becomes cold
For Jaguar, Knight and White dear
No words in books here
Have a look there's something in the air
And measurements of time
Crumble and climb for Jaguar, Knight and White dear
No words in books here
Here's a little tango
I can't see you do tango
Well, not yet.
Living in jungles of radio waves
I never, now, no never, no yesterday
And just now in the air
Where black becomes clear
For jaguar, knife and white deer
In the woods in Buccia
I will look for something in the air
And measurements of time
Are grumbling and clang
For jaguar, knife and white deer
What's to be seen
Just a space
To get to the dark
Oh, no
Awoo
Take a rappin'
・・・・・・ural
On to explain
Isn't that right
Nice and white, yeah
4J Wild Night
Thank you!