Fire! Fire! Fire!
Well, it's halftime.
God's exciting game, dear friends.
And you bet.
This is the All-American Football Crusade.
Coming to you this week from the convenient
Karate Baptist Chapel of the Bulls.
Built right down close to the freeway.
Because God loves all you
safe drivers best.
Yes, friends, this is the mighty
Reverend Bob Tackle.
Fans asking, what happens when you're
shaking inside to go wide?
When you go out on a pattern and get overthrown?
When it's man-to-man defense and you
anticipate the snap? What a rush!
Look out! Another quick penalty.
Another personal foul. An elbow
is caught and you see it. Is it sudden death
or sudden victory?
Well, friends,
the dual isolation can slow you down.
But you know,
the other day a guy once played ball with Notre Dame.
He's a pretty powerful man
in state politics now.
And the ball is not just a ball,
football with real life.
It's a game you can feel a clean hatred
for your opponent, he said.
It's a clean hatred since it's only
symbolic in a jersey.
Well, it's almost time out down on the field now.
And you know, he's watching with you.
He's the number one fan.
And whatever happens, he's enjoying it
because he's hot dog
and not the other way around.
There's no score yet.
It's your ball, dear friends.
Don't give it back.
You've been listening to the All-American Football Crusade
with Reverend Bob Tackle.
And the game just concluded.
Oral Roberts outscored
Chelsea Daly 11-13.
.
I must not fear. Fear is the mind killer. Fear is the little death which brings me.
Bob, it's a Bob world after all. It's a Bob world after all. It's a Bob world after all.
It's a Bob, E, Bob world.
Let's do this.
Subgenius Radio Ministry, hour of slack.
I want to make diversity of the forms open to my words.
You that divide and multiply it, hear my sounds.
I make yield league to you, ancient associates.
And fellow wanderers.
You that move the heart in fur and scale.
I join with you, you that sing bright and subtle.
Making shapes that my throat cannot tell.
He is Bob.
Eager for fun.
He wears a smile.
E.B.M.
Ready to run.
I want you to put your hands on the TV.
Finally there's an end to your life.
Though this is your end.
Hopefully you will pass the army,
I won't be put down for my sake.
E,B.M.
I take applied NAUётся,
I not only take applied NAUpedo andACH thatcan,
Also, my teeth cannot cred sini.
I'll put up a other euphoric eyeball in a's bag,
I will complete that Adjust your Io and other internal ór?
This is Baldwin.
Welcome to the ground.
I'm not connected.
Bob, are you leaving?
I don't believe in this stupid thing.
I'm not going to leave.
Do not try this on your own.
It is extremely dangerous.
I'm not going to leave.
Somebody crashed my party
and stole my cat.
While all the revelers
sang a reverir.
old Lang Syne, this kid came uninvited, the little brat, and took away that cherished cat of mine.
The year before it wasn't any better, for then was perpetrated this foul crime. A party crasher
stole my favorite sweater. What's worse is I was in it at the time. And how could I forget the year
before when ten hell's angels sporting black tattoos unceremoniously broke down the door,
went to the kitchen, and drank all the booze? But my next party will be safe and fun,
for next time I shall not tell anyone. You must make a friend of horror. But through the miracle
of modern radio, we've invited some of our friends from the eerie coast to put on our radio shorts.
The horror.
Yes, they owe us a few.
We owe them a favor, or we owe them one, so they accept it, or we accept it, or something. So, uh,
tonight, radio shorts may be a bit baggy with our one-size-fits-all special presentation,
True to Life Fictional Adventures, with Lonesome Cowboy Dave, country music's least known and least
loved country song stylist and abused substance abuser, his holistic Indian guide, Psychopath
Finder, and his idiot savant, Moron Psycho, who's been a great friend of mine since I was a kid.
I should have been a pair of ragged claws, uh, scuttling across floors of silent seas.
And a very special guest appearance with the Reverend Ivan Stang.
He's a great man. I'm a little man. I'm a little man. He's a great man.
Our story takes place, as it usually does, from a mobile home precariously parked alongside a toxic swamp.
It is November 8th, 1992.
No, no, no, no way. It's January, uh, January something. 1993. Remember New Year's Eve? You drank so much,
you went sunbathing in the Waldo Tunnel, and then...
Uh, well, yes, but this is make-believe. It can be any time. It can be any time.
Like Quantum Leap. Cool.
Uh, yes. Well, uh, radio shorts.
Come on, baby, take a chance with us.
Oh, I used to be...
a dandy, all dressed up from tip to toe.
My clothes, they were the finest, even if I do say so.
But now I've changed my style, and it really suits me so.
I hang around in radio shorts and have nowhere to go.
So take back your knickerbockers, petticoats, long johns, bloomers, and briefs,
bikinis, pantaloons, boxer shorts, or even a cut-fit.
Cause now I've got my radio shorts, I really love them so.
Please listen.
Listen very closely, now we're going to start the show.
Let's join Lonesome, Psycho, and Scabby at their RV near the Toxic Swamp
as they listen to Reverend Stang on the Hour of Slack.
We return now with the Reverend Ivan,
and the Reverend Stang on the Hour of Slack.
Reverend Stang's final message of resire, panic, and acceptance.
Oh, yes, dear friends, enemies, and everyone in between.
You know, a lot of people have asked me,
how can I go about accruing slack?
How can I be a nuclear subgenius?
How can devivalation fit in with my rumba lessons?
People want answers, but listen to this now,
and maybe you'll learn something.
Why give answers?
When you give answers, that just leads to more questions.
Well, the answer's, stop here.
I won't fall into their trap.
Who are they?
You know, the you-know-whos.
They are the people beyond the puppeteer.
All I know is, if you want to get something, you have to give something.
And while there are no true guarantees in life,
I know of a giving you could give
that would help you all on your quest for what Bob is all about.
What?
And that is your vote.
Get out and vote.
Vote Republican.
That's right.
Voting a straight Republican ticket enhances your chances to go into trances.
Now, I must be going, dear friends.
The limo from limbo is awaiting.
Did you hear that, engine valves?
Am I losing my mind or what?
Did I just hear the Reverend Ivan Stang say to vote Republican?
What the flock, man?
I can't believe old Ivan would stink and try to help them Republicans.
Something stinks around here, like rotten fish in Denmark or something.
Me know what stinks.
When last time changed socks?
Being clean, good for mental health.
What do you mean?
I just put them on last Christmas.
And Fleming, wait, what's going on with this subgenius guy?
He was supposed to be politically neutral, and now we find out he...
Ivan's a Bushman and Bob Dobbs is Ross Perot.
Ugh, Perot.
Perot.
Perhot.
I'm just going to have to talk to Scabby.
He's the only person around here who makes any sense.
Dave, super glue my left nostril on again.
Hey, Dave.
Right, yeah, right.
Yeah, sure, sure.
That's it, okay.
I'll have to talk to myself.
I'm the only person smart enough around here to understand what the hell I'm talking about anyway.
What's up with Stang?
Did someone get to him?
Or did he just shell out?
Well, how the hell do I know?
What am I, a psychic?
I'm having awful touches tonight, aren't I?
Yeah, so?
Yeah, so this.
As I reiterate, how could Stang do this?
Or was he forced into it?
Dave, where are my bowling ball nipple rings?
I can't find them.
You're wearing them, Scabby.
Oh, thanks, Dave.
Let's listen to this subgenius tape again.
I record it all.
This time we're going to play it backwards.
You know, the secret messaging stuff.
Like Pat Robertson said, there were secret messages in everything.
All kinds.
All kinds of recordings.
Let's see if there's a secret message on this recording, man.
I gotta find out.
Yeah.
Hey, there's it.
Here, I'm the kill-by-pirate.
Here's not said that.
Well, if the dispassar could have get you to assemble,
then we'd have us meet down there.
Listeny.
Yeah, listen.
I am listening.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, I'm listening.
Here, you're worried again, didn't you?
I didn't hear nothing.
Yeah.
You talking to me?
You mean me?
You must be talking to me.
I'm the only person here.
Yeah, me hear something.
It says,
Script sucks.
No, no, listen.
Listen.
He's saying something.
He's saying...
He's saying DNA level C.
Can you hear it?
Listen.
Yeah, yeah.
That's it.
Listen.
Oh, my God.
What the hell does it all mean?
DNA level C.
Don't you remember?
Last time, Reverend Stang,
on our show,
he said Cleveland was DNA level C
spelled backwards.
What that mean?
Me not know.
I know maybe.
There's a DNA building
near the Abnormal
to design new authority building.
That's where I go
to get my chromosomes
broken down and vivisected.
I'll take you there.
I've got an appointment today.
No possible connection.
A-sector pathfinder.
Engine cleaner.
See, see, see.
There's something amiss
with this setup.
I knew it.
This Reverend Stang is a ringer.
And the only way
we're gonna find out for true
what the hell is for true
is go to his DNA building,
level C,
and scope it out.
And...
Oh, maybe right, chemo sappy.
Hemingway,
me do anything
to move this script along.
Let's mount our pinto, men.
You too, Dave.
We'll be right back
after these messages.
Well, I, for one,
I'm just glad that Christmas is over.
It's such a rat race.
Oh, I know.
Shopping for everyone
is such a headache.
And it's gotten so expensive.
Except, you know,
I bought a couple,
a bunch of those,
those funny sets
of hand-carved nesting dolls
of former Soviet leaders
from Russia.
They were really cheap.
Yeah, I know.
In fact,
that's how I solved
all my Christmas
gift-giving problems.
You mean gifts
from the former Soviet Union?
Yep.
It's amazing
how far your dollar will go
when you buy Russian.
For instance,
I was able to pick up
a dozen of those
Soviet Army watches
for 15 bucks.
Really?
A dozen watches
for 15 dollars?
That's great.
Hey, that's not the half of it.
I bought one of those
Raskolnikov portable color TVs
for only 35 dollars.
Wow.
Yeah, 32-inch screen
on heavy-duty casters.
No remote,
but for 35 bucks,
who's complaining?
No kidding.
Then I picked up
a couple of next-to-new
KGB staff cars
for 75 dollars a piece.
I talked them down
from 100.
Gosh.
Lots of options, too.
Uh, what else?
Oh, yeah.
I got a couple of
I got a really nice
30-unit, 60-year-old
apartment building
for 450 dollars.
I had out-haggle
this really aggressive
Slovenian guy.
He wanted 10,000,
but it was pretty easy
to get him down to my price
when I told him
I'd throw in a case of camels.
Camel cigarette?
Oh, yeah.
They're really valuable there.
These ex-military guys
really go for them.
In fact,
that's what helped me
swing the deal on the subs.
Subs?
You have to get out of the boat.
You mean submarines?
Sure.
They're having blue light specials
on all the military hardware.
Now, I had wanted to get
one of the new
Phantom-class
deep-water cruisers,
you know,
with the sonar evasion,
but it bumped the price
up another 50 bucks,
so I decided to settle
for one of the
Demon-class models.
They were more within
my price range, you know.
Oh, sure.
You have to stick
to your budget.
Yeah, and I didn't have
to blow it all on the subs
since it was only 1,200.
Need some paint
and a couple gallons of caulk,
but otherwise,
it's in mint condition.
Nukes and all.
Nukes?
You mean...
But where I really scored
was on the MiG-22.
They're practically
giving them away.
In fact,
they were running
a buy-three-get-one-free sale.
But, you know,
the cockpits
are kind of cramped,
and it's all that old
vacuum-tube technology,
and I don't know
how to fly.
I mean,
I thought the kids
could use it as a fort
in the backyard.
You know,
I just couldn't see
buying more than two,
and especially since
they wouldn't budge
on the price below 750 bucks,
and they had disarmed them,
so I figured two was plenty.
Wow.
Roll over, roll over.
Goodbye fighter
fighting all the time.
Yes, bad dog, beware,
or you'll wind up
tender, crunchy, juicy meat
on my barbecue grill.
Hi, folks.
This is Tiger Man Solitaire,
bon vivant connoisseur
and champion prize fighter.
But you know me best
for my world-famous
Tiger Man Solitaire
open pit bowl barbecue sauce.
Yes, Tiger Man Solitaire
has been creating
unique soul food specialties
for 35 years.
But now,
as a community service,
I'm helping clean up
the neighborhood.
Take a bite out
of criminal dogs
with my New Orleans-style
blackened filet
or Cajun-flavored sauce,
my St. Louis sweet and sour,
or my Chicago smoky savory.
Tiger Man Solitaire's
open pit bowl patented
meat tenderizing system
turned any tough dog gristle
into mouthwatering treats.
So don't worry about
that nasty neighborhood dog.
If you can't beat him,
eat him.
Tell me about me
and that cornbread duck.
Well, just don't leave it
burning, man.
I got to run.
Don't forget.
A Tiger Man Solitaire
open pit bowl barbecue sauce
can be found
in fine gourmet shops
everywhere.
Not available in Blink's.
Keep it to yourself.
Hello, ladies.
I'm Bernie Furman
of Furman the Furrier,
and I'm here to tell you
I'm his father, Ive.
Friends, the Furman's family
has been in furs for 45 years.
It's 1944.
And as my dad always used to say,
Ladies, don't wait
till there's a nip in the air
for that look of
decade in elegance.
Come now to Furman the Furrier.
Don't wait for Club Baby Seal
or Beheaded Young Otter,
Sable, Silver Fox,
Mink, or Ehrman.
Mink, Schmink, Foxy Schmoxes,
Ehrman, Verman,
we got exotics.
Only in the Furs.
Only five black rhinos
left in the world?
We got four skins.
Oh, you ain't got no four-skinner.
Shut up, Jerome.
Looking for ivory buttons,
spadges, brooches, or pins?
We got the elephant's graveyard.
You want real warmth and comfort?
Go to the Army-Navy store.
You want the look of
decade in elegance?
Come to Furman the Furrier.
And remember,
if it's going extinct,
we got your mink.
If it's endangered,
we'll arrange it.
That's Furman the Furrier,
corner 6th Street in Kill Mammal,
Seapop Run, New Jersey,
repeat address.
Don't just repeat.
That's Furman the Furrier,
corner 6th Street in Kill Mammal,
Seapop Run, New Jersey.
Can I do it?
I'd like a word with you.
Excuse me,
do you have any grape of pawn?
Yes, you,
Mr. and Ms.
Decadent Yuppie American.
Are you one of a minority
in control of your life?
You know,
I'm rich.
Well, if you are,
you should drink the coffee
that says,
I'm well-to-do,
and I don't care about you.
Drink Waster's Choice.
Waster's Choice is made
from chosen choice coffee beans
from the fields
of Colombian slave labor camps,
controlled by right-wing elements
of their secret
governmental police force,
exploiting the poor
for the exporting of the rich.
It takes a lot of money
to keep those police in uniform,
those slaves in command.
That's why Waster's Choice
is so expensive.
But what do you care?
You've got it.
So spend it for you
and your kind's better tomorrow.
Waster's Choice is easy to fix.
Just add eight heaping tablespoons
of freeze-dried Waster's Choice
to some boiled Perrier
and stir.
Take one taste
and chuck it.
It's awful.
But you feel awful good
about your bank account
and political affairs abroad.
Waster's Choice,
the extreme right-wing taste
for extreme right-wing people.
Yes, sir.
Hello.
I'm a bit confused here.
Normally, I would be doing
my most infamously renowned
Hello Art segment
of the show,
but apparently
the producers lost a poker game
over the holidays,
and yes, sir,
it appears that the
Reverend Stang
isn't quite himself,
and well,
who is?
Anyway, I wonder if he can draw.
But anyway,
oh, that's probably one of the producers,
but never mind that.
Scabby Days, who is a drawing,
and Psychopath Finder,
who will draw,
hopefully, they're figuring all this out.
But back to the adventures,
and of course, I'll be back next time
with tips on making faux food
and, oh, yes,
don't throw away
all the wrapping paper
from your holidays.
See you next time.
I'll be showing you
how to make ties
for next year's gift giving.
That's all for now.
Back to your shorts
with the Stang,
Stang, Stang.
The Horror.
He's a great man.
Oh, Stangy, Stangy, baby,
my hero sandwich.
Something ain't right.
He was my last vestige of hope.
Yeah, underground media, my canards.
It's like saying army intelligence.
Mutual exclusion of terms.
Stang's been gotten to it.
I know.
He's been gotten to it.
They got him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We'll see.
There's the Abner Mall,
and there's the DNA building
behind a mile of bad road.
Oh, it's going to be heap tricky.
Lucky for everyone concerned,
me bringing visibility omelet
and a darn some great, great,
not so great, great grand farmer,
two elks,
four play,
who use invisible omelet religiously.
I'm a student of balanced American history.
Wasn't two elks, four play,
shot dead, buck naked
after running through a cavalry post,
after being caught in a lady shower?
Oh, yeah, lucky shot, get him,
but him still invisible at times.
A hundred lucky shots?
Well, if you don't believe in magic,
Emily, that won't work anyway.
Park behind Club Foot Locker at Abner Mall.
Okay, good.
Now I'll have to climb
200-foot electrified barbed wire fence.
Good.
Now I'll walk through football field of landmines.
Now cross pit loaded with extinct P.O. Tyrannosaurus rexes.
Okay, good.
Let them see, try that on TV on shoestring budget.
Okay, here we are, DNA building.
Wow, looky there.
A helix-shaped spiral staircase.
We can just engineer our basic black-blue jeans up there
and we'll be able to see what the hay's going on.
Dang, man.
Oh, me hope this no wild goose step,
Chase.
Uh-oh, uh-oh, I'm picking up a radio signal
from one of my fillings.
I hate this when this happens.
My teeth are becoming radio wave broadcasters.
At last I have control of your radio tubes.
Uh, and I do too.
Good.
This is Rand the Black.
And this is Stimson J. Cat
of the Ren and Stimpy Show.
And you're listening to the...
The Hour of Slack.
Keep listening, you idiot!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Else I shall deal you!
Wow, yeah, we'll be right back to, uh,
the horrible and terrifying adventures
of Lonesome Cowboy Dave, uh, just momentarily,
as, uh, we jump into, uh, Show Side number two.
From right here at Show Side number one.
Thank you.
Now, you're listening to Show Side number two.
And don't forget to subscribe to the channel.
You'll be the first to know when this video is up.
Uh, I'm out.
Bye, everybody.
Oh, hey.
You know, I thought you were a little more
I'm in the show.
You can't have me on a mission.
but the you-know-whos.
Oh, I can hear it.
Can you hear it, Lutzen?
I can hear that.
Yeah, I can hear it, man.
Slapstick.
Knee slapping, side splitting,
rib splitting, gut busting.
Laugh, I thought I'd die.
I think all this is a crock.
I don't think anything's gonna happen.
I don't think there's any real differences here
that I'm fed up with.
It's piping hot and it tastes real good.
Throw out your hands,
take out your push.
Hands on your hips,
give them a push.
You'll be surprised you're doing
the French mistake.
Voila!
You-know-whos.
Oh, I can hear it.
Can you hear it, Lutzen?
I can hear that.
Yeah, I can hear it, man.
You've got to save me
and save the planetarium.
Hurry, they're trying to bomb me.
Bomb me.
What?
Oh, man.
Oh, no.
Here, now, break it up.
Here, now, now, break it up, you boys.
What are you three doing?
No more than two people can congregate together.
This part of the state's under martial law.
Now, break it up before I call
50 armed bacon sandwiches.
Oh, listen, orificer.
This free country's still
we American citizens.
What?
Hey, hey.
Except for Dave.
Him's still waiting for green card,
but it's coming in mail, I'm sure.
America this.
Over the goat.
That's it.
You guys are through.
Say your prayers.
Eat your tax dollars at work.
Lead your political stooges.
Woo!
Wait, wait, wait.
Don't shoot us, armed and Gandhi.
It's me.
It's Scabby.
It's not you, me boy.
Yeah, it's me.
How are you tonight, Corporal Punishment?
Oh.
Just a little edgy.
Seen some mighty spooky things
are in and around the shop here.
Oh, what are you doing here
this time of day?
They're gonna straighten out my nose hairs
with a genetic generic spinal tap tonight.
Mmm.
Oh, these two are my government-appointed
doctors right here.
That's right.
I'm Dr. Schlazmup.
And I am Dr. Neurosurgery.
Oh, so doctors in loincloths
and cowboy hats, is it?
Yeah, yeah, you see,
we're side.
And as a male dance review,
you know, we're a little slow on cash,
so we shake our booties
for lusty middle-aged women.
Oh, I know what you mean.
Times are tough.
I used to unclothe myself
at the old folks' home,
Bailey Acres,
to make ends meet.
Huh, you're okay.
Move along now, boys.
Thanks, pal.
Say, Scabby,
on your way through the shop,
could you stop at the pharmacy
and get me those special pills?
You know, the ones that make me normal.
Okay.
Sure, got ya.
Prozac and Xanax.
Uh-oh.
I'm picking up another message.
From my teeth.
Save me.
Hurry.
Take my cat out.
Wash the car.
Call my agent.
Save me.
Is staying part of a conspiracy
to cheat the FCC
by broadcasting from teeth?
We'll find out
after these impotent worms.
If you can keep your head
when all about you're losing,
there's a blaming it on you
if you can trust yourself.
You'll remember what happened
before we were so rudely interrupted.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
the Psychopath Finder,
and Scabby Days
have set out to find
if the...
The Reverend Stang has sold out
or is being coerced
by the Republicans.
They've perforated
the DNA building level C
weird government
political mutation factory
and discovered a room
full of Stang clones.
He's a great man.
To find the right one
true Reverend,
they've decided to hold
a casting call and audition.
Okay.
All right.
I mean...
Next.
Okay, now,
imagine you're the Jewish tailor
Ivan Stangstein.
Slack!
You want slack?
You want more slack?
Look, I've already done
two alterations.
Any more will cost you extra.
Besides, I can only take in
so much slack.
By the way,
you like slack.
You'll love my slacks.
I got all kinds of slacks.
All colors.
Cheap, cheap.
Don't call us.
We'll call you.
That wasn't a real Ivan.
Next.
Okay, uh...
Ivan over there,
give me a Captain Biscum's
police pirate
with severe brain damage
and syphilis,
Reverend Stang.
Uh, uh...
Slack.
You'll get slack,
all right.
Right before I'll hang you
from the yard arms,
I'll give you a little slack
on the rope, me buckos
and buckets.
Lonesome, you're wearing
lip rouge again.
Oh, here come the dykes.
Crack.
Bally want some crack?
Next.
You.
Hey, I want a Mexican
slack wrap.
Are this Reverend Stang?
He was close.
Boom, chick.
If you're on your back,
I'll cut you some slack.
If you need some jack,
If you need a half-wheeler slack,
I'll cut you some slack.
And if you're whack on crack,
don't cut it.
Next, next, next, next.
Look, you lonesome.
We finally whittled down
our auditioners
down to one more.
God in him,
it has to be the real Stangy.
It's gotta be the real Stangy.
Give me a question
only the true, real,
real, true blue Stangy baby
could answer.
Oh, Sagebrush Sigmund,
that's a right.
Roger Maris,
oh, possible true Ivan,
what is the universal conflict
between good and evil
in regards to the concept
of Bob Dobbs being
two with the universe?
Boy, am I glad
you asked me that question,
brother,
because I can tell you
here and now
that Bob Dobbs
is not only all for one
and the one for us,
all but unequivocally
the male burner
behind all that we perceive
as to what is
or isn't
freedom
in this country.
Can you dig it?
He's a great man.
And furthermore,
furthermore to end
this flimsy plotline,
Dave, my friend,
you're not a Judas.
I'm a little man.
I'm a...
He would have been a doubter.
For it was not I
who bade my followers
to vote Republican,
but a cruel clone
concocted by your
federal tax dollars
to further spread
this depression
of alternative thoughts
and solutions.
Had you not saved me,
what other fiendish plot
would have happened?
That's cruel eggs indeed.
The pantomime stangs
on every station in America
spewing lies
and counter lies.
My friends,
I and my legion
under Bob
owe you all
a debt of gratitude.
Oh, how can I
ever repay you?
I thought you'd never ask.
You see,
we got 109 episodes
of this brain rot stuff.
125 count Western
and them guys out
in San Francisco.
And I thought you'd never ask.
I thought you'd never ask.
On KSF,
something like that.
And see,
we got funny ads too
and commercial parodies
and funny stuff like that.
Oh, yeah, right.
See, and maybe you could
like play some of our
funny, funny parodies
of life and pre-apocalyptic
industrial devolution
on your show.
Well, now,
I'll tell you what I'll do.
I'll do that.
Well, that and more.
I'll play this whole
bizarre, disgusting episode
to my entire
worldwide audience.
How's that?
If you give me the type scores.
That's great.
Just give me the type scores.
It's great, Ivan, but could you lend me a fast 500 bucks, you know, till the recession clears up?
Yeah, well, I'm kind of hanging short, too, man.
After all, you know, we saved your life from the cloners and stuff.
Okay, now, you guys will take a check?
I don't know.
Hey, my check's good.
Now, what do you think you're talking to?
Now, listen, you guys, really pull and tighten up that slack, don't you?
Now, don't you forget to pull in that slack while on X day.
X day, your soul will be laid bare.
You will be sucking them damn church air canisters till they're all run out of soul.
You'll be going, oh, give me some more soul, Bob.
If only I had some more soul in there.
I've learned this a good song.
I didn't see any myth at all.
I don't know.
Do you know who's in command here?
The part of Princess Leonardo was performed by Shakespeare's and the Money Funny,
and the part of Reverend Ivan Stank was played by Les Miserables,
which is no longer showing.
Thank you.
And the part of Psychopath Finder was played by I.K. Murley, the orgasm thief,
and the part of Lonesome Cowboy Dave was played alone.
The part of Scabby Days was played by, well, if it was played.
And thanks to West from the West, and a whole lot of other people that don't make no difference anyway.
And I say to you, I say to you, I say to you, I say to you, I say to you, I say to you, I say to you,
I say to you, I say to you, I say to you, I say to you, I say to you, I say to you, I say to you.
Well, thanks for putting us on.
This has been your Radio Shorts with Wes.
Do you know who's in command here?
Jenkins, Lauren.
Never get out of the boat.
Nelson, Kyle.
I should have been a pair of ragged claws scuttling across floors of silent seas.
Bogertman, Cleveland Wall, Jim Pearson, Patricia Pearson, Dave.
Deluca, Dan DiDonato.
Smith, and of course the lovely Ivan
Stang,
the Princess Wiardo,
Queen of UFOs, and
Sadie Smagola, with
Gusty Kundal, Jim Serra, Megan,
Aaron, Joe, Bill, Annette, Tambourine,
Lisa, Martha, Margaret, Mike,
Lynn, John, Sean, Remo, he's
a dog, John Isham, Ellen, and
of course, everybody else in their
radio shorts. Thanks for putting us on.
Oh, and next week, we are preempted
for basketball. That's hoops.
Hey, hoops, man! B-ball!
Geek basket! Go Dons!
Go Dons!
With extreme prejudice. Terminate
with extreme prejudice.
Let's stop at this ranch here.
Looks like a pleasant place.
Maybe we could...
Look at the...
There's some people riding out.
They're on horses.
I think it is the nearest sheriff.
Uh-oh.
I don't like the way he's slapping that big club
in the pot of sand.
I don't like that skinny little
redneck that's got the giant gun
next to him. And the cattle prod in his
other hand. And that little boy wearing
a clad bike. That guy's half fish.
He's got a noose with 13 knots.
I don't think us northern liberals
should have come down to this little southern
town guy.
Well, I guess we're just gonna march right into that
Mayberry lunch counter then, huh?
That's right. Have some rhubarb pie.
Be served.
Boy, cut my hair, huh?
Freeze! All right. Hold it right there.
You're under arrest. Okay, spread them.
Get your hands up there. Okay, now you.
Uh, yeah, he'll be out of town. He'll be back.
You have the right to remain silent.
You have the right to a court-appointed attorney
should the need arise if you find yourself without counsel.
Anything you say may be held against you, and probably will.
You have the right to one telephone call.
You have the right to order a large pepperoni pizza
should the need arise and you find yourself without pepperoni pizza.
You have a right to wear checks with plaids, but only in case.
You have the right to go to places where you are not wearing stripes.
You have a right to borrow money from a loan shark or a concurrent Saturday or Tuesdays if bail is not saved.
If a bond is posted, you may waive this right.
You have a right to wave and whistle at policewomen in long skirts and leather hose,
under permitting.
You have a right to exercise periods in prison,
a light fruit salad with safflower oil mayonnaise,
and a glass of Perrier water with a twist of lemon peel.
You have a right to play golf with the other inmates on Saturdays in unlimited sauna privileges.
You have a right to a literary agent should your prison novel become a merchandisable bankable property.
If you have no agent, a court-appointed representative will be provided.
You have a right to a selection of gourmet foods, low calorie, prepared with great skill by our institutional chefs and food service personnel.
You have a right to a choice of coffee or an after-dinner liquor.
You have a right to an after-dinner mint.
If you do not get a mint, a court-appointed after-dinner mint will be provided.
You have a right to a full facial treatment, tanning machine session, and mayonnaise full body massage.
If you desire a milkshake, a milkshake will be provided by the court.
All right, take him away.
Yeah! Okay.
Excuse me, you with the dreadlocks, would you put your hands in the air, please?
Uh, yes, sir.
All right, just move away from the car. Move away from the car, please.
Uh, yeah, but that, uh, I...
Just move away from the car, please.
But Mr. Car will miss me.
Turn around slowly.
Oh, okay, I'll...
Turn around slowly, thank you. Keep your hands in the air.
Thank you. Just an routine check, Eric.
Okay, now...
Oh!
Officer, that's...
That's uncalled for.
Hey, just keep your hands in the air, pal. Now, reach, stretch the ankle.
Oh!
That's cheating. I couldn't do it for you.
I want to call the precinct, ma'am. Welcome on down here.
Oh, yes, bring them all over. Bring the whole precinct.
All those that give a drill, all that one-night-long assault,
you gotta call 10-4 on 9-0-1-8.
10-8-3-5-7-8.
1-2-5-9-8-4-8-4-4-5.
Hey, you weasel little rat, get off the air!
Air, air!
Look at that skulking little vermin.
He's an example of the worst scum that ever walked the earth,
the criminal cast.
Look at that strange doliosophallic skull,
the narrow-set eyes,
the quivering rabbit-like chin,
ever moist with a veneer of spittle,
the long, cadaverous, twitching hands,
the clashing, badly coordinated suit, vest, and tie combination,
the Ralph Lauren polo shirt
with the tiny, engraved polo ponies,
and last but not least, that disgusting, syphilitic wart
right in the center of his inflamed nose.
It looked like a cat scratched him across the forehead,
and it seemed like a good idea,
so I brought out Cappy and I let him have it.
This man's been scratched by a cat over a hundred times.
Call an ambulance.
Here comes the dog patrol, and not a moment too soon.
Another bulldog drumming adventure.
Out of the fog comes one relentless man
with his underthrust jaw ready to bite out a chunk of crime.
We have a Gen 15 at B711 at 12 to 34.
Be there.
And we have the store attendant bending over
and grabbing his ankles, and we're photographing the area.
Four-throwing, and he's got a gun.
We're talking to the kitty now.
Trying to find out from the kitty just what happened.
Standby, Ralph.
Can you get stuff in control?
Standby, over.
Maybe Sheriff can explain all of this.
Yeah, after the suspect's been over,
we'll put the log over the wall into the rectum.
Okay, now pull out the...
Oh, no, that's not how it goes.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
That's not showing.
Not right.
No, no, no, no, no.
So we've got to...
Hello, I'm here.
Hi, this is General Fordell.
Oh, no!
Oops, it seems that our caller fell down.
We'll return you to Night of the President after these messages.
That's...
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Okay, wait.
Hold on, wait.
That's Digby, the biggest president in the world.
Okay, well...
And that was former President Gerald R. Ford,
who took a tumble off his golf course, a cart...
I thought that was Chevy Chase.
Oh, Chevy Chase.
Oh, sorry.
You think it was?
Oh, it was so funny when they did it.
Oh, well.
It was funny, those were the days, I'll tell you.
Yeah.
Yeah, it could have been so fun, but...
In a related story, a freakish accident on the set of
The Karate Kid 4, The Final Beginning,
took the lives of Hollywood's entire Brat Pack actors.
Among the dead were counted Ally Sheedy, Emilio Estevez,
Judd Nelson, Corey Haim, River Phoenix, Mary Stewart Masterson...
It's the same news every week.
...Jarren Reeves, John Friar, Molly Ringwald...
It's the same group of people dying.
Most of all, the same crash.
The same...
Oh, that would have been actually...
Oh, what...
Oh, now you're showing that kiddie porn again.
Ah, well, you see, the tragic trade in kiddie porn
was one of the basic needs of the movie.
We've heard the news stories of the past year,
but we didn't seem to be able to interest the electorate
in previous news stories of the recent past life.
But we happen to think, confidentially,
just between you and me...
Yeah, that's right, folks.
Down at subgenius hell or heaven, as the case may be.
A judge in Santa Ana, Orange County
levied a $58 fine against a driver for a mortuary transport service
who failed to convince the court
that four frozen cadavers in his van were legal carpool passengers.
Oh, yum yum.
In a related story, a 10-year-old Tucson, Arizona boy
stole his mother's car and drove it 65 miles an hour
to the Mexican border where he tried to sell it.
Yes, safe sex is for everyone, even necrophiliacs.
And the safest of all sex is the church of the subgenius.
Doctors at Torquemada General Hospital in Balaponga, California,
a suburb of Los Angeles...
...in the San Luis County,
announced that the removal of septic ichor
from the minuscule brain of the 40th President of the United States,
Ronald Wilson Reagan, was, quote,
a screaming mad bitch and cool, droovadelic,
nidokino-egogo success, unquote,
according to an official spokesperson
who spoke only upon the condition of complete anonymity.
As a subdural hematoma caused by President Reagan
being thrown by a bucking syphilitic horse
in Death Valley days of July,
dictated the fluid it collected underneath the dura,
a membrane that covers the brain inside the scar.
A hematoma is a pool of blood as in a bruise.
The blood it collected on the top of the unkillable President's brain,
causing the former President to operate from the left or liberal side of the brain.
Before the operation, Reagan had advocated unilateral disarmament,
nudism, the Equal Rights Amendment, eating oat bran,
giving in to communism, legalizing all drugs,
and turning the country upside down,
scraping the crap off it and giving it back to the Indians.
President George Bush tried unsuccessfully to contact
the former chief executive from his command post aboard Air Force One,
but was impotent to abort Reagan's tirade.
Former television evangelist Jim Baker was transferred Friday
to a federal prison here to serve a 45-year sentence
for fraud, conspiracy, and unmanly unbecoming crime.
He'll be teaching dancing down there in the special management.
Police kept jeering onlookers away from the entrance to the Federal Medical Center
when a van brought the disgusting Baker to prison just before high noon.
I just want to know when the vehicle was for the, uh...
I mean, what is it that you can slip to somebody that makes them
put their head under the couch and curl up in a fetal position?
According to the prison's information office,
Baker had been held in Alabama since October 24th,
when a judge in Charlotte, North Carolina,
sentenced him to 450 years and fined him $500 million
for defrauding his PTL followers and wearing designer glasses.
Unless his appeal is successful, authorities have said
Baker will serve at least 200 years before being eligible for execution.
At the medium security prison in Rochester,
Baker will be placed in a 300-degree oven and roasted to a golden brown.
He will stay in a room without bars or alcoholic beverages
and have access to basketball courts, a baseball field,
polo practice, intermediate swimming, developmental activities...
It's just better that way.
...in prison.
Ladies and gentlemen, we interrupt this program
to bring you a live, extemporaneous interview with the Reverend Jim Baker.
Whoa! No, we don't!
Uh, dear friends, wonderful little bits of, uh,
the KPFA subgenius show that is the, uh,
more than an hour, less than a show
done in Berkeley there by the, uh,
Dr. Howell Robbins.
Howell and Dr. Howell and, uh, Puzzling Evidence.
Engineering and muttering there in the background.
And, uh, I've got this lovely little cover tune here that,
uh, the Rudy Schwartz Project did.
Our friends, uh, Rudy Schwartz Project in Austin.
And, uh, Joe Newman there.
Some of you may recognize the wonderful Max Fleischer cartoon
that this piece is from.
Scariest, scariest damn cartoon I ever saw in my life, friends.
¶¶
Now beware, have a care, you're just filled with air
A single pin would rip your skin, and the pincushion man in the forest there
Would pop you both if you don't take care
Most is trash in the flesh, I'll settle his hush
I'll bust right in and twist his chin
I'll get rough, I'll get tough, I'll just call his bluff
No, no, no, no, please don't go
guitar solo
I'm the old pincushion man, terror of balloony land
Folks all hate me how they hate me
Tickles me the way they rate me
Always have a pin at hand
That's the reason I am panned
How I stop them when I pop them
Ah ha ha
Oh, that pincushion man is a fake
I'm not afraid of his pins
Ah ha ha ha ha
So you're not afraid of pins
Ah ha ha ha
guitar solo
I'm the old pincushion man, jailer of the old
Just literally everyone called me Jack
Damn, I'm good. But the documents are all good
Being in a square yard at Everyone seems to get tired
before Holland shutter early Where we go to sleep
Thank you.