I'll switch on the system.
Can you hear me?
Here comes Bob.
He's smuggling a girl up the seong on one of his flower boats.
Along with a cargo of opium.
Smuggling a girl?
He's a shortwave enthusiast, too.
Of course, that's only natural.
A white girl?
Yeah, I'd trust that guy any day of the week.
Speed's taken a great liking for Bob.
I'm going to do something with him that I never do with strangers.
Take it easy, fella. Don't get your feathers ruffled.
Well, I know, I know.
It doesn't do any good, but I've got to get action.
What on earth can he be doing?
He's Bob.
Sometimes he's overconfident.
He started shadowing me.
There is the shortwave set there.
Here.
Give me that old Thai religion.
Don't give me...
That's a penis.
I rate a slap.
Right? That sounds very charming.
Very charming.
Uh-huh.
And of course, it's cracked to be really elegant.
No, man.
Then I suggest you get your money back and go home.
Okay.
Okay?
Bye-bye.
He said, Bob said, I won't tell you what to do.
I will only tell you how to think.
And you will pay to know what you really think.
It's so true, friends.
Bob sold it.
I smoked it.
That settles it.
It's as simple as that.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Bob's mouth.
The centaur is very ugly.
No, he won't just do any of it.
He doesn't talk, he just gallops around.
Okay, round two.
Stinking old Thai.
Round two of the show.
We're beginning the really funny parts of the show now.
Yes, dear friends.
Welcome to our little carnival.
In this first show of the new year.
It's nice.
It will be.
It's all fresh and clean and slick and spam here at the show.
We got all that bra do from last year swept out.
Big pile of it by the street out there.
I noticed when I came in, there was all these dirty, messed up old coffee cups.
We got those?
Yeah.
They're all clean now?
They're all clean.
Our coffee cups are clean.
Can you believe we do this for you, the listeners?
All of our big stacks of coffee are stacked up nice and tall again.
And our special sauce is back in its package.
And our pens and pencils are neatly arranged in their little utensil, pencil tray bin.
Yep.
It's the birthday of the new year.
Oh, how sweet.
Oh, it's wonderful, too.
Hey, look, it's...
Look!
Beautiful little cutie new year.
Oh, yeah.
It's Cardhouse Robot.
Cardhouse Robot, that is.
And of course, your other ever popular hosts and co-hosts and pre-hosts and co-hosts.
And it's the birthday of the new year.
It's the birthday of the new year.
On the Puzzling Evidence Show, it's the beautiful little...
The beautiful little shiny new year.
We have to go see Slumdog Millionaire and you have to go see, like, a bunch of other movies.
If there's any evidence on this show that's not puzzling, we'd like to get rid of it real quick.
Well, what nobody realizes...
You put it in a box.
It's already gone by the time you hear this show.
All you hear is raw puzzling evidence here.
Yeah.
In little plastic jars.
Let's empty ourselves.
Have your way with us.
Anti-religion.
Atheism.
Uh, um, uh, uh, um, atheism.
Have your way with us.
After, uh, uh, um, I want to say atheism is, okay, logical atheism.
You see, and the point is, uh, uh, anti-religion, logical atheism.
We're coming up with a plan to help save the economy.
We are?
Yeah.
I'm almost finished with it.
I was going to try to run it up the ladder and see if I could get you.
I'm just going to wait until we get approval.
Get the, uh, to float a balloon?
We could get Hal to, like, salute it when we run it up a ladder.
You're talking about that print more money scam?
Yeah.
All right.
We'll have a flagpole at the top of the ladder so that once we move it on up the ladder,
we'll get it to the flagpole.
Then we'll run it up the flagpole and we'll see who salutes it.
Then we're going to, after we get through with that, we'll throw it up against the wall and see what sticks.
But those aren't patriots.
Those are sheep being controlled by advertising and propaganda.
Puppets jerked around on strings by instinct, not using their rational souls or the divine spark of intellection.
Well, that's true, but it was, it's, they were more thought up by, by robot marketing programs.
Another renegade radar-operated robot now in the marketing department.
Yeah.
Brand new, beautiful, shiny, bombastic.
Now we have programs that dream up new products.
Program files.
That are products designed to dream up other new products.
And then they reinvent themselves every 10 years when a new crop of consumers comes out.
Well, now what do you think, when do you think the singularity will occur?
Will it be in, in 2050 or will it be earlier?
You mean where all marketing programs collide with one another?
I think it's a one giant product to one giant customer.
To itself.
Yeah.
And it's itself.
It's just a sneaky itself.
The predicted algorithmic point where the.
And the customer buys it himself.
Computers overtake us and artificial intelligence.
The customer is a product.
Surpasses human intelligence.
This is a real deal.
From that point robots are on their own.
Yeah.
Okay.
Robot number two.
And we'll have one hair product.
I'll take robot number two.
Okay.
It's a little Roomba.
It's now cleaning up the.
Now let them go.
It's a robot.
That's what Dr. Hal said.
Oh my God.
Did we ever need this?
That was a.
I think this thing eats hippies too.
Oh, what happened to them?
A little Roomba.
Oh no.
It's jamming on the hillbillies.
It's losing power.
Those hillbillies.
They're jamming up on us.
They're wrecking everything.
Those are those new batteries.
They only last long enough to fire up the unit one time and then it goes away forever.
A case of battery if I've ever seen it.
And so the hillbillies had to move on.
Yeah.
Well.
I know they moved on because they had no.
They were free.
They were not there last week.
So the hillbilly problem apparently has been solved.
They.
It was?
Well.
Well, I didn't see them there last week.
Nobody told me.
They were lying low.
Yeah.
They had.
They were hiding from revenuers and so forth and so on.
They'll be back.
The minutes passed slowly for the.
Maybe they went out on a coon hunt.
Minutes went away from the coon hunters.
They somehow got held down underwater by a rack of coon, John.
Oh, I see.
There they are.
They're breathing heavily underwater.
The sailor home from sea and the hunter home from the hill.
Yes, old Festus is back, but he doesn't realize that he's already passed on and is walking
to the happy hunting grounds with his faithful coon, Tickhound, on the twilight tour.
The robot Bob in that short transition was by the large.
Long transitions are by the small.
And among the collagiastes, such as Limor and noralpref.com, we're also enjoying new
collages by Reverend Sweetness McGee, who is associated with yet a fifth Swedish coon
hunter.
Welcome to the Subgenius Radio Ministry.
The Ministry of Slack, which you can Google and which like all the other shows is listed
on the radio page of subgenius.com.
This is hour of slack number 1187 and is otherwise almost entirely robbed from Dr. Sinister's
Radio Synesthesia on WCESB Cleveland, with Lonesome Cowboy Dave and others calling in
and mostly from Puzzling Evidence Show at KPFA in Berkeley
with host Puzzling Evidence, cool guy Dr. Philo Drummond,
and the great Dr. Howell of AskDrHowell.com,
who is never at a loss for words.
Oh, well, okay.
So welcome to the show. Here we go.
Oh, did not you have any New Year's resolutions for this year?
So far, did you declare any on New Year's Day?
I had nothing to declare at the customs office.
I actually had a negative bank balance.
And the crowd goes crazy, because they do too.
Everybody in America has a negative balance.
So you haven't declared to somebody why you were, like, in the hole.
That's right.
Yes, the gross liquid product of Halco in this quarter
has been just showing a slide into the deepest red.
You were so far down in the red.
Investors and shareholders of Halco have expressed
that they are not going to be able to get out of this.
So, I'm going to give you a resignation.
Pink.
And some impatience with the failure of their favored sanctuary.
So, did you look for a bailout out of that hole,
out of that red tape and red hole they were in there?
Fortunately, at this time, we were able to purchase
even bearer sterns.
You started a carbon offset company while you were down there.
A carbon offset.
Every time we make a carbon footprint, as you might put it,
we will donate one sheet.
We will donate one sheet of carbon paper to the National Register.
The show that we two can be green.
Green.
And I guess, you know, listening, I don't know,
what would this show sound like when you're in,
out there near East Ontario Avenue?
Pepper Corner.
I know I've been to Pepper Corner.
And now, Philo's pants are being inflated.
What good is bail?
Help me!
No, it feels, it's all right, man.
It'll feel better.
It's me, ma'am.
Oh, it tickles!
Oh!
What the?
On him!
That's a little kangaroo-shaped object.
Don't stop with, don't stick my pants with that.
You old witch!
What's the matter, you old bag?
Get your hands off my pants pockets!
It's the return of Aunt Bertha.
Pickpocket.
Hello, Timmy.
What on earth?
Get Aunt Bertha away from my pants!
We were just...
experimenting.
Experimenting again.
Aunt Bertha, the air is starting to freak out.
Thank goodness!
Every evil thing that ever happened...
Oh, no, thank you, thank you!
...was a result of experimenting.
Oh!
Experimenting again.
Aunt Bertha disapproves of experiments.
And Bertha is back.
She's up all the way, Tina.
Back always here with us.
She's warming up down beside me on the floor.
Aunt Bertha's getting ready for the show.
She likes to go out there.
She's got a glass of lemonade.
She tosses a few one-liners out.
You know, when I was in the crowd...
She tosses a few glasses back.
Everybody worships Jesus.
She tosses a few glasses back,
and then tosses out a few one-liners.
But now I only...
And the crowd tosses a few tomatoes.
...while we were going or retreating to the...
I'm loading Aunt Bertha now.
The Aunt Bertha device is powered with these hydraulic lifters.
And we were able to move her to the other side of the stage here while Hal does this...
She looks like Robocop in that outfit.
I do not understand.
I know, I know.
We're trying to work on that.
It's a little bit crude, but...
Into my head.
Why does she make those faces?
What happened to her face?
I command my spirit!
She really can try to finish all that, though.
Tina, you can do this!
Wow, she shrunk down to mouse size.
That's an incredible special effect.
Yeah, pretty neat, huh?
We'll be able to really wow them with that.
And now you're going to make her big again, right?
Yeah, well, I think...
I'm not sure how much of her reaction...
You know how to do it.
I don't know how to do it.
I don't know how to do that.
You say you don't know how to do it?
I don't know.
We haven't hooked that up yet.
Yeah, yeah, you do know how to do it.
Yeah.
The only thing that ever bothers me is their gibberish.
When they start raving...
Do you feel brain?
Are you mad?
Do you feel like...
We ain't gonna stand with no grudges out here.
I'd like permission to study the new...
I don't know what the hell's in there, but it's weird and pissed off, whatever it is.
Don't just pull someone's skull apart without a little lower arm strength.
No one sees you.
They think I'm insane.
They're the ones who are insane.
What's the boogeyman?
As a matter of fact, I'd want...
Bob said,
Too much is always better than not enough!
He said,
It's a lie, but it sounds good.
Don't just eat that hamburger!
Eat the hell out of it!
Yes, friends, and every hamburger is the ultimate hamburger of slack.
That's the secret I'm revealing today.
The stupider it looks, the more important it probably is.
I guess we're really important, if that's the case.
Hello, you're on the air.
Shoo fly, shoo fly, shoo fly don't bother me.
Oh.
That's all they say, but I know you're on to more extreme topics now.
Well, you know, there's no topic too extreme, be it extreme in its, you know, in its controversiality,
or extreme in its, you know...
It's topical flavoring.
It is at extreme times, so I would say that...
We could be extremely boring.
I'm pretty good at that.
I doubt it, but, you know, it could be like being in an oven, and it's just...
We think we're frogs or something.
Being cooked, and the next thing you know, we're all cooked.
At least that's how I feel about it.
I think the economy crashing, and most of your friends out there crashing, I think it's all part of one big liquid asset that needs to be eliminated.
So what do you think about that?
I think it's time to...
I think...
I don't know.
You haven't been downsized, have you?
I have not, no.
I'm fortunately hanging in there, doing all right.
Things are looking all right on that front for me.
So, but, do you see any horizon, or is it just, you know, one day to the next?
I don't...
Looking at...
You know, without going into too much detail...
Without going into too much detail, it looks like I have job security for now.
If I can just keep showing up every day and doing what I do.
The way I do it.
I think I'm probably going to have some job security.
Because, you know, I...
Just...
I don't know.
My employers are doing all right.
No arch collapse or anything like that?
No possible...
Well, they took a little bit of a hit this year.
They did have some, you know, investment holdings that didn't turn out so well.
But it was really a small...
Really just a small amount compared to their other holdings.
So they're hanging in there.
So are you holding anything right now besides your glands?
Yeah.
No, I don't...
Well, honestly, I'm young enough that I'm not terribly concerned about the state of any retirement savings I have right now.
You know, it'll come back.
If I live long enough to retire, then it's probably going to make a comeback.
If...
Unless civilization collapses completely, which is what some of us are crossing our fingers for.
Actually, I kind of am too.
That's a terrible thing to say.
I know I'd probably be screwed without civilization as we know it.
But I just kind of like to see the disasters unfold.
And what can I say?
This program is like...
This program is like a little black box recorder on an airplane.
You know, we're just documenting...
The descent.
The rapid descent.
Yeah.
That's the way it is.
Things are getting much, much worse and we're just chronicling right now.
And rather than capitalizing, which we should be doing, we should actually be making our own fortunes off the misfortunes of others.
But since that's not our nature, we'll just chronicle the crash.
Hmm.
I think.
I'm not sure.
I guess Reverend Stumpy is trying to call also.
Ah, yes.
I figured.
Let me get him on here.
He believes in many of the same things we don't believe in.
But he...
He's alive too.
Hey, buddy.
Listen, if society did crash, how do you think you would stand if that happened?
I mean, would you be able to go out there and fight?
Like I was saying, I don't really...
I don't think...
Like I said, I don't think I'd really survive very well compared to some other people out
there who've been stockpiling, you know, supplies waiting for the apocalypse for the last 20 years.
Oh, yeah.
I'm not sure.
I mean, there's other ways to get around that, though.
You know what I'm saying?
That's right.
I mean, you know.
No, I personally don't know what you're saying.
What are the other ways?
You know, when you're wet, I mean, come on, dude.
You know, first thing, if you see it happening, I mean, you don't have to stockpile everything
for 20 years.
You can stockpile a little bit of water, buy some booze.
You can trade booze for guns or, you know, women or whatever is what's going to be worth
money in those days, you know?
You never know what's going to be worth money.
I'm guessing.
You're talking about a pirate's life, huh?
Yeah, well, I mean, if society crashed, what else do we have?
A pirate's life.
You're exactly right.
You got to have stuff that'll work.
That's the number one.
Can't lean.
Stuff that won't work.
I think we're like the little chattering monkeys on the beach that the pirates are going to
open fire on very quickly, though, just to get them out of the way.
I don't think we're-
You sound like a butt pirate.
A butt pirate?
Hello?
Ah.
What is that?
If you don't already know, I'm not going to tell you.
Is it like a secret initiative?
Is it like a secret initiation that I'm not allowed to tell if I would-
No.
Do you blame the Illuminati or any other secret groups for the financial collapse like
so many other radio hosts do?
I don't know.
I just-
I just, yeah.
Who are the Illuminati exactly?
That's what nobody seems to be able to answer definitively.
I am ... Actually, I read a little interesting ... Honestly, I will not chalk up to an organization
that is organized, tightly controlled, well-oiled conspiracy machine, things that could be
so easily explained.
Because one thing I have learned about humanity over the years is that we're ... Nobody's
as in control as he thinks he is.
Nobody is really in control.
The people who think they are in control are not.
They have managed to ... A few of them have managed to hold on to their money, but they
have ... I don't know.
They have pretty much been thoroughly discredited.
And if they were really in control, they would not have discredited themselves the
way they have.
If they were really in control, things would probably ... Because they want the illusion
that everyone's doing well.
The illusion that everyone's doing just fine is really good for you if you are oppressing
the masses in one way or another.
Or if you are cheating the masses.
You want the masses to believe that everything's hunky-dory.
And now the peasants are in open revolt, and that is not a sign that the conspiracy is
really in control of things.
Well, a sign that they're still trying to be in control is that nobody knows who
to revolt against.
Everybody's angry about something, but they're not really sure who's ... You heard on your
show someone was talking about Rob.
I think it was Rocknar was mentioning Rob Blugovic.
Yeah.
Rob Blugovic.
Rob Blugovic, as if that current news story were of any import into the actual what's
going on right now.
It's just another sidewalk, another side cake, as they call it.
Or no, a sidebar.
That's it, a sidebar.
Side show.
And tonight's show is a sidebar.
From PR News in Washington, I'm down 250 billion percent from a year ago.
That's the largest drop since 1921.
1868.
Most economists expect to go rock.
Not because it'll help stabilize the financial system.
Jimmy Carter is far worse than initially thought.
The former US president has already been floating outside the International Space Station today.
House Financial Services Committee Chairman Barney Frank says to pump struggling homos.
Frank said, quote, there is no good reason for further delay.
Residents of Gaza shot up today as they sought gas for cooking in staples like flour.
President-elect Barack Obama says this is PR News in Washington.
In other news, Senator Mitch McConnell of Kentucky represents a state that is home to Toyota's
biggest plant outside of Japan.
Senator Richard Shelby of Alabama represents a state that is home to Mercedes-Benz, Honda,
Hyundai, and Toyota.
Just to keep in mind, yeah, Mercedes-Benz.
I'd like to have a home state for Mercedes-Benz.
Bob Corker of Tennessee represents a state that is home to Nissan's 9-cylinder engine.
Yeah, where's my Nissan?
Come on, where's my bailout?
I'm ready for my bailout.
Can I have my bailout?
Would you put my bailout in the back of my Mercedes Nissan?
Now, who lives in Germany that would listen to us?
A German person, the Mercedes owner that he's talking about quoting.
Really? Okay.
Trying to find out once and for all what is the actual date.
What's Bob's date?
What is Bob's real, ineffable name?
What is Bob's name?
What is the name of Bob?
And he's out in the middle of nowhere here.
Really? I don't know.
It's their show.
Answer these questions tonight.
Okay, we're going to drop below the 50-foot level here and see what we've got.
Slack can come when you throw good money after bad and bad money after Bob!
And you can do that at our lovely sales table down there.
Hello, you're on the air.
Oh, hey, Dr. Sinister.
Ah, finally. Good to hear from you.
The original parrot.
Not the original parrot.
The parrot after the original parrot.
I've been sitting here stewing in my own bills.
Up to your eyeballs in them?
Yeah, yeah, paying bills.
Now I just had to downsize myself.
I can't fire myself completely.
I can't really lay off my own.
I'm a lonely employee because he's also my boss.
But I did have to give him kind of a cut in pay and shrink him a little bit.
Well, did you give yourself a boost in pay, a bonus for cutting your...
No, in fact, I got just the opposite of a bonus.
My bonus shrank down when I saw what my balance was.
Parts of my body actually shriveled up in terror.
Well, I just...
A downsizer is in the business to make money.
Huh?
A downsizer is in that business to make money.
The more heads he rolls, the more he rolls in dough.
Yeah, but I've only got one head to roll, see.
And I never was a very good bowler.
And I owe half of my soul to G. Gordon Gordon in Dobbs Town.
It's looking rough, you know.
It's like Santa and the elves.
I think are hard-pressed this time to produce all those such good toys for nothing.
That nothing doesn't stretch as far as it used to.
You know what I'm saying?
Well, Chinese elves use different, what do they call them, standards.
Like when they build toys, Chinese elves use the metric system.
And that's thrown things off.
Santa's elves, rumor has it they've been, you know, putting melamine in the candy canes.
To make them appear more nutritious than they really are.
Well, I just have a feeling this year the kids are going to be getting fewer Skeletor's castle
with the operating guillotine and more little wooden hand-carved toy trucks.
Think about the children out there that are actually going to be, literally,
going to be getting lumps of excrement in a stocking that's holy.
I mean, I don't mean as, you know, holy.
Well, I'm giving my kids toilet paper.
You know, this day and age, if Santa actually leaves you a lump of coal, that's actually useful.
Yeah.
You know, you can actually burn that, you know.
We'll be warm for another two hours this Christmas.
God bless us, everyone.
Ah, the biopic.
Yeah.
The biopic.
That's what this show is. I think this show's limping along now.
Yeah.
It's on its final book. We've got it on live support.
Here.
It's on its last radio trip.
It's got kind of an erratic beat there.
Yeah.
I think it may not last the evening.
I think that the show may be on its last legs.
Already, the newest new show of the whole new year.
And here it is. It's dying before our very hearts and eyes.
And why? It's because you, the listener, did not call when you should have
to give us the very live support that we need.
Oh, so desperately needed.
Then we should shut away the air.
Then we should help the X-Man by explaining his purpose on this Earth.
You would help the X-Man by explaining his purpose on this Earth.
No, I don't know about that.
And mention, Slack is what you need on the show.
Miller of Eternity.
More of.
I don't want any Miller of Eternity.
Before the show dies.
And it's your fault.
Your fault.
You could have saved it.
And it's sold in the brand newest new show of the new year.
You could blame it all on Hitler and his ambitions.
It's just a new show.
It doesn't know how to live yet.
It's just so new.
Oh, brace up.
It's not that bad.
It's like a tiny infant.
You have to tickle it on its body.
Give it a little talcum powder.
A little baby show.
Pat its little tissue and say, come on, little show.
Come on, little show.
Have another bite, little show.
It's just Bob is what it is.
It's just, it's literally Bob.
Someone actually stole an aluminum ladder worth about 10 bucks out of my yard and brought daylight so that they could get a rock and probably couldn't sell the darn thing.
Can you imagine that?
A hard workman like Dave.
Just goes to lay down on the job for a few minutes.
And while he's got his back turned, somebody runs up and steals his entire inventory.
That's why you got to use steel ladders.
They're harder to run away with.
This was a steel ladder.
It was aluminum.
Aluminum.
And the price of aluminum went down that very same day.
So these.
Jokes on them.
Probably couldn't tell it wasn't copper or something.
But, you know, it's spawning a whole new breed.
Of thieves who don't even know how to steal right.
It's.
Now this is just a coincidence.
I happen to have come into possession of an aluminum ladder.
How much can you get?
Where do you take one of those?
Where can you get for one of those?
I'm just wondering.
Just, just.
I'm sure it's coincidence.
I just happened to come upon a aluminum ladder.
Well, just so long as you know which way is up, take the slap, Humphie, salvage or anything.
Any of these places around here, they'll, they'll take your money.
They'll give you a small amount of money.
They'll take your aluminum ladder.
And also take your advice.
All I need is money for cigarettes.
You know, I got swore off eating because I just really couldn't afford it.
But, you know, so I'm down to just the real necessities of life.
Have you tried pantyhose tea?
No, I don't have to have the pantyhose.
I spent enough on that over the years.
Well, the first thing I did was I got a little bit of a hangover.
A lot of the brewers that's coming by, even hard to I mean, it's hard to come by the
brew.
Never mind.
So.
But still, you know, the bills come in.
Bill's for Dobbs Heads.
You know, we got through a lot of Dobbs Heads here and they cost.
It adds up.
Yeah, I always wanted to ask you where those heads are made.
Are those made in China?
Actually, they're made in Taiwan.
So that's why the mouths are where the heads, where the eyes come in.
It should be in the nose is where the ears are.
Yeah, well, they're cute.
Some of the kids pay more for that with the big friendly eyes.
The dog sits with the big anime look to them.
I don't think that's the problem.
I think some of them are just defective.
Just from the quality of the workmanship there.
And you pay for it, meaning you pay little.
You pay less than you pay a good, decent, union American worker.
Dave, it's a moot point.
Nobody's paying anything for anything right now.
They're all just sitting on their...
They got their money in the mattress and they're sitting on it.
With squinty eyes.
If we get caught into a deflationary thing,
that might actually yield pretty promising returns.
Is that like if the wheelbarrows...
If you have to take a wheelbarrow full of money to buy bread or something?
That's inflation.
Deflation happens when the price of everything just starts falling.
And if...
And if that happens too much, too fast,
that can be really harsh on a lot of industries and a lot of workers,
a lot of owners of things as well.
Usually what'll happen to get that rolling is nobody's buying anything,
so they lower the price to try and entice people to buy it.
They're saying, okay, well, we can make a little less profit on this.
And then eventually they're trying to...
They'll sell something at a loss just to have some revenue.
And as...
So that kind of pressure on a market is what can cause prices to fall precipitously.
And that, you know, can be a disaster.
Well, that's what they're predicting for right now because of the Christmas season.
Because some of the toys are so, you know, like a matchbox set of trucks and stuff like that for $5
and everything, they're just like trying to head them up and move them out, so to speak.
Well, the price for sex has fallen quite a bit, but the demand hasn't.
It hasn't.
And Bob Prophecy said that this econocataclysm was coming.
And when I still had a few dollars, I invested it in a big, sturdy barrel
that I have almost ready to set out on the street corner.
I need to drill a hole in it at waist level and put a big bow on it,
put lipstick around the hole.
And I was going to put a little...
I don't know if I put a bell on it, but my neighbor, the other subgenius on the block,
Mr. Sister, kind of beat me to it.
He's already got his barrel out there with a little jingling bell.
There's a Salvation Army guy right down the street.
It's kind of funny, you know, you see the church people go to the Salvation Army guy
and give him money.
And then after they felt forgiven, they'll go down to the barrel.
The problem is everybody's over a barrel already.
You know, nobody wants to be over a barrel yet one more way.
What we have to worry about is what happens when everybody's in a barrel
and there's no more customers for the barrel.
Then we're like the fish in the barrel that they shoot at.
Oh, no, I didn't want to think that.
But you look at, you go down, up and down Mayfield Road now,
there's on almost every street corner, there's a barrel with little Christmas decorations on it.
And they're having a price war.
It's like 50, 75 cents will be marked down to 70 cents
and then marked down.
It's 65 and they're all.
Well, what kind of sex can you get for 75 cents at a barrel stop?
Only only one kind, really.
Like the quick handshake or something.
And you certainly.
Yeah, that's pretty quick, I guess.
In fact, it's too quick.
I wouldn't even call that sex when it gets down to 25 cents.
That's when I know that we could truly call it a recession.
And there's no sex involved.
There's just having thought of it.
You pay 25 cents to somebody to think about having sex with a barrel.
By the way, this would be a great time to let everyone know that the views and opinions expressed on this program are not those of WCSB or Cleveland State University.
Now, continue on with the whole sex with a barrel thing.
This is a.
You were talking earlier.
Never heard of this before.
Well, there was an article in the PD, wasn't there, about stopping barrel stops?
These, there are these ignominious barrel stops.
Are there hookers hiding inside the barrels?
What? I don't get it.
I don't get this.
I've never heard of this.
Hooker. Hooker is rather a rude way if we prefer to think of ourselves as sex industry workers.
Of course.
But at a barrel stop.
You could be a hooker as well as a hooker.
Well, you kind of end up doing both.
Keeping abreast of the market on Wall Street.
The Dutch Gilder surged upward again to a new and higher high.
The biggest extension since June.
And the breakup of IBM and the SEC caused Rockwood Computers to jerk to life again.
Texas Instruments pulled out of a sinking spell and spurted 12.2%.
The bullion boom is sweet and penetrating a whole new consumer market as private gold ownership rises to an all-time high.
And topless interest rates jumped 2%.
In a bottomless market.
And Detroit took a new beating today.
When General Motors plunged at the news of stiffer emission controls.
A full five points to a new low.
As sugar futures floated.
Up and down.
Superior oil's chances flowed freely at 1,168.
To stimulate the aviation field, Rolls-Royce is in for a big, thick, fat government contract to sell jet engines to the Arabs.
Oh.
And Lockheed is moving up a stiff, well-positioned nine points and reinserting its dividend.
To wipe out a very bad year.
It's an uphill battle of big versus little.
And on Wall Street today, everyone is buzzing with the unconfirmed rumor.
That.
Little...
Gary.
Oil.
Is being absorbed.
By the giant G.R. Conrad organization...
to corner a full 10% of the world market.
Could one of you guys like to scoop up the table.
What's the actual value of a consultants cap?
I called me wife to tell her I'd be late.
A full 70 patrimonial statues of oil.
Yeah, mine too. That was from the movie The Happy Hooker with Lynn Redgrave playing our friend Reverend Xavier Hollander.
See Xavier.com or XavierHollander.com about her new memoir.
But now let us return to Puzzling Evidence, or rather let us let in into your mind via the doors of reception.
I just came in the back door and I'm walking forward between the two lobes.
You didn't sign anything.
No, no, I don't touch anything. Because if I touch anything, your whole mind changes.
And we don't want to change minds, that's for sure.
Yeah, we don't want to change minds, not at this hour, because 4.16, four minutes away.
We want you to stay in your life the way you are, because if you change now, who knows how that could change the future.
The whole universe could change, and we're into saving the universe and saving the planet.
And if you're going to save it.
What are you going to save it from except change?
Look out, here comes change.
You've got to keep it from changing.
Look at all that change.
Move up the future and the planet.
Blinking in the sun.
To be like we love it.
Like a cool Brookside chat with our friends.
Did you bring the tabbouleh?
Nay, I left it behind.
Oh, well here, have some cool.
Cooling.
Tastes great.
I'm getting so sleepy.
Refreshing too.
In the sand.
Someone left the cake out in the rain.
What's changed?
Help, help, help, help.
Put up, put up.
Organized religion.
Bad, bad, bad.
Whatever.
I'm.
Bad.
The whole.
Whatever.
Put them up.
Do it.
Whatever.
Just don't.
I'm.
Don't.
All.
Do it.
Really got.
Really got me.
Don't.
I'm gonna put up Charles Darwin.
Celebrate.
The United States of America.
Give.
Me.
Secular progressive society.
Our secular progressive society.
We don't like religion.
Put up, put up, put them up.
Put up.
Then.
Really got me.
Got me.
Celebrate.
Society.
Secular progressive society.
Correct.
I'm the whole.
Whole.
RICHARD CHER
We're secular progressive society.
Organized religion.
Bad.
Whatever.
I'm.
Bad.
The whole.
Whatever.
Put them up.
Do it.
Whatever.
Do it!
Secular progressive.
Secular progressive society.
I'll turn it back on.
Some day...
Right now.
Slow down, man.
It's not worth it.
Easy, easy.
Happy New Year.
I'm at a loss for words.
Thanks for saving the show like you did.
You know it was yours, it was up.
You saw that there was a job to be done and you rose to the occasion.
You called the show and you saved it.
Thanks for roasting the occasion.
Thank you.
I love the show.
I wanted to support the show.
And you've done a good job over the year.
It's a small short year, I know, but the job you've done so far this year has been exemplary.
Now the caller is laying the show back in its little cradle.
I feel better already.
Good, me too.
You're having another glass of wine.
The power of the show.
I'm having another glass of wine.
This is sort of like art for one person.
Why don't we share that bottle?
This entire...
You can.
This entire show is just for that...
The guy who just hung up.
We could have a big swig on that bottle of wine.
Look, that's why this horrible music's playing.
I'm like, I'm too wimpy.
I can't even get the thing in.
BYU do ya wee.
11,008.
I'm a seeker.
67.
B-A-U-B-Y.
And a P-H-S-S-S-U-U-U member.
2001.
Bonds that make us f- coming to ourselves.
Y-U-Y-U-S-10-30-34.
With one great grand trial.
Three years ago.
200 stink stink.
Excuse me.
R stink.
S-upthr-s-upthr-76.
Job.
Sex.
Three missions.
Second.
The t-the t-the t-the...
Three days.
Nothing.
Subgenius.
Do nothing.
And second.
He knew how to touch a boy like no one else I've ever known.
A very uncooperative repeat offender.
Be the man.
Second.
Excuse me.
Subgenius.
Increasingly atheistic.
This way.
21.
Burning.
Also.
Contempt for simple religious faith.
Religious faith.
Wasted time.
It's sickening vulgarity.
And much more.
We subtly but surely lend ourselves to the devil's project.
Make it very hard.
Carnal and violent good.
I think of...
Singing mothers.
LSBS.
Yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes.
Shaken.
S-speculations.
Deep deep plan of happiness.
We be like.
Stop teaching the gospel.
So little thought.
We like.
And we be.
Subgenius meet.
Living together.
An alternative.
Cull.
Cull desire.
Hi.
Ahem.
Visit our website.
And that would be subgenius.com.
Or norellpref.com.
Who also did the previous collage as well.
Friends here at Tarzan's radio studio in the throne office of the slacker mansion.
While listening to background music done by yours truly.
We're getting ready for Winterstar this February.
By preparing new subgenius cerebral reformatting programs and videos.
And if you want to you can see roseandcomet.com for info on the Winterstar Simulator.
Which also features other alternative religions and thought forms.
Or there's always the events page at subgenius.com.
And here's Dr. Howell to tell you about our new cruise ship.
Here on the cruise ship known as the Lovecraft.
Only top flight subgeniuses get to use these facilities.
And I'd like to.
Welcome you to the special Bob Dobbs lounge.
Where only the top swells of the church are allowed to participate.
This is the well stocked larder.
Fully equipped with every kind of computer game.
Here the hot tub.
Hot and cold.
This is X-Tate.
Oh this is everything in the subgenius suite that only the hierarchy are permitted to use.
And across the way.
The special rustic wooden retreat.
With the door that you can actually lock from the inside.
Yes.
All has been prepared.
And all is in readiness for your sacrifice.
For you shall have the honor of being the sacrifice to the great God.
And you know if it wasn't for the honor and uh.
That's a record.
Oh I see.
Hark the storm is coming up.
Such an electrical storm as we have not had for twenty years.
Philo is scanning.
Accessing.
I see.
It's a Bucky Beaver for Ipaner toothpaste.
Going over that railroad trestle once again.
We'll have to hide in the storm cellar Mabel.
Down with the roots.
On the root vegetables.
The cans.
The persimmons and parsnips that she's put away.
Ought to last us through the winter.
Pork snouts there.
And the ham jelly.
The hawks.
We've got it all.
But uh.
It's just a dirt floor but it's home.
Might be a hard winter in this stony soil.
Hard for a man to put down roots.
Something there is that doesn't love a wall.
Old man winter is coming in.
I can feel it in my bones.
Temperature will drop down to.
Sub zero.
Lakes will freeze.
Pipes will burst.
Okay you're right.
Hide.
Bones will crack.
Get into the couch quick.
Old Jack Frost leering at the windows.
Don't let him in.
Jack Frost.
Nibbling at your fingertips.
Nipping at your nose.
What's with the nose thing that Jack Frost has?
Is this like.
He's a mean old man.
And I've got a baguette of trouble for you.
I'm sorry.
A baguette?
Oh lucky.
It's just not a bag.
It's not a real bag.
It's a baguette.
So what's your bag man?
Well my bag is the things that I have grown accustomed to over time and become adept at.
At which I have become adept.
Like Johnny Adept.
Oh I see.
Now.
Oh.
It is.
It's easy for you to say.
I'm a man.
I'm humble before this level of scientific development.
But do you actually see with your eyes or do you see with your mind?
Who is this guy?
Can you comprehend what the weather has to tell you?
To our people it is a special goddess.
A spirit who sits on the highest of the mountain peaks.
She weaves the webs of night in which the stars are spread.
And the moon is carried through the heavens by her scuttling imps.
Look at them scuttle away.
That's a scuttlebutt of his.
Leaving their serious spore behind them.
When angered she would brew up clouds as black as ink.
You're talking of Aunt Bertha?
No.
The old spirit of the mountains.
Of the Catskill Mountains.
Oh.
At the radio station, music and speech are picked up by a microphone
which turns these sounds into electrical impulses
that correspond exactly to the pattern of the original sound.
At the radio station's transmitter,
another electric current is being produced by a device called an oscillator.
This current, known as AC, or alternative current,
continually changes its direction of flow.
It flows in alternate directions about a million times a second.
It could be said to have a frequency of about a million hertz.
A million.
That is better expressed as a megahertz.
Or in ouches, I think.
Are we going station to station?
We are going station to station.
Satellite to satellite?
Station to station, you mean person to person?
You know, a trunk call.
Yep, on the radio.
That's what we do here on the show.
We go satellite to satellite.
Who will be my love tonight?
Literally, folks, because we get in on your mind.
Get out of my mind.
But your mind is not my mind.
My mind to your mind.
So put on your plexi leather pants and dance around in your orange wig.
But I'm tired.
And I'm moving.
My orange...
Hey, someone got my orange wig.
I gave it the Orpheus.
Oh, man.
Bob.
Praise God.
Well, if you can't see that clue why on earth am I even using this cardboard box.
There's yellow trash in it.
Oh, the pink one is even alright.
That's the hit.
Or there are other ones out there.
Oh, yeah, those are the River misters.
Yeah, those are good.
here at the radio station now.
We had to cut back a little bit.
All the colons on our digital clocks
had been replaced with semicolons.
Oh, wow.
Had to cut back a little.
Well, that's a sure sign, man.
Things are sliding.
I had to have a colon replacement
after my colonoscopy, yeah.
That's so good.
They gave me the two little dots.
And that probably cost you...
Because I was down to like a semicolon,
which it's...
I don't want to go into too much detail,
you know, with bathroom stuff,
but it becomes tricky.
Yeah, I can imagine.
People with hyphenated names are...
You know, you would assume
that they would be making money
because they were the richer classes to begin with.
But they just dropped the hyphen now
and maybe it's the middle part of the name even, I guess.
Hyphenated names strike me
as a little more contemporary,
a little more modern.
I don't think those were...
You know, like historically,
people of the aristocracy
would have multiple last names.
You know, four or five of them.
But they were not hyphenated, I don't think.
Right.
They'd carry around the originators of the family
like an orangutan.
Well, now, Princess Wee and I,
if we wanted to be trendy,
we could be...
I could be Ivan Stango.
And she would be Princess...
But see, she just really didn't want to end up
being Princess Wee R. Stang.
She just...
That was not going to work for her.
It just doesn't quite work.
So she's...
She kept her maiden name of Doe.
She was never a maiden.
I thought that that meant she had money.
Boy.
Oh, well.
We're making do.
If we knew what planet...
What her home planet was,
she's probably rich.
You know, if we could just...
If we could only find her a way back.
I think if we got rid of all the planets
and started from the very beginning
a new start for mankind,
a new April for the apes of Japan,
a new beginning.
Dave, I've got news for you.
The people of the future did that,
and this is what happened.
Well...
Us right now is what happened.
Because people tried to perfect...
They went back to the beginning
and tried to make everything work right.
And this is the best they could do.
And they keep doing it, though, right?
So that's why the...
kind of the third layer of confusion
keeps on...
Well, nobody knows for sure
how many times it's been done.
See, that could...
You know, you want to be an existentialist
or something,
there's your lack of meaning right there.
What if you've already tried everything
about 5,000 times
and you don't know it
and you think you're doing something new?
Some of the really bored science fiction writers,
modern sci-fi writers,
have tackled that subject.
But they really...
Those really are the dull ones, you know,
because it's just the same story
over and over again.
With very minute changes each time.
And it still ends up being depressing.
No matter what.
Well, these are the people
who would trade an apostrophe
for a decent snack,
a day's work.
Hey, you know,
if you've got holes in your shoes,
maybe you'll let go
some of the letters in your name.
I've got an extra S in my first name,
my slave name,
that I could probably drop.
Nobody would know the difference.
Save a little tiny bit here and there.
We could even get past the initials,
like there'd be no R or S,
or, you know, you just...
Why do you think Kentucky Fried Chicken
changed their name to KFC?
The signs were a lot cheaper to paint.
Yeah, we're getting close to the end here
of the Puzzling Evidence Show.
More in the distance.
Where you can go out to YouTube
on Puzzling Evidence TV.
Time is swinging night here.
And you can see episodes of the show
also on Philodrum.
That's episode 8,
Philo vs. the Giant Scorpion.
We have some regular
Puzzling Evidence shows set to
never end.
And don't forget, the last episode,
the human of the paper.
www.quiveringbrain.com
If I were hung upside down,
say a railroad bridge,
and set in motion,
then I would...
Of course, you could go to your
kpfa.org archives
and retrieve your podcast
at your leisure.
Join us next week for more of
The Human Pendulum.
Send them to your friends and your enemies.
It may work best for our show
if it is your enemies.
A swarm of Wall Street bankers,
a war machine,
13,000 corporate lobbyists,
nay, saying Republican and Congress people,
right wing yakety yakkers.
They already think that, so...
Weak-kneed Democrats.
Oh, good night.
Double-chinned...
Oh, you have to go?
Well, alright then.
Hail and farewell.
Uh...
Could you say that again?
Sure.
Where do you want me to start?
The beginning.
Start at the beginning.
AT&T was wiped out today.
Polaroid dived.
And the whole market
sunk right down to the bottom.
Praise God!
Hail Dottie!
For more information about the Church of the Subgenius,
look at subgenius.com on the internet.
Or you can write to us for free information at,
got that pencil ready,
post office box 181-417.
That's box 181-417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
44118.
Here in the US of A.
And we welcome all the news stations that are now playing the show.
By the way, the background music here is by the Flyin' Ryan Brothers from their CD, Totality.
You can learn more about them from Ryanetics.com,
as they are the Flyin' Ryan Brothers.
Friends, praise Bob.
And happy new month and year.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's just Bob is what it is.
It's just...
It's literally Bob.