From PR News in Washington, I'm indecently assaulting thousands of lawyers over the internet.
Hundreds of the attorneys were injured.
A nursing home fire in Russia has called on Oprah Winfrey to restore the country's new media, including DVDs.
They said firefighters were searching for short or careless women's bodies to perform indecent acts.
It has to happen every once in a while, and it's alright.
On Wall Street 3-13-5-6-7-4-4, the Supreme Court has agreed to kill at least 29 people in the third quarter.
Talk show host Condoleezza Rice has pledged to use tear gas and clubs to disperse PR News from Washington.
Bob.
Doves.
Hello, Mrs. Dobbs. What is it?
Well, it's probably not...
The Self-Genius Power of Slack.
By God.
Well, well, well.
Sober he couldn't think, drunk he couldn't talk.
Why, he couldn't even identify himself in a mirror.
Careful now.
That's right, Captain Shotgun.
Well, well, well.
I found this little piece of grass.
What you'd better do is dig up that grass.
Tattooed.
Tattooed?
I got bitten by a...
Tattooed whack once.
All right.
Okay.
Right.
Okay, boss.
That's right.
Yeah.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
Thank you, Mr. Fernandinende Lee Murr.
Friends, did you know all of his stuff is available on archive.org?
Well, it is.
Welcome to Hour of Slack number 1,757.
We're going to call Lonesome Cowboy Dave in a little while to see how his buzz is doing.
And later we'll go to the earlier 22X Day with Dr. Howell, Dr. Drummond, Reverend Angry Larry,
and the man known as X.
But first, from the brand new Rudy Schwartz Project album,
Take Me in Your Arms and Sing to Me Like Dick Powell,
a little ditty called The Medicinal Properties of Chicken.
Did you ever feel like dancing on the ceiling when you're reeling from the karma of your body?
Don't you think you're straining from the training that's remaining in your struggle to become a sedentary turd?
Lick your spoon.
Force the issue neatly when you find yourself humming so sweetly
to the sound of poultry praying while the chemicals are spraying.
Oh, and the things you've been saying seem absurd.
Practicing Registered Nurses and Paramedics recommend
that you never underestimate the medicinal properties of chicken.
A man that you never underestimate.
The medicinal properties of chicken.
Like the same registered person.
Hello?
Okay, Dave, I guess we're going to start the show.
Is that okay?
Should we start it?
Yeah.
I've got Nino Rota's 8.5 score in the background, but you can't hear it.
Oh, I love 8.5 score by Nino Rota.
I've always thought it was silly.
It was Sarangina's Roomba.
Remember Sarangina's Roomba?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Sure.
Yeah, that'll be coming up somewhere in the background.
You won't be able to hear it because of our special Tarzan sound.
What makes you think I would even want to do that?
Well, in the writing?
In the radio station, it was sort of fun.
You could hear the same thing everybody else heard.
That's what I say.
All you can hear is what's coming through my phone.
That's all I want to hear, I guess.
Yeah.
Who needs to hear anything except what's coming through Reverend Stagg's phone?
Now, I don't have much of a buzz right now, but perhaps...
Here, take some of this.
Hey, don't bogart that.
It doesn't work except for on Tuesdays.
I hate it.
Oh, here it comes.
I stretched the phone in the yard too far, and there was a big buzz right there.
Yeah, yeah, I heard it coming.
I was just turning the music up, going, why is there singing in the background?
And there's the buzz.
But I don't care.
Just let it buzz away.
I'll let this Italian sing.
It's a fierce buzz, though.
It might even be a fierce...
It's a fierce...
Now, this is a defeating buzz.
It is a pretty fierce buzz.
Yeah, listen to that buzz.
It makes your voice kind of saw-toothed.
It makes me sound kind of rodent-like.
Yeah.
If you looked at the wave file...
If you looked at the waveform, I mean, it would look like a sawtooth pattern.
A form of artificial intelligence-gathering devices?
All masked into one?
One small device?
Well, that's probably what we're hearing is feedback from all the surveillance things
that the government turns on once they realize we're recording.
Yeah, they never miss the hour.
It's like, I've had requests, though, and I just told them where to go.
You know, just go to the website, and you can download any damn show you want to,
and just leave me alone.
They didn't even care.
I think it had something to do with this.
Have you ever heard this phrase?
It's you can flunk it, you can flop it, and you can get titties or something.
I think it's German.
Yeah, since it's German, no, I haven't.
I don't worry about that.
De flunking, huh?
What?
De flunking, I forget.
I'm not sure if I even remember it ever to begin with.
You know, you forget something, you have to remember it to start off with.
Right.
That's the big problem.
But maybe what we ought to do is, to grapple with the buzz, maybe we should hang up,
and I'll just call you back again.
Oh, that would be quite all right.
Let's try that.
Bye.
Okay, now I've got to call him.
Let's see.
Oh, it feels wonderful.
Oh, so much better.
Oh, my God.
Hello?
Go to hell.
You.
Need a helping hand.
I'm going to have a stuck.
Touched by monkey.
Bob Dobbs pipes never go out.
Of the dog.
Hey, hey, hey.
That wonderful collage was by our old, old friend, Reverend Rasta Billy Bob Diddley, called Diddlin'.
But kids, I have to cut in here with something serious.
I'm 66.6 years old, and I started hearing something like this OK Boomer thing years ago.
Some of my fellow old folks may not yet know that OK Boomer...
OK Boomer is a phrase lately used by snarky young people to blow off old folks' opinions or otherwise scold us for being luckier than they are due to accidents of birth or, as some would see it, evil, conscious, and deliberate greed.
And I have a response, of course, a little rant that I call, I'm OK Boomer, You're OK Boomer.
A title I stole from Philodrum.
Rummined, which probably only boomers would get.
Here goes.
Sorry, non-boomer.
Sorry you received one-tenth the education I got in world history, math, and science due to my generation selfishly using up all the available learning resources, such as, apparently, brain cells.
Thus, you can easily imagine the thousands of generations before boomers.
Those billions born.
Before 1946.
Living in perfectly balanced harmony with nature.
Up until exactly 1946, when callous boomers unanimously began their carefully constructed plan to deplete as many material and economic resources as possible, specifically in order to deny them to our own children and grandchildren.
Except, hey, wait a minute.
Admit it.
You younger generation.
Deliberately stole all the miracle cures for chronic and fatal diseases for yourselves and stashed them all away in your future where we can never get to them.
Therefore, the only rational response is death to all resource users.
All of them.
Because let's face it.
This is the, no, you are decade.
I've never seen it this bad.
Hey, that guy you admire so much turned out to be a lying, thieving bastard.
Nuh-uh, you are.
Hey, that guy who says he's a huge patriot actually dodged the draft.
Don't you wonder if that one news network you watch that says all the other news is fake might actually be the fake one?
Nuh-uh, you are.
Why is that rich, honest, stable genius?
Why is that?
Because that's the one guy you voted for, the genius family man you voted for, hiding his grades, his taxes, his bankruptcies, his payoffs to hookers, and throwing snowflake temper tantrums.
Nuh-uh, you are.
And so on.
As the unpronounceable French philosopher said, no persons are more frequently wrong than those who will not admit they are wrong.
Easy for me to say, huh?
Yeah.
Churchill said, I have often had to eat my words, and I must confess that I have always found it to
be a wholesome diet. Still, we all need someone to blame. The poor have sometimes objected to
being governed badly. The rich have always objected to being governed at all, as G.K.
Chesterton put it. And as Uncle Dr. Onan Canterbite so famously said,
the conspiracy is vast enough that all efforts to combat it are valid.
Full-time street activism or mild temporary annoyance, a lifetime of screaming or a single
click of the tongue, railing against global economic and ecological collapse, or an eye roll
that the preferred crisps are on a different shelf than last time. Class revolt against the
powers that be, or sniping against one's peers. Any anti-conspiracy action by a subgenius is correct.
All non-subgenius action is suspect. And as Uncle Onan also opined,
think of the thing that you like the most.
Do that for a living. You're guaranteed to like it less over time. Think of the thing that you like
pretty well. Do that and keep special things special. You can apply this principle to beliefs
as well. Tell the world that you believe pretty well. Do that. Keep special things special.
Or you can insist on sharing your most special beliefs with everyone and insist that,
they share them too. Let me know how that works out. Thank you, Onan.
And Paul Mavridis of the Lies Foundation recently had this to say.
One of the many reasons why a free press is vital, and one of the reasons why warlords and
war profiteers in every country try to destroy an independent critical press,
as their first strike at any conflict they engineer. In America, the independent
press is on its knees. Our public eyes and ears blocked or taken to pieces at every turn by
corporate vulture capitalist ghouls, cable quote news unquote network choke points,
anti-democracy libertarian right tech titans like Zuckerberg, and extremist right billionaires like
Murdoch. When the Republican eco-terrorists are finally routed from office, the next targets for
political extinction are the moderate.
Or corporate right Democrats. Most of them are as corrupt as Republicans when it comes to addressing
this planetary emergency. There's no more slack left in this battle for corporate stooges,
neoliberals, and pseudo-environmentalists to sabotage forward motion. But finally,
friends, let me quote the saint of sales, our guru and God King man, J.R.
Bob Dobbs, who said, concerning all of it,
Balderdash! Yes, friends, Balderdash! I dare repeat it. I say it too. Balderdash!
Sure, non-boomers, we boomers aged. Fancy that! Some of us guessed wrong. Fancy that!
I didn't, though. It's just that my most pessimistic guesses turned out to be grotesquely
optimistic, as proved by my 1973 movie, Let's Visit the World of the Future,
as seen on YouTube, if you don't believe me. And yes, it was a hell of a lot easier for us
boomers to get a college education if we were white and middle class.
Here's a good quote. By the way, I'm getting these from The Week magazine.
It may be risky to impugn the worthiness of old age, but I'll take my cane to anyone who tries
to stop me. Those who feel that it's not worth it to be a man of the old age, I'll take my cane to
a man of the future. I'm not a man of the future. I'm not a man of the future. I'm not a man of the
Welcome respite from the passions, anxieties, and troubles of youth and middle age are either
very lucky or toweringly reasonable. Yes, we should live as long as possible,
barring illness and infirmity, but when it comes to the depredations of age,
let's not lose candor along with muscle tone. The goal, you could say, is to live long enough to
think, I've lived long enough.
Mae West put it more succinctly. You only live once, but if you do it right, once is enough.
And President Theodore Roosevelt said, death is always, and under all circumstances,
a tragedy, for if it is not, then it means that life itself has become one.
As a consequence of all this philosophizing, Dr. Philo Drummond, with the approval of his
close personal friend, John F. Drummond, said, I'm not a man of the future. I'm not a man of the
future. I'm not a man of the future. I'm not a man of the future. I'm not a man of the future.
They are Bob Dobbs, has handed down these new revised subgenius slogans, updated for older
subgeniuses, as follows. The subgenius must have snack. You'll pay to know what you really ate.
Have sex with your beautiful live self.
Pull my eyelid over my own eye. Too much is still almost always better.
If I can't whip it, I will avoid proving it. And any head good, any head good.
And now, back to the battle of the buzz, in which we finally figure out what the problem is.
It's Dave's head.
Oh, the buzz is worse.
I heard it go off for a second.
Try picking your nose or scratching your butt.
Disappear something on there.
There's a radio on another room that is buzzing itself and it doesn't make much sense for it to be buzzing for no reason.
Maybe it's causing the sound, so hang on just for a minute, all right?
Okay.
Princess, we just arrived. We're, we're, come back. The buzz went away.
Dave's still on the line, but the buzz went away.
I want a buzz. I thought I was going to get a buzz.
Well, I'm sorry I removed the buzz. Maybe I can do something and the buzz will come back.
Oh, okay.
We need to restore the buzz now.
No, that's okay.
Okay, good.
Yeah.
Dave ran off.
Oh, boy.
To turn off his radio, which was in the background going .
Oh, no.
What's that?
That's the buzz.
That's, it came back again?
Not like it was. It's not as bad as it was, but there's still some buzz. And the funny thing is-
Now it's off again. On my line.
What did you do? Anything?
I took a step with the phone.
That's what it is. You need to take a step because when you were, when you ran off to deal with the radio, Dave, when you ran away from the phone to deal with the radio, very shortly the buzz ended completely. And then when you came back, it went . So I think it's something inside your head that interacts with the speakers.
I think it would have to be.
It sounds good right now.
Yeah, it's a self-created universe. This is what I want to hear right now. So live with it or live with it.
Live with it or live with it. That's what they always used to say.
Self-created universe. Yeah, sure.
Well, what, you don't think we should all be exhumed from the outside?
I did that time I took acid. I thought, oh, this is self-created universe. I invented this whole universe myself. And now I've woken up from the dream and I want to get back to the dream. This is confusing.
Yeah. Who doesn't really? You know, that's all I dream of every day.
I was 16 years old.
One of these days I'm going to walk in a room.
I thought, this is self-created universe, just like Lonesome Cowboy Dave said when I was 16.
And I was wrong. I was wrong because after the answer.
Have you heard of the philosopher Descartes? Have you heard of Rene Descartes, the drunken old fart?
Descartes, the French philosopher, Rene Descartes. How do you pronounce it?
Yeah, that's Descartes.
Descartes.
Descartes. I always read it.
Yeah. It was a Monty Python.
It was a Monty Python song about Descartes.
Rene Descartes was a drunken old fart. He could drink you under the table.
Well, all I know is that when the acid wore off, it stopped being my self-created universe and went back to being God's self-created universe,
which meant I wasn't getting any special treatment anymore.
And it was back to normal. And when I stubbed my toe, it was going to hurt.
So make your own reality, man. But can you really make that stubbed toe go away?
At least you're not raising, you know, fighting gophers anymore. That could be a crime, I guess, in Oklahoma or St. Louis or someplace.
You know, raising them to fight, you know.
Oh, yeah. The fighting gophers. And that was a great team.
Yeah.
It sounds like a great team, but actually it was a bunch of substructurally different people.
And they were disoriented scientists, starting with the name Bill and continuing on into, you know, South America,
Tierra del Fuego and all those places where the walls are melting.
I don't think Dave's acid has worn off yet.
How long has it been since...
Okay, we were 16 years old when we dropped.
It's been 116 years since then now.
That would be 50 years for me.
That means you're 20 years old, yeah.
Yeah, 50 years for me.
And that is one long, strange trip.
Yeah. Long, strange dream.
Actually, that was... Long, strange dream was the wink, wink type title of an art movie I wrote a script for after my teenage LSD trip.
And it was about a young man who had grown up on a concrete plane about the size of a spillway outside of a lake.
An abandoned spillway.
And there was a whole society of people living on this little concrete square.
And they never stepped off of the concrete square.
They felt that they did have to be there because that was reality.
And they grew up knowing that if you left this concrete square and went out into messy, confusing nature,
which was all around this big concrete square at this abandoned lake spillway where I was going to film it,
then you would trip.
You'd go to hell.
And sure enough, self-created prophecy, this dopey kid who's going to be played by my friend Gary Potts
sneaks off the concrete and goes around a bend and instantly becomes disoriented and lost
because he's on uneven ground for the first time in his entire life.
And it was a metaphor, Dave, for a bad acid trip.
I like allegories and animal...
It was a mighty metaphor.
For whom I do not know.
Like acid, a wind ripping through a gigantic tuba.
We're going to ignore Dave for now and go back in time six months to 22X Day.
In four seconds.
It said it was running.
It's subgenius.
It looks a lot like one of our charts.
Look at this.
Wow, that is a...
It's a very subgeniously looking chart, but I don't see any overt subgenius...
Well, you see, you've got your masonic symbol...
The dick is labeled dick.
That's the one part of it that's like, well, yeah, that looks subgenius-y.
The hand lettered.
Add it on to everything else.
Man. God. Dick.
Oh, Potter and Petal Nostril have entered the room.
Yes, it's all coming together.
At least we know that these aliens have four fingers, a thumb, and a dick.
They're just lazy.
Too lazy to draw all the fingers.
I wasn't sure of that one.
I know we heard that it's not a visual radio show today, so...
That's why we have to describe in relentless detail everything.
I thought if anyone could describe it, it would be you.
Well, I did my best.
I mentioned masonic symbols and other things that were present in that document.
It was indescribable.
It kind of looked like what I'm wearing, the Tree of Knowledge.
Yeah.
Yeah, except it was...
Somebody else getting in on that bandwagon.
Mm-hmm.
On that hayride.
That's me.
Yes, we have the special pills.
We're all set up for the broadcast, but I sense a lack of will to go forward.
A lack of will to proceed and make it.
Make actual hay while the actual sun shines in the sky.
I sense a lack of sense.
But, I...
That's because my sense of hearing is wrecked.
The other part of my hearing, my headphones, fallen off.
The soft part.
Do you see it anywhere?
You must have...
Oh, it's over there.
It's way over there.
God!
Over there.
How in the world did it make its way over there?
Here, let the dog get it.
It's trying to get away from...
There you go.
Well, that's why it's loose.
The dog got it.
And it leaves weird little crust on my ear.
What's up with you?
People have been looking at me like, boy, Stan...
Your face is on fire.
You could take a little bit of...
I've been getting that.
When I take these headphones off, it leaves this crust on my ear and people will be talking
to me.
I can tell they're looking at the ear and thinking, he doesn't bathe.
I have a set of headphones that do that.
Stan's like bathing.
He doesn't bathe.
I have headphones that are black and you get it off there and it's like, it looks like
he pelted you with some coal.
Disgustipating.
You have to say, I fell down the stairs.
I fell down the stairs.
Those are Chinese headphones.
It wasn't Lucy hitting me.
No.
I fell down the stairs into the coal bin.
They're super cheap though.
They're much cheaper than other headphones.
They eat your ears.
Well, that's a pretty cool album here.
There's a lot of vision.
They're cheap.
So cheap they fall apart before you get to the end of the line.
No.
They usually fall apart before you get to the end of the checkout line.
The center cannot hold.
The front.
Mere energy.
The front end, not the back end.
When you get in the checkout line, that's when the Chinese product puts it on.
Lean into the microphone, Dr. Trump.
You get into the checkout line and that's when the little old lady way up at the front
starts arguing about a coupon that she's got in the bottom of her dusty reticule.
Wow, Philo.
You sounded just like Dr. Holliday.
right there. That was an amazing ventriloquist.
Did you see how I threw my voice?
I'm standing there with my melting ice cream
raging impotently.
An impotent rage.
Anybody can sound like Dr. Howell
for a little while.
And then what happens?
Well, then it becomes obvious
that it's an imposter or a robot.
A robot?
The Howellbot 3000.
Yeah, there's a picture of it right there in that paper.
The first thing I seen on here
was that the bear cubs stomp lovebirds.
You're looking above the fold.
That's an inside joke.
Above the fold.
You have to look below the fold.
This doctor was apparently
a quack.
And I should have known from his haircut.
You should have seen this doctor, Hoffinstetter.
In Dallas.
He had this poofy haircut like a sportscaster.
In the days when
hippie long hair was real cool
and sportscasters started to try to look
a little bit hip.
So he'd have this boofy...
Carl Sagan could pull it off
but these guys couldn't.
They were just jocks.
Carl Sagan as a sportscasting weatherman?
No, he could pull it off
with that kind of haircut.
He could never do.
Because he wasn't trying very hard.
Did you know that Carl Sagan
was a habitual pot smoker?
Can you believe it?
He could have had frop all that time
but instead he smoked May Rwana.
Daily.
Carl Sagan.
Smartest guy in the whole world.
I can't believe a person who's smart
could possibly be on that stuff.
It wasn't until I tell Dr. Howell.
Yeah.
That's the way I answer those questions.
I don't look you straight in the eyes
as if you were the Federal Bureau of Policemen.
I would say I did not know anybody
who compressed that sound attack
through the tuba
that we were talking about before
nor did I know that Carl Sagan
was a famous pot smoker.
Yes, he was.
He was a pot smoker.
He didn't talk about it
until he was about to die
of old age or something.
But he did.
Yeah.
Of pot smoking.
He's about to die.
Pot smoker.
He finally made it.
Yep.
Been a pot smoker every day for years.
Fool him.
His last words were
pass that over here, please.
Yeah.
The compression's deep too.
I guess when you're dying
and stuff like that
and you want somebody
to smoke a joint with you
and everything.
If they were to lift you up
there'd be like real dark,
deep bun ridges
and head ridges
from where you've been
laying in a pillow
for a long time.
That must be what happened to Philo
because he was a pot smoker.
That's what happened
to Mr. X too
but they're confused
about his real identity
so they just call him
Mr. and Mrs. X
in case he shows up.
I didn't know he was married.
Mr. X?
There's a Mrs. X?
He has a transgender personality
where he dresses up
like Betty Fulton
and then he walks across the room
and shakes his hips.
Oh no.
I know X.
Oh yeah.
He was at X Day.
X was at X Day
and he was on the show.
I got tired
after two hours.
I said,
somebody come up here.
Anyone from the audience.
Well, there was only one person
in the audience
and that was him.
It was X.
X.
And he came up
and sat down in my place
and held his own pretty well
with Hal and Philo.
He did.
He was fairly sparkling and funny.
So your rants were held down
by the appearance of X.
No.
I wanted X to get up
and relieve me.
Tell some trigonometry jokes
and stuff, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, and he did.
He was great.
He was really pretty funny.
World's smartest
Trump
versus the world's
dumbest genius.
That would be Bob.
And who would win?
It's really
because the world's
dumbest genius
is a little bit dumber
than the world's
smartest Trump.
Well, dumb
could be interpreted
in a number
of different ways.
I know.
If you
dumb as someone
who doesn't talk.
Have the resources
but not
employ them
to solve
the problem.
The problem is
a dumb thing to do.
So if you're
a dumb genius
by definition
since you can't talk
you're probably
almost certainly
definitely not
a subgenius
because
well,
here we are.
You might be
a dumbass though.
I might be.
A dumb, dumb bullet.
You might be
a dumbass.
Well, I think
I reworked that old thing.
But maybe I just
act like a dumbass.
Yes.
So everybody
will treat you
like an equal.
It's a good method.
Good plan of attack.
Act like a dumbass.
It's the, you know,
it's disarming
people.
But what kind of an ass?
They're so stupid
they can't hurt us.
Yeah.
People feel friendly
toward you.
Do I need to act like
for them to treat me
like a superior being?
You've got to start
by being treated
like an equal.
Then after that
you can aspire
to a superior being.
Superior being status.
But I want to
perspire to greatness.
So we want to leap
from the low status
to the high status
without going through
the various changes
of degree
and slight alterations
of the personality
to leave them.
So you're going to be
doing those
ontogenetic reverations
on me again,
is that right?
I'm just suggesting
you may.
You know,
as a sort of
pig,
guidance counseling
thing,
to try to
suggest.
I mean,
I already gave up
my 47th chromosome
because you said
it wasn't doing nothing.
Well,
I wouldn't want
to be
misunderstood.
And now my hat
don't fit.
So I've got to
work harder
so I can buy myself
a new hat.
That doesn't seem
worth it, man.
Why all the hats
in the world
will be yours
in a few days.
Oh, you're probably
talking about that
revulsion X
that, you know,
X day is coming.
X marks the spot.
X is the answer.
If X is the answer,
what is the question?
The question is why?
X, why?
I can only say
you must be hard up
for religion
if you want to smoke
a smoke.
Smoke a book.
A bunch of X.
Yeah, if you want
to smoke too many Xs.
X, not speaking
specifically of Xs,
my friend.
I'm speaking of Xs.
X equals MC Square Dance.
MC.
That sounds horrible.
I'm MC Square Dance.
No, nobody's ever
used that name.
MC Square Dance.
It would take a minute
to, especially in a club
where they were selling
a lot of E.
Right.
You know,
where'd you get all that E
you're tripping on?
And you'd go,
E equals MC Square Dance.
And MC Square Dance
would be up there
playing square dance music
and all the disco hipsters
on Ecstasy
would be doing
very, very bad imitations
of, you know,
formulaic square dancing.
Yeah.
I can see it all right now.
I don't know.
I think you'd make
a lot of money
but you'd have to sell
an awful lot of cowboy hats
and yellow buses
and all that stuff.
And E.
You'd have to sell
a lot of E
and Ecstasy
and...
Oh, yeah.
And...
What's...
MOL...
MDA and...
Antler Dust.
Yeah, and MOLLE
and all of those
different drugs.
Tiger Ball.
MDMA and MOLLE
and E and Ecstasy
and all of those things.
You might even...
Each one of them.
But don't mix them, man.
Don't mix them.
And whatever you do,
stay away from the
hydrogen dioxins.
No other way.
I thought I'd revved up
my motor pretty well.
But now I learned about
porting and relieving
the block,
cylinder bore,
racing flywheels,
custom camshafts,
exhaust headers,
dual exhaust,
tolerances,
new ignition,
high compression heads,
hemispherical combustion chambers,
dual carbs,
dual point distributors,
dual intake.
Well,
I needed a mechanics dictionary
to even follow
what they were talking about.
guitar solo
What superhero feeds the bears?
Uh...
Ranger Smith?
Oh, yeah.
That's it.
Hey, everybody.
We're at X-Day.
That brings to mind
that fabulous John Kay
Yogi Bear cartoon.
Isn't that wonderful?
I'd like to see that one again.
It's a Ranger Smith cartoon, actually.
Boo-Boo Goes Feral.
Oh, yeah.
Boo-Boo Goes Wild.
Because they realize
that they're bears.
Right.
They're still a bear.
They might look cuddly
and everything else,
but they're still bears.
He takes off his bow tie
and slobbers.
He goes,
he goes,
I have it on DVD.
Well, first they leave the cave
and they're reminded
by Ranger Smith
that every animal
in Jellystone Park
has to wear at least one item
of human clothing.
So they go back
and they get their little hat
and necktie
and so forth.
But eventually
they give it all up
and they're out there
surrounded with flies
and feces
and slobber.
And then when,
when, uh,
what's it, Daisy Bear?
Who's the female?
Cindy Bear.
Yeah, Cindy Bear.
Cindy Bear sees Boo-Boo
in his feral house.
In feral state,
she goes native.
Yep.
And pretty soon
they're both in the bushes.
Arrgh!
And Ben,
he's horrified.
That's a great cartoon.
And Ranger Smith is going,
Yogi,
I'm going to have to shoot Boo-Boo.
You know,
what the rule book says.
When,
when they get this way,
I have to,
I'm going to have to put a bullet
through his head.
You know,
Yogi can't argue with it.
They're,
they're about to do it.
This isn't,
this is an actual cartoon.
Yeah.
This is,
this is,
they,
they did make these,
they end up
clawing each other's buttocks
into bloody shreds
in the joyful finale
of the,
of the cartoon.
Well,
it's like,
what would happen
if real nature
entered the Hanna-Barbera universe?
Oh,
yeah.
You have to put Boo-Boo down.
Deputy Dog.
Yep.
Oh,
let's not go there.
No,
Deputy Dog is not,
I don't believe
He also did the Jetsons too.
They did a version of the Jetsons
like the,
Really?
He did.
Well,
that was,
that one would be well worth
catching up with.
John Kay.
He's in the
Clampett School of,
Clampett Style.
Yeah.
Boy,
he sure got shafted,
didn't he?
Well,
yeah.
John Kay.
Just like anything.
Hope Judy plays a prominent role.
I thought she was hot.
Of course she was.
She was like,
what's her name
from Lost in Space?
Linda Clark.
Yeah,
Penny.
Oh,
my God.
Judy.
Yeah,
Judy was,
wasn't Judy the mom?
Judy is the daughter.
Who was Penny?
Penny was the,
Penny is on Lost in Space.
That's what I said.
Yes.
On Lost in Space,
it was,
it was Penny.
Yes,
Penny.
Well,
there was like a teenage girl,
a mom,
a teenage girl,
and a 12-year-old girl.
Right.
Well,
I was 12 at the time.
Right,
so that'd be Penny.
Therefore,
it was okay for me
to think certain ways
about this underage girl.
Right,
I mean,
you're talking about
the Jetsons or Lost in Space.
I was thinking,
when I was 12,
I was thinking about
the 14-year-old Judy,
or 16,
17.
That's sick.
Well,
it wouldn't get you
very far today.
It could happen.
I always thought
the mom was pretty hot.
Actually,
we should never,
none of us will ever
be able to run for Senate
having said the things
we just said.
We're tainted forever.
Good.
Unless the,
the Senate loosens up.
I thought just hanging around
with everybody here
would just kind of
taint you for,
you know.
It will fully besmirch you
and darken your career.
There's way too much
taint up here,
as Susie just said
from the second row.
There's way too much
taint up here.
Well,
some of us are ready to go,
willing to serve.
Yes,
anytime you want.
We are willing to
do something here.
Yeah,
I've been sitting here
jabbering for 55,
five minutes,
so anybody else
who wants my mic,
you can hunt it.
Hey, listen,
you know what'll happen
if he leaves,
right?
Mike, hunt.
Then I can play my shit.
See,
so he might want to
think differently
about his,
uh,
Well,
you want me to play my shit.
Oh,
no,
I do.
I'm just saying.
Oh,
shit,
this microphone's on.
This mic is hot.
This microphone's hot.
It's a hot mic.
Now he's gonna know everything.
I,
I'm not in
with anything
that the dog is doing.
Yeah,
sure.
He didn't,
he didn't really care.
You guys are,
you're a bad influence
on each other.
You don't,
Philo's already bad enough.
He doesn't need
any encouragement.
Yeah,
were you,
were you brought back,
held back a grade
because of some kid
that you wanted
to hang around with?
No.
No,
neither was I,
but could have been.
Instead,
he went to a Catholic school.
Should have been.
Moved this kid,
who's my best friend
in like fourth grade.
We did,
you know,
everything.
And yeah.
What kid was this?
thought I was some kind
of a bad influence,
so they put him
in Catholic school after that
and I would never
see the kid again
until high school.
And did he come out
a full-fledged Catholic priest?
I would think so.
Yeah,
no,
maybe not a priest,
but,
you know.
Oh,
the other night at,
we had fireworks
in our town
and tons of people
and this guy,
these two guys
in a really hopped up
brand new-ish Corvette
come rolling around
the corner going,
hey, hey.
And they're handing out,
I should have grabbed them,
but I think they were like
Chick Tracks or something.
But it was all about God.
He was like,
you need to know God.
And I go,
dude,
I am an ordained minister.
And he goes,
well,
then here.
And I go,
I don't want your,
I know all about your God.
But Chick Tracks
are intensely collected.
And then he got pissed at me
and then he insulted me
essentially by,
you know,
saying,
well,
if you know God,
you sure don't like to share.
And I didn't know
what that meant
and I kept saying
praise Bob after that
and then we kept,
and I wanted to ask him,
it's like,
oh,
did your God help buy you
that Cadillac or that Corvette?
Because he probably did.
They believe in the prosperity gospel.
In the future,
you should just take the pamphlet
and grin
and then like pretend
like you blow your nose on it.
Those pamphlets
are collected
by Kurt Kirsteiner
and other unspeakable persons.
I don't know
if they were Chick Tracks.
Actually,
they almost look like business cards.
And on the back of this Corvette,
it said dumpster rental.
So it was his own.
Now the truth comes out
about this religion.
It's like dumpster rental.
Great big letters.
I'm like,
oh yeah,
you get a nice vet
confirmation.
Invertible,
riding around.
What would Jesus do
dumpster rental?
So much for Buzz and Todd
and their flashy car.
But you know,
they want you to evangelize.
That's what the thing
about sharing is all about.
And I hate your stinking guts.
I can smell you
from a thousand miles away
and you smell like air.
Oh,
we just finished breakfast
that morning
and Phyllis went out
on the front porch
to see if they burned the paper.
When she noticed something
sticking up out of the ditch
over by Mr. Lopez's
hydrangea bush.
The neighborhood dogs
all started circling it
and making all kinds
of commotion.
So I figured I'd better
go have a look.
I noticed some blood on it
once I was about 15 feet away.
And I was afraid someone had done
run over one of the dogs.
I thought it was a local
propyopithecus
that are indigenous
to these parts.
But it turned out
it was just some fella
in a black uniform
with leather boots
and some sort of
funny looking arm band.
Dead Nazi by the side of the road.
He wasn't twitching or nothing.
So I figured I'd better try
and flip him over
with a tree branch
so I could see if he had
any personal identification on him.
Just in case the city road crew
wanted to notify his next of kin.
Dead Nazi by the side of the road.
Once I flipped him over
I noticed someone had done drilled
a two inch diameter hole
in his forehead.
Some of his brains were sticking out
like when you mash down too hard
on some toothpaste.
There were some bugs
that bit off a chunk of his face.
And his eyeballs were looking off
in different directions.
Like he wasn't sure where he was coming or going.
Dead Nazi by the side of the road.
And lie face down
where the grass got mowed.
Mrs. Cooper's Cocker Spaniel Rex
ran up and started
humping on that hole
with the brain sticking out of it.
Lord, I never seen that dog get so excited.
He was just panting.
And pumping his little behind
up and down so hard
I thought he was going to dislocate one of his hips.
But after two or three minutes
he lost control of his doggy bowels.
He lost control of his doggy bowels.
Music
Music Music Music Music Music Music Music Music.
Music Music Music Music Music Music.
Music Hofhofs Spiel encouraging music.
Well, when she finally got up
the brains was gone.
But there was a trail of Rex's seed
oozing up out of the hole
and Splattered across the deadfeller's mega-cat.
Philiss had called The City.
so they pulled up and scraped up what they could.
But a few days later, I noticed they'd missed a couple of fingers.
Again for Mr. Lopez, and he's been using them to keep squirrels out of his soffits.
Dead Nazi by the side of the road
Lied face down where the grass got mold
Dead as a rotting corpse at the bottom of the Atlantic Ocean.
The Rudy Schwartz Project did that song, Dead Nazi by the Side of the Road.
Good old Rudy and Waldo.
Before that X-Day conversation featuring guest Reverend Angry Larry,
we heard the instrumental Cheater Slicks by his band, The Slot Rods.
And now, the news.
From NPR News in Washington, I'm still a threat and still trying to get weapons, pointing a gun at the camera.
The government jumped by the fastest rate in four years and went up nearly 5% in one hour of work.
On Wall Street 1456.
NASA's watching the nation's most extensive Supreme Center.
It's watched closely because it's a key indicator of NPR News in Washington.
George W. Bush.
Moleskine molest.
Yatka vichyta. Yatchit vichyta. Chytatka vichyta.
Papagool.
He knows it's more than a haircut.
We're partying here.
Dave can't hear it, but we're all marching around like a big circus in Felliniland.
Now we're not. Now we're not.
Oh, the part, the parade went by.
It's the fight we heard in the distance.
Some of these interpretations of this music I have never heard before.
It's crazy.
Crazy stuff.
Can you hear?
I can hear.
Oh.
Thankfully.
I don't hear those.
Do they bother you when they're together?
They're, they're friends.
They're doing it too fast.
See, I did three of them so far and you don't even have me, my microphone on.
And you can't even hear it.
It's a lot of notes, too.
Dave knows this.
And Dave knows it, though.
He just sang it.
Yeah, it is a wonderful soundtrack for a wonderful movie.
It's one of the few movies I've watched every year.
Wait, I haven't watched it in three years.
Uh-oh.
We better pull out our eight-and-a-half subtitled DVD.
Are you building a rocket ship, and do you have, like, many different types of female affairs?
No.
Well, no, there was a short, there was a real brief time when I thought,
this movie is just like my life, only minus the money and Hollywood or Shinichita
or any of the beautiful zillions of affairs.
Well, he was only having one affair with that babe.
Who, Claudia Cardinale?
No.
No, I forget.
And our audience is too young to even know what the hell we're talking about.
There's like three people going, oh, yeah, eight-and-a-half.
Yeah, that was a weird day.
It's the polka dots, girl.
Yeah, these people are all dead by now, too.
They're 20 years dead.
Yeah, even the young people are already dead by now.
So I don't even know why the hell we're talking about this stuff.
By the time the show comes out, we'll be dead.
I'm not an in-think.
It is of historical interest, dear.
It is?
Yes.
Yes, somebody has discovered.
Historical interest.
One of these days, they'll discover it, and everything will be just peachy, creamy, yellow gizzard.
What happened to Dave?
Screaming yellow gizzard, huh?
Did you just shrink?
Did I shrink?
Oh, it's big again now.
There he is again.
Oh, I can't.
I don't know.
You were shrinking me and deflating me and inflating and coflating.
Well, you were talking like this, and then you got smaller and smaller and smaller.
I was like, you were like just a little atom-sized voice, and then suddenly you were back big again.
Well, don't you think that's important?
Don't you think that's earth-shattering that I can do that?
He's, well, Tickman, Ant-Man and Tickman.
You think I'm going to be able to mess around over here and smoke frop all day or something like that?
I wish.
Ant-Man and Tickman can do that, but they're just characters.
Wait a minute.
Dave's a character, too.
Yeah.
He can do all kinds of stuff.
He's on the radio.
Never forget you and your character, and make sure that plenty of people will never let you forget your character.
Yeah, Dave's a character.
He could have long hair or short hair.
He could be a giraffe or a person or a penguin.
He's a character.
He could be wearing cowboy boots or sandals.
Yeah.
He could be a...
Any way you want to look at things from the upside down.
Well, you're a lonesome cowboy, so you have to have the cowboy boots and the hat.
And you have to be lonesome.
And you've got to be singing the lonesome wail, moan the lonesome phone.
Yeah.
But otherwise, you could be any...
One of these days, you know, I'll get around to it, I'm sure.
Characters can fly.
Characters have super strength if they need to.
Characters.
Yeah.
Characters, sure.
But this...
Okay.
But Dave, look, it's getting late here.
The sun's going down.
What time is it?
It's 3957.
That's pretty long.
That gives me 20 minutes of music, which...
And what we just heard was, you know, that kind of thing.
Yeah, all that stuff.
I'll have to do that part later.
Okay.
Yeah.
But that means I still have time, daylight, to walk the dogs and mark a trail.
Because I'm Mark Trail, Bob-looking character.
Some people would say Bob looks like Mark Trail.
But Bob was born in the 20s.
And Mark Trail's just a drawn comic book guy.
You're a comic strip, newspaper strip character, right?
I'm not familiar with it.
Yeah, yeah.
It looks like Bob.
Look it up in your funk and waggon.
Yeah, Dave.
Okay.
Well, we're going to go now.
And we'll release you.
And you can go back and immerse yourself into the buzz.
Rejoin the buzz, Dave.
Go into the buzz.
No, wait.
Turn around.
Don't go into the buzz.
The monsters are in there.
It's hell.
No.
Whoa.
He did.
He hung up.
Well, friends, this is my excuse to say you've been listening to the Hour of Slack number
1,757.
Yay, we got another one done.
57.
All right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And if you want to know more about the Hour of Slack, Church of the Subgenius, J.R. Bob Dobbs,
or pretty much anything else, go to the Hour of Slack.com.
Anything that is not worth knowing.
Or it's opposite.
TrySubgenius.com.
Praise Bob.
And now that we're in the section that's not on broadcast radio, I can tell you that the
Slack Friday sale is going to be on the air.
The sale is still going on through Excessless Nesmus.
December 24th, conspiracy dating.
You can get two Subgenius ordainment kits for the price of one.
Although, albeit, the postage of two.
It's not the same price as buying one because of the postage.
But, friends, and you can get Lonesome Cowboy Dave's book, Neighbor World, directly from,
well, not from Dave, but from me.
Yeah.
Personally, I'll be the one who stuffs it into the book.
I'll be the one who does the envelope.
They go to Subgenius.com to order it, eh?
Subgenius.com.
Yeah.
And Dave, and also, if you look at the radio section of Subgenius.com, I'm not lying, all
of the Hours of Slack from number one through number 1757 are there.
Or will be there after I quit talking.
Available to delight your eardrums.
Yeah.
And also, you can...
There's a link.
There's a link to donate to Dave.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave, well, just between you, me, and the public listening to the internet,
Dave's pretty perpetually broke.
He used to work as a newspaper reporter, but the newspaper's all closed down.
And there is a GoFundMe.
And as much as I'd love to tell people to help me personally, Dave needs it more.
Yeah.
A lot more.
And so, be like Anonymous.
That great guy, Anonymous, who gave Dave 500 bucks last week when I told him, no, give
it to Dave.
Mm-mm-mm.
I really did.
I know.
He was going to give it to me, and I said, no, give it to Dave.
You're a wonderful person.
No, I'm not.
I just...
What?
No, you are a wonderful person.
I can't do what Dave does.
We need him.
I can't talk like that.
I know.
I can try, but it wouldn't be the same.
It'd be like trying to play like Jimi Hendrix.
Sure, for about three seconds, you can do it.
Okay.
Friends...
Oh, and what else?
Oh, Triology Soap.
Have you tried Triology Soap from TriologySoap.com?
That's T-R-I, not T-R-Y.
TriologySoap.com.
Our good friend, Lord Ferg, makes Triology Soap, including numerous flavors and scents
of Dobbshead.
Yes.
Soap shaped like a Dobbshead embedded in a square bar of translucent other soap.
It's not only good soap, it's high-quality glycerin soap.
It's delightfully wonderful to use.
Yeah.
TriologySoaps.com.
Subgenius.com.
Woof!
Soap shaped like a Dobbshead embedded in a square bar of translucent other soap.
Thank you.