Well, I think it's about time now.
We tipped her, we tipped her, we tipped her...
He's looking at his watch.
We dipped her with the prairie...
Dip the prairie squid, did you say?
I'm ready for some of that.
I'll dip a prairie squid.
Oh, it's that other tape. That's what it is.
Chocolate-covered prairie squid, did you say?
Yeah, yeah, and that's a recipe that we probably don't want to put in.
Man!
Did I just wreck your computer there?
Oh!
I just stepped on his guitar, folks. It's been a long day.
Let's try going to the phone.
What a clumsy ox. You're going to pay for that.
Every cent should be calculated and taken against your account.
I hope you're satisfied.
What do you have to say for yourself?
I hope you're...
Sense.
Well, with the surviving populace clinging tenaciously to useless routines
in hopes of retaining that one last tiny vestige of sanity,
you know, the least necessary and most superfluous aspects of society,
such as bureaucracy and red tape, will remain in place down to the final possible moment.
Mm-hmm.
And the deorgasm, popped-out, depleted mankind-ordnance of the de-unruptured subgeniuses
will be left to handle the machinery of state or snakehood.
Shane, look out!
The subgenius powerhouse.
What?!
I'm tired of that cosmic version.
I'm tired of that cosmic stuff.
I am, too.
I'm into the just down-to-earth bacon and eggs, meat and potatoes...
Rubbing sandpaper all over your nipples and your chest and your...
Good old time prairie squid-loving...
Coffee and lemon pie.
Or oil and oil.
Or oil.
Yeah.
I forgot.
You know, coke, peanuts and Coca-Cola of old days.
Goobers and chomping on your...
Chomping on yourself.
Yeah.
I'm sick of plastic cards.
I'm sick of pulling up behind gas stations and punching into, like, little concrete monoliths
and having pieces in Unix...
Yeah, me too.
Yeah, I'm sick of it.
I hate that stuff.
I hate that stuff, and I hate when people pull up behind you in some monstrous vehicle
that was never meant to be, fueled by beings which may or may not have existed based on
someone's own Freudian preclusion.
Or some Velikovsky nightmare.
When the whole time we could be space-traveling billionaires.
We could be eating fried chicken in the park.
Yeah.
We could be...
That burns me up, man.
What does?
What you just said.
All those dwarfs in the trucks and everything.
Yeah, all the dwarfs in the trucks and the times that...
Hey, you guys sound like idiots.
There's two of them.
It's getting hot in here again.
No!
Wait, wait, two little pulpy and I'm praying for some pain!
Dave, what is this hegemonic gaze about you?
It's that the sound is from the Yeti.
Oh, Mr. The wimpy laid-back universe sound.
. . .
Yes, that's the true Yeti sound.
. . . . . . . . . . what it's like to have an eroding.
What it's like having an eroding.
. . .
Put that thing down.
Yeah, it's not funny, man.
Put the gun down, Dave.
It's not.
It's not loaded, is it?
It's not a real gun.
It's one of...
Look.
See, it's a liquor made thing inside.
Just take a little chew off the top.
Just put it down, Dave.
No, no.
Just try it.
Just come over here and try a chew on it.
It's got lemonade inside of it.
Okay, look.
Awesome, baby.
Just give it a little try.
It's wax, man.
It's made of wax and you bite it and it's got lemonade inside of it.
Right, right, Dave.
That's right.
Yeah.
Do you want some wine?
Would you like some lemonade stuff?
Ma'am?
Just give me the keys to the truck.
Huh?
I've been driving so long, I...
What?
It's okay.
There, thanks.
Fits very good.
Now, Princess, we will escort you to your hive chamber.
Do I have to go in there?
For reprogramming.
I have to go in the hive thing?
Just put on these shackles.
But I can't remember all this stuff.
I go in there and I get...
Okay.
Be careful while I clamp them on.
Oh, my feet.
Do I have to wear these things?
I can't stand that sound.
What's with the guns back there?
Yep, his gun still works.
Too bad about his mind.
It was said that Don Carlos, when he discovered the Emerald Tablet,
had devised a plan where all the priests within the immediate vicinity
would come to make out its veracity to check,
to go through various biblical sources
and see if it indeed did indicate some sort of apocalypse
coming in the year 1998.
Eh...
Nostradamus said that from the sky would come the great king of...
Jacques Horay, or could it be perhaps pronounced Jokery?
Could we stretch it that far?
It was...
He predicted Hitler, though he spelled it Hister.
But yet he said in 1999, from the sky would come the great king.
Edgar Cayce said that 1998 would be that time.
Would be Jacques Couture's time to come back from...
Jacques Cousteau said that it would be 7 o'clock in the morning on July 5th.
Wearing pampers.
Out on a broad Jamaican sea, staring scullers.
People used to watch television.
People that make peanut butter, jelly sandwiches, and leave other people alone.
That's Jacques Cousteau right now.
I thought that was the meteor magnate.
Er, the meteor man.
Is that the weather man?
That's Peppy in the background. I'm home again. I'm dreaming.
I think it's Peppy. Listen.
Wake up, Dave! Wake up! Wake up, Dave!
I stepped on Peppy!
It'll be okay. It'll be okay.
It's just a dream, Dave.
I never had no dog named Peppy.
Your friends are still here. Me, the Tin Woodsman.
Tin Lizzy!
Yeah, and the Cowardly Lion.
Oh, the Cowardly!
Yes. It was only a dream. That horrible, boring world of trucks and sidewalks.
And sausages.
It was just a terrible dream.
And banel onions.
You've been here in Oz all along.
Oh, it's my... These flakes on my mouth. It's so dry. I've been here all along?
Yeah, you were just... You got knocked out.
Well, how the hell did I get knocked out?
When they dropped that house on your head.
Oh, I thought it was when I was arguing with that bitch. You know what I mean.
Yeah.
Thank God. I don't know what his problem was. You know, what the hell. She was giving me some stuff, so I might as well...
Oh, there! Here it goes again! Am I in there?
Yeah.
Boy, I think something's missing here now. This looks like a little teeny tiny room. Now, how the hell did I get in here?
We've been orbiting the whole time, Dave. You're still in a little tuna can in space, remember?
It's gonna be another nine months before we get on all the way over to Jupiter.
Yeah, but when do they hatch? Do we get to get out before they hatch, or we gotta wait?
Oh, you'll know when they're hatching.
I thought I'd be in some kind of hibernation chamber or something.
Well, but you... Most people wake up for the last few seconds of their life as the thing is bursting out.
Well, what the hell are we doing this for, then?
Well, you signed up.
Yeah.
You signed up. The contract is in the computer.
Well, I...
You thought the corporation was a great idea. You said we should all climb into the little capsule, and we'd get paid. By the time we got to Jupiter, we'd be paid a million bucks each, and sure enough, we will. It's just that it's our estate that gets it.
Yeah, but it's...
Because you didn't read the fine print.
Yeah.
Dave, and now we're all stuck here with you for another nine months.
Huh. I never...
Yeah.
I was never capable of reading a fine print. I just...
And you just keep having these dreams and going off into fantasy land, thinking you're back on Earth doing radio shows.
We have to keep nursing back.
And every time I have a dream, how come one of you guys changes? Like, I dreamed my wife was attacking me with a car, and next thing I know, out there I was out in the side room, and some Russian was talking to me, and a woman was attacking me with a car.
Somehow I think you guys were involved in this.
Yeah, and what are you keeping back there? What's in that big box anyway?
That's our space hyena.
Well, what's the...
Rover.
And it's...
And the...
The scorpion rooster creature that we picked up on Mars.
Well, how come we don't get to lick at them?
You can lick them.
You can lick them any time you want. Remember what happened last time you licked them, though?
What, the eye socket thing?
Yeah.
Well...
It wasn't easy getting that scorpion rooster barb out of your eye socket.
I thought you said that was another dream. Give me a mirror. I want to see if there's anything wrong with my eye socket, man. Let me look in the monitor.
You can't look at your own eye, Dave.
Yes, you can. If I look in the monitor, I can look at my own eye. I'm not listening to you right now.
What the hell? I have no eyes in there.
Why don't you calm down and take a stress pill, Dave?
I don't see what difference that's going to make.
Now, I'm looking in there and I'm not... Am I hallucinating or something? I have absolutely no eyeballs in my socket.
Now, this isn't what happened in the eye socket and before. Usually, it just like ripped out a chunk of the side of my face.
You can't see your own eyes, Dave. You can't run from your own legs.
Jayner told you that a long, long time ago.
Yeah, but you can't talk to your own voice. You can't smell your own nose.
Well, now, wait a minute. If they pull one...
You can't swallow your own throat.
If they pull one eye out, as just before the...
Just before the optic nerve severs, that one eye just for one second...
That's true.
...can look at the other eye. Is that not so?
That's true. If you pull it out, and we did this with Jayner, we pull it out just enough and turn it around.
You have to be very careful turning it. One eye can actually be seeing the other eye.
But that's not really the point. The point is, say, a one eye. You can't see your own eye with that eye that's seeing.
You can see your other eye.
But you can't see...
...that...your eye that is doing the seeing. You can only see the other eye.
You can look in the mirror, but that doesn't count either.
This is all mere metaphysical...
You can't digest your own stomach, Dave.
...juggling and juxtaposition.
And you can't hide from Bob, because he's stupider than you.
I can't believe that.
No, it's true. That's the miracle of it. That's the beautiful thing. That's why Bob hates you.
Well, I don't know...
I'll be whipped by Miracle Whip.
...and it's kind of dangerous to believe that, Bob.
I don't want to believe that.
I didn't want to...
Be careful with that. You could turn into a frog or something. You know, you never know by saying those kind of things.
You've got to keep it kind of...you know, I mean, you know you're entitled to your own opinion and all that.
See, he's talking about the convicts, too. See, he knows. He knows. I was talking about...
Well, when they hurled those convicts at Jupiter, I think that's the kind of thing that'll keep people...
Yeah, but it will turn into a frog.
It'll teach them a lesson.
When the plutonium lands there?
Well, it's more of a discouragement for Christ.
It's more of a...you know, if they see they're...you know, see, you kill somebody, you propel them into Jupiter.
Carrying the back...carrying plutonium on your back is...
I think it's a cool way to execute criminals.
I know, but don't you think it's cruel-wee to have people ejaculate into space with plutonium on their backs to ignite a third sun in our solar system just because they might have maybe murdered somebody?
Well, yeah, I think that O.J. guy, they ought to shoot him into Jupiter, because he's guilty.
I saw it on TV.
Yeah.
I saw B.Y. get drunk one time, then T.M. got drunk, too.
And then I saw Z.B. got so damn drunk, he shot his old woman, and then X.M. got drunk, too.
Papa Booey. Papa Booey.
Wow.
Where'd they come up with that?
We are in search of...the...f...post...at the...found of the falling tree.
And it's midnight, the witching hour, when some geniuses and lonesome daves come crawling out from under their moldering, rotting logs and their damp...stools.
Biting bugs and slapping each other with their long, sticky tongues.
All moist and sleepy.
Midnight.
When those who should not be on the streets are the streets.
It's red light, man! You idiot! You almost ran it!
Captain Anvil spit. Do you have a quarter? Do you have, like, a 50 cents or a dollar?
To wash a windshield?
Yeah, can I give you a dollar? Look at this, uh...
Hey, man, I'm like an alcoholic.
I'm really hurtin' for...like a quarter bear.
Can you give me a dollar?
I got it on the right, because it's about five and a half years ago, and that's why my arm's all bent up like this.
But if I had a quarter, see, then I could probably tell you...
Who's this balancing act?
All the best drunks are named Bob.
Bob could take a leak right there on the third rail.
Some guy went over there after Bob took a leak on the third rail and tried to put his tongue on it.
And, uh, it went right there, right...some Bobby, they called the guy, like a Bobby type, um...
You know, and he was...had all the claws on and everything, he stuck his mouth on it.
I'm gonna be just like Bob. I'm gonna stick his tongue in my mouth.
I'm gonna go commune with aliens.
Only just like Bob.
I'm gonna play on that third rail.
Huh?
I'm gonna go...I'm gonna go lay in front of the bus like I seen Bob do that one time.
Why can't I commune with aliens?
That department's like Bob.
They're figuring out just how we gave our secrets all away.
Yee-haw!
And Congress has appointed a committee, so they said, to find out who's American and who's a low down red.
Keep it going, Big Jim.
They called him up to Washington to speak for Uncle Sam.
But when they asked them what they are, they shit up like a clam.
I wish they'd take and put me on the witness stand today.
I'd shout so loud old Stalin could hear me all the way.
I'm no communist.
I'll tell you that right now.
I believe a man should own his own house in Warrentown.
I like in private ownership.
I won't be left alone.
Let the government run its business and let me run my own.
Yes, Bob Dobbs is no communist.
It'd sell you the shirt off your back.
The more they hired to work for it,
the more they have to pay.
I'm not talking about the leasemakers.
Be proud and honest here with me.
Instead of taking bribes and dressing up their wives in vain.
The taxes keep on going up, of that very little town.
But still they just can't take it in as fast as they dish it out.
Our national debt is monster-sized and going every day.
Our children's children still unborn are gonna have to pay.
Our dollar used to be the soundest money on this earth.
But now people will even buy one good dollar's worth
unless we stop inflation and take care of what's in the earth.
Yes, that's right.
Grinch, Grinch, Grinch.
At the sound of the falling tree.
Can you tell me a story before I go to bed?
Yes, I can, dear.
I'll tell you a story about the shrinking intellect.
It's about a whole town full of people whose brains got smaller at one time.
Well, it actually took about five years.
I don't know what started this.
I don't know where it began.
But it reached such a sorry state that people would walk up and down
from one edge of the town to the other, burbling inanities to each other
and sniveling off people they didn't quite dig.
And then, pretty soon, big hunks of their teeth fell out
because the decay had seeped down from their brain area all the way into their mouths.
And next thing you know, the time has come.
The tongues was a-wiggling, and they were in pain.
That's right. They were in some heavy, dark pain.
But the tongues kept a-wagging. The brain was dead.
The brain had actually atrophied into a piece of lumpage.
Say what?
Another prophetic vision brought to you by WCSB Cleveland.
You'll think it's weird.
Man, I'm glad I got that one on tight.
Now, I heard once that Bob was the queen of sailors.
That Bob actually was a hermaphroditic. Was hermaphroditic.
Oh, Bob has...
You know, they say that God has... is everything.
Yes.
Yeah, Bob has already been everything else.
Well, I think it's...
You know, when we invited you to come on Gay People's Alliance tonight,
we thought maybe we would talk a little bit about
how Bob was androgynous, and then is Bob his God?
Is that what you're trying to say?
Well, androgynous isn't really the word for it.
It's more like he's all man and all woman all the time, all together.
Well, that's a combo I'd like to be, or...
He's too much of everything.
Too much, too much.
It's never not enough.
Mo' Bob.
So, how long will you be in town, and what's with the groovy shirt?
I think that's just beautiful.
That's a beautiful shirt.
It looks like Curly Howard, isn't it?
Yes, it's a Curly Howard.
Andy Warhol, Curly Howard.
Oh, I loved Andy Warhol so much.
And yes, he did Curly just before.
Yes, the tragic woman.
The tragic woman with...
What was her name?
Edie Shrimpton or something.
I forget her...
Shrimp Pocket or...
But I remember...
She was wonderful.
I have a lot of her things.
Now, again, this Bob guy, you're going to be in the Newkirk Mall tomorrow night,
riding the ponies, and you'll be endorsing...
your Bob or whatever it is.
Oh, I'll be endorsing your Bob, Dave.
Well, we're on the air right now, so we'll talk about it later.
We're going to break away.
This is really making me uncomfortable trying to talk this way.
I don't know.
I just...
I mean, sometimes I can at a party.
If I'm dressed up, if I have the wig and the dress and everything, sure.
But I'm sitting here with the headphones, and it just...
I know.
It feels...
If I'm not wearing a pair of high heels and stockings, I just can't do it.
That's the way I feel.
You know, it's like...
No, no.
You got to be in the mood.
It's more than the mood.
You got to...
It's a certain feeling when you say wig.
Yes, I guess it's just that certain genre that fits sometimes, and sometimes it just
doesn't fit.
Yes.
Bill knows.
Bill's all dressed up.
He's...
Doing a hell of this?
He's looking good, Bill.
He's looking just like the Princess Wee-Ah-Dow from Queen of All the UFOs.
That's my best costume.
Do you also do Liza Minnellian and...
And what's the other one's name?
Did you do...
Yes, I have the Liza wig and the lashes, yes.
And the Connie Merkin.
Yes.
Oh, well, every woman should have a Merkin that makes her feel just like Connie.
Prescripture's 917.
That is in Prescripture's 917.
There's even a picture in this new subgenius book, Revelation X, of which I have the first
11...
Most of it all laid out here.
It looks like you have most of it imprinted on your forehead in a micro...
I have it...
Well, it's just behind my forehead here in the chapter four, Mondo Connie, the gossip
according to Connie Dobbs.
Look at this picture, folks.
Oh, I...
Let's just...
Let's get like Fiorilla LaGuardia.
Take it down.
Describe the three pictures you see on this page.
It looks like a tantric Shiva woman with a million tiny small arms looking at a bald-headed
Mohawk woman and struck by a hammer.
Am I wrong?
Well, but the bald-headed Mohawk woman, that's not a Mohawk.
That's the Merkin...
That's the Merkin.
...off of her head that makes her feel just like Connie.
And anyone can...
Can they snap a Merkin on, like perhaps like a teasy little toupee you'd wear out to the
mall or something on a Sunday?
Or is a Merkin something that's a weed?
If they can just bust free from their chains of inhibition, if they can throw away their
wallets and purses, slap that Merkin on top of their head and that underwear around their
brow, and just parade through the streets, just flaunt your abnormality.
That sounds like a point of carnage.
Take that hammer and nail that thing right in the head.
Right through that organ.
Nail it.
Nail that sucker.
Nail it to the table, man.
Just show the normals what for.
That's a point of carnation I think should be mentioned over and over again.
Nail your organs to the floor.
But what exactly is a Merkin?
It's not a weave.
It's not an implant.
It's not Rogaine or some sort of topical solution.
A Merkin is a sort of a wig.
It's a...
In the Middle Ages, women were often...
Similar to a codpiece.
...there were many skinned as well.
And the reason for that disease is of course we didn't have the miracles of modern medicine
that we have now.
And women sometimes became bald-headed just like men.
And sometimes they became bald-headed in like their armpits, shall we say.
And a Merkin might for instance be used as an armpit hair.
Because in those days...
Or perhaps any other part of the body where a hairy part might be needed, right?
You could slap a Merkin perhaps...
Like a forehead in your case.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
I could slap a Merkin in my forehead.
Or a palm.
Yes, it does.
But there's a paste.
Is the paste have anything to do with what happens afterwards?
This is not really just a cosmetic Merkin.
This is actually a medicinal, I guess...
Frank Sinatra has to wear one.
I have that confidential...
He's got the medicinal blue.
He's got the ice blue Merkin.
Yeah, you can't even tell when he's singing.
No, the ice blue Merkin is doing the song.
He's just...
He's dancing in step.
He's...
It's just the bag that's singing.
Well, it's just like with Bob.
It's the pipe that's talking.
It ain't Bob.
He...
You know, the pipe is...
Well, I shouldn't say that.
Bob is talking, but the pipe is directing what Bob says.
It's the amplifier.
I mean, it's good.
It's...
Bob's not doing...
It's not like the pipe is some evil entity that controls Bob.
It's that it amplifies Bob's already powerful slack force.
Is there anything like that?
Well, I'm not sure if Bob's...
If Bob's left of the original J.R.
Bob's...
Bob's left, if indeed the pipe is actually doing the magnificence, the utterances which
come out of his foul trap are enough to make you...
Well, the autopsy showed that the brain matter was still present but was interlaced with
tendrils of an unknown...
And the pipe...
They couldn't get the pipe out of his mouth.
Bob had...
By the way, the autopsy, Dave, showed that Bob only had...
one beer. How many did you
have, man? I didn't have... Just think about
that. Jeez.
Was he killed by one beer?
Or was...
Or was it the beer that was
talking? I have what?
Some people have moles.
But I don't care to discourage
about it. And I don't want to be...
I lost one. Moles are
beauty marks anyway. Yes.
He said with a wan smile.
I thought they were like
ferrets. The magic-esque
creature that crawls from holes.
The magic mongoose. Yeah, the
merkin was a mighty ferret.
No. In the Middle Ages,
during the bubonic plague, didn't they put
a place of ferret on their forehead to ensure
some sort of magnetic surprise?
Yeah, but the funny thing was that
the plague was actually carried by
fleas, which were carried by
the ferrets. So
those foolish
medieval people and their silly,
superstitious medical treatment
ments. I'm sure that
our current modern medicine
will always seem incredibly
advanced in future ages.
They call it moleskin.
That's kind of a condom,
isn't it? Did I get it?
What? She said something about
moleskin. I still like to be bled.
I like... Well, we're
all going to be ruptured, I hope.
Maybe that'll be some sort of topical
disenfunded... Who else but Bob can
you trust during the rupture,
my friend?
True words were never spoke.
Who will give you that feeling of support,
I suppose? Besides Bob.
Who can hold
your guts in
when they're
screaming to get out?
Out. Out.
Yeah, it's been a long
night of guts screaming to get out.
As a matter of fact, my thorax
tried to pop out through the top of the
tube, and it's not allowed to go
above that little green line there. See?
Your thorax fell
into my abdomen.
Wasn't that a joyful collusion
there? Your abdomen fell into my
thorax.
Say...
Say, my cranium
was severed by a gigantic
septum of some
sort.
My septum was deviant,
and therefore it could not
parlance. It did not learn
the correct and the crude.
It caroused.
It had its day in the sun,
and then went to sleep under a distant
moon.
Wow.
I knew a guy whose
bad septum, his septum
developed a hole in it.
This one guy I know.
And he had to have his
septum replaced with a plastic
plug, but he kept
the piece of meat that had been removed
from between his nostrils
and hired
a well-known underground
painter,
a famous guy, to paint
his septum for it.
Paid 500 bucks for a painting of his
diseased septum.
And then never picked up the painting.
That was the best part
of the story. It was the concept, man.
So somewhere
in San Francisco,
there's this
black velvet painting
of a septum, of a
guy's septum, and it's
it wields a sinister
influence, the painting does. You gaze
into it, it's like looking at a picture of Bob.
You just get lost in it.
It's so tiny. A septum is a very
tiny painting to be on.
And also, what would it hold?
Like, perhaps Elvis smoothing a velvet tiger?
Yeah, he had
on the tiny septum, the septum was
only about an eighth the size
of your little fingernail.
Oh, Jesus, less than the Michael A.
He had painted this tiny
microscopic picture of
Elvis, as if on black velvet.
Oh, then it was Elvis.
A picture of Elvis doing a sword fight with a bull.
Well, I like to see
Elvis bullfighting pictures.
I had quite a few of them.
I had crying clowns. I had the
tigers. Did you have the dogs around
the bar? Oh, hell yeah.
The dogs playing poker.
Yeah.
You know, that scene will come true in real life
after
1998 when the
excess technology is left on our
benighted planet.
People will turn themselves into
creatures that look like that.
And that corny old painting
will turn out to be a perfectly
ordinary common sight
in downtown bars.
It's one way to go wandering in
Dallas and just maybe clip the turn
around into the old, in Chafee's Bar
or someplace like that. There'll be people walking around
askew with, askew with like dog masks
or just literally full of hair.
Their face would be, have been, have been
genetically morphed
so that they were in fact dog
faced old men sitting
around smoking cigars and playing
poker. And they'll be, you'll be able
to, there'll be millions of people
walking around. Every city will have
dozens of people who look like Kennedy
for instance or
Martin Luther King. You know, you can look like anybody.
Think how many
Elvis's and
Michael Jackson's there'll be.
Or some cousin of yours in the Air Force that you never
really knew. Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, I think that's what it was.
It was, his head, his mouth was slightly different than it really was.
You could be, you can be anything that time around.
I think I'd like to look like a kind of a doggish JFK
with a little bit of that Bob smile to it.
Well, now think about it though, Dave.
This ain't like getting a tattoo.
You mean? It only goes one way.
You're stuck. But think of the things that teenagers will do to themselves.
The things they do now, think what they'll be able to do when they can like grow giant bat balls.
Devil wings or what they can all look like, you know, have pumped up Rambo muscles.
Yeah. Or can wear clothes that look like barbecue aprons.
They'll look like the Mitchell and Tyre man.
Yeah. Or actually barbecue grills.
There'll be, there'll be teenagers, teenage girls who look just like Snoopy.
Peanuts.
Jeez, what a rush that would be. And you'd go to jail for that, wouldn't you?
There'll be Garfields walking around on the street.
And there'll be these hideous visages every now and then.
There'll be people who look like Bob.
They thought it would be real cute to be permanently changed,
have their facial faces surgically altered,
to have that sardonicus-like grin,
that hideous rictus grin that would,
and the pipe implanted in their teeth and everything,
their eyes given just that insane glint, you know.
It's, yeah, I don't know.
I mean, ain't no kind of world for an old man no more.
Well, after this espousal,
I can only wonder what kind of surgery you must have gone under
to get the pipe-like grin and also some of the weird brain fusions.
Oh, they tell me I was born...
I'm not a joker, man. I'm an ace. I want you to understand that.
I can't understand the difference between the cards yet.
I know I'm trying, but...
I'm not a joker, man.
I'm not an ace neither.
It's more like a quagmire I'm lost in.
It's just a splattering of 52 different numbers in a deck,
and I can't figure out which one to go with.
I thought I'd like to be a ten of clubs,
but it turned out I was a ten of club foots.
Yeah, that'll get you out of Vietnam.
That got me out of Vietnam.
Why did you want to go there?
Panty waste.
Uh...
The post says WCSB,
and I'm about to tell you what I want to hear.
Hey, this is getting more realistic and lifelike.
There's, like, retarded people calling me up,
and talking in my head.
I doubt if we'll ever be able to resurrect these sea monkeys.
Jeez.
Look at this one.
It's sprouting a whole new head.
I wonder if I mix this solution back in again.
Maybe some of them...
I could make it take a spore from one of them,
and reclone the spore.
Eh, I'll just go take a nap
and write a little report to the committee.
I'm telling you...
Bob?
I haven't heard the voice of Bob.
There's just something in the background there.
I can't make that voice out.
Well, the only thing for me to do on this shift is...
I'm going to go to the bathroom.
Well, I gotta remember to call the bathroom.
And I gotta...
Well, remember to eat...
Eat that stuff they call food.
I can work out again.
Eh...
Hell with that.
I'll go read some more technical manuals.
Take on some more stuff on the monitor.
Hell with that.
I'll try on this Mr. Peanut suit.
Yeah, this thing's been laying around for weeks,
and I haven't had any fun with that.
He's hallucinating the peanut suit again.
You'll have to make note of that.
Tell the psychiatrist.
Mr. Peanut used to come to all the fairs,
and he'd pass out donuts and give favors to the kids,
and bags of peanuts, of course.
I love that monocled eye.
You know what's funny?
All of those volunteer, quote, astronauts, unquote,
start imagining the peanut suit.
Something about Mr. Peanut...
Do you suppose the Russians had something to do with that?
Could they have breached security
and implanted the Mr. Peanut fantasy?
Hello, boys and girls.
Look, he thinks he's Mr. Peanut.
Here's a bag of bag of peanuts.
I'm Mr. Peanut.
And if it's not Mr. Peanut, it's Reddy Kilowatt.
Dad, we enjoyed the opening of the 7-Eleven.
Remember, it's a child-famed corporation.
It's...
You're not allowed to steal the peanuts.
Condominium.
It's sad, in a way.
Oh, boy.
I'm taller than all the other Mr. Peanut men.
This is a very, very big, important convention of Mr. Peanut men.
I think I'm standing...
Do you suppose his suit is over-medicating him?
I wonder...
I wonder if I stood up even taller if I would stand up much more from the rest.
But why...
Why old advertising figures?
I mean, Mr. Peanut's not even used anymore in marketing, I don't think.
It's something from his past.
They're comforting things.
Oh, Mr. Potato Head.
One of the, uh...
The people on the way to Proxima Regulus were all turned into Mr. Potato Head.
Around the six-month mark, just like him.
We'll have to remember that.
Yes.
We'll make a note of it.
We'll have to tell the psychology department.
Oh, now I'm blonde, Mr. Potato Head.
And now I've got red hair.
We ought to tell the cruelty department, too.
They can start implanting evil Mr. Potato Head.
At an evil Mr. Peanut.
No wonder they gave me a shriveled-up Mr. Potato Head.
Because now I can scare the little children.
I like this mask you're using.
Oh!
What the hell was that?
There's no welts on the back of my potato.
This must be some sort of, like, Stanislaus Lem movie or something.
Anything you think of.
Welts?
Mr. Tuber costume.
It's the big sweet potato head.
Oh, I love this one the best.
It's carved out in the middle.
Huh.
Do you suppose...
Do you suppose he has any inkling that all of his silly antics are being broadcast to
all the people on Earth?
Oh, I don't think so.
On the crazy astronaut channel?
He's fully lost.
Hey, if somebody was watching...
One of these days he's going to switch through those channels and he's going to come upon
the channel with him on it.
Oh, man.
I might as well look at the box for a while.
This is getting boring.
Might as well look at the box for a while.
It's me!
This is getting boring.
Hey, it's me!
It's getting boring.
It's me!
It's my face is up there.
Hey, my face is up there.
You!
My face is up there.
I can feel my little mouth.
It's not real.
Dave, your gyros need stabilizing.
Dave, check your computer.
Wait, who?
Your gyro...
Your...
Your spinning!
You're in a spin, Dave!
Whose voice is this?
Stabilize the gyros!
Is this a real voice or is it just a real voice?
Turn up the oxygen switch!
Oh, I'm getting lightheaded in here.
Reach for the oxygen switch, Dave!
I think I'll turn on the oxygen switch.
Oh.
There, he did it.
At least he thought it was the oxygen switch.
What's wrong with the switch?
I'm just grabbing.
I'm gonna get my brain stuff going on.
Good, he needed a good washing.
They always panic when the suit fills up with the cleansing fluid.
Right up to their nostrils.
It's like he doesn't...
Church air switch.
My hands are clean.
My face is clean.
Hello? Hello, Dave.
Feeling better now, Dave?
What?
Everything I say itches.
No, no, no. We're not doing that, it says.
It's just...
It's just us, Dave.
The voices in your head.
We didn't want you to be alone.
I bet I could write a whole symphony on this hollow potato.
That would be something to do for five years.
You'd sit around going mad.
It's that alternative.
There's been great symphonies written about hollow potatoes, Dave.
Why don't you try it?
It'll keep you busy for a month or so.
Yeah, why don't I try it?
I could, like, make thousands and thousands of little holes.
Like some sort of chromatic key.
I could just get a little...
Dave, the cat's loose in the spaceship.
So let me check the monitor for...
Shit! The cat's loose!
Damn cat!
It's crawling all over all of...
You better catch that cat, Dave.
It's walking across the control panel.
You're going into a spin again.
You're destabilizing.
Oh my god. I'm gonna destabilize.
This thing's gonna start flipping.
If I don't get down there right away...
Shh!
Ginger!
Ah!
Oh good, look!
Princess Wee the cat's mutated.
Just as we were hoping.
What the hell are you...
He let it wander into the cargo hold where it was exposed.
What is that?
Ginger?
Is that you?
Sheesh!
What the hell's
a slime all over your neck?
What you getting into?
Just let me get a little closer, kid.
What's wrong?
Try to make friends with it, Dave.
I'll try and make friends with it.
Try to make friends with Ginger.
Yeah.
Ginger's always a nice little kitty.
It's just sick or something.
I'll make friends.
I'll pet it and take it back out of here.
Ginger?
Ah!
Now settle down, Dave.
Try to communicate with it.
It's a new form of life.
No one's ever seen a cat spider before.
It could teach us things.
Oh my god!
Think what it could mean to science.
Go on in there, Dave.
Can I get rid of it?
Go on back into that cargo hold
with that giant mutated cat spider.
If I could just talk to her, maybe.
It's gotta be intelligent if it's mutated this far.
It maybe has something to tell me.
A little kitty?
Or whatever the hell you are now.
A little cat?
What the hell's up?
What's up?
Oh, it just needs to be comforted, Dave.
Your music soothes the savage beast.
Why don't you put on some music?
Ginger, I was gonna play a little song for you.
Maybe you should put out some milk for it.
A little try of milk.
Um...
I was wondering...
Be careful now.
Don't let it get hurt.
A bird can burn a hole directly through the spaceship hole.
It would create a terrible vacuum
and suck you out into space like
toothpaste out of a tube.
It looks like you're going for it, man.
What do you mean, cause?
And whatever you do,
don't let any harm come to Ginger.
The War Department is very interested
in your little tabby.
I am in big deal with this right now.
I don't know how to talk to her.
What's coming up over there, brother?
It's a big, big, blue spider.
And we'll be back to the lonesome cowboy Dave
flipping out in outer space channel
after these words from
our controller.
Cue up the...
Cue up the controller tape!
From PR News in Washington, I'm undergoing treatment for alcohol.
From PR News in Washington, I'm undergoing treatment for alcoholism.
On Wall Street, 1686523.
PR's Ed.
Dangerous, malicious, and reckless.
PR's Ben.
This is PR News.
House Speaker Dennis Hastert used banned
performance-enhancing drugs.
Two Americans are winners of this year's Nobel Prize
in PR News in Washington.
Dealing with overpopulation
involves more than birth control.
I say kill them all,
let God sort them out.
I say send them
back to Lexington.
I'm into the
voluntary human extinction movement.
I say let them eat green cheese.
Let them eat green cheese
and let the cat sort them out.
Let the mutated
spider cat.
I say exterminate all
of these funk monsters.
Everything's future dogs.
It's the end of them.
Stop the whole genetic purge.
Is there any coffee on this spaceship?
Is there any
vitamin in this
little tiny
little box?
Now come on Dave,
I know you got some of that whiskey stashed
somewhere,
backed with the bio-samples
from Mars.
Bio-samples?
The samples are stuck in my home?
We're coming up to the magic hour.
I know this will help.
I'll do what you can.
You know, I'm just
a little drunk.
We can't understand a word you're saying, Dave.
I'm a sour pussy, that's for sure.
What?
He's lost
in space, friends.
Sad.
But,
it's part of the risks these astronauts
take.
Thank God cremorah don't make you sleepy
like some of the other ones do.
Well, at one o'clock your suit will put you
to sleep.
I'm waiting. I'm waiting.
I'm waiting for my suit to put me to sleep.
Over the last five
and a half hours,
my suit has enthralled me.
My suit has put me to sleep
and waked me up again.
My suit fed me.
My suit evacuated my bowels.
My suit lulled me into
a false sense of security.
It's a comforting suit.
My suit talked to me.
My suit made me feel very insecure.
My suit,
my suit expanded and contracted
a few times. I didn't understand what that
was about.
It was punishing you, Dave.
The suit punishes.
The suit punishes and the suit rewards.
The suit rewards you, Dave.
My world
is in this suit.
This is my entire world.
The suit is your friend.
It's a nurturing cocoon.
Oh, look at the cut of the suit.
This is the kind of seasoning
that would make any, any young man
in America jealous as hell.
I'm a true hero.
Wearing this suit made me a hero.
I'm proud of it. I'm glad I signed up now.
I think my suit's
filling me with pride.
I'm afraid that's not pride, Dave.
You shouldn't have eaten those
freeze-dried beans this morning.
They just had a little fuzz on them.
I didn't see nothing wrong
with those beans.
The suit may be filling up with a lot more
than mere pride.
Oh, there you go. He's using the zero gravity toilet again.
Oh, boy.
This is kind of a...
Whoopee!
Oh, no. He left the flap open.
Look. The stuff is floating around
inside the cabin now.
It's coating the windows.
Oh, on the window.
Way to go, Dave. Smooth move.
Ha, ha, ha.
Oh, no.
Well, now the emergency
lights have gone off.
Little robots have to come out and clean up
after you again, Dave.
Hello?
The suit's going to have to...
The suit's going to have to punish you again, Dave.
Hello? I need a clean up
on the front window.
Oh, shh.
The thing's going to be stuck there for weeks now.
Of course,
in this vacuous atmosphere, it won't smell much,
I don't suppose. Now, just don't take
your helmet off.
I wonder what would happen
if I took my helmet off.
I never tried it.
No, don't do that, Dave.
Wait a minute. Maybe something might...
This is not a pressurized cabin.
Might not be such a good idea
after all.
Fiddle around with these...
Oh, look. He's trying to light
a cigarette again.
He can't get it up to his lips through that helmet.
Damn.
This must be the five thousandth time
he's done that.
Sixteen cartons of luggage,
and I can't smoke a damn cigarette.
It was a brilliant move on the part of the psychology department
to put that no smoking sign
blinking in there,
and those twenty cartons of cigarettes
that...
keeps up the sort of tension
that keeps the astronauts...
Oddly enough, it keeps them
mentally healthy.
You know, it's so alone out here,
the only friend I've got's my own guitar.
Lucille,
you've been with me through thick and thin.
Can't smoke,
can't really eat a good meal,
but I can still sing a song.
I think I'll sing a song
about my intergalactic exploits.
Scott can't even hardly touch
these fragile, these big mitts on.
Years have gone,
and years have gone,
but still I'm a flying bug.
Someday I'll get there,
and maybe I won't,
and I'll never know
the reason why.
Shh, it's the worst one yet so far.
Can't you keep on working it, huh?
I'll have my opera all figured out
by the time I get there.
And then, I'll make it back to Earth.
It's more herodom and fame and fortune
for me. Just chop that up
and...
You'll be the biggest folk music star
on Alpha Centauri, Dave.
Oh, God, I could see it right now.
I could be like the
Woody Guthrie of Alpha Centauri.
You'll be the only musician
in the whole star system, Dave.
Of course, yeah.
I'll be the only musician in the whole star system.
You'll be the only music fan
in the whole star system.
Yeah, and my head will be shaped like a gigantic fan,
like one of those
Komodo dragons, or what do they call them?
Monitor lizards, when they get mad.
Good, we've got him
doing stream of consciousness again.
That should keep him amused
for a few more days.
I wonder if they got
a reefer on Alpha Centauri.
hot like Earth-type babes
on Alpha Centauri.
The suit is your girlfriend, Dave.
It's clamping down.
It's constricting.
It's tightening up.
It's form-fitting, isn't it?
I didn't know a suit could do this.
What the heck is going on?
All right, that's enough.
Turn off that phone.
This is the function of the suit.
Now let's make him exercise.
Put the suit in exercise mode.
There we go.
He's flopping.
My knee joint's going out again.
What the hell is this music in this case?
Good aerobatized music.
We must keep our astronauts
in good shape.
I hate these resistance calisthenics.
And jumping jacks
at this time of the morning.
It'll be five years of this
if he's lucky.
I mean, I can't do this for five years.
I can't do this for another minute longer.
If he doesn't happen to hit one of the planets,
if there are any in the Alpha Centauri system,
then he'll just have to go on to the next star system
20 years past that.
But you'll probably hit a planet,
some sort of a planet, or a moon,
or an asteroid, or something,
some body of rock floating around in space.
Think of the romantic cartoon man on a desert island
with nothing but one palm tree and a shark swimming around.
That romantic fantasy will be yours.
Only high-tech style, Dave.
I'm a high-tech style romantic hero figure
abandoned on a distant moon,
cast into space like some piece of effluvia
on the sea.
Someday I'll be home.
Someday I'll touch the shore,
a distant shore somewhere.
It ain't much longer of a wait.
I'll get there someday.
If you get bored, Dave,
you can always just put a note in a bottle
and send it out into the radio waves
like you've just done
for the last time.
It's just two hours.
This has been ESO Radio
on WCSB Cleveland
with my guests Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
the Reverend Ivan Stang,
and the Princess We Are Doe.
My name is Chaz,
and I'll see you all next week.
Yay for Chaz.
He's the mix master.
Yes, friends, thanks to Dave and Chaz
and we and the callers and WCSB Cleveland
for that strange and wonderful broadcast.
Nice recording there.
For more information, of course,
it's subgenius.com
and we really do intend to do our X-Day celebration
up until the saucers get here at 7 a.m. July 5th
online, I guess.
I mean, I'm not sure what we're going to do.
It should be interesting.
To tell the truth, I imagine what the X-Day Zoom meetings
will probably be all day and all night practically
for that week.
It'll be about like the real X-Day
in which the best part is standing around in the road talking
or sometimes sitting around a campfire talking.
But mostly it ends up being standing in the road.
At least for me.
That's my favorite part of all those festivals.
The music is fun and the jibber-jabber from loudmouths
on stage is fun, but really the best part is just the talking
to the other subgeniuses.
It's interesting.
And now this.