The revolution begins immediately!
And welcome, dear friends, to the Hour of Slack!
Praise Bob!
For the next hour, sit quietly and we will control all that you see and hear.
Wake up, puppet boy!
We are conscious of our responsibility and obligation to provide programs which will be enjoyable, entertaining, and tasteful.
There is absolutely no other possibility.
The Hour of Slack
Hey, this is a motel.
I'm a cop, you idiot! I'm Detective John Kimball.
Well, if you're a cop, you idiot, come over here and talk to me, okay?
You son of a bitch!
And I don't know what he does. This is a switchboard at the Gator Lodge.
Stop it!
I don't stop nothing, you idiot!
Hi.
You son of a bitch!
How are you?
I'm alright. Who do you want to speak with?
I'm Detective John Kimball.
Charles Kimball?
Yes.
This is Cotton's Barbecue.
Ice for Charles Kimball?
Yeah.
Ice for somebody named Charles Kimball.
Charles Kimball.
Um, sir, could you describe Charles Kimball?
Yes.
Could you tell me how Mr. Kimball looks?
I'm Detective John Kimball.
Detective?
Oh, he's a Detective John Kimball.
Hey, I'm a police officer.
Oh.
I'm a cop, you idiot!
I'm Detective John Kimball.
Um, excuse me, um, sir, but this is Cotton's Barbecue.
This is not a police station.
Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob! Bob!
Well, now, you keep talking about this Bob, and I've seen pictures of him, certainly a lot of drawings of him, and yet I've never heard, you sent me several of the books and the tapes and stuff over the years.
I've never actually heard Bob's voice. I've never seen a photograph of him, as I know.
Well, Bob...
I've seen plenty of photographs of him. You pick up any old, uh, Better Homes and Gardens, Popular Science, from the 50s and early 60s, uh, Bob modeled for ads.
He's that guy with the pipe, the, the grinning, sort of a Ward Cleaver-ish, Dick Van Dyke-looking fellow with this sort of slightly crazed grin, and he's, and he's got a pipe.
You may have seen pictures of him spray-painted on bridge abutments and, and, uh, uh, dumpsters and so forth.
And tattooed on, uh, foreheads and hands, and branded on backs, and in, uh, brain pants.
Ah, yes, we have a theme show tonight.
Sex and War are our themes, the scariest things of all in the primate world!
Ah!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
This goes out to all the women and men,
from New York to London,
from L.A. to Tokyo,
struggling to keep their self respect in this climate of misogyny,
money worship,
and mass production of period.
hip-hop's illegitimate child hip-hop this especially goes out to gil scott heron friend
living legend and proto-rapper who wrote the revolution will not be televised much respect
your revolution will not happen between these thighs your revolution will not happen between
these thighs your revolution will not happen between these guys
the real revolution ain't about booty size the versace's you buys or the lexus you drives
and though we've lost biggie smalls your notorious baby your notorious revolution
will never allow you to lace no lyrical dush in my bush your revolution will not be you killing
me softly with fujis your revolution ain't gonna knock me up without no ring and produce little
future mcs
because that revolution will not happen between these thighs your revolution will not find me in
the backseat of a jeep with ll hard as hell you know doing it and doing it and doing it well you
know and doing it and doing it and doing it your revolution will not be you smacking it up flipping
it or rubbing it down nor will it take you downtown or humping around because that revolution
will not happen between these thighs your revolution will not have me singing
And ain't no nigga like the one I got
Your revolution will not be you sending me
For no drip drip VD shot
Your revolution will not involve me
Filling your nature rise
Or helping you fantasize
Because that revolution will not happen
Between these thighs
No no not between these thighs
And oh my Jamaican brother
Your revolution will not make you feel
Bombastic and really fantastic
And have you groping in the dark
For that rubber wrapped in plastic
You will not be touching your lips
To my triple dip of French vanilla
Butter pecan chocolate deluxe
Or having Aganelli's dream
A six foot blowjob machine
You wanna subjugate your queen
Think I'ma put it in my mouth
Just cause you made a few bucks
Please brother please
Your revolution will not be me
Tossing my weave and making believe
I'm some caviar eating ghetto mafia clown
Or me giving up my life
I'm behind just so I can get signed
And maybe have somebody else write my rhymes
I'm Sarah Jones not Foxy Brown
You know I'm Sarah Jones
And your revolution makes me wonder
Where could we go
If we could drop the empty pursuit of props and the ego
We'd revolt back to our roots
Use a little common sense
On a quest to make love de la soul
No pretense
But your revolution will not be you
Flexing your little sex
And status
To express what you feel
Your revolution will not happen between these thighs
Will not happen between these thighs
Will not be you shaking and me
Faking between these thighs
Because the real revolution
That's right
I said the real revolution
You know I'm talking about the revolution
When it comes
It's gonna be real
When it finally comes
That's right
It's gonna be real
Yeah yeah
I guess that's what it's like
Ah that was Sarah
Jones, Sarah Jones with DJ Vadim, posted to alt.binaries.slack by Sister Deck.
Sexy.
But to counterbalance that with an ode to subgenius-style bonobo yeti sex,
who better than unsaved superstar James Kochalka?
You've got to talk to the wookie, talk to the walking, talk to the wookie.
Talk to her.
The wookie is hairy, ugly, and scary, but she is a nice girl.
The wookie is hairy, ugly, and scary, but she will rock your world.
You've got to talk to the wookie, talk to the wookie.
Talk to the wookie, just talk to her.
Talk to the Wookie.
She'll never forget you.
You'll never forget her fine.
You gotta talk to the Wookie.
Talk to the Wookie.
Just talk to her.
You gotta talk to the Wookie.
Talk to the Wookiee, talk to the Wookiee, talk to her.
The Wookiee is hairy, ugly, and scary, but she is a nice girl.
The Wookiee is hairy, ugly, and scary, but she will rock your world.
You got to talk to the Wookiee, talk to the Wookiee, talk to the Wookiee, just talk to her.
Let me give you a hand with that.
Oh, boy. That tickles.
Oh, yeah, right there.
Oh, I say, do that again.
Friends, remember Women of Sodom?
Well, the Countess, formerly of that group, has this concept band,
and a new CD with this hate-filled parody rock opera called Shooting Star,
which is great, and I've got bits of it to play here.
So let's, with the Countess and Shooting Star,
let us go behind the glamorous superstar scenes.
16.01.
You expressly acknowledge that your and the artist's services hereunder
are of a special, unique, intellectual, and extraordinary character,
which gives them peculiar value,
and that in the event of a breach by you or the artist of any term hereof,
company will be caused irreparable injury,
which cannot adequately be compensated by money damages.
Accordingly, company shall be entitled to injunctive relief,
in addition to any other rights or remedies which company may have.
Company shall be made happy.
To enforce the terms of this agreement.
Proceeding sentence shall not be construed.
We will clean the artists from opposing any application from such relief
based upon contest and other facts alleged by company in support of such application.
Please place your order.
We are stretched.
Dr.
Professor Letsits say who you are.
Too much fame without shame.
Everybody knows you're missing.
atom 175 mitts,
atom 17 ml.
Thank you.
Thank you all for sitting here tonight.
And people who blew their minds.
What is wrong with this picture?
That is crime.
And crime must be dealt with forcefully.
Law and order have broken down.
The CDs are burning.
Burn, baby, burn.
Get down and kick out the jams, all the jams.
Remember, once the volume control is set, do not readjust.
It is important that the sound level remain the same
and that the sound level remain the same.
All of the people listening should be seated approximately six to eight feet from the speaker.
If the music you hear sounds a little peculiar, do not readjust.
It is important that the sound level remain the same.
With this record, I have provided you with a weapon that will destroy the monster.
For the love of God.
Get a copy of it into every American home.
Service.
Noise.
Is the main weapon of our attack.
Get down and kick out the jams, all the jams.
Get down and get down and get down and kick out the jams.
Rock music just airs us and excites us.
And may I say right at this point,
the same beat produces the same evil inclinations.
Even if we tie the word, kick out the jams to it.
And I can teach it to you.
.
You really just gotta live on me.
Like a plague, it spreads.
It's an obvious documentation.
It's what the newscasts do every night.
It's called a soundbite.
I mean, it's letting people know what happened.
Surface noise.
This powerful process of duplication
can be used to duplicate literally anything
so that you can use those strategies
to create what you want.
Repping off the old masters,
but all in a good cause.
Horror Fu
Exactly!
Exactly, they're ripping off the fucking people.
And we have a right to fucking appropriate.
That is fucking bullshit.
You are nothing but a fucking,
wholesome, fucking kleptomania,
fucking moron.
Fuck!
Uh, Surface Noise, friends.
That amazing collage was Surface Noise
from their CD, Copycat Suicide.
Surface Noise is,
here's their information.
That's our old friend, Reverend Urania235,
and you can email him
at urania235
at media1.net
That's M-E-D-I-A-O-N-E dot net.
Urania, U-R-A-N-I-A-2-3-5
at media1.net
And the Countess, Shooting Star,
friends, just amazing.
The Countess is Cynthia von Buehler
of Boston,
and there's an order form
for the Shooting Star thing
at, got that pencil ready,
drawbridge.com
slash countess
or
www.triagemusic.com
But you should look at
drawbridge.com
slash countess.
And now,
a break from the theme, friends,
with a little bit of educational material
from Dr. Howell
of the,
the KPFA
Berkeley subgenius show.
Let us consider the affliction of tarantism,
that mysterious dance
thought to originate in the bite
of a venomous spider.
Legend, if not history,
identifies this spider
as the European tarantula,
Lycosa tarantula.
It was said that after having been bitten,
the only thing the victim could do
would be dance around it.
And soon these dances,
these spider dances,
or the tarantella,
as they were called,
became all the fashion,
and the church had to denounce them
for the lascivious sexual excesses
and groovy raves
that they were having,
flinging their bodies around
in empty mantles,
you know,
to alleviate the spider
tingling.
But,
the fact is the European tarantula
does not cause these symptoms.
However,
people who are stung by scorpions
in the southwest
often are unable to keep still.
They have to fling their bodies
back and forth.
Is this not similar to the
tarantism?
Yes, it is.
And in fact,
the difficulty was
the identification of the wrong spider.
The phone only takes messages
which cannot be answered.
Please leave a message.
Thank you.
All of northern central California
can now leave a message
by calling 848-4425
and the 510 area code.
Get on the radio with us
and we hope that we'll be
hearing from you soon
because we want you
to call us on the radio.
So you can
read.
Man.
Yeah.
We're walking around.
Hey, you know,
we're really pretty gnarly dudes
but we're
trucking around
the man
reporting on the sites
drinking lemonade
out of a big plastic jar
and eating leaky
fruit gel cups.
And now,
let us speak of a certain spider
which once spun a web
in a garden in Provence
in 1870.
You don't do that.
This one is a matron.
She dates back to the year before
1869.
Her majestic corpulence,
so exceptional at the season of July,
proclaims the fact.
We know her as the angular epiphyllum
here, Araneus Angulatus.
She has taken up her abode
at a convenient height
for observation
between a row of cypress trees
and a clump of laurels
near the entrance
to an alley haunted
by moths.
The spot appears well chosen
for the epiphyllum does not change
it throughout the season
though she renews her net
almost every night.
Punctually, as darkness
falls,
our whole family
goes and calls upon her.
We stand amazed
at her wealth of belly
and her exuberant somersaults
in the maze of quivering ropes.
We admire the faultless geometry
of the set
as it gradually takes shape.
All agleam in the lantern light
the work becomes a fairy orb
which seems
woven of moonbeams.
What delightful
simple evenings we have spent
looking at the moonbeams.
Looking into the spiders workshop.
The
spirit is so pure
and you are never wrong.
Please sir,
I've got to see the wizard.
The good witch of the north sent me.
Prove it.
You wonderful prat S Around my juniorander I
wish she were only須
The book eating öğrenzek
He is a boy
Enthusiastic
and my abused
famous
A treatment of children by yours truly.
But now, an example of the weird treats to be found at Dictionariochi.org.
Dictionariochi.org.
This one by someone called Stop the Children.
We don't need no education.
Education.
We don't need no thought control.
No dark sarcasm in the classroom.
Teacher, leave them kids alone.
Hey.
Teacher.
Leave them kids alone.
All in all.
It's just another Britain the wall.
You're just another Britain the wall.
All in all.
Five, five, three, two, one.
This is a world destruction.
Your life ain't nothing.
The human race is becoming a disgrace.
Countries are fighting in chemical warfare.
Giving a damn of the people who live there.
Not your dumbest predicted coming of the Antichrist.
Hey, look out!
The Dalai Lama nations are on the rise.
A democratic communist relationship.
We're standing in the way of the Islamic force.
The CIA.
The CIA is looking for other tactics.
The KGB is swarming.
The brainwashed mentality is to control the system.
Using TV and movies.
Religions and course.
Yes, the world is headed for destruction.
Is it nuclear war?
What are you asking for?
The world is headed for destruction.
Fight, fight, fight, fight.
This is a world destruction.
Your life ain't nothing.
The human race is becoming a disgrace.
The rich get richer.
The poor are getting poorer.
Fascist chauvinistic government fools.
People like the Muslims, Christians and Hindus.
Are in a time of suicide.
Searching for the truth.
Who are you to think you're a superior race?
Racing for your everlasting doom.
We are time zone.
We come to take the bomb on you.
Fight for destruction.
Kaboom! Kaboom! Kaboom!
Come along.
Oh God, I lied.
I have a movements.
Karmoh did you hear someone?
My brain is in battle.
I can't awesome.
My man the revolution is going to be televised.
On the internet man.
Maybe that's what happened convert.
Maybe thats what's finally happening.
They're coming.
They're just zapping cities left and right.
It's like you humans are too damn stupid.
Well, it could be.
There ain't nothing worth saving in that crap.
It's the Harry Potter reference that we were talking about.
It could be Harry Pooper or the Rockefellers of the CFR exploding us with nuclear mushrooms behind our backbones.
You know, the kind we can't see.
It's all of those things and so much, much more, dear friend.
Well, thank goodness that the magic is, you know, keeping the noose at bay.
Did you say Frank goodness or?
Frank goodness.
Yes.
He's the one actually in charge of keeping the nuclear bomb exploding.
I see.
That guy is a jerk.
Have you ever tried to get in touch with him close to anybody's lunch hour?
He's either a jerk or he's goodness personified.
If they're not sure if his name was really, you know, goodness because that's what he was or is,
or if that's, you know, a name he just gave himself.
Well, that doesn't explain his rubber pants, you know, or any of those pictures.
Really?
I was wearing those rubber pants for as far back as anybody can remember.
But remember, they're thick, insulating rubber pants.
Well, right.
Because people are always trying to shock him.
Right.
And he's, yeah.
And, and, and, uh.
Just a self-defense, you know.
I mean, this is, let's face it.
This has never, ever been discussed by anyone ever.
But why, why don't they replace him?
At least he is old, you know.
At least he's, I mean, I think he's at least a thousand years old now.
Well, yeah, yeah.
But, you know, face it.
I mean, we're talking about this, this on the.
On the radio right now for the first time ever.
Uh-huh.
And, and, and, in fact, we're having.
In the words.
I didn't even know you knew about this, right?
In the words, gone as soon as you hear them.
Exactly.
That's the amazing thing about this media.
This is, no, but, you know, I mean.
Gone.
You're writing about conspiracies and stuff.
As soon as you hear it.
Right.
This is, this is.
Calhounka County Emergency Services, C-COMS, conducting weekly emergency alert system tests.
Repeating.
Tests completed at.
Oh, 100 hours.
December 7th.
What the hell is going on in this?
An alert has been received.
Alert.
The civil authorities have issued a civil emergency.
Message.
But it doesn't say what it is.
You don't need to know.
Are you sure that's not, not just.
Look, turn your lights off.
Cover your windows.
Everybody, you have to turn your lights off.
I'm not kidding you.
There has been an alert received here.
In your homes.
No, it's probably.
Are we getting some nasty weather?
But I don't know.
If anything else comes through.
This is the only message I've received.
Maybe the people sending this message.
Have been.
They're already gone.
They're gone.
Yeah.
In a matter of moments.
The next war will be fought with sticks.
Oh, Dave.
I forgot about you.
No, I'm just telling you guys.
I had this weird dream last night.
When I got up.
I had this weird dream.
It's a world's ending.
I was not supposed to go to Rhodes Tower tonight.
And that somehow my car would get sick on me.
We should say that.
You should scan this and put it in the.
Put it up on the website.
With the big mustache.
Look, it isn't perfect.
How it travels.
Trails off.
Yeah.
That's scary.
On AMWCS.
Is that really happening?
Yes.
This can't do something with it.
Narrow strip of paper.
I missed a very exciting moment.
Came reading out from the machinery here.
That this is, I guess, part of the civil defense alert system.
I mean, I did hear the zipping.
And I wondered where it was coming from.
My forehead or perhaps in the studio there on the other end of your line.
You're just worried the next day may come.
When they least expect it.
So they're trying to get ready.
It will come in an hour that you know not my friend.
Well, I got Chino.
We actually heard it.
Flashing rapists in the night.
You tied your shoes this morning, The Undertaker.
My tie in tonight.
You believe the weapon was effective?
Can't tell there's too much smoke.
Now a new sound drifted in the soft evening sky.
For Colonel Dan Butterfield, a courageous and able soldier, was also a man of music.
To honor his fallen comrades, he had composed a simple and heart-rending melody.
On July 2nd, in the year of 1862,
its strains floated over the graves that scarred the dark Virginia earth.
It has been more than a hundred years since that sound was born,
but those notes have never died away.
Every night of the year, throughout the world,
fighting men of America from the North and the South, East and the West,
close their eyes and sleep to its call.
And in each of their hearts, there glows a fierce surge of pride.
And they beat the poor little warlike people
and bring peace forever and ever, just like real life.
But then the evil art dictators come.
The art bombs have finally taken power in the far future
and they object to the firing of the space gun.
They incite an unruly mob to come forward and smash the space gun.
But it fires anyway,
shooting a young, comely pair of youths into space.
Male and female,
seeding the cosmos,
they seeded earth
to the Indians for $24.
It was a mystery.
A mystery wrapped in an enigma.
Surrounded with creamy milk chocolate
and velvety nougat.
And little rice crispy things.
They didn't actually have a name.
But they called it...
a
your safety list please correct all statement and questions to my attorney I request that my attorney he present before any search on this vehicle or my
person is conducted.
Who is arrested?
Do not surrender any of my constitutional rights except on the advice of my attorney.
Without
unless everyone sinon fundamentalists share the database It should act.
advise you of that fact. If this is the case, please notify a police supervisor, as I request
his presence at this location. If you give me a lawful order, I will repeat it back to
you before performance, solely to ensure I both understand and fully comply with that
order. Once you have issued me an order, I have repeated it back to you and complied
with it. I will not perform any further action until you have given me a subsequent order,
or released me from your command. If I am, or am becoming, physically incapacitated,
or I am unable to comply with your order for any reason, I will inform you immediately.
If you wish me to repeat these instructions, please ask me now, and I will do so.
Lions and tigers and bears! Oh my! Lions and tigers and bears! Oh my!
I'll tell you what I think. The future is in the sink.
Don't eat.
No plunger.
Going down.
And under.
Oh my! Me bop.
Trip.
My hip hop.
And what not.
Good idea, really!
And what you got?
Did you read all the infos?
What love is to me?
Is all of the information you need?
The answer is
Well enjoy the movie.
.
Yes.
that is relevant
to the common man
it's seldom mentioned
of course we're talking about
the missing link
and the alien experimentation
oh my people
I'm not about one night
talking about
the death of the ape man
the genetic splicing
was so enticing
well what do you think
how do you think it'll work out
shit I don't know
ha ha ha
fuck it go for it
talking about the time
that is seldom mentioned
talking of course
about the time
of the alien
experimentation
dig down and use your hate
what?
are you looking down
and using your hate
oh do we have to
Jedi
Dr. Vader
oh he wants us to
use our hate power again
don't you know
that your head
was transformed
use your hate
so much for your rebellion
Jedi
silence
with a snapper
friends that long rant
was
the
expatriate
from
fedcoms
fedcoms is an active
subgenius group
in New York City
and you can look at their website
at
digimind.tripod.com
slash
fedcoms
F-E-D-C-O-M-S
and
the clips
that we've been hearing
were sent
to
alt binary slack
by
Lemur
and Mr. Sister
New Monet
Artemia Salina
did the
John Wayne smash up
we heard some
ESO swamp radio
we heard
world destruction
by time zone
and the background music
you hear right now
is Einstein's
secret orchestra
by the way
we now
make
ESO
CDs
the music CDs
are now available
through the subgenius
website
subgenius.com
friends we also heard
some KPFA
with Dr. Howell
and puzzling evidence
from our
current
analysis
that
have
infinite
income
through
extreme
fundamental
Porchand,
liberal
aptitude
is
Blood
houd
just
in
your
at
some
investments
so
dedicat
quick
gets
some
We want you to be ready for the coming ball.
The coming apocalyptic...
Yes, there's a time when all the springs are going to uncoil.
The pendulums will disintegrate.
The hours will bleed upon the floor.
A couple of minesweepers from the U.S. Army.
The minutes and seconds are exsanguinating.
The P.I.A. and the schools and administration,
she's decided to come back and dig some of those up.
And there you go.
It's beautiful floats and costumes,
and just everybody's turned out.
It's wonderful to see the police here in horse today,
and in costume, too.
The police? What are they doing here?
That's right. The police are in costume.
And it's a nice turn of events from that 1986 April Fool's Day massacre.
The martyrdom of Bishop Joey, which...
Sorry.
I'm just imitating...
Hey!
...subgeniuses here in my...
I guess...
There they go, and there goes those helicopters.
...live broadcasts of St. Stupas.
And there's St. Stupas on the top of the building,
waving hello to all the parade participants.
They're still up there with their flashing nipples,
throwing us all the way.
Who needs a dipstick when you can have a laser spy tool,
or even better, a laser level that makes leveling any project a snap?
Whether it's laser...
...or lining up pictures on adjacent walls,
laying floor and ceiling tile,
or building a brick wall,
there's just no easy way to know you're working on a straight level line.
Yes, I see.
Yeah.
But the laser-equipped level is much better than the one with the little bubbles.
Oh, yes. Much better with the bubbles.
Once the level is properly aligned,
it projects a sharp, easily seen line
that allows you to work on any flat surface,
even ceilings,
with laser accuracy.
Yeah, that's true.
You could detect electromagnetic fields,
ease shoulder and neck pain,
get jogger's dog protection,
and even have unusual Halloween fun.
There'd be no need to curtail your lifestyle
because of pesky earthquakes and other national disasters.
No.
You could take the easy road to success.
Touch me.
I know what you're after, Dave.
Poltergeist or gas.
Well, put it this way.
If they ever did bottle that really good thing...
I got thrill pills for all the little chickies.
And I got funny cigarettes for all you boys.
And I got dirty pictures for all of you together.
Well, I guess I better go.
I see the campus cops coming.
I better split now.
Remember Leon Trotsky, do you?
You have to put a dropper on it.
Special and tequila.
Clever loser.
Because it's not a problem.
Spandex pants.
In the spandex man.
It's like purple spandex pants.
Exactly.
Can we just swat one dirty old man now?
Swat him.
Of course.
10 more.
We love the spandex.
Pop up where that one was.
That's a baby boomers for you.
What, liking to spank old men?
It's a civilization of dirty old men.
And dirty old ladies, man.
Hail Connie.
Well, they have the public spankings of the dirty old men and ladies now.
I am not technically a baby boomer.
Remember how a lot of the people used to show up for those?
You're just a couple of years behind the baby boomer.
Yeah, I'm not.
The people have actually written about me.
And that we're the ones that never got a name.
The baby fizzles.
We never got a name.
That's because they refused to pull your pants down.
Gen X, we weren't part of Gen X either.
Nope.
But we weren't part of the baby boomers.
The baby duds.
So, but the article, one article I read.
It did point out that we will be paying the bills for the baby boomer.
Praise God.
You'll be paying for our diapers.
That's true.
I'm only a couple of years older than you, but I'm part of the baby boomer.
Mm-hmm.
See, and he'll be wearing diapers at the same time you'll be wearing one of those Speedo
swimsuits for elderly folks.
I think I'm part of the space age, Gen.
Because that's when, when I was born was the first year that anything went into space.
Sputnik.
Sputnik went up like two days after I was born.
It's the first year anybody noticed.
Oh, that's a sign.
Anybody who's like 12 years old now.
It's a space boy.
Yeah, space boy.
Anybody who's like 12 years old now is part of the trapper keeper generation.
Really?
That's cool.
Trapper.
Yeah, we were baby boomers.
They're the trapper keepers.
And what a terrible moniker to carry around your whole life too, especially if you have
to wear those big dog boots.
But that's what they're going to have to do.
You know, you get, and people can only pull your earlobe so far before the whole ear falls
off.
I mean, I'm talking about scarification is not a way to live.
No.
Next will be the hunter gatherer generation.
Yeah.
Well, they'll come after the trapper keepers because they're going to realize that, you
know, then you have to domesticate the food and stuff and everything too.
So then you'll have the hunter gatherers and you'll have the agrarian farmers.
Work their way back up.
The feudal warlords again.
Yeah.
For a thousand years again.
The macro hyper industrial gen will then follow up after that.
They'll have natural selection stores where you can stock the manager and steal as much
food as you want.
The other ones where you cooperatively have to live.
And what about the hyper industrial postmodernist gen?
Again.
Exactly, Jez.
And how many times can it be modern and postmodern, folks?
Just think of it.
Post-postmodern.
Yeah.
In your silly Egyptian chairs.
Right.
You know, wearing your scarabs and looking at a strange glowing box that the Pharaoh
hath created for thee.
Come on now.
Yeah, but the curve's going straight up now almost.
It's almost the end.
Of what though?
About three more minutes, in fact.
Yeah.
Oh, the almost the end of this loop.
Well, this particular-
The Mayans knew it.
I'm going to play that again.
The Aztecs knew it.
The gypsies.
That's the same of the-
The Dobbses.
The Lovecrafts.
That's the same of your adults.
The Lovecrafts knew it.
I mean, it is exactly the same thing, this thing that they're sinking up.
The big door is closing.
No, it's not sinking up.
We have to eat our tail.
The sink is over with.
If you've got a tail, start doing it now.
Sink is draining.
You know what I mean?
Sink is-
No one told you when to run.
I forgot that.
You missed the starting gun.
If you're a movie, it's about whooping.
You run and you run to catch up with the sun, Dave, but it's sinking and racing around to
come up behind you again.
Behind you again.
I know.
That is so freaking heavy.
The sun is the same in a relative way, but you're older.
Man.
Shorter of breath and one day closer to death.
I am going to wear a honey truss the rest of my life with those words inscribed in
the middle and one of those fuzzy little pom-pom things to remind me of that message.
Man, that colostomy bag will probably help remind you too.
Yeah, but when you fill it up with wine and drink from it-
No, they have the colostomy bags now.
With your favorite 60s band.
I said, no.
I think they did have the Pink Floyd colostomy bag.
I saw it.
Did you go to the festival though, man?
In Milwaukee, they had a whole festival, I guess.
So how's your lumbago lately?
Sitting at the swag tail of the swag hair.
How's your rest home lately?
How's your vertigo?
I guess.
How's your bingo?
Oh, it's fine, but I can't hit portals.
Oh, yeah, everyone has a good postion.
Okay.
Now please don't hurt me.
Need just to go and drink the beer.
Let me know what you've been drinking.
Yeah, I am a זה pussy!
You drunk as F veyaflowing Carolina!
You're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
For free information on Bob Dobbs and the Church of the Subgenius, send a self-addressed stamped envelope to...
Got your pencil ready?
Bob, Post Office Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
That's Bob, P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
Stay tuned and praise Bob!
Oh, my friends, I want you to check out www.subgenius.com.
It's as beautiful as that music.
And, uh, uh, yes.
If you don't eat your meat,
you can't have any pudding.
How can you have pudding
if you don't eat your meat?
California oranges, Texas cactus,
we think you need a little more practice.
Throw them in the graveyard, cover up their feet.
J.R. Bob Dobbs can't be beat.
Yay!
Yo, Carson Bratt,
look what you've done!
I'm melting!
Melting!
Oh, my world, my world!
Who would have thought I could love her like you
for destroying my beautiful wickedness?
Ah!
The boat!
I'm going!
Ah!