Sound impossible?
Yes, you rub it between the forefinger and the thumb.
Oh, well, then.
You take the pinch of salt, you rub it between the forefinger and the thumb,
walk with your shoes around a burning, decapitated child's head,
and then jump into the grave and say,
hop on my thumb, hop on my thumb,
this is a problem I must overcome.
Throw in a dead cat, or a live cat that's not feeling well.
Then cover with the sod,
and when the birds chirp on the third Saturday after Micklemas,
take a large dill pickle and insert it in the tumulus.
Insert it in the tumulus, the heap, the shambling mound over the grave.
And this time you will experience a divine regurgitation,
somewhat like unto the immaculation of J.R. Mockadob,
the slain and martyred epop of the Church of the Subdivide.
I believe it's something God puts in us.
It's something somebody put in us.
Fusion.
The help.
Hydrogen fusion.
Hydrogen fusion?
Hmm.
Well, it's...
Hydrogen fusion.
Join the Church of the Subdivide.
Hydrogen fusion, hyper-confusion.
This material contains information affecting the national defense of the United States
within the meaning of the espionage law,
Cital 18, U.S.C. sections 7098 and 74,
a transmission or revelation of which in any manner to an unauthorized person
is indefinitely prohibited by law.
This material does not derive them without second feelings.
Hang in that perfect place where one could hear the concerns and remarks of thousands of
A beginning is a very delicate time.
Shut up.
That's it.
Look out, guys.
No way.
A beginning.
is a very delicate time.
Well, we're tuning in on you right now.
And there, we're centered on...
Oh, okay, we're on lock.
You are interested in the unknown,
the mysterious, the unexplainable.
That is why you are here.
We are controlling transmission.
No trouble.
Just get set and get going.
Hey, man.
Recording.
Everything's going fine.
No trouble.
Wait a minute.
Wait.
That's this switch here.
Okay, I think we're ready to go.
Let's go!
Hey!
Welcome, dear friends,
to the subgenius hour of...
What?
This is Doug Smith, radio operator.
Ah, it's so nice out here in the little studio.
Welcome, Dear tokast at the fautique magazine.
Welcome over to the Prophet Club.
I would like you to likebeast calm.
how to to make Aaa fir eад a O 48.
Well, that is it.
let's prepare ourselves
Central Services
We do the work, you do the pleasure
Hi there. I want to talk to you about ducts.
Do your ducts seem old-fashioned?
Out of date?
Central Services' new duct designs
are now available in hundreds of different colours
to suit your individual taste.
Hurry now, while stocks last
to your nearest Central Services showroom.
Designer colours to suit your demanding taste.
The rumour became reality.
Another satanic cult.
Yes, just another evil cult that was supposed to be a good one.
This is how the war gets on the radio.
I think a lot of subgeniuses originally believed
they were doing something good by joining the church.
That wheel and chain set up makes the sound of moving artillery.
Sounds like a real battle.
Well, it's nothing compared to what it takes to move this show.
Don't be alarmed.
It's a lot more work than saving souls, believe me.
That punch didn't connect.
The sound was faked.
Although, Stang suffered a real blow
from an infuriated Gabofran.
Oh, that was a great blow.
Yes, the mallet on a grapefruit gave the sound of that blow.
Curiously refreshing.
It was a lot of fun, too.
But here they come, there.
The guard is forming to march the guilty offender away.
Yes, those who believe...
...the wrong lies in the book of the subgenius
taken into the stadium near Dobstown
and all the Malaysians pour into the little wooden seats.
For the clumsy child with the hard-to-fit shoe size,
Cap Bigfoot, our 31st season.
Boys and girls, 6 to 18, 10D to 15, EEEEEE.
Our patient understanding staff has had outstanding success
with the clumsy, uncoordinated child.
Our unique patented method starts your child from scratch,
from crawling to early walking,
to full walking, trotting and running,
until he is actually strutting, dancing and doing gymnastics.
Many of our graduates are now prominent in ballet and jazz tag.
Write to George Trefeld, Camp Bigfoot, Peppermill, Oregon, 65201.
We like you and should ignore you.
But instead, we...
Oh!
Jedi.
Nya!
I sure do hope y'all are listening in headphones.
This is a real headphone show, so please do take the time.
A beginning is a very delicate thing.
A beginning is a very delicate time.
Here and there, clowns and ballerinas everywhere.
Bob?
Hey.
What?
Oh, yes, dear friends.
This is the VT, a Chinese subgenius.
And you are listening to the Hour of Slack.
Remember, Bob is a comrade of all people.
He is a channel, just like in America.
And people need slack.
That's a lot of fun.
In Chinese, we call slack le ting tang.
It must be true slack, not the bad slack of our conspiracy.
Boy, will you look at that guy's slack.
Help me somebody.
Thank you, Lily Jing.
Yes?
My friends, we have the great Ivan Stang here tonight.
Ivan Stang himself, the grand auditor and chief inquisitor of the subgenius faith,
who has every subgenius's name on his special basement computer,
and he's here tonight to make the hour and a half of slack seem like, well, like forever.
Ivan Stang.
That's Stang, you stangs.
Sibley.
He's stoner of rank.
Of Serlo's claws and Jeter's fangs.
When the peaks are upon us,
when its day finally is on us,
the peaks will roil, but not in zona.
Nature and man will stand aside.
The jaws of doom shall open wide,
while Ivan Stang shall perch in Zod.
Where from?
Godlessness and pitiless dwells, false prophets from their citadels, he topples down to nether hells.
He judges pigs and guinea-paws, and renders into visit-blobs those who profane the name of dogs.
He rules the vast subgenial host, evens his lags on the coast, a flage from his name as from a ghost.
Where can we go? Where can we find? No place in all this world so wide shall escape the dire subgenial tide.
The jaders howl, the sternoes plead, Bohemondus rises from the sea, no hiding place.
No hiding place.
For you indeed.
What future does our doom procure us?
Empty earth indeed endure us.
Let the damn wolf dogs it lure us.
A rancorous fangarack, the gangster of the gang of gangs.
Let us now welcome Ivan Stang.
Ivan Stang.
Get out there, you jaders.
Alright, here we go.
Hey, guys.
Integral bait.
All right.
Blend them together, men and unit.
Dmitri!
All right.
Be sure to stick around.
We're ready, Ivan.
Unplugged.
One.
This hideous, hideous place.
Bob lives, friends.
Bob lives.
Don't let him tell you otherwise.
He ain't dead.
Oh, what is this?
I should know.
I'm the guy that has to read sooner or later all the mail that comes to that P.O. box
that you probably thought was just made up.
The opinions expressed by Ivan Stang do not necessarily reflect the opinions of the staff
and management of this radio station.
The other staff, the relations and spouses of the staff and management,
or the staff of this staff and staff.
That's really true, Hal, but he doesn't know that there's all over the place these days.
Bob's body dragged out of the Victoria Theater with these eyes.
These deadlights looked on Bob and the light was drifting from them forever.
There's saint of sale corpses dotting the landscape.
All the way up to the top.
All the way from Little Rock to Berkeley here.
I don't know what the big deal is.
I mean, just because there's a Dobbs corpse there doesn't necessarily...
I mean, can Bob really die?
I don't know.
I just couldn't be bothered to believe Bob's body was real.
uer!
The second.
The third.
The fourth.
When it blows its stacks
He ain't nowhere to be found
When the wolves crawl
While we're down
The billow box out
Now we're around
Hide all them women in town
Hide
When it blows its stacks
When the dolphins avow
When thebandw avow
Before we go wild
When we blow our dicks
When we blow our scavens
Down on homes
When we cut theitive
Ten stank vulc on her bunlar
Oh!
He takes them out, out on the nice mud.
Count them a-blomping, so y'all see around.
When he's straightened up, they all bend down.
He don't bow to bad water, he don't push it around.
Well, it blows the stacks.
Well, it blows.
Oh, the stacks.
Well, it blows the stacks, the angels.
No well to be around.
No well to be gone.
No.
existence.
Ah, ah.
Oh, ah.
Yeah.
No, no, nope.
No.
you gals out there. We haven't gotten any more entries in the win a date with Cleve
Duncan contest. I mean, I'm not even going to go into, if you don't know who Cleve Duncan
is, then you probably don't deserve the date. But if you do, go ahead and try. Go ahead
and try. It's important. Very important.
What?
what?
Stop it!
You're always right.
bateuc
I don't like that name.
Woof, woof, go!
Heave-ho!
Woof, woof, woof, woof, woof, woof, woof, woof, woof, woof, woof, woof, woof, woof, woof, woof, woof!
Slag faster, make it down faster
They've made it out of the smoke through the bone
He's the one I got, shake it off your behind
If you wanna know the truth, then that's a fact
Somebody scream, give me more slag, give me more slag
Do you like slag?
I like it
I say, I love slag
I love it
Do you want slag?
I want it
Do you need slag?
I need it
You like me?
No
How about I need me?
What about you?
No
Look at me, I'm a dismal
Get down to program
No
Ride, ride, you hobo boy
Feel like Trinitraline
No
Got the motion
Yeah, he's been hopping to the barbershop with more slag
I gotta have my slag
Give it to me
Yeah, praise Bob
Hey
Stay down on that, stay down on that
Stay down on that
Boy, I mean, slack is better than red beans and rice.
On top of a snow key
All covered with sand
I shot my poor teacher
With a red rubber band
I shot her with pleasure
I shot her with please
I couldn't help miss her
She was forty feet wide
I went to her funeral
I went to her grave
Everybody threw flowers
But I threw a grenade
The police came and got me
And put me in jail
But I brought a best friend
To go and shot him to H-E-L-L
Oh, thank you, Tevis.
That was a beautiful rendition of a classic, classic childhood song.
And there'll be more from the tiniest subgenius prophet coming up.
But friends, you know, we've been griping about those who didn't pay their pledge.
But we haven't really thanked those who had.
And...
Well, the Willa Dobbs and I got to looking at this board in here.
This poster that they've put up
that keeps track of what shows are ahead
and what shows are behind on the pledge drive.
And, uh...
Friends, I could scarcely believe it,
but the Hour of Slack
is number five among all K-N-O-N shows
as far as paid pledges go.
And the other, the four shows,
out of 80...
What, 81 shows, I think?
Yeah, 81 shows.
Out of 81 shows, the four shows that made more money
during that pledge drive than the Hour of Slack
were all on for, like, 10 hours a day.
They're on every day.
We did better in Pajama Party, better than anybody.
Now, the gospel shows, they got as much pledges as the subgenius show,
but strangely, only 8% paid.
Wonder what that means.
Well, anyway, 50% of you subgeniuses have paid, I think.
By now, probably 50%.
And those who haven't, if you haven't gotten the calls already,
you will.
You'll get that call.
And it's all being recorded,
not only on magnetic media here in this century,
but on the Akashic records,
the records of all things that have ever occurred,
even inside your brain.
That's all recorded,
and we have access to those through our guru.
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And friends, we're going to continue with the show.
I hope you're, once again, I hope you're in headphones.
This is a real headphone show.
We'll be right back.
How do we know you're not being tied, Bob?
Okay.
Good God.
You'll never tell them we don't see anything.
Screaming.
What's up, Dean?
What's the world coming to?
Don't listen to him.
There are, yes, you can find help.
You can be deprogrammed.
You can find out the truth.
They beat me up today.
It's a hell of an imp.
I know you're a dumbass.
They force you to sleep on four.
But it's not fast.
It came fast.
They're weak.
They're going to.
Is that all right?
Some geniuses came in.
They took all my furniture and sold it to buy me this neck brace that I can't take off now.
They said it was a living being.
Bring the upper lip down below the upper teeth.
Be sure to keep it down until the fingers are in position.
At each corner of the mouth, insert a thumb under the upper lip.
Now slide the thumbs along the inside of the upper lip until they are positioned just below and to the side of each nostril.
The results are thrilling.
Everywhere these messages are heard, souls are being saved and sick bodies are being healed.
I, too, refuse to send money to the Church of the Sub-G.
And I, too, fail under the power of the e.
Stop right there.
Sorry for keeping you in, doctors.
Go on.
Don't leave me here.
You've got to leave me here.
They made me say.
Don't leave me here.
They tortured me.
They make me save things.
Don't leave me here.
They torture me.
They make me save things.
Don't leave me here.
I understand.
I'm sorry.
Don't let them kill me.
Torture me.
I understand.
They torture me.
Don't let them kill me.
What could be saying this?
It's been the subgenius, parrot, and parakeet training.
They torture.
I hate this place.
It's been the subgenius, parrot, and parakeet training.
Don't let them kill me.
I hate this place.
I'm calling my names, but...
Yee-haw!
Let the sons of God and man be a witness.
Even in the belly of the Thunderbird,
I've been casting out the false prophets.
I'm busting the gut and blowing my o-ring.
No!
Please.
We have a witness from the Ministry of Information.
Deputy Minister, Eugene Hellman.
Good evening, David.
What do you believe is behind this recent increase in terrorism?
bombings, bad sportsmanship. A ruthless minority of people seems to have forgotten certain good
old-fashioned virtue. They just can't stand seeing the other fellow win. If these people would just
play the game, they'd get a lot more out of life. Nevertheless, Mr. Helper, there are those who
maintain that the Ministry of Information has become too large and unwieldy. David, in a free
society, information's the name of the game. You can't win the game if you're a man short.
And the cost of it all, Deputy Minister, 7% of the gross national product. I understand this
concern on behalf of the taxpayer. People want value for money. That's why we always insist on
the principle of information retrieval charges. It's absolutely right, sir, that those found
guilty should pay for their periods of detention.
And for the information retrieval procedures used in their interrogation. Do you believe that the
government is winning the battle against terrorists? Oh, yes. Our morale is much higher than theirs.
We're fielding all their strokes, running a lot of them out, and pretty consistently knocking them
for six. I'd say they're nearly out of the game.
One law-abiding citizen has to subsidize criminals. But Mr. Helper, the bombing campaign
is now in its 13th year. Beginner's luck. Thank you very much, Deputy Minister.
Thank you, David. And a very Merry Christmas to you all.
Know then that it is the year 10,000.
1991.
There have always been Bobs. There has never been a world without a Bob.
Just as there's never been a Bob without a Dick, his corresponding evil twin brother, Dick Dobbs.
After a mental mutation.
The demons you may see during the initial hallucinations are not real.
Get him away from me.
If you do not panic, this phase will end after a few minutes.
Jack.
So always resurface from the hypgnosis slowly, dear friends.
Excuse me.
Yadda yadda yadda.
Hoo! Hoo! Hoo!
Hoo!
Oh, yeah, I wanna...
Hoo! Hoo! Hoo!
Hoo!
I wanna... that's not right, Gary. That should be a...
Hoo! Hoo!
Hoo!
Okay, that's good.
Hoo! Hoo!
Well, yes, I was gonna make serious funny noises.
Because we all know that Bob is the man that makes all the ladies go...
Hoo! Hoo! Hoo!
It is the man that makes all the men go...
Well, please take a little rest.
It ain't an om-chanting laid-back universe, dear friends.
It's a...
Hoo! Hoo! Hoo!
...universe.
Shhh!
An action-packed universe.
Oh, yeah.
Hello, what's this?
Yes?
Hmm. A boring and...
A virulating and putrescent biologically active universe.
...the holes between their shoelaces.
Just because.
Enormous bioplasm that stretches throughout infinity.
Hoo! Hoo! Hoo!
Oh, did you get some of that, too?
Yes, it was delicious.
And then he forced me to eat this big, ugly piece of meat.
Hoo! Hoo! Hoo! Hoo!
He was a little, short, chubby guy, and that's where Bob got the idea.
They say he came in with checkered pants on, but I just don't remember.
He was allowed to eat all he wanted.
challenging, anything she wanted.
Bob's big boy
was a real person.
That's true, for there was
a real Bob.
And this parable
goes to show that there is indeed
always a real Bob.
There has to be a Bob, dear friend.
Even the things which you cannot possibly
believe in, Bob's big boy
indeed, turn out to be an actual
historic person. And as it is
with Bob's big boy, surely
it is with the far more impressive
and major deity we know
as the Avatar of All Slack.
That's how
we know him. Others
call him Pimp or Mongo.
Others call him a demon
or your mama.
Indeed. And the children of Bob are
everywhere. Bob lives on in his
millions and millions, literally
millions of illegitimate children.
All of them pressing lawsuits
against me
personally. Well,
doctor, I'm sure you're used to it by now.
Well, when I took on the job as
sacred scribe at the church,
I had no idea what I was
going to be getting into. We had 500
employees in 1980.
Now it's just me and someone else.
Well, that's just the
Reagan-esque spirit
that's been infusing us together
for its own sake. And yet they
say that Bob doesn't even exist.
There are some who say that there
is no Bob. If there's no Bob,
then where did all of those dead
bodies come from?
What about all those ads in the 50s
that he posed for?
Right here, the body store.
Dead Bobs for any occasion.
Oh, put that away. That's not impressing anyone.
No Bob too small, no Bob too big.
No, really, guys, all kidding aside,
all kidding aside,
at least
the official Father Church,
the subgenius foundation,
which we don't expect any of you
to accept the stinking Bob.
To cling to.
Nevertheless, we have the only
true word of Bob,
the original apostles.
And as far as I'm concerned,
this whole thing about Bob
being dead is a ruse.
Bob staged that whole thing
himself. It was fashionable
in the 60s.
It's the same frontwards and back, friends.
And there's a reason there's an O in
the middle.
A hole in the middle between those two
Bs. It's symbolic, friends.
You can look through that
the center of that
O in Bob's name
and see the future and the past.
The spice
must flow.
Mr. Chron
guardian takes him along way to
Once you get to홓
H flagteş
A woman, age 93, was killed in a merry-go-round when she and her wheelchair were thrown from the thing in Sherman's amusement park.
The woman was killed in a merry-go-round when she and her wheelchair were thrown from the thing in Sherman's amusement park.
You have reached the correct number. However, your call has already been analyzed and rejected.
This matter is out of our hands.
As soon as we are able to transcend the time problems inherent in life on Earth and gain control of the situation,
we will return you to your previously scheduled conversation.
If this had been an actual phone call, you would have been instructed to leave your name, number, time,
and number of the person you are calling.
You will receive a message when you hear the tone. Thank you.
Ah, Reverend Stein, praise Bob. This is Robert Anton Wilson,
and about my appearance for the church of the subgenius Jeff Rosenbaum, who arranges the tours,
we'll be calling you about that because he's the one who has all the flight plans and the airline tickets and his controls,
and he'll be the one who arranges the dates with you when I'll be there,
and I better shut up because I'm running out of time. Praise Bob!
Praise Bob.
Well, yeah, that's right. That was Robert Anton Wilson, and about ten of you listeners probably know who he is.
We have the chance of setting up a lecture and or show or whatever with Robert Anton Wilson.
He's going to be coming through Texas to do shows, at least in Austin, at the Book People's bookstore.
I know about that one, but we could set one up here in Dallas.
But we need like about $450 or $500 front money, see, to get him in, and that's just the cost of the show, basically.
So we also need a place to do it.
And if anybody is wild and crazy about Robert Anton Wilson and wants to get real involved in bringing him to Dallas,
then let us know.
For those of you who don't know, he's the author of Illuminatus and Schrodinger's Cat and several other cosmic science fiction,
books that, well, you just have to check them out.
But write us here at the station or write to Bob at EO Box 807 Glen Rose, Texas 76043.
So we're going to continue here.
Oh, my dear negative land.
We have a swimming pool.
Well, as you can hear, Dr.
Paul Robbins and Gary Gabroga,
I guess,
put them in several movie soundtracks.
That's what we're doing is movie soundtracks.
You're hearing the soundtrack of Brazil in stereo.
That's why I insist on the headphones.
Brazil, Big Trouble in Little China, and Dune are our favorite sound effects horrors for tonight.
So.
Doug, this is Steve.
I'm going to be in town on time.
What are you talking about, man?
But hurry.
Alright, it's Nick.
Give me a call.
Well, too bad we missed you.
This is Mike and Pam in Chicago.
Um.
We didn't know if you had caught.
Pee Wee's Playhouse this morning,
but Bob was prominently displayed on the bulletin board.
If you didn't get it, let me know,
and I'll send you off a copy.
Have a good one. Bye.
How long have you been in the U.S. of A?
Fremont.
Where from?
Hong Kong.
What happens?
You stay here a while?
Old girls leave, new girls come in?
Maybe.
Take your tie off, please.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
My wife gave it to me for Christmas.
I'm going home anyway.
I'm trying to start a new business.
He said he's in the other conquered countries.
I'll run along again.
You've seen a lot of memory.
in Europe
Mm-hmm.
Good anyone.
No!
Explosions.
People flying in and out.
That was not real.
I want to talk to the cops.
I want my truck back.
Now, where the hell am I?
That's right.
You're lucky to live in the end time.
Here's my money, bud.
Wise up.
They're out to get you.
Moving podium.
Prod.
And having once prodded, moves on.
I'm not moving.
You know, the subgenius is not just below a genius, whatever that may be.
The subgenius does not pretend to superknowledge, but to subknowledge.
Knowledge of the underthings, the underwear lurking beneath the clothing of existence.
The foundation garment, if you will.
The underlying reality.
You see, the subgenius is a strange beast indeed.
Give me a can of sound effects while you're at it, would you?
Oh, yeah, and some show stretchers.
And listen to him.
I need some show stretchers back.
Yes, friends.
How about something to eat?
Little did many of you know, but this isn't the only subgenius show.
In fact, there's six weekly subgenius shows now in New York, Beijing, New Jersey, Richmond, Virginia, St. Louis, Dallas.
Come on, hurry now.
We have to catch the last dog's home.
I get it, I get it.
Virgin, a high protein.
I'm a protein tassel wash.
I'm a bacteriological weapon.
I'm armed and I'm loaded.
I'm a fission reactor.
I fight plutonium.
Power plants are fueled by the sweat from my brow.
When they plug me in, the lights go out in Hong Kong.
I weigh 666 pounds with zero gravity.
Come and get me.
Come on.
eagerly soars through space,
a supreme
soon they'll begin to fold space
soon they'll begin to fold space far off in the control rooms of spice gas.
traveling without moving.
Ivan Stang, 15, shows scars after being attacked by an alligator
near West Palm Beach, Florida, Monday.
Ivan and a friend were swimming in the lake
when suddenly he was grabbed by the head
and pulled underwater by a giant sharp-toothed saurian.
I couldn't see anything but teeth and didn't know what had hold of me
until the gator let loose and swam away, said Ivan,
who suffered wounds requiring 41 stitches.
This is supposed to be a religious show.
Now what is the interpretation of this parable, my friends?
The alligator is the worldly mob, the rabble,
who always seek to devour and assimilate the holy men of the Church of the Subgenius.
The lone swimmer, buoyed up by the fluid element,
represents, upon the other hand,
the subgenius.
The striving outward force of the Church of the Subgenius,
which requires 41 stitches,
the same number as the number of bullet holes in Bob's bullet-reddled body.
Praise Bob, praise Bob, praise Bob.
Praise Bob, praise Bob.
What are we going to do?
Wouldn't you like revenge on these mediocrities?
Well, I wouldn't go that far.
These pink boys, these box-dwelling Barbies and Kens,
these normals who have made normality the norm?
Well, no, I wouldn't like revenge on those people.
I'd like revenge on you, Ivan, because you've taken one too many $20 check from me.
I've never gotten...
I want my slack!
Let's see your subgenius membership card, hmm?
Now let's not get...
I mean, say the end times came a little bit soon, Gary.
Do you think you'd make it on the escape saucers of the sex goddesses
without your little subgenius membership card?
I'd sure try.
Ah, this is...
Great example you're setting for the people out here.
That old party pleasure.
I've got my Bob a miracle. I've got my Bob a miracle.
I've got my Bob a miracle.
Oh, it's a magic card here.
It says that I'm paid up to...
Eighteen ninety...seven?
You see, Gary is the Rasputin of the Church of the Subgenius,
often sought for, but rarely encountered.
And it is this self-same learning for slack which separates us from him.
The human may live out his entire life in a grinding cycle of slacklessness.
Yet he never feels cheated.
He thinks it's natural.
He thinks it's fine.
Who cares?
Well, dear friends, this is Reverend Ivan Sangh, and we've been getting some calls tonight
from people who apparently never heard of the Church of the Subgenius before, don't
know anything about it, don't know that there's acres and acres of reading material available,
which is up at least to the level of the incredible mixing you're hearing on this show.
And you can write for information.
That's all we can tell you on this station, for very good reason, because you need to
send your money to the station.
But you can send your letters of your questions, send your questions to Bob.
That's JRBobDobbs, and friends, that address is coming up as you stay tuned for Ron Lindsay's
Soul Oldies.
Have that pencil ready by now?
Well, you need to write to Bob at P.O.
Box.
807-722-4222.
That's 807-722-4222.
So friends, your hour of slack is coming to an end.
But be ready for more slack, more slack dripping and leaking all over you from Ron Lindsay's
Soul Oldies.
There are nothing but half-witted cattle racing each other to be first to the slaughterhouse
and stampeding you along with them.
But what do you care?
You've got slack.
Slack.
Yeah.
Anybody want to get down to slack?
That's him.
Oh, get along, little bobbies.
Go head on down to the Dobbs Town.
Get on in that Dobbs Town crowd, you little bobbies.
Hey, hey.
Oh, there's a nice fat one.
Yes, you'll be a good trading commodity come the bargaining session with the X-ists.
Huh.
It's just some cheap stuff.
Oh, that's a nice fat one.
First off, I noticed y'all don't talk about religion much.
I guess it's real hip out here in California.
It's more of a humanistic approach.
No, we believe in just letting the holy benediction of Bob
flow out like pus and mustard.
Just don't understand the true power of the show.
It's very fashionable to say Bob is a good man.
He was a prophet, but the son of Jehovah.
I don't know what superstition is.
It's very fashionable.
It happens.
It's not his.
But silently, my spirit leads my spirit back to Bob.
In humble trust, my violent spirit.
In reverential resignation.
No.
We should describe to no thought expressed only a sense of suffocation.
With the groove I only got, we shall all be moved.
Ready or not, here we come.
Getting down on the one which we believe in.
Can I get it on my foot?
Good God!
Oh, turn my gas down!
One night, we will all be moved.
So take and shut us down.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, yeah.
Don't tell me now.