And now, the subgenius hour of SWAT!
Oh yes, dear friends, today we're at Dr. Philo Drummond's over mansion in the laundry office.
You can hear the show making machine cranking away here in the background.
We've been making show. This is one of those hours of slack that's really a
puzzling evidence show or part of one in disguise as an hour of slack. It's tricky
because puzzling evidence show is two hours long. The hour of slack is only one
hour. So we may have to split up this otherwise perfect seamless
hour of slack.
It's called the wisdom.
Ocean of wisdom or whatever it is. Noise anyway.
So, I just wanted to let you know to avoid any confusion. Oh, and at the beginning
of the show, puzzling plays old hour of slack stuff. So really it's an hour of slack disguised
as a puzzling evidence show that was at first disguised as an hour of slack.
Right.
Do you have anything to add to that, Dr. Drummond?
Everyone, please enjoy the show.
I'm glad you enjoyed the show because it was made with love and purity of heart.
Everyone.
Merry Christmas, everyone.
And happy Valentine's Day.
If it weren't for the KPFA Puzzling Evidence Show, Puzzling Evidence, Dr. Howell, and sometimes
Dr. Philo Drummond.
If it weren't for such as they and the Einstein Secret Orchestra Swamp Radio and WCSB Cleveland
why this show would take place and the stuff sent in by all the wonderful subgeniuses,
well I guess it would be a pretty boring show.
Yeah.