from PR news in Washington I'm still getting powerful shocks alongside interstate 10 this
morning a decision that sparked a string of protests on Wall Street 80 10 5 26 24 2 3 17
President Obama says this is PR news a top Taliban leader could be a shift Pakistani
officials confirmed that peer news is odd PR is odd Hugh Johnson chief economist at Johnson
Ellington advisors says analysts thought 36,000.7 percent instead of the 50,000.19 percent
analysts had predicted but these numbers don't include people who have stopped looking for PR news
yeah we're slack being a guy that Bob smoked every day
and you know and knowing my nature I know what the deal is and if I ask for Bob's forgiveness
at that last minute if I ask for Bob you know to to save me I can get in still blessed to see who
comes in the name of the Lord every cathedral has its dead wizard Bob knows how many popes are there
there's always like some body part that's a shrine that people pray yeah they keep bones and oh yeah
oh yeah they got to have their pieces there must have been a huge business and body pieces of
saints it's right there that Bob's head bro holy shit yeah yeah you'll
get we want to drop to your knees just see the amount of affectation and the amount of elaborate
sort of mind fucking that went into getting people to believe and that's why stuff like
that could always work man on an educated populace particularly you know when when the origins of
this all because you're talking about people going wow it's so big Bob must be behind this
of course weird reverence from morbid fascination yeah like that's the truth that is the greatest
if you can truly realize your own divinity in this lifetime real treat yourself with some goddamn
difference yeah yeah I mean the weed in a big way yes better than that fucking realize your own
divinity in this lifetime get paid to be you in this life and you're not boys
because we're gonna fucking die we're all fucked so you can choose to be fucked or you could just
fucking fight the fucking ghetto fucking death camp as hard as you can like no saying you can't
be prepared for some shit but it's like getting all that out of sorts about like an event that
hasn't even occurred that's it that's it like you know it's a dream it's yeah it's your head yeah it's
a fiction I mean yes there's financial it's a fiction but you know because I'm watching these
puppets heading toward the furnace man Bob was Bob was Bob will always be a huge business and
mind fucking Bob's head treat yourself with some goddamn Bob blessed to see who comes in the dead
wizard hey Waldo time to get up I'm making sausage sausage that's right Waldo sausage and eggs hey is
this gonna be one of those songs with lots of soft
more exceptional innuendo you bet it is Waldo are you ready you bet I am well here we go oh boy
cock cock doodle do the band on the corner says cock-a-doodle-doo when the clouds roll away and
the sun peeks through sing a song a cock-a-doodle-doo grandpa's really getting out of hand
fussing and complaining about his prostate gland but he still packs a stiffy with the
veins so blue when the blood comes into his cock cock doodle doodle do the policeman
says cock-a-doodle-doo when the clouds roll away and the sun shines through everybody cock-a-doodle-doo
Willie Johnson's on the slab for an appendectomy Willie's feeling nervous cause with one little
slip you can jump on the tip of a cock cock doodle do the nurses laugh and sing cock-a-doodle-doo when
the patients wake up and the surgery's through everybody cock-a-doodle-doo
hey Waldo let's go pick up some groceries I'll get the car keys yeah I could sure use some
zucchini let's get a box of those Jimmy Dean corn dogs aren't you gonna make cucumber salad
pushing our cart at the grocery store these prices are high I'll tell you that's for sure
yeah the cabbage and taters make a mighty fine stew when we throw them in the salty potter
cock cock doodle doodle the grocer man laughs and says cock-a-doodle-doo when he wraps it all up in
a bag for you sing a song a cock-a-doodle-doo grandma shops for garters at the five and ten
cent store the store clerk likes to barter cause he knows that granny's such a naughty little horse
cock cock doodle doodle the store clerk likes to sing cock-a-doodle-doo when the shades roll down
and the day is through everybody cock-a-doodle-doo ah bonjour monsieur comment allez-vous qu'est-ce
que vous avez pour moi de 80 sous j'ai des haricots blancs et du saucisson je ferai un cassoulet ah si c'est bon
co co cocorico monsieur au coin du cocorico con le soleil jetez un coup d'oeil à vous
riez du cock-a-doodle-doo
the milkman asks any eggs today everybody cock-a-doodle-doo
so um uh anyway let me crack and um
uh uh pink penis stop your pee um it it makes everything better
um and so i recommend you connect with goodies at the
power with honey block shop and pick up any of the money you would like to
buy anything um i'll let you know all those details about overall world
condition as you see um you probably can do it without the cool Pi 365
ordinance when by the way marina let's start many hours later into formal practice yeah marina
Yes, dear friends, it's so beautiful.
A little collage there by Reverend Heart Ignition.
This is one of those X-rated internet-only episodes, obviously.
Number 1,331.5 to triple X, in fact.
Cock-a-doodle-doo was by the Rudy Schwartz Project
from the great new album The Year They Switched to Cornmeal.
A Rudy Schwartz Project, friends.
Links on the subgenius.com radio page.
Before that, a collage by a new guy,
Reverend Dr. Royal Decapitator from La Forge, Wisconsin.
And we'll be hearing a lot more of his work.
The El Queso All-Stars did the title music,
and Leemur did that PR news.
And more to come tonight.
We will...
probably go over 60 minutes this time,
because who cares?
This isn't for radio like most episodes.
And now, Captain Beefheart and Frank Zappa
in a piece from 1959, believe it or not.
Lost in a Whirlpool, a very rare cut,
followed by the 180 G's.
The 180 G's.
Who cover songs by Negative Land,
in this case, the Casey Kasem U2 intro remix,
Praise Bob, etc.
There's a big brown fish
Lookin' at me
He ain't got no eyes
How could that motherfucker possibly see?
Ooh, baby, baby
I'm gonna be afraid he's gonna touch me
I've lost in a whirlpool
Ooh, I can't even see
And I've lost in a whirlpool
One, two, three, four.
Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm.
And now, we're up to our longest dedication.
And this one is about kids and pets, a situation we can all understand, whether we have kids
or pets or neither.
Uh huh.
Hmm.
It's from a man in Cincinnati, Ohio.
Here's what he writes.
Dear Casey, this may seem to be a strange dedication request, but I'm quite sincere.
It'll mean a lot if you play.
Recently, there was a dad in our family.
He was a little dog named Snuggle.
Little dog named Snuggle.
But he was most certainly a part of the company.
Start again.
Coming out of the record.
Play the record, okay?
Please.
You can't get on the rhythm to the rhythm.
I'm on the rhythm.
You're the son of a bitch.
That's the letter U and the number two.
The four-man band is Adam Blaine on bass.
Larry Mullen on drums.
Dave Evans, nickname the Edron.
Ooh, this is bullshit.
Nobody cares.
He's passed off from Franklin.
Who gives a shit?
Oh, yeah.
Just a lot of what you can have, so don't take any shit.
I'm sure, for sure.
You guys don't know where it's at.
You don't know shit about it.
This is bullshit.
Sounds like he's portable.
I'm sure.
This is abortion through bitchy putty.
Rap music now.
Oh, you can't get a hold of me
Your little fucking twerp cocksuck
Fuck you
So can we find out
We want your blood
Here we go with the shit
Trying to find him again
When we find him
You've got to have him found
Couldn't find your fucking asshole
If your fucking butt wasn't connected to it
But your fucking body's on this land
You can't find shit
I want a bastard, definitely
I'm sick of the fucking phone
You ever found anybody
Anywhere, anytime
You never have, you've got a correct address
Right on description
Or a call, nothing
You've got some fucking bullshit info
You haven't done shit with him
Couldn't find you yet
If I need a first time
When was the first time, huh?
When was the first time?
Hey, I told you about his address
And what it looks like
And all that fucking information
You've got to have him found
Goddamn, got somebody there
And I don't know who
Go ahead and get all that shit out of you
Why don't you go over there
And knock on his fucking door, man
Think you know where he's at
And all this shit
See you when you come out of the temple
Goddamn numbers, man
It's impossible to make those transitions
Then you've got to go into somebody's time
Goddammit, if we can't come out of the low record
You don't understand it
Why you got to go into somebody's time
Why we doing these instrumentals
Cause we got to
I don't understand it
This is also nothing new
Well, we found something
And it's really there
Somebody find out the goddamn answer
In the 50s, they considered it vulgar
And despicable to have songs like
Teach Me Tonight
Let's Do It by Cole Porter
All of you by Cole Porter
These were considered euphemisms
For something dirty
Who gives a shit
Some vulgar dirty ass
Diddly shit, diddly shit
The Kingston Trio sang a song
That used the word damn
It was banned on the radio
Goddammit
In the 60s, it was a song called
Louie Louie
Goddamn
It was played upside backwards
Every way they could play it
Looking for the dirty message
Goddamn
Never found the dirty message
The FCC brought it
Oh fuck
In the 70s, people went through the same period
Looking for the dirtiness of the song
Say
I
What
I really don't think the Titanic message is this
Go out and walk your fine new man
No goes
You better be prepared to meet your maker
I
I'm after your ass boy
Sounds like one of those gay babe boys
No goes
You're gonna need to meet me at Moline and the Monument
I wanna personally meet you
You'll see me
I'll be wearing a bow tie
A red and white baseball cap
Says KBC's Potterpots on it
Can't miss the sun
Oh it sounds like the real Fancy Dressen
I don't even have a hat
I'm gonna whoop your fuckin' ass
I want a goddamn concert at Ebony
To find out what record it is
So fuck it up, it won't record
Every time I do a goddamn death dedication
It's the last goddamn time
I want somebody to use his fuckin' brain
To come out with a goddamn record that it's all that it tells us to know
And I gotta talk about a fucking dog's eye
Hey guys, it's the 70s
And there's so much shit
Stupid shit
Who knows
Who knows what the fuck's gonna get done
What's the point
Of a fucking punk
Punk
This is American Top 4
Right here on the radio station you grew up on
With Music Radio 1384
Oh fuck you, Liz
Fuck you too, Richard
Yeah, I'd love to, wouldn't you
I'm such a nice kid, though
The 180Gs on C-Land Records, NegativeLand.com
NegativeLand without the E
There's some guys in Detroit, The 180Gs, who do covers of Negative Land experimental collage songs
That particular cover contains so many underground radio trash songs
or inside jokes you can't even imagine.
By the way, the negative land originally got hold of that Casey Kasem outtake
from a member of the Church of the Subgenius.
Now, some good taste from Heart Ignition on pussy taste,
followed by the song Can't Keep a Secret by Nervous Energy
live at the Devotional of 2010.
We've got three very strong flavors.
Pussy.
But I need something from you to satisfy my sweet.
Quote, quote, action.
I'm totally fine with strong flavors like purple and grass.
Is that true?
Please.
But getting them fresh is obviously the best way to go, right?
Well, if you find them at the market and they're still on the stem,
that's one of the best ways to buy them.
You know that they're fresh.
Pussy.
And they are bizarre looking.
It looks like a cabbage for most of the year
and gets this long stem on it with this kind of cabbage-like,
head on the top that starts popping out.
What kind of a vagina do you have, darling?
Squirt.
My life was ended way too short
And now I'm standing here in the pearly gates court
Right in front of a brown wall
Head boy
He tells me to call him Leroy
My life is a book
He holds in his hands
My final judgment he sternly demands
Remember the time
You pissed on your cousin for no good reason
You were 17 but you shit your pants
Remember the time
You jerked up in the corner while watching a three-way
You told a bunch of people there was some dude in the woods trying to molest you
And there really wasn't a dude there at all
And everyone went out looking for him
And of course they couldn't find him because he wasn't really there
But everyone went anyway
And you know what they did find?
They found a fucking bee's nest
And everyone got stung
Because of you
Not very cool, bro
I knew I recognized this kid from somewhere
But where could I find him?
Where could it be?
Hmm
Perhaps a series of children's literature
Started in 1963 by author Donald J. Sobel
And then briefly a 1989 television series for kids on HBO directed by savage Steve Holland
Better known as the director of Better Off Dead and One Crazy Summer
Yeah, maybe that's...
That's how I knew the guy
Can't keep a secret, can't keep a secret
Can't keep a secret from Encyclopedia Brown
Keep a secret, can't keep a secret
Why should I let you in?
For being ridiculous and admitting sin
I should send you to hell
With vermin and swine and R.L. Stine
But at least it made me great
At least it made me great
It at real
An wielder
At least it made me great
Can't keep a secret, can't keep a secret
Can't keep a secret from Encyclopedia Brown
Keep a secret, can't keep a secret
Keep a secret from Encyclopedia Brown. Keep a secret you can't keep a secret.
Can't keep a secret from Encyclopedia Brown. Keep a secret you can't keep a secret.
Can't keep a secret from Encyclopedia Brown.
From PR News in Washington, I'm considering a request
for tens of billions more dollars to be deployed to Afghanistan.
Afghanistan. Federal authorities in New York generated $20 million in illegal profits and
then detonated a suicide vest, killing a prominent turd. But apparently the turd is one of the
wealthiest men in America. The complaint says $7 billion. Peer News. On Wall Street 399957,
the federal budget deficit is $4. This is PR News. The Department of Justice posted
disappointing quarterly results. Justice Department profit fell 2 billion percent
from a year ago. The military says this is PR. I didn't consider that sexual abuse, but
I know that I did get involved in abusing some. One of them is Michael.
I knew it was wrong when he tried to get my bone. But he'd beg and beg and plead all the
while on his knees. I told him I preferred vagina over the producer of diarrhea. But
I don't know what to do right now. Cause I'm in love with a Catholic priest.
He's got me down on my knees. Catholic has a new meaning. I'm in love with a Catholic
priest. He's got me down on my knees. Catholic has a new meaning. I asked him why I had to
lick his asshole. He said the Bible says so. He lured me in with gum. Then he baptized
me with his cum.
I took a shower. I could see. He leaves me feeling undermined. And I say at my age, Look
at this old year's
up Promise I 힘. I'm not saying I complaining. I took a wide it gets enough stinks off my
new meaning
he converted
me
where it's dirty
he converted me
alright
where it's
dirty
he converted
me alright
he said
I've been a bad boy
as he punished me
with ash joy
he converted me
alright
I'm in love with the Catholic
priest
he's got me down on my knees
Catholic
has a new meaning
I'm in love
with the Catholic priest
he's got me down
on my knees
Catholic has a new
meaning
he's
a這個
Pastor
That makes my body
and I feel
I live
on the edge
I see
world
in me
all over
I'm healed
Hip Hip
Hey
you have to fuck life
in the gallbladder
that song
I'm in love with a catholic
priest was by
dead body
sectus
not s-e-x
s-e-c-t-s
dead body sects
sent to us a year ago and I don't know
much about the artist dead body sects
look it up
next from the evolution
control committee and ministry of slack
with slander bob
recorded live jamming
at 14x day drill
at wisteria in southern
ohio the subgenius
annual music and butt fucking
vomiting and shitting
festival
this
DJ Jam tonight
Spotting me a tender pain
But there you are coming baby
Don't you want to forgive me
Don't you want to hand me
You gotta do much better
If you're gonna dance with me tonight
You gotta put your jet black
I don't think they're ready for that
Dilly for no more
Dilly
We don't take a shit and care
It's time for take off
We're ready for this jam
My body's too booty
This shit's for you baby
I don't think they're ready for this jam
My body's too booty
This shit's for you baby
I'll show you every chance
When I whip up my hips
Just listen to the track
I'm hoping you can hear
All the jelly that I have
Now let's cut the rug
While we shake off
I'm about to break out
Ain't time
Going home
When your hips
Let my back
To me
My hair's on my arm
My heart's hot
Hot dog
Slamming good
Cool the light
I found a club
Gonna short it
Blow your skin
Can't you handle
Handle this
I don't take much better
If you're gonna dance with me tonight
Gotta put your pepper
Oops, I didn't realize I didn't
It came out of my crotch
My vagina is
Is this cocktail of disappointment?
Oh, I hate that
I love the smell of semen
What's going on in that bed?
Thanks to Heart Ignition
for that short bit
and to Evolution Control Committee
Ministry of Slack
and Slander Bob at 14X Day
for the jam before that.
Now, back to X Day Drill
for a segment on stage
with Dr. Howell,
Dr. Philo Drummond,
and yours truly,
Reverend Ivan Stang.
When you picked up
your program book,
you may have noticed
these papers that show
that have blanks
as if you're supposed
to fill them in.
The gorillas and demons
in your life,
have you ever felt beset
by an inner gorilla
that was making you feel small
or an inner demon
that made you want to go
shoplifting or be mean
or whatnot?
A refugee from a gorilla loving.
inside your head on this
and later in the festival
when we run out of material
we'll use yours
and read from it.
There's also
the What's the Next line
for senile dementia patients.
Thank you.
It starts with famous
fairy tale or nursery rhymes
and the poor old person
is encouraged to remember
the second part of the nursery rhyme.
Of course, subgeniuses,
half of them never heard
those nursery rhymes to begin with
so they fill it in
with their own ideas of
what happened to the little girl
who had a little curl.
Right in the middle of her forehead.
Well, you know,
most subgeniuses have also
not even been in a nursery
even to purchase a potted palm.
Is that the same one
with the necklace made of pearl?
No.
Right, there was a little girl
who had a little curl
and on top of that
a necklace made of pearl.
That's the kind of thing
people...
That's how it goes.
Georgie Porgy pudding and pie.
I'm sure you can finish that one.
Stuck a red hot poker
in his left eye.
Yeah.
Wee Willie Winkle
runs through the town.
Wee Willie Winky
runs through the town
upstairs and downstairs
in his nightgown.
No, but...
Well, I come from San Francisco.
Al's gonna play it straight.
There's nothing...
What are you saying?
You're gonna play it straight.
With his tiny penis
made up like a clown.
You should give a good alternate verse.
Peeping through the window,
squinting through the lock.
Are all the children in their beds?
Because now it's eight o'clock.
You better get tied in your bed
because I'm gonna grab your cock.
Yeah, he had the ox sound to work with.
Back off.
Wait a minute.
I can't use this stuff on Hour of Slack.
That's right.
Remember, the seven dirty sacred words.
This is an Hour of Slack, right?
This is gonna be used later on the radio.
There was a little woman
who lived in a shoe
and her husband had a fetish for poo.
But you could...
Hush, little baby.
Don't say a word.
Now, you gotta have turd
at the end of the next round.
Well, no. Only...
I'm gonna have to pay for your doctor, Trevor.
It's important.
Little boy blue, come blow your horn.
The sheep's in the meadow.
Who's getting the corn?
That was so easy to...
Diddle, diddle.
Little child that looked after the sheep.
Diddle that dumpling, John.
Daddy's gonna humbly...
My son.
Diddle, diddle dumpling, my son John.
Diddle, diddler and chicken diddler.
The trick of picking chicken...
It's an old saying.
Picking what chicken to pick.
Diddle the chicken with a chicken feather.
And this is how you use the divine gift of speech?
Yeah. Bob gave us the gift of tongues.
And this is what we use.
Yes, the gift of tongues.
Just a tongue each other.
Speaking in tongues.
I always used to enjoy a good tongue sandwich.
We used to eat that back when I was a boy.
I don't know who does now.
I prefer a tongue bath.
They're good with horseradish.
The sandwich, not the bath.
Warning!
The Bible warns against...
The Bible.
The Bible is bold.
We are believing the prayer of morabilities as it is of evil.
Fast and bulbous.
How much of...
Expect.
That's right.
It is the business of the future to be...
in...
Al spareeen.
True.
And one to die for.
There is no other...
Cu...
San...
In...
My eyes бу...
Fascination.
Ahcall, at most, to right...
Guido...
Tonight, you...
My friend...
We're the ingredients for the New Worldamos
and throw you off the balcony, you stinking little cocksucker.
If you don't hurry to tell me where and what's left of that fucking dope
that you and that other fucking weasel have been slamming into your dope-fiend fucking vase
during your fucking convalescence.
God, Mr. Swindler.
Jesus, what a fucking stink!
Not to mention you killed a fucking chink courier,
and the headache over that I'm going to have with fucking woo
if I ever get this fucking stench out of my fucking nostril.
I just shit myself, sir.
I'm saying it now before the smell gets you.
Bob!
Bob.
You know, there was this gangster dude.
He was a gangster, and he was telling everybody,
man, I'm a gangster, G.
I'm a gangster.
Follow me on Twitter. How the hell is you a gangster and you got internet access?
Can someone please help me out here? How is you a gangster and you updating your Twitter?
How's that gonna go? Man, I just shot four people, dawg.
Man, I just raped a bitch. I'm selling this crack, nigga.
I got that weed, son. If you need some bootleg DVDs, look me up, man.
Stop with the Twitter. No one gives a damn.
In just a moment, tonight's story, but first, a message from America.
The whole country's talking about Mr. Carl Moore of Kingston, Pennsylvania.
It's still as new-looking as when I bought it, but you'd never know it to look at my 54-inch paint job.
But first, a brief message from America.
From coast to coast, more funny. More in Comps, more in Performanford, and more in the coast.
But only through Midship Ride and the fine rubber front seat. You'll agree, more funny.
Only by smooth ability. Once you've priced, how much agree?
Vogel. Yeah. Uh, Vogel.
Good night.
Mr. Carl says.
Mr. Rooster says.
To the cat.
Here's a duck.
The sheep.
Here's a chicken.
Money works best inessional.
And I said to Mr. Rooster, you never live a day with getting more meat than you're needed to deliberately keeping on.
I said to him, if I use any 500 quid you were gonna have to pay an all year pension or soqué, he'll feed you to whatever dining table can give him air.
He said, There's no letter for this.
The business difficult for you.
The business for a guy that's got to come up here and tell the truth.
Come up here and tell the truth.
Come up here.
From PR News in Washington, I'm turning ugly.
President Obama's plan for 5.6 million homos is running into trouble.
Sales were down 2%.
But 902,000 homos can't deal with all the PR news, at least temporarily.
At last, check on Wall Street, 2010, 5-4, 2287, 1435.
Exiled former Haitian President Jean-Bertrand Arras.
Arras says he's ready to set up roadblocks out of corpses and rocks.
Even worse.
This is PR News.
But, but wait, wait.
There's hope.
We are not hopeless.
We have hope.
Because if you spend $30, just $30.
How much?
$30.
Think about it.
You spent more than that in the dealer's room today.
If you spend $30, you will be saved.
Not only will you just be spared the torment of being burned alive for weeks on end,
you will also get to go to the saucers with the sex goddesses or sex gods of that church.
And if all you've ever been dreaming about doing is missing Tracy Lawrence,
you can have that.
Whatever it is that you want, you can have for $30.
And the great thing about it is it doesn't just apply to you.
So you know that great chick that you've been banging?
Because if she doesn't have $30 paid for her, she's going to burn too.
Because everyone will burn.
So what happens then?
Well, you better pay your girls $30.
Because then you can share a saucer.
And you can share a sex goddess.
And guys, you know you've thought about that.
You and your girl share on a sex goddess.
You know you want it to.
But let's say maybe you're not into that, you know?
Because I don't care what you're into.
Maybe you're into, you know, your dog Fluffy.
If that's what you're into, that's fine.
But if you don't pay your $30 for Fluffy, Fluffy burns too.
And if you're willing to let Fluffy burn, I don't know.
Maybe we should get Fluffy.
Maybe we should get you to go hang out with Mike Vick.
So this is what we're here to tell you about.
I know you want to see stuff in that.
The truth of the matter is that they have to register in a while.
So you guys think.
It could be worse.
It could.
Why don't you play some music?
You're a DJ, right?
You're a DJ like every DJ there ever was.
Who's convinced that his...
His mix is the hottest thing ever.
And it will be the hottest thing ever when the X's come and he burns.
Oh, really?
Really?
You know what?
You guys are nothing like some genius hecklers.
I gotta tell you that.
I really do.
I want...
It's like, I'm going to give Bob a gift.
Because he's so funny.
Yeah.
That's so fucking weird.
Yeah, right?
Oh, it's fucked up.
It's fucked up.
Oh, you did that?
And what?
Oh, yeah, sure.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Dude, I was in.
I drank the Kool-Aid.
From the dark.
Alert.
And the end.
Bob.
It's Bob.
And...
Alert.
Please do that sex with me.
And...
Alert.
Fuck Bob Dobbs by Reverend Heart Ignition.
Before that, the Kool-Aid clip was from Reverend Royal Decapitator.
And the live rant with a big crowd was Priestess Pisces at Dragon Con
preaching about the church and Tracy Lords and Pinks
against a tide of the latter, actually.
Lee Murr did PR News.
The children's book was Evolution Control Committee and Ministry of Slack at 14X Day.
And other collages were by, going backwards in time,
Reverend Decapitator the Large,
Reverend Sweetness McGee of Ministry of Slack,
Jason Myrek,
and the nursery rhymes business was Dr. Hal Philo and I at 12X Day,
or one of those X Days.
The background music, by the way, right now is from Devo,
the musical-only tracks from their latest album, Without the Vocals.
And now, a segment about titties.
Oh, and thanks to Reverend Abnorm Nihill for that Devo.
Thank you.
This segment about titties, I mean breasts or teats,
starts with Radio Synesthesia from WCSB Cleveland,
right after Hour of Slack.
Two songs about titties will follow by Rodney Carrington and the Psychoskeletons.
You know, one of my memories of, actually one of my memories of Chaz,
is probably,
I have a lot of memories hearing the Hour of Slack tonight.
Stuff from 2002.
Yeah, that was a real emotion-packed one, if you were...
And, you know, 2002 was actually the first year I went to X Day.
Wow.
But one of my fond memories of Chaz was him,
he showed me like this live footage of a Skinner concert from the old days,
and it was outdoors, and he like pointed to the front row in front of the stage
with all these young topless chicks jiggling their titties back and forth,
and he said,
he said,
that right there, that is what rock and roll was all about.
Praise God.
Hey, I'll reveal to you the punchline,
the ultimate end sentence, you might say,
of my rant at Starwood to the pagans,
was, I actually borrowed this from our friend Mr. Sister,
but the line was,
you know, people ask me what I really believe.
Stang, you must believe in Satan.
We know you don't believe in magic,
but what do you believe in?
Well, I believe that I would really enjoy
crawling across an ocean of titties on my belly.
Okay, I might like that too.
I had women were coming up to me all day today,
quoting that to me.
They'd like this wheelchair.
They love it.
And I would love it.
And when that day comes,
that dream will come true,
the ocean of titties,
the bare belly crawling across it.
My friend, anything you can imagine,
anything there.
I promise it's true.
Yes, dear friends.
Mr. Sister, what have you started?
Oh, shit.
What'd you say?
Love you.
I love you.
I don't know if I love you,
but you sound like somebody I could love.
You know, drunk and horny.
And I love that.
Oh, it seems to me this whole world's gone crazy.
There's too much hate and killing going on.
But when I see the bare chest of a woman,
my worries and my problems
are all gone.
No one thinks of fighting
when they see a topless girl.
Maybe if you would show yours too,
we could save the world.
Show them to me.
Unclasp your bra and set those puppies free.
They'd look all right.
They'd look a lot better without that sweater, baby.
I'm Ceriola Gray.
Baby, you got two fun facts.
God bless you, woman.
Show them to me.
I don't care if they don't match
or one's bigger than the other.
You can show me one,
and I'll imagine the other.
Even if you're really old,
there's nothing wrong.
Don't be sad, your boobs ain't bad.
They're just a little long.
Show them to me.
Lift up your shirt and let the whole world see.
Just this wrong.
Show your clothes and a happy man I'll be.
And if you got dos chichis,
which is Spanish for two titties,
and I think we just love two Spanish titties.
Show them to me.
I've met a lot of them,
but never one I've hated.
Even if you've had thirteen kids
and you think they look deflated,
there's no such thing as a bad breast.
I believe this much is true.
If you're a big boy,
I'm a big fat man,
I'm a titty fan,
and I'd love to see yours too.
Show them to me.
Just like the girls gone wild on TV.
Just lean back and show your act,
and I'll be in ecstasy.
If you got two cassavas,
show them to me.
Come on baby, let me see
all the world live in harmony.
It'll do you good,
and it'll give me what
will make history.
If you love your country.
I'm gonna say it one more time.
I said if you love your country.
Dallas, Texas,
do you love your country?
And you stand your ass up
and show them big old titties to me.
Ah, woo, boo, boo, woo, woo, woo.
My God.
I'd like to shake your daddy's hand.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
These tits were made for milking.
Milk right in your face.
One of these days,
these tits are gonna milk right in your face.
in your face.
I'm glad you
respect me
enough to
call my bluff.
Chip off
the old shoulder.
A3
calls lovely.
I'm glad
you respect
me enough
to call my
bluff.
Cute
curiosity.
The
present has
ended.
Here
is a poem
for any women
who may be
listening right
now.
Don't bang the cable
guy. Not even if
he's a Greek man
or a Portuguese.
Geese don't bang
the cable guy.
Not even if he's a swirly
Italian or a
Spaniard. Don't
bang the cable guy.
But if it's a black dude,
go for it.
Keep me out
of your
revolution.
Cause today's the day
the teddy bears have their
picnic.
Oh, and what
teddy bears. That one,
meat on meat anti-manifesto
was by the Psychoskeletons.
And the previous song,
Show Them To Me,
was by a
Rodney Carrington.
A Carrington with a C
and two R's, which we
copped from a YouTube
video. Next, a little
story from Reverend Sweetness
McGee's razor.
And then some live
14X Day Drill
double teaming.
Tell me a story.
Blood and blood.
Tell me a story and
blood.
A story?
Sure, I would be glad to tell you a story.
Then wash your hands with soap.
Right at this minute,
the finger of death
is pointing at their little family circle.
And the sad thing about it is
they do not know it.
I'm sick.
Got to be careful that I don't hurt it.
Then wash your hands with soap.
Is it a lie?
What on earth?
There. You'll die.
Music
зав broadcast
Get that sharp butcher knife and hold it in the fire.
Why?
Hold it in the fire, Betty.
We have to get it hot until the germs are burned off.
Then wash your hands with soap.
Betty, give me the knife.
Now hold still, Billy, and don't try to pull away.
I've got to do it.
There's no other way.
Die, die, die, die.
Is he dead, Mother?
Yes, he's dead.
He's dead, poor fellow.
Put my mouth on the wound and suck out all the blood.
Now do you see why I told you to wash your hands with soap?
Yes, I do now, now that it's too late.
Then wash your hands with soap right now.
This is the legend of an unsung subgenius folk hero.
Some of you who have been in the chats might remember it.
It is the legend of Zappy McPeepy.
Zappy McPeepy meant no offense when he took a pee on his neighbor's fence.
But his neighbor had grown tired of the stinky stains and electrified that fencing chain.
Zappy McPeepy got quite a jolt as his urine turned to thunderbolts.
And everybody says, but nobody ever looks, that Zappy McPeepy's wieners cooked.
With his fence-pissing days well in the past, some children came to him and asked,
Old Zappy, is your wiener burnt and crisp?
Then Zappy's smile made a funny.
And out from his pants a burnt sausage fell that made the chillin' scream and yell.
And with the kids off his lawn and the wind at his back, Zappy picked it up and he had a snack.
Old Zappy had a secret he never did tell.
But if you stood near enough his house, you'd smell some sausage crisping in the pan.
That Zappy always was a mischievous man.
Zappy's dick didn't have much girth or punch.
But to hear some tell it did have crunch.
That Zappy McPeepy does get around.
With a grin and a shuffle and a faint sizzling sound.
Old Zappy McPeepy meant no offense when he whizzed upon his neighbor's fence.
But the thunder left up to his dick and Zappy, somehow, he made it stick.
Morose or Dr. Holocaust?
And the drugs they give you are so powerful that you wake up going,
I went, where am I?
Cleveland.
Why?
Yeah.
Bob.
You're so vulnerable in a weird way.
It is so fucking insanely powerful drug.
I can't date these humans.
They're disgusting with their skin and their, their lives.
But they have this weird like thousand yard, you know, post acid stare that just burns into your fucking soul.
Yeah.
They are so touching.
Woodward.
Thank you.
Friends, that was the Evolution Control Committee as redone by the
DJ Two Beans, who is also heard in the background.
He took the piece that was recorded by Evolution Control Committee at 14X Day,
recorded by Frodo Shaw, and did more to it.
That's all I know.
That's DJ Two Beans in the background.
And now, what?
DJ Two Beans, who is also heard in the background.
Open your mind.
The human centipede.
Priestess Pisces
and Saint Byron Werner
try to figure out how to end the show
and whether I'll need my ride from the station to bed.
Praise Bob.
I think that Stang is going to have to escape ever so briefly
unless, of course...
Unless my ride is listening to the radio.
But what are the odds?
Right, right.
Actually, yeah, there are some odds against it.
Oh!
Oh, no!
I'm sorry, somebody should keep talking.
Somebody should keep talking while we're on the...
No, no, everything's going everywhere
and there's...
But the workmen are here
and they'll put everything back in place in the proper order.
They'd better.
That's what they always say.
And they're going to clean up after they're done, right?
They're spilling stuff all over the place.
They always leave that.
There's a greasy outline where the body fluid soaked into the carpet
because we didn't clean it up right away.
Well, you have to.
And they have to do it every 108 minutes.
Mm-hmm.
I've told...
You know, as far as the cleaning up the blood,
I mean, I don't know, you know?
It's not the blood.
There's some other goo.
I'll tell them where to go.
Excuse me, I have to go tell somebody where to go.
She's really good at that.
She really is.
You know, I usually do that, but it's okay.
That can be done by someone else.
And, oh, look, there are...
You know what?
It only gets worse from here.
Sometimes I don't have to tell people where to go.
I can just kind of raise one finger and show them where to go.
If you're very careful, you can raise one eyebrow,
and that one eyebrow will go up with a look.
Yeah, and the person that had the best eyebrow control,
as far as I'm concerned, is Greta Garbo.
Oh, yeah.
Much better than John Belucci.
I don't even want to mention John Belucci in the same breath,
but I already did, so...
Oh, too late.
What are you going to do?
Too late.
Yeah.
There's a lot of subgeniuses who have the eyebrows.
There's a lot of eyebrow control as well.
You can sort of see it across the room.
Probably not Garbo fans, I'm guessing.
Well, you know, there are some.
I don't know.
I mean, it's a very strange group we are
with our different thoughts and different imaginings.
Yeah, they're probably more Gummo fans than they are Garbo fans.
Well, yeah.
I don't mean Gummo Marks either.
Look, he's got Gummo Marks all over him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Gummo was filmed in Ohio.
Typical Ohio neighborhood.
I love Ohio.
There was Groucho film.
I really absolutely adore Ohio.
I have no desire to live there.
I like the part where it's round on the ends, you know?
High in the middle.
High in the middle and round on the ends.
Because my first experience with Ohio was Youngstown,
it sort of burned it up for me.
I understand that they've got a couple of cows in Ohio,
somewhere.
Isn't it the state bird?
No, that's the Buckeye.
Ah, yeah, you're right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I still think that's a very high price for an eyeball.
I find the Buckeye is interesting because it's not edible, is it?
I don't even know.
Eyeballs are edible.
I don't think it's edible.
And it's like worshipped as if it were Jesus' nut.
Hmm.
Ah, is it Sunday already?
Yeah, actually it is.
It is.
It is indeed Sunday already.
And since it's Sunday, we're in church here at WREK and sort of in...
The Church of the Left Nut, is that what it is?
No, this is part of Bob's slack time.
The Right Nut.
The Right Nut for the job.
Right.
Yeah.
The Left Nut to just...
The Left Nut...
I don't got anything for that one.
You know...
Left Nut was left.
There's a series of head and nut jokes.
That I just can't run with.
I just can't...
I don't have anything for it.
It's best.
It's really...
It's best that way.
Well, I was thinking that you could show a triple bill of the movie's monkey...
The monkey's movie, Head, with the Blaxploitation film, Shaft, and the Barbara Streisand film, Nuts.
And have a pretty good program there.
It'd be a long showing, I'm sure.
It would be like five, six hours.
Well, you know...
Right now, ladies and gentlemen, I know you're thinking about it, but mashing that up would be just fine.
I think you better do it in that order, though.
Right, right, right, right.
You don't want to have nuts first.
Well, it depends.
I mean, if you start out that way...
Why do people pick on me like this?
I don't know.
I was going to ask you.
Yeah, no, Charlie Brown used to say that.
You know, who walked in the classroom cool and slow, who called the teacher Daddy-O?
Charlie Brown, he's a clown.
I think...
Why is everybody always picking on me?
From PR News in Washington, I'm growing more violent as the FBI investigates the attempted Bloody Cock block.
Troops fired rubber at crowds of protesters near a cock park.
Authorities have been demanding cock for weeks, but the demonstrators want to be shot in the cock, possibly by a renegade army officer.
PR's agents fanned out across three search warrants this morning.
The investigation has led agents to the PR News.
Home of the 101st Division.
Hawaii's governor has signed a bill saying this is PR.
Hawaii's state officials say they can ignore PR News.
Today, the Labor Department dropped by a fourth to a seasonally adjusted 4.9 per 4,000.
At least 41 people arrested in the riots that broke out after PR.
Like.