Oh, I hate to take you out of that one,
but we've got things we have to do and say, dear friends.
This is the number one thing to say.
This is KNON 89.3 FM in Dallas, Texas.
You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery
which reaches from the inner mind to...
The subgenius.
Our house.
Watch.
Welcome to Temple.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
Welcome to Hour of Slack, number 150.
Yeah, we've done 150 of these shows now,
and to celebrate, I'm not going to talk.
I'm not going to say a word, except on tape, a lot of that.
But at the same time, this is going to be another one of those introductory shows
where you can tape this and play it to your friends,
and relatives, and they won't think you're as crazy
as if you played them last week's show or next week's show.
Some...
I get interviewed by people out of town and out of time
if they're not out of town.
So we're going to play some old interview tapes
and a lot of music, a lot of new subgenius music,
Bob songs, and you'll find out just what this is all about, won't you?
In the meantime,
you can call for information.
Call the Will Adobes.
He's still here at...
Insert local number here.
If you must.
This music in the background is Danny Elfman's score for Beetlejuice.
My favorite movie music.
I'm a composer now, I think.
And now we go from the Supreme Court to a different form of court.
This court you might call the Church of the Subgenius.
You might ask yourself, what do you mean by Church of the Subgenius?
Well, we sent our own Bill Cates out to find out, and this is what he learned.
Okay, we're here with the...
Reverend Ivan Stang, who is the...
Well, what would you call yourself in relation to this church?
I am the sacred scribe of the Church of the Subgenius,
a mere servant of our guru and saint of sales, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Praise his sweet name.
Now, for those of our listeners not familiar with just who the Church of the Subgenius and J.R. Bob Dobbs are,
could you briefly give us a capsule description?
Well, the Church...
The Church of the Subgenius is what you might call a disorganized religion,
or you might say a non-organization for non-joiners,
for people who wouldn't be caught dead joining anything.
It is a church, but it's a church for sinners, disbelievers, or people who believe anything.
Mutants, misfits, you know, your class clowns, your blasphemers, and talk show hosts.
And who is J.R. Bob Dobbs?
He's the...
The guru.
Bob Dobbs is the...
Technically, he's called the high E-pop.
Actually, he's the very salesman of the gods, that man, if he is indeed a man,
who has come to keep the conspiracy of the normals from buying your slack away from you.
You see, preachers have to do more than just lay people,
and Bob Dobbs, I think, is here to bring...
Slack to the slackless.
And if you...
Friends, if you don't know what slack is, then it's probably too late.
You should probably just shut your radio off,
because you're going to find out how much you've been missing.
Okay, what is slack?
Well, if you have to ask, you'll never know.
As the Hell's Angels once put it,
those who know don't say, and those who say don't know,
which leads me to wonder why they said it, actually.
Slack is, well, to compare it to happiness.
Uh, slack makes happiness feel like having your eyes gouged out with a carrot peeler.
It makes the nirvana of the Buddha feel like being buried up to your neck in sand,
waiting for the ants to come and eat your face away.
Or maybe a lawnmower to come mow your head off, perhaps.
Sure, sure.
Hmm.
I've got the recipe for a grandma face sandwich, if you ever need it.
Essentially, what we're doing...
To get serious here,
what we're essentially doing is we're...
The Church of the Subgenius is trying to tempt sinners away from the devil.
Now, what they do and where they go after that is up to them.
But Bob Dobbs is a mighty, mighty man.
Or God.
We're not sure which, and it doesn't really matter.
And he operates out of his skyscraper headquarters in Dallas.
Texas, where I work, in the Bible Belt.
And what we're essentially doing through our magazines, our radio shows, the tapes we sell,
and our new videotape, we're trying to unbuckle the Bible Belt
and get them to sort of drop their pants and make them face their own private desires.
So, friends, if you could just open your heart and bend over,
because Bob's coming.
He's coming.
And he...
And he comes not...
He comes not to forgive your sins.
We leave that to better connected deities.
Bob Dobbs comes and comes again and again to justify your sins, my friends.
To excuse your sins.
To offer you that great excuse that I know you need, my brothers and sisters.
How can you tell?
Oh, there's no way to tell.
Because Bob's coming.
He's sneaking up on you.
Can't you hear him?
Can't you feel him?
One, two, Bob's coming for you.
And Bobby's here.
Jehovah one is Santa, new Messiah.
He's the one who grins and smokes the pipe.
For in a world of darkness...
of danger and despair.
We can go on smiling
because we know that Bob Dobbs
is always there.
And I know that Bob's on my side.
I know it as sure as I'm born.
He will make the proper deal
with the exes' whore.
Then we'll come to meet him
and we'll greet him
and rule forevermore.
Bob is my one true savior.
You can't keep all of the rest.
Looking at his smiling face
helps me when I'm depressed.
For the pinks, I sure feel sorry.
For tomorrow, they'll fry
with all the rest.
Bob has got no real brain
to speak of.
Though his luck has seen him
through the lack.
For all the geniuses
led us down the wrong track.
Least we know a subgenius
won't turn around
and stab us in the back.
The con thinks they have us suckered
but I know that that is a lie.
They're due for a big surprise
from demons from the sky.
Makes me so glad I wised up,
got it sized up.
Hell, I'm a lucky guy.
Bob brought me slack
and that's lots more
than I ever got from the con.
Though I know it's only
because of all those pills
he's on.
Heck, I know he ain't too clever
but whatever he says
I'll do or die.
There's a shining golden city
where the robots live
beneath the central sun's
eternal glare.
And when the saucers come
from space,
to massacre the human race,
I know that we'll find
peace and safety there.
Through the holes in the poles
we will flee.
Sailing down to the lovely
central sea.
Leaving torture, death, and madness
for a land of joy and gladness.
Within the hollow earth
we will be free.
In atomic-powered go-karts
we will roam the land
while the aliens
devour human slaves.
They'll squirm beneath
the master's boot
or roam in packs
in search of loot
while we will laugh
to think that we were saved.
Through the holes in the poles
we will flee.
Sailing down to the lovely
central sea.
Leaving torture, death, and madness
for a land of joy and gladness.
Within the hollow earth
we will be free.
We'll ride in flying submarines
through air and through the sea.
While the aliens destroy
the works of man.
When they leave our blasted world
at last we'll rise again
without a past to implement
our splendid master plan.
Through the holes in the poles
we will flee.
Sailing down to the lovely
central sea.
Leaving torture, death, and madness
for a land of joy and gladness.
Within the hollow earth
we will be free.
We will be free.
Oh yes dear friends.
Go ahead, try to change channels.
You can't do it, can ya?
Oh, Nan,
can I bite in the background?
Says you can't.
And, uh, those last two songs
you heard were, um,
the first one was by
Reverend Orton Nenslow.
Up in Boston.
Praise Reverend Nenslow.
No, actually, the first one
was by Ahmed Fishmonger.
The second one was by Orton Nenslow.
The very last thing you heard
was Orton.
Uh, Ahmed Fishmonger
there at the beginning doing
Uh, Bob
is my one true savior.
Uh, and isn't it true?
I'm gonna go back to, um,
see here,
this is, uh,
that radio show was
Bleepo Abernathy
um,
pretending he didn't know me
doing an interview on
K-Rock, uh,
KRXS, I think it is
in New York.
The biggest station in New York City, how about that, huh?
And this was prime time.
This is what, this is how
we
take advantage of you.
The listener, thank you.
You need my brothers and sisters.
How can you tell, um,
if you are a subgenius?
Well, the easiest way to tell
is by sending, uh,
$20 into the church of the
subgenius sacred post office
box for membership.
Uh, the other way to tell would be
if you're the kind of person who
uh, hates
most normals,
uh, we're looking for people
who love to hate.
That's what I might say.
Although most of us have to, uh,
maintain the illusion that we ourselves
are normal.
We're out to teach people how to exploit
their abnormality, to quit hiding it,
and to, to
actually learn how to make money off of it.
Now, money is not exactly
the same as slack, but, uh,
uh, slack
tends to come a little easier with money.
Now, I remember hearing
somewhere that the church of the subgenius
is actually the only church that
admits it's in it for the money and, and, uh,
in fact pays its taxes
without complaining.
Right. We are the world's first industrial church.
Bob does not believe that, uh,
the public should have to subsidize
religions they may not happen
to believe in, besides which
I doubt seriously if the IRS
would ever let us get away with claiming tax
exempt status. But, uh, those
things aren't, those worldly things
are not important here.
We're, we're discussing,
uh, we're discussing the fact
that people should get out there
and buy that Simon & Schuster
book of the subgenius.
Yes, my friends, the book
of the subgenius and its companion
volume, High Weirdness
by Mail. Now, what is that? No, you're not
supposed to do that. You
can't do that! Don't go
out there and do such a thing.
I'm sorry, we're not, we're not supposed to get to
that part. But,
here's a word from the League
of Women Voters of Dallas.
This is a nation of people.
By the people and
for the
people,
they say. So
exercise your voting right
November 8th.
Your vote is your voice.
The League of Women Voters says
let it be heard on election day
November 8th.
Because otherwise, what do you think's going to
happen? They
will come in.
They will take over.
And do you know who
they are, don't you? They're the ones
you don't like. They're
everyone you never cared
for in your whole
life. And they'll run this whole
country if you don't get out
and vote. I'm not going to say exactly
who they are because I think
you know, don't you?
Would you sing the neighbor's song when you're
with me now?
They're the early risers.
They bomb bombs and they don't aren't. I'm just
singing in the rain. Pungy sticks and bamboo
splinters work much better making things.
Give me lots of death and torture. Give me lots
of gore. We may have lost battle,
but we haven't lost war.
I am not a man
of violence. I don't want
to use my fist.
We can settle this.
We will be smart. Don't you think
that we should talk and try to work it out?
Cambodian girls are hip.
I like those violent faces. And Leo's
so oh so sexy. Tribute to the racists.
I'd trade them all today and
give up all my money if I could
just be home with my Vietnam
honey.
Odie and his crew took a ram into you
and set up ship to go to Hades.
Odie poured a drink offering for all
souls and prayed to the empty shells of
the dead, dead, dead, dead.
Hey there, that's a sporty jacket. Where'd you get that tie?
Are those shoes real alligator? Do you
like apple pie? So this is your
democracy. It's very, very pretty.
But I think I'll be going now. That's
the Saigon city. Where'd you put my brain
today? Am I dead or am I gay?
Where'd you put my brain, you fool?
Am I dead or am I cruel?
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
Dying in a rice field with a Tommy gun in hand.
Shoot the nasty Yankees who have
come to take our land. Hot costume
basic black up north. It's all the rage.
While that olive green draft wouldn't
make the fashion page.
Yo, hippo.
An evil army of
advisors.
Lakeworm got the early
devices.
They bomb bombs on Agent Orange. I'm just
hanging in the rain. Fungi sticks and
bamboo splendors, which might better make him faint.
So give me lots of death and torture. Give me lots
of gore. We may have lost the battle,
but we haven't lost the war.
V-5-0-4. A bomb for you
to go destroy. Be you alive or
be you dead, at least you tried to stop the
red menace from consuming good and taking
over the neighborhood. Won't you be
my neighbor? Won't you be my neighbor?
Comodian girls are hip. I really
like their smiling faces. And Mayos
girls are oh so sexy. Tribute to the
races. I'd trade them all today and I
would give up all my money. If I
could just be home now with my Vietnam
honey.
Where'd you put my brain today?
Am I dead or am I gay? Where'd you put
my brain last night? Am I black or am I
white? Won't you be my neighbor? Won't
you be my neighbor? You're hip,
so am I. We both eat ham and Swiss on
rye.
Oh, thanks to Janine, Reverend Janine
C for that one there. That was the
neighbor song by the Bloody Mannequin
Orchestra. I don't know where she finds
these things. A true subgenius. She
really looks around, I suppose. And you
can too if you call the station here.
Please do.
Hey, what's up?
Uh, yes, and we're going to go to another
radio interview from the old days. This
one had me, Reverend Ivan Stang, and
Pastor Buck Naked, the mighty Pastor
Buck Naked, and the sneaky G Gordon
Gordon. All three of us on Halloween
night about three years ago on a show
hosted by the New York Times. And
hosted by a lady named Karen Denard.
Thank you.
We should have slack, that we were
born with original slack,
but that there is a vast
and insidious conspiracy,
more insidious than most people ever
dream, trying to sap
away our slack.
And you know who that conspiracy is?
Oh, it's them normals.
That's right.
Yeah, it's a conspiracy.
It's a conspiracy that doesn't even know it's a conspiracy.
There's a...
It's a go-along conspiracy.
But have you ever... Do you know J.R. Bob
Dobbs?
The day I came to know...
Yeah, that's real funny, Buck.
That's not exactly true, Buck.
It was bad security.
What happened? I don't know. Stang was standing
right there, and his buddies just
pow, right in the head.
Oh my goodness. J.R. Bob Dobbs was shot
a year ago January in San Francisco.
Oh. And did you read
about it in the New York Times?
No. Did you hear about it on all things considered?
Was it in the Dallas Papers? No.
That proves a conspiracy. It wasn't even in the National
Inquirer, dear friends.
And...
Wasn't on Morning Edition either.
No, no. Bob Dobbs died, and
life went on. Oh yes,
the people
just kept going to work every
day, not thinking about what they were
doing it for. They don't have
slack. They don't realize what has
happened. It may be too late for a lot of people.
Did he appoint you as his heir
for the Church of the Subgenius? Was he
leading the Church of the Subgenius? Just so
I understand what
J.R. Bob Dobbs role was. Bob leads
Bob leads by
mistake. He became
the leader of this thing by mistake. He doesn't
consciously set out to do anything. He's
a lot of us think he's the world's
stupidest man, and yet he's so lucky.
He has attracted all this wealth.
And he sells. He became
a salesman, and he just
sells by pushing himself
which is the product. In other words, nobody cares
the piece of junk they leave with.
They only go in for
the treatment, which is Bob. I see.
G. Gordon Gordon? Well, I
just wanted to say that a lot
of people aren't even aware of the fact that Bob
is dead, and it's really presumptuous
to speak about an heir to Bob
at this particular time, because
Bob will be coming back.
Bob will come again. There's just
no two ways about it. When, we're not sure,
and exactly where he will show up,
but there is no heir to the church.
The Reverend Stang was selected by
J.R. Dobbs as the sacred scribe
and as the man to stand up
and take the heat when
Bob isn't there to answer for
any and everything. Now, I
understand that there are
some very illustrious
members of the Church of the Subgenius.
Somebody told me Todd Rundgren,
Pee-wee Herman.
Oh yes, as a matter of fact, those
people get our material,
but they don't send us money. Todd asked for us
to send him a bunch of stuff, and then
he never sent his twenty dollar subscription.
Because I called Todd, and he told me
he never heard of you guys. You did not.
I did so. And he didn't, uh-uh.
He didn't say that. Well, you call him up
and see what he tells you.
Well, I'm not going to argue over
rock stars. These are mere
rock stars. And Karen, you must
understand, there are those people
who will, even though they have used
Dobbs, or they think they've used him
at this particular time of their life,
to further their careers, to further
their wealth and their personal standing,
many people will not admit
that J.R. Bob Dobbs
is that one person that has tilted the luck
plane to enable them to achieve
these heights. Mm-hmm. You're talking
about the normals, of course. Well, yes.
Todd Rundgren may want people to think he did it
by sheer talent. Oh, I see. He may
at this point not want to let
on that early in his career Bob Dobbs
Bob Dobbs sold him a
wood nickel or something that somehow
tilted his
fate in the
direction it's gone. But we do have some
other people who acknowledge the
existence of Bob. Oh, yeah. If you want us to
name drop, we can name drop.
Let's say that you and your
family... Well, this is puzzling evidence.
The host and
the mixer for most of these shows.
Reminding you
appoint one member of your family...
This schizophrenic show
is for your benefit,
not ours.
Yes, you are
able to hear
such religions as
the subgenius church,
the saint stupid,
the discordians,
all those other
favorites that you ask about,
many of whom appear in the now
modern book
High Times by Weird Male,
and others who have
not yet been added to the
pantheon, and still others who
predate the subgenius by quite a lot.
But in any case,
if you whirl around the planet,
keep in mind,
that we love you.
Is this the end?
Is this the end of the show?
Okay, here we go.
Almost time for the news to come in.
Our space cadets
have just finished their nap.
Space cadets have just
begun their role.
They've just begun the bagaing.
I have not yet begun
to fight.
I have never known
no man that has begun
so many times
to fight.
It's like I've never realized
how many times they started fighting.
And then it was over.
No man can realize the effect
of that same fight upon
the young brow.
And no man knows how large
these beasts make.
Is my microphone on?
I don't see any of it.
No, you're not with us any longer.
Because it's the end of the show.
Well, why don't we fill it up with merriment
and laughter?
El Casa de 8484425.
What is happening on the radio?
There's no sound.
Yeah, I don't hear anything,
so it makes me kind of wonder.
There's a little bit of something.
It makes me scared when I don't have
that psychological support
in those background sounds.
Well, put a little wow
in your life and turn it up
for you.
Look, there's a collar.
What's a collar doing at this hour?
The adolescent years can be more
than just a difficult phase that a child
is going through. They can be dangerous years
when many young people drink too much,
eat poorly, and even consider suicide.
The startling information was compiled
through a study of 11,000 8th and 10th graders
in 1987 from 217
public and private schools.
The study revealed a troubled teenage
population in which 42% of the girls
and 25% of the boys said they had
seriously considered suicide.
Surprising numbers said they had
smoked marijuana and even more
had had five or more drinks on one occasion
in the previous two weeks.
And while most teens understood how AIDS
is transmitted, a majority of those surveyed
thought that birth control pills prevented
transmission of other sexually transmitted diseases.
In fact, 2.5 million teens
contract STDs each year.
With all this in mind,
it's not surprising that the study found
that many teens either overindulge in fatty foods
and sugary snacks or use unsafe diets
such as fasting, diet pills,
and laxatives.
All of this together indicates that the problems
that adolescents in America are just as serious
as the problems facing adults,
and there are no easy answers or simple solutions.
I'm Laurie Johnson, and that's 60 Seconds.
Roger Dodger, all you true subgenius fans out there.
Now I hope you have your membership books
and your special Boeing cards
and your secret ring.
Then we have got your secret ring
when you look inside and you see your wowie picture
that you're not supposed to let any of your women folks see.
Now we're going to tell you how to get this swell watch
and this beautiful ring in about 25 minutes
if you keep listening to our program.
Ah, there was the first Boeing of the season.
Ouch!
Waited by me on unamplified mode.
But when...
As we wander through this charnel house,
this abattoir we call life,
specifically how it is organized
and how you should use it,
with this information,
you will be better prepared to...
Can I get a witness?
Help me somebody.
Now, we've covered some of the most obvious
aisles of hate,
but what about some of the
less apparent?
What about the liberals, you might ask?
Do the subjugates also hate the liberals?
Friends, we hate anyone
who doesn't try to completely
and utterly destroy us.
Now you might ask,
what about what's left?
What we sometimes half-jokingly refer to as
the liberal party?
The cattle.
What about it?
Labor!
But contrary to popular belief,
the cattle aren't
entirely useless.
They shall have several uses
after 1998.
They can be used
as a cheap source of labor.
They can be taxed.
Kept in the home as pets.
They can be used
as a toy.
Or upon a whim,
they might be unleashed and well,
hunted for sport.
Can I get a witness?
You know, I went over to my friend Rick Maverick's
house the other day,
and I was feeling kind of down in the dumps.
I was kind of depressed that day.
He took me out in his backyard
and he showed me something that just
kind of raised my spirits.
And it was just kind of neat
that he could do something like that.
It kind of filled me with a sense of warmth.
He had,
out in his backyard,
he had just spelled out,
have a nice day
in the skulls of normals
he had decapitated.
And I just said,
that's neat.
That's kind of neat.
Mrs. Robinson and I took
the local subgenius clinch Sunday school class
on a field trip last Sunday
to one of these normal neighborhoods
and let me tell you,
it's every bit as bad as the pamphlet makes it out,
okay?
Now, I'm not prejudiced or anything like that.
A lot of my best friends are normals.
I just think as long as they know their place.
Well, they reproduce like animals.
We're thinking about moving soon.
Maybe even off-planet.
The cattle, ladies and gentlemen.
Now, what we're thinking about
is what is the next theory
of the Church of the Subgenius
I'm going to discuss tonight?
The next theory is always more hate.
Hatar!
I love it.
We're looking for people who love to hate.
You know?
That was Jayner Hyperkleets
live at the
New Orleans
World Science Fiction Convention
about a month ago.
Prior to that, you heard
a couple of clips from the
KPFA Subgenius
show in Berkeley.
Puzzling Evidence, Hal Robbins,
Philo Drummond in this case,
Mobius Rex,
and Gearing a Broke Friend.
Oh, yes.
And, uh,
well, you know,
uh,
I guess I ought to go back to the
to the talk shows,
the talk show radio things,
so that I can then make a smooth transition
to the ironic, um,
pardon me,
Diet Coke there,
the ironic, uh,
Eberle Brothers tune,
Jesus in a Red Dress,
or something like that.
So, here we go.
I'll bless you.
And, uh,
oh,
Mark Mothersbaugh of, uh,
Devo, uh,
Devo, okay.
Now, we could,
we could name some rock stars
that are in town right now,
but I,
we're just not too sure anymore.
Okay. Gee, go on, go on.
It's clear to me, uh, Reverend Stang,
you know, when you say Reverend Stang,
and when you say Pastor Naked,
uh, that conjures up, you know,
an idea of what that is.
Now, G. Gordon Gordon,
you need to, uh, clue me in as to
what role you play in the church.
Well, officially, I'm the,
I am the mercenary of mercy,
and I'm sort of a hit man for Bob.
And, uh, I...
We say this to ensure disbelief.
Yes. And, uh, we, we don't mind admitting it,
because just like the CIA and everything else
in the conspiracy, if you admit it,
everybody doesn't believe it and thinks it's a big joke.
But there are certain things that require work
of a quasi-legal
nature that, that Bob,
Bob has to have done for him.
As an example? Well, certain people have to be
removed in certain places. Security has
to be maintained in other places.
Computer files have to be emptied.
Sometimes we have to change their minds,
so to speak. So you have your coat on
for what reason now? So you can,
so your weapons don't show?
No, actually, it's cold in this studio, so I thought that, uh,
normally, yes, normally, uh,
but we, this being Dallas,
uh, people frown on you carrying guns.
Malaysia, it's no problem. Unless you're
got presidents in the, in the
sites, then you're okay.
Okay. Uh, Reverend Naked,
uh, Pastor Naked, forgive me,
um, tell me what
you think the appeal of this church
is. I mean, since you say it's
different from what we know
as, as the church. I think that just like
any cult, when you're starting out, you have to
promise something for free, you know,
free money, free love, you know,
something for nothing, and we do that
more than, more than I think other cults
are right now. And what we're
offering is value, as I'm ranting to you,
Well, just by, just by,
just by that, right. Just by the-
just by the- the doctrine of, of total
slack, and the, uh, approach to
slack, uh, you know,
what is slack? A lot of, a lot of if I'm
asking, well, it's, it's getting money for not
98 at 7 a.m., and all the subgeniuses will be ruptured up into the pleasure dimension for eternity,
or depending on how much money they've spent on the church.
Uh-huh.
And those who sat around and said, oh, well, I'll...
Take me off to space, take me off to space.
Come on down, you saucer man, and take me off to space.
Stick needles in my belly, take samples of my skin.
I don't care as long as I can live with saucer man.
I know that you don't take requests, but I'm a special case.
Take me off to space, take me off to space.
Come on down, you saucer man, and take me off to space.
Hey, commutators, let me join your crew.
Let me Pu can pas vez pas.
Give Pnau, a little touch of the water in your punch.
Me and I, you bet your life I'll cut up cows for you.
I don't care if you're some kind of ghastly beast without a face.
So come on down, you saucer man, and take me off to space.
Oh, take me off to space.
Take me off to space.
Come on down, you saucer man, and take me off to space.
Come down, you tiny robot with your little nipper claws.
You pale and bug-eyed alien with white and clammy paws.
Life is just a sucker's dream and death is a disgrace.
So come on down, you saucer man, and take me off to space.
Oh, take me off to space.
Take me off to space.
Come on down.
Come on down, you saucer man, and take me off to space.
Take me off to space.
Oh, friends, boy, if you only knew what an all-star lineup that was doing that song just then.
That was the song by Orton Neslow, known by other names, which you'll hear.
Katie V.
You'll see.
Ahmed Fishmonger on background vocals and Donna Cossey and Pagan Kennedy.
Oh, yes.
Great subgeniuses up there in shadowed Arkham, Massachusetts.
Oh, yes, indeedy.
And said, oh, well, I'll buy that $1 pamphlet about Bob.
Or I'll have Bob tattooed on my head, but I'm not going to send in that $20 for those magazines.
And those people will fry.
They shall fry along with the helpless pink.
And mediocritans who compose most of what they call humanity.
Helpless pinks.
And also, Pastor Naked, you were going to say something?
Well, I'll say goodbye.
I'd like to say...
Mother had on high heels a red dress for Jesus.
I'll pour that on the town.
Well, she did her best to outdress the rest who found their way downtown.
Oh, Lord, let her look that good in heaven.
Saint Peter said.
God made her that way.
Mother had on high heels a red dress for Jesus.
Dressed for a night on the town.
She was as pure as Mary Magdalene.
She sure could throw it down.
Oh, Lord, let her look that good in heaven.
What will Saint Peter say?
God made her that way.
Oh, Lord, let her look that good in heaven.
What will St. Peter say
Oh Lord, let her look that good in heaven
God made her that way
It's the winning side
And everyone is cheering for the winning side
And the children leave their homes to join the winning side
And when Jesus comes
He'll march on with the king
And we've got all the right answers
In the guiding light
When we're on the right
And we have no fear
No, we have no fear
Waiting for the signs
We will give our lives
And I feel so awesome
And it's so lonely
To feel that night
To almost feel you near me
I imagine that you're with me
On the winning side
We don't ask too many questions
And I've got this strange sensation
On the winning side
I don't recognize the faces
Of the people I love
On the winning side
And we all live here in cages
Someone cried last night
And it made a sound
With my eyes closed tight
I hear everything
I can hear your voice
When I kiss the ground
And the lights go out
You know you better
And I'd like to know your name
I could really show you something
If you give me half a chance
Cause I'm on the winning side
Yeah
On the winning side
You're with me
Thank you
Foratti
Too bad
I am fraud
To be
Be
A fighter
I'd like to take you somewhere that you've never been before
And I feel so isolated
And I feel so all alone
Here on the inside
Yeah, on the inside
Ladies and gentlemen, here he is, Mr. City.
Yeah.
Mr. City, hey.
Oh, thanks, thanks.
Yeah.
Sure is nice to...
to be here
in the city
where the rate of everything is going up.
Yeah, especially crime.
Yeah, the property taxes.
The high-rise building.
Yeah, but mostly crime.
And, uh, yeah.
Crime.
Yeah.
Especially crime that's on the rise.
What are you gonna do about it, huh?
But, uh, you'll be glad to know that Mr. City is working it out so that for every crook,
there's a cop.
That's that boy!
You know, of course, where, uh, crime begins.
Well, why don't you sing about it some, huh?
Okay, I...
I will.
Yeah.
It all happens in gardens.
Oh, by the way, you don't mind if I eat this?
The apple.
Yes, sure is a crime.
I don't have more time.
Apple.
Yeah.
Sure is a crime.
You don't have more time.
The apple.
We don't have more time.
Sure is a crime.
We're gonna put you away.
Throw away.
Sure is a crime.
Like I said.
And we don't have more time.
Sure is a crime.
We don't have more time.
Yeah.
Last time I saw you.
I saw the judge.
I asked him what he meant when he'd say judge not.
He got so mad.
The judge did.
Sure is a crime.
He went into solitary.
Had to do it.
We don't have more time.
People in glass houses and all that sort of thing.
More crime.
It's a crime.
We don't have more time, friends.
That was Ken Nordean from the Texas News.
We're gonna do a five minute live tape triple talk which you can get from Snail Records at 6106 North Kenmore Avenue in Chicago.
60660.
Oh, and this is Mondo Logic?
Ha ha ha.
Fine.
All right.
I'd like to say something.
Yes, you're good.
You're good.
One of the reasons I think that the church is one of the fastest growing cults in the planet, I would probably estimate, is that every...
Now, you just came from Brazil, did you tell me?
Yes, yes.
And there was the Church of the Sub-Jesus there?
Oh, I am the Pope of Brazil.
Brazil and the Southern Hemisphere.
Okay.
And that we're not putting you on.
I mean, none of this, everything we've said so far is true.
But more by what you would call true.
True.
But one of the reasons...
Because the church accommodates anything in a person's belief system into our dogma.
Anything the subgenius spouts becomes instantly part of our church dogma.
Yeah, you can believe, unlike most religions, you can believe anything you want in this religion.
That's right.
We believe in everything.
Okay.
Now, you were making a point.
You go ahead and go.
Well, I think...
One of the points is that the reason why the Church of the Subgenius is so popular is because
most religions of every persuasion of the...
We call them the false churches.
...require a great deal of hard personal work, concentration, studying, deprivation.
The Church of the Subgenius does not require you to give up anything in your diet.
They do not require you to give up any of those vices that many other religions require you to...
We're trying to find new ones.
Now, that's exactly right.
And we don't...
We know that people don't have...
We don't have time to spend 17 years on a mountaintop meditating.
Is your work the work of the devil?
Let's lay it out right on the table right now in here.
Heck no.
As a matter of...
Heavens no.
I wonder about that every now and then, but never for very long, because the devil doesn't operate that way.
We're way too open for the devil.
Basically, the devil has no sense of humor.
You know, if the devil is as tricky as he is...
There you go.
...then, you know, who would he be imitating?
He sure wouldn't be imitating...
Imitating Bob.
Bob, us.
I mean, what would that get him?
You're going to find the devil in church.
Mm-hmm.
But not our church.
Okay.
Now, there's...
Stuff.
Now, now, I'm...
You think you saw a monster, but the human mind often plays strange tricks.
Like this one.
I won't do that again.
It's too hard.
Okay, it's too hard, he says.
We're backing down the show...
It's a rock.
You gotta do this.
Then, scratch it!
Ahh ah ha...
Logic control fails...
I hermane ero J.
A submission way myself.
Africa's since ,
but it might make him a fan
It might have some business points.
I mean, it's Yeah, but some sorts or something.
this on TV, It's this.
part of the thing.
So miss not until we're ready, then you can enter a home.
band of Myers about in Virginia .
I see on us during that minute really does. reach out.
We'll get control of the show back any minute now.
Something ought to be done about these boys.
Because they don't take Jesus into their heart.
That's true. That's ever so true, friend.
You mustn't be like these wicked men.
Don't do it.
The Bible says that he who broadcasts late at night or early in the morning
shall bring upon his heart the abomination of desolation.
And Jesus said we should always stick by our God
and do what we think is right, whatever the other fellow says.
That's the truth, friends.
And you can get some more of that abomination and desolation
by writing Bob at...
Box 140306 in Dallas, Texas.
75214.
Once again, free information.
You'll find out.
Just try. Go ahead. Try us.
Box140306, Dallas.
75214.
Just address that to Bob.
And stay tuned for Robert...
Wisdom.
Zzzz.
...American Music Party.
Friends of audience elimination,
if you leave here alive,
if you're good enough to survive the training in Dobstown,
if you can take that fishhook bone member down your throat
and tickle that bat just right,
extract it without hurting the bat or yourself...
Then you can sit through all of this.
Then you will no longer be maggots.
You will no longer be pukes.
You will be full-fledged subgeniuses,
and you will be weapons.
Weapons for Bob.
Praying for slack.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, who next?
Any questions?
Any other authors out there?
Um...
In disguise?
Yeah, you never know.
So...
So what the hell are we doing on the panel?
No care, sir.
So what is...
So what is Three Fists of Tales of Bob?
What is this, Three Fists of Tales of Bob?
Well, Three Fists of Tales of Bob, unlike the book of the subgenius,
is actually a book of...
fiction.
Or partly fiction.
Uh, some of it is...
You don't think it's fiction?
It's a book of metaphor!
A book of...
A parable!
Literature!
Huh?
We thought it was an instruction manual for de-beaking the squid.
That's not even fiction, Doug.
Well, it was originally, friends.
Ah, God.
We'll get back to that next week.
That's a little panel discussion from...
that New Orleans, uh, science fiction convention.
With, uh...
I don't know who was on that.
Pope David N. Meyer, Nancy Regalia, John Shirley.
Jane or Hypercliques.
Books... Brooks Carruthers.
Sternodocs Keckhaver.
And Willa Dobbs.
So, uh...
Yeah.
I couldn't see.
There we go.
And I...
Wait a minute.
I can't see it.
No, no.
I couldn't see it either.
We have to get it down on the bottom deck so that Robert can take over with his tape.
See, it's okay.
There we go.
And I...
I thought I looked down and I saw my own body.
We have to put it back together ourselves.
Yeah, might as well.
And I do that all the time.
You remove the watch.
No, you just look down.
You see your eyes.
Your arms.
Your legs.
Whatever, you know.
Do you?
Do you have mirrors on your seat?
Your original.
Goodbye.
I don't need them.
I can see my own body wherever I am.
It's a power that I've possessed since birth.
Created.
I simply look down along my own axis and I see all the parts of my body except...
...the parts of your body.
Radio.
Then you can't see the inside of your own eye?
Of course not.
Don't press that button.
Oh, don't use that button.
That's on show.
Reluctance.
It's only on one side.
Randomize the show.
What about the aerobic report?
Delayed from the subgenius world of physical fitness.
Shut up, door.
Today on...