This is London.
Sink into the abyss of a new dark age,
made more sinister and perhaps more protracted
by the likes of perverted science.
The subgenius power of flesh!
This was their finest hour.
Master of
I turn our heads into sin,
and I pray.
Tears slip into my eyes,
I remember the spring days so that they don't spill out
Like a lonely night
I look up and walk
I count the stars that have blurred
I remember the summer days
Like a lonely night
Happiness is on the clouds
I look up and walk
I count the stars that have blurred
Like a lonely night
I remember the spring days
Happiness is on the clouds
Like a lonely night
I look up and walk
I count the stars that have blurred
Like a lonely night
I walk, crying, so that they don't spill out
Oh, that was the Martian National Anthem as the audio file was titled,
also known as Sukiyaki, by Kyou Sakamoto.
On this hour of Slack number 1754 we'll continue with
last week's conversation with Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
recorded by phone from Ohio,
here in Tarzan's radio station at Stang Ranch,
Texas. But we'll be alternating it with all manner of weird music plus unheard subgenius radio and
podcast ranting from both X Day with Dr. Howland, Dr. Philodrum and also from Overlord Animal and
Dr. Brouhaha of Austin. But first, Dave explains the problem with utilitarianism.
You know what will happen if you support a utilitarian? You'd have to be reduced to your
lowest common denominator. And I guess that's two thirds or something like that. And then you
have to, once again, you have to report to the police station every month or two.
Now who wants to go on living like that? Not I. Hey, speaking of living like that, Dave, we found
a place where if you became homeless and didn't have any place else to go, we found a place that
was a little bit more than just a place to live. And it's a little bit more than just a place to live.
And it's a little bit more than just a place to live. And it's a little bit more than just a place to live.
Princess, we remember we were exploring around my sister's deserted house.
No.
Which she's going to be back in. But there was a camper top from like the top that you put onto a
pickup to turn your pickup into a camper. Well, just that part was laying an ancient one, like 50
years old, sitting on the ground back in the woods.
Oh, I love 50 year old.
I love 50 year old.
I was thinking that was just like the perfect bedroom for Dave.
Yeah.
That's where Dave would stay.
Reverend Stang is always scoping out a place for you, Dave.
He's always looking for a good place for you.
A place where it wouldn't be too much of a firehouse.
You see, I don't think that's a good place for Dave because it doesn't have toilet facilities
or any place for him to wash his hands.
Yeah.
I've had to go to the toilet every once in a while.
I know what that's like.
It happened once.
Well, yeah.
It's not like he's got any goods.
He could, you know, he could just kind of let go of anything.
But I wouldn't want a rattlesnake to snap on my scrotum, if you know what I'm saying.
Thank you very much, Dave.
That's a good point.
That's an ouchy point, too.
The ouchy point, yep.
Well, this camper top still has a window part that falls down, so you could lock it up at
night once you snuggled in there.
Yeah.
You'd only have about eight inches clearance.
In your bedroom.
But there is enough room to lay down out of the rain, you know.
And if he had a little, had enough hot peppers in there, rubbed all over his body, he'd stay warm.
Reverend Stang, you have a very great imagination.
Oh, I imagine all kinds of things.
Oh, yeah.
I imagine all kinds of things.
Isn't it true that you live?
Are you part of the time in an imaginary, entirely world?
No, I wish.
That's been my goal for my whole life.
I've come about as close as a fella can in the real world to live in an imaginary world
because all my friends, they don't have names like David or Mike or Trevor.
They have names like Pope Sternodocs, Dr. Philodromus.
I'm all about the
old.
I'm about the old.
And lonesome.
See, lonesome has an O.
Lonesome.
It's always got an O and an N sound, isn't it?
Are you saying you're isolated?
some data, some cruelty from this information?
Yeah, it's the big O.
The big O, it represents the zero,
the nothing in Buddhism.
The goal.
It also represents the big O, the orange juice.
If you ever had a big O that rolls up to Lawson's in 40 hours,
you roll on, big O.
Get the juice down to Lawson's in 40 hours.
It's an orange juice story from Ohio many years ago.
I was going to say, that must be an Ohio thing.
That one's not, draws a blank for me.
They guaranteed that that juice for sale,
that orange juice you would get at Lawson's,
which no longer exists.
It was a series of chain stores like 7-Elevens and stuff.
The orange juice was guaranteed from Melrose, Florida, 40 hours.
If it was one second over 40 hours,
you could return your orange juice.
That's right.
From so-called PR News in so-called Washington,
I'm in so-called Washington.
Orders for so-called terrible goods fell in so-called October
for a third consecutive so-called month,
more than most so-called economists predicted,
but less than most so-called economists predicted
in so-called September and so-called August.
On so-called Wall Street, so-called 2, so-called 6, so-called 9.
On so-called morning television shows today,
so-called Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice said,
I don't want to make peace.
The so-called U.S. Army has notified so-called top officers
at so-called bases across the so-called country
to draw up so-called plans for massive so-called layoffs
if the so-called White House and so-called Congress
don't break their so-called deadlock over a so-called spending bill.
So-called President Bush is due to begin in earnest
December so-called 12th.
So-called NBC says this is so-called PR News
in so-called Washington.
Washington.
I'll collect some grease.
The deep appreciation of the natural world.
You know, as an assistant cameraman,
I learned the value of nose grease,
which we would use to lubricate the film gate.
Are you kidding?
No, I'm not kidding.
But it gets on the film, doesn't it?
Just lubricate.
It lets it slide through better.
It can get hung up in there.
But the emulsion, you don't want to...
Oh, well.
Well, hey, you know, for a buttercrust bread commercial,
nothing's too good.
We used only the finest nose grease.
Bring home the butternut bread.
Yeah, I was taught that by a professional cameraman.
He learned his trade in the British Navy.
So how can you question that?
It's great for removing scratches.
He says it's great for removing scratches.
Scratches?
Scratches.
From Kodachrome film.
Yeah, there you go.
Scratch removal.
We used to pay extra for that.
Some of us used to clean our film obsessively
with the film cleaner to keep those little specks.
I'm going to have to go look for that thing.
What, the check?
Yeah, I don't know where it is.
Well, you just want another one.
You hadn't endorsed it, had you, son?
It was for me.
He says it's right there on the table.
Right over there.
Anybody could have picked that up.
And taken it off and made hay with it.
At any rate, now that mystery is solved.
That trifling problem is dispensed with, disposed of.
Anybody need their film gate cleaned with some nose grease?
I've got plenty of forehead grease works, too.
But you don't want to get the emulsion of the film
a compromise.
Are you questioning the British Navy film production?
Well, they probably cleaned it, too.
No, you even spelled my name right.
I-V-A-N.
Okay, pop her in your secret pocket there.
Right.
Shafid.
My name, my real name is Shafid.
Right.
Your name?
Ole.
Aswipe.
Yes, that's the way it's pronounced.
Okay.
Right in Shafid here.
Aswipe Shafid.
Mm-hmm.
The Bollywood star.
Probably Aswipe Shafid III.
Yeah.
It's always the third or something.
And his co-star.
His co-star, Lemangelo Arangelo.
Boy, we already did that horrible chunk of history.
With the singing and dancing talents of Medula Oblongata.
Hey, now I remember what I was going to say when I turned on the recorder
trying to record what I thought that I had.
But it had to do with the fact that this little town and whole area is so Christian
that you can't find me anywhere else.
Yeah.
I've been to Mazzaballs or any kind of Jewish-type food, even at H-E-B in the big city of Granbury.
And you'd think it because it's pretty...
H-E-B, Hebe.
Ha-ha.
Very funny.
The fact is, H-E-B actually stands for the name of the founder of that chain of southwestern
supermarkets, Herbert E. Butts.
But they couldn't...
really name their supermarket butts i'm gonna go over to butts for some fresh milk and eggs honey
i'll be right back well put me up some bear would you i'm over butts over going over to
butts are you get me some fresh chicken over there at butts all right so i'm a pack of butts
and butts you know piggly willy piggly wiggly was founded by a man named uh butthurt and so
they couldn't call it butthurts so they called it piggly wiggly for just about as bad it's many
places in the south to piggly wiggly win dixie i don't know if they still have oh yeah they sure
do dave you remember right piggly wiggly win dixie and it was skags was yes it's like some
poor some guy named skags started a business and actually kept the name so it was called skags and
skags albertson but uh
butthurt e butts wisely decided not to call his store butts my name was skags i changed to smucker
um and then there were stuckies and you know duckies where i have very fine pecan rolls at
stuckies or pecan logs i guess i guess they call them because they're shaped like a log and they
have tree branches growing out of them sometimes they even have like these weird
subspecies of them and they're like they're like they're like they're like they're like
a гол ghost like you know thatachts right a dead Force hugrife or something like that
color in music and they know um they were made from people and they are like having an
offer to burn poblvar really the spPorb yeah cool and it got pretty and then a lot today
about probably the neurosciences they just get more involved with this and more favorite
spaces have changed in a zoom are just made like graphics you can do stuff on Vancouver
PCD CS인지 Savage offers Clark SEO services and really I do because I have information
about that as well right now and I later had the campeon toward the end of last term and i've
seen this in LinkedIn about 2 million times in now and i want some answers and and i want to tell syrup
That's what we pay you for, or we would were you paid.
Yes, if we could afford to pay you, that's what you would be being paid for.
That's not what I'd ask for if I was reported being paid.
I'd ask for twice as much in a 10-year contract.
Well, we're working on it.
I've decided I'm going to sell it.
Old Bessie could live without, well, I don't want to say,
but there's a certain part of her body.
That she could technically live without.
And I'm thinking about selling that.
But really, you know, it's getting down to where there ain't going to be much Old Bessie left.
I know.
I hate to, I mean, I hate to even look at her.
Yeah.
The way it is.
And, you know, when we walk out to the pen, she just gets this look like,
oh, no, they're going to take another part.
I know how she feels.
I feel that way every time the mailman brings a new bill.
An industrial horse?
Another part of myself or her.
Pig.
Is it like an industrial horse?
He asked if Bessie was a horse, and I said Bessie was a pig.
Well, that's what we tell people.
Oh, a machine pig.
That was one of my first bands was the Machine Pigs.
Yeah, yeah, that's right, a pig.
Yeah.
Yeah, you know, it's just an animal.
One, two, three, four, oink, oink, oink, oink.
Yeah, this is not some Texas Chainsaw Massacre thing.
You know, Princess Wee thinks that movie is just fictional.
Texas Chainsaw Massacre.
So do I think that anything about Cannibal Rednecks is also fiction.
Yeah, she thinks there was no Ed Gein in her world.
It's all fabricated.
There was no Tom Landry.
Somebody made it up so people could have bad nightmares.
None of those pedophile serial killers ever existed.
No.
No John Wayne.
They don't exist.
They're just fictitious.
Then why do they have all those movie trailers for them all the time?
There's...
The Texas Chainsaw Massacre.
Well, they're movies, but they're based on real life stuff that happens a lot.
A hell of a lot.
Yeah.
These people are definitely inbred.
There are very many of them.
The consequences have not been positive at all.
I don't think so.
They only do it to Yankees for the most part.
Yankee tourists.
What, grow a third eye on their forehead?
Chop them up and turn them into barbecue.
And serve them to the next...
Sell them to the next Yankee tourists that come by who are doomed to become the next
bunch of barbecue.
Yeah.
Duh.
I mean, haven't you ever walked into certain roadside cafes or bars, convenience stores
where you'd stop just to get gas or ask somebody directions and you'd walk in and you'd just
go, holy...
Holy...
Holy moly.
Yeah.
This is a hotbed of cannibal rednecks and I better get out of here.
No.
I never have.
Well, I went to get butter one time.
You have.
In fact, Princess Wee, you just didn't recognize it.
I want to hear Dave's story about going to get butter.
I don't want to hear about me not recognizing cannibal rednecks.
I had to drag you out of that last place.
Especially after I saw it was written on the bathroom walls.
Come on now.
Dave's going to tell us about getting butter.
Come on.
Okay.
All right.
Dave.
Uh, I heard that you went shopping to get butter.
Have I stopped ovulating yet?
Have you stopped ovulating?
I don't know.
Have you?
That's what I was asking you.
You should...
You're a woman.
You should know.
But what about...
What about the butter?
What about the 12?
What about the butter, man?
The butter?
The butter.
You went to get butter.
Remember you went to the store to get butter?
Remember?
Couldn't find the butter, man.
I found the butter, man.
I forgot to come back.
I'm sorry.
You got that right on the head.
You nailed it.
Dave forgot what he was going to say.
Oh, man.
That's okay.
I forgot I was going to get butter.
Well, next time, just go get the butter.
If I could only congeal it massively like some sort of outer space pilot.
Speak up, Dave.
Speak up.
If I could only congeal it dramatically like some kind of space pirate.
Or pilot.
Or, you know, one of those types.
You're talking about the butter still, right?
Right.
Space pirate congealing the butter.
Is that the name of your next Bulldada album or something, Dave?
I mean, is this some kind of surrealist metaphor that nobody's supposed to get?
Or are you seriously talking about...
They're supposed to take a life.
I mean, the thing is, just when you think Dave's just spewing...
Spewing a bunch of nonsense, you find out, oh, that was in the paper in Ashtabula that day.
Right.
That actually happened.
Pirates congealed butter in Ashtabula just offshore.
Mm-hmm.
Farm fresh.
Yeah.
Farmed a table, right?
And they take it right out of the river sometimes, too.
Pirate congealed?
It was very, very sad with that tiny little log.
There was no...
See, that's how I like to express myself.
I'm displeased.
Well, I don't like it that you're displeased, Dave.
You should not be displeased.
Well, then thank you very much.
I agree with you.
Really?
Take your hand and walk slowly down the land until everyone is free.
Of what, I don't know, but it sounds good.
It sounds great.
And now this.
Thank you.
Frank Krumit did that epic song.
Next, we relive a terrible crisis at 22X Day in the summer of so-called 2019.
What jackanapes knocked the screen out of this pipe?
I don't know.
It's useless without the screen.
Oh, see, that's terrible.
I don't have a replacement.
i don't see any jackanapes around here so jack in apes another jackanapes um look around the
vicinity see if there's a little screen lying there uh there no i haven't opened this it might
be in my pocket i suppose look in your pocket look in your explain the smell reach into your pocket
it knives journey to the center of stangs oh so that's what those are and uh yeah uh there don't
seem to be any screens in there but uh contents of the dead man's buckets redo flashing around chimney
diagrams notes to self the heartache and thousand natural shocks that that flashes air too yeah i
wanted to remember
that at uh x day permission letter for peas one year on one product rolled joints yes in nevada
there will be what's that joint you can buy call oh these are like a flying saucer oh i see that's
a hearing aid battery okay for aliens de-glamorize it yeah okay no screen nothing else left in your
pocket at the very bottom of the linty
uh yes there it is i thought so with product in it there's the soul of a bobby who felt went astray
and never his check bounced so we have his soul and we're smoking it up slay not the moth nor the
butterfly for the last judgment draweth nine i wouldn't do this sir go ahead nobody's watching
nobody cares go ahead what do you mean
these guys fbi and
uh you mean a democrat would they not
the fbi they're all anti-trump call me guy yeah so mueller mueller i mean those democrats light
up and live wait wait what am i saying no set fire to that there root there hey man did i give you
that check hey he asked you about a check a check did he give you a check check check
check just go hunk a check you know uh written promise a promissory
note to deliver certain funds to the bear when endorsed no of course given to rep no
and he probably stole my lighter too institution well you have a lighter
and you have some fraud oh this isn't tip but it's an herb this is just a an herb it's not a drug
it is fry but it's not what everybody else calls from urban urbanatraptor
bicentennial blossoms and buds with macro earthworms each in its own earthenware urn.
It'll help my allergies. Unless that's what's making me allergic.
So it's allergies, is it? And there's no little hole? Oh, there is a little hole.
That's what he said.
Lens whites. Is that what they're calling them now?
Yeah.
She's never drawn a passive breath and you'll rot your teeth on the nape of her neck.
She combs her hair with gasoline. She's got blue and yellow, oughta make some green.
She's got a sugar daddy's fortune buried in the city don'ts and she's got the map written on the wall.
She's got a diamond on the bottom of her bum. And if you get down on your knees to read the twat,
she's got a 20-pound ember stringing at your head.
She burns me down in ecstasy till I'm in love with destiny.
She threw away my satisfied mind.
Slung her teeth into my spine.
Stay tuned for a special presentation. She's back in the helm, back, back in the station.
Don't change the channel if the screen gets fuzzy. Can't change the channel if the screen gets fuzzy.
She burns me down in ecstasy till I'm in love with destiny.
She threw away my satisfied mind.
Slung her teeth into my spine.
She's a high-heeled emergency.
Still I'm in love with destiny.
She threw away my satisfied mind.
Slung her teeth into my spine.
Keeps me in love with destiny.
A heartless day will resume.
Spotted an earlier tattoo from love that makes me feel like I belong to a good boy's heart.
I always thought bargaining was telling.
MR SLUNGFIED
Baugh did that song, Destiny Detroit, with his band Massive Hot Dog Recall, and yes,
he is related to those mothers, Baugh's, and lives in northern Ohio, like I did for 20
years.
Where Princess Wee and I did the show at radio station WCSB Cleveland, and it's still on
there, but they're playing CDs that we record in our living room underneath the preserved
decapitated head of a large bear heard screaming in the background.
During these sessions, if I sense that we've been blabbering randomly for way too long,
I can try the cut point for later editing by saying things like, and now this.
That was a cut point.
Now we're back to talking to Lonesome Cowboy Dave on the Hour of Slack number 1,753.
Wow.
53.
Something like that.
Somewhere around there.
And that's a lot of show, you know what I'm saying?
Oh, God.
It is a lot of show.
It's weighing me down.
Every time I do one of these shows, I'm thinking, you know, in that day I spent on that show,
day and a half, with all the copies and the putting online and censoring and everything,
it's like, I could have spent that time producing an entire new subgenius 10-volume
subgenius.
It's a set of hilarious art and written words.
But instead, I just blither away on this stupid show.
It's not stupid.
How much longer am I going to keep telling myself this ridiculous...
You need to be marched in the right direction like the Soviet Georgian choir, like the Soviet
Army chorus.
You need to be marched in one direction.
Yeah, backwards.
Let's just start doing reruns from now on.
There's nothing wrong with that.
And pretend they're new.
And everybody will think, wow, Dave and Stang sound so much healthier and more alert and
bright and funny and loud.
What's their secret?
Yeah, and clear.
Yeah, and you could play them all backwards, too.
So it would be like, yip, ship, bloop, boop, boop, boop, and stuff like that.
And that could add another extraterrestrial dimension to our congealments.
Actually, I used to do that before we even got on.
I used to do that on the radio.
And I realized it didn't really work, and it's stupid and boring.
Unless you're on LSD, then it's great.
Oh, wow, it's brilliant genius.
Woo!
Those were the days.
The 60s were fun, but now I'm paying the price.
That's a Stan Lee quote, I think, from Ant-Man and the Wasp.
Yeah, that's his cameo in Ant-Man and the Wasp.
There's a chase scene, and the Wasp and Ant-Man are shrinking, or they're sidekick, they're
humorous sidekick, are shrinking things right and left.
And this old man, Stan Lee, the Marvel editor and writer, walks out to his car, and it suddenly
shrinks, disappears.
And he mutters to himself.
The 60s were fun, but now I'm paying the price.
And the audience laughs.
Nowadays, they have to do a digital Stan Lee to get the cameo in, because he's dead.
But they still have to have him.
Have you heard of the Roy Orbison tour that's going on right now, the hologram tour?
I have heard that there's hologram tours of Elvis and Frank Zappa.
I just heard that today.
But I don't know anything about it.
You guys are putting me on.
No, I'm not.
I actually heard there was a hologram tour of Elvis and a hologram Frank Zappa.
No way.
No.
Oh, yeah.
Uh-uh.
No.
I saw a play about this was going to happen, but this is actually happening now?
Oh, yeah.
Anything that there was a play about.
Dead Roy Orbison's on trail.
James Dean is starring in a big Hollywood movie that's coming out.
Yeah.
I mean, seriously, that's not a joke.
They're going to do an all-digital James Dean.
Good Lord.
See how it is when there's a dearth of ideas, when there's not enough ideas.
They'll jump on one idea, which may or may not be a good idea and should be developed,
and they'll just keep on just killing the thing until it's dead.
No, they jump on the ideas that have been market-tested to be sellable.
Right.
Always, you know, good ideas that will make a story.
That people will go and see.
There's a formula for that now.
At least they have to interpret the data, you know, but still, it doesn't matter.
Those Marvel movies are perfect examples of those, and they're really good movies, if you like that sort of thing.
I do.
What?
I like both sorts of things.
I like arty-farty dramas and black-and-white dubbed in English with Italian subtitles,
and I like big Hollywood blockbusters with The Rock.
And all those tough guys.
Well, are they worse than Neighbor World?
I mean, are they—what's the quality of the hologram, the holo-zig?
I have no idea.
I don't know.
I just—I'm old.
I don't see this.
I still imagine a 1980s hologram that looks like it's semi-translucent, and you can stick your hand through it, but it's like dim.
I can't imagine it.
I thought that would be so weird, you know, if you had one really look like people, maybe small, little, teeny, tiny people, but—
you know, just as they is.
I don't know.
Boy, things are—
Everything's kind of like a lie, you know what I mean?
Because Roy Orbison is quite dead.
Well, yeah, so is Elvis and Frank.
But his hologram is alive.
And James Dean, but you can still make him seem to be—I mean, the Star Wars movies had Princess Leia and Peter Cushing come back to life.
But digital doubles.
Fairly convincing.
Yeah.
There's a little bit of Uncanny Valley in there.
They look realer than Bob looks, and Bob's real.
So—
Yeah, I guess you got a point there on the top of your head, anyway.
Yeah.
Yep.
It's fair.
Okay.
Up next we haveça antibodies.
From PR News in Washington, I'm there.
Defense Secretary Robert Gates is bad today.
Gates quotes senior Pentagon officials as saying Gates concluded the two women who alleged that they were sexually assaulted by Gates remain too volatile in civilian courts.
The court heard arguments.
Gates acknowledged that Gates pushed out of the south and west of the country and moved for his country.
She also remains dangerous and problematic.
The Supreme Court heard PR News in Washington.
Thank you, Mr. Lee Murr.
His works are all on archive.com, you know.
And I think this is Lonesome Cowboy Dave and Reverend Avery Larry of the next day in the background.
And now we finally get to hear some female subgenius interjected into this pathetic sausage fest.
Yes, vagina, there are female subgeniuses.
And I...
I have had a crush on pretty much all of the ones I've met.
I especially love the spoutings of these two particular wacky rant partners down in Austin.
Overlord Anna Mall and Dr. Brouhaha.
So, well, the moon was in Aries, so...
The full moon.
It's gonna awaken the fires inside.
I'm feeling it.
Yeah.
Oh.
Just...
Don't eat too much spicy food.
I did.
Actually, no, I ate too many grapes.
Yeah.
Which is my equivalent of spiciness.
That's like the level of spice that I can handle.
I can handle the spice of grapes.
The spicy grapes.
It was hard to do.
I didn't know that that many grapes would do what it did to my body, to my body.
Yeah.
I feel so clean.
They're pretty, yeah.
It was horrible.
You were renewed in the fire of grapes.
Yeah.
It was horrible.
The freshness of the grapes.
The crisp tartness of grapes.
No longer drinking them, just letting them stomp me from the inside out.
That sounds like a good time.
It was painful, though, for a second there.
I was like, oh, I've got to suddenly find this place that I like to spend quiet time alone
with possibly some excrementatory meditation materials.
I need a book.
I can't grab one fast enough.
And luckily I have church pamphlets on the bathroom wall.
There you go.
Yeah.
Church of...
Church of all that good stuff.
Man, I tell you what.
I got my pleasure saucer diagram on the wall there.
That's good to go over that, so, you know.
Oh, yes.
Good thing in time.
Maybe I don't need, like, two hamster cages and a gerbil pit.
Maybe what I really need is a butterfly enclosure.
Well, you know, you could have the hamster's wheels helping power the, like,
gentle breezes in the butterfly enclosure.
Ooh.
So.
That sounds excessive, though.
What are the sugar gliders going to do?
They'll just glide on the gentle breezes.
That's not really what they do, though.
Well, I mean, they're, like, bonus, aren't they?
Are they?
I thought they would be.
They're going to, like, they're obviously going to...
I think you're thinking of lemurs.
Shout out to lemurs, yo!
What?
Anyway, just saying.
Yeah, I could be.
They got...
They're pale sugar gliders, don't they?
Aren't they little?
And they're, like...
They just smell like piss.
They smell like sugar glider piss.
Well, that's exactly what the hamster wheel powers the gentle breeze.
It all seems very, you know...
There's not enough breeze on the saucer.
So I really...
I'm just saying, maybe leaving rodents behind.
If you have to.
They can catch their own pleasure saucer if they were meant to go.
I don't think they paid their $35.
I will pay $35.
On behalf of rodents.
Because I can't handle people being too happy.
Okay.
Your pleasure saucer is not my pleasure saucer.
You're going to have to get your own pleasure saucer.
Speaking of which, how are you going to keep...
If you're taking your raptor friends...
If you're, like, up on the...
Well, that's why I need rodents, obviously.
How are my raptors going to eat?
So it's not because you want them there.
It's because you need them there for a food source for your raptors.
Well, yeah.
Yeah, and entertainment.
They don't want to just, like, be fed, like, you know, like, replicator meat.
You're going to sew them tiny outfits so they have a fine dining experience.
The raptor's going to swoop down and it's like,
Ooh, look at those sequins.
I'm going to go after that one in the long gown with the tail.
Maybe.
I will definitely give them a gilded, like, perches to sit on at the dinner table if they want.
You know, they can have all they want, those raptors.
And the mice can have, like, furniture.
Which raptors will wear the monocles?
Because I'm just imagining at this point, somebody's going to have an opera glass.
Somebody's going to have a monocle.
How are you going to be divvying that up amongst the raptors?
I mean, it's kind of like a first-come, first-served thing, really.
But I'm definitely going to save, like...
Well, yeah, if you only have a couple of hamsters and a gerbil bit.
I'm going to save, right?
I'm going to save, like, a cummerbund for, like, the falcon, maybe.
Ooh.
Yeah.
That's some highfalutin.
Wow.
It's a fancy falcon.
Yeah.
I was, like, I was going to, like, have my...
I am keeping the tiger.
I, yeah.
I mean, why would you ever leave your tiger behind?
I thought you all were tight.
Yeah.
We hang.
We hang in Tiger Town.
So I was thinking, though, it's, like, you know, not necessarily, like, a suit for,
like, not like a dinner suit kind of thing, but maybe just going with, like, a leopard onesie.
For the tiger?
Yeah.
You think it would?
Maybe.
Urban camouflage, you know?
I don't know.
Maybe just switch it up a bit.
Maybe he just wants to be, like, a leopard sometimes and, like, just live his life.
I mean, I would ask the tiger, but I'm sure that maybe...
No judgment.
I mean, I'm into it.
Oh, Tigger, he picked it out.
I'm going to pick...
I'm going to paint tiger stripes on myself.
That is offensive.
Just because I can't.
That's offensive.
Hey, I'll be in my own pleasure, Soster.
Your tiger won't be there to be offended.
I'm offended, knowing that you would do that.
I don't think that we...
I don't think that we can hang out anymore.
This is...
No, no.
It's Siberian tiger stripes.
Oh.
You know, like, white and black.
Fluffy white.
So, like, a zebra.
So, my tiger would think you're food.
Yeah.
Cool.
Come over.
See what happens.
I got raptors, though.
Just saying.
Raptor tiger fight!
Wait, I've had that dish at the restaurant before.
Oh, that is such a good one.
It's like...
It's like shark shrimp.
Eagle tiger fight?
Scrimp.
Yeah.
Phoenix and dragon.
Oh, yeah.
I think it's what it was.
But I think what it was is really shrimp and sturgeon.
And not to disappoint any Pokemon Go fans out there that might be living in the same fantasy
world that I once did, but apparently Gyarados is a sturgeon.
Which, in real life, looks just like a Gyarados in my fantasy world.
But it's like...
It's terrifying.
A sturgeon?
There's terrifying beasts.
They're like...
They're scaly and have teeth.
Monsters!
With fins on them somewhere.
That is many fish you just described.
Every fish.
Every fish is scaly.
But extra scaly.
Extra...
No, like planks.
Yeah.
Like platelets.
Yeah, like...
Giant...
Godzilla-like scales.
No, Gyarados.
It's a Pokemon.
Anyway, so like...
Sorry.
Basically...
Confusing my genres here.
Horrible monsters of the...
Not ocean.
Not that deep.
And there's more than one kind of them.
Now, in Pokemon, we can get lucky ones.
In Hawaii, Aloha ones or whatever it was.
Or there's also shiny ones now as well as the regular ones.
But I don't think there are that many types of sturgeons available for fishing.
In the real world.
But I do know that Primus wrote a song about them.
Which one was that?
It's about a sturgeon.
I thought that was weird.
Weird Al.
No, no.
No, that's like a sturgeon.
And that is...
Spawning for the very first time.
Like a sturgeon.
I got stuck on your 20 test line.
There you go.
Ooh.
Yeah, that's actually...
Because I've heard that one.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Actually, the part of the...
It was like I pulled in a 60-pound sturgeon on a 20-pound test.
You know, kind of thing.
Oh, there you go.
It was actually a very beautiful song that...
The Fish On song.
Yeah.
Yeah, there you go.
I got that tape.
Yeah.
As opposed to Float On by the...
No, not that one.
The Sad Mice, which we talked about earlier.
They get eaten by the raptors.
The Mice of Humility.
So modest they were.
Yeah, they didn't want to...
They didn't want to wear the sequined gowns.
Not bragging at all.
At the dinner party.
They wanted to just wear their demure...
Rodents.
Yeah.
That band.
The demure...
Can we do like a cover band?
A modest mouse cover band?
All women.
Like the demure rodents.
We'd have to give it maybe a slightly better name.
Like some kind of rodent in particular, maybe.
Maybe it doesn't even have to be a rodent, but rodent-like.
Maybe.
Demure lemurs.
Yeah.
Rodent-like.
I don't know.
Demure lemur.
Yes.
I like it.
It's ladyfied.
It could be mopey.
Mopey lemur.
Yeah, let's go rock out to some mopey music.
You ready?
Mm-hmm.
All right, cool.
That's great.
Oh, just wanted to shout out to the rest of the subgeni out there from the women of Austin.
Kudos to everybody that's doing their bit, not doing a thing.
And we'll check with you next time.
Thank you so much for stopping by the revered Overlord Animal.
Oh, anytime.
Anytime, Dr. Brujaha, you know, that I feel like imposing myself, I will.
Thank you.
Yeah, no problem.
You'll like it.
I remember back when I was almost a terrorist.
I think it was 1950, 60, 70.
You were like 9 or 10 years old, Dave?
I was like 9 or 10 years old.
That's what it was.
And I had made up my mind that I was going to conquer the world in my own name.
You know what I mean?
Like Charlemagne, Dave the Great, something like that.
Well, we all did that one.
When we were 10.
You get your sister to bring all her friends over,
and then you have to teach them all kinds of weird stuff.
And then they get bored and beat you up.
Yeah.
Yeah, we've all been through it.
Until our drunken parents come home, pull down their underpants and say,
Hey, kids, take a look at this.
Oh, God, man, you're bringing back real horrible memories, Dave.
Don't go there.
That's what I'm trying to do.
Oh, man, you're triggering me.
I'm triggered.
I'm trying to try.
Freaking out.
I'm trying to trigger you.
I'm having flashbacks.
I'm doing it on purpose.
These are the first letters that I was forced to recreate over and over in the sandwich.
Number four, number three, number eight, number two.
Yeah.
See, I know all those numbers.
I don't know what they mean, but...
But they're lucky.
Yeah, they're lucky.
You can tell they're lucky.
Yeah.
They're lucky.
Unfortunately, not for me, but...
I was trying to figure whose breath I was hearing.
It wasn't mine.
It could have been mine because it...
Sounds like bellows in the background.
Huge bellows.
I think it was Dave's nose.
Does it sound like my nose now?
Here's what mine sounds like.
Oh, what a little dainty, girly nose.
Well, Dave, I had my nose up against the radio microphone, not my phone phone.
Here, I'll do it with my phone.
All the pretenders to the throne say that.
That sounds like the...
The EvacuGen ward in the hospital.
That was a stereo breathing.
Well, when the doctor had me do that, he said,
Oh, you're fine.
Then he got in the bed with you and pulled up the nighties, pulled up the blankies, right?
No.
Then he told me how much my co-pay was.
Well, it's the same thing as what he was trying to do before, only in a different way.
Same difference.
Yep.
The rape.
It's rape.
The co-pay was rape.
But not his fault.
It's the insurance company.
That's my fault for getting a cheap insurance.
Yeah, but he...
He wanted the electronic hoard.
If I wanted to avoid paying that $30 co-pay, I should have paid the $1,300 a month insurance bill.
Then I would have avoided paying that $30 co-pay.
Wouldn't that be a smart thing to do?
What a great idea.
But who wants anything smart to happen?
Not a subgenius, apparently.
And not a human normal, either.
Apparently, nobody wants anything.
It's like anything that ticks off the smart people, oh, that's what they want to do.
Just show those smarty pants what for.
Even if it destroys your own town and environment, at least as long as it sends a signal to Hillary or Obama,
because they're still president, and that's all that counts.
Yeah.
Because they're evil.
I don't want.
I heard that on the radio.
They're the...
What do you call it?
The secret state?
The deep state.
They're the deep state that actually won the election while losing it.
Yeah, that's exactly right.
They actually won.
They're in charge.
Yeah, they made it look like they lost it, but they really just dug in even deeper.
They're that deep.
They're so deep.
They're right underneath China.
Yeah.
They're so deep.
If they go much further, they'll be on the surface.
They won't be deep at all.
They'll be right up front, but they'll be in China, and the Chinese will kill them.
Yep.
That's what they're doing in Hong Kong now.
They're beating up all the testicles.
Yeah.
And telling them, you know, you're not allowed to flambé the equipment around here, buddy
boy.
Remember the great leap forward.
If you can barely vaguely walk backwards, you've got to remember the great leap forward.
Yeah.
Oh, God.
Oh, man.
Over the days.
You know, I had personal friends in China who lived through the Cultural Revolution.
It wasn't fun, and they barely survived.
Yeah, I know.
I guess I shouldn't joke about it, but I can't help it.
I will joke about all kinds of narcotic things.
Braunschweiger, old goats, anything that's taboo.
We're willing to take on them.
There's one good thing about it.
Don't you think so?
He's fading.
You know, I think I'm fading.
My machine here says that we've been on the air for 108.
I believe that it has been.
I was looking at that as well to see about how long it had been.
Well, the first eight minutes was actually me futzing around trying to remember what
I was doing.
I was going to say.
Oh.
Yeah.
Then I got a hold of Dave.
Good.
And we had to call him back twice.
Oh.
But it was okay.
Okay.
Everything's okay.
Good.
So we can take the buzzer now?
It must have been a crappy show because Buddy and Claudia slept through the whole thing
and never applauded or barked or made any noises or anything.
Buddy is yawning right now.
Put them both to sleep.
Oh, he's yawning.
So that's a slackful show.
Yes.
It doesn't get people all aggravated.
It just puts them to sleep.
Yep.
Put some cartoon bubbles over their heads saying, man, that's old and stuff like that.
Actually, the Dave call has only been going on for 59 seconds or minutes.
So if I quit it right now, if this is the end of the show, then we're done.
Post office box, 8-9-1.
07 Glen Rose, Texas 76043 or subgenius.com.
Well, I'm going to go right now.
Is there something I must attend to?
Yeah.
Is that what they're calling it now?
Okay, Dave.
Well, Dave, be careful.
Thank you for sharing your wisdom with us.
I am a wise person.
He's a wise person.
He's got his wisdom and his humours.
He shared his humours with us, too.
Some people can't recognize sarcasm.
No, but seriously.
You mocking my wisdoms?
No, man.
Man, I'm the occultist's guide to better history.
I think you just ...
It's true, Dave.
We love you, man.
We love you.
Sure.
Sure, man.
I've heard that before.
Price Bob.
Okay.
Have a happy birthday.
Praise Bob if you can.
Hail Cotton.
.
Hey, Dan.
When I'm calling you
Will you answer too?
That means I offer my love to you
To be your own
If you're asking me
If you refuse me
I will be blue
And waiting all along
But if when you hear
My love call ringing clear
And I hear your answering echo so dear
Then I will know
Our love will come true
You'll belong to me
I'll belong to you
guitar solo
You'll belong to me
I'll belong to you
You
Hey listeners
Don't you want to live in a historic
Previously
Stang and We Are Doe
Owned house
This is like the birthplace of
Church of the Subgenius and Starwood
Not actually but
Those two things did live there
For a long time
And it's a wonderful
Nice
Solid old house
Beautiful hardwood
Details
In a beautiful wonderful neighborhood
With high taxes
That means
You know it's not low
Lives they don't they run you out
If you're a low life
We had to work real hard not to get run out of there
And we left it
Just like we found it
It is a beautiful home
In a wonderful neighborhood
Close to fine schools
And a shopping market
Within a shopping center
Within a walking distance
Two blocks away
With a bank, post office, grocery store
And Dave's
Dave's
Yes
You gotta wear a snorkel
What are you waiting for
Buy that house
Today
Well if you like it
Like built in cabinetry
And faceted leaded glass windows
Yeah
You'll be in luck
Yeah the Bob Museum used to be in there
Spectacularly beautiful
Many people find that one of the most desirous places
To live in the Cleveland area
Is in the Heights there
Yes
Yeah it's a nice middle class neighborhood
It's very park like
Big trees
The next street over looks like
Beaver Cleaver Street
Looks like a leave it to beaver title scene
Castle like houses
Yeah
Not our block
But the next one
But the next block over
Yes
Yeah
Oh it's mixed
Like a New York neighborhood
There's Hasidic Jews
There's artists of every stripe
Queers and weirdos of every possible kind
All colors
All getting along and going to block parties together
Mmhmm
You know
Ethnics of every kind
It's like a Jehovah's Witness pamphlet picture of heaven
Mmhmm
And you can have this
By buying our house
And freeing us from this onerous and terrible burden
That's just about wiped us out man really
Come on
Yep
Houses in Cleveland are incredibly cheap compared to say this area
Or North Texas
Or Cleveland
Or Califip
I mean our house would sell for a million bucks
Easy easy
In San Francisco
And the yard would sell for another two million
Mmhmm
Yep
But it's in Cleveland
Right
Yeah
So people may be like
Yeah it might as well be Detroit
It's cold there
Yeah it's a hell hole
I've heard all the jokes about Cleveland
It's a hell hole
All over it's just trash
It's a dump
Actually that only describes parts of Cleveland
Much of it has come back
Has bounced back from the dire ancient days
When the river was so toxic it was flammable
Yep
There's one or two live fish in that river now
And you can rent a kayak and go out in the poodle
I mean the pond
And take a long long trip
And hope the Coast Guard didn't come by and arrest you for
Terrorism
Yeah terrorism
Yeah
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to do that
You're the boss
Thanks for the frog
Can't do this
Frog
How much was that triceratops?
Cause whatever it was I gotta send Dave that much
14 dollars
Okay
That's it
That's an incredible deal for 14 bucks
I know
Well, one guy was charging, there were three different guys working there.
One was charging $14 and another one was charging $16.
I got it from the one that was charging $14.
Some son of a bitch.
Wait a minute, that doesn't make any sense.
This thing's handmade.
I know.
It's been hammered into shape.
Yes.
I know.
And all those welds, you know, every one of those welds.
It's welded and screwed together and painted.
It's painted.
Yeah, and it's got all kinds of detailing on it and $14.
Yep.
These are desperate damn times.
If an artist is selling that, that means he sold it to the dealer.
Well, this was the tiniest one.
Right, but that means he sold it to the dealer for $5.
There was a bigger one that was $24 and an even bigger one that was $34.
And they had the same thing in.
There were Tyrannosaurus.
There were Brontosaurus.
But I got us the Triceratops because we kind of have a collection.
Yeah, we kind of do.
We sure as hell do.
Triceratops crossing.
They're meant to be outside.
Yeah.
Oh, we're doctors.
Holy hit.
Don't worry.