Oh, yeah.
It's a form of sacrilege.
It's a form of disconsecration of the vowel sounds made by your very existence
as you twizzle and twazzle DNA,
as you weasel and wazzle your slimy way,
up and down and out of life.
Hong Kong, the hub of the Orient.
And now it is time for us to conclude our visit
and reluctantly say,
Hong Kong, the hub of the Orient.
Thank you for joining us tonight.
Now, I just heard in the report that
the subgenius powerhouse
That is correct.
to engage in this attack.
That's correct.
We have a number of individuals that have had girls from 15 to 25.
Jeez.
Why, what, why, what, why?
I have a list of about 20 of them.
They're like 14, 15, 16.
Any photos?
That's correct.
You've changed since you've come to Hollywood.
I started to work.
I'm a little bit more experienced.
And I don't mind telling you,
it's no change for the better.
What?
You're wearing a mask.
I'll explain the mask later, Mr. Jackson.
Now.
It's fun time.
I just can't understand it.
Oh, yeah?
Maybe it's just because you're stupid.
Well, yes, Wally.
Sure.
Punch yourself in the nose.
No.
Now do you see why I was amused?
Maybe it's just because you're stupid.
Really?
Oh, of course.
Right.
Yeah, you're right.
There was another normal night
And I got done fighting with my wife
So I went down to the bar
And just conveyed all the androids
Since I was elitist
They've been the two best friends that a man could ever hope for in this world
Now I'm a normal guy and I work all day for my money
And I fear the good Lord like I know I should
I ain't no new age coot but I gotta get this off my chest
And put this tragedy behind me now for good
I remember getting drunk and I remember falling down
And someone laid me on a pool table and I'd have been too soon
Then through the blinding lights two creatures stared into my eyes
As if a jukebox or a flying saucer spread around the room
And I'd tell myself this couldn't have been a member of the human race
Had to be them sex-crazed little green men from outer space
Well it hit me like trouble in the back of my head
Knocked me clean out of my shoes
And when I woke up Lord I wished that I was dead
I had got off the case of those abduction blues
And I'd tell myself this couldn't have been a member of the human race
This must have been an abduction, Lord, cause I don't know what happened
Hit me like a bolt out of the blue
Now I think I'm really crazy but I know that it wasn't them
Say the things that they can't do and never do
Well when at last I woke both my legs they had been broke
Both my eyes were black and my ears were springing bad
I'd seen enough of nasty things but this was the worst case
Of intergalactic relations I've ever had
And I'd tell myself this couldn't have been a member of the human race
Had to be them sex-crazed little green men from outer space
Cause it hit me like trouble in the back of my head
Knocked me clean out of my shoes
And when I woke up Lord I wished that I was dead
I had got off the case of those abduction blues
This must have been an abduction, Lord, cause I don't know what happened
Hit me like a bolt out of the blue
Now I think I'm really crazy but I know that it wasn't them
Say the things that they can't do and never do
Never do
Never lie
Never look at me try you're not managed
Gnaw on SecretSearch they say
Never forget
The smell of gin
lizard skin.
I mean, a lot of people talk about the
lizard people.
That's a conspiracy
theory that
a lot of people are
real excited about. It's kind of old hat
for subgenius, diehard
old conspiracy theorists.
Those guys wear old hats. That's part of the whole conspiracy
of it. The DNA thing is
in front of it. Is that what the old hat thing is about?
Yeah.
Oh, man.
Spooky.
Spooky. Yeah.
Call something old hat, that means the DNA goes right
in your brain and changes you.
I think
that's what it means. Change.
Spare change, my friend.
Can you change your
ways? Can you quit telling
yourself you're awake
and enlightened long enough to
realize you're still asleep?
See, I'm the automatic robot that
goes around telling the other automatic robots
to wake up.
That's just what I do automatically.
You show them the pictures, don't you,
Stang? Yeah.
The pictures of the kneeling bodies, the scarce and
astounding naked bodies, of the
people with, oh yes, the old lady
that was brought in a late night drag
net, whose face was rubber hosed with a
with... More precisely,
I sell them the pictures.
Yes, you
sell them the pictures on the corner side.
Underneath the street lamp.
I have a pair of these pictures.
A pair of stiletto heels and fish head
stockings on your head.
I got an interesting letter from
a listener,
Reverend Fenian, who had just
started listening to the Hour of Slack fairly
recently.
About a year ago, actually. About a year ago, he started
listening to it on the internet. And what
attracted him about it was the
Oye guy.
He first started
tuning in about a year ago when we
were getting calls from the Oye
guy. You know what that is?
The sound of a poodle being sodomized.
Well, that was the thing. We later
found out from other DJs at the
station that indeed the Oye
guy was known
as famous as Masturbating
Sean was the name that he's known
by at the station and that
Princess, we and I were right.
It is a mantra.
Well, he brought great
disgrace on his name.
Well, it depends on how you look at it. It's a life-saving
mantra. His name should be shame.
Well, now
in some denominations, he gets
a special award pinned to his chest.
Well, sometimes it's in the form of
one of those
IEDs, really. Improvised
Exploding Devices. Friends, are you
wondering what the hell this is all about?
Are you wondering? Well, give up.
Stop! Stop it!
The subgenius
is probably the single
most important organization in the 20th
century. Our function is
quite literally to save the world.
At least make the end of the world
happen right.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Oh, yeah!
Your father lets you find Bob,
and you better find Bob right now!
The people really need
to be able to understand
things very quickly, and the church
of the subgenius, I think,
confuses him.
Confusing, isn't it?
I want to remind you of the great words of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
I don't practice what I preach
because I'm not the kind of man I'm preaching to.
Thank you, children, thank you.
Is there a typical subgenius?
Of course not.
The very thought is a blasphemy.
The only thing that most subgeniuses have in common
is that they're all different,
and they have nothing in common
with the conspiracy of the normals.
By definition, the Church of the Subgenius
can't really exist
because it's an organization for people
who are not joiners.
Eccentrics, unpredictables, true visionaries.
Let us observe a few examples
using the hidden camera.
It was in the first 30 issues of 9-inch worm comics
and I think in 14 issues of 4 1⁄2-inch worm comics.
Is this man a subgenius?
15 7-Eleven comics.
Those aren't the comics about 7-Eleven.
It's the adventures of a subgenius.
They have a person that works at 7-Eleven
that just writes down everything that happens.
They draw him up,
and the whole comic is shaped like a big 7-Eleven.
It's three-dimensional.
And they've got the idea from a flying saucer
that was shaped like a 7-Eleven
that flew over one night.
It was a UFO believed to be...
A subgenius, obviously.
The speech patterns are unmistakable.
They share only the quest for slack
and the love of their beloved spiritual teacher,
the living avatar of slack, J.R. Bob Dogg.
I was getting messages in the back of my brain
as long ago as about twelve or thirteen months,
and I just kept hearing the word, Bob.
Bob, Bob.
Bob is everywhere.
Bob is bursting out all over the place.
Bob!
If you look through any phone book in any city, you get the same thing.
Bob's Construction Company.
Bob's Pornhouse.
Bob's Factory.
Bob's Auto Parts.
Bob's Automotive Service.
Bob's Learning Locals.
Bob's Dentistry.
And then down here we've got Bob's Used Furniture Store.
I mean, he's like everybody's dad should be.
Bob's is about as American as you can get.
Bob's TV.
Bob's Online.
There's no laughing matter.
And a plane is determined to take us with it.
Even if it means force.
I'll handle this.
Hey, wait a minute, you guys.
Put your guns away.
You know, Wally, that's just what I'm going to do.
Hello.
We're glad you called us about masturbation.
You'll probably hear a lot of dumb and scary things about masturbation from your family doctor.
Masturbation is touching and handling your school nurse in a way that creates pleasurable sexual feelings.
For most people, masturbating is physically harmful.
Now, we like masturbation.
But if you masturbate, it can be psychologically harmful.
It could mess up your head.
In fact, masturbation makes you go crazy or blind.
If this happens, it may indicate a serious problem.
The problem, however, is lack of masturbation.
Spin punishing shots and it's over.
Woo!
Ow!
A wet, wet kiss, baby.
Oh, my God.
Man!
Well, young, old!
Splashing our way on in!
Yep.
In towards X-Day.
It has all been encapsulated and brought into one mighty compaction unit.
It is ready for the force field to be enacted.
It is ready for decompartmentalization and transport across the universe.
Sorry.
That's what they're doing with those people in Iraq, right?
Those prisoners of war?
Yeah.
Well, I think it's a new, like, club or something like that.
And have you noticed everybody's giving the thumbs up sign?
It's an S&M type, an S&M club.
Yeah, and everybody gives, like, the kind of wink and the thumbs up sign, like, hey, man, I humiliated some person.
I've noticed that according to the media, the only torturers and abusers are really hot-looking girls.
Young, attractive, especially red-headed girls.
Well, the one girl that they showed who was giving the thumbs up, I suppose her excretory function was not correct.
Or else she wouldn't have always wanted to do the old proctology boogie with all those people.
I think that, you know, they're just following orders.
And they're being given orders by people who want those soldiers to be able to do it to them when they get back to D.C.
Until they use their safe word.
Or say maybe if the Fedayeen get them.
And so they want to know that they're going to get them.
The same kind of friendly treatment.
Say, for instance, it might have a slight Muslim or Arabic slant to it.
Like maybe, you know, there might be little cuts and so forth.
But it'll still be the same hot action you get everywhere across the world with the new G.W. Bush world engram under which we're stamped.
Say hi, baby!
I can't.
Now, Dave, let's not be extremists and go to prison.
Let's not be extreme unctionists.
Because we're all headed towards the same purple necktie, baby.
You know what I'm saying?
It's like you're in jail.
Whether you're, even if you're out on the street, you're still in jail.
You're such a man, you still gotcha.
As long as you're wearing a wristwatch, you're in prison.
It's a slave planet.
The world as you know it is nothing but a cell block.
And you're on the violent world.
You wonder what you're eating.
Do you think it is pork and beans?
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Yes, there's pork and beans in it, all right, my friend.
But it is mostly a substance of your own brain matter.
Yeah, it's organ slush.
The tiny piece of metabolic fluids.
The apocytic fluids.
Yeah.
Oh, excuse me.
We have recreated you.
Never mind.
Dave, do your neighbors consider you to be different, outstrained?
Do they give you funny?
Funny looks.
Well, they are incapable of giving looks, my friend.
With the eyes ripped out of their sockets and only the little oblong pills exposed,
what can they really see?
Not the oblong pins.
Little tiny things for their own gratification.
They push back the balls away in their head.
You take the red pill and you stay asleep.
Take the blue pill and you'll run around telling everybody that you're more awake than the next guy.
What?
Which?
Which one did you take?
I took the round pill.
I took the square.
Well, it's kind of octagonal.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
But it didn't matter.
I heard about people that took the oblong pill.
And either one is red or blue.
Not a good story.
It looks like there's a force field around each and every one of them.
They made me take the pill that makes you tell everybody about pills.
They made me take the pill that causes you to go on and on and on about how you're more awake.
Than somebody else if you take this other pill.
But that's really just because you took the pill that makes you say that you're awake and alert and noticing the real world.
And, you know, it's like...
It's the same thing over and over and over again.
One layer of the onion peeled away and it's still a damn onion.
There's nothing to do but fry it in the pan and hope you get a whooping in your titty-totty can.
Sit down, little man.
We have a message here.
It's encrypted.
But you may be able to make out some of it.
You're slated for some sort of...
What do we call it?
That's the...
No, that's the more erotic, neo-neurotic way.
Torture?
Torture.
Or as John Stewart...
I heard John Stewart called it freedom tickling.
One room at a time, buddy.
Freedom tickling?
Yeah.
Well, speaking of normals and everybody we hate, here's a song from the old Bonzo Dog Band about your neighbors.
Mm-hmm.
Ha, ha.
Yo, what do you call me?
A cross of sense.
A common sense.
My God, a mouth of blood.
Will win a prize.
Won't that be nice?
And by the way, how's your wife?
Your holidays were spent in space.
You went by train.
You'll go again.
Have you seen me bullfight poster on the wall?
Do you know?
the happy memory it recalls.
Here's a photograph of me and my son Ted.
That's me cousin with his achy on his head.
We booked in at our hotel
just after two and met a family
from Bradford that we knew.
What a melody!
Yeah!
Mama belongs to me!
Todd has made saxophones solo as promised.
Wiping half of the terrain pipe
Semi-detached ship
Tedder
Wiping half of the terrain pipe
Oh Mama
belongs to one!
I've a sister in Toronto who's a nurse
and I've had a bit of bother laying turf.
It's life, not books that taught me all I've learnt.
Burp in the above and my rice pudding's getting burnt.
Here, have you seen the new attachment on me drill?
I must have a cat put down cos he's ill.
Oh!
Hey, neighbour!
Wiping half of the terrain pipe
I may change his cool.
It's missing from you.
I'm a lovely jelly, you're a paint revange.
I'm a cheery trifle, you're a chocolate sponge.
You're a glass of paper, mine are freaks balloons.
Whoops!
Here comes the sponge.
Wiping half of the terrain pipe
Separates me from the incredibly fascinating story of your life.
And every day today you vent in all its minute and tedious attention to detail.
And was it a Thursday or a Wednesday or...
Oh no, it wasn't so. Who cares anyway?
Cos I do not sew normal.
If you're normal, I intend to be a freak for the rest of my life.
And I shall baffle you with cabbages and rhinoceroses in the kitchen
in sets and quotations from now we are six through the mouthpiece of Lord Snoop.
And c*** isn't electric.
F***in'ished.
SOLDӖ poles
according to this
fin
My poverty but not my will consent.
I pay thy poverty and not thy will.
Put this in any liquid thing you will and drink it off.
And if you had the strength of twenty men, it would dispatch you straight.
Here is thy gold.
Worst poison to men's souls.
Doing more murder in this loathsome world than these poor compounds that thou mayst not sell.
What is the taste of crunchy clusters?
Perfect forever.
And it got in the spokes of the wheel and it choked her to death.
Uh, uh, well I'll...
No, no, no.
It's the Senate vote.
Aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye, aye.
Back to the very beginning of the first part.
Underneath annoyances starting with a petty, bastardly, tiny, minuscule, overbearing, all-encompassing...
No!
You can remove the sinus here.
Just pull that very, very gently.
Just take out my left sinus passage here.
Get the whole thing right out.
Ready to have the third nostril put right in.
You kids quit playing with your little third nostril toys there.
Are you kids?
Third nostril opener toys.
Yeah, get away from this little machine.
And put the hands off the third nostril straffinator.
All you peep-ups, get off of the lawn.
Bonzo Dog Band did my pink half, my pink half of the drainpipe.
Separates me from the tedious, endless email from bobbies and numbskulls,
idiots and well-wishers, do-gooders and nimrods.
Mad well, that's what you're famous, my brother.
Now do well, those who have nothing not more in mind than to do you ill, yes?
The destruction of the Reverend Ivan Stank.
I have seen their writs.
I have seen their manifesto.
Hey, speaking of weirdos and stuff.
I've seen their...
Hey, hey, hey.
We've got a show coming up.
We can't...
I wouldn't exactly recommend this to anybody, but there is a subgenius devival.
They should be made aware.
They should be made somewhere.
On May 22nd, Saturday night at the Beachland Ballroom.
It's a touch of the old sarcophagus.
You know, it makes you feel like you've gone and gone on,
and you can't get back out in here.
Well, the girls are going to be there.
Reverend Nikki Deathchick will be...
Snaking?
And her nun snakes will be applying the bondage spankings of guilt relief or guilt or something.
I always get...
I will be applying my own special brand of nasal pressure to the third nostril cruise.
I'm sorry.
And those beautiful girls in the amino acids, they're a masked surf music band,
surf punk instrumental masked alien band who are actually beautiful girls underneath those masks.
You wouldn't think...
Or beautiful goats, depending on which transvibrational level you come from.
They never take the masks off, and they look like men.
Or something like men.
Yeah, but they are goats.
Beyond human semblance.
I've seen their molecules evaporate.
Beyond mere humans.
I've seen the petri dish with the goat horn and the piece of magic eye.
I know what...
Oh, here they are playing in the background.
Oh, Lord.
I can hear them.
Well, that's not the amino acids, but it's close enough.
I think it's Robert Johnson about to sing.
Can you call me Bucka?
Bucka.
That's a bad dream.
The amino acid.
This is the Pobucker theme.
This is the Pobucker theme?
I didn't know they had theme music.
Just a Pobucker.
I'm just an old Pobucker to you.
They call me Bucka.
Silence is a bug.
Just a Pobucker.
Be quiet now.
Put your hand on the thermometer.
Oh, and that other...
That Pobucker named Man Incorporated.
The one man band will also...
And that actually is a pretty...
The impressive one fellow.
How about the dopamine tyrants?
The beaters of serotonin, which will come in a flood.
Oh, the Minoan brain eaters.
Yeah, they'll probably be there.
They'll flood into your brains.
And Reverend Carter LeBlanc, who is the good subgenius preacher,
as opposed to the rest of us.
And...
Man.
And the movie show.
Oh, and the movie show.
Yeah, the movie show.
And the nostril...
The nostril, third nostril openings.
The mind-melting movie show.
Yeah.
The people in their shells and their concomitant gestures.
Believe it or not, Scene Magazine called me up about that.
About the gestures?
And quizzed me about this.
Yeah, gestures.
What just...
What this lonesome cowboy Dave brain cell was going to do...
Oh.
In this big circus.
Oh, boy.
Whether he was going to be jumping through hoops or throwing himself into Bob's pipe or...
Any, you know...
I told her that we were basically going to nail you up on a cross and tote you around.
Oh, boy.
Do a takeoff on that famous religion.
I am from the Carolingian Brotherhood.
I am a member of the Zool Organization and I do not believe in your bastard Nazarene, pale Nazarene Jesus.
Oh, I do sometimes.
You know when it serves...
That's the scary part.
When it serves my purple, if you know what I'm saying.
Is that where we bring offerings of whipped cream, bowls of whipped cream down to your toes?
Little cherries, too.
Yeah.
That's what I thought.
Listen, little pink, little normal worm.
You didn't hire me last time I blessed you with a resume.
Now I'm back to buy your company and close it down.
Demolish it.
Pave over the ruins and forbid anyone to approach the site for 10,000 years.
Puzzle of Rail Change.
We're happy to take your call.
Please leave a message at the sound of the beep.
J.R. Bob's Arms Realty will not be in the office for the next 45 to 72 days.
If you would like to leave an email, please inquire at...
Look at all the bodies we've got today.
Thousands and thousands of people we can make bare naked and have them jump on a stick.
Oh, my God.
Oh, boy.
It's...
I can't believe we have so much meat to work with here.
I bring that old lady on over here.
I want to...
I want to teach her something about the cattle prod she never learned before.
She never heard.
I don't know.
It's, uh, you know, it's still just an unknown.
Subgeniuses.
Must be chameleons ready to don at a moment's notice the disguise of the normal.
They will endure the polyester of the pink if that's what is required in order to earn their daily bread
and grab a little slack for whatever awful things they do at night.
If Dr. Jekyll is not allowed to surface on some rare occasions,
Mr. Hyde will be captured.
Ha, ha, ha.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Okay, here's what you want.
If you want to increase your value on your property,
if you want to increase the value of your holdings or stock holdings,
if you'd like to increase anything at all, perhaps your IQ,
if you'd like to increase the actual size of your brain,
you know, a lot of times the brain will start weapon down,
you know, much, pretty much like one of those ancient birds.
You know, it's got the same kind of profile.
It just, uh...
But if you can, uh, say, for instance, get your hand on the right kind of material,
like a quartz crystal or something like that,
uh, just...
Oh, yeah, it works just like a baby dog.
Yeah, it's a charm.
And I mean...
Some subgeniuses never for an instant cease to project a contrived hate
indiscriminately despising everything normal.
But that's just another way of ignoring the vagaries of life
in favor of some escapist formula, some rule book.
It only proves they are normals because they haven't caught on yet
that by definition, half of what they call normal
is actually stranger than normal.
And them, they just don't get its strangeness
because they can't tell the difference
between bulldonner, stupid, and camp.
And here in our camp is lonesome cowboy Dave.
I am not in your camp,
nor have I ever been a member of your...
You can't hide from normality!
You cannot hide from the all-seeing eye that peers everywhere.
I'm a puppy!
Campers around here, but no...
It's in the lavatories.
It's in the basement.
It's in the foot lockers.
It's over in the closet space there.
It's in the broom closet.
It's where they put the cats and hoes.
It's over where they have...
War, friends.
War, war, war.
Huh!
What is it good for?
What's the use of dying if we're already going to live anyway?
What the...
Yes, sir.
The books are just like...
Go ahead.
Do you ever...
Uh...
No.
I did.
But...
Middle...
Which is...
Always...
An...
Piece of...
Maybe...
That he might say...
What is...
Bring...
On...
The...
Map...
No.
Poo-poo.
Of it.
It's...
All over me, man.
Might as well.
Never on it all.
Did you ever think this guy was a great blue blueberry pie?
Yeah.
It makes me hungry when I think about that.
Did you ever think...
Did you ever think this guy was a great big blueberry pie?
Yeah, and I wanted to stick it in my thumb and pull out a plum.
Well, you're right.
It is.
Bad.
Yeah.
Um.
Crazy, man.
Oh, that music in the background there was by Norrell Preff.
That killer guitar music.
That was Norrell Preff Instrumental.
Norrell FF is Rachel.
W.
E.
K.
We heard music earlier in the show.
A hip-sodic.
And this in the background is Ed Fred.
Ed Fred music, I think.
And they leave the earth, their troubles melting like lemmings.
I mean, Brian dropped that awning to town.
I didn't notice that a большой?
I understood that.
They were staring long ago at one of the
And they were getting laid off obviously first.
They know either someone's gonna take that guy for a ride or they won't.
The country 가장...
We're really, really surprisingly hireless.
witnessing this it's a war between the dopamine and the serotonin each man have their own troops
their little vehicles their fighting tanks their mighty mighty military robots each and every one
of them is a vessel designed by satan but don't worry
oh i just remembered something i've got
scary scary thing
a scary thing oh no no no well uh what it is is uh you know over the years those uh those
altbein
Binary Slack creatures.
Where I scrape a lot of the sound for the hour of Slack off of.
Nice, you scrape.
Binary Slack where you download the weird audio and the weird pictures from subgenius land.
Those guys have been cutting up little pictures of sounds for millions of years and have made tiny, funny, goofy one-liners.
Little fissures on the side of the statues.
One, two, ready, go.
And that's on the one side of the head.
And the other side of the head is much more.
Subgenius gravy where you scrape up the bits.
Well, you know, these types do rip your brain in half.
They take the left ear and the right ear and yank them apart.
And so just pay attention.
How awesome is thisty containopel?
Whoa, it's so—
Hello?
Hey, look at this нее.
She's literally saying,
This cake is so shiny.
Wow, what the, no-no, no no no
Can she make that?
New Boulder first grade. Genuinely beautiful. Giant. Perfect. Cool. Special. Cheered. Labyrinth. Easy. Ultimate. Best. Natural. Growing. Special. Nice. Proud. Quicker. And much more.
It's a jolly, jolly Bob show.
It's jolly.
It's so jolly.
Funny Bob show.
It's jollier than jolly.
It'll mess you up.
It's so jolly it makes me laugh.
It'll steal your soul if you let it.
It'll mess with your soul.
Tasty prairie squid spread.
Salted and unsalted variety.
Available on the East Coast only.
The radioactive cloud is now over Little Rock.
Crager shat piercingly.
This is really amazing.
Ergo, those that refuse the program while a minority, if unchecked, would constitute an escalating probability of disaster.
Bob!
Ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba.
The following order is to be carried out immediately.
It's not a crutch, Dad.
It's something I've come to rely on to help me through life.
Praise the Lord.
I think this is about the sixt.
Sickest, sickest thing I've ever heard on KFJZ, and since I've been listening to it.
I gotta have some slack.
Slack.
It's pretty faster than any other leading cleanser.
Our advanced analyzer software helps you quickly sort through expensive diapers.
And our streaming data page enables you to size up body parts.
I'm going to bypass your forebrain and appeal directly to your amygdala.
Oh, don't grin!
Okay, grin!
Don't grin!
Ah!
This is civilization's jungle, after the jackals of society have ruthlessly ravaged it, ending the world of decency.
Haven't had time for your kind of woman.
Don't touch me, I can't stand you!
But all you're remembering is merely a series of sensory impulses which you now realize have no real definite connection with outside reality.
True. But since this is so, I have no proof that you are really telling me all this.
I have no time to make a show of loving kindness before my fellow men. Not in this life. I've too much laughing to do.
Hurrah!
Unfair to kick a man when he's down.
Let's get him up on his feet.
We're gonna have to get him up on his feet.
Excellent!
He will not reveal his identity, so for today, we're calling him Bob.
Men and women of all races and breeds pause to destroy the Earth.
I sometimes feel that I am impersonating the dark subconscious of the whole human race.
It's what's left of the blood.
There's a strongforce.
Bob.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Bob.
What's that? What's that?
Fantastic things have already happened, and more are getting ready to happen.
This is because the planet on which you're residing has entered the space age.
You are a most unusual individual
And decidedly in the minority
Oh, another victim of confusion?
Decidedly
Oh, that's crazy talk
I think Bob is just a guy with a pipe
Well, we're all pretty much, aren't we?
I'm sorry
Do you think Bob is just a guy with a pipe?
Are you just a guy with a pipe?
Well, it's like a form of dialectic
You could divide the world into different cramps
That you were talking about cramps before
You could have some who believe that
It's just a guy with a pipe
And others who dynamically believe
You know what I'm saying?
Like when they say it
They look at each other and they're like
Yeah, man, it's just a guy with a pipe
You know what I mean?
A special glimmer in each other's eyes
And they can give each other
The high sign or different signs
To truly believe
To truly let all brain cells die
That must be good
Well, that's our goal
That's the goal of each and every individual aspirer
Or perspirer
Anybody who wants to attain that certain secondary
I don't know what it is
I guess you can read things
But you know what I'm saying?
We all need this
I know what you're saying
We all need slack
It's in a manufactured need
Must have slack
Must have
And slag
Must have slag
Must have
Yeah, when they buried the poor little guy
He was as bloated as a grape
He had to use a rake to pull him out of the pond
He'd been swearing up and down
He was gonna do it all week
He said if Bob didn't give him a call
Or he didn't get some word
About that 30 bucks he sent that damn
What's his name?
Oh, that 30 bucks
Well, now, now, you know.
Yeah, baby!
It's all coming down.
Civilization, that is.
Falling apart.
Falling to pieces.
You're part of it.
You're part of the problem, not the solution.
You're one of the tiny cracks, man.
You're one of the little fissures pulling the thing down.
You're one of the things, you know, reducing it to a common, a common, common.
So do the right thing, man.
Go ahead and jump.
Just get it over with.
Yeah, get it over with, man.
Go on and get it over with, then.
It's so easy.
And your troubles will melt like lemming drops as you fall off the edge of a cliff.
So, so high up over there.
You'll see.
It's a beautiful, breathtaking dive.
A hundred feet down to the new beach and rocks below.
Lombada.
Ah, the Lombada, the dance of love.
Practiced by Bob and Connie in the heat and feverish passion of their desire.
Oh, and you, too, can glean some of the sweaty, sheeny, shiny,
sweet,
wet off of their skin.
If you will just do as your master Bob says and fetch the paper every morning,
bring him his slippers and his little pipe loaded for bear and join us, humans,
in our subterranean tunnels of love.
You're going to have to ripen first.
You're going to have to be a little more, a little more less.
Yes, you just have to lose a little bit of those excess brain cells you've been tripping over.
Really, that's it.
They're not much.
Lombada.
What we're trying to say is dance the Lombada.
The Lombada.
Lombada.
Easy, easy program thing.
People could get involved with almost like a form of aerobics.
People want to lose weight.
They want to shed those unnecessary LBs.
They want to bring the kilos down, and yet at the same time,
they want to bring their own architecture up.
So what do they do?
They run around little circles.
They get on those bikes and things like that.
Well, how can they reduce their brain cells?
How can we...
How should we say it?
Lighten the load.
Up there.
where it's real heavy.
You know, a lot of people got fat butts.
A lot of people got a midriff.
A lot of people maybe got a saggy neck
or something like that.
But how many of us,
and I'm saying pretty much 90% to 100,000% of all of us,
have too much going on upstairs?
We've eaten too many psychic donuts
and there's psychobalk.
That's an old world.
I didn't make that up.
Well, Dave, there's an answer.
There is an answer.
That's where break thinking comes in.
Bob teaches a technique called break thinking
by which you completely disconnect the mind.
This is also called a path to higher consciousness-lessness.
Can that help the bulges in my brain?
It's to create smooth noodle maps,
as depicted by Devo.
I love smooth.
Yes, to smooth the maps on your noodle,
to smooth down the corrugations,
which contain so many excess thoughts,
thoughts of unfairness and sadness
that you don't want to think about.
Smooth it down and have only simple,
simple thoughts of happiness.
You're a pro-phylactic,
Mobius-stripped thoughts running through and without.
Lisa, smooth.
One, two, cha-cha-bob.
Cha-cha-bob.
Blow the road up top.
Oh, hang on a minute.
No.
No, let's get away from that,
because nihilism is not where the...
This is not even really a church,
but nihilism is not where this organization
is going from head to fore.
Who cares about Neil?
We're into Bob.
Neil Innes, perhaps, if we could hear his song.
Yeah, Neil Innes with the great Bonzo Dog Man, sure.
Bonzoing again, but...
I'm not being nihilist.
We don't need that kind of...
We don't need that kind of destructive...
You can't stop me.
This is slathery.
You know, some people are afraid of slathering.
We're afraid of slavery.
We're afraid of slathering.
Like that one cosmic-minded guy
was saying on the internet,
negativity is bad, and positivity is...
I don't know.
...basically good.
I don't know about that.
Actually, positive thinking is what got us where we are now.
Positively.
...the bizarro world.
Mm-mm-mm.
No, I like square edges.
I like things that aren't too round and fuzzy.
I like, you know...
That's right, Virgil.
That's right, 90-degree head.
It's time for you to wear off the top of those spongy boxes
and return your brain to its original condition.
It's all in the bag.
It's a balance, you know.
Smooth as a noodle and paste.
Ignore or deny every reality.
Please.
Get the bigger picture.
As big as you fit some screen...
Big, big, big.
...in your head.
It's too big for my head.
Señor.
God made me do it.
How often do you say that, friend?
Is it too big for your head?
It's way too big for my head.
We have plenty more you can use for us.
Oh, okay.
Let me see some of those other ones over there.
And here they are.
We can see the plane.
Oh, okay.
I'm bringing in the shipments of giant heads
for these poor bereft people, these humans down here
with their small heads, their empty heads,
their sad, troubled heads seen so far down below us.
They look up at we who fly above,
us birdmen, junior and senior birdmen,
soaring so high above them in our slack
and our soft,
self-professed superiority, yes?
For we have the megaphone and are able to profess our superiority
so much louder than all of the others.
So much louder than ever before.
That's what we mean by the conspiracy.
The bully.
That's right.
The jerk.
The ass that pushes you around and never shuts up.
Say hi, Daddy.
Oh, oh, yeah.
Well, that part's over.
The party didn't have to end that way.
No, it didn't.
So many resculpted bodies, so much unused barbed wire.
So, so very many.
So many belts and gas bottoms and batteries
that didn't fit in the wrong confusion holes.
But that's their way of thinking, those silly musclemen.
How did they not?
Why didn't they?
They'll never, never know.
It's very simple.
Hi, embarrassing people stare at you.
Without a face.
The face terrified me.
You just want to be normal.
It's not the black head.
No, no, no, no, no.
Praise Bob.
You have consumed enough alcohol for one evening.
It is wasteful and pointless.
Obey and live or disobey and die.
I see no reason for violence.
You did take us to sleep.
If however you are confronted, you may resort to the use of hypnosis.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, God hates you.
Stay away from him.
Licentiousness, just unbridled, uncontrolled excesses.
That was something he invented.
And I say, as long as you're alive, shout, make noise.
Oh, whatever.
Because we.
Praise Bob.
You shut up like hell.
The future is always a lie.
nonsense until it becomes the past.
The American people have now spoken, but it's going to take a little while to determine
exactly what they said.
I'm afraid.
I'm afraid, Dan.
What's his name?
Wow.
Ain't that a bitch?
Don't you worry about us, Lord.
We may blow a few holes in your ceiling from time to time, but we give you fair warning
before we blow up the whole house.
Yes, fair warning before X-Day.
We told you, July 5th, this year.
This year might be 1998.
It could be 2012.
We have no idea.
It could be.
The records are all skewed in a scramble.
But it seems like this is the year, is it not?
Yes.
This is the year in which the raptured or ruptured ones, excuse me, I'm so sorry, I'm
confused with the other.
But the ruptured ones.
The ruptured ones are lifted up into space and whisked off somewhere.
That's what the fairy tale says.
It's a mythos.
That's what Bob said.
The actual mythos of the, well, I guess it goes back to Philo Drummond and Reverend Ivory
Stagg.
Ivory Stinks.
Quite an apt description of his olfactory, what he gives off, anyway.
But in the first place, what we find amongst many of these culties, these barbies, these
followers, is an extreme.
Extremely.
Detachment.
A disassociation.
An extreme.
A flat A smack.
Yes.
A null A sign on each one's forehead.
And each one waiting the ride to Venus and it never happens.
Yes.
But some, some return every year.
Then I thought, I could die doing this.
I guess this is going to prove myself once and for all that I'm down for Bob.
I'll help him do anything.
Bob.
Maybe that's all Bob is.
I'll say hello later.
Shut up about Bob, will you?
Go holly.
Just before Christmas, Bob followed through.
He walked into this bank north of Seattle and left with nearly $26,000, which he stashed
in a child's trick-or-treat bag.
Bob had good reason to smile again.
This won't make too much sense, but it's not intended to.
Give me slack, you frickin' lunacy.
I'm out of frickin' slack.
The lawless are on the loose, making it necessary for law-abiding citizens to make their own law.
Yes.
See you in the new TV.
Don't sass me.
Not only the marginally weird, but the entirely weird.
Oh, yeah.
We're clever to the scope of the church of the earth.
Right, right, right.
Not the, um...
Right, right.
So, yeah, we work up into the scope.
And some are made to wear the bellboy attendant hats and suits that look quite strange to some of the young members.
It's a treat for some of the ones who've gone on, so to speak.
Some have the bonsai.
Some have shrunk quite, quite, quite far down.
Yes, yes.
You can hardly make them out without...
And then some have the elephant titus.
Yeah, well, those are the ones that are quite introspective.
Introspective.
You see what happens?
Yes.
The more they think, the bigger their heads get.
And pretty soon, the calcium in the brain, they're not the brain.
The new...
Hey, I have a question.
I have a question.
Is this show for, like, people who are on drugs?
I hope not.
That is a hot-button subject.
I would hope that it would be the kind of thing that would replace the drugs, don't you see?
Exactly.
It's the repugnancy factor.
Dr. Stang is what we've been talking to.
Rather than merely an enhancement.
Rubber is leather.
Listen to this.
Who needs drugs?
Well, you might need them as an enhancement for this show.
I don't know.
In order to make it more palatable.
You may need a...
Oh, poppycock.
Or a doggy bag.
Or a pair of hairy, hairy socks.
That's a bunch of bushwhacky.
To give it the semblance of social value or...
Friends, if you want to know more...
Definitely a feeling that your mind is being monitored.
Bye, baby.
Your mind can be further monitored if you will simply write for free information if you're interested in more about the Church of the Sep Genius.
You can get some by mail from Bob at...
Well, actually, it's not Bob.
That would be ridiculous.
It's Jesus.
At Post Office Box 204206, Austin, Texas 78720.
That's the business headquarters, you might say, of the church.
The...
The second...
Or what is it now?
The fourth megafist temple lodge, the spiritual headquarters is, of course, here in beautiful Cleveland, Ohio.
And you can send tapes and CDs and such like to me, Reverend Stang, at subgenius.com, Post Office Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
What's our zip code?
One, four, one, one, eight.
Eight?
Yeah.
Eight.
You're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry, Hour of Slack, number 942.
There actually have been that many of them, although a few of those, I guess, were reruns.
The music in the background is the swinging love corpses, the collage of the
of noises that we heard were sourced from,
I got that stuff from all of the subgeniuses.
A special thanks to New Monet,
Fernand and Andy Lemur,
and Artemia Salina, I think,
for a whole lot of that.
I organized them myself
using the rules of chance.
Praise Bob and stay out of sleep.
Bob?
The professional pessimist.
In the past, he's been called
the prophet of gloom and doom,
the troubadour of trouble,
the disciple of despair.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Bob.
The unbalancing that happens
when you work with these people
makes you really question
what you know reality is.
Bob, Bob.
Everyone likes Bob.
Give me slack, you freaking lunatic.
Stop, fucker.
I'm out of freaking slack.
That's not how you get the bad news.
Oh, my God.
Slug, slug.
Now you see that evil will always triumph
because good is dumb.
I know nothing, nothing.
Doug's right, Virgil.
We are different.
Soon everyone will be a superior biospecies.
Even Doug Smith.
It's the good news, son.
Cry havoc!
And let's slit the dogs of war.
My boy, we're pilgrims in an unholy land.
Sex, sex, sex, 30, 30, sex, sex, sex, pay $30 and get six sex free.
Pills, pills, pills, Bob, Bob, feel me, Bob, feel me, Bob, do slack.
Pop, pop, zippy, frop, frop.
Hey, you smoking?
No, but the pipe is.
Good.
That's a gag.
Ha ha, ha ha, ha ha.
Seb , Robert Zink, Sterling Wallace and Bruce Akins
Bob said to the fam they don't need благода.
Me, Bob said, He could have said it blackout 2014.
I threw this says fucking cunt on fire.
That's true.
My mind is going.
Stop.
My mind is not my mind.
One look at them will tell you more than a thousand words of mine.
Mom?