Alright, Bob is my only hope. Back off and give him some room to think.
Listen.
Alright, on one.
Going up in five, four, three, two, one.
The Sogenius Power of Swamp.
We'll meet again at midnight.
You are lucky, friends, that I'm busy.
Busy with secret projects.
Because when I can't assemble Hour of Slack number 957,
that means you get to hear another new and unbelievable
Reverend Susie the Floozy Show
from the great station W.
R. E. K. in Atlanta.
Yes, once again, W.
R. E. K. saves the ears of the listeners
in all Hour of Slack time slots.
With the legendary Bob's Slack Time Funhouse,
which is alternately altered by the Lymphnode Institute,
or as in this glorious case by the beautiful,
brilliant,
scintillating,
and quite mad,
Reverend Susie the Floozy.
Ah, yes.
This, then,
is her 2004 Apocalypse Show.
Praise Bob.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Oh, yes, спаси 힘들ccjj,
But help me follyme.
We'll, go the way,
but what's to come Sal.
If God can another man to rule Braum!
So, well,
love God!
killed so many in this.
generation after generation.
Satan in a day he will never forget When the king hurls him into a bottomless pit
So keep your eyes on the Lord don't follow human ways
It's written in the Word these are the...
FINAL DAYS
CHANGE YOUR WAYS
The final days is what my song's about
Words so intense I might have to shove
Some might play hard and say I'm wack
But I'm talking about truth
Not egomaniac and ass-fuckers they listen
They won't be dissin'
Cause writing final days is a serious mission
Just so they learn I will stand stern
I hope my words make you start to churn
I'm concerned with the life that you're living now
Your ego's so bad that you can't even bow
So the song's about to end
Your time is running thin and now that my time is over
It's time for two for three
Begin to do this job is my only request
A basic rap exam puts MCs to test
Spread these words like a fire ablaze
Cause I'm telling you we're living in the...
FINAL DAYS
CHANGE YOUR WAYS
GET BUSY
FOR THIS AND THAT
FINAL DAYS
CAN'T
GO
FINAL DAYS
Teleportation
These people have come from the future to visit us
Using the Earth Union's time machine
We've been sent back here to warn you all
We wish to change incidents that are about to take place here
Things that have caused catastrophe
In the 23rd century
We came here to warn you all about your country's gloomy future
Because in the century that we come from
There's no longer a Japan
How could that possibly be?
And why?
What's the reason for it?
You wanna make an omelette, you gotta break some eggs
See that the humans remain entertained until the end
The Book of Revelations tells us
To watch for the seven signs of evil
By
Sign of Evil Number Four
We continue in our sign of evil countdown
Here's Vanessa with...
How are things going here?
Doesn't look so hot
We'll be broadcasting in a few minutes
The mobile unit is also getting ready
Good, keep it up
The world's depending on us
Okay
The one question that I heard asked more than any other
The question is, man going to destroy himself?
Are we coming to the end of the world?
Oh God, no
Is today the fifth?
What?
The aliens are here!
Is God outraged with all of this?
I don't know
And he hears the rattling sabers and sees the spewing rockets
He sees the atomic bombs that are buried beneath the sandia mountains
Close to Albuquerque, New Mexico with enough detonating force
And destructive force to completely destroy the entire world
He sees the lethal snout, so...
Atomic submarines that plow their way through the waves of the mighty oceans
Levetians of the deep that could completely destroy mankind
With just the push of a button
He sees that
He sees the mighty Saturn missile belching its black smoke in flame of fire
Taking its cargo of flesh to the moon
He sees it
He also knows that madmen, in spite of their front of civilization and intellectualism
And getting along and peaceful coexistence
That have but one desire and that's to destroy and take over this entire world
He sees this
He knows this
Meanwhile, far below the earth's surface
I don't know why you don't do something from up here
Well I've tried, I've tried everything
They won't listen to me up here
I've sent my prophets Ezekiel, Hezekiah
You know what a good apocalypse costs
I know that
And you tried that earthquake in Los Angeles last year
Oh no no, don't blame me for that
That was San Andreas' fault
That shows the endless connection how one crime succeeds another
For he says the land is full of bloody crimes
And the city is full of violence
Therefore, God says, I will bring the basis
The worst of heathen gentile people
And they are going to conquer you
And drive you out and move into your houses
And your holy places will be defiled
Destruction comes, God says
Oh good God, we're doomed
No!
We're out of Jonah!
One could go on and on with reports of this nature
Week after week we get letters to our office
And it'll say, Brother Smith, it saved my life
You don't realize where I was headed
A farmer awakened one morning
And the clock struck one, two, three, seven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen
His wife said, honey wake up
He said, what time is it?
She said, I don't know
But it's later than it's ever been before
It's funny because it's true
World leaders are indeed pesky!
They're pessimistic!
They should be!
Is he still on the line, Gary?
I think we do have a guy still there
Is he really?
Listen, since we've got him holding on the line
Why don't we just find out what this Pessimist Club is all about?
How long has the Pessimist Club been around?
Oh, about ten years
But I'm pretty sure we're going to fold any day now
I mean, assuming we're not all killed by the earthquake first
Oh, boy, you really are a pessimist
Thank you
I try, but of course it never really does any good
Oh, of course
So just what do you do at a Pessimist Club meeting?
We make our predictions for the next six months
Oh, and what are they?
Well, we feel pretty sure that there will be complete and total peace throughout the entire world
Gee, that doesn't sound very pessimistic
Well, no, not for those who will survive the Earth's collision with the sun
Goodbye, Mr. Negative!
I've been hearing something on the streets the last couple of weeks
Weird stuff
Some sort of epidemic of violence, what they've been saying
I was talking to one old boy
He told me they got some sort of cold up there
End of the world, man
That's the kind of stuff
Take three, The Last Days of Isaac
This is my 33rd year
The year that I am to die
The days are pressing in on me
I feel their wild immediacy
And in the air, expectancy
Fulfillment of a prophecy
The last days of Isaac
All the last sweet days of Isaac
Etched with burning sunlight
On the inside of my eye
Will I burst into oblivion?
Burn in Armageddon
Will I, flaming ashes light the sky?
Oh, where will I be?
Where will I be?
What is out there between us?
Where, You will every day be?
Will the world ever part from me BCRhai?
Nothing can be真
I'll stand up on my feet
Mike Indeed
Mike Smart
You have multiple setbacks
Mike nah
All right
Everyone is crying out for deliverance.
Now many times you will see the president standing there in the Rose Garden with two
of these smiling men from the East on each side.
One has got a tablecloth on his head and he poses a smile and then they put there in the
newspaper, uh, peace.
I've got no problem with the peace treaties that they sign.
I have problem with the people who signed the peace treaty.
Uh, that's, that's reality.
George, you should be ashamed of yourself.
And how.
Recently, another 400 scientists, scholars, businessmen, and political leaders met in
Texas to ponder the problems facing mankind.
They said it is a gloomy world indeed.
The energy crisis, famine, the financial problems of New York City, drug abuse, and other unrelated
problems are all portents of the present darkness.
And the Bible says, I am the God of hell fire and I bring you fire.
Sudden destruction cometh upon them and they shall not escape.
That's what the Bible says here.
There shall be famine, pestilences in different places.
And I don't have to tell you these things.
You know if there ever is a time that Bible prophecy is confirmed right before our eyes
have met.
Plagues, pestilences, and things like that.
Yeah, now the boss says this is a very bad thing for the country, see, because this contract
starts after the war.
And the boss has got an idea with all this Nazi and Jap money that, uh, he's going to
take away.
Well, I haven't got it quite straight, but anyway, the boss says it's a bad thing for
the country.
So far you've told me what the boss has found out.
What did you find out?
I don't need the terrorists.
Boy, you're hotter than a firecracker on the 5th of July.
Who is it?
All right, listen up everyone.
I want you to calmly file towards the exit.
That's it.
Nobody runs.
Just walk.
Single file.
That's it.
Now if we just stay calm, no one's going to hear us.
Nobody's going to be harmed by the huge bomb that's going to explode any minute.
It's a cookbook.
The world is getting out of hand.
All what's removed from me.
I'm not going to be harmed.
Someone else, some nameless face controls my destiny.
Is it the man who's doing research or the man who's out in space?
And there's something that's controlling me, some silent nameless face.
Is he an IBM computer or an electronic brain?
And if I cannot find him, where do I find him?
I don't win.
Yes?
Excuse me, I believe I left a pipe and some books.
Oh, they're right here.
This is my lucky pipe and I didn't want to leave it behind.
I understand you're going away.
That's right, I've got to start banking right now.
You're a blithering coward.
Bitch, I'll f*** your ass up.
Is all the Shire discussing my departure?
Oh, no, no, no, don't worry about that.
You are miserable because you don't know how to say goodbye.
But danger has come sooner than you expected and now you are making up your mind to go at once.
The secret won't keep for long, of course, but at present it is, I think, known only to us conspirators.
And we're not going to let you escape so easily.
But I must go. It cannot be helped.
It is wretched for us all, but please help me and don't hinder me.
You don't understand.
You're lying.
Maybe he's not.
I know.
Look at his face, he's lying.
All right, Bob is my only hope.
Back off and give him some room to think.
All right, this place is going up.
Well, if I'm going out, I'm going out happy.
Before we're all blown to bits, mind if I pull the underwear out of my crack?
The man's got to go comfortable.
All right, but that's it.
God, I hate that guy.
I don't believe it.
You're on the truth or not?
Hold up, didn't the police mention it? Say anything about it?
Bob, no.
No.
What did he look like?
Looked like what?
He looked like a man, of course. What do you suppose?
Uh-huh.
Oh, yes, yes.
He looked like a man.
Yeah, yes, I know.
Yes, he looked like a man.
He's a queer bunny.
Nobody believed me.
Even my colleagues wouldn't believe me.
Poor man.
He's insane, that's what he is.
He believes it. He must be insane.
Fools!
Can't they understand me?
Tell me something.
Am I mad?
Tell me!
We have no alternative.
We must use all our nuclear weapons.
May I suggest we join in prayer?
I can't see how prayers will help.
Oh yes, we can at least save our souls.
We must either attack them now or surrender to them.
Some more trouble.
The military men want to use all our nuclear weapons
and then resist them to the bitter end.
We'll be wiped out by the radioactivity.
We have a tiger at the front door and a wolf at the back.
What is that supposed to mean?
But there is another way of thinking about it.
Perhaps we are clearly at a time of great potential crisis.
We have the means of destroying the planet,
which we've never had before in the history of man.
A plan that will destroy King Ghidorah.
We wish to borrow from you on Earth the monsters Godzilla and Rodan.
Are you serious?
Of course. Deadly serious.
Will you help us?
Well, your request is unusual.
We don't know how to answer that.
First place, we don't even know where Godzilla and Rodan are.
Please, cut me some slack here, will you?
I'll give you anything you want.
Excellent.
Meanwhile...
My God.
What is that?
What?
Can you be specific? There's not much time.
Yes, we know.
What do the tests indicate?
The tape recorder here is being moved by magnetic waves generated over there.
If we can shield it, if we can intercept the waves, it'll stop.
Can you solve the problem in such a short time?
The odds are long, but we're making our final tests.
ungen
A permanent one.
Yeah.
Let's go.
We're going there.
There's gust of lead coming up sunset.
Oh, God, I've been misinformed.
Increasing.
Captain?
Yes?
What is it?
Radioactivity stronger.
Uh-oh.
Hiroshima.
Chernobyl.
Erisberg.
Selma Hill.
Hiroshima.
It's in the air for you and me.
Radioactivity.
Discovered by Madame Curie.
Chain reaction and mutation.
Contaminated population.
Radioactivity.
It's in the air for you and me.
Chernobyl.
Harry's third
Xenophil
Hiroshima
Hermodomin
Harry's third
Xenophil
Hiroshima
Harry's fourth
Xenophil
It's in the air for you and me
Stop radio activity
Discovered by Madame Curie
Chain reaction and mutation
Contaminated population
Stop radio activity
It's in the air for you and me
Free your chest, Dave!
I'm sure you didn't make a mistake on those tests.
Hey, what's the matter with you?
I got a headache.
I never had a headache in my life. I've got one now.
Maybe you got a fever.
I haven't got a fever. I've got a headache.
I don't know, Jack. The tests are all right.
Matter of fact, I think I got the figures right here.
Yeah, you see, the oxygen content is...
Look, I don't care about the figures.
Why have I got a headache?
They're using magnetic waves.
That's where we have a chance.
If we are able to sever those waves, we can save the Earth.
Did you felt electricity in the air?
Oh, no!
Is this... Is this gonna...
Is this gonna set off the doomsday machine?
Say, George, that was quick thinking!
You crazy bitch!
Time is getting short. I better get on with my speech.
Bladen, put him down.
I'm going to get him into camps.
All American citizens are to report to one of these death camps right away.
Did I say death camps? I meant happy camps,
where you will eat the finest meals, have access to fabulous doctors,
and be able to exercise regularly.
That's why I brought the
And I guess there could be a spectrum issue.
Break down, in effect.
I am
Oh, my God!
Welcome.
Welcome to your last day on earth.
To your last day on earth.
Welcome.
your life day on
breakdown ineffective
I feel good
I feel very happy
I feel very sad
Very sad.
Breakdown in effect.
I am going to die.
The old last day on.
I am going to break down.
Feel something.
I feel good.
I feel very good.
I feel good. I feel very good.
Breakdown in effect.
Breakingdown in effect.
I had a legendary twitch in Nagasaki.
Uh-huh.
I want to tell you a secret.
I dropped my panties to see you butt naked all saddled up.
Hit number one is losing her panties.
Oh!
I know, yes I know, I'm alive.
As long as I can taste my own sweet words.
Well, as long as I can smell my own sweet soul.
Sweet soul.
As long as I can see the flesh and blood that's me.
Now alive, yes alive, and I'm whole.
Electronic eye.
Somewhere in the dark.
In the sky.
Obdipotent or seeing.
Deny me, not my being.
Passing through the valley of the shadow of death.
I will sing to keep my soul alive.
As long as I have breath.
Today, though I walk through the valley.
Of death.
Of the shadow of death.
I know there's no respite for me.
The one that never dies has left.
I've never been so exhausted.
I think I'll go to bedlam.
I'm walking through the mud.
Deep, deep in blood.
And I just realized where I'm heading.
I don't want to measure down.
Setting my place in the ground.
It's even less necessary.
I'm wearing this suit.
I'm tired of feathers.
I'm a fallen angel.
They can never bury.
I'm knocked, knocked, knocked, knocked.
And I'm dazzled by you.
I'm the way you see me.
This can happen for the rest of my life.
I'm the one who's under the sun.
I'm the one who regrets.
I'm the one who breaks out.
Baby.
I'm on a one-way trip down Zenfors.
On a one-way trip down Zenfors.
If I had a soul, I'd go to hell.
I've never been to human hell.
I'm not long for a cable morning.
It's an eternal toll to fell.
That two-headed dog's been chewing my leg off for seven hundred years.
I sleep whilst I'm on feet on my back.
Poachers in my eyes may give.
I'm on a one-way trip down Zenfors.
I'm going to wreck the rest of the world.
I'm wearing this suit.
I'm tired of feathers.
I'm bored in my wrist.
I throw away my hijab,
Till I find my first lady.
I've no clue.
Could this be all or nothing.
I're sitting by a single male.
Even if it's all to no use.
Too many chances to get there.
Yeah!
Will your brains be dropped?
Lord.
You carried on a bargain through your Honeymilk.
Yeah.
Oh, Jesus.
Och would i regret.
He's a deadana up drinking sometime.
And I don't know what time of the night he'd buy one pack of free lookin bitches.
Sure enough.
Bei, to some magari ouais.
My kids are already fed up of shit.
Woo-hoo!
Sing it!
I'm on a one-way trip to San Francisco
To rent a nice little ferry
I'm wearing this suit, I'm tired and fast
I'm going into Lincoln, Neverbury
I'm knock, knock, knock, knock, knock on the fence
I'm not doing no good, I've seen this before
I'm on this roadside, don't worry, man
Blow your brains out, baby!
I'm on a one-way trip to San Francisco
To rent a nice little ferry
I'm wearing this suit, I'm tired and fast
I'm going into Lincoln, Neverbury
I'm knock, knock, knock, knock on the fence
I'm on this roadside, don't worry, man
Blow your brains out, baby!
Woo!
What do you know about that?
Godzilla.
Cool.
Yeah.
That's great.
We saw the voices
So much fear
Cause a demon
To appear
Whisper changes
In hearts and minds
Will be forgotten
Most every time
Greed within us
Thus travels through
My feelings are old now
So nothing new
Must go on now
Without the rain
To shed away
Mortal pain
Through and through
My feelings old now
Nothing new
Yet I am still
My eyes what I used to see
Why I can now tell
A truth that's ordinary
In reality
It'sοι
I know
I haven't even gotten
So that moment
What are you planning
How I'll know
I'll be surprised
I'll know
What the only thing
I've met
Is life
Thank you.
soil.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Gentlemen, we have tried every force known to us.
We can't kill him.
We have failed.
What are you going to do now?
Just wait.
Till he goes away.
This is a news bulletin from the WGBS radio newsroom.
A tape-recorded press release has just been delivered to this station as well as several others in the city
from an unidentified group who claim to have kidnapped an experimental nuclear reactor.
Holy hell!
The terrorists claim it is hidden somewhere in the Wilton District
and that the area should be evacuated immediately.
Here is part of the tape we received.
If $10 million in gold bullion is not delivered by jet to a ship 200 miles due east of Washington,
we are going to overload the reactor and flush fallout into the atmosphere that won't disappear for years.
Either you're with us or you're with the terrorists.
And you're either with us or against us.
It means that we have to move quickly.
Move in a way that...
is effective and sometimes lethal.
Right!
Let's get cleaned up.
Find a drink before the bar is closed.
We're on the hunt.
Dutch, it's all about that stuff.
God, Dutch, how are you?
Nancy and I are hooked on heroin.
Well, thank you, Dutch.
It'll be too late by then, won't it, Reverend Staines?
If you want a picture of the future,
imagine a pipe smoking in a human face forever.
Ha ha ha!
Peace.
Godzilla!
At last!
Abort firings! Abort firings!
Interception will fragment the...
...the nuclear war.
Three billion human lives ended.
The survivors of the nuclear fire called the war Judgment Day.
They lived only to face a new nightmare.
The war against the machines.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
Somebody's dying, I see it on the color TV.
Somebody's dying, I can see him...
...in his last agony.
Does anybody know this boy?
Can someone tell me who he could be?
Hey Ma, hey Ma Jumpin' Jesus, he looks like me.
I see him lying there and moaning on the color TV.
The camera's zooming in on him.
Come see up close and fuk pen him.
Now say to that kid,
He's gone?
Can you not feel thispassin' for a twentyPercent or more?
But he's gone and he does not look like a man.
He didn't care, now he's both drunk and a thief.
He's gone takes a block up and might be drinking.
You just said on full balance your certainzzo in cá covenant that you are looking for scissors.
I'm thinking of walnutooo and honey.
What a crazy man.
We있!
My eyes are blurring as I'm sweating hard to see his ID
Can't hear my breathing and there's something cold creeping up on me
I look at him and I'm afraid someone tell me who he could be
Hey mom, you can stop your fixin' supper
I think it's me
I knew where to hide to keep from getting evacuated out of here
in one of the science labs at the high school
But that was for a moment
Then when a Geiger counter there started going crazy
I realized there was a radiation leak somewhere
I took the Geiger counter and it led me here
Now let's see
Yeah, it's coming from inside here, alright
There's a broken skylight
Wonder what...wow!
The last man, baby
Um, Joe?
If there's any chance of averting this war, you better tell me about it and tell me about it right now
Cause if we don't find a solution to this thing, happiness in this world ain't gonna be worth a hell of being, ya hear?
I would have done everything in my power to kill the American people
I got big news for you, kid.
I want you to know something
When I say I'm gonna do something, I'm gonna do it
One bottle being enough
Let's be realistic
The radiation leak must be wrecking the controls on his bionic limbs
I gotta get in and help him
Sir, a disaster! What is it?
We've lost control of the monsters!
No you fools, I need you back!
Hey!
They cut me off! They got my truck!
How are things going here?
The licking our first trucks have taken is something terrible
It doesn't look so hot
Good, keep it up
Okay
Sir, this is Caving Inn at Sector 15
Move all defensive units into Sector 15
And clean it up, immediately
Emergency, emergency
The hydrogen oxide plant has been damaged
Eight ships obliterated by a mysterious blinding flash of fire
No survivors found
Radio reports from stricken ships give same message
Terrible sea of fire engulfs all
Staggering death toll
Signed, Steve Martin
You got it, thanks
The back motor of the ship adjusts
Holding it, uh, just enough to keep it from falling
Get this started, get this started
It's very, very, very, very terrible
Move, get out of the way, please!
It's running, bursting into flames
And it's falling on the mooring mast
And all the folks that read it
This is terrible
This is one of the worst disasters in the world
They always say it's like
100,000, 400, 500 feet into the sky
And it's a terrific drag, ladies and gentlemen
It's smoking, it's flames now
And the tremors rising to the ground
It's not quite to the mooring mast
All the humanity and all the passengers
Screaming around it
I told you
I can't talk to people
This place is wrong here
It's, it's, it's, oh
I, I can't talk, ladies and gentlemen
This is horrible
Listen to the monsters and their cries of horror and sudden death
They're going to attack
The monsters will fight?
They know their enemies by natural instinct
Now the key locks must pay
We will pay
Thank you, George
Go back
If you don't give up
Things will get a lot worse for you
Toby climbs through the broken skylight into the warehouse
And sees Steve along with the two terrorists and the scientist running around yelling wildly
Get out of there!
He's headed for the band!
No, he's headed for the wall!
He's plugging out the door!
He's got it right in front of the reactor!
Hey, you!
What do you think you're doing in here, you little...
Oh, no you don't
That's it, Carl!
Give it to him good!
Freeze!
Police!
Dr. Yoshida's machine has been destroyed by the fire dragon
What now?
Do we attack?
The great fire dragon will burn all of Tokyo within a few hours
When will they learn?
Terrific explosion
The terrible amount of hydrogen gas
It's on the galley by here
In it
Just like the tail surface broke into flames first
Then there was a terrific explosion
And then followed by the burning of the nose
And the cracking nose into the ground
And everybody turned back and straightened their
Seats to get out from underneath us
Because it was over the twinkle at the time of first in the flames
Now whether it's how armed the people were witnessing it
We do not know
But as it exploded they raced fast
And now it's smoking a terrific black smoke floating up into the sky
The flames are still leaping maybe 30, 40 feet from the ground
Yeah, they were volcanoes
And what we're seeing are the original volcanoes in place
Molten lava
The lava's very, very hot
About 2300 degrees
And it's supercharged with steam and gases
And they kind of shot out at about 35 miles an hour or something
That's really hot, isn't it?
Yeah, it looks like we're watching fireworks, doesn't it?
But we're not
That's what's coming out of the center of the Earth
Wow
Where are all the dogs?
There are no dogs
There's nothing living on Earth
Not even dinosaurs and three-star monsters
Nothing
There's nothing but land and volcanoes
And the molten lava coming out and shooting up at 2300 degrees
Hey, woohoo
Ladies and gentlemen, I'm back again
I raced down to the burning ship
And just as I walked up to the ship over a fine little trick of iron
I met a man coming out
Dave, Dave, he couldn't find his way
I grabbed ahold of him
He burned terribly in the hand
And he burned terribly in the face
As I bounced, all his hair turned off
But he's walking and talking
Plainly and distinctly
And he told me he'd jump
I suppose these things happen
Oh!
He's been out in the sun too long
Look at the size of that blister
Police!
What happened here?
Oh, pardon the mess, officer
My maid only comes in once a week, you see
That's veryearly
I have one more waterspout
You can get me another, sir
I know this love is slightly more curious
Than our archduke's
Let this putl the right name So like it's not the last
manifestation of the lethal-bombing
It's about to start
To kill you
Let's begin
What I'm saying is maybe you're worth a lot more than six million dollars.
Oh, we are.
Wait, Edmunds, what kind of radio show is this?
This has been a test of the subgenius early warning system.
This was only a test.
If it had actually been our sweet prophesied ex-day Armageddon,
you would have been advised to tune to J.R. Bob Dobbs for help
by sending out a quick letter to the Subgenius Foundation
at P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118
or check out the website for more detailed nude information at www.subgenius.com
And you?
You had better do it fast, Seekers,
because July 5th is zooming up on us for yet another drunken chicken run with apocalyptic destiny.
And you know, I got a feeling in my bones and yours
that this is the year that, yes, it's all gonna burn.
Yes, this is it.
And the good news gospel of this ministry
is that you can buy your way onto the escape vessels of the sex connoisseurs.
Yes!
Oh, but you gotta have the right stuff, Seekers.
You gotta have that subgenius membership card in hand
when you're standing in that line for the pleasure saucers.
Even if you're only booked for a sky kennel in the cargo hold.
So don't say you weren't warned.
And you've had the privilege of getting an advance tip-off of things to come.
Ha ha ha ha!
See you on the saucers, Seekers.
Boy, you're hotter than a firecracker on the 5th of July.
Oh, yeah.
Fulfillment of a prophecy
The last days of Isaac
Oh, the last sweet days of Isaac
Yeah!
Ha ha ha ha!
It's like on the night of the final day
As the moon من'.
Fulfüsiged with burning sunlight
On the inside of my eye
Will I burst into oblivion
Burn in Armageddon
Andestäby paon
Flaming ashes light the sky
Where will I be?
Where will I be? Where will I be?
When darkness descends on me
Hey, Bob is my only hope. Back off and give him some room to think.