You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to...
The Self Genius Hour of Life!
Okay, okay, here it is.
Dad just said I was a mutant, but I said I was a butant.
Because I am internally...
Whoa.
I am internally mutated, but outside I am beautiful, so I am a butant.
A butant.
Butant.
I'm a...
Titi!
You've convinced me.
I've contributed a new vocabulary word to the Self Genius Charts.
Tell Dad.
In your book, can you do that?
Oh, yes.
I'll put it...
I'll work it in as soon as I can.
As soon as I can.
You've invented a new...
It's a new concept.
It's a beautiful new concept.
It's a butant...
Butantful new concept.
My Titi, I'm so proud of you.
Put her there, pal.
What a...
What a wonderful...
You're part of the young generation, that sick generation who must ravage and plunder for their kicks.
Scenes of such brutal honesty will be shown on this screen that we strongly recommend that impressionable young people,
or those people of any age who are upset or affected by scalpel-slashing, arm-twisting, axe-hacking motorcycle maniacs,
now close their eyes for the remainder of this coming attraction.
Thank you.
And check!
Keep your brain clean so hard.
I'm the Reverend Mary Squared.
Oh, downtown.
Kiss me, tie me, tie me up and spur me.
I want to holler, but the town's too small.
Oh, my God!
And I am, of course, a good friend, Reverend Ivan Skag.
Ivan Skag me!
And we have many special guest preachers here tonight.
Preachers Square.
Indeed.
Sister Susie the Floozy from Atlanta is here.
Boys!
Oh, my God!
Boom!
You know, this is a different quality of preacher than you're used to seeing on St. Bob's Hill.
Oh, yes, it is.
Slaggers.
Hopefully by the end of this evening, we will have worked up.
Even you people will be feeling mega slaggers of guilt.
Bob Dobbs is coming New Year's Eve, and he's bringing the wire.
It is useless to resist.
The Church of the Subgenius and Club No present the first Dallas.
Subgenius the Bible, December 31st, Thursday night.
Thought you tried everything?
Well, we have!
And now we're going to make you do it too!
This may be the most important decision of your life.
Man, this must be a great, you know, this must be the one true religion.
It is the one true religion.
You know, just look.
I mean, here we are, frappy whiskey babes.
What more could we want?
Our religion.
Money.
Yeah, money.
What about the money?
Well, yeah, I got a question.
And yeah, I wanna know.
Yeah, I got a question.
Because I just saw this show.
And which came first?
Religion or money?
I said, which came first?
Yeah, religion or you?
Who?
I wanna know
Yeah, I got a question
You think I lied just on this show
Which came first, religion or money?
I said, which came first, religion or money?
Money
This is what I said
In your stable
This is all I got
From all the people
You paid the cash
It's a gamble
On your eBay
We're gonna pay for the loan
Yeah, I got a question
Yeah, I wanna know
You think I lied just on this show
Which came first, religion or money?
I said, which came first, religion or money?
We're in the action
For our money
Which came first
I did come first
What's in the money?
Money
Well, hello, and welcome to church
and with the Church of the Subgenius
you can have religion and you can have money too.
Because time plus money equals slack.
And that's what we're here for.
We're here to give you a little radio scent heaven.
And most religions promise to deliver you from evil.
But only, only the Church of the Subgenius can promise
not only to deliver that evil directly to your door,
but if it isn't there in 30 minutes, the evil is free.
Now that's a church.
You know, I've been trying to tell you that only people will give money
only if they hate.
And we just don't have enough hate in our religion.
It's like those Christians, man, they hate everybody
and they send them millions of dollars.
Those Ayatollahs, they get bankrolled by, you know.
It's like you've got to hate.
You've got to find an enemy.
Certainly we have all normal people.
But that's what we're trying to get the damn money out of, Doug.
Well, no, we don't really.
Because the Subgeniuses never have decent jobs.
Subgeniuses never have any large amounts of money.
And if they do, they don't know they're Subgeniuses.
They're guys like Howard Hughes, you know, or Jimmy Hoffa.
Yeah, they haven't been turned on to it.
That's the problem, you see.
Maybe we should make this church, you know,
like the anti-Satanic and demonic force church
and we could get all that money that police officers are getting
to go around and elect your school boards
about how to recognize Satanic cults in their neighborhoods.
Mysterio can pay off for you.
Yeah.
Witch baiting.
That's a great idea.
Let's get into witch baiting now.
Have you liked my new baiting suit, boy?
A lady just got out of the room, damn it!
I heard Susie the Flazy from here in Atlanta.
Band of men, can you do a stripper beat?
Can you do a striketta ball?
Who?
Shut up!
You!
Jesus!
Woo!
Boy, I'm sweating like a whore at church, baby.
And this is the church to be in.
Woo!
I'd like to thank the sweet, sweet guy we were not going to stay.
Miners, please.
Our heroes split four ways
But there's one thing this church is guilty of
And that's cats and fags and chicks
Like Connie
Connie Donald
And in tunnels, ex-ceramic gardens
A wet spill on Isle 5
It took Connie to tell me I didn't have a scratch
I thought I did
I did it good
I was such a good girl
I hated the police
And I spent all my money on buying products
But despite my most efforts
Couldn't get a scratch
And I kept the track
I kept the track
Until Connie
Came in and won my life
She said, Salute
The only sin in this church
Is the sin of slacklessness
And I said, buddy, insurance, Sam.
And Connie took me to Apple.
And she said, boo.
Boo.
That's so perfect.
Do it again.
Keep rolling.
And now, somewhere in Washington, D.C.
Oh, man.
Time's running out.
Won't be long now.
What a world.
What a world order.
Four years, she's the president of the number one superpower in the world.
And you can sure collect a lot of money.
A lot of homage.
A lot of booty.
Look at all this garbage.
Crates and crates of Desert Shield and Desert Storm paraphernalia.
Just look at it all.
Desert Storm dishes.
Cigarette lighters over there.
Desert Storm blankets and action figures and pillowcases over there.
All over there.
Matchbooks.
Desert Shield T-shirts.
Sanitary napkins.
Comic books.
Pilots.
Treatments.
Desert Shield the movie.
The whole damn nine enchiladas.
I was sure popular.
That thing sure was popular.
The number one president in the last 50 years.
But mustn't dwell.
Mustn't dwell.
Jumping baby Muhammad.
Look at this, will ya?
Giant iron curtain that Mikhail left here.
Boy, I sure had big plans to put it up here in America.
Big plans.
Ungrateful electoral wouldn't let me do it.
Not gonna go there.
Let's not dwell.
Let's not be grim, brothers.
Let's not point bangers.
And what do we have here?
My, my.
Look at those frequent flyer miles for all those trips to Tehran in 1980.
Those were the days before, you know, the 400-day hostage crisis deal.
Excitement.
Meeting all the M.A.M.s and mullahs.
TV sure helped us with that one, boy oh boy.
Better send Dan Rather a belated Christmas card.
Me and Barbie could use the mile.
Got a funny feeling I might be going incognito again.
Heh heh.
Betcha I get a pretty penny for this.
Autographed picture of Jesus in a three-piece suit.
Shaking hands with Pat Robertson.
Heh, my sentiments exactly.
I always knew he was a Republican at heart.
Old J.C. for a genuine conservative.
A real conservative.
And what am I gonna do with all this stuff?
I know.
I'll have a White House rummage sale.
Rummage sale.
Featuring a...
Whoa! Hold everything.
What do we here?
My name.
My notes.
From the Iran-Contra fiasco.
But no, Walsh loved to get his mitts on these.
He got a better chance of seeing Ronnie Reagan.
Heh.
Good thing I got my J. Edgar Hoover vacuum cleaner.
The best covert vacuum cleaner in the world.
Suck up all this incriminating and covert itineraries and a Jaffee.
J. Edgar Hoover sure built an impressive governmental machine to suck the truth out of anything and go unreputated.
Leaves everything righteously clean.
Squeaky clean.
A kinder, gentler clean.
Well, now I've taken care of some loose ends.
Might as well open up shop here.
Over there.
You, sir.
Hello, sir.
Right over there.
Step right up.
Can I interest you in this purple crucifix from the Mexican Free Trade Delegation?
Quarter.
Don't be shy, man.
Come on, look around.
There's plenty of stuff here.
I've got this.
I've got a Melville Marcus's shoes.
I've got a Ronnie Reagan.
I've got a Reagan's toupee.
And of course, we're going to bring in the new year.
1993.
The 90s are going to make the 60s look like the 50s.
Ho!
Praise Pope Fife, Wilson.
And of course, you know, they call it, the conspiracy calls it 1993.
We in the Church of the Subgenius, we're about to inaugurate the new year of 5BX.
5 years before I say you better start counting down now and send me your money.
It's the most important five years.
It's the last five years of human reality as you know it.
That's right.
It's the 90s.
You take or get out.
And we're not going to be on the same page.
We're not going to miss the human reality being totally destroyed.
No, we won't.
Not much.
Not one single bit.
We might have little nostalgic twinges.
I like those for the day.
Oh gosh, I really miss counting that.
Jehovah One Productions takes you on the strangest journey you'll ever encounter.
A place that's beyond what any other studio has ever dared show you.
More frightening than The Exorcist.
More fantastic than Star Wars.
More absurd than Monty Python.
The real world is here.
See incomprehensible beings with unquenchable appetites for the inhuman.
I'm going to get me one of them Z cars.
And what is the hideous secret of the thing in the mirror?
More dead than the Frankenstein monster.
More evil than Dracula.
More destructive than Godzilla.
In the real world, the monster is you.
The real world is a comedy.
It was reported that the US bombed Libya today.
A nightmare.
I can't find my keys!
A mystery.
I'm trying to find myself.
See undead beings involved in nightmarish occult rituals.
What you sign, honey?
Can I buy you a drink?
Gasp at the bizarre fascination that is found in spectacles of violence.
I just know the Packers are going all the way this year.
Tremble at the strange worship of a human sacrifice cult.
Mr. Homosexual Communist School Teacher, sir.
Mr. Do you hear me, Mr. Phil Donahue?
The answers are all found in this book.
The monster is you.
And who can imagine what kind of loathsome entity dwells beneath the mask of...
The Thing in the Mirror.
The monster is you.
Now we're only doing this for your own good.
You know, Reagan makes you proud to be an American.
Hey, you can bet your ass there's no blacks in this town.
More casualties were reported in Nicaragua today.
Escape from your escapism.
See the real world for the first time.
If you dare.
Can't we wait till it comes on cable?
The real world is available in reel-around with omniphonic sound.
Coming soon to a theater near...
Oh my God, no! It's already here!
Radar. Required viewing for everyone, all ages.
Some portions might be offensive to anyone.
Parental discretion is advised.
This is very true.
We have the Pink Lincolns queued up.
Ready to go?
Yes.
I got my tie on.
Ready?
Yeah, which is kind of a corporate anthem.
What it is to be pink.
So we can experience the pinkness and not have to taint ourselves with actually working.
I'm a cog in a wheel in a lubricated world and I wanna marry an office girl.
I've got my tie on.
I set my watch, I set my goals when I get old.
I wanna be fat.
I've got my tie on.
It's a string around my finger, it's a noose around my neck.
I'll go to grass, pick laces, prove I'm not a derelict.
I've got my tie on so I'll be sure to hold my head up high.
I can't forget why I got out of bed even when the morning paper's red.
I've got my tie on.
I'm riding across the tile floor.
I've got my name on the office door.
I've got my tie on.
It's a string around my finger, it's a noose around my neck.
I'll go to grass, pick laces, prove I'm not an idiot.
I've got my tie on so I'll be sure to hold my head up high.
I've got my tie on.
It's a string around my finger, it's a noose around my neck.
I've found a penthouse with a view I know I've got a job to do.
I've got my tie on.
I've picked my side.
I've made my choice, I've gotta have a damn good choice.
I've got my tie on.
It's a string around my finger, it's a noose around my neck.
I'll go to grass, pick laces, prove I'm not a derelict.
I'll prove I'm not a derelict.
I've got my time, so I'll be sure to
drink my summer pie!
That was the Pink Lincolns, a band
from Tampa, Florida, which, coincidentally,
that was my brother singing.
So, uh, subgenius
blood runs in my family.
Actually, although
it's the Pink Lincolns, there's nothing
pink about these boys.
Bob Bob. Bob Bob.
Bob Bob.
More? More
sex!
It's always
better than not enough!
And we're not talking about
your plain old human
penis. Oh, oh!
Au contraire! We're talking
about your get-shy-ly
miss-miley-squeeze-me
telly hurts
kind of fun!
Sex hurts!
I'm telling you, it feels so good!
It hurts!
And in order to do that,
of course, um,
well, I think we should probably do it before the New Year
because we should make sure everybody in this
room has undergone it.
You can't get away from it. Has undergone it.
You're in now. We're locking the doors.
The short duration
marriage.
So, Jesus Christ,
the most touching
and beautiful ceremony in the church,
that's through the launching of the day we have our own
and the short duration divorce.
Yes, that's important.
That's important. This is something new.
Just last week on the,
at the radio station, we got
a call from a couple,
a subgenius couple from Fort Worth,
I believe. That's right. If you're married,
now in the audience, don't
despair because on the
contrary, you can get a
short duration divorce and marry
anybody else in this room that
you want to. That's right.
This couple called up and said, look,
we have, we're looking
forward to that short duration marriage ceremony
where we're going to be married
to anybody we want to and
do whatever we want for 24 hours.
But, I said, we're already married
and we don't think it would be right, you know, to
go fornicating with somebody else until
we've had a 24 hour
divorce, too. So that's a
new thing. We'll have to wing it.
None of us are lawyers yet, so.
Help us, Steve!
Praise Bob!
He may be dumb, but God, he's cute.
Bob. Bob. Bob.
Bob. Bob. Bob. Bob.
I want to witness for Bob.
Bob. Bob. Bob.
Clean me out. Thanks to Bob.
I've reached a
zen state. I have nothing.
Thanks to Bob.
Anyone else?
I'm sure you all know
our next speaker for Bob.
He's been with
us for a real long
time.
It's the Reverend
Dr. Saint
God Living
Deity, Reverend Sterling
Dunst, who little rocks in his
dicks.
Praise Bob!
Woo!
Yeah!
We've got about five minutes
until 1993
when Reverend Stang
and Sister Mary
Damn Squirrel caught
a gun.
We'll be back up here for a demonstration
of time control. But first I've got to
I'd like to take a little survey tonight.
Here in the belly of the beast
in Babylon, I'd like to find out
how many real drug addicts
we have in the audience tonight.
Just as I suspected!
Well Bob can help you
kick those cheap conspiracy
street drugs and get you
higher quicker!
How'd you like to smoke a little of what's in
Bob's pipe, huh?
Well being an ordained minister
in the Church of the Subgenius enables
you to be on the waiting list
to receive vast shipments
of the legal immortality
herb, Habifroxipulops
or FROP
for short, which grows only
by moonlight on the graves
and droppings of
dead Tibetan holy men
and full-blooded yetis.
Now we're gonna bring
in the new year tonight, and we're gonna
tell you what you're gonna be next year.
We're gonna tell you how to act, we're gonna tell you how to FROP
we're gonna tell you how to get SLACK
because the first rule
of the Church of the Subgenius is
the Subgenius must have
SLACK! What must he have?
What must he have?
He must have SLACK!
The night get killed or praise Bob!
Come on, help me somebody!
Alright, another rule of the Church of the Subgenius
I want you to drill into every one of your
heads is
anybody you see driving a
Porsche doesn't deserve it!
You deserve it, and you deserve it
and you deserve it, and I deserve it
They don't deserve it!
Do they deserve it? Say no!
Do you deserve it?
Say yes! Yes!
Get killed or praise Bob!
Help me somebody!
Now children,
many people have asked me
Reverend Sterno
how did you become a
subgenius?
How did you find Bob?
Well I'd like to tell you
about that tonight children
and a happy tale it is in the telling too
for it was in the winter of
Ironically I was walking down
the streets of Dallas, Texas
Children I was depressed
Say oh no!
Children I was dejected!
Say my God!
Children I had not
The accent wound of a
recently assassinated U.S.
President in weeks!
I was down to my last two cc's
of bat sperm antidote
pudding! Say oh no
Sterno!
Children I had
not launched the bleeding head of
Arnold Palmer in six months!
Oh God Sterno!
Sterno!
Children
I was at the end of my rope
It came to me that the only
solution to my problems
was suicide
and I didn't even have the money
for a Saturday night special!
I was walking to the pawn shop
praying to Bob
that I had enough money
to buy a Wednesday
or a Thursday night special
to blow my brains out!
When I happened to glance down
into a mud puddle children
and there in that mud puddle
covered with mud
was a pamphlet
and their children
emblazoned on the cover of that pamphlet
was Bob's mighty face
beaming up at me!
His enigmatic smile seeming to say
Here model is this cheesy ad
in 1953
I know exactly how that smile will look
when Reverend Sterno needs it in 1965
Well I picked up that pamphlet
children and I read it
and what it said in essence was
Get in on the ground floor
of a lucrative new cult now
while raped for love
Well I was one of the few people
to do that children
and now there are thousands
nay millions of zombie eyed
panhandling teenage followers
standing on street corners
and cities the world over
selling that self saying pamphlet
and sending me the money
which affords me considerable slack
as you might have guessed
So if you are what they call
different
if you think we're entering
a new dark ages
entering ages
if you view the entire universe
as one vast
morbid cosmic joke
J-Live
if you are searching for an inherently
bogus religion that will condone
superior degeneracy
and tell you that you are above
everyone else
and most important of all children
if you can help us
with a donation
we would be grateful
to the church of the subgenies
who just provide you
with the slack you've been lacking
Slack! Slack! Slack!
Slack! Slack! Slack! Slack!
Join Gunchu with the truth
and the seed brave
and Peter Bob man
it's sin your genes
Buy out the gland owners
with what you earn
with your skin
and Peter's face of pain
Bleach the piece of the fine ass
Have a fuzzy big bollock
and strike your heart best
soft blow
with a rack coin
the rocket racket
This face outer belongs to your worship
in the crotch of your choice toys
and Ivan
falling in the flush
like it appears
to let him stack
you know who's a coming
Them chins ain't mean to harm
You just work in the
buzz of the good
and they'll be gone by now
baby
But this has been your Re-Annunciator
Thank me
What you've been listening to
recordings from the New Year's
Devival here in Dallas at Club No
with Sister Mary Squared
Pope Sternodocs
St. Janer Hyperclites
a lot of what I've been playing is actually
from Janer's new album
or tape actually
and also some stuff from
Reverend Susie the Floozy
on her local Atlanta
Hour of Slack show
on WREK in Atlanta
Praise WREK
Oh you know some
a couple of subgeniuses said
Reverend Stang
I don't think I'm going to make it
to that Club No thing
because you know
because well I just know
there's going to be a bunch of
those PIBs there
people in black
and I'm too cool to
be seen in a place where there's people
trying to be too cool
and let me tell you something
I'm a little bit tired sometimes
of subgeniuses saying
oh that person's not weird enough
because they don't look weird like me
they probably have a
job or something
I'm just thinking
because those are the people
those backsliders
are the ones that don't spend any money on us
the damn fashionable looking
bobbies are the ones that spend money
we've just about had it with the
true subgeniuses
we like the bobbies better
let's spend more money
I don't know who you are
or where you come from
I only know one damn thing
and that's that it's street law
now I don't
I don't know how you do it
I only know how you do things out there
in California
or LA
or whatever
continent you come from
but I want you to see
this damn line I'm drawing on the ground
call it McCannie line
step over a McCannie line
you're in McCannie
I ain't talking no P. Lasky county
you're in Muck county
step over this line
now you
you step over this line
I'm gonna shoot your ass
I'm gonna shoot your dead
you fall on that sidewalk
I'm gonna give you a ticket for obstructing traffic
you can't pay that ticket within 30 days
you're gonna go to jail
jail ain't no place you can be
especially if you're a dead boy
now I don't know how you do things out there
in California
or LA
or San Francisco
or whatever country
you come from
but
but down here in America
what we like to call Arkansas
we figure Arkansas ends in
Kinsaw
and we can't
we can saw
we will saw
and we do saw
and I just want you to understand that boy
in McCannie we've got three different kinds of
offenses
we've got
misdemeanor
we've got felony
and we've got a sodomy
you're busted for felony you can serve time in the federal penitentiary
you're busted for
sodomy
you can get your ass sawed
now you get busted for sodomy in someone else's precinct
they might just saw you a little bit
you get
you get busted for sodomy over here in my precinct
I'm gonna cut your damn ass in half
I'm gonna saw you boy
I don't want you to know that
I just want you to understand that
now I don't know
I don't know that much about
about
synthesizing usable
sugars from
the food I consume
I only know one thing that's Dallas street law
I don't know that much about
converting
oxygen to
workable food substance
I only know one damn thing
that's Dallas street law
I don't know much about hemoglobin
counts
I don't know that much about
maintaining a physical
existence
in a three dimensional reality
I
I'm gonna get you for that boy
that's all Bob cares about
but I
this week
the Dallas observer
see here's the thing
this is the damn problem with this church
I have to spend so much time doing the PR for a show like this
that I never get to come up with an original sermon
but
fortunately
there's always a huge supply of hate
and hate of course
is what keeps this church going
it's actually hate
hate
I don't feel that hate
hate is actually
hate is actually what keeps all religions going
and we're
we're a secret
how come
how come the Christians and the Muslims
hate at least as much as we do
look how much more money they're making
so we gotta crank up
some world class hate
so
I
I don't think that
now here's something hate worthy
this is slightly hate worthy
can I have a little more light
damn you're good okay
now
the Dallas Observer had this
they gave us a blurb you know
like a little bit of PR but it had a
smarmy snide
sort of blurb
this blurb will be nailed to their
back
in fact
this blurb will be nailed to their
back in hell and every time they try to
pull it out it'll just be put back in with
a bigger nail
but they said here
now this is the way
our
local entertainment paper
describes what's happening here tonight
folks
folks who dig
satirical overkill
they got the overkill part right
will get their
that's kind of snide
they will get their fill for the whole year
as if too much is not better than not enough
with
yet another
church of the subgenius event
I know there's just been
way too many subgenius events
in Dallas I'm sorry
we won't do it again
this first
the first annual random rave
subgenius devial actually we've done
three of these in Cleveland
is yet another
membership drive event
for and get this
the clique that wants
to be a cult
the clique
that wants to be a cult
I have news for you friends
this is the only cult
that is trying not
to be a cult
and that's not easy
because I guess the
Dallas Observer didn't
I guess they uh
the Dallas Observer didn't read this month's
playboy
and
we're going to
go back on page
which were on page
thirteen of course it says
YOU waren cities
giving some slack
those of us who don't get
poems of us who don't get
family values
the church of the subgenius is thankfully
preaching the virtues of slack
same way
uh
they said
But after listening to various attempts at expressing the inexpressible, because slack, by definition, cannot be defined, we felt a giddiness that, when we look back on it now, prepared us for a mini-revelation.
The voluptuous Sister Mary Squared of the Church said,
The curve is mightier than the sword.
And suddenly, everything started making sense.
It's entirely different. It's entirely different.
But everybody, yes.
Now you have yourself, now you have, now you have two kinds of Kentucky Fried Chicken.
Let me get that scratched off of there and quit looking at it.
Quiet, please!
That real crusty, real what kind of damn?
Crispy.
It's really different.
Now you can have two kinds of Kentucky Fried Chicken to choose from.
My regular recipe.
And my new, extra crisp.
Crispy.
New, extra crispy. I thought I said that.
One second.
Now you have two kinds of Kentucky Fried Chicken to choose from.
Cut it.
It's entirely different.
It every bit as finger-lickin' good, you see.
No, every bit as finger-lickin' good.
You see, I found a way to cook chicken deep down to get that real crispy crust some folks like.
I better do that again, haven't I?
Yes.
Alright.
Cut.
You don't want me to sing, do you, for Christ's sake?
We're rolling.
This is the good one. Take five.
Most folks, most folks, most folks, most folks, most folks have heard about it.
Alright, that's good. Good, very nice.
That's why folks call it finger-lickin'.
Sounds good.
That's why folks call it finger-lickin' good.
That's why folks call it.
I'm not getting anywhere with this damn thing.
Okay, fine.
Oh, now, isn't that sad?
I mean, he had money, but he didn't have slack, and you can tell it in his voice.
It's sort of pitiful.
I have a theory about what happened to Harlan Sanders' brain, and it's a good one.
You see, inside the brain, you've got your subgenius Yeti cortex.
You've got your subgenius Yeti cortex.
And it's hidden deep within the innermost recesses of the brain, beneath that part that
scientists have mislabeled the reptile cortex.
Now, I know reptiles.
I've served with reptiles.
And the pinks don't have what it takes to evolve up to reptiles.
They're better instead to call it the pink cortex, or right now, I guess we could refer
to it as the pea brain.
Originally, we're born with our Yeti cortex open and free.
Ready to receive Bob as our personal vibrator.
But then, then the insidious programming of the conspiracy begins and the pea brain takes
root.
This pink cerebral crap collects around the pure, shining Yeti cortex, coating the pure,
shining Yeti self with stinking, odious, gelatinous glop, which eventually smothers it and strangles
it into abject dozing submission.
But it can't entirely kill it.
Oh, oh, no, no.
No, no, no.
I      esimerk
16 CONTENT Mworth eight minutes
sono
She taught me how to get you and Jim on that island.
She taught me honesty is the best policy.
She said guns don't kill people, girls kill people.
And Connie said I was just her cat.
So thanks to Connie I'm on a rampage now.
I gotta go charge the conspiracy with a grand theft.
We got our slack, we got our slack, we got our slack.
We could use it much better than we did.
Sister Susie the floozy plays the policy.
How many times have you known some hopelessly lost conspiracy dupe?
Someone who hasn't yet figured out how to use these newfangled opposable thumbs.
They just suddenly come up with an almost enlightening,
blatant idea from out of nowhere.
It's that poor little yeti brain trying to break through.
That usually doesn't have a chance against a pernicious pea brain crap on its own.
But this creepin' crud can be defeated, yay!
It can be overcome, it can be cleansed away.
With a scrubbing action of the toilet bowl brush of Bob and Connie's sweet love.
So turn your before life over to Bob.
Just get down on all fours and tell him,
Bob?
Yes?
My head feels like a lava lamp that's been loaded down the truckload of Portland cement.
What can I do about it?
And what does Bob say, dear friends?
Bob says,
Take that miserable life-sapping crap and blow it out your butt!
Yeah!
Excremeditate it out of your system before it kills you.
Before you're nothing but a host body for a shambling, pathetic, nine-to-five Joe Schmo pink boy who doesn't have a damn clue.
And when you've blown out your butt,
when you're clean of all that pink conspiracy crud,
the void around the Yeti cortex fills up with pure distilled essence of slack,
and your precious brain pod simply floats along in that sublime bliss.
It's like a beautiful dream, Bob.
I was gonna tell you about the doctors for bobbing out in space.
Seem to be a major motion picture from some genius film studios.
Well, the doctors for bob have attained the brain of Charles Manson,
which they must take to Mars.
So they pick up their rocket and they head off in the direction of the stars.
And they've got the brain, and it ain't no strain.
The brain ain't old, the brain's quite young.
It's the brain that belongs to Charles Manson.
It's a...
doctor's brain.
Remember that cuenta?
You don't even realize what that means.
You better read it.
That brain, Seagull.
I think I know what it does.
Children die.
It has not been hitting its Jakara and units.
It has had a history of death and consciousness state forever.
It's a triconomically VR pretendent.
If this folks brain
who's gonna know.
Here we go.
in the Oscar Studios, in conjunction with the Paloma Frans Studios, in conjunction with
Hitman's Yardman Studios, in conjunction with Two-Headed Yardman Studios, in conjunction
with Three Hooded Yardman, while Techno-Kill's Studio Show, in conjunction with Five Hooded
Yardman, and the Fifth Yard Dash with Jesus Society Show.
That demonstration was an example of the only two things that concern us tonight, children.
The two things that we're here to do are fight the conspiracy and praise Bob!
I was born on the East Coast in France.
I was a member of the difficult.
It wasn't that I couldn't put the answers of life together, it was that I wouldn't!
I would beat myself in!
I would bend the third eye, stick me with a fork, I am dumb!
Twist me and turn me and tie me up and spur me, my mouth bent and twisted in ways that
I couldn't possibly imagine!
Until I met the church, and then I realized what was going on.
I was suffering, my friends, I was suffering from astral slug possession, a hard one!
Get your blades out!
I'm waiting back over here, I want to see you work your stuff!
There's no mischief in my mojo!
As long as you know what to do, we can just go, go, go all night long!
And I discovered, gosh, Reverend Mary, Sister Mary, that's an awfully hard way to run your
life!
And I discovered, I discovered all kinds of things that I was doing to make my life
as hard as possible.
You know what I mean?
Miscommunication, another lesser known delusion, all the time!
Beware miscommunication, because she'll make you think that you want one thing when you
really want the other.
She'll make you think that you want cheap conspiracy slack.
She'll make you think that you want all that fame and all that glory and all that money.
Well, honey, au contraire!
It was slack that I was looking for!
Slack, true slack!
Slack that you can't find in the store, slack that you can't find in politics, slack that
you can't find anywhere on this earth except within yourself, and you are truly grounded
and self-centered.
And I realized what kind of bull was going on!
What kind of bull was going on!
What was going on during the end times, because believe me, my friends, it is the end times.
New York was flooded.
The Catholic Church is talking about having women priests in their organization.
It's the end times, people!
It's time to start asking some questions and getting some anger!
And feed me, milk me, pet me, eat me!
Eat me!
It's time to stop prohibition and start to bitch it!
Start asking yourselves where all the bull in your life is coming from!
Every day we're bombarded by advertisements.
Every day we're bombarded by the pinks and the normals and, well, what are those people
doing and I won't do that unless my neighbors do that.
And gosh, what if my church isn't there?
And my church doesn't expect me to donate quite as much as I did last year?
I just don't know what to do with the extra money!
And oh, my gosh, I didn't make Mrs. Jones' tea party!
That's such bull!
Life is such bull that way!
And it's time to get rid of our bull.
It's time to join the cult of the living bull!
Where men are men and women graze in their pastures and wait until somebody milks them.
Move, baby, move!
Have a very dairy Christmas and a happy new year!
We are back live with Suzy the floozy.
Mmm, yeah, the reverence of Suzy the floozy.
Boy, I'm on my knees for the church.
Which is a good place to be because, uh, you know, life in the gutter, I've often said,
it's easier living in the gutter because that way you don't get hurt rolling off the curb.
And that's a nice thing.
I think that's the great thing about the church is that all over, in every sort of thing you encounter during the day,
can become something incredibly spiritual and devotional.
It's not restricted to just supposedly cleared stuff by some sort of nameless, faceless hierarchy.
And I want you to think of everything that has ever gone into you.
Anything that ever will go into you.
Anything that you've ever wanted.
Anything that you've ever wanted to go into you.
And I want you to take a deep breath.
Are you ready? On the count of three.
One, two, three.
And hold it.
And let it out.
And I want you to take a second inhalation on the count of three.
And this time, I want you to think of anything that's ever gone out of you.
Anything that's ever shot out of you.
Anything that's ever spewed out of you.
Anything that's ever been caught in between.
It's just been ripping to get out of you.
And you plan to get on it sometime.
But you just don't know when.
Take a deep breath.
And hold it.
Hold it.
Let it all out.
Now, on the third inhalation,
and this is the real important part of our meditation,
our excremeditation,
I want you all to think of anything that has ever gotten caught in between.
Pieces of chicken in your teeth,
your brain in your head,
anything that has ever been caught in between
and has been preventing you from making a difference.
And I want you to take a deep breath.
On the count of three and hold it.
Ready?
One, two, three.
Now, when I rub my hand at the top of my lungs,
we're going to scream all as loud as long as we can.
If you've already lost your breath,
just take another deep breath.
Are you ready?
We're going to scream until the windows break.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
10.
11.
12.
Praise Bob and Al Coddy!
Now, there are some questions that we've got going on here tonight.
There are some questions and there's some anger and some sacred hate boiling in the audience tonight.
1992, they said, was the year of the woe man, but oh, all contraire, 1993 is what's going to get a lady like me off, if you know what I mean.
Current 93, and if you all listen to the beat dicking and the witchy deities and their wisdom,
you'll find out that 1993 is the year of the woe man.
1993 is a very important year.
Alistair Crowley, a very weird, weird alien.
Praise Alistair Crowley.
The Book of the Law, 31, 31, 31, which if you add it all up,
if you take 31 and 31 and 31, which is the number of those three books, you get 93,
which, which,
which sums up the Book of the Law, which is do what thou wilt,
shall be the whole of the law.
Do what thou wilt.
And the whore of Babylon, and I could babble on and on about this,
embodies the current 93.
And Connie is Babylon.
So 1993 is going to be the year of the woe man, or woe tan, or however you have it,
but goodness gracious me, oh my woe man.
We've got a job to do, sure.
Okay, so we think we've got it going.
We think we've got it going.
We got a Democrat in the Oval Office.
Yeah, he got in.
We got in.
We knew he would beat Bush.
Sure.
We collectively licked Bush in 92.
But will he stay hard enough to do the job that's needed?
Only Hillary knows, and Jennifer Flowers,
and Jennifer Flowers,
but Connie knows,
that Bob is capable of doing the job.
And anyway you push and shove it,
if you let them fud it and blow real hard,
and again and again and again,
she'll just keep on sucking.
She'll start doing it in all ways, shapes and kinds,
because now that we've got a Democrat in the office,
it's starting to think on her own terms,
because now she's a little bit more liberal,
and she's a little bit more pink on our terms.
Yeah.
She may be pink, but well, he's not normal.
But we gotta start pushing it more.
We gotta start getting more army,
because Bob is coming in 96.
Bob is coming in 96, and we gotta get ready for him.
Only a pink boy.
Connie is coming with a nine iron,
and the ball she aiming with ain't for playing golf,
if you know what I mean.
It's time to end the bar, America.
Because happy up and have a good time.
Let's face it, we're an ugly nation.
We're an ugly society.
We pick our notes.
We power flatulate to the gods.
We step on old women and old men, and we praise you.
We're ugly.
We sweat like pigs, and hey, sex is messy.
Pays the Mexi sex.
It's time to start asking some questions,
and getting some anger.
We were ripped off by the 60s.
All the old hippies sold out, and got all the goodies.
We were stuck with VCRs, and transistor radios,
and Walkmans, and Topmans, and get yourself Offmans.
So, there are no goodies to get, even if we could sell out.
It's time to start asking some questions,
and getting some anger.
And here to tell you all about that sacred hate on,
I hope you boys have by now,
is the one and the only, Reverend Ivan Stein.
Ivan Stein.
Thank you.
Sister Mary squared.
Oh, yes.
And, well, we'll be moving out now.
You have been listening to the Sub-Genius.
Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
For free information on this church,
just please write to Bob at post office box 140306,
Dallas, Texas 75214.
I've spoken my piece.
I'm getting out of here.
You can have it.
It's all yours.
Oh.
Gosh, what was he talking about?