Ah, yes, there.
You see that coin?
That is insured for $10,000.
See how it seems to gather the light and draw the eye?
Yeah.
I get great repose from these things of age and beauty.
They soothe one and seem to induce sleep.
Sleep.
Close your eyes, my friend.
Hello, everybody.
Look out!
Shut up!
Come in.
$772,000.
Shut up!
$341,000.
Shut your face!
Is that correct?
Yes, it is.
$61,000.
Thank you.
Shut up!
That will be all for the present.
Very good.
The Subgenius Powerhouse.
Watch.
Excellent.
And at the top of the show, we've got a very interesting guest to be sure.
Reverend Ivan Stang.
He's the founder of the Church of the Subgenius and the book,
The Subgenius Cyclopedia of Slack, the Bobliagraphon.
That's right.
Stick around.
You're going to say, what?
Of course, the question is, who's Bob?
Well, Bob's an interesting guy.
He gets high on the real thing.
A full tank of gas and a clean windshield.
All righty then.
First off...
Worried about covering the lower half of your body?
Here's Bob One for A1 Slack.
Things go better with slacks and trousers.
Things go better with slacks.
Hi, this is Bob One.
And I wonder how many of our go-go-now-generation-action-man-on-compass realizes
how important it is to keep the lower half of your body covered
without disguising the fact that it is indeed the lower half of your body.
Well, there's nothing like a pair of trim-fitting A1 slacks.
They're better than skirts and a lot warmer, too.
Thank you, Bob.
You're welcome.
And now, back to our movie.
Looks like we're going to find more and we expect it.
Bob.
Bob Mom.
Babm!
Ba!
Ibam!
Ah!
Jizz!
But Terry Pratchett went first.
Thanks to Lee Murr for the song and intro,
Reverend Zontar for the ancient fire sign theater actual radio ad,
and Frankenstein1970 from 1959.
Welcome to Hour of Slack number 1143,
a Bob Renewal reintroduction to that most important thing in the world,
for those who might have briefly forgotten.
The first in a series of shows using categorized bits of the recordings
from a dozen recent Lives of Genius outreach events,
hither and yon, which it has taken me many days to chop up.
Besides the collage work of Noor El-Pref, Lee Murr, and yours truly, Reverend Stang,
we'll also be hearing from the Winter Star Devival of March 1, 2008,
John Hell's show on Pirate Cat Radio from last December,
a puzzling evidence show from Berkeley on February 22,
and a radio synesthesia show from WCSB Cleveland on March 9,
and a Denver, Colorado talk show excerpted from Rick Barber's show on KOA Denver,
and also some real radio ads from the fire sign theater, more of those,
prompted by Zontar.
We're hearing Bonobo's Convergence in the background, recorded live last X-Day.
And I think that's all.
Oh, Bonobo's Convergence will be at next X-Day, Drew.
We've been on the road a lot, friends,
and I've just now chopped all this audio into millions of tiny bits.
And also tonight, I'm working in some audio swipe from a great movie called Slipstream,
directed by Anthony Hopkins,
which makes David Lynch look like Michael Bay.
And we even have some new songs.
And next week or two, it'll be all politics on the show, friends.
Yes, I'm afraid so.
So let's bask for now in pure, untainted bobbery, at least for this week,
starting with what the curious heard as they approached the giant subgenius circus tent
at Winter Star 2008.
Last March 1st.
Ladies and gentlemen, step right up.
Welcome to the subgenius medical curiosity show.
It's all real, all here, all alive.
And it's all on the inside.
See the smart boy who can't keep a job.
See the pretty girl who can't get a date.
Alive and on the inside.
We have diseases that are spread through sexual...
Congress.
We have debates settled by fisticuffs.
We have people famous for being famous.
And they're all inside.
Alive, alive, alive.
See grown men and women talk to an invisible monster that lives in the sky.
See your own body become ever more fragile before your very eyes.
Feel the horror as schools turn innocent children into innocent adults.
Listen to shock.
Listen to shocking tales wherein you pay to work.
They're all here on the inside.
We have pictures of a salesman who smokes a pipe.
What other religions charge all worldly goods for what we offer at a discounted and guaranteed low rate?
Eternal salvation or triple your money back?
Read words on a cathode ray tube and attend amateur religious satire performance art.
Get slacked and feel alive.
Alive on the inside.
Praise.
I wish I could say that I wrote that, but actually that was recorded outside a freak show by Dr. Onan Canobite.
I don't think they ought to live for that one.
Anyway, that's what happened on this date in history.
Well, we're going to talk about something that you may not know about.
And those of you who have heard of it, you might find this most interesting indeed.
The Church of the Subgenius, founded in 1953.
And although its current popularity is traced to the publication of Subgenius pamphlet number one in 1979,
it's found quite a bit of acceptance, especially in underground pop cult circles,
embraced on college campuses, in the underground music scene, on the Internet.
And because the tenets of discordianism, the Church of the Subgenius is often described,
as a syncretic offshoot of the belief.
However, members state that the organization developed on its own with the publication of Subgenius pamphlet number one,
also known as The World Ends Tomorrow and You May Die, by Reverend Ivan Stang, who is our guest.
And Reverend Stang, good morning.
Well, I praise Rick, praise Bob, and happy birthday, Dan Quayle.
Dan Quayle.
It's not true, but it's alleged that, of course, you know, he was head of the space program
during Daddy Boy.
Bush's era.
And there was...
Appropriate.
Yeah.
And there was...
There was this...
This kind of this, you know, almost underground, shall we say, legend that Dan thought it would
be a good idea to send a mission to the sun, but because it was so hot, he thought we'd
do it at night.
There you go.
See?
And that's my kind of guy, you know?
All right, Dan.
We always considered him a sort of an honorary subgenius.
Well, he...
Even though he never officially joined up, he somehow...
He definitely was not a genius.
He certainly not.
So we knew that he would qualify for our august organization.
Indeed.
Tell us something about the Church of the Subgenius.
And by the way, who is Bob?
J.R. Bob Dobbs is our guru, and sort of, you might say, the god of the subgeniuses, and
of strippers, I'm told.
Cool.
Yeah.
Bob, some of your listeners may be familiar with his face, which you see tattooed on kids
and spray-painted on cars and so forth.
He looks like the 1950s version of the all-around good-guy dad on sitcoms.
That's right.
And if you look at any old magazine, it'll be full of ads of these square-looking, happy
guys with pipes.
They're always smoking a pipe.
Right.
Laying in a hammock while somebody else mows the yard.
And we, my partner and I, Dr. Philo Drummond and I, had noticed that the same figure popped
up in all these old magazines and in old movies.
We thought, it must be the same guy.
And at that point, Bob revealed himself to us through weird coincidences and messages
and things.
Yeah.
And we went to the newspaper and we found out that not too many people have actually
met Bob in person and survived.
In other words, you cannot look upon the face of Bob.
Well, he's so lucky, I think he manages to avoid most of his followers without even trying
to.
I'm looking at the picture of the Kababala.
We owe a lot to other religions.
It's true that we...
When we were...
Trying to put the Church of the Subgenius structure together, we, as Bob directed us,
we studied all the great religions from Zoroastrianism all the way up to Scientology.
And we picked all the good parts, you know.
Yeah.
When you were a kid, you'd find your dad's secret stash of paperbacks and look for the
good parts.
Uh-huh.
That's what we did with our dad's holy books.
Nice.
I was always looking for my own stash of Mad Magazine, which my father would hide.
Well, you just mentioned one of our true holy books is Mad Magazine and their great publisher,
William Gaines, and the great Alfred E. Newman, who is a cousin to Bob.
I always thought there was a kind of a connection there.
Yeah, he's...
Well, Bob's better looking.
But, yeah, they are related.
I think Alfred E. Newman was more like the country cousin.
And he's a little older than Bob in real life.
They both are.
They're ageless figures.
Now, the...
And by the way, I'm looking at some of the names that involve high-profile names like
Paul Rubens, Pee Wee Herman, who placed a picture of Bob in every episode of Pee Wee's
Playhouse.
David Byrne, Mark Motherspaugh, Penn Jillette, Penn and Teller, Robert Wilson, Robert Anton
Wilson, science fiction writers Rudy Rucker, John Shirley, actor Bruce Campbell, and even
Frank Zappa.
Yeah, so far, all of those are true.
I don't think any of those are lies or exaggerations.
Well, I'm almost certain it's probably true, especially in the Pee Wee Herman stuff.
Well, you could see it.
But he had Pee Wee in his title sequence every Saturday morning.
All the kids of America saw Bob leering over Pee Wee's shoulder during the titles.
Pee Wee never paid for his membership.
He left a phone message asking us to send him an ordainment package.
He could be a minister.
But he never, and he said, Bill me.
And we did, but he never paid up.
In our church, really, it's a pretty major sin.
But I figure putting Bob on CBS for a year was worth at least $10.
Well, at least.
Yeah.
I mean, and afterward, you had to give the guy some slack.
Yeah, poor Pee Wee.
He really is.
It's a shame.
It's a shame what happened to him.
Well, yeah, I always wondered, you know, all you got busted for doing what?
It's a big deal.
Try your 13-year-old kid.
Like the old T-shirt used to say, we're pulling for you, Pee Wee.
You betcha.
Bob, if he isn't done.
Bob?
Yeah, I dig you, Bob.
Bob.
Oh, Bob.
How long will it be?
Bob, I'm gonna miss you.
Bob's a bad influence on me.
Bob!
Oh, Bob, he's so charming and continental.
This is Bob.
I know Bob.
Oh, Bob, I don't know when I've been so hungry.
Bob, you really shouldn't have given me yours.
Oh, Bob, I don't think I can eat one.
I'm full of greens right up to here.
Fill me up.
I got pot.
You naughty, naughty boy.
Bob, would you like to buy some information?
I've got it, Bob.
Oh, Bob.
So, what is the Church of the Subgenius?
Good question.
We're still trying to figure that out ourselves.
It's like, well, is this a joke or is it a real religion?
And our answer is, why not both?
We are probably one of the only serious religions
that admits that we're completely full of crap.
And as such, possibly the only true and honest religion.
Doesn't that just figure?
You know?
But we have the problem.
We have the problem of bobbies.
They're the ones that want to, they're so excited about it,
they immediately want to start telling all the inside jokes,
and they haven't even gotten the outside joke yet.
And some of them, I mean, really need luck getting that.
But basically, back in 1953,
this man,
this young man, J.R., Bob Dobbs,
and by the way, the J.R. doesn't stand for anything.
It's on his birth certificate,
even with quotes on the name Bob.
Bob was a mere salesman.
Well, not a mere salesman.
He was actually the greatest salesman the world has ever known.
And he was pretty, but he was a very young man,
and he was just starting out on his road, his path.
Religion had nothing to do with it.
He was just interested in money.
Like any sane person.
But he was tinkering with a TV,
he was trying to build his own TV set.
And he was in his basement, standing in a puddle,
and suddenly he had this, he was seized up in the spirit.
He had this epiphany,
which we call the divine immaculation of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And in this timeless moment,
Bob was communicating with an alien,
an alien,
an alien intelligence calling itself Jehovah One.
You may have heard that name before.
This creature had been masquerading as God
to many cultures for centuries.
And it revealed to Bob that throughout history,
there had been a conspiracy.
Not the kind that kills Kennedy or gets Bush into office
or hides UFOs and so forth.
None of that stuff.
This was a conspiracy of plain, ordinary, garden variety,
normal.
Human beings who didn't even know they were part of a conspiracy,
but just automatically out of the fear of anything different,
uh, had been keeping down and oppressing the slack of all the
weirdos, the abnormals, the different people,
uh, the disbelievers,
and most importantly, those who will believe anything.
And that is when the church of the subgenius was formed,
not on a solid,
solid,
rock like some of our more prosperous competitors,
but on a shifting sandy beach of pure hypocrisy.
Hypocrisy friends.
That is the beach our church is built on.
Every there's,
we have a million rules,
uh, which can all be read in our three books,
but there's only one that really counts.
And,
um,
since there's no one here,
but children,
I'll say it in full,
uh, full,
uh, vulgar English.
The one,
one rule of the church of the subgenius is,
f*** them if they can't take a joke.
So if you are feeling tender today,
you should perhaps leave.
Uh,
but
the Bob show brought to you by Bob's show.
I'm Bob permanent,
perfect,
permanent,
perfect.
And here he is.
Bob.
Smile,
stop,
smile,
stop.
You bet your life.
There is heaven right here on earth.
Yeah.
Dick jazz.
So come on guys and gals.
No fussy Frizzy curls for.
This smart girl.
She has a Bob the perfect permanent,
permanent tight,
kinky with a Bob,
because Bob is so easy.
You can do it yourself.
Just regular pin curls and gentle Bob motion.
That's all.
You need a Bob,
a Bob,
new body.
Make your next permanent.
Uh, Bob,
Bob permanent, permanent.
My mamadon told me, my mamadon told me.
My mamadon me.
A worrisome thing, a worrisome thing.
Train it, train it, train it, train it.
My mamadon, my mamadon me.
You'll just love Bob
Be sure to listen again next week
When Bob Perfect for Today
Again brings you
The Bob Show
From Bobby Wood
This girl knows that
Bob is the essence of romance
Who tonight?
Then did Norrell Preff
Dot com
Is the essence of collagery
As most of the subsequent
Collages will continue to demonstrate
And just as
Fernanda Nandeli-Mur
Is the killer of Bob
You'll have to get rid of him somehow for good
But how?
Suddenly you found the answer
It's as simple as kill Bob
Kill Bob
If he contacts you, don't try to help him
He's dangerous
Bob
Hello?
Did you hear the news on the radio?
They say I killed Bob
Guess that's when I must have fallen asleep
Bob
The only person I can kill
I can kill Bob
First thing I saw was Bob's body
Then the gun beside me and I killed Bob
Are you sure?
I'm afraid so, Bob
I don't think the police will believe it
But it's the truth
I killed Bob
Yes, Bob
You've got to answer it, Bob
Hello?
Hello, Bob
Oh, darling
Listen to me, Bob
She was in love with Bob
Oh, no, Bob
I was at the party
I actually did it for her
I thought I could kill Bob
Where did you go after the party last night?
Somebody set up a boob trap in your cabin
It was a dark one, Bob
Then it did just that
I said I could kill Bob
She meant that boob trap for you
Don't look away, Bob
Perhaps I did kill Bob
Doesn't that make sense?
Well, yes, yes, it makes sense
Yes, Bob
Bob
Listen, Bob
I was talking about Gavin, but he's a little stressed
Okay, but hell, he doesn't have to be stressed
I'm going to jump down my throat
Does he have a family or relatives?
Yeah, I have a wife and a child
You know, the deceased, what's his name, Dobbs
Does he have a family?
Yes, he does
He has a family
He has a wife and two young kids
I think they're divorced
His kids are divorced?
What is wrong with you?
Do you laugh at anything?
I mean, do you just laugh at anything?
A man has died
She thinks this is fun
Are all you movie people like this?
Go, go, go
Here's Bob
Bob won for A1 Slacks
Hi, this is Bob won
Years ago, my grandfather Abner won
Known for short because he was
Invented the A1 Slack
However, today's go-go action now generation man on campus and off
Wants a little more out of life
So we added another leg to our super slim trim fitting A1 Slack
And came up with super slim trim fitting A1 Slacks
A1 Slacks, the two-legged action slacks for the two-legged action man
Thank you, Bob
You're welcome
And now back to our movie
Looks like we're going to find Bob
And we've, over the years, because of the church
We went public in 19, actually July, January 1st, 1980
We printed the first sacred subgenius pamphlet
And have been misunderstood from that day on
But you know, as they say
Those who know don't say and those who say don't know
So we should all just shut up
But look here, we keep blabbering on
And we're not going to do that
Is it the drugs?
That's what the Cleveland Police Department might tell you
In fact, a friend of ours sat in on a lecture
To the Cleveland Police Department
By a cult expert
Who explained that Bob was assigned for Satan
And drugs and stuff
But obviously, friends, this is a religion
Bob is here to replace the drugs
Just look at that
Just looking at his face
Eats up more brain cells than most of your drugs
If you're doing it right
Like a real subgenius
If you can meditate upon the dots
Every little dot
So many of you have done this, I know
You just focus on that thing
And after a while
You feel so much slack
It's like heroin combined with PCP
Combined with DDT, LSD
And you're like, oh my God, I'm so drunk
And marijuana, as my father puts it
But what Bob's preaching is
The joy of drugs
But not necessarily with the drugs
Although those can certainly enhance everything
For the first ten minutes
But what Bob preaches is slack, friends
And slack is so simple
That I can't explain it
Because it's different for each person
Everybody has their own form of slack
Some people get their slack
From sitting on their ass watching TV
And drinking beer
There's nothing wrong with that
The conspiracy of the normal people
Would love for that to be the only way
You feel you're getting slack
We're here just as a pep talk
Just a reminder that slack
Slack is whatever makes you feel
Like you're doing what you were supposed to be doing
And that could be anything
For our friend Dennis Murphy here
Slack might be
God, I can't even begin to imagine
Maybe I should have picked a different
Some people like bird watching, right?
Some people like pornography
Some people like movies
Some people like people
And just hanging out and talking
Can be your purest form of slack
And you can steal that slack
While on the job
As you've learned around the coffee machine
I'm sure
As my good friend and speechwriter
You might say, Dr. Onan Kanabite put it
Slack is the oomph in uncomfortable
That's it
See he has
He has some stage
He has
He says slack is the oomph in comfortable
He says oomph is accompanied by a gesture of vigor
From the hips among adults or a pumped elbow on US TV
So it could actually be slack is the oomph in uncomfortable
Why do I keep wanting to say uncomfortable?
I don't know
And as I said, slack can come when you throw good money after bad
And bad money after Bob
And that's why that sales table is out there
This, oh, and we have a new book out
Intelligent Design for Dummies
Our new publication
So be sure if you think you've already bought
All the accessories that go with Ken and Barbie
There's some new accessories out there
So
So you know Bob has many death days
What's his birthday?
Bob has had so many lives
So many past lives
That by chance, you know, one of almost every day of the year
Is the birthday of a Bob
Where is Bob now?
Is there somebody that we should be looking towards?
Where is Bob?
Is he mayhats fishing on Lake Titicaca
With G. Gordon Gordon?
Is he perhaps selling ice to an Eskimo somewhere in Alaska?
Is he perhaps selling hypocrisy to a subgenius in San Francisco?
But Bob is a traveling salesman
And resides at no fixed address
Unlike the god of the Mormons
Who is known to be on a planet circling the star Koloff
Having sex with his many spirit wives
He's a star about a guy named Smith on Terrapin Pieces
Although we don't know where Bob is now
We know that Bob is coming
And when I say that I don't mean
It's not like when Jesus is coming
That usually means Jesus is on his way
He's due to arrive
When we say Bob is coming
Bob is literally
That is what Bob is
Is always coming
And it's true, but isn't he sometimes there
And then at other times not?
When you come tonight you will see Bob
I'll be looking for him
About an hour and a half
That's terrible
I'll be home by then
And you can't move
I know, but I just don't want to see him during that thing
You don't want to be everywhere
But don't you think you'd understand it all at that point?
Or maybe not
I think that's when the shark bites you
That's the part I thought about
You're out there swimming around and a shark bites you
Because you're being distracted
Yeah
If you're together enough to understand that last big organism
Then you're pretty well set
Instead of music stopping
You're just left out there
Like some amateur show
It's now that Bob's coming your way
He is?
Ah!
Oh!
Karunch?
Bob!
I mean, no, I said oh God
I mean, oh Bob, I did
Well, there are no atheists in foxholes
Not 저기
Bob's coming
You're just right
No I mean, don't you think
Bob's coming
I do
Oh, I wish you Let's preach
It's called In the Name of Bob.
Around Robert Downey Jr.
Plan B Productions, I think, is slated to produce that.
There's that Lithuanian actor.
Johnny Depp plays the young Ivan Stang.
And Jim Carrey plays Violet Drummond.
I don't know who else has been cast yet.
But Bob would be Andy Serkis.
The guy that played Gollum and Kong.
Right, Andy Serkis.
That would be good.
So he would basically be a performance capture.
And Mike Myers is the voice of Cthulhu.
You can see we've been thinking about that.
Very true.
Any love interests in the film?
Yeah, the hero would be Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
And I think he'd be courting popular bull girl Dave Vina.
He's voiced by Lindsay Lohan.
In a bikini.
Just because.
And they're all penguins, right?
Yeah, I love them.
That's right.
They're all CGI penguins.
Thousands and thousands.
And then there's the Spielberg Saturday morning TV show, Little Subgenius.
Dear Subgenius!
I said Lil.
Lil.
Lil Subgenius.
With Pip and Squeak.
Well, we've been waiting for the remake.
That was the Sid and Marty Croft production.
What, the remake?
That was a great remake.
Original, Lil.
Second big feature was another one of my favorites.
I never saw the remake.
What is that about?
What is this thing?
It stinks.
That was a joke.
What is this thing?
The second big feature was a possible name for a Subgenius feature.
What was the name?
Second big feature.
I thought they were like a real band.
Second big feature?
Yeah.
But Philo disabused me of that notion tonight.
He said it was just negative land.
The Swingin' Love.
Wait, write that down.
That's a good name for a band.
Yeah.
Not negative man.
Negative land.
Nobody expected what happened next.
Sensational career.
I'm Bob.
So why are so many people flocking to, to, to, to, to?
My message is that God is a hoe.
That he'll take us places we've never dreamed of.
It's hard.
You may be misleading some people.
So big.
Being gay.
Gay and generous.
Leading them to some false god or something like that.
Deluding and dumbing down.
You know.
Right up there with gardening.
Bam.
There's a hit.
Great, great, great, great, great, great.
Wait, you're saying that.
Oh my God.
Nothing.
Make beautiful women fall all over you.
No doubt there.
Take steroids.
Slack, slack, slack.
Cut, cut.
I'm weak.
Now, a lot of people say that some terms that are in the, in the, as you say, the
Bobliagraphon, the, the, the, uh...
the, the, the, the cyclopedia, uh, it kind of, uh, uses, uh, notions similar to, not the same
as, but, but in the same area as Scientology, or kind of a New Agey, but, but, but in a fashion
that, that's almost Dadaesque.
Well, um, you know, any religion or priesthood is, uh, based on impenetrable jargon.
Lawyers, doctors, for instance, and we get a lot of, of, uh, lawyers and doctors joining
up because they appreciate it.
They appreciate that impenetrable obfuscation, uh, and, and, uh, invented words and, uh, words
that have been recombined so as to, so that when you're reading this stuff, you feel like
you're really part of a secret army.
And, and the great thing is, you are.
It's, it's not much of a, I mean, it's still a secret, so it's not that much of an army.
Not much of an army, yeah, right.
No.
But, you know, it's kind of like they, what they used to say about Fight Club.
Yeah.
First rule, don't talk about it.
Don't talk about it.
Yeah.
Of course, naturally, everybody talks about it.
Uh.
Well, and, you know, the Hell's Angels used to say, those who say don't know, and those
who know don't say.
Mm-hmm.
And we should probably just shut up.
Well, yeah, and, and this show will go right to hell.
Um, I, I like one thing about it, and I always say, you know, this has got to be the best
deal in organized, uh, shall we say, religion or, or church.
And that is, uh, guaranteed.
Salvation or triple your money back.
That's right.
Eternal salvation or triple your money back.
That's a, that's an offer that no other religion makes.
Well, I, you know, I, none of them do.
And, and I'm thinking, you know, now there's one you can, you can grasp.
That, that's the kind of church I can get behind.
Right.
Or in front of.
It costs to join.
And that means that if you, at the end of time, find yourself in the pit of hell, uh,
we will gladly refund your money.
We'll give you $90.
Now there is a little book that you can, that Bob sells down there called, uh, hell on five
cents a day.
Well, I think it's 89, 95 nowadays.
Yeah.
And a day lasts a long time in hell.
Normal hell.
Now subgenius hell is kind of like a endless party.
Well, that's my idea of a good idea.
Right.
Yeah.
Now we, I, you know, this, it's possible.
Some people think the subgenius thing.
It's just a joke.
And I mean, some people compared to what though?
Right.
Exactly.
You know, everybody's religion is going to be a joke to somebody else.
Yeah.
One of them has to be true.
What if it was this one?
Who knows?
Crazier things have happened.
I know.
Look at the inquisition.
Look at the news.
See?
Yeah.
You know, I, so I wouldn't be surprised at anything, uh, that would happen.
Although we're.
We are kind of behind Scientology.
We got started a little bit later.
That's all right.
So did L Ron Hubbard.
Hold on a second.
If you will, uh, Reverend, we're going to take a quick break here.
Reverend Ivan Stang.
He is the founder of the Church of the subgenius and talking more about the
Church of the subgenius for those of you out there who've never heard of it.
Well, here's a chance to find a religion you can really get behind or next to or
in front of her.
Yeah.
Something.
I'll put it over.
Me.
I'm serving it now.
Feed it.
Now.
You've known him.
I see it for you.
I'm McBarber.
You're listening to radio.
85 K away.
Kids just don't understand.
What's that horrible stench?
The laughing lemur.
Is there much communication with other worldly subgeni?
Well, there's, um, of course on other continents, there are the Euro subgeniuses.
There's a Euro subgenius.
Yahoo.
Very much.
They're busy.
And, uh, you know, oddly enough, as the dollar becomes more, less and less valuable compared
to other countries money.
We get fewer memberships and ordainments here in the U S but we're making a mint off of
all of a sudden in euros.
People in Europe are joining up and Australia, all the English speaking world, but, uh, we're
also starting to hear from Russians.
And oddly enough.
A lot of Nigerians.
Keep offering us a huge fortune.
As long as I give them your bank account number.
Yeah.
It's, it's, it's definitely one of the world's fastest growing religion, but it's not a snack
religion.
Well, it is a sac religion.
No, a snack.
Oh, you sure?
It's a snack religion.
Okay.
Very good.
First short.
We push Bob as a short duration personal savior.
We don't expect you to cling to him.
We don't expect you to cling to it forever.
It's we don't want you to use Bob as a crutch rather.
We want to let you should let Bob use you as a crutch.
You are Bob's crutch.
I'm interested in your information.
I'd like to subscribe to the newsletter.
Wait, I already do.
You go to subgenius.com and click on the news button.
It's actually all very logical.
There used to be a hard copy, but a famous publication, the stark fist of removal.
But in the cyber age, it doesn't come out very often.
We allow special members to print out the online version.
Well, you know, and, and, and Dobbs made most of his important deals in strange places when
he first started out like a waffle house in Haightville, Georgia.
I thought it was Ellicott city, Maryland.
It was a Stucky's in Texas.
Well, there were several.
He knows all this stuff.
Right.
Where, where was it?
I don't know.
He fell asleep.
Um, I think, I think he's suffering the wounds of crates.
Hey, you know, I got a joke.
What's the, what's the difference between Jesus Christ and a picture of Jesus Christ?
Are you guys talking about me?
We were saying we're, uh, I was actually, uh, uh, was, I'm in the process of flipping
a, a tape.
So, uh, are we supposed to be funny?
No, we're not.
No, no, no, no.
No, I don't think so.
No, we wanted to know the connection between the Raelians on the one hand, Dr. Sinister's
show and Bob's hardest sell, not anything to do with primate arrest.
So what is, what's the difference between, what's the difference between Jesus and a
picture of him?
I don't know.
Oh yeah, that was it.
Yeah.
What's the difference between Jesus Christ and a picture of Jesus Christ?
You only need one nail to hang up the picture.
Oh, Hey, what's the, what's the difference between Jesus Christ and a picture of Jesus
Christ?
Jesus Christ.
The picture is real.
Oh, keep going.
Oh, but Bob is real.
Bob is real.
You should be careful.
You know, you, you don't want to offend the Arabs saying Bob is real.
Bob is real.
And there was a waitress in, in, uh, Hapeville, Georgia who, who told, I can't say this stuff
on the air.
Sure you can.
No, I can't.
Um, it, it, it, it, it, I get in trouble.
Did somebody found a Dobbs head in a pancake?
No, no, no, no, no.
It's much more complicated than that.
Um, when I met her, I was, it was about three o'clock in the morning and she was waffle
house waitress, which she knows pretty normal.
And uh, and she started telling me I had on a Dobbs shirt and she said, I've seen him.
He was here with these weird guys.
And she tells me this long story and I can't really tell it on the air to not giving, I
don't want to give away too many secrets.
Like the guys weren't really guys.
They were like aliens or, you know, what's, what's the, but she had met Bob just that
she had met Bob.
Oh, she had served Bob a cup of coffee.
That's not unusual.
Uh, Bob often has been where a sub genius arrives just before the sub genius got there.
You hear that all the time.
So actually I've seen him arriving just as Bob has just has left.
I've seen him a couple of times actually.
People wonder if he's a memory or a premonition.
Cause the, it's so fleeting and they're just aware of something having happened.
I've seen him driving away twice.
I've seen him getting Bob on the highway at least twice.
Actually I saw him get thrown out of a coffee shop actually cause he wouldn't put his pipe
out, you know, and they, they threw him out and like exactly.
And then I, I, but I figured I'd just leave it then, you know, hands off more chance,
you know, and uh, I don't know what exactly it was, but the people in there got really
upset about something.
They forcibly threw him out.
Like literally threw him out.
And right as soon as he threw him out, a big bus came by and hit him right as he threw
him out there.
And then he was gone.
You see, all I saw left behind was like, there was like some, uh, like a smoldering of the,
uh, of like a broken pipe there.
But then again, you know, next week I saw Bob again, you know, he was fine.
Yeah.
Well, you know, it's funny.
The reason the waitress was asking about the shirt I had on is that Bob never paid his
bill.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, why is it always the rich ones?
That's how you know it really was Bob.
Why is it always the rich ones?
Well, if you tell me, it was like the first night they were open at this particular location.
So this had to have been back in like 58 or 60.
And she still remembered the guy cause he stiffed her.
You know?
Well, you always remember the person who stiffed you.
Yeah.
Especially if they look like that, you know, they're grinning while they do it.
Your first night getting stiffed.
Yeah.
We always remember that.
Has anybody delivered a pizza to Bob?
And you know, I don't know.
13 cents tip.
Get the idea.
Wow.
A whole 13 cents.
That's pretty good.
Bob doesn't tip to drivers either.
That's happened.
I know a driver who delivered to him and Bob doesn't tip.
Bob says, let me give you a tip.
Don't get screwed or something really dumb and witty like that.
Yeah.
He grabs the food and it's the same thing to every pizza delivery guy.
My dad does that too.
Do you know how leprosy he is?
He's got a leper leaves a tip for a hooker.
Oh.
We can stop there.
Man.
That was a quick one.
That was quick.
It's old.
Yeah.
Old like me.
You know, and when I get home, I'll chop up another three shows out of this one real fast
and take off for Texas, to Stang County, where we go every December.
That's right.
We're building a big cult compound in Stang County, Texas.
You don't want to go down by Stang County, son.
It's near Dead Branch Pass.
Actually in Stang County has a nuclear power plant that serves Dallas.
It has a really big tax base.
We have a lot of tax money because of that.
Yeah.
And my family is very involved in city politics, county politics and so forth.
So we've been able to go forward on construction of this underground bunker.
Started as a missile, an abandoned missile silo bunker.
Even better.
There are a lot of those in Texas.
They've done the digging for you.
Yeah, that's right.
I saw something a while back about people living in these, in the bunkers, owning them,
right?
Yeah.
In their home.
We did that.
And we also have extensive tunneling going on.
To the mall.
Luckily there's uranium, raw uranium on the land of Stang.
Bridge.
And goats.
Like every good compound.
Why goats you may ask?
Well, because there was a drought.
Why a goat?
And the cows, there wasn't enough grass for the cows or the zombies.
Goats in Jehovah.
Yeah.
But the goats, the goats are happy.
We actually have a cult compound in Texas with goats.
Slightly radioactive goats.
Yeah.
Machine gun, you know, encampments.
The horns glow.
It's a terrible thing.
So we, most of the time the other members of the Stang clan run the ranch.
I just go down there every now and then to oversee.
The Stang.
Stang stomping ground.
The killings.
Stang likes to go down to supervise the killings.
We're going to build a big TV studio there.
And a crystal cathedral.
And a drive-through crystal cathedral so that, and a creation.
Drive-through.
Drive-by.
And we're going to have a special museum about the way evolution really worked.
Where subgeniuses really came from.
Where they'll be displayed.
Audio animatronic yeti.
Yeah.
Arrival of the exes.
The creation of the humans by the yetis and so forth.
That's actually my favorite part of the episode.
Audio animatronic Stang and Grover.
The guys talking and their arms kind of moving.
Are you familiar with the creation of the humanoids movie?
Yes.
Most certainly.
That's a great film.
The creation of the humanoids.
Mandatory subgenius feeling.
Why doesn't he listen to you?
What's his name?
Gavin.
Right.
Garvin.
I can never remember his name.
So why doesn't he listen to you, huh?
Because I'm a human.
I tend to rattle his cage.
He doesn't like it.
Well, was it like this before the actor?
What was his name?
The one who died?
Dobbs.
Yeah, Hobbs.
What was going on then, huh?
Anarchy.
Dobbs was rewriting the script.
He'd call script conferences every morning before shooting.
It made everyone crazy.
Well, we already had a script.
What was the problem, huh?
He was an actor.
What can I tell you?
He wasn't even good at it, you know?
He was the look at me scratch my school of acting.
Oh, such asses.
I asked this guy, Dobbs.
I asked him last week.
I said, why are you doing this?
What did he say?
He said it was a joke.
It was a generational thing.
And what's that mean, huh?
Beats the hell out of me.
Little puke.
Come on!
You couldn't do anything to stop it?
What could I do?
Gavin had no control.
He was terrified.
Couldn't make decisions about anything, even about breakfast.
It could have helped me, you know?
Works.
Dobbs, Dobbs, Dobbs, Dobbs.
Colts, Colts.
Just out of time.
Dobbs, Dobbs, Dobbs, Dobbs.
Went off.
The incredible last wrong committed.
Committed.
Now you do know, Colt.
You know, with ADHD and, you know, just kind of, you know, you know, just kind of, you
know, you know, uh, you know, um.
You know, uh, put your arm around these young men.
Watch it.
You know, but, Colt, I, I, it's my Colt.
I, uh, you know, you know, Secret Life on the Internet, Colt.
Uh, uh, uh, well, doody, doody.
Uh, uh.
It doesn't make any sense, you know.
Action.
And so we were, you know, coming.
You know, it's, you know, you know.
Hmm, hmm.
So we got off, you know.
I'm really deeply involved in girls and boys and girls today.
Mm-hmm.
In a cult.
Perfect.
Gone down the wrong road, but beautiful.
Crazy things get said.
Dobbs, Dobbs, Dobbs, Dobbs.
Back again.
We're up right against the top of the hour and, of course, a news update.
But want to, uh, get some final details from our, our, our good guest, the Reverend Ivan
Stang.
He's, uh, uh, the, the, uh, head, head, headmaster, I guess.
And.
No, uh, my, my, uh, title is Sacred Scribe.
Cool.
All right.
Sacred Scribe number 273.
Uh, Bob Dobbs is the living avatar of Slack.
Wow.
That's his official title.
Not to be confused with the other Dobbs down the road from us.
Um, uh, for those who wish to find out more and, or get your books and your, and your
DVD and, and also, by the way, that, that hell on five cents a day kind of thing.
Um, how does one do this?
If you're on the internet, the simplest thing would be to look at subgenius.com.
Mm-hmm.
And I'll, uh, uh, subgenius does not have an O in it.
Oh, okay.
I have to say that because there are a lot of subgeniuses out there.
It's S-U-B-G-E-N-I-U-S.com.
All right.
Very good indeed.
And Reverend Stang, I'm going to, by the way, I'm going to put you on hold.
My producer, Steve, needs to speak with you, but, uh, I want to thank you so much.
It's been a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
I'm just, I'm a little concerned that I'm going to have those Monkees songs stuck in
my head for the next three days.
An ear bug is the worst, isn't it?
Yeah.
Thank you very much.
Indeed.
And thank you very much.
Okay.
And please stay there, Reverend, but thanks very much indeed.
Praise Rick.
And praise, praise Ivan.
Anyway, we're going to take it up to the news.
From PR News in Washington, I'm involved in a prostitution ring.
President Bush says the U.S. will help Poland modernize its childhood obesity.
Mr. Bush says health officials are overweight.
I'm optimistic that we'll be able to live in deprivation and fear.
Health officials say children and teenagers are not immune from congressional and congressional
subpoenas, as claimed by the Bush administration.
The president also said today that this is PR News in Washington.
A thanks to Leimur for that and PR News and laughing.
This has been Hour of Slight Number 1143 with Dr. Hal Pasling, Evidence, Philo Drummond,
John Hell, Mongoloid, and Kay Rob in San Francisco, Dr. Sinister and Princess Pisces, and Lonesome
Cowboy Dave on WCSB Cleveland, and Governor Ratnar, and No Money Mark, and Dr. Robert
Lowe, and the movie soundtrack that is so weird is from Slipstream, and the background
music is Bonobo's Convergence from Last X Day and Next X Day.
And now, from Norell, this message.
For the safety of your smile, see your dentist twice a day.
The Bob Show, starring Bob and his guest star, Lone Thrill.
How do you do, ladies and gentlemen?
This is Bob.
I was so glad to be back, I went down to the blood bank and gave a pint of blood.
W.C. Fields was there, too.
He donated a fifth.
Trip the Light, fantastic.
Have you tried going a little buggy with a girl and a horse with a horse?
The horse wants to go out for a little buggy.
Get a horse, black or brown or gray.
But a horse wants to go out for a little buggy.
Get a horse.
Robert, quit putting it in your pipe.
Jugs.
I thought you used your nose for that.
You talk like I was a freak.
I was a freak, freak, freak.
Father, I'm down here with a nice young man.
Get a horse.
Hello.
Wrong number.
Uh-oh.
Hello.
Remove that film.
Quickly, easily, safely.
No one.
Get a tube.
Ladies and gentlemen, you really like the girls, don't you?
Yes, Bob, I do.
I'm a little bit scared.
Now, ladies and gentlemen, I'd like to introduce one of the reals of genius.
Thank you very much.
I presume you're Bob the genius.
I'm becoming known as the Bob of this generation.
Bob.
Magic Bob.
I know, Bob.
Why do I stand here reading this stripe when I can get a good job at Lockheed?
I'm Bob.
Sit down, Bob.
I'll read your future.
I can tell you who's going to be in the White House.
I do a lot of deep thinking.
Get loaded.
So, uh, someone died?
Yeah, died.
Ah, Dobs.
You wrote the part of Ray for an African American, right?
I did.
Yeah, man.
What's wrong with you?
Are you on drugs?
No.
I'm not on drugs.
Ray, the character that Dobs was playing was black.
Dobs wasn't a black actor, man.
He was white, like her.
Oh, my God.
Why did you kill me off feelings?
Barbara.
I was just a script supervisor.
That's all I was.
Miss Barbara.
Now, you have no continuity.
You have no authority.
Nothing makes sense anymore.
It's so unfair.
It's just so unfair.
So unfair.
Go, go.
Mommy.
In dealing with supernatural reanimated mummies that play the old age home.
Just like DJs at Pirate Cat Radio, ladies and gentlemen.
One day they are going to mummify us.
And it will be an honor.
Your encrusted sarcophagus, rich with jewels and hieroglyphs,
will be lowered into your own personal vault and sealed by the sands of time.
I want to be frozen in loose art.
Like Bob did.
Bob is, one of the Bobs is in loose art.
To be frozen in the ice.
Scott Scraper in Dallas, which we lost.
Lost? Where did it go?
Well, I mean, we lost ownership of it.
But that's where Bob is? One of the Bobs?
The one that puzzling evidence shot.
Damn you.
But he's like a...
Was a real flesh and blood Bob, that Bob.
Wow.
The scary Bob.
When I introduced...
When I introduced people to that Bob, they would...
I remember where I was that day.
...do a great big double take.
The last thing you expect is actually to be introduced to Bob.
A small Bob.
But then came that terrible day, the Victoria Theatre Show.
The anniversary of the beheading of Louis XVI and Marie Antoinette.
The assassination of Bob.
Yeah, we all remember Bob.
We all remember where we were that day, don't we?
I know where I was.
In Indiana.
And it's on videotape to prove it.
So, we have one Bob buried in Dallas.
Is that right?
Well, if you go back over the Hinkey Commission hearings,
the entire official answer was sort of cobbled together out of variant strains of rumor and innuendo.
Where's the director?
No!
Let's get on with it!
Cut! Cut! Cut!
Hey, Harvey!
I didn't know you were...
It's his money, isn't it?
Well, I'm sorry, but you got a shot.
Hot shot! What are you talking about?
What are you doing?
I gotta get out.
I'm gonna get out of here.
What are you doing?
I'm going to get back.
I'm sorry!
Oh, my God!
I've gotta get back.
It's four o'clock.
My time's up.
I've gotta go back.
Please, don't be crazy.
My time's up.
I've gotta go back.
I've gotta get back.
I'm almost home.
I'm here to hear it.
Please, don't hurt us!
We're not gonna hurt him.
What's wrong?
You have some kind of medication?
Hey!
Wait, wait!
Oh, my God!
What's that, dear?
Oh, yes, I heard.
I heard.
Poor old Felix.
Cut!
That's lunch, everyone.
That's it.
Good.
Take care.
Now I will count three.
At the count of three, you will wake up and remember nothing.
One, two, three.
Ten thousand dollars. What do you know?
Yes, beautiful, isn't it?
Ah, this castle is filled with rare old treasures.
Feel free to browse, my friend.
Thank you very much.
A pleasant good evening to you.
Thank you.