I'm afraid.
Be quiet.
There he is.
Look at his face now, David.
Yes.
I see it.
It's composed.
It looks human again.
Perhaps we're not meant to tamper with the natural.
So genius.
Powerful.
Be quiet.
He's looking this way.
It's me, though.
No!
The god damn it.
He's still coming.
The story of Bob goes back in time to the very beginning of time.
And it's a tale that keeps repeating itself throughout the centuries.
We hope all young people throughout the solar system
will be able to see the power of God.
And we will join us in celebration of this great day in our faith.
We only wish you could see it, folks.
This surging crowd of subgeniuses.
Intractable and unruly.
I can't help thinking.
Barely kept in control by the last semblance of civilized behavior.
Everything is bullshit.
Which they cling to as so many foul and soiled rags.
But how would that be different from any other day?
Soon their souls will be scrubbed with the steel wool of tradition.
And they will take off into the noosphere.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one.
Yeah!
A beautiful trajectory.
A beautiful liftoff.
Here at Cape Canaveral Gravel this morning.
The great silver rocket climbing on a pillar of flame
and toward fame and fortune.
Already hospital facilities have begun to crack under the strain.
And civil defense authorities state the situation is much the same
across the entire country.
Martial law is now nationwide.
Bob, follow that channel.
This is a class one...
You won't need your wallet here.
Ten thousand miles from the atmosphere.
And your home.
I got exactly what I wanted!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Two, one, two, three, two, one.
Woo!
Someone's crying on the roof above.
All the media here for the show.
I've been waiting for our friends to come.
Night spiders and ropes with me falling.
A dirty rampant for a visit.
I can't.
We met one in Termin and mostly fall.
And now...
The moment you've been waiting for...
The aliens are about to materialize before your eyes.
They came to us from a far distant planet.
And now here they are in our midst.
I insist.
Let's hear it for...
The alien.
We are coming! We must be able! We must be able!
We're all going to die!
Let's kill him.
You wanna kill him? I don't think that's a wise thing. Not a wise thing to do. Do you really think that you can't even see him? You will feel him. And if you're dreaming that you can take him, I don't think that's a very wise thing to do.
And now we look through a curtain of mist.
As the new subgenius paradigm is being born.
An efflorescence here. Vegetable uprising of tendrils, shoots, tiny quivering timorous leaves and huge dank creepers of Spanish moss.
Descending like the snaggled teeth of a broken jaw to cut out all light.
Philo, why don't you take that drum?
Robot down. I hate him.
Chappy is out of control.
Shut him off. Blank him. Erase him. Hey, you too, Hal. Put it...
Where's my background music? What did you guys do?
Well, we assessed the situation and then just like...
Just like old Daniel Boone, we said, be sure you're right.
Then go ahead. And so, since we thought we were right...
Be sure you're P.
Went right ahead on that terrible planet of the apes.
Get your filthy paws off me, you damn dirty pink.
Oh, oh, this is terrible. Terrible. Just terrible. Oh.
I'm out of here.
In the foavyatar, g рассказывation and even more terrain.
What up, Princess Williams?
I have information about the food available him.
Food? Well, bring it on.
Availability.
I guess we're having hot and sour snails.
Yes.
Rubber spiders in...
What is available are, for the next half hour,
you can get ham and Swiss plus chips for $6,
or just the sandwich for $5.75.
A terrifying revelation.
Grapes, hummus, and pretzels for $5.
All mixed together.
Chips for 50 cents.
Chips off the old block.
Gripped grapes for $3.25.
Pre-gripped grapes.
And hummus and pretzels for $2.50,
and that's available for the next half hour.
I'm talking about real food, man!
Hummus, another word for soil or dirt.
We call it earth,
and we intend to chew the soil over slowly
to masticate it to appreciate its local quality.
She was going to make some grandma-faced sandwiches.
Yeah, but they got those down here.
No.
They only have ham and Swiss.
And it's really ham.
It's just, you know...
Well, if it's a genuine hummus Alabamus,
I'll just have one.
But we've got schmoo meat up there.
Well, whatever is easy, we should do,
and whatever is hard, we should not.
They slice themselves up for you.
Yes, I know.
And obligingly, with a twinkling tear in their little eye.
Oh, but they're happy.
They love to do it.
It hurts.
But that's what they...
always wanted to do, the schmoos.
And those tendrils, those little mustache-like feelers
that they have quiver with excitement.
Oh, is that what those are?
I thought they were just a mustache.
They're like a mustache.
That's it.
All the creatures in the Valley of the Schmoon have them.
The schmoo grow in Slobofia, right?
No, they come from the Valley of the Schmoon in Dogpatch.
Oh.
I thought they were...
They come in, you know, in the upper Slobovia.
It would have been lower Slobofia, but I don't think so.
I believe that they came from the Valley of the Schmoon.
Hey, Reverend Stang.
Yes, sir.
Give me this kind of output,
and let me plug it in with these kind of inputs.
Yes, he really puts out.
We are having technical difficulties.
Please, stand by.
Now, what about the electrostimulonerve reinforcement bracelet?
They all have to have one of those damn things on,
and they don't come off, neither.
No how.
It's happening.
What?
It's an attack.
Excellent.
Now it's time we scream death.
Meanwhile, far below the Earth's surface...
Lieutenant.
Yes?
Dobbs and I have been training local pilots in Cobras
for their own strike forces against the cartel.
Lead, this is Snake 2, entering Sector 4079.
Roger.
Advise to leave Robbs in our position.
Will co, Dobbs.
How's the view up front, buddy?
I'm not crazy about it, man.
I'll be glad when we get out of this canyon.
I was flying wing that day with Captain Tejada.
Lieutenant Dobbs, the other American,
was the flight leader in the front program.
We were entering a sector we'd never been before.
Stop.
The thing of it is, Bob, I got a bad feeling on this one.
I don't think I'm gonna make it out.
Get thee behind me!
Are you in danger, Pastor?
All right, roger.
Just a little argument with my co-pilots.
Over.
That's great.
Meanwhile...
The units are approaching the station.
They're coming straight at us.
It's the most...
Nah, it can't be.
It is.
Ah!
Rob!
I have visual.
Snow.
Fearing 235, 40 degrees.
What the hell is going on?
We're under attack.
Yeah.
Right.
Nice.
Bob is my only hope.
Back off!
Did it go off?
How can what ordinary man have so many enemies?
Of course, that's just the start.
You smack bastard!!
We were five miles from the objective when we saw the scorpion attack helicopters.
value.
Try to jump the other way now, Dobbs.
Dobbs, move it. You're 12 o'clock.
Stone, you're on your own. Take your next shot.
Here I am.
He's turning over.
Dobbs, ain't a guy like to be taken advantage of.
Breaking formation.
Steady. Steady.
Stay with him.
Next shot.
Here you are, Dobbs. What I owe you. With interest.
Bob!
Thank you, Blackhawk. Get the hell out of there.
Bob?
Can you read me?
Do you copy?
We're dubbed.
Bob.
Bob is dead.
They shot him in the head.
You want to make an omelette, you gotta break some eggs.
Son of a bitch!
I'll get you for this!
What did you do to me?
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
I don't want to live!
I do not want to live!
Oh, mama!
He is cool.
So,
space travelers come halfway across the universe
to this planet,
and this is how we greet them, is it?
With rocks!
And with...
with avocados!
You ought to be ashamed of yourselves!
These aren't space monsters
with TV aerials stuck on their heads.
They haven't come here to zap your planet
with their ray guns.
These are fellow beings.
Come in peace.
You do a bit of shopping.
People of Earth,
people of Earth,
we should count ourselves privileged.
Yeah, you're privileged
to greet these intrepid pioneers
who come so far across the space.
Hey!
They took me off!
They got my truck!
Oh, who would have believed it?
What happens is gonna happen to you, and all of you.
And it's gonna be worse.
A lot worse.
That's great.
No, let's have no more curiosity.
Let's have no more curiosity about this bizarre cover-up.
If you are laboring or in distress,
you can be assisted by following the simple rules
outlined in this publication.
It's quite convenient and without complication.
There is no difficult machinery to buy or assemble.
Just pick one up free of charge
here at X Day,
22.
The clouds will open,
and the dreadful judge in middle air
shall spread his throne.
The second coming shall be at hand.
The quick and the dead shall be judged.
As soon as we get hooked up.
Yes, we're belting for Bob.
Belting for Bob.
Releasing the foul gases of decomposition
to leave the earth.
The vacuum will leave behind the purified new man.
The subgenius of the new eon.
Alfred E. New Man.
Yes, the new man is a new man.
A novus homo.
The kind that will walk the earth
after the old kind are all swept away
by the dust rag of history.
And the end dust of doom.
And the vacuum cleaner bag shall cover and absorb them all.
And the Murphy's oil soap of fight.
With the lint of long usage.
The wine press of wrath.
The blender of anger.
Yes, and the osterizer.
The egg scrambler.
The killer of justice.
Oh, here it comes now.
Run!
The sword of truth.
The helmet of justice.
No, this is the shield of justice.
What's this helmet here for?
The helmet of idiocy.
Oh, well.
Don't put it on.
What was that?
I can't hear you with this helmet on.
You're pretty funny sounding.
Hehehe.
Tune-ups of the gods.
This is the show, by the way.
This is the best show you'll hear tonight.
Just run her up there on the platform.
We'll take a look under her.
This is our best show.
This is the best show you'll hear tonight.
The pits pointed.
The ingrown hubcaps replaced.
That was actually the Sween Love Corps' hit song, which this is our best song.
It was a terrible, terrible song, but it set a low bar and low audience expectations so
that if anything good happened, then they were pleasantly surprised.
You see, it's self-referential.
It's postmodern.
It's looking back at its own belly button.
It's what everybody does these days.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a cool new thing.
It's a trendy thing.
It's breaking the fourth wall and the fifth wall and picking the third nostril.
It's a deconstructionist, you know, that whole thing.
Yeah, yeah.
It's postmodernist.
That's what it is.
It's a satire, officer.
It's just a joke.
Yeah, exactly.
Just like Mad Magazine, officer.
These aren't the people you're looking for.
We was just looking at the stars.
These aren't the drugs you're looking for, officer.
What are these boys doing out here in this field?
Why, they's just looking at the stars.
That's right.
They's looking at the stars, huh?
These boys are so sensitive.
And the wandering stars.
The ones that won't stay still.
We're watching those two to make sure they don't do anything.
We wouldn't like.
And while we're waiting and doing this, delicious sand-widgies are being prepared in the kitchen with gleaming culinary science.
Ready to be delivered for an overwhelming jolt of sensual everyday pleasures.
Well, we're waiting for the schmoo sandwiches from the...
Up the hill, from the big house, where we get to stay.
That's right.
The big house.
It's also the reason why we never make any profit off of that stay.
The big house has big bills.
Actually, it's quite reasonable for normal people, but, you know, it's hard for such geniuses.
Okay, I'm gonna change something up again.
I'm gonna reverse that last decision.
All right.
A big bill can go whistle for his separation.
Gotta do it.
All right, all right.
All right.
No, I'm gonna do it.
I thought I was gonna do it.
He's gonna do it.
I gots to do it.
Okay.
Are you sure it's the red wire you're supposed to cut?
I thought it was the black wire Bob said.
Ayee.
Oh, no, not that again.
You know, that monkey...
That wind-up monkey has gotten a lot more of a repertoire, I've noticed.
Pull that...
Unplug that one there.
You want this one unplugged?
Okay.
Roger.
No, you unplugged me.
You unplugged me.
There you go.
Now look what you did.
What are you doing?
That didn't work.
Say back that one we had before, Reverend Steins, Emil.
Reverend Schlemiel.
The one that I put away already because you said we wouldn't need it.
Yeah.
Now we're, sometimes you have to go backward in order to go forward.
You have to get yourself untangled from a mess of doctrinal error.
And you have to get that all straightened out before you can climb over the fence.
Into the pasture of pleasure.
You know, every time you have me do something, it causes me terrible physical pain.
How about that?
You're causing Reverend Stang to feel pain.
I get up to you.
You know, I am completely imperfect.
Do all physicals.
Physical pain.
You didn't like that one.
Except my own, of course.
And things like that.
What was it?
Ah, but.
Now we're going to have a really hot video of people just sitting and not moving around.
We'll want to watch this very carefully.
Multiple times.
Can you turn down that output level a little bit on that line?
It's really putting out.
Can you put up your stuff?
I think you need the nine iron for that.
Output control.
Okay, no output control.
We're going to fly blind here.
And you can see the incredible presentation being given here while we're waiting for the people to assemble on the main stage.
The subgenius dancers are giving it all.
It's an incredible spectacle.
Whirling flaming torches of pure palutonium around their heads.
They're producing a fiery spectacle.
Which ranks second to none.
And now exhausted, they drag away the temple priestess.
And at this point, the flathead sisters come out with their special offering.
It is laid reverently on the folded cloth.
Before the dais.
It's a miracle.
Ivan Stang's arm.
It's going up, up, up.
That's it.
Just pull up arm A with arm B.
It's a backup system.
Most of Reverend Stang's parts are bionic by now.
Occasionally, they may need a little time in the shop.
All that tinkering and rewiring.
Cross-circuiting to be, you know.
A little bit of that.
Why, he's good as new.
Ready to roll out.
Like any radar-activated robot.
And are there any special messages for the aliens this year?
We are ready to transmit.
We're transmitting?
This is a whole list of gripes and grievances.
A laundry list of bitching to be sent to our unearthly allies.
To show how truly ready we are.
For them to make their belated appearance at last.
Just show up.
As Woody Allen said.
That's the major part of succeeding.
Just be there.
You know, Onan had a whole rant about showing up.
Like, you could...
You don't have the right to complain about anything until you've actually shown up.
Yes, you can't sit back in your underwear and complain about everything.
Wheelchair generals.
Armchair quarterbacks.
Why, I ought to...
Yeah, they don't...
You can't sit while you're shitting on your own pants.
You don't want to fall between two stools.
You have to be ready.
You have to be whipcord ready.
You say you can't...
Did you, Dr. Drummond, did you say you can't sit while shitting on your own pants?
Now he says he didn't say that.
Yeah, no, I said that.
I did say that.
You cannot shit while sitting on your own pants.
He says a lot of things.
Every time you use that pro...
Profane language, I have to make a special version for the broadcast radio.
It'll have to be redacted.
Children's show.
As soon as he starts flapping his lips, you're going to have to put in a...
Sound effect.
I should just make a filter that automatically makes a beep to replace anything Philo says.
Or you could just beep anyway.
And people would think Philo was talking.
Boop.
See?
There's Philo right now.
But we only have to do that for the broadcast.
Older.
Allergy site.
My allergies are killing me.
This pollen.
What kind of plants grow here?
I can barely breathe.
Just cut them up like regular chicken.
Where's my Runtussin DM?
There it is.
Oh, God.
Just in time.
Must reach oxygen.
It's right over here.
Too late.
Good.
I...
If the bag does not inflate, you're shit out of luck.
Well, uh, also...
My...
My will...
The will and the treasure map are hidden in the...
In a plastic packet under your seat.
Inside the table leg, it unscrews my secret medicine for my heart.
Ah, that's better.
Two hundred percent alcohol, indeed.
But whatever it is, uh...
It, uh, serves the purpose.
Easy things to understand.
Breathe an acid spray.
Well...
Ahem.
Bah.
Bwah.
I don't understand why people say that crap's supposed to be healthy.
It is.
It's...
It's real healthy.
It's health...
Good health...
I end up...
Ah.
Just...
Unable to breathe.
I...
This planet's atmosphere just isn't right.
And the gravity so heavy.
Oh, it's horrible.
We need to go back to where Princess We came from.
If only we could figure out where it...
Where it is.
The city of helium.
The greater and lesser helium.
Ahem.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The incomparable Princess We.
So...
Uh...
Um...
See, uh...
United...
Uh...
World...
The green men of the Dead Sea Bottoms and, uh...
Well, you know...
You take it from there.
Only now, this is supposed to be Earth.
So, everything is all turned around, turned upside down.
Well, they want you to think it's Earth.
Squeegee, de-joo-jawed, jim-jammed.
So...
Uh...
You just have to...
To figure it out.
But...
Um...
If it...
It wouldn't be so heavy if, uh...
They hadn't messed with the gravity.
Uh...
You know, Dr. Howell, in the virtual bit world where many of us live, uh...
You can actually adjust the physics.
For instance, I got to mess with a doctored bit world of Grand Theft Auto...
In which the friction had been turned down to zero.
Uh...
Slip and slide, eh?
Yeah, yeah.
If you even bumped a car, it would shoot off at high speed or flip through the air.
And driving, of course, was just crazy.
It was fun.
Blow your mind, man!
Yeah, that was the whole idea.
Blow your mind.
So, you can just turn those knobs and make it weigh next to nothing.
Eh?
Microgravity on demand.
Well, that's the problem with artificial gravity.
You'll get those glitches.
Uh...
Captain Kirk had to deal with that.
He and Scotty were running through the engine room of the...
Either the engine room of the Enterprise or else an abandoned beer factory in Cleveland
that had been dressed up to look like the, uh, Enterprise engine room.
And what?
The gravity failed?
Yeah, the gravity's kind of shut down.
It was just sitting on and off.
So, they're, you know, they're trying to run along these catwalks and things, but then
suddenly they're bouncing off of them.
And then the gravity comes back and it's like, hang on to something again.
Well, it comes with the territory.
Hell yeah.
They don't let just anybody in the Starfleet these days.
Not like they used to.
In fact, uh, they're gonna bring what looks like chips and dip, uh, baby carrots, uh,
mushrooms, uh...
Little snails, uh...
There's some cocktail sauce.
Uh, those look like shrimps over there.
But they're babies!
Who cares?
They lost out.
They're losers in life's lottery of luck.
Time to chew them up and swallow them down.
Oh, you got that from that last Trump rally.
It's terrible when you're starting to steal lines from Trump.
Well, we just want to, uh, enjoy all the baby shrimp that they've got.
Agh.
Comm我說
It's time to go.
Gonna mash the
duck spots.
Now, the Loop Metro of Oklahoma has turned into an old school
garbage dump.
That's just...
Who?
The Shrieking Ghost.
Oh, really?
Just when her album had turned golden, she had to go and do something stupid.
That even happens to spirits now.
If they're famous, fame is what kills them.
It's more the fame that kills them than anything.
They die of it.
I've made sure that that won't happen to me.
Yes, we're well protected from that particular stroke of fake weapon.
No accidental Heath Ledger type high-priced death for us.
Our doctors wouldn't trust us with any kind of those kind of pills.
Not for ten minutes.
Not even them kind pills.
Oh, speaking of which, we have them kind pills.
We do?
I've got a whole bag of them.
Yes, I do.
Are they tasty?
I'm afraid to take them.
You've got to throw them to the audience.
That's what they're for.
I like them kind sugar pills.
That's what they're there.
We'll throw up the pills onto the audience.
Yes, we'll throw out the pills to the audience,
and they will gratefully take them.
They're on the spot.
Oh.
That's it.
Fight C. Todd just brought this slogan on a piece of cardboard.
That's actually Reverend Argus Fox.
That's his motto.
Not a rebel, just an idiot.
He just said it once, and I cracked up when I heard it.
Youthful idiot.
It sounded so true.
He was sitting right here at the time.
He said, apropos of nothing, I'm not a rebel.
I'm just an idiot.
Well, who characterized him, mischaracterized him?
It stuck with me.
I thought, that's the subgenius condition.
I'm not a rebel.
I'm just an idiot.
There, there.
It's all right.
Here they are, the pills.
More than kind pills, Bob.
You see, you shouldn't have mentioned the pills.
Now, here they are.
We're being inundated by pills as we attempt to do this program.
I don't know which ones I should take here.
The colors, the types, really bewildering, amazing.
What are those?
They really are them kind pills.
There's a bag of them.
It says that on the prescription, on the jar, them kind pills.
It is a prescription label with a barcode and everything.
Rx, Bob Dobbs Pharmacy, to you.
It expires, oh no.
It expires 1998.
It says, them kind pills, there's a little picture of Bob, take only as needed or whenever you want.
What?
There you go.
Let's have some now because I need and want them.
Well, there's a good, they have cotton holding them down.
They, oh my God.
Yeah, it's king cotton.
They're multicolored.
Yes, they're brilliant.
It's like somebody playing Candy Crush over here.
You'd almost think they were M&Ms, but there's no M on them, so they must be them kind pills.
Yes.
If I owe you one of them, here they are.
Sure.
And, you know, these.
They look like those over there.
The counter go fast pills.
These pills actually come from the family of the late Reverend Roberto de la Rosa.
I just took one.
I took one.
He was the one who first begged Bob for more them kind pills.
And, of course, as you might expect when you're that way about those kind or them kind, his, he didn't last forever.
And his.
His widow has now distributed for free these prescription bottles of them kind pills so that all subgeniuses can go the way of the brave Reverend Roberto de la Rosa.
Well, he went before, as it were.
Yes, a true pioneer.
And he didn't pack a suitcase either.
Could you send me some more of those pills?
Them.
Pills?
Bob.
Kind pills?
I.
I really like them.
A bucket of pills will cure your itchings.
Pills, Bob.
Bob.
Yeah.
Sandy Boone, the director of the great motion picture called J.R. Bob Dobson.
And the church of the subgenius.
Made these were going to be handed out to audiences at the premieres.
And she forgot.
Well.
And every time.
But we caught up behind her and we've got those pills right here and now in a large plastic bag.
And we intend to distribute them.
Listen to that bag rustle and crinkle, folks.
That's no ordinary Foley sound.
That is the sound of a bag of pills being fondled.
And now they're being put out on the tabletop.
You have to come up here so we can see that you don't take more than your fair share of them.
Yeah.
And you're going to be able to see that you're not taking any more than your fair share of the bag.
Incidentally, unlike the kind that we distributed at Devivals long ago, these might have sugar.
So we don't want to kill any diabetics prematurely.
Wouldn't be enough unless they gobbled every last pill here.
But, you know, they are also a nostrum panacea.
They're good for what else?
They will help you all along.
By the way, and what have we?
Oh, my goodness.
Look at that.
It's tall.
It's Reverend Fenard.
Well, she's brought more of those allergy pollen bags.
Take care of that allergy suppressant, Reverend Stang.
I've got to learn to take it easy with these allergies.
I can barely breathe.
Yeah, my problem is I can't inhale, Reverend Fenard.
She's pointing out that her allergies are delivered in an inhaler.
But I've got my allergies are so bad just naturally now.
I've never had them before.
You know, the excess are rupturing us one part at a time.
Bit by bit, they are collecting the remains of our mortal bodies.
They started with my, in my case, they started with my hair.
Then my parts of my memory.
Then my morals.
Then, and then lately it's been terrible things.
My immune system.
My resistance to arthritis.
My health.
They're rupturing one thing at a time.
In fact, there's another one thing they took from me right about this time last year.
Yeah.
It's, I'm not going to go into it because it's really, really bad.
It's really sad.
Well, all right.
Yeah.
But they do.
They are constantly filching.
They have taken some people.
It just, you know.
You know, this, our number has been depleted by people lifting up the saucers before their time as we measure time.
They're stealing a march.
They're gaming the system.
Well, that is the same with everything, including this.
The angels needed drive-in movies.
So they ruptured.
Dr.
Dark.
They needed somebody to kick their ass.
So they ruptured legume and they needed a really good barbecue.
So they took heathen.
They needed a really, really sweet girls.
They took Reverend and atrocity.
There's just an endless list of them.
It's terrible.
They're selfish is what they are.
They're magpies picking over the subgenius treasure trove.
No kidding.
And what?
And look at what they've left us with.
Look at what these people.
Look at those listeners.
Yes, they are fine specimens.
I'm sure they'll do just as well.
We need to feed those sex right there.
We can't even afford viewers.
We can only afford listeners.
And only seven or eight of them.
It's funny how on your screen it says how many viewers you have when it means how many listeners you have.
Did you ever figure that one out?
No, that's not.
My screen doesn't say.
My screen says listeners and it never goes above 25.
It says like 28 peak 34 or something like that.
Peak meaning I guess when the most are listening.
50 is the peak at WCSB.
Of course, we have much more sophisticated equipment here at Tarzan's radio station.
It's just talking about something.
We peak on about it.
About 2,000 micrograms.
I'm afraid Dr. Drummond is having an episode.
Learn to cough like Dr. Drummond.
Where's the cough button at?
Those pills he took in Arabia.
Every now and then it affects him like this.
But he'll be back to normal in two shakes of a fish's tail.
Yes, Dr. Drummond has had these episodes many times before.
Yes, sir.
He has to ignore him and he will soon be his usual affable self.
Ere the Leviathan can swim a lead.
That's a very charitable way of describing Philo's normal self.
Affable.
Yeah, that's right.
You're not exactly lying.
I have an alien affability.
Except possibly by gross omission.
But yeah, no one more affable than Dr. Drummond.
That's right.
There may be other things.
There may be other things about him as well as affability.
Well, now, Stan, I've noticed that often you're making a marvelous complimentary statement
and then you have to qualify it in some way in the interest of pure lexicographic elucidation.
That's our way.
It's the way we...
It's called ball busting, you know.
We have a ball busting...
Or ranking.
You're ranking on him.
You're just ranking on him.
Everybody got a gold ball.
Ball busting...
Now, Dr. Drummond, you know, you can't be heard very well unless you lean in to the mic like so many refuse to do.
Lean in.
Especially me.
Lazy over men and...
And uber women who even have their own radio show but still won't treat Mr. Microphone properly.
Yeah, I can't get him anywhere near my microphone.
Microphone.
It's Mr. Microphone.
Hi, girls.
Yes, you drive around your neighborhood to act like a flaming...
And they come a-running.
Reverend Stang, do you have some batteries I can borrow?
Now...
Can you be more specific?
Philo's bionic parts.
I remember your fid chuli saying, I need a ride from the airport.
Yeah, he's double A's.
Double A batteries I can borrow.
Whether it was 6.38...
I'll pay you back.
6.30 p.m.
Or which airport.
Or what day.
Can you pick me up in London and drive me to the...
Method of transportation.
Once I get my saucer, I can.
What's left of London.
I need to pick up the British Museum while I'm there.
Thanks for reminding me.
How about the Imperial War Museum?
I've never been there, but I figure one of my friends will get it.
Yeah, it's got...
I'll still have a chance to see it.
You'll probably get it.
Yeah, right.
Right.
Papa Joe Mama will get all those war museums.
Oh, I actually have my eye on the Rijksmuseum in Amsterdam, but it's for the furniture.
And if somebody else wants the artwork...
You don't like all those gloomy paintings in there?
No, I don't really care.
The babies, the baby Jesuses scare me.
Yes, there is something eerie about them.
Yeah, they...
The light of the world beaming from their wee countenances.
Yeah, for several hundred...
For several hundred years, artists in Europe really hadn't learned how to do babies in a non-terrifying way.
Well, it wasn't just any baby.
They had to draw of numinous quality.
Yeah, it was Jesus, of course.
Baby Jesus.
Hundreds and hundreds of scary, scary pictures of baby Jesus.
Well, these days, he's riding a triceratops.
Well, these days, you know, heck, everything goes.
He's riding a triceratops.
Jesus is riding a dinosaur off the edge of the flat earth.
I like the way that one movie portrayed Jesus, you know, like you always think of Jesus in his infantness.
He has these very...
Hello?
Jesus, on the line for you.
Who's she on?
Oh, here, I'll get that one.
Take that call.
We have callers coming in here.
Could that be my phone?
Yeah, we've got phones, phones, phones here at Subgenius Headquarters.
And we do take your calls.
Your calls are important to us.
Oh, no, I'm not falling for this.
Oh, what is it?
What is happening?
Brigham City, Utah.
Oh.
The phone call was coming from Brigham City, Utah.
A good idea to avoid that one.
They wanted to try to get you to be a Mormon.
Oh, it'd be an angel with a flaming sword coming to kick our butts for not being Mormons.
Well, they can get you after they're dead.
Speaking of angels with flaming swords, where's my lighter?
We're the same as Mormons.
We're just missing one M.
I don't know, man.
I didn't see it before.
In the middle.
We were using a thing that had its own inboard.
Where's my fire stick?
We were using a stick that already had fire attached to it somehow.
Philo, do you have your...
Which one of you thieves stole my fire stick?
Oh, wait, here it is.
I did not, but I...
Philo, your mic sounds strangely much louder and rougher than everyone else.
The voice of authority.
Is it because I'm too close to it?
May have been, yeah.
I probably need to be right here.
You'll be right here.
And no closer.
You'll be sorry.
And no mother, father closer.
Right.
No mother, fathering closer.
That's the way to do it.
We can always put in the cuss words.
You want me to clean up my speech, right?
Just lean over and put your lip on the microphone.
Yeah, but that does mean I...
I have to put the cuss words back in for the internet version or they'll say we cheated
them.
Some of the bitches.
I don't know.
Wait a minute.
No, we don't have to.
That's free.
That part's free.
It's free.
They paid it for the censored version.
The censored version costs.
That shows you've had an editor there.
Yeah, well, somebody asleep with their finger on the cuss word button.
The one at WCSB is very irritating.
The loop that plays when somebody says a bad word.
What's it sound like?
First, it makes a loud noise.
It's a good guitar riff.
Twang.
Inappropriate.
But it lasts about five seconds.
Yeah, I've heard that.
Yeah.
It's a...
How about where they take the bad word and they flip it around so it's backwards, but
it's still there in the...
You know what word I hate is the...
Why do you do that with music?
I hate words too.
I hate the word inappropriate.
Inappropriate.
I don't think people should be allowed to say it.
It triggers me.
I get triggered when I hear inappropriate.
When somebody says inappropriate, I don't know what to say.
I think inappropriate.
I think that's something like tiny little child.
Inadequate.
I need a knock...
Never mind.
I was going to talk about brutality.
That's what you were thinking a second ago.
I was going to...
You're going to go back to...
I was going to speak about personal brutality.
...Philo Drummond's knock ahead-itorium again.
I see.
It's easy to get him going on that subject.
I'm not the living crap.
Pressure is building up.
In fact, Pastor Pressure and Reverend Joicer.
I see.
They're all here.
Oh, good.
That's great.
They just pulled up in their pressure cooker mobile.
We were talking about clubbing and being the well-known club man carrying a large club
of stone or wood to vent one's anger.
That's Reverend Caveman.
It's all the such geniuses literally live up to their...
You let stone you when you're trying to do your thing.
They're funny names, like for Pastor Pressure is always under pressure.
Right.
And Reverend Funny Name is always...
He's always being ridiculed for his ridiculously stupid name.
And whatever you do, don't mess with Fight C. Taj because he lives up to his...
He will fight and then he'll say, C. Taj you so.
Right.
Yeah, Taj you so.
So that's what his name stands for.
I'm trying to get rid of these.
I never can remember.
He's told me what it means every year for 25 years now, but I always forget.
Some trick name, Fight C. Taj.
Well, you have to be a 33rd degree subgenius to understand that.
Yeah, yeah.
You got to be a genius.
It's part of the inner mysteries of the inner mainspring of subgenius.
When I've been told I understood it, I just forgot it.
But again, let's see the exes are coming every year, but they're just taking bits and pieces.
They take the holes out of the Swiss cheese sometimes.
Man.
Which is how our brains often end up looking after exes.
Spongiform.
Well, you see, people don't eat enough fat.
If you eat enough fat, your brain will be okay.
But otherwise, you'll get the onset of the amygdaloid plaques and other things because
there's no lipidity.
There's no fatness.
Okay.
Well, we've used up the Planet of the Apes score by Jerry Goldblum.
Your brain is made of fat.
Fat has been demonized by the sugar industry.
Fat doesn't even make you fat.
Essential part of the human diet.
Human fat is the best kind of all.
Humans have already made that fat, but as many can recollect, chicken fat is considered
by a great number of people who should know.
A healthful thing.
You know?
Yeah.
I think we should all try to apply to individuals struggling with some sort of minor illness.
Just like Grandma used to do back in her kitchen.
God bless her.
Yes, we remember the old iron stove, the spice cabinet, and of course the concrete steps
down to the fruit cellar where there were all the jams and jellies put up for the winter.
Sometimes she'd give the neighborhood urchins a popsicle.
That's why we came here.
We came over there and hung around until she gave us a popsicle.
Otherwise we wouldn't leave.
See, she had to get the idea.
A popsicle.
And now...
Well, but then we'd go over to our clubhouse in that old refrigerator that we used.
That's right.
With the little hand-drawn pictures of Bob on the wall and the no girls allowed sign.
Read those Tijuana Bibles in there.
Yeah.
We always thought...
You know, I didn't realize for years.
We had the S backwards on girls.
Now it just seems like an adorable childish mistake.
Then it was a source of embarrassment.
Dr. Drummond, is that necessary?
I'm Dr. Drummond.
I was afraid of that.
The minute I said the subgeniuses live up to their name...
The Subgenius Percussion Ensemble with Dr. Philo Drummond will return in a moment.
Tori, I'm sorry.
Tori over there is famous for tearing men in half.
Good Lord, you're not safe anywhere.
It seems like such a pleasant campground, but everyone has a secret sinister superpower
who you meet here.
Don't do that Dr. Drummond.
Sometimes it's better not to know...
Oh, well, look at that, well...
You're interfering with this perfect fact?
Put your headphones on, you can hear why you shouldn't do it.
Well, why do we have to...
Put your headphones on, you crazy man.
Must we cruise direct each other's performance?
Oh, no, look, everything's going oxy.
off the table.
Yeah, you're going to get
disconnected here.
Oh, my filthy shit.
Do you see why?
Do you hear the music in the background now?
Yeah, that sounds awesome.
That's our clubhouse music.
Yes, here in the honeycomb hideout.
Look, he can't stop.
He's just like a dog.
A little kid.
Like a dog, he hunts in dreams
and thou art staring at the wall.
This reminds me of when I invited my
grandsons, age six and age
eight, to be on the hour
of slack. Boy, was I
sorry. What, were they
fidgeting and bored out of their
stuff? No, no, no. They shrieked and
screamed nonsense that they'd
heard on television and YouTube.
And we did
manage to do one skit
where we hunted Bob
until Bob turned around and hunted us
in a dark cave.
There were a lot of scary parts in that.
But I had to edit the hell out of that.
That sounds scary to me.
Yeah, I'd like to hear that one.
That sounds like a real winner.
But they did
the same thing Dr. Drummond did.
They couldn't resist everything
I requested they not do.
Well, those could be like a Foley effect,
you know, like when you're
talking about a fist fight or something.
You could add in those bumps
and bumps to make it real.
I can't hear what anybody says
when you do that.
Nobody's saying anything when I'm doing that.
Twister punch.
Nobody's saying that when I'm doing that.
Everybody's waiting for me to do it.
No.
No, that's not true at all.
Everybody's treading you, Jeremy.
All six of those people in those chairs right there.
I don't know what all
you're looking at.
They're on the edge of their seat because they're about to leave.
Please, please, play the drums.
No one will be admitted
during the last four minutes
of the presentation.
Just for you.
Watch for the fear flasher
and the horror horn.
Can you at least turn it down a little bit?
All right, I'll turn it down
a little bit.
He certainly did.
Look what you've gone
and done again, Dr. Drummond.
Here's another fine mess
you've got us into.
Is that better?
No. Is that better?
It's a little better. It'd be better if it was silent.
The burbling, tweety
electronic noise
is great, but you're drumming,
Dr. Drummond.
The burbling of innumerable brooks.
So what you're really saying is you
bring back the burble tweeting noises.
No.
The electronic tweeting
noises, but quietly.
Just in the background
so that the people listening
think maybe they're losing their mind.
The tweeting, tweet birds, and the straw
built shed.
Because there's this nice clubhouse music.
I got you.
The echoing horn.
It's all clear to me now.
And for a limited time only.
Clear as mud.
We're going to induct you
into this cult of cults
called the Church of the Subgenius.
Whether or not you came with your credentials
entirely in order,
when you leave, you will
cleave even further
to these special principles.
Is this a practice we're doing now?
It's sort of like practice, right?
You hear nothing but the sound.
This is the first show
of the event day 22,
Dr. Violent Drama.
Okay, testing.
Testing 1-2.
Oh, wait.
I think we ascertained
that you didn't really need to be kissing
the phone.
Testing 1-2.
2-9-3-0.
It's an uphill battle.
The Slackless Children's
Dinosaur Fund.
Did you know?
I was outside yesterday
and I heard a bird in the trees
and it said, it actually said
this. It said
tweet, tweet,
tweet.
I couldn't believe it. It was like the bird.
The bird.
Was your baby walking down the street?
The bird that defined the sound
that birds make.
Was your baby walking down the street?
No.
I was just walking down my own
driveway and I heard tweet.
I said, sweetie, listen to that.
It's the bird.
It's the tweet bird.
They decided,
what's the sound that birds make,
generically speaking?
And somebody said, oh, they say tweet, tweet.
They Twitter.
The swallow Twitters.
This is the bird that defined what the default
generic bird sound is.
And I heard it with my own ears.
It said tweet.
And smaller foolers mucking melody.
Distinctly.
As if it's the spoilage.
Tweet.
I want to meet the dog that actually says bark.
I've met that dog once.
In Ripley's Believe It or Not,
there was a dog,
and I don't know whether I believed it,
who said, I want some.
I want some.
Supposedly.
I can believe that.
That's no problem for me to believe.
I can either, but that's all my dog says.
He just doesn't enunciate.
It's so easy to believe that.
My dog would say it, but he just hasn't really gotten there yet.
But he does go,
Well, that's part of it.
At least he's attempting to make communication with a sound.
I might even have a little video of him doing that.
Oh, well, make sure he watches the video
so he gets drawn into the loop.
I have a whole 15-minute album of my pit bull, Claudia,
going, I can't imitate it.
It's not a human or canine sound.
Well, one that expresses that.
I'll have to just cut to a sample here, now.
There.
I don't know.
Oh, well, will you look at that.
Yes, you can teach an old dog new tricks, according to Mr. Ivan Stain.
Is that a hint?
David Heights.
Here you see him frisking and frolicking with his two obedient pet dogs.
Yes, it's a great day to be out, as these frisky fellows can show.
Time to smell the trees and to try to dig under the fence.
To try to burrow out of the yard so they can run away and never return.
That's horrible.
Well, that's what I...
That's Aspen.
Oh, it's pretty loud.
I thought it was your voice.
I thought you were uncannily doing a really good dog bark.
I couldn't see your mouth.
Huh?
Uh, Wiley Philodrum.
It was.
You fooled again.
But it wasn't Philo.
Well, it was caused by Philo.
These events were set in magnum motion by Philo.
What?
And now we're settling in to our new roles here.
Putting on the dog a little bit.
Are you going to take a break or are you going to do a show?
Yeah, we're going to take a break.
Okay, this is official.
We're going to continue to play the effect of the faithful hound.
Look at the way the audience responds to that news.
They're applauding.
They're so happy we're taking a break.
They're cheering.
Yes, they're...
I guess they must have really liked our show.
Waving and the subgenius beanies are flashing in the sunshine.
And I'm amazing.
Yeah, you take it.
Okay, friends on the internet, where I can flog our swag legally.
If you want to help yourself and the Church of the Subgenius
and get a pretty cool package with like 25 different nifty things in it,
like pins and bumper stickers,
and a real preacher card,
You need to go to subgenius.com and click to become a minister.
You'll see photos and a list of all the stuff you get
and you really do get to go to the Scrubgenius forum.
Which is members only and where we talk in ways that people don't talk on Facebook.
Much, much smarter ways ironically enough.
Isn't that funny?
We also have things like T-shirts and damn near everything.
you can think of with Bob's face on it.
That and a huge selection of other subgenius graphics.
And we sell several very weird DVDs and CDs of the Bob songs
and old MP3 stashes of this show.
And best of all, from our main online store,
you can buy the Book of the Subgenius,
which is by far the greatest thing we've ever done.
It's an actual Simon & Schuster book,
22 bucks, in print for over 30 years.
And every copy that we send out is signed by yours truly.
For that matter, your address on the puffy envelope
is handwritten by me also.
Keep my fingers nimble.
That's subgenius.com.
And remember, it's only money.