For men on the go, it's not what's in the pipe, it's the pipe itself.
The Bob Dobbs Classic Meerschaum, hand-carved by the finest craftsmen in Malaysia.
This and other fine Bob Dobbs smoking accessories cast a spell on the room for the discriminating smoker.
Bob Dobbs pipes never go out of style.
Available at Kmart, Walmart, Target, and Hypermart.
Oh, too much church now.
Praise the Lord.
And welcome to the subjealous radio ministry.
Yeah.
Now, before we really get going with this sermon here, I'd like you all to share something.
This is something we've done.
We've been in Texas and Arkansas for many years.
It's just to kind of make people understand the solemnity, the profundity of the whole thing.
Lower your heads and we'll share a sacred moment of noise.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
People, people, people.
All right.
Yeah, here we go.
I see some people that are in there.
These people have slack.
The sound.
The sound itself.
It has a stink to it.
It's bad.
Who's going to drive that greyhound, children?
Greyhound.
Sonic and Sonic are coming to the middle.
For the sake of Christ.
The floor was dry, 55.
Oh, I'm by the bridge, educated.
Water故-
They're hitching a ride to the Holy Nation.
There's no smoking here, or thrashing over armor.
A soldier rows and down in a taką oito.
Thank you.
I dare you to kill me.
This is the mark.
You can always tell it's going to be a Bob
righteous revival when there's technical
problems and headaches.
And when there's
always a
normal group and not normal
group.
the potheads always seem to show up wherever the subgeniuses do.
As a matter of fact, I went in the restroom to make sure my fly was up,
which is the most important part of any public preaching, by the way.
And somebody in there said,
Hey, Reverend Stang, you want to blow one before the show?
I said, man, Bob is the only drug.
That's the only drug. You can't come down from Bob.
I just say no.
Just say no.
That's it.
Ah, yes, dear friend.
Praise Bob! Praise Bob! Praise Bob!
All right, I can see we got the spirit.
The spirit is moving tonight.
All right.
This is the subgenius radio ministry hour of slack.
Spreading the seed word of KR.
Bob Dobbs.
High Epoch of the Church of the Subgenius.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Wow.
Ha .
Proudly crowd, we strangely tripping and tripping.
Tonight, the primary source is that this is going to be a big
day.
These players have совершенно naturallyеровtraining.
Ha, Ha, Ha.
Let's see if he's remembering how to control himself through
Well here we are at Columbia University's Halloween Spook House.
I recognize your voice man.
Hello.
You are the radio guy.
Yeah.
Dude he's the radio guy.
I heard about him.
I've read the book.
That would be you.
I've read that book.
I'm kind of one of the.
Okay wait you gotta explain something.
You know what.
Yeah I got some.
I got on the senior 21st floor.
I'm gonna send him an opinion.
Then you're still peeing in the eyes of Bob.
That's why you gotta keep reading.
You gotta keep reading that book because those mudflats are gonna be angry.
Well anyway as I was saying some people think the church is like some sign of the end times.
The mockers that will come at the end times and those people should be damn glad we're
helping to fulfill biblical prophecy.
To us who've been with the church a long time it's a mystery.
We don't know what the hell this thing's gonna turn into.
If we did it'd be fantastic.
It'd be boring to us.
It founded, the church actually was founded in 1953 by that man J.R.
Bob Dobbs.
Hey Bob.
Bob founded his church when he discovered that there was a conspiracy, a conspiracy
of normals robbing away the slack of the true subgeniuses as opposed to human beings.
Mere fumes as we call them.
It's sort of a do it yourself.
Mere self religion.
Bob founded his church not on a rock but rather on sort of a shifty, shifting sandy beach
of hypocrisy.
Every church must have its fair measure of hypocrisy and certainly we've got more, we
dole out more of it than anybody else.
Like I said it's a non-organization for non-joiners which makes it a little bit difficult to raise
funds at times.
But the point of it is that all subgeniuses, people say well what the hell is that?
What the hell is a subgenius?
There's no definition.
They're all different.
That's what it means.
There is no typical subgenius.
If any two are alike one must die.
The only thing that the subgeniuses have in common is that they have nothing in common
with the conspiracy.
What we're trying to do is tempt sinners away from the devil.
Because Bob is a better tempter than the devil.
However, what they, where they're going.
Where they go after that it's up to them.
The subgeniuses believe in the God that doesn't want you to believe in it.
And our, one of our missions, we're, the headquarters is in Dallas, Texas, what they often call
the buckle on the Bible belt.
What we try to do is unbuckle the Bible belt so that its pants may drop and it may gaze
unflinching upon its own private design.
It's a wonderful thing.
It's a war, dear friends.
It's a war against the normals.
And we're just the regular kind of mutants we're talking about here.
These are more like the monsters, the monster type of mutants.
It's the humans versus the subgeniuses.
And the ironic thing is in the early days of the church, 80 million years ago in fabled
Atlantis, we helped to design the humans.
Probably our biggest mistake.
So.
Friends, as I said, you know, the fact that Chester, Jesus smoked Chesterfield's, even
though they didn't exist 2000 years ago, it's an example of our faith.
You don't use your mind to think about your religion.
You just feel it.
You feel it in your heart.
Bob sold it.
I smoked it.
That settles it.
It's a question of faith.
This is like the sorrow of world religions.
Putting those two C's on both cheeks.
the bloody marks on the beefy seat of the conspiracy.
It's like the Robin Hood of world religions,
robbing from the lost, who were mostly thieves to begin with,
and giving to the saved.
And if you, my friend, can make it,
can buy this book of the subgenius,
that videotape on sale for only $30 tonight,
if you can make it to the jungle encampment in Dobstown, Malaysia,
if you can survive the acubating, the excrementation,
the pirate flatulation, and the head-launchings, my friend,
you will be a weapon for Bob,
a weapon for J.R. Bob Dobbs,
a minister of Bob, praying for slack!
You and your subgenius fools shall never defeat me, Bob Dobbs.
Oh, no? Then have a taste of my stark fist of removal, Dr. Conspiracy.
Neegy's henchmen won't get any slack
when they face Bobco's new Bob Dobbs action figure
with flying rocket fists,
flamethrower pipe,
and magic briefcase.
Too much is always better than not enough
when you collect the subgenius universe.
Bobmobile not included.
Batteries and some assembly required.
Action figure sold separately from Bobco.
I am a subgenius!
And by that threat you would touch what falls to scrap!
You are a man!
My power wasn't given to me in exchange for prayer or meditation.
I paid for it in cold, hard American dollars.
Salvation you get for free is worth just that.
Doesn't you, queer?
Of course, your money ain't worth jack anyway.
The conspiracy sees to that,
but a very important element of your soul
adheres to those otherwise worthless greenbacks
that Bob needs.
Bob needs a job.
In order to pursue his plan for world domination.
I say, Bob guides my head in all things
and pays me off in pure slack!
So I say to you whips, you fools, you dupes, you pigs,
give me your money!
You own the end of the future!
The future offers you naught but destruction!
You know what I mean?
I mean...
I!
I dare you to kill me!
I need to be, I mean, I'm one of the good guys!
My cards shall prevail!
Let out the crazy man inside you, he knows what's what!
Smile when you call me a fanatic!
Oh, you say, me!
Me!
Crying me!
Over man!
You think I'm dumb, but you are blind to the conspiracy that runs your life!
And you have your geniuses running things for you
and you think they're gonna make things safe and simple!
And I'm gonna make things safe and simple and easy for me!
And the entire sub-demon's rich!
Even if it means wiping out your sick society in total!
With no more sentiment that involves swatting the blind!
All right!
I'm gonna make you all just say, we might survive the end times!
You know why?
Because I am!
I am!
A sub-D!
I say, all you blow-dried, white-wired, sippin', designer, jean-clad, French film watchin',
walkin', totin', hip-wimps, a few house-coated, inquirer, riddin', trailer and temp, mall-shoppin',
hair-curl, motorheads, cock-holsters, all you dupes!
Stop corporate big money!
Oil, explore, tree-killin', land-raping, food-freezin', desk-warmin', tryin'-natterin'!
The establishmentarian vote!
Huntin', backstabbin', poverty-spreadin', bomb-wieldin', meringue-headin', pencil-neck, eraser-headed,
politicals!
Kill the conspiracy!
Kill them and eat them!
Kill them and eat them and f*** their wives!
Who do you think you are?
What do you think you're doin'?
Do you think you got it good?
Well dispose of those illusions!
Dispose of them all right now!
Because on July 5th, 1998 at 7.30 in the morning, you shall be judged!
Calculating alien races!
I'm your own!
If you don't want to fight, you won't escape their scrutiny!
You will fight!
Well we will party!
Bottle of Thunderbird, I'm gonna get down and do it right here, nasty and dirty!
You know why, daddy?
You know why?
Cause...
Now some of you Christians out here may be getting a little upset at what I'm saying,
but I'd like to remind you that the founder of your religion was not quite so squeamish
as some of you!
Yeah!
Ogre King!
Billy King!
Bit ofug houses get smacked!
You brats picking always get heла took some old which again, not up we shall cut off.
You bring in lesser surprise and raise the Turbo SP prosecutors there will bite you cheap!
Trollora Monster!
What better word thatrove others thus can give a big war if those robots are so spare!
Farewell you smoothies!
O equal Fnumbered Raid cœury!
As if you are auve ha, hunted the
Hey hey Cidreiro your buddy P Micro you are Software.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
This is your host and good prayer partner, Reverend Ivan Stang.
And the amazing rant that you heard just a little while ago
was a heavily censored version of Brother Cleve Duncan's testimonial
with background sampled music by huge,
huge voodoo.
More on that in a minute.
I'm really sorry about having to put cuts in that rant
where the taboo verbal expressions were excised.
You may or may not have noticed it.
But, you know, until the grudish, word-fearing conspiracy is defeated,
well, you know, we're not allowed to play certain words.
Because of the assumption in some quarters
that some words can actually harm you.
More than the images of rape and violence
shown pretty much all the time on television.
Uh...
Someday these things will change under Bob.
Now...
Almost all of the rest of this show
was recorded this weekend.
It's almost all material recorded this last weekend.
Last weekend.
In New York and New Jersey.
By myself, Reverend Ivan Stang,
and especially the Reverend Dr. D.K. Jones,
as well as his friend, Reverend Bruce Grant.
Before, during, and after,
a subgenius revolted,
a revival at Columbia University.
D.K. Jones, uh...
is a subgenius musician you'll be most familiar with.
I guess from his score for the subgenius video, Arise.
And, in fact, the music that'll be coming up
and that you've heard some of already,
the stuff with preachers,
sampled bits of preachers over it,
is by Bruce Grant and D.K. Jones,
going under the name of Huge Voodoo.
The more linear instrumental background music,
such as the stuff behind us right now,
is by D.K. Jones and myself,
believe it or not,
but mostly D.K. Jones.
I would like to thank
all of those who helped support the station
with their pledges
last couple of weeks,
and especially,
to those who helped with the pledge drive,
such as Reverend Willa Dobbs,
and the good Pope S. Cecilia,
and the bad Reverend Trickster Shaman.
Praise Bob, dear friends.
Stay tuned, and, uh...
you'll eventually hear the post office box number
to write to for information regarding
this mighty church of the subgenius.
This radio voice program,
you're now hearing the subgenius radio ministry,
Hour of Slack.
Praise old Bobby.
Bob?
Um, do you think I could have more of them,
kind of,
and I want you to play some Pills.
You don't want to remembered,
he was trying to put you on that desired path,
You don't need no cocaine.
With hip hop or Jesus,
it enjoys you, okay?
They warned me, but I didn't listen.
I went ahead and tried the frappy.
They said, just one time, it won't hurt you.
But they lied to me.
So that's our background track, huh?
Yeah.
Sir Valpert at 16.
This is soundtrack for Cleve walking home,
light it.
The lonely Cleve walking home,
light it now.
He's had, you might say, one too many.
And suddenly, he ran into the brick wall.
Oh, my head.
What happened?
Where am I?
The last thing I remember, I was trying my first hit of frog.
Oh, what has it done to me?
I never should have joined that church.
It was...
There's only one thing left to do.
I must kill Bob.
Yes, that's the answer.
It is my duty to kill Bob.
Oh, my God.
Harvest what you can and what remains because
tomorrow you'll be empty and alone.
I feel like I'm doing this for nothing
Don't have a house campaign to rent
Somebody, would you believe it?
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
You weren't bleeding your head on a Thursday.
Why was you wearing them big green straps?
You know you should not do that, Benny.
Take it easy, Doug.
Doug?
Doug, I'm gonna call a doctor.
Doug.
Doug, there's something I want you to know.
You were the best assignment I ever had.
You wouldn't shoot me, would you, Doug?
After all we've been through.
If things have gone wrong, I'm talking to myself,
and you've got a wet towel wrapped around your head.
No, no, I'm sorry, Bob. We didn't mean it.
We didn't mean it to...
We won't call you anymore, Bob. Please don't call me that.
Don't.
No, Bob. Don't do it, please.
Once that bomb comes in here, Bob,
I already filled up my will.
Excuse me.
I'm gonna call the little one.
Niggy.
Bob, frog Bob.
Where in the world can Niggy be?
Niggy.
Where is to, Niggy?
Where is to?
I know you are there, Niggy.
You're not going to get me this time, Niggy.
Because I have the gun.
And the diamonds.
And the map.
And the documents.
And I have the device.
Yes, I have the device.
And you are foiled finally, Niggy.
Niggy?
Where did you go?
Where did you go, Niggy?
You can't fool me this time, Niggy.
I signed the papers already.
You can't.
What?
No, what is this?
The tapes.
The blank.
The documents, they've fallen to dust.
The negatives.
What about the negatives?
What, they're gone.
They're gone.
I had the negatives.
I had the device.
I had the girl.
The gun.
The map.
But, but, but, Niggy has them now.
I should have told you, Niggy.
I should have listened in the temples of the old ones when they told me.
They told me that for every Bob particle, there must always be a, a NIGGY PARTICLE.
Why didn't I listen?
Oh, oh, the, the pain.
To think, I could have had it all.
I could have had everything, but, but, Niggy has it now.
Uh-huh.
You can go to Dotson Town and get the formal training for coming over, man.
I skirted him.
In Malaysia?
Sure.
I skirted the formal training.
I sort of came in and it all happened.
Did you go to Malaysia?
Oh, man, I laid the first cornerstone.
It was a human skull.
A human skull, not a subgenius skull.
Have you ever seen Have a Nice Day?
It was spelled out in the skull of a normal human.
Get right back.
It's sweet.
It's kind of neat.
Or save the earth spelled out in the chopped off arms of a Peruvian peasant.
It's a joyful play.
Yeah.
It's so neat.
It's like the new age.
Yeah.
Ray.
What are you?
Shh.
It's all right.
It's okay.
I'm all right.
I got it.
Ow!
Damn.
Don't let her go!
She's got to make a move.
Where'd she go?
Here, here, here.
Here, here.
Let's get you.
Keep back.
Don't care.
Grab her, man.
We're going to lose her.
Damn it.
Keep back I'll grab her for you.
Get back.
We'll show you.
Stop.
There.
Thank god its working.
Oh, there we go.
I'm the king of the animals.
Wait.
No, you don't.
It's OK.
You're going to be all right now.
Shh.
Be.
It's going to be OK.
It's all right.
You're going to be OK.
No.
Shh.
Oh, yeah.
You know, there was this woman in line ahead of me at the post office this morning.
She was wearing a new Connie Dobbs perfume, you know.
And that reminded me of you.
And.
Oh.
And I don't know if it's too late now, but our search has already begun.
I, I, I don't think I can control this time of the, of the, of the time.
I, I, I, I don't know.
The light is always on
I'm the king of the world
I hold the control
The world is my own
I'm the king of the world
Where is our lucky groom and poor pathetic bride?
And poor martyred bride?
Let's see, I guess if y'all would see Brandy and Glenn.
If y'all could stand.
Yeah, right there.
Wait, wait, we gotta get...
Woo!
I'm more used to preaching in tents.
Ah, yes.
Hey, if Reverend Sun Yung Moon can marry thousands of people who've never even met,
then a Church of the Subgenius short-duration marriage could be the answer.
Yeah, as a matter of fact, this is one thing you can do as a subgenius minister.
You can do legal weddings.
You can also do the short-duration marriages.
This certificate here produced by Reverend Bucknaken in Dallas
can come in very handy.
Because a short-duration marriage can last for an hour, a night, a week, a year, whatever.
And the divorces are cheap.
They come with the certificate.
All right.
Anybody else want to get married tonight?
Step right up, get your holy short-duration marriage certificate here.
Test your mettle and win the little lady a rubber Snoopy doll.
Guaranteed, friends, to absolve and sanctify all otherwise illicit couplings.
Free short-duration divorce if you're not completely satisfied.
All right, now you two stand together and face me.
Ooh, I like that.
All right.
Let's be solid now here.
Do you, Glenn, take, uh, swear to tell the truth, the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth, and tell the Snoopy Bob?
I do.
Do you, Brandy, swear to tell the truth, the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth, and the Snoopy Bob?
Yeah.
All right, good.
Okay, now, how long do you wish for this period of sanctified couplings to last?
One year.
One year?
Oh, yeah, that's right.
You told me that.
One year.
Me.
Uh, you sure?
Yeah.
All right.
Oh, yes.
Dearly beloveds,
we are gathered here today in the presence of J.R. Bob Dobbs and, uh,
insert other deity names here, any, any other deities,
uh, to join this man, Glenn, and this woman, Brandy,
in the bondage of holy matrimony, for better or for worse, but not for long.
Do you feel the spirit?
Then put your hands on each other.
If there are any here who feel this man and this woman should not be joined temporarily,
just hold your peace, because we don't want to hear about it.
Hold tight.
Hold tight now.
Oh, lovely.
Lovely comments.
Do you, Glenn, take this woman, Brandy, to be your lawful wedded wife and short-duration
subgenius matrimonial, to have and to hold for richer or poorer in sickness and kinkiness
for the next year?
Say, say, I do.
I do.
Do you, uh, Brandy, take this woman, Brandy, to be your lawful wedded wife and short-duration
subgenius matrimonial, to have and to hold for richer or poorer in sickness and kinkiness
for the next year?
Say, I do.
I do.
Shake on it.
And say, it's a deal.
Woo!
Now, get out.
Oh, we're not over.
We're not finished yet.
We got a really important part, the symbolic part's coming up.
Get out the ring.
You do have a ring.
The best man.
The best man here in seven years.
Give the hands to the best man.
All right, um, we take this ring, give that to, uh, to Glenn, and Glenn, you, uh, and she
inserts, uh, her finger into the hole.
We take this, we take this ring as a holy symbol of the estate of marriage as well as
of the pole going deep into the hole repeatedly, obviously.
By the authority invested in me by J.R. Bob Dobbs in defiance of the laws of the state
and of nature, I pronounce you man and wife of the state.
You are now officially married for the next one year.
You must, you must now kiss each other right in front of all these people.
Praise Bob!
This is so, yeah.
Take it off.
Yay, yay, yay.
Praise Bob, praise Bob.
Praise Bob, praise Bob, praise Bob, praise Bob, praise Bob.
You are now duly authorized and excused for sexual couplings of any perverse and unspeakable
couple.
for a period of one year.
Ashes to ashes, dust to dust,
it is done, amen, and a-women.
Praise God!
The Philippian ball garages
of rock and roll music
is obviously a meaning
by which the white man
is driven to the level
with a nickname.
The Philippian ball garages
of rock and roll music
is obviously a meaning
The Philippian ball garages
The evil feeling that you feel
when you sing.
Why I believe that
is because I know how to beat.
The evil feeling that you feel
when you sing.
And all the last positions
you get into, the beats.
Well, if you talk to
the average teenager of today
and you ask them what it is
about rock and roll music
that they like,
if they're playing bad mites,
it's so simple.
If you talk to the average
teenager of today,
Drops his and call his name.
You've all put theedor
If you talk
to the average
teenager of today.
teenager of today
a beat, a beat, a beat,
a beat, a beat, a beat.
The evil feeling that you feel
Why I believe that is because I know how it feels
In the name of Jesus
Go!
Make my words
The devils of hell
I believe that is because I know how it feels
In the name of Jesus
I know what it does to you
I know the evil feeling that you feel in the name of Jesus
I know the lost position that you get into
In the feet
Well, if you talk to the average theater of today
And you ask them what it is about rock and roll music that they like
The first thing they'll say
Is the beat, the beat, the beat
Go!
The beat, the beat, the beat
Make my words
The demons are the righteousness of God
The evil feeling that you feel is sacred
Now I want you to hear it
Come out, come out of this place
Come out of this place
Come out of that place
Come out, come out, come out
In the name of Jesus
It is the beginning
We want your body
We want your teleport should have been
The guy's party
The open the door
It is the beginning
Beweep
We want the truth
Beweep, picture the fighting
The beat, the beat, the beat, the beat, the beat.
The evil feeling.
The beat, the beat, the beat.
Why I believe that is because I know.
Sub-genius hell.
It's a cold, cold kind of hell.
Cold in here.
Wish I could light this here pipe.
They gave me all the frappy in the world.
And it's too cold to light this pipe.
Oh, Bob, where are you now?
Why did you leave me in the hands of me?
However, Bob will offer you eternal salvation or triple your money back.
Which unfortunately gives some the image in their minds of,
Bob.
Bob standing at the gates of hell handing out $60 checks.
Well, that's real funny.
I hope you boys are having a good time.
I bet you thought this old church thing of yours was going to be big, big fun, big barrel of laughs.
Oh, yeah.
I bet you thought you were going to be some kind of high school lawyer with that Bob fellow of yours.
Well, you're looking at a pretty damn long eternity.
Oh, by the way, here's that triple your money back.
That's what?
$60.
One for you, Smith.
One for you, Jones.
And don't let this deter you from doing business with us again.
Yeah.
You're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
For free information on Bob Dobbs and the Church of the Subgenius, send a self-addressed stamped envelope to...
Got your pencil ready?
Bob, Post Office Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
That's Bob, P.O. Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Please check out subgenius.com.
Stay tuned and praise Bob.
Well, Dennis locked me in this little box.
I can't feel anything.
I can't see anything.
It's totally black.
I have no sensation in my hands.
I don't know if I'm moving or what.
I'm just in this little box.
He said I could talk to you.
He said you'd know what to do if you wanted to help me.
Oh, good.
Happy Peter Wellman.
I promise I'll pay you all the royalties that I didn't tell you about.
And whatever you want.
I mean, anything.
Tevis.
You can have Tevis.
Just get me out of this box, Wellman.
Please don't.
No.
Don't believe what Paul told you.
It's all a lie.
Whatever I did, I am sorry.
I'm sorry.
I let you out of the box, Wellman.
I can't.
This is a bad show, Wellman.
This is a real bad show.
She says she'd almost rather see me in Tevis than in nothing at all.
Bright, perky, almost psychedelic.
The Tevis line of fine men's undergarments.
Underwear you'll never change.
Sweet talk me all you want, but you'll never get me out of my Tevis.
And if you think that was bad, friends, you should be glad you didn't hear what was originally
on the end of this show, which was some music by DK Jones and myself, which unfortunately
had myself in it.
So to close out, let's go to some modern.
Goodyear pimps.
From the pimps.org.
The Pimps.org.
They'll get you out of the jail, man, crickets, come on.
They'll open the bag, next to the bus, cheerleader, and pound.
They were jumping around, they don't like that cricket sound.
People freaking the pound, I'll get those bitches out, without a doubt.
That's when I heard the principal shout, hey, crickets, what you talking about?
Hey, crickets, hey, crickets.
They'll get you out of the jail, man, crickets, come on.
So if you're in a situation that you need to get up,
unleash your crickets and spite them around.
They'll create a distraction, and you can finally slip away.
Tell me one, one, who unleashed those crickets?
They'll get you out of the jail, man, crickets, what you talking about?
They'll get you out of the jail, man, crickets, come on.
They'll get you out of the jail, man, crickets, come on, crickets, come on.