From PR News in Washington, I'm king of at least six people, most of them security guards.
I'm farting from upstate New York to Maine.
And the mayor of Boston staggers home.
Heavy wet farts.
That's been a benefit.
Farts today.
On Wall Street at this hour, 152.
The White House says that this is PR News from Washington.
The popular social networking internet website PR News has reached agreement with more than
145 sexual predators to protect $20 billion worth of weapons.
An Israeli official is supposed to fly within 125 miles of PR News in Washington.
PR comes from low-income women's and children's and families.org.
In a few generations, their legs will grow slim, their bodies thin, their tusks longer.
Goodbye.
The baby!
Finish.
Title two, directions four, inward filthy lusts.
Direction one, drink wine or strong drink.
It is better for you than beer.
Direction two, think of tempting filthy objects.
Number three, eat windy meats.
Number four, copiously evacuate.
And if you do not, you perish.
Bite.
Number five, eat maggots.
Direction six, prepare to sodomize for their filthy lusts.
Direction seven, be corrupted with money nor perverted by flattery.
Direction eight, cause that pernicious deliriation in the brain.
Direction nine, produce temptations to lust.
Direction ten, let your apparel be suited to your disease.
Direction eleven, don't drink.
Don't think what your admired carcass will be when it is laying a few days in the grave.
Direction twelve, go back when you see the bait.
Beaver.
Starring, starring Barbara Beaver.
But dad.
You know, Beaver, your mother and I were very...
Ah, that you deliberately...
Nah.
Yes, sir.
Well, Wally, I, uh...
I had a clop you won.
Ah, Wally, I don't think...
I thought I told you to shut up.
Yeah, well, uh, I'll just...
I don't know.
Okay.
Winnie the Pooh finds tail.
And then he put his head down and looked between his front legs.
I, Winnie the Pooh, will find tail food.
So Winnie the Pooh went off to find tail.
To the hundred acre wood.
L-O-L.
Pooh looked at the knocker and...
Large somethings.
Pulled the knockers.
Ow!
The knockers.
Pooh looked at the bush.
Nailed it.
So happily.
Ow!
Winnie the Pooh came over all funny.
Pooh found tail.
I said Pooh.
I found tail.
I want scarlet sin and the moral leper.
People think of full and complete sexual intercourse and every form of sexual deed
and think of fornication between a man and a broad or not.
Thou shalt fornicate in...
Body and behavior.
Or better, thou shalt engage in any sexual activity whatsoever.
And of course, let each wife sexually submit to very shameful, awkward, perverted, irremediable,
extended, intense sexual activity.
Utilizing the sexual parts in a sexual manner in total permanent sexual subjection to,
all forms of perverted sexual urges in our minds.
And of course, engage in perverted sexual perversions.
But, what one has to do is to plead with God to give one that gift of total sexual action.
Because otherwise, we need to get pornography to look at the strange woman and be seen her underwear.
As far as I'm concerned...
You can go too.
Go back to Tony's and that woman you were mooning.
Oh, knock it off, will you?
Now, you pulled a boner tonight and you know it.
Why?
My husband.
Huh.
inside out you associate with women don't have personal preparation financialick
Wow.
and
Anita
N
Thank you.
with our own organs as we will.
Well, all things bright and mutable.
So that would be like getting to fifth base
if someone were to palpate your pancreas.
If you have more than one sexual organ,
you can imagine...
That's like going all the way, but then some.
Oh.
I know what first base is, second base, third base.
In theory, I know what these things are.
And a home run.
Well, theoretically.
But pancreatic palpation would be...
the fifth base, I guess.
Beyond all the way and through to the other side.
Through, break on through, man.
See, I knew you were going to get it,
but think about your liver and your spleen.
And the myopic fund you can have reacting in such a way.
I mean, if you had one, you don't have much spleen.
Except I noticed when you bit my leg on the way here.
But outside of that, you see, not a spleenless man, but...
Not spleenless, but...
Not heavily spleen.
Yeah, heavily spleen.
We could say.
I've known a lot of people, I just call them heavenly...
Heavenly, hell no.
Heavily spleen.
Now, friends, while I'm still thinking about the news of the cult...
It's a hands away from it.
You know, X Day's coming up, the end of the world.
Once again.
On July 5th, the planet will be destroyed at 7 a.m.
How many times is it going to end?
And if not, we'll have more, get more practice for that moment.
Because as the...
Yay!
The lesson is, you don't know what day X Day.
The rupture could be any day.
Any second now.
Any moment.
Are you ready?
Lesson one?
There is no lesson.
Anyway, you can...
So we're getting ready.
We're getting all geared up for our X Day drill in Sherman, New York, later on in the summer.
And I got so excited about it because I put up a pictorial on the Subgenius website,
which you can look at if you're interested.
And it's free.
It's a...
Also, just look at our...
If you look at our Vips page, then scroll down to the X Day part and you can't miss it.
It says, the X Days of your pictorial, adults only.
And it is in fact, the naked adults only pictures of our grandparents at X Days in the past.
Quite indeed.
It's...
They're really...
It's pictures from X Days of the 30s, the 20s even, the 30s and 40s.
So it's kind of old fashioned.
It's old fashioned.
But it's sexy.
Nice sepia tone.
Because even the subgeniuses of yore, well, if they hadn't been sexy, we wouldn't be here.
Now, would we?
I like the funny writing on the back of it.
Dearest mom and dad, I bet you'd have thought you'd never see me this way.
Signed your daughter Erna.
Erna.
What was it?
Erstwhile?
No, that was the guy.
Anyway, I love when they write off these little diaphragms to each other in Uniclaw language.
And they have before.
Well, you can't see those on these website pictures.
Because you can't flip the picture over and look at the handwriting on the back of the snapshot.
But I scanned all those old photos that your folks took at X Days and Prince of...
Everybody's, you know.
There's some...
And it's a lot of...
My great-grandpa looked great in like a hat and a pipe and nothing else.
That's right.
I couldn't believe that an old guy that I look at as a very old guy could actually be strutting around there like...
People wear more clothes there now.
Hardly anybody goes there.
Nobody goes completely nude at X Day.
Well, that's the nature of the world.
Everyone wears more clothes at all times because clothes are...
It's not the nature of naturists.
No, certainly not.
But who follows their followings?
Those are droppings.
You know what I'm saying?
That's how you find Bob.
You follow the droppings.
Follow the droppings.
And the cotter pins.
Yeah.
And the jello.
People forget.
You said before they were hand grenade cotter pins, not jello.
What else have we got coming up that I can announce because I'm not getting paid for it?
Hamburg Devival.
We're not going to be there, but if you friends happen to be in Hamburg, Germany on May 3rd, just follow the...
Look for the smoke and the flames and that's where the big Devival will be with all the Euro subs, which includes several American subs who can't go home to America.
Can you imagine?
We've stooped so low that our droppings won't even allow our alien friends to return to their homelands.
It makes you want to seep and cry like a tiny...
My droppings aren't stopping anybody from...
From doing anything.
I don't think.
Oh, I didn't mean in the sub-natural, I meant in the over-gross, or the uber-gross, I guess you would call it.
The uber-grossian-mentioner.
Speaking of uber-gross, what else?
Actually, people who are interested in uber-gross subgenius events may want to just look at subgenius.com and look at the news page because there are things coming up that we can't tell you about.
You understand?
That's how good they are.
We're not allowed to...
Are we allowed to tell about the Princess We Are Doe's band singing at the Hessler Street Fair this year?
That's for free, yes.
Yeah.
Revel will be at...
Ever revel-read, hopefully.
May 17th, the Hester Street Fair.
Hessler, even.
We can't tell you anything that does us any good.
That's the law.
But we're going to...
It's not a subgenius law, that's the human law.
No subgenius can do anything it wants.
That's the law.
That's the law of the land.
That's the law as it's written in the books now.
And the Bible and the Holy Constitution.
And yet the 14th Amendment says that anything that more than one subgenius businessman does is therefore legal, becomes legal at that point.
Yet so she all be done to by thyself.
So if you're doing it by yourself, it might still be illegal.
But if two of us are doing it, then it's okay.
And what yet two businessmen do, only they do...
That law was written, it didn't say...
And it said businessmen, it did not say businesspersons.
There it is.
So, you know, it's that old double standard.
We have to take...
We can't take that at face value unless we're like a pack of two-faced liars.
We have to assume that that meant business...
You know how women used to have to call themselves men when they went to work?
And then they had to call themselves men in the afternoon?
And by the way, I'd just like to mention the fact that you forgot to plug my little thing that I'm doing at the Communist Party meeting of the Communist Party of the United States of America.
I didn't know that.
I didn't know that either.
Sure you didn't like it.
I knew you were a commie, but I didn't know that.
I've been emailing you guys all week.
I'm going to be speaking at the Grand Function with the frock fairies and sores of my comrades, my tovarishes.
Well, it's not really Russian.
We just call ourselves comrades.
We're going to be having the fish dinner...
Well, the fish luncheon afterwards.
And we're going to be having POC beer that's been in the basement for 40 years.
What's POC mean?
Pee-pee on Cleveland.
Or it used to mean Pfeiffer of Cleveland, but...
Pride of Cleveland.
Right.
I always said pride of Cleveland, but it really means pee-pee on Cleveland or poop on Cleveland.
Oh, that's just a vernacularism.
When we were childs we used to say that.
But I'm going to be speaking about the movement itself and also the fact that I think the subgeniuses, and many of them, should join me.
The commies?
Should become communist, like me.
That's like the opposite of Bob's.
Bob's like the ultimate god of capitalism.
Well, then don't you see the irony in the perfect six things?
Making money at the expense of the sucker.
Don't you see that's the succinctly perfect statement for the irony of the ironic thing?
Customer is the sucker of the world.
It is the sucker of the world, but as long as...
So why should we be interested in a bunch of commies?
Because we're all suckers.
Yeah, but some suckers are more equal than others, Dave.
And I'm one of those more equal ones.
So that means if I was going to be a commie, I'd be the commissar.
You would be dressed up in the pig suit.
I'd be the equal guy in the pig suit that got driven by a human chauffeur.
To the big barnyard in the Kremlin.
Well, I'm going to be wearing Lenin's...
I'm going to be wearing Lenin's overcoat, man.
I'm going to be talking to the mass...
I'm wearing Lenin's underwear right now.
Are you really?
My Lenin's, I call them.
Your Lenin's, Lenin's.
How long did it take you to get those things?
I guess they were real expensive on eBay or something, right?
They're so intimate.
Ah, the right state.
What's this noise in the background?
That's the rural war room.
It's the rural war room thing.
It's the rural war room machine.
It plays on and on and on.
You remove the crown with your thumb.
Your prehensile thumb that Bob knows.
No, not Bob.
That duh, duh knows.
That nature does not know.
That nature...
Remove your thumb from your eye.
Now stand near the door.
Move out of the door.
Move out the window.
Now flap your arms.
Flap your wings.
You can fly!
Yep.
You can fly, baby.
Just get with Bob and grow your wings.
I'm flying!
Grow the wings in your mind, man.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Bob, I'm sorry.
Bob is like a pink, glarp, normal.
He supports the conspiracy, sports class division.
He ought to be killed.
But he's a pretty nice guy for a personal savior.
I know he is.
To quote a drelloid mutant.
Get off my flight!
The late drelloid mutant.
The late, late drelloid mutant.
Oh, we're gonna be playing a song by the...
Later on in the show, we're going to be playing an ancient song that somebody found in a pile of 78s that appears to be a Church of the Subgenius Hillbilly gospel song from like the...
30s or the 20s or something.
It was on a wax record, but we'll get to that.
We can't figure out if it's an oaky or if it's actually like, you know, from West Virginia or something, man.
It's way up here.
We're trying to figure out the label.
I guess it was on the Sugarfest radio show.
Yes, we can't tell if it's an oaky or a pudding.
But I can't play that because it doesn't...
It may be a pudding.
It doesn't come up yet.
Like a pudding.
However...
Is it?
Let's just see what happens if...
It's a story.
Hold it.
Love That Bob.
Starring Bob Cumming.
You're going to look sensational in a bathing suit.
I know that.
We're swinging.
Bob didn't take this.
Bob can take better pictures.
Take, take.
Rock and roll rears its ugly head.
Bob, Bob, rock and roll, rock and roll.
You're big.
Hold it, baby.
Oh, I'd love to.
Oh, peckers.
Peckers.
Well, Bob, I just found a way to get the guitar, Bob.
Hey, swell.
Swell.
Who could he be?
Crazy.
Where can I get that kind of sausage?
Bob's rock and roll.
So Bob Bob.
No, no, please, please don't ask me to show it to you.
Guitar wizardry virtuoso.
You'll never get a girl with rock and roll.
Bob, the girl's flip.
That's so true, John.
Really, really, really.
Pop, pop, pop, pop.
Focus.
The Center for Strong Homosexual Issues.
Internet pornography.
Pornography.
Let me wallow in ignorance.
Anxiety.
I need help.
You know, you know.
But I need to do it.
Lower and lower and lower and lower.
She.
All the way down to your zitter.
And she went, and I just felt really, however that worked, in touch.
I care about dogs.
Dogs.
We do hair.
It goes both ways.
But it's all paid for with public money.
So there.
It's been fun.
Fun.
I am chip.
A chip.
Everybody.
Bye-bye.
San Francisco.
Oh, very...
The rest is rat version, rat version, rat version.
I don't like it.
Wait a minute.
No extra work.
You're in check.
What are you trying to pull, mister?
You don't think I'm telling the truth?
Don't be too long.
It gives me pleasure to...
San Francisco, I...
Oh, big story in papers.
Big trouble.
Hey, boy.
I've been very concerned.
I've been very concerned with you these past days, Victor.
What kind of dealings do you have with the director of the morgue?
Are you interested in corpses?
Oh, God, Fleets.
I shall really have to tell you the story of the inquisitive commandant.
The one at Belsam, remember?
They might believe that you want that atomic element to supply electric power.
But I...
What are you trying to say?
I don't know.
I don't know?
I have no idea.
I don't know.
Could I repeat what I just said?
Unless, of course, you could repeat it for me.
No, no, no, P.P.
Ah, do svitanya.
Shtova.
It's a nice deal.
It's...
It's a Russian bust.
It's a big deal.
I don't know.
I would like to smell my shoe.
Repeat.
Repeat in English.
I would like to smell your shoe.
I am the shoe smeller.
That's the language of God.
The pure language of the angels.
Unaffected by three rows of teeth,
the animals who speak the language of God
are known for miles and miles in the Amazon basin
for releasing loud, unctuous quantities
of good old Mother Nature's food.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
And as long as they worship,
they worship at the foot of the statue of the piped head,
they all is well in the kingdom of sweat and vigor.
Sha-la-ka-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta.
My shoe smell funny to you?
Repeat in Hintekorosh.
Sha-la-ka-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta.
The shoe is angry with me.
Sha-la-ka-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta.
Oh, my God.
Repeat.
Bob is the shoe.
Me-kip-a-lo-bo-bo Bob.
The shoe...
Kani.
Kani me-kik-kik-kik.
Kani is the high heel pi-hat-sha.
Repeat in Urdu.
Ur-ta-ta-pa-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta.
Kani.
And now in Panglossian.
Uh-oh.
Time to turn the background music up.
I don't know what to say.
Oh, look, Dave, you have to go let somebody in.
You have to go open the door.
Friends, it's just you and me listening while Dave runs the door.
Well, this unexpected invitation to...
Prince?
Oh, my God.
Maybe it's okay.
Fine.
Fine, you got no滾
Would you like to basically only do..
에
σ
Now how would youURDO them?
Now how would you like them?
Now, speaking of...
Shotzi, my little pearl.
I know that you are wearing lederhosen on your ears.
You're not supposed to notice or speak of the lederhosen.
Lederhosen are a personal part of women's attire.
And they're meant to be smelled by men with big, big hair.
And big noses.
And you know what a big nose means.
Yes.
Vegan nose hair clippers.
Does not want any other man to smell the lederhosen.
Would you like to languish in the aquarium with me for a short duration?
Does that line ever work?
Sometimes.
Yeah.
In Parfait, it is said,
Noshcap in handy, ratatal.
I knew a guy who would go into a bar and walk up to every single woman and say that to her.
And he would go,
I'm going to get slapped 30 times.
But sooner or later, he'd find one who'd go,
Yeah, baby.
Your place or mine.
Your friend went for the slaps only.
That's possible.
Highly likely in this case.
I don't know.
It was the only way he could score.
Wasn't he the one you called the two-tongued rabbit of Bob?
No, you're thinking of someone else.
That was the other guy.
He was working the percentages, man.
Now, let's...
We got this piece, this old record from...
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Actually, she didn't send the record.
She sent an MP3 that she had copied from this record.
Our friend, Reverend Samantha,
who all the regular devotional goers would know Reverend Samantha.
She used to be the only girl at the Devo shows.
And that's changed.
But she was the first.
Anyway, she sent this song.
And a letter.
I'm going to read the letter.
Reverend Samantha said,
This little musical gem, which I found lying in a pile of old dusty 78s in the attic.
Kids, that means old CDs only before CDs were invented.
They were big wax discs.
It appears to be a Depression-era Church of the Subgenius hillbilly gospel song.
Can it be?
There's no reason why it couldn't be.
Although it's...
It's rare to find something from that part of the country.
Anyway, she says,
I could just barely make out the words on the record label.
It seemed to say something like,
Look away from the pinks to the billowing pipe.
That's the title of the song.
By the Mutant Mountain Boys.
Interesting how they got away with such politically incorrect names back then.
I think it's interesting how pristine it almost is.
I mean, when you look at it, it looks like it was just cut yesterday,
and yet it is one of those, like, old OK Bluebird type of, you know, renderings there on 78 RPM.
Well, we're going to play this.
She figured out the words to it, I think, because they're really hard to hear on this old record.
And kindly printed them for us to be able to...
Yes.
Who's kindly?
Let's see.
Is that another person involved?
No, that's me.
I'm kindly.
Kindly, all right.
She said, you know this...
This just might be the only existing copy in the world,
so here I am now spreading it like a virus.
I'm going to play it now, and the singers will sing along.
Look away from the pinks to the billowing pipe.
From your life of work and toil, look away.
There's a hole in your soul that's burning you alive.
We're slacked and we'll never decay.
Look away.
Send your chariot.
For eternal sleep.
From the pinks to the billowing pipe.
Billowing pipe.
Look away.
For the morning past.
From the pinks to the billowing pipe.
Billowing pipe.
I saw a vision above.
Look away.
I can walk again.
Of course there's nothing really wrong with my legs
and a good old 10 ton crusher wouldn't care.
I need my body to be ripped off of the stones I put in life.
Self-responsibilities getting harder to bear
in your blind walk of life.
Solstice.
There's a hypnotic man who is beckoning from
with his disembodied head,
always there to stay,
Look away, look away
From the pain to the glowing heart
I can almost see again
I can almost walk again
I can almost hear again
I can almost, I can almost
If your conflicts with normals
Bring struggles and strife
Live onward your rantings ensue
Look away from the pain to the glowing pipe
It's raining in dives down for you
Look away, look away
From the pain to the glowing, glowing pipe
It's a beautiful, beautiful
Thank you, Reverend Samantha, for finding that.
And all the voracious loving, I must say, I've never met you,
but it seems to me if your knees were as knobby as your head,
I'd be in love once again.
Her knees are as knobby as her head, if I remember correctly.
They are not.
Her knees are perfectly sleek and beautiful.
Well, how about all these polygamists lately?
Back in Stane County, Texas, they've been running the polygamists.
They're hydrocephalic down there, and there's more than one of them, I guess,
and they're all married to each other.
And the smallest one is only five years old.
That's right.
And Grandpappy is pushing 109, but believe me,
he can still be an indirect old thumb on it.
You're not kidding.
I'm not. I'm trying not to be anyway.
Texas is a great place for cults.
You know, even the Mormons had to move down to Texas
to do their really cultish stuff.
Had to move out of Ohio and New York.
Well, now, I've heard,
there's been food riots in the news all over the world
because there's been an 83% price rise over the last three years
in foodstuffs in general for the entire planet.
Yeah, I thought it was 40, and I guess it was 40 in one year.
I thought it was 40% over three years.
That's right.
And that even includes us Merkins paying more,
and pretty soon everybody's going to be dead.
You mean you've been eating your Merkins?
You're so hungry you're eating a Merkin?
We've been driven to that.
There were times when we were so wroth.
I remember Mom and Dad were so,
they not only took in laundry and other children's ducks and stuff like that,
they also played with others' behavior models
just to survive, to get by the next day.
They ate chest Merkins, man.
Chest Merkin.
We had it on Thursday night with lasagna, man.
Chest Merkin, you know?
Well, they're literally friends.
There have been food riots all over the world lately.
Haiti, the Philippines, Egypt, Columbus, Dayton.
La Vie.
And you know every place is Dayton Place.
Yeah.
I say that because nobody would understand Payton Place.
The only old people know where Payton Place is.
Well, Dayton Place is where the three original alien sky choppers were regulated.
It was where they first crashed.
Yeah, they took them from Roswell, too.
And they used Roswell as a cover-up for the Dayton Place UFO crashes, saucer crashes.
Well, there was, at Wright-Patterson, remember?
Right, yes.
You said you inspected the bodies, and they argued with you about it.
Yes, it was all quite foul and disgusting.
It's weird when a corpse becomes animated right while you're arguing with it.
And yet charming somehow at the same time.
Well, you know, dead people do have a certain charm about them.
They're kind of distant.
There's been a debate lately about who do you like best,
the running, fast-moving zombies,
or the shuffling, lurching, stumbling zombies.
I'm not a big fan of the stiff zombies,
but I think it would just be too scary to have a long-legged, gazelle-type zombie just chasing you down.
And there's the hooker zombies.
That lure you in.
And the sails zombies.
Man, the speed zombies are the scary ones to me, man.
The speed zombies?
Speed zombies are the scariest of all.
Meth zombies.
Yeah.
Cochasa zombies were a big deal in Brazil when I was down there.
That was the local drink.
Cochasa zombies were real scary.
Cochasa.
Is it like, TJ, it's a sped-up beer that a native lady spit it up?
No, no.
That's a different beer.
It's made from spit.
A different beer, they call it.
Cochasa is sort of like tequila, but it's like a liquid-fluid thing that makes your brain messed up.
Yeah, it's made from potash or something.
I forget what.
Wow.
That is really, really hard to believe.
But there are zombies.
I can believe that part.
Literal.
You know, Cochasa zombies.
Those who have thoroughly deadened their brains with Cochasa.
I don't think I'm pronouncing that right.
I had one too many myself.
One too many zombies?
I came close to being, I have had a zombie.
What the hell is that?
When I was younger, when I was a young man.
Oh, you carnal, you little corny.
You have to cut their hands off because otherwise they'll scratch you and claw your eyes out and stuff.
Yeah, they have no idea of their strengths since they're just on temporal motor slabbling.
And of course they have to be nuzzled.
You have to muzzle them.
Yeah, because they want to eat your brain while you're nibbling at their ear.
And you, you know, the smell is not great.
And you don't want to do any like weird numbers.
And the bits fall off.
The bits falling off is not cool.
Yeah, call me when you guys are done with this conversation.
But can you imagine doing one of those like old sexual numbers, you know, they give them numbers and stuff like that?
Number 72.
Can you imagine doing 72 with a zombie?
What do you mean imagine?
Yeah, I can.
That's what I was getting at.
Yeah.
I'm from Texas, man.
That's not that big of a deal down there.
So, Ed Geins.
I've noticed people are kind of, kind of weak stomach up here.
They're kind of, kind of picky.
They are a body, visceral race of murderers and biters and biters.
That's us.
Ed Geins, Geins.
Praise Bob.
He led us in the way of the Texas businessman.
I thought you were going to say he led you into the desert instead of out.
And the zombie.
Yeah.
The Rogues Ouch.
Szemerov.
Szemerov and you know, the Szemerov guy.
And they never lonely hang out with you.
Oh, no.
And they never leave, right.
No, but they never listen to us or anyone in the store.
I know they have a cuvier of all the freавайas.
What's it called?
Xyzulโ aus?
I don't feel mean to like brother, you know.
UFOs? It's kind of like one of those that sprang up around a tech shop?
Now, it so happens that if you put a video camera on the mysterious lights
and another video camera at a highway about 10 miles away across the desert,
the car lights seem to dictate how the UFO lights move.
And there's kind of, some people say that it's merely a mirage situation that's always in place
so that what appears to be mysterious lights flying around in the desert
are really just headlights from several miles away on the desert
bounced by atmospheric freak.
But that's as supernatural as the damn UFOs to begin with.
Yeah, right.
So it's like, what you gonna do?
Yeah.
What are you gonna do?
There's no fractal fissuring to create an illusion of a thermoscopy.
There's no way that you can get around it like it's flaming fire and you still can't see it.
I'm sorry, I'm frothing at the neck.
It's getting messy.
And so, they all remembered.
It wasn't the first time the little lady from Brazil had her star to tell.
Things were bad everywhere.
We took her back to Sao Paulo where she hoped to meet her father, Rex Rumroy.
He was a rum runner, all right.
He brought the last big bottle of booze up from Franquas and landed in Boston last week.
Yeah.
But don't ask me.
I don't know about it.
Ask this little lady right here.
The one with the exposed skull.
I think you're still sick.
I cannot speak.
My voice, vocal cords have been removed by lonesome cowboy Dave.
I cannot speak no more.
You're still sick.
That's it.
Good girl.
Did it hurt?
I'm being paid.
I'm getting paid.
Find yourself again.
I'm not lost.
You're working yourself up into a...
Full-size nervous breakdown.
Serene, clear-eyed.
Let me take your photograph, will you?
You're still sick.
Okay, I'm sick.
The symbolism.
No.
Look, this whole thing is nothing but a hallucination.
Let me come with you.
No.
That's the end of the shaft.
No, I'd better phone the scientists.
I'll be in charge.
Petrified historic man.
But everybody will see her in her nakedness.
Nakedness.
What is time but a conception of man?
She's not an object of vivisection.
I will be in charge.
Well, we were all somewhat excited, I would say, and we still are.
How would you like to rap, rap, rap, rap, rap?
Oh.
Six, maybe seven.
This is quite common, John.
You have a fear of the future.
Is that why I scream?
You want it, yet you fear it.
Five.
Might be a winner.
I want him now.
Now, do you understand?
Get him!
Enlightenment comes more easily in the dark.
Oh, yes.
It smells funny.
Then drink your tea.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Look.
Why all the games?
Can't you just get on with it?
What do you want us to do?
We want you to praise Bob.
My friends, that's all we ask.
Well, it's actually not.
That's far from all we ask, but that's the first thing we ask is that you praise Bob.
Where did I hear that?
What are you two muttering about over there?
We're just having a little discussion about folks with brain injuries returning to the
job as full-grown zombies.
You know, at where we work, zombies come back every day and have to be rehabilitated, and
it costs the boss lots of money.
Indeed.
And that's why we think Dobbs is our answer.
Because Dobbs is not only going to get rid of those pesky monkeys, but he's also going
to kill the administration of the company as well.
In fact, no one's going to be left alive but me.
Maybe that's not Bob.
Maybe that's just my own.
You know what I'm saying?
How often do we ascribe to Bob feelings that are really just our own?
You know how it is.
You go, well, I feel like having a hamburger or ice cream cones.
I'm sure Bob would feel the same way.
He'd feel like it was okay for me to have that ice cream cone.
I'm sure he would.
And you know he would.
Yes, he would.
He's like the Lord baby Jesus, at least that way.
Too much is always better than not enough, Bob said.
He was lying, but it sounds great.
And that's all that matters in your proper religion, modern religion.
Yes, you left off the antecedent found years later.
That's the only thing that's important is the antecedent.
Maybe that's what we ran over on the way here.
Bob's antecedent?
Yes.
Remember that thing we smushed all the way that squealed?
It was before the pipe, so it might have been the pipe.
It could have been actually alive.
It could have been physically in corpus columnum.
Too much is always better than not enough, but it's almost as bad.
It's much worse.
Believe you me.
Look down here.
Ew, I don't want to look down there.
Oh, look, there's plenty of skulls being opened.
And they're putting little Bob implants in each one.
Look at those biological urges down there.
Yes, you can see them flashing on the rhythmosphat and the displays.
And of course, if you jump over here, make a little bunny jump or else you'll be electrocuted.
No, no, jump over there.
That's not a bunny rabbit.
That's an ugly baby.
That's all.
That's all it was.
Yeah, we wouldn't do that to a rabbit.
Of course not.
But a redheaded stepchild, anything goes.
Is subject to immediate electrocution.
Or is it elocution?
Hi, I'm your favorite redheaded stepchild.
And I'd just like to say in my perfect English that Bob has saved my career, whatever the hell that might mean.
Your electrifying elocution?
If only we could remember what your career was that he saved.
And who it was.
You could finally make some money off of it.
In fact, we can't find it.
He'll save your career, but he won't tell you what it is.
That's Bob for you, man.
He's a mystery god.
He's a little bit of a...
He's a conundrum wrapped in a mystery.
Deceiver.
A little bit of a coco pele child.
The blanket of cloudy weirdness around it.
They say Bob plays in mysterious ways.
They say Bob sits around in mysterious waters.
They say Bob plays with himself in strange places.
They say Bob is a strange place.
He has unusual choices of where he's gonna expose himself.
And they say Bob smells worse than stewed poohs.
Well, that's cause he smokes that pipe.
Subject or the object.
And he's got the real frop.
He doesn't have some street marijuana or wog hemp.
He's doing the real thing.
Have a frop zip you locks.
Marifazolupina.
That's where that smile comes from?
For short.
Can I ask you a question?
That's what Bob's smoking and that's what you smell when Bob wafts by.
Where did it come from?
I mean, the frop or the zip you locks?
Can I ask you that one question?
Oh, it comes from Tibet.
It only grows in Tibet on the graves and droppings of dead Tibetan holy men or yetis.
Full blood yetis.
Under the light of a full moon.
If it would grow on the droppings of a half-breed yeti, then we'd be up to our necks in real frop.
But we ain't.
We're not up to even our toenails in real frop.
It's hard to get, friends.
Maybe that's for the best.
I don't know.
The Chinese both want it because they don't have the frop or zip you locks.
And that's why they want Tibet.
Is that what you're saying?
Starek!
Yoo-hoo!
Is this what I think?
I feel like I'm on something.
This is one of those shows that's messing with my head.
It may be this rural war room background that's...
I can see the Fuhrer in my mind.
He's standing up there by the great map.
That's Groucho Marx, isn't it?
Oh, that's Captain Spalding.
That's not Hitler.
No, that's not Captain Spalding.
That's Rufus T. Firefly.
That was Charlie Chaplin.
Oh, that was Germaine Greer.
Whatever is Germaine to me.
Countess St. Germaine!
It was the scientific segue.
It was the easy way.
Ouch!
I thought it was the occultist segue that hit you, Chit-Zone.
Well, some of us are made of real DNA and others are made of...
Constructed materials, if you know what I mean, Reverend Diamond Stank.
I know, I know.
We're not all cranked out to be.
We're over here trying to help you with your show and you don't seem to pay much attention to us.
And what show is this?
Why, friends, this is Hour of Slack number 1149.
Where days seem like minutes.
Number nine?
One of the most official voice boxes of the Church of the Subgenius.
1149?
Located in the intranet.
That's at www.subgenius.com.
Subgenius spelled sub-genius.
And there is not an O anywhere in there except the .com.
There's an O in the dot and an O in the com.
Although you don't write out the dot.
I suppose you could try that.
Speaking of dots, we pulled out our magnifying glass recently and started searching for animalcules.
Again.
That's one of our hobbies.
We like to look at hideous, crawling, writhing, abhorrent, formless things that live in everybody's backyard.
Every square inch of dirt has hideous monsters.
Right under your toes.
The air you breathe.
And under your nose.
In between your eyelashes there are horrible, ugly worms chewing their way through your ducts.
Your tear ducts.
They live in there.
There's these spiral gyro looking things with all kinds of horny things sticking out of them.
They live in your lungs.
Can you imagine?
We scraped the newt cage last night.
Princess Wee and I did.
We went up to the...
We have only one slave pet that we keep.
A newt.
They're very low maintenance.
Fig is its name.
He's about as big as your little finger.
Yeah, he's not very big.
But he's very, very old.
Princess Wee acquired this newt 28 years ago.
And for all we know it was a thousand years old then.
Anyway, we wondered...
I think it's a spirit creature by now.
Yeah, well, no.
He's still really there.
Yes, he is.
He eats on a daily basis.
There's not much meat on him.
I know he's well and all that.
I mean, I think he's one of the old ones from before.
Well, we wanted to see if maybe he was living with those.
And what else was in the murky water before we cleaned his tank.
So we scraped some crud off the side of the tank and put some of that on our slide.
And took a look at it.
And guess what, Dave?
There was a horrible transparent nematode worm writhing frantically.
Because its water was drying up almost as you watched.
And...
He was all speckly and 3D-y looking.
You could see right through him.
Writhing in pain.
A tiny wee tubular life.
That you can't see with the nude eye.
But that little newt was no doubt...
Kind of covered with them, I suppose.
I would imagine so.
We could scrape him, I suppose.
And take a look.
Probably subsists on them partially.
You think?
You think he eats them nematodes?
I would imagine so.
What if there's a secret parasite that's going to get on you now, too?
And he's going to eat on your head and all the different parts of your body.
That's the wonderful thing about looking through your own $30 kid's microscope.
Because it's just theoretical in your mind.
That there are microorganisms everywhere.
Organisms.
Creeping through your nostrils.
And coming in and out with your air.
You're breathing tiny insect skeletons all the time.
Did you ever scrape a breech baby for any such hematodes?
That's next week.
But we have...
A project to project kind of thing.
When you actually look at those things, you get a concrete knowledge of the fact that...
Actually, I think Nenslo figured this out.
This is what it all boils down to.
All life, the universe, and everything boils down to this.
Dirt is mostly poo.
And poo is mostly corpses.
So friends, it's the circle of life.
It's not necessarily that poo is our corpses.
You see, it's mostly poo and corpses.
This is the detritus of the human condition.
No, poo is corpses.
It comes out of you while you're living.
And dirt is mostly poo.
And it is left behind.
So the whole world, really, if you think about it...
Is defecation.
There's more of that than there is...
There's more crap than there is living, breathing non-crap.
This is like the poopiest conversation I've heard.
Well, it's natural.
It's a naturistical thing.
It's something you don't tend to think about.
But the biomass of those tiny creatures far outweighs the biomass of animals that you can see.
But it's literally hoo-ha.
I personally like to crawl around on them.
And they smell funny.
I mean, just think of these thousands and thousands of generations living on a mound of decay.
And that it's making itself.
We're self-perpetuating and self-engendering.
Think of a sting.
We'll live forever on our own feces.
Well, they're living in my hair.
They're living in my bowels.
They're living between my toes.
Things.
Things, things, things.
And yours too, friend.
Listener, I want you, as you go to bed tonight,
I want you to think about all those little monsters that live in between the creases of your body.
If you didn't take a shower in the last 15 or 20 minutes.
Oh, well, of course.
And even then you wouldn't get most of them.
I mean, a lot of them would still, would cling on.
Like miniature Klingons.
And on and on and on.
The little cities in your ear canal.
Those little tiny universes and malls and a room.
The original theater in the crack of your behind.
Think of it, man.
You're a city of little tiny, little things.
You know, I was doing okay until you mentioned the crack of the behind crack.
That one crack.
I was fine with everything until you said that.
Now I'm disgustipated.
I'm sick.
Sickened.
Where would you live if you were such a creature?
I'd live in 1998.
Friends, that's where I'd be forever.
And that's where we have to go now because the show is now coming to an end.
We have to make room for show next.
And so, say goodbye.
Goodbye.
Oh, dear listeners, parting is such sweet sorrow.
And we thank Norrell Preff for the collagiastical upcomings.
And also John Hell from A Season in Hell.
Thank you.
Praise God.
Shell dividing.
Thick intelligence.
Thick urges.
Biological weapons.
Use logical agents.
Let me take you inside and share with you thick urges.
Urges.
We have logical weapons factories on wheels and on rails.
We have vague hints programmed.
Logical poison.
Poison.
Program.
Enjoying our, yes, exactly.
By the way, there were a whole bunch of weddings going on right there during the barbecue that day.
Numerous, a number of the brides were all pregnant, which was quite interesting, in their dresses.
And then, the thing is, right down the street, like, there's a, the house is at the end, sort of, of a street.
And then it just turns to the left and dead ends at a church.
Just maybe about 100 yards, not even that, 50 yards away.
And so, all of a sudden, during our fabulous family reunion, a real wedding began to take place at the church.
So, all of the brides ran out about, we're talking about maybe half a dozen pregnant brides, run out of the party and approach the groom.
The real groom at the real church.
And start throwing themselves on him about how he's their baby's daddy.
And you've got all the ushers.
Excellent, yeah.
The whole wedding party there, family, very, sort of a, it's a happy joyous family celebration.
Children are getting married.
What a lucky group they were.
Six pregnant brides.
Yeah.
All that guy's responsibility.
Well, yeah, he actually looked like he recognized a few of them, too.
Yeah.
He looks scared.
That's what you get.
I rise, the ugly baby.
Baby.
Bringing this forward.
An ugly baby.
Ugly thing.
No, no.
Nah, nah, nah.
And this will be just baby.
Baby.
This baby is ugly thing.
I rise, the ugly baby.
Across the nation, communities and the parents of Boy Scouts are observing Boy Scout Week,
agreeing with the boys themselves that adventure, that's scouting.
Boy Scout Week.