From PR News in Washington, I'm not as bad as initially thought.
The Ford Motor Company is bombing London.
PR's bad.
Federal Reserve Chairman Alan Greenspan warned of painful free abortions.
Greenspan could happen gradually and with much disruption,
although it might mean lower asses and a disturbing time.
Federal Reserve Chairman Alan Greenspan's bad.
Greenspan could be quite painful for the pernicious world economy.
Greenspan tackling morons from Washington.
PR's bad.
Also, the government says this is PR News.
Hi.
Where is it?
Where's what?
This is a genius toy off-snack.
Boy, that's neat.
Yes.
All right, children, you may go.
Yep, yep, yep.
Dairy Queen has legs.
This is so little and so silly,
but I thought it was...
It was funny.
Someone in the third world.
Big.
Powerful.
He fabricated a scam.
Fast cars and loose slots.
Okay.
The Church of Fast Cars and Loose Slots.
Very superficial.
There's all kinds of drugs and filth and perversion.
All about Dobbs.
Dobbs out of control.
Sick, sick, sick, evil.
That's what Dobbs is saying.
You gotta let people know.
Right?
A little bit.
Kill judges.
Fix the judiciary.
I'm curious.
Considered a crank.
Cranked by a lot of people.
How absurd.
And this is common.
Murdered.
Steal.
Committed adultery.
So here's how I'm sexual.
Just tweak it a little.
Twist.
One hour.
Big bone.
It was in her hand.
So wouldn't that be neat?
That makes you a queen.
Eh.
Send a check.
Thanks, Bob.
Uh, Bob, how are you?
Welcome aboard.
I do have a problem with discipline.
Um, Bob, use physical discipline.
I believe...
Believe in discipline.
Be spanked with a wooden paddle.
Spanked with a wooden paddle.
Do it.
Um, um, if it was administered properly,
then serious, serious marks on our buttocks and elsewhere
from 12 severe whacks.
Whack, whack, whack.
Sean, we should do this.
Are there broken bones, lacerations?
What about welts?
What about 12 welts?
Okay.
Using a paddle or a strap or a switch on the backside.
Good spanking.
Well, my, look, my, my...
Spanking.
We are losing.
Good spanking.
Well, my, look, my, my...
Your hands are made for loving, cuddling.
There's so many other techniques.
Spank me.
Firmly.
We love the rods.
It hurt.
Spanking.
Despise the government.
Degenerating into an animal without the ability to see or hear or speak.
Thank you, Bob.
There she sat with a very happy look on her face.
The same look she had the night before.
The same look he tried to overlook at the bar.
Now he had to try to get her out of his place.
But there she sat
with a very happy look on her face.
It was late last night in the red bar light
and she looked all right.
Oh, no.
She had a slutty kind of appeal
and there was definitely something to her.
And you could think of friends of yours
who if you knew if they could, they would do her.
She had a dirty sock kind of appeal.
Oh, God, no.
You shower one time, you still smell her.
You shower two times, you still smell her.
You smell her nipples on your breath
and all the rest of your friends watched you leave together
so they know.
And your bedsheets.
My God, her smell is in your bedsheets.
A scent that no amount of detergent
can dislodge and your pillow stinks too.
Oh, my God.
It's time to go
to Billy's Pinkfuck Gazebo
where the loathsome men go.
Oh, my God.
And you can have a cup of Joe
at Billy's Pinkfuck Gazebo.
Oh!
Yeah.
Thanks, Bob.
And thanks, Norell Preff, who did that,
and who disciplined Bob there at the beginning.
Lee Murr did the startups.
There have been and there will be
Dr. Philo Drummond, Puzzling Evidence,
Dr. Howell, Michael Pepe,
yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang,
and so much more on KPFA,
Over the Edge, blah, blah, blah,
the Puzzling Evidence show, friends.
And that song that we just heard,
Billy's, is by The Billy Nayer Show.
More of all coming up on this hour of Slight Number 1028.
But now...
From PR News in Washington,
and for regular Oklahoma.
Secretary of Defense Donald Rumsfeld today
blew himself up at a shopping mall in Honolulu.
The United Nations is getting worse.
It's infected with HIV than any single year.
Federal officials might unfold in the United States.
PR knocks that story.
A federally financed study might enter the United States.
The study would leak into the country
despite efforts to screen travelers for PR news.
On Wall Street, 310-83-56221.
Europeans have raised alarm that Europe would be detrimental to the United States.
Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice issued her defense
of the way the U.S. treats secret PR news in Washington.
I want to teleport.
You want to teleport? I think that's a different show.
And not the mafia.
I want to teleport.
Who was it and not the mafia? What?
It was you and me.
Who was it and not the mafia?
As soon as you get through, monger.
Monger.
Jack Ruby?
Jack Ruby was well aware, had mafia connections.
And the cool thing is the city had those lit corners.
So they had lights, I guess, at one time in the corners of the streets.
Jack Ruby worked for the mafia his whole life.
But a long time ago, the city had stopped putting lights in the corners.
So they were these cool pillboxes-like things.
A mafia home?
But they had the best killers, and the CIA tried to use them.
They were professional.
We always brought up their professional life.
They got into trouble over Mabute.
What was his name, Neil?
The African, uh, La Mamba.
And these were Mamba.
They handed him over to the Congo.
Mamba.
But Sidney, Dr. Sidney Gottlieb had got his poison ready and had it all, you know, set out in his insane laboratory in Virginia.
And, uh, it almost, I think it made it there and they didn't use it and they sent it back.
I discovered a garrison didn't know.
Okay.
No!
Do we still have that sample in the, uh, in the warehouse?
Yeah, you can't use it.
It's a dead...
Oh, we used it.
No, no.
I can't use it yet.
I was talking to this microphone.
Can we...
It's a storm of lies.
I know.
Can we...
Can we still use it or is it, uh, a dead sample?
Uh, I, I think it's a dead sample.
Dead.
Oh, yeah.
Unfortunately, he destroyed, uh, I don't know, Gottlieb's lab, I think.
You're out of power.
You know, but he was Strangelove.
We'll be, we'll be wanting to use that sample before the end of the show.
Uh, exactly.
A blizzard of lies.
A hurricane of lies.
To make good on our promises.
Yeah, lies, I'm sorry, lies is not here.
You're living in every day.
Well, I'm here.
Uh...
Yeah.
What did I miss?
Everything?
They must have a lab that has a new weapon.
Well, we're trying to get serious about this business thing because we want to get this done before 5 AM.
Our time.
If you're really creative and you go into weapons...
Yeah, because it's like three hours in the future in Cleveland.
Right.
It's, the end of the world's already happened there.
But if we keep running ahead of the explosion, we can...
We can never be in the end of the world.
We'll never, and our show will never stop.
Yeah.
Which it doesn't anyway, because it is eternal.
And, uh...
We're sort of working on a, on a thing similar to Mayan time.
It's an eternal show, folks.
We don't go off the air like normal mortal shows.
We go off all night long.
I thought it was Australian, aboriginal talk.
We don't have to have a job.
We don't have to talk.
We don't have to, uh, talk.
Um, the guys that live out by the NASA thing.
If you support us...
And the fire goes in the sky and they talk about how they can travel.
Michael Heffi is now broken.
You know, I am...
I don't like to talk about that.
Teleporting thing.
That confuses people.
Uh, he's not here officially.
Okay, we're off the air now.
Oh, let's call him.
We have to be as soon as they say that we're dead.
Okay, guys.
We're off the air now.
Off the air.
Okay, let's go.
Out of the pool.
Everybody out of the pool.
Back into the business meeting.
Get back into that business meeting.
That sounds like the kind of line of meeting call.
Yeah, that's right.
Into your, uh...
You're supposed to be reading those line items.
I know.
We gotta start at that page 13 of the budget.
Did any of you guys, uh, turn in the, uh, federal employees?
Uh...
I turned in the sensitive language forms.
That's my job.
I think, you know, I think those were...
That's all you did?
Well, and the indecency signature form.
I turned in my neighbor.
Along with the...
Giveaway forms.
Are you gonna...
Emergency on air studio import form.
Didn't we roll something in that form?
River Stang, do you open yourselves up to these government agencies?
Come on.
I turned in the clock watching form.
Oh, the...
The highly colorful magazine.
In the interest of sunshine and...
You colorful, colorful...
Some of those government agencies you're talking about are subdivisions of Bobco.
I mean, I...
Say something, caller.
But Bobco itself is a subdivision of some of the other federal agencies.
Bobco?
Oh, I see.
I see.
There's a caller.
Where are you from, caller?
...form itself in a light egg batter and then some cornmeal...
Whatcha doing over there in Fresno, caller?
Yeah, you can do that.
This is like, uh...
Fresno's a negative name.
Bob Tortillas?
Serve warm.
That's a positive name.
Fresno...
They take little birds...
Picture dark nudity on...
Uh, no.
We shouldn't talk about that because he knows that's a negative name.
The only one who's listening right now is Reverend Howell, a 420 guy and not K-Rock.
Where is Reverend Howell?
Reverend Howell?
He's in a car right now in the horrible traffic that always occurs at 2-3 in the morning.
Howell, come back to us, Howell.
Is this denated for four hours?
Just as he walks out his door.
Good morning, Howell.
They're trying to prevent him from being on the show because...
Suddenly traffic piles up from his door all the way to the station and then evaporates
as soon as they arrive.
...the roadblock.
...he's going to...
...a knuckle walk...
...a silverback knuckle walk...
Michael Pepe's taking your space, Howell.
Oh, no.
...the nakedness.
He took all of your words and changed them to him.
Yes, well...
But it's a naked Michael Pepe versus a clothed Howell.
Exactly.
Yeah, I'm the way that...
Old six-eyes.
...I want you to think Howell is or should be.
...is defended and foisted upon the people...
Exactly.
That's what I try to do.
No foisting zone, please.
...no foisting.
Just...
Hey, please foist behind the building.
...because, you know, just in order to warp your brain to that extent, it needs no explanation.
Why wouldn't someone want to warp your brain?
It's so...
It's so easy after all, isn't it, folks?
...in our society.
Well, it's kind of constantly happening...
Yeah, anyway...
...and plus you warp your own brain...
Right.
...if you're...
You really don't...
...alive.
Yeah.
...that only describes less than half of the people.
That's right.
People, yeah.
Oh, people, sure.
Sure.
But this, this...
People, listening to this...
Soil and grain is people.
That's our audience.
Soil and grain is people, right?
Soil and grain, yeah, sure.
Yeah, sure.
People, yeah.
But this...
...is the worst load of ludicrous crap I have ever heard.
...soil and grain was an inspiration to the church.
You know, that was the first caller to the first subgenius radio show.
Yeah.
The first appearance...
That's why we honor him.
...subgenius anywhere...
...soil and grain is...
...by remembering him.
...and that was the response.
Yep, people, yeah.
People, sure.
Sure.
But this...
This is the sickest thing I have heard on KFJZ.
Mr. Pridgen?
Yes.
Let me say this.
Can I say something for just about a half a minute?
You bet.
Go right ahead.
It's a free country for a little while.
I...
As high a regard as I have had for KFJZ and even when the...
Oh, what's the name?
Otis is on.
Yes, sir.
All that stuff.
I think this is about the sickest, sickest, sickest thing I've ever heard on KFJZ and
since I've been listening to it.
I'm just...
I am thoroughly ashamed of KFJZ right now.
I don't...
I don't know what to say.
You know, I'm getting strong trance indications from this man that he was the high liar of
Baghdad at one time.
I don't...
I'm not interested in you.
I'm just...
In your past life.
...I don't know what I think about this sick, sick, sick program that you're putting on
here.
Well...
KFJZ as of now, this is terrible.
You don't believe people should start their own cult if they want to?
People?
I mean, yeah, people, you know...
I mean, I don't know.
But not this, this is the damnedest thing I've ever heard of.
Okay, well thank you for your opinion.
Thanks a lot.
Well, I...
Apparently, there's somebody out there who was not a subgenius.
He wasn't able to figure this thing out...
Well, no, I think he recognizes that we're beyond human.
That's right.
He...
Yeah, I see.
We...
Above or below, it matters not.
I ain't listening to KFJZ no more.
But the funny thing is, he called in next week real friendly and denied being the son
of the same caller.
Oh.
I don't care.
For the sake of being...
You know...
A true subgenius out there.
Somewhere, there was one.
Well...
And we honor him almost every show.
Honest subgenius.
And now he slipped through our fingers.
Yeah.
We lost him.
We lost track of him.
Where is that man?
We're searching for that one honest subgenius.
If you're it...
Please call.
Call in.
Call the show, please.
But actually, these magazines not only...
4895,000.
Yeah.
Yeah, please call in.
You really...
What was it?
69,000.
And then, of course, once you...
If you call in, we can start to get the business meeting started.
Also, if you're my long lost father, call the show now.
I want to talk to you.
Why you left when I was 16.
Call the show right now, please.
Michael.
Michael, this is your pa.
You was just an ugly child.
That's all there is to it.
Why did you hook yourself up...
He's still an ugly child.
And he's right.
Just because you were...
You were born with a beard.
You just looked ugly, Michael.
I'm sorry to say that.
What?
Just let go, son.
Here I am.
You're out of our lives.
You look just like your mom.
This is the last you'll hear from us.
Bye.
Pa?
I knew the show for what it was.
I knew Buzz and Em for what he was.
I was trying hard to be good looking.
I tried to...
How many radio stations have we heard on?
I tried to be normal.
I tried to be normal, Pa.
And they just kept calling me subgenius trash.
They called me weirdo.
I tried to be normal.
They called me freak.
What a gay-
I'm-
They called me nerd.
Nerd.
They called me bookworm.
Uh, what do you-
They called me...
They called me geek and nerd.
And-and-and-and they said I have two more eyes.
They called me fat dog.
They called me four eyes.
They called me fatty.
They called me bold, I don't know.
Fat, thick iş, four, imagine you.
But they called me-
They called me Hong Kong.
They called me bald genius, bald genius.
The big
snapshot.
Yeah, uh, yeah.
They made fun of me.
It's just not fair, Bob.
Yeah, I hear you whining.
You crybaby subgeniuses.
Is that what you call slack?
Feeling sorry for yourself?
Lollering in self-pity?
Like a pathetic little humanly, normally warmly warm boy.
They beat me up.
Yank yourself up by your own red straps.
Poor girl.
Big red straps, that is.
Big old red straps.
Get up and do it.
You're going to have to get up off the butt.
I have subgenius boobs.
You have subgenius boobs?
That means you have a pipe emerging from each one.
Does that mean one goes up and one goes down?
I don't know.
No.
It's just a boob.
I got her all tied up.
Yeah, a boob.
Boob.
Ooh, he's got her all tied up.
That's what he's saying.
He's got double boob.
Boobs.
Double boob.
And they're smiling.
She's got big bobs, daddy.
They're about to blow up.
And with lesbian implications.
That lady has big bobs, daddy.
Wait, they're dots.
Dots incredible, as the guy said once in a tape a long time ago.
You've got a bobble on the side of one of them.
Ooh.
That's where the show is.
I hear my memory is on all the tapes.
I hear a little tire patch will fix it.
There's a little bubble on the side of each cassette.
Soak it in water and see if it bubbles.
Ooh.
Cassette?
What's that?
What's a cassette?
Just pump it.
Just break it.
It's those things that the brown dust falls out of.
It'll explode and all that pus will shoot out of.
Pick for leaks.
Yeah, oh, you know, the little sponge thing dies.
Just put a pimple on your breast or even you guys on your penis.
Well, that's what you get for having a single thing.
Just go ahead.
No, just go ahead and squeeze it.
Give it a good squeeze and squirt all that pus out of.
Ew, gross, man.
Wipe that crap off me.
Ugh, God, typical Michael Pepe.
That's from KPFA's Puzzling Evidence Show.
And friends, this is the Church of the Sub-Genes.
A disorganized religion for non-joiners and weirdos, right?
Yeah.
Now, imagine some of the people who got into it.
Okay, now imagine my office answer machine heard in the background
and the calls that we might get on an answer machine at a weird cult like this.
Now, actually, don't try, friends.
Just listen, because what I'm about to play are some typical messages left on the Sub-Genius Foundation,
Answer Machine, on one typical day last month.
Hello, friends.
You know, the psychiatric industry is probably the stupidest part of this conspiracy.
It believes we are all our brains.
There is no God, souls, or mind as materialism is.
It rejects all religion and worships narcotics.
All these doctors do is look at...
...the brain.
Kill books all day long.
And memorize them.
And basically what they do is most of the time,
and his friends, these places, these half-waths of hospitals,
and that's what Mickey Mouse concentration camps,
right here legal in America.
And it's praise Bob, praise Wayne Zappa.
This, this is me Bernard.
You know, I just wanted to say, you know, you Sub-Genius ministers, God bless you.
Please take cover because, you know, these pinks, you know, these normals in the conspiratorial American establishment union is really making me angry.
Just take cover.
This is being said by an angry mutant.
I'm the real deal, an angry mutant.
Take cover.
Comrades.
All right, friends.
There are four rules in Rick Strass' second book.
First rule, I'll put the more energy you put out, the more energy you get back.
Energy is a time-loving E of Einstein's equation.
The second rule is the rule of qualitative return.
Energy is a...
Whatever you put out, resentment, anger, forgiveness, and love, that's how you get it back.
And I'll take the third and fourth rules later on tonight or tomorrow.
Praise God.
Praise St. Sabbath.
Bye.
Hi.
This is Steve Bernard.
I just want to say to all the sub-genius ministers to take cover.
I'm sick of this new wave neo-fascist police state adopting conspiratorial pink human regime here in America.
This is a state that we've been forced to adopt, I mean, to exist in.
Take cover.
Words spoken by an angry mutant.
Steve again.
Some of you may be interested in reading William James' Psychology of the Brief, of course.
It's...
And he talks about the self.
I don't know.
I didn't get that far.
But somebody could read that.
Maybe someone could write an article for this dark fist on the self.
Maybe someone could read the article over the hour of slack.
Thank you, bye-bye.
Praise God.
Praise St. Sabbath.
Hi.
This is Steve Bernard.
You know, the conspiracy of these genetic human normals are really making me angry and frustrating me, increasing their tyranny over everything.
All that I can just say is just, you know, the sub-genius ministers and comrades.
Just take cover.
Take cover.
The conspiracy of these genetic human normals are really making me angry and frustrating me with their tyranny over everything.
You know, with the ending of the 20th century and everything that's going down.
Take cover.
Words spoken by an angry mutant.
I know I'm a mutant.
I've seen it before my eyes.
Take cover.
Yes, thank you.
This is Gary.
I'd like to order some t-shirts.
Friends.
The more energy you put out, the more energy you get back.
Get back.
Praise God.
Elephants.
Stupid as part of the conspiracy materials to look at Mickey Mouse concentration.
Praise God.
I don't know.
I didn't get out of the slide.
Praise God.
Praise my example.
Making me angry.
Angry mutant.
Deal.
Human normals are really making me angry.
Angry mutant.
It's making me frustrated.
Take cover.
T-shirts?
Order some T-shirts?
Hey, Bob.
The men in white picked him up yesterday.
With a nuts hunt for squirrels, ha ha.
Oh, and then the days got worse.
And then the days got worse.
Oh, at last they let me out.
I need to pray.
There you go, yes, I'm coming to take me away.
We are just in a good eye.
The funny farm where life is beautiful all the time.
And you'll be stay and play with my new friend.
I'm normal, I'm okay.
With the people all smiling like.
But this.
Hey, hi there.
You would make me flip my lid.
It was a joke and so you laughed.
And you, the day you swore you'd all.
Ha ha, they're coming to take me away.
Oh, ho, hee, ha ha.
To the valley.
There's no way I'm snitching to serve you.
Leave me mad.
And I'm happy they took you away.
Ha ha.
Oh, no!
I heard ham and I spread rumors it's.
You and how I should cut my hair.
And look upon all them.
Tom, Tom, Tom, Tom.
And you're right.
I am making friends.
You.
I cooked your food.
I.
And that gives me the.
Who's.
Get.
Out.
Losing you would surely make me.
And.
The.
To take.
A.
Push.
As though they're.
Coffee.
Ha.
Well, you just.
You'll get just what you deserve.
Where's trees and grass and I don't.
Just my thumb and feed my lizard.
To drive me sane.
He he.
All of this.
Ha ha ha he he.
Here to you.
And that's the day.
Young man in a green white coat.
And.
They're coming.
Where life was ludicrous all the time.
And.
They're coming.
And flowers and chirping birds and.
Farts.
Who speak and smile and twiddle their.
On the wall.
Ha ha ha.
Noro Pref.
Did that last cut up friends of their coming to take me away.
And he also did the cut up of our church answer machine messages there from Steve and Bernard.
And now a cut up tape of an old tape of the newest show.
But I have a tape of the first time I saw a tape recorder.
Aging Palo Alto.
The show is still.
And it still plays fine.
Reflection of your mind.
Aging Doctor Howell.
Lieutenant Commander gave my family the tape.
You have a pimple on your penis.
And it was.
Just give it a.
And I can remember singing with my mother.
This show is simply a Christmas of your imagination.
Three years old.
And I was staring at what would replace my VU meters.
Remember the little exciter lamps.
Yeah.
Same thing with farts.
I was staring at that.
Those that come back.
You gotta fart folks.
You know.
On what?
Just let it go.
On computer screens.
It excites me.
I read Stang.
What do you think about farts?
I mean.
You get excited by lamps?
Keep them in.
Like cider lamps.
Yeah.
Let them go.
Better than.
Cider lamps.
Fart and bear the pain.
Long gone.
My end and the whole.
The fart and bear the pain.
Return.
According to the show.
There's a pimple on the side of the show.
On which no one would ever lie.
Fart and bear the pain.
People.
I mean.
Yeah.
People.
But not.
Not this.
This is the dumbest thing I've ever heard of.
For people.
Getting high was important.
For some people.
It's even more important.
You've tried just about everything.
Excellent.
Now medical information comes in handy.
It comes along that says you need to get high.
Good.
Now what do you do?
Well.
Getting high was not for everyone.
Including people with serious side effects.
Do you still need to get high?
Get high with your doctor.
From PR news in Washington.
I'm swathed in mud and sand at a chemical plant.
A radio reporter reached new highs in the Philippines.
The tenth journalist to be in the country this year.
November came after two Gulf Coast hurricanes.
Analysts say they were let in yesterday to collect damage firsthand.
You have to say this has been a very, very good, real good, very, very solid pee performance.
The head of China's protection bureau resigned today after a crisis over a toxic polluted Chinese citizen.
And the United Nations says that torture remains PR news in Washington.
The wedding guests are arriving.
And your bridegroom, Count Vernon, grows impatient.
Ha ha ha ha.
Huh?
Well.
What?
What is that you said?
That one clean-minded said genius.
In my day we could burp and fart at the same time.
But of course they don't teach in schools now.
They don't have the education now that they have.
Now, you know.
My day.
You get paid overtime tonight?
Yeah.
Really?
In Bob dollars.
Like that time and a half?
I think it's a good hiccup, boop, and perp.
Music by Inhibiting Factor.
Yeah.
That's what it is.
At the same time.
Did they play these songs live at Dockstock?
I mean, at X-Day?
Was it live?
No, they played them in the back of my head.
From PR News in Washington, I'm supposed to pass through the opening.
Officials in France say a trash can fire has plagued poor suburbs of Paris for nearly two weeks.
In addition, three dozen policemen were seriously rioting.
More than 800 cars were racially harassed by police on Saturday night.
Police in Toulouse in the south sprung up in Nantes, Orléans, and Rennes.
This is PR's Tips.
The president of China has pledged that clean tear gas will be pushing back the crowd.
The Bush administration is a big supporter of PR News in Washington.
She was a bird of prey.
She came to me in the night.
She left when things weren't right.
Stand up, sit down, fight, fight, fight.
Now I'm alone at night.
I'm alone at night.
From dawn to dawn.
From dawn to twilight.
I look for her in the evening sky.
Stand up, sit down, oh God, why?
She put her beak in my heart.
And she removed the good part.
I found it near the cable car turnaround.
Dried up, rotting.
On the ground.
I peeled it off of the sidewalk.
With a straw and a paper towel.
Wiped off the dirt and picked out the rocks.
Everything's gonna be alright now.
Everything's gonna be alright.
A bird of prey.
By the...
Billy Mayer Show.
And that band will be coming to X-Day.
I believe, as well as the amino acids.
Hopefully will be.
And we hope little Theodore and Babushka.
And the devil.
Devil, devil.
The devil's after me.
I'm on my way to...
Devil, come this way.
The devil.
Devil, devil.
Lives inside my heart.
He'll be with me where I go.
Devil, come this way.
Devil, devil.
He'll be with me where I go.
The Devil's After Me
Thanks to Norrell Preff.
Friends, have you ever wondered how...
we subgenius preachers...
are able to seemingly talk forever...
just as if we knew what the heck we were talking about?
You're talking about...
True, true stories.
I had to memorize all this stuff at Dobstown University...
at the Divinity School.
And where's that?
I mean, uh...
Malaya.
They don't call me Reverend for nothing.
Oh.
I thought they did.
What are you, Reverend?
I have a diploma from, uh...
from the Divinity School.
Oh, you have a diploma.
Oh.
Yeah, I have a piece of paper.
That's what you like.
You have a piece of paper that says your mind's okay.
Yeah.
No, Dob...
No, Dobstown University.
P.O.
Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Illinois.
You do have a heart.
44118.
You do have a brain.
What you lack is a diploma.
I want a diploma.
What you lack is a subgenius membership.
At the flea market.
You have something other than a Universal Life Church diploma?
Is that what you're saying, Rivstang?
No, this one's from my family.
Yeah.
Yeah, I've got a...
So you have...
...doctorate of divinity from, uh, Dobstown University.
Oh.
Yeah, but you see, I got a...
Duh!
Oh, gosh.
Okay, all right.
It's Church of the Subgenius.
Yeah.
It's a no brainer.
I see.
Oh, that's Church.
I got...
I got one from that church too, I think.
Hey, we have a bunch of witches in Subgenius now.
That's right.
We've recruited Wiccans and Druids, uh, using this, uh, Starwood Festival to brainwash
them.
Oh.
And, uh, we use Ed of Technicolors.
Ed of Technics, we learned, and Esalen, and also from the Masons, which are the same
ones used by torturers in the U.S. military now.
And Arika, and Sinanon.
And we use those to recruit these, uh...
Or in any good S&M club here in San Francisco.
...Neopagans, Wiccans, Druids, and so forth.
Is there a catalog of them?
They, uh...
Yeah.
Uh, their women are comely.
Yeah, in Amsterdam.
Yeah.
And their men are strapping.
Uh, if a bit dense.
Big red, is it?
They make good subgeniuses or...
Big red, pay for that.
...subgenius pseudosub.
Yeah.
Pseudosubs.
Librarians.
Maybe they can protect the sub...
Or breatharians.
Or Pyparians.
Yeah.
Librarians.
The Pyparians only eat pipes.
Oh, the Pyparians.
Yeah.
That's what they exactly...
Hey, isn't Pipes of the Piposphere being remade?
Yeah, it is.
Some of these are a remake of Pipes of the Piposphere.
What?
We're not actually supposed to talk about it because I think they'll want to...
Yeah.
Is this allowed?
Pipes of the Piposphere was one of the classics of the 50s that brought the idea of the...
Wow.
The good thing about it is that Dobbs helped to finance.
Thank you.
It had a weird conceptual special effect.
Now I have a really good show now.
It didn't take off very fast.
Hey, no, I...
It was big in France and Sweden.
Much better.
Thank you.
I was going to say certain circles.
Did you buy it?
Very big in Sweden.
Also, you know where else?
A couple other places.
Eastonia.
Oh, my God.
Doug, it's so loud.
And southern Papua New Guinea.
Doug, you should turn down.
For some reason.
Love that movie.
Oh, wait.
It's so...
How do you do that?
Okay.
down a little here.
That's right.
Okay.
That's good.
It's still playing in Winnipeg.
It's been playing for 35 years.
Yeah.
Yeah, at this little place in, like, the really sleazy part of town.
That is fine.
That's the best part of town.
There's some Polynesian island where they worship it.
I'm so glad I brought my women's choir to this show.
Yeah.
They have pipe cults in which they built giant jobs heads and pipes.
Just like pep cults?
And made big runways.
They don't really know what they're for.
Oh, no, that's X Day.
Oh.
That's fresh music.
I was watching without the sound in my head.
Are these like pep cults?
No, there's also some Polynesian island where they do.
They don't do jobs heads with just the pipes.
Oh.
And they build canoe, pipe canoes.
Yeah.
Many people get their spiritual knowledge from pipes.
They don't have a face.
They think the pipe is Bob.
Yeah.
The pipe is an alien.
For their primitive conception, they can't conceive of Bob.
I've seen the rough road map.
They can't conceive of a man holy enough to hold the pipe in his mouth.
Right.
Who could do that?
It's a symbol of the snake.
That's like one of us pushing an Easter Island head up by ourselves.
It's the symbol of the snake, you know, this knowledge, which has been formed into the pipe.
The great phallus snake of knowledge, like Uroboros.
So you're all phallus.
This is an orbeal round.
Yeah.
The pipe that smokes itself forever.
It smokes itself forever.
Is that kind of like the snake that we use?
That's why people are attracted to it.
Yeah, it's a lot like the Thaddeus stick where subgeniuses who meet each other in the forest will hold out sticks and snakes.
Boom.
Yeah.
And communicate with the pipe.
They hold their hands thusly and say, bop.
That's why the topless wicked stop really into it.
And then the druid guys, which are old antlers.
As Hal found out last year at XD.
Yeah.
What?
Did he what?
Now, this next upcoming XD at Brushwood, we have some musical acts that we haven't had before.
The Billy Nair show.
Oh, my God.
We'll be performing at XD.
Famous.
Apparently, they live in New York.
Famous musicians.
They will be at XD.
Magdalene.
Reverend Magdalene of the subgenius business office.
I know her.
Wait a minute.
Apparently, seduced this band into appearing at XD.
Yeah.
They did a film called The American Astronaut.
The American Astronaut.
Yeah.
Which is pretty good.
It's really nice.
Pretty good.
And family oriented.
And everybody should see it because it inspires you to do better in your life.
He is only.
Well, if you're.
A birthday boy.
Every day.
Since.
You really want to do better.
You really want to be a birthday boy.
Why are we pushing him?
Because.
You can learn how.
You know, my show.
I actually get to play God in my show.
Really?
What's it called?
Yeah.
It's a show.
A Satan show.
You get to play God.
Being put on at Christmas time.
The weekend before and after Christmas.
And I play God.
This guy, Shannon, that did the zombie show with Don Paul where I was decapitated.
I used to do that.
And played a different part.
And I'm going to play.
Wow.
Yeah.
So I'm now God.
And so come to my show.
And.
The show is God.
The God Show with Michael Pepe is God.
God.
The voice of.
Wow.
Is God.
Michael Pepe is God.
The way there is no God.
Wow.
Yeah, there is.
His name is Michael Pepe.
There is no God.
If you're going to.
No.
There is no God.
There's no God.
That is the 44th.
The passing.
Of wickedness.
Follow the Torah.
Follow it.
Well, yeah.
Crazy.
Yeah.
I mean.
I think you're crazy.
It's crazy to go back in.
Do some family life.
Whether you live it up some two ways, showcasing God.
Rottenượngesme.
God anything.
And I need a.
No pat Maya.
The essence of the lone spaz nerd.
What the devil?
Squalling out in anger.
What do they want?
Holy righteous, the anger of the persecuted hate nerd.
Anger persecuted.
Bursting.
A fettertable hard-on of hate.
Fettertable fart-on.
You're on drugs.
From PR News in Washington, I'm not ready for full democracy.
The Louisville, Kentucky Police Department is solving some crimes.
Police say many of those police have lengthy criminal records.
One of the surveillance videos shows police in several Louisville bank robberies.
Police are considered armed and dangerous and warn the public not to try to apprehend them.
Louisville has had a record number of PR News.
The White House says this is PR News in Washington.
The White House, who is the parti mind of the White House, has Yet
had the record number of police, performing some acts of terrorism.
Police are also concerned that Booo Booo Booo.
Booo Booo Booo.
Good luck.
They're out of control.
They're demanding to know when the food will be here.
I understand the caterers are here.
We have babies here and old people who need medicine.
We need all the doctors in the central studio.
This is a health crisis.
You heard the PA.
I'm just going to run up to the Sky Room.
The National Guard was supposed to be here.
We're going to flip-flop these functions over to the Coast Guard.
We're going to have to suspend the law for the duration of this crisis until the doctors report to the central studio for the budget meeting and the photo op.
And so we'll be having that meeting now.
Entering our...
That which provides sex gratification for the participants.
Now this, uh, this is...
Female garments will be required.
This picture, of course, merely confesses on the cover of the magazine the charges we have made.
Of course they sound better.
And last longer, I think.
Oh, I'm so glad to be alive in this modern age.
And that's why I don't want to die.
In this ad...
The titles of the magazines and their table of contents speak more eloquently than I of the tremendous problem here presented.
But there's not a whole lot I can do about that now.
Except maybe eat more vegetables.
And I think I better marry my girlfriend.
Am I not to be desired?
Look, how about getting us out of here?
And to thin slices.
The time is up for...
Arrange those succulent charcoal-tasting slices on a hot, oven-proof platter.
Oh.
And on the hot platter, have a sauce of melted butter and a few drops of Worcestershire sauce.
Oh, yes, I suppose it is.
Rush to the table and the fun begins.
Because he did not want to commit hundreds of thousands of boys to Vietnam.
Get out!
You grow up!
Dark-satis!
Hate you!
I want nothing!
I'm calling the police now!
Call the police now!
Yes, I am!
Yes, we want!
Call 911 now!
Call the police now!
911 now!
Everything's ungodly!
He went hamper in the end.
Now I'm sad and stuff!
He's not a Christian!
I'm...
Entire hell starts that at two!
Gargoyle!
Slag it!
Pain it!
Doing anything with my family!
God, I'm a gun warrior!
That's a lie!
Slag it!
Why are you doing this?
No!
I asked you nicely ten minutes ago to unzip my older ass!
I don't have time!
I gotta get back to work!
Get me that goddamn card now!
To the flip-second!
Can't you fucking let me $50 right now?
You're my son!
Get out! Get out!
You grow up! You grow up!
I hate you!
God damn it!
I want nothing! I want nothing!
Fuck off!
I want nothing!
You're gone! You're gone! You're gone!
Fuck off!
I want nothing!
That's a lie!
God! I'm a God's warrior!
You grow up! You grow up!
Hey, hey, hey, how you doing, how you doing?
I'm calling the police now
Call the police now
Yes I am, yes I am
Call 911 now
Now, now, now
Now, 911 now
You know what, asshole?
If you insult my picture in the camera, fuck
Call the police now
Don't give me the film and the camera
I'm an animal photographer
That's it on me
Dark Saturday
I hate you
Get out, get out
You grow up
I want nothing
Fuck off
Are you at Aborigine?
Neuropath did it
Lemur, however, did this
From PR News in Washington, I'm taking the drug
It's wrong
The advisory panel concludes that the neurologic problems were caused by PR News
Today to turd
Blew themselves up
At least they killed 65 people and injured dozens more
Today, South Korea said it strapped about a third of its 3,200 troops with explosives
A U.S. commander was severely PR'd
Federal health advisors have concluded that serious illness was safe
And now Bob of the Washington PR News
He needs a new PR News in Washington
You're on the air
Oh, hi, Dr. Sinister
Hello, Evan Stang
How are you?
Thanks for baby-tasting
Sitting the show earlier
Oh, that's what I do
That's part of my job description
You'll sit on the right-hand side of Bob for that, I'm sure
And together you two can start World War III
Yep, yep
We're gonna bomb Bernie's place first
Not really, no, I didn't really say that
I found out what it's like to be Jewish recently
I was informed by a person who's been posting on alt-slack
That I'm a satanic Masonic Jew
Your story is coming to an end
My story has a Ç
Haifa!
As the new Neopagan
Enthusiastic
Sie-
Slender
It's my-
God
Cos-
Me
C 좋아하
His name's
Sae-
other than the one true God of Abraham is Satan.
Well, this guy accused me and really, in a way, the whole church of the subgenius of
only making fun of one religion, which offended me.
Yeah, really.
I found that really offensive.
I actually got so tired of making fun of Christians.
I mean, that's why everybody does that.
Yeah.
So, I mean, you know, that's sitcom stuff now.
So I picked on New Agers as much as I could for a long time because they were the other
group that were in my face.
You know, we try to be equal opportunity offenders.
Thanks to Radio Synesthesia there, Dr. Sinister on beautiful WCSB in Cleveland, where actually
a whole lot of this show, Hour of Slack, is produced.
Yes.
One is Hour of Slack number 1028.
The background music we've been listening to is Xerophonics.
That's X-E-R-O-phonics.
Copying machine music found on this album, Xerophonics, by Stefan Helmrich on Sealand
Records.
This one, the one we just heard was the Xerox 5818.
Okay.
Pretty good, huh?
Anyway, friends.
If you want to know more about Xerox, go to Xerox.com.
Or come to the Church of the Subgenius at www.subgenius.com.
Or you can write for free information from Hour of Slack or Subgenius, post office box
181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio, 44118.
For those of you without playback, that's P.O.
Box 181417.
That's P.O.
Cleveland Heights, Ohio, 44118.
Praise Bob.
From PR News in Washington, I'm regrettable and tragic.
General Motors opened fire on a family in a minivan, killing five assembly plants and
a number of other facilities, and eliminating tens of thousands of children to build public
support for the U.S. invasion of Detroit.
This is dishonest and reprehensible PR news in Washington.
PR's bad.
Police in Tacoma, Washington are opening a shopping mall, killing at least three children.
On Wall Street, 1-10-7-8-7-2-2-2-9, Vice President Dick Cheney is sharply criticizing
PR news from Washington.
No.
Silverbacks of Geni that have changed the world.
It's the end of the world.
Irreparable harm to the world.
Environments that have caused in Pakistan earthquakes as well as the tsunami.
The church that is behind the war in Iraq.
The war in Iraq.
It's playing twinkle music.
They were behind.
But X Day.
You were out there.
Michael Pepe, weren't you out there with the Desert Institute, the original X Day?
I wasn't even there.
I was denied admission to that.
But instead, my body was rolled into a roll and blown up.
It is the end of the world.
The world is we know.
We could actually have X Day happen right here on the show.
What if it happened early?
If it happened early, then we'd still be much more busy.
Unfortunately, it didn't even happen on schedule.
Which means the schedule must have been screwed up in the beginning, possibly because all
calendars have been tampered with since the Gregorian system was first invented.
Maybe the whole reason they invented it was to screw up Bob.
By setting their plot in motion thousands of years before it would come to fruition.
And what do we see as a result?
A chimpanzee in the White House.
A gorilla in the premier's robe room.
A pope who's a gigantic vampire pig.
What has this world come to, friends?
These are the end times.
These are the end days.
The last days.
I hope.
Wouldn't that be nice?
The world as we know it is the end times.
Some people are more optimistic about that than I am.
A new one.
It looks like Bob's helicopter is coming in to the top of the station.
Yay, Bob's here.
About time.
He usually avoids being around shows where you are posted.
I don't think he's going to land, yeah.
Why is that?
You're just going to hover past him.
I'm going to hover past him for about three hours.
That quad-vulfer gun I have up on the roof.
I've got a reception from that.
Couldn't be that silver bullet lodged between his two ribs just above his heart.
Couldn't be those other bullets stuck in his skull preventing him from doing his math.
They have in the beautiful script, they say puzzling evidence on the sides of those bullets.
The pain of being him and having him.
Is that a chimpanzee quad?
He's a chimpanzee.
And then he was on that floor.
That shrapnel wound.
While he was on acid, I understand.
The shrapnel entered his brain and told him he's got to get into radio.
This was, as I understand, and then he had to take heroin to get over the effects of the
What is Pepe babbling about over there?
Some kind of weird acid radio UFO story.
Actually, you know folks, you have a rare opportunity to talk to the comments.
LSD?
of UFOs on this officially over the edge show although both shows constantly cover UFOs.
An authority, a person who has been in the ship and who has called the show many times
from the mothership.
That explains all the UFO sightings that have been happening in the San Francisco Bay Area
over the holiday.
Especially over Concord.
Have you seen them?
Have you seen those lights in the sky?
Have you been abducted?
Call in and tell us.
Have you spoken to Bob?
Have you been abducted and probed?
She has called in.
She's on the phone.
Oh.
Oh, she just pulled up.
I can't hear anything really.
Did you see the memo?
I can't hear anything.
Did you get that TPS report?
Uh, you'll have to...
Hi?
We'd like you to put that report... the cover sheet on the front of the show, alright?
Yeah.
Wait, what is everybody doing?
We're gonna need you to come in on Sunday.
What happened after the J.D.
You'll have to do a little bit of research.
They took you aboard the ship.
They took you aboard the ship during the weekend.
Yeah.
They took us aboard the ship and they set us in front of these control panels and they
stuck microphones in our faces.
They said, now just start talking, Earthman.
And that was the last thing I remember.
He brings his hands to his throat in a protective motion.
They made it seem like it was just a dream.
I think mine is off.
They made it seem like it was just wishful thinking.
I don't think that I'm on.
They made it seem like I was just some po-buckers looking for attention.
Yes, I can drink more wine and stay sober than all the human enemies in Asia.
Yee-haw.
That's blowout.
I am a more ale.
I am a Kamado dragon.
I am the killer whale, breathed of its pup.
I have a triple backbone.
I was sired by the wolf man.
Give me all your slack.
I told Jesus I wouldn't go to church and he shook my hand.
I have my own personal saviors.
I change them every hour.
I don't need to be a slave.
I don't need to have sex with if there's life after death.
I want to know if there's even any frigging slack after death.
I am a galdarned visionary.
I see the future and the past in comic books and wine bottles.
I eat black holes for breakfast.
I bend my jeans and wiggle my DNA with the sheer force of my mighty will.
I steer my own galdarned evolution.
I ran out of heaven and sold it to hell for a profit.
I'm enlightened.
I achieved Urbana and took it home with me.
Yip, yip, yee-yee.
I'm so ugly the speed of light can slow me down and gravity won't up-net my cuffs.
When the rapture comes, I'll make them wait.
They'll never clean my cage.
Now give me some more of, tape runs out.
From PR News in Washington, I'm not filling prescriptions for contraceptives.
President Bush said efforts by the US and allies have helped 400,000 sub-people get AIDS in China.
We're working on it.
We're working with our partners to expand condoms correctly.
Democrats continue to delay the ability to stand up.
Looking at Wall Street, 951097126121261.
The Office of Federal Fannie Oversight hit a record high this year, last year.
The United Nations says this is PR News Washington.
She's got big bobs, daddy.