Who's there?
The subgenius, the power of...
SWAG!
Now I know all about everything.
What? Yeah, yeah, yep, yeah, yeah!
I named a man about a story by Stoomson Tilly Ted
Mermaid found a cub, his fur like a deer bound
And then some dad cute, he wish they won food
And Groob and Blubbubble come and grab the groom of two
Thank-ly-mer!
Oh yes dear friends, we're going to 23X Day
Right in our own homes!
And much of this episode is the first hour of the first day
Of the first X Day that was held entirely online
By teleconferencing
And it started this way
On July 5th, 1998, 7 AM
When we all have hangovers
Wotan's judgment will take place in the form of what the pre-scriptures call
The Advent of the Angelic Host
Like any other prophet, Bob preaches about the end of the world
Only his predictions are just a little different
July 5th, 1998
At 7 AM to be exact
The men from Planet X, as the news media will call them
Will arrive to rupture the subgeniuses
The true believer subgeniuses
Up into the escape vessels of the sex goddesses
And believe it or not, plenty of people
4,000 of them so far and more every day
Have already joined up
Suddenly the joke has become serious
And profitable
Your standard religious rip-off, right?
But can anybody take this stuff seriously?
Dear Bob, it's time to close my eyes
Remember now
It's no surprise
If I should be found dead someday
I'll think that you were in the way
Oh, gimme Bob
Confusing that face
With my own
Can't remember my place
Bob's role on this planet
High profit, little return
Is to see that the Earth is not sold
On that glorious or terrible day
We call X-Day in 1990
What year?
I didn't say what year it is
Oh no
Nineteen something
I haven't had my hearing aids on all day
So you forgot what he said?
Yeah, I actually
I'm gonna run get them in a second
They're nearby, next to my bed but
I had to go to the
Get a CAT scan this morning
In the next town over
And I got there
I realized I don't have my
Ear bones
And everybody's wearing masks
So everything sounds like
Vrrr, vrrr, vrrr, vrrr
That can be rather disconcerting
Yeah, I'm gonna go get my hearing aids
You guys
Reverend John Shirley has his hand up
Let me pull John in for you
So's Modemac
Actually, for all we know, everybody is
But this is the very first show
So we have to stick with that
We're professionals for the first twenty minutes
Oh, well, that's
That's
Man, I should
I should step back
Cause I'm
You're the only one who really knows what he's doing
Hey, John Shirley
Let me see if I can assist you here
He's down there
I asked him to start his video
There we go
And I'm going to ask him to unmute
It's funny to ask a mutant to unmute
Right
Unmute
I never thought of it that way
What you
Mutate can't
I can't unmute
I'm mutated
I'm unmutated
How am I gonna unmute?
Mutate can't
If you want that raise, son
You're gonna have to unmute
I tried, I tried
I really did, too, man
I
There was a period in my life
When I tried to unmute several times
Yeah, me too
When I was twelve
I burned all the comic books
That I had drawn in elementary school
To prove to myself that I wasn't gonna be a weirdo anymore
Did it work?
One time I quit smoking pot
To prove I could quit smoking pot
And once that happened
I started smoking pot again
I proved I could do it
You know?
That was my only point
After a certain point, you know
You realize you can't unmute
And
But you can wear the masks of insanity
Which was Philo's way of saying
You have to act normal
Or you have to act like a dumb shit
There's also the asks of insanity
Where you just go up to people
And you ask them the question that
Will set them off
So then they can do all the talking and
They'll think you're a good listener
And you're real clever and sympathetic
That has worked for me
That would be insane
I've got standing invitations
To several famous people's houses
Because I listen to their wives
Without opening my mouth once for a whole hour
So that they didn't have to listen to her
Well, it was that the wife wasn't used to anybody
Listening
While they jabbered
And I didn't have anything better to do
I was trapped
I put these crystals on my PowerPoints
It's a messenger, hold on
I was going, where'd Motormat go?
And then I realized, oh, he's on the page
I wasn't expecting him to be
Phil's HR
Well, you can teach us how to cook
If it gets really boring
People can learn stuff on a seminar like this
What kind of things can they learn, Dr. Drummond?
There's one of those asks
There's a long tradition of the story of the
Straight man in a comedy troupe
But we're not limited to just the straight man
We can have a whole troupe of just straight men
Also hate men
It's good to have the straight man be
Just everyone on the street that you happen to encounter
That's your straight man
Or your boss
Your boss is actually the butt of your humor
Can you be a straight man if you're gay?
Reverend, there's a stigmata
Hi, Philo
Hi
Hi, Becky
Hi, Sting
Hey
We're Facebook friends
We are Facebook friends
Well, I don't have that many
I've only got about 200 or so friends
I'm real careful about that
I only will put on people that I either know face to face
Or maybe if I've known them for 25 years
Right
Oh, there's Hal
It's Hal
You have to be swimming in a canoe with him
Before you put him on there
Hal, here is the reverend
Hello, Hal
Dominique Stigmata
And there's
And that's raw eggplant to everyone
Raw eggplant?
Man, I feel special
Raw, says raw eggplant
And there's Hal with his
With his
With his sacred Ask Dr. Hal
Yes
Ascot
Fez
The Ascot Dr. Hal
It's a Fez
The Ascot
Fez of Dr. Hal
The Fez what says
You have your shoulder, Philo
Can you hear us, Dr. Hal?
Yes, how about me? Can you hear me?
We can hear you exquisitely
You sound wonderful
Well, opinions vary, but...
Well, it's funny how the blue screens work
They work fine for some of us
Philo is a floating head about half the time
Because he's a green shirt
You mean in life or do you mean on Zoom?
Both
John Shirley looks like the invisible man
About halfway through the process
With his paint wearing off
This is the secret
I'll show you
There, you see my green screen?
That's the secret
That's everything you need
Just a sheet
Any color really
Because you can match the color
I'm kind of liking my solarization effect
Even though I didn't intend it
I kind of like how it works
There's a lot of people
It's like a 1970s special effect
Since I have a green screen
I have a picture of what's behind it
On the green screen
Ah
Well, Onan has something like that too
I saw the picture of Onan's little special set yesterday
And Philo's just wearing his green screen
So his head ends up on these other characters' shoulders
He's on a statue right now
There we go
That's uncanny the way that works
Well, once again we're talking to the viewing audience
And not any kind of radio audience
So screw you radio listeners
You can't see any of this green screen stuff
That's what you get for not spending your 35 bucks
And joining the church
You're missing out on the mind-breaking special effects
Well, the other thing they're thinking is
Well, I don't hear any ladies' voices
I thought X-Day was supposed to be a bunch of topless babes
I thought I heard a ladies' voice
There's babes here
But they're, you know
They're topless
I could take my shirt off
I've got pretty good tits nowadays
Well, I'm gonna leave it up to Joyce
But I've got five bucks that say she doesn't take her shirt off
Oh, you're so smart!
I was like, I see the computer reading it
I love Smart Chicks, by the way
Can we make a song about Smart Chicks?
Smart chicks
So smart chicks
Give me a bad
Smart chicks
The smarties
Bravia
Maybe contacts
Smarties
Smart chicks
Those smart girls
And by the way, we like smart guys, too
Those smart guys
Ooh
Going down the hallway
Those smart girls
Meeting up the wrong way
Those smart guys
Going down the hallway
Those smart girls
Better stay away
Those smart guys
They're out looking like they know something
Mm-hmm
It's so funny
Like they know something
Those smart guys
It's so cute
Those smart girls
Now watch out for those smart girls
Better watch out for those smart girls
Because they're all smart chicks
Watch out
For those smart chicks
Those smart guys
Those smart girls
Watch out
Always tripping the girls
The smart girls
Those smart girls
They don't
Learn more than
Both
Watch out
Those smart
Girls
You gotta watch out
To learn more
That's right
Learn from a motherfucker
They're going to learn
Doesn't matter if you're a guy or a girl
Why don't you just learn
From that smart girl
Or that smart guy
The subgenius kids
Did that song smart chicks
And they were
At x day but not singing
Although I think
They sang that during a zoom
Subgenius meeting
Which those happen every week
For members
More of the subgenius kids will be coming up
But now
Back to 23x day
Day one hour one
I'm wearing a Dallas
Paleontological society
Shirt
I had to go into town today
That has much good magic
You don't want to wear your
Bob
I'm wearing a shirt
Into town
Because the profile people
Come after you
I wore a shirt today
That at first glance
Looks astoundingly
Offensive
It's John Carpenter
See
And it's
It's
They
John Carpenter
But it's like the Carpenter
Yes
It's the
They live characters
See
Right I get it
Oh
That is pretty cool
I didn't realize it was the
They live characters
That's pretty cool
Yeah well see when I first saw the t-shirt
I thought they were making some bust on
Karen Carpenter
And her anorexia
She starved herself
Yeah I thought
I thought they were busting on that
And I thought it was funny for that level
But then I realized it was John Carpenter
Why not both?
Sure
But it was
For a second there
It was the darkest bit of humor
I'd seen in a long time
Go figure
Then they
They remade They Live on a budget of about 20 times greater than that and called it The Matrix
They Live was a great documentary
Haley said yes indeed
Expose of the Reagan administration
I told my kids it was a documentary
Stan did Wee get in?
Yeah where's Princess Wee?
I don't know
She's heard off screen
Turning in comments
She might have been in the movie
With Mark Wiel climber
And got some
I've wanted to die
I don't know
Wee putting that off
I've lost my hearing
A kid who had an limp
dinosaur turns into a fossil dinosaur. So there you have the question of, was there a zombie
dinosaur in between those phases? And do robots also, do robots have ghosts when they expire?
I'll turn that over to the panel. Do robots have ghosts? I can tell you about the dinosaurs.
I don't know about dinosaur zombies, but they definitely turn into ghosts. And as ghosts,
they're still heavy enough to leave footprints. Because along with the clear live dinosaur tracks,
I suppose could be zombie dinosaurs as degraded as they are. We also really do have ghost dinosaur
tracks. Are you referring to the article in the Prehistoric Times which said that dinosaur tracks
aren't deep enough? Did you see that particular article? What were they claiming about?
Well, they're the ghosts that only leave a shallow track.
Yeah, right. Well, we have tracks made by ghost dinosaurs. They're blurry.
And I used to just joke that they were ghost dinosaur tracks. Until I saw, I started noticing
in photographs that were taken during certain periods of dryness versus wetness in the creek,
the little depressions would become more clear if they had a little mud in them.
And I realized they probably were dinosaur tracks. They've just been exposed for a thousand years,
and now they're just these smudges.
Yes, they weather.
Only a thousand years?
Only a thousand years of exposure, and millions of years preserved before the time of exposure.
Right. The tracks at the state park, some of the oldest ones are gone now, but new ones are exposed
every day.
They're gone now, but they're still there every time there's a flood.
Do you think that the dinosaur ghosts actually felt pain?
I don't know about that, but they definitely left smudge-like tracks.
They might have felt existential pain.
What if it was wintertime, and it's cold outside, and they're having a walk, leaving their tracks?
They might be tiptoeing more, you know?
Dr. Drummond brings up the ghosts.
The dinosaur ghosts were pointing Sartre to one another.
These dinosaurs that were over here are now over there.
Yeah, that's the whole point.
That's the whole thing, that they go around, they float around like on giant icebergs, and
they visit their friends that way.
Stang, do you remember where the Chilophysis specimens from the Triassic were extracted?
The location, the name of the location?
You'll have to refresh my memory.
Ghost Ranch.
Wow.
Do you recall that?
Where all the major fossils of Chilophysis came from?
Coincidence?
I think not.
There's no coincidence.
There's no money to be made.
May I say.
Other dinosaurs of famous reputation come from hell too.
There were many dinosaurs that had gas bags of lighter-than-air gas on their head or down their spine.
In their bones.
That helped them stand up more erect, you know?
They would just kind of tiptoe.
They would just tiptoe across the ancient world, leaving these little dainty footprints, even
though they were sometimes like a mile high.
And sometimes it was just their toes, you know?
And they would just eat and eat and eat and float away.
They didn't leave as many fossils, but if you can get to the moon, that's where you'll
see.
They wanted to.
They do want to get to the moon.
They all want to leave fossil footprints, don't we?
You can see that kind of stuff.
That's how they filmed the moon landing where the dinosaurs did it.
They did it.
The dinosaur fossils, yeah.
If you read Dr. Doolittle's adventures, you may remember that there were dinosaurs
on the moon when he visited it.
I rest my case.
Inevitably.
First, Dr. Doolittle's garden, then the sequel, Dr. Doolittle on the Moon, where a giant
moon moth comes and carries Dr. Doolittle and some of his friends to the moon, inhabited
by human giants and dinosaurs left over from an early age.
It was the early era.
Would the fact of the moon being a giant abandoned skull explain the hollow ringing sound when
you strike it?
The bell-like sound?
It's definitely hollow and it reverberates when struck, as a special experiment showed.
The moon does?
Yes.
Well, that would be of interest to H.G. Wells.
Well, I remember reading a comic book years ago.
standing in the drugstore next to my house,
which suggested the moon was a giant egg
that was about to hatch.
And it does in the comic book.
What comes out?
Some large griffin-like thing.
That wasn't a comic book.
That was an episode of Super Friends
from Saturday morning.
Well, you've got to feed the monster.
They'll put in an idea from anywhere.
X-Day in 1998.
When the men from Planet X arrive.
Now, it may sound ludicrous.
It may sound ridiculous to many believers out there.
Are you saying they're all nuts, all those people?
Maybe, yeah, maybe.
You once were telling me about Planet X, Dr. Morbund.
Evil on Planet X is more than you could think of.
Evil stalks them.
Every night and day they wait to see the evil they go through.
Do they come down in flying saucers?
Flying saucers are bearing on us.
We don't know what to do.
We're here all alone.
The planets are fading.
The blood is running.
The lights were fading.
And they stalked us one by one.
Today.
This is the Man in Black, here for the Roma Wine Company of Fresno, California.
Fresno!
Are we controlled by secret forces?
Do you ever get the feeling that we're being attacked?
Free will is a joke.
Do people think you're strange?
Do you?
Then you may be on the right track.
Give me slack or give me food or kill me!
Kill me!
That was when Super Friends actually was going downhill.
I mean, it reached its peak with Challenge of the Super Friends.
And then it had a couple of seasons that were, well, less than mediocre.
What kind of a challenge can there be if you're super?
It's like Challenge of the Go-Bots.
The whole thing is rigged from the beginning to end.
It puts the media in mediocrity.
Yes.
There are many with tattoos on this.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
The radio audience can't see the cool thing.
There are so many cool backgrounds that many of us have.
Yes, you can see into subgenius sites here.
The radio audience can send away for a series of magic lantern slides to hold directly in front of the face
and then shine a Klieg light directly into the eyes, one per eye, and burn those images in.
Then they can see them at any time.
Yes.
In fact, they will never...
Whether they want to or not, because they'll be there forever.
Yes.
Also, it's available at no extra cost in the Church of the Subgenius.
If you would care to see the green energy demons, simply look at the sun and wait.
You'll see them.
Well, our president does that.
Yeah.
We can make some branding irons for the eyes, little branding irons for the eyes with images that we like on them.
You know.
And sear them forever with those images.
Oh, I mean, a lot of the younger subgeniuses did that already.
They have tiny bobs tattooed on their eyes backwards.
So it looks right to them.
Eyeball tattoos is a thing in prisons.
That's for real.
Well, is there any chance we are going to get Xanthea Octo-Torona on to discuss paleontology?
Is that all you can think about?
What did you say?
Paleontology.
Did you see the picture she posted yesterday?
How do you like my bob?
She posted a picture of how do you like my bob?
Well, she was posed about like this.
Yes.
She was climbing out of a swimming pool, stark nude.
She has a really good bob on the inside of her arm.
And you could see the top and bottom of her boobs, or her bobs, shall we say.
She's cute.
She's the one who's offered to move Ex Day to a nudist camp in Florida where she resides.
Yeah.
No, she and her dad own a resort in Land of the Lakes, Florida, that is also a nudist
place, and would be perfect for Ex Day, except you can't make noise all night.
The neighbors are a little too nearby.
That's okay with me, personally.
I'm usually in bed up the hill by the time that happens.
No, by the time we get there, the newer generation of subgeniuses will have earbuds and their own noise.
Is it true that good fortune comes to those who join the Church of the Subgenius?
Yes.
It actually is.
Absolutely.
Yeah, I got a visit from good fortune, for instance, because I joined the Church of the
Subgenius, Xanthea Akhtar Shreem came to visit me.
And I found out that, much to my surprise, she's really intelligent, fun.
Nice, subgenius-y lady.
And, get this, she's a fossil hunter.
She knows her geological periods.
Yeah, she does.
And-
How old do we have on here?
Every month.
I don't know, you want to check, take a roll call?
Who is fit for the Hall of Heroes?
The Hall of Heroes.
The Go-Goth has arrived in the attendee.
Yes, yeah, I'm going to pull him in.
Hey, the Go-Goth.
I got him, I got him, I got him.
Oh, shit, I got him.
You know, I asked him if he wanted me to pull him into the panel, and I never waited for
an answer.
I just said, come on in.
He has a presence here.
Yeah, come on.
A lettered presence.
Mono-bro.
I just remembered a dinosaur joke.
Yeah?
Please?
Please do tell.
That would be an old one.
Why do you never hear pterodactyls urinating?
Oh, oh, oh, why?
Because the P is silent.
Oh, oh, oh, that makes perfect sense.
Did the dinosaurs all speak a common dinosaur language, or was it straight, broken up by
the different geological eras, or how does that work?
Well, they did different species.
One species of dinosaur considered all the other dinosaurs to be just animals.
No, they spoke Esperanto.
Their speech was mostly motion and color.
It was like movements and colors with a little bit of sounds and snorts.
We know this from the, what are those historical dinosaur novels, Harry Harrison, is that him?
Oh, the, yes.
The Eden series.
Yeah, the Eden series.
Winter in Eden and so forth.
Were the dinosaurs intelligent in those?
I don't know those books.
There are intelligent saurians who keep the humans in subjugation in those books.
Cool.
Oh, it's really cool.
There's even-
It could only be an improvement.
There's even a scene.
A what scene?
The dinosaur queen adopts a little human pet and has her way with him, and when he
grows up and escapes from the dinosaurs, he can't have sex with normal looking cave
women, but only a hair-lipped girl.
He meets a girl with a severe, you know, cleft palate and falls-
He's sort of like-
She kind of reminds him of the dinosaur queen that introduced him to sex.
The mergue.
But they are quite advanced in their genetic science and can adapt to the environment.
They can adapt other dinosaurs into vehicles and submarines and boats and things like that.
Yeah, all their tools are actually other animals that have been genetically modified.
Their guns are lizards that shoot pellets out of their- poison pellets out of their
butts.
Paralyzed lizards.
Quite deadly.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's amazing.
And they speak with each other by motions and ducking-
Awesome.
And their tails come in real handy.
Right.
It makes it frustrating for a human who doesn't have a tail to try to do the postures that
signal certain tenses and frames.
I'm just telling Mickey that I've learned to do bee dances to tell bees where things
are.
You can do the waggle dance?
And we're trying to first bees, so I do these dances and I get them to come to our flowers,
but you have to do it right and make a noise and it can be learned.
You can't learn-
Exactly.
What happens if you give them the wrong directions though?
Well, actually once I did something wrong and they followed me instead of going to the
flowers and then we had a hundred bees in the house and I had to run from them and these
things can go wrong, but it's just don't-
I'm sure it was not you.
Don't get the dance wrong.
Otherwise, they'll feed you to the queen.
Sounds like a bee movement.
You can't run from them anyway.
They'll catch you.
You ever been bit by a dead bee?
No.
Ever had a beard of bees decide to sting you all at once?
When one stings, they all sting.
Regarding the dinosaurs, there is this comment by a creationist that he once asked, how
come man survived the asteroid and the dinosaurs didn't?
And somebody replied to them, social distancing.
They were 65 million years apart.
That was-
You don't need that microphone.
You don't want the microphone too close to your mouth.
It's kind of too close.
Sorry about that.
Yeah.
Work on that.
Okay.
Our dinosaur ancestors are still judging us for our proximity to the microphone.
Ryan Aldiss wrote a story where one insane person said that humans were derived from
the theropod line of dinosaurs.
There is some kind of line of procession from dinosaurs to the early primates.
They're out?
Yeah.
They had two eyes.
They got two eyes.
That's what we call imperative anatomy.
Everybody has the same skeleton.
Humans and dinosaurs have the same skeleton, the same body plan.
Coincidence?
I think not.
You're either on the insect side, the invertebrate side, or you're on the vertebrate side.
And if you're on the vertebrate side, you've got a pelvis, ribs, skull.
Having a bad time.
Two eyes, four limbs.
There was never any exception to this, except back in the weird Burgess Shale, where all
sorts of alien creatures tried to get started and did not.
Except for the ones that did and became Yeti, which became subgeniuses.
They resembled the great race that H.P.
Lovecraft described, in fact.
Oh, good lord.
The cone beings with the long stalk with the head on the end with multiple eyes are actually
represented by a Burgess Shale creature called Anomalocaris.
Burgess Shale.
Yes, the Burgess Shale is in Canada.
Story ideas.
It was about the...
Stephen Jay Gould wrote a book about it.
If evolution had gone slightly different, you know, we wouldn't have this division into
insects.
We'd have insects and vertebrates that we have now, but we'd have these exotic, strange,
utterly alien things.
When we were admiring the lady, we might be admiring her mandibles.
It's like a different reality.
From a safe distance.
Her sexy mandibles.
Yeah, from a safe distance.
Sexy reality.
Because in the mating process, she will bite off your head.
The passion is there.
Well that does describe Monty.
I don't know if it's my second or third marriages, but never mind.
Never mind.
Let us not dwell on the horrors.
Unspeakable horrors.
Everybody feels real good in Fool City.
Each day brings a new surprise.
Johnny came two thousand miles to Fool City.
Came to see what makes things tick.
Cut his hair and bought new clothes in Fool City.
Finally found his life's ambition, oh.
Kind of doing nothing perfectly.
Diniz styles so gracefully.
His life was so delicious in Fool City.
Outside the Homes on the Street.
Don't stop for you in Wool City.
Someone standing in a doorway.
In Fool City.
Ah,
They open the door and check him out so casually
The music's blasting all night long in the pool city
They recognize his face so it's all right
He said to move or write the dress
Even though someone in a band
The others wait all night standing in the pool city
So hard to make the right friends
You might have to sell some skin
The nights go on forever
The blacks, they all hate the whites
The whites think they're tough but they're not
The boys go out with each other
The girls wanna be amoebas
If you're high, you're in the right place
Pool city
Animal
Seek out their own kind
Shake some hands and take a lunch in pool city
Someone's going to try and tempt you
Listen to all the brilliant bands in pool city
So be now in your bay, let it be it yourself
Ready the objects on the wall
Please let young and motherful old
So come on
And let the music play
The world is fun
Go drink
Snow and wine
And there's the nights when the day should be winning
Pool city
That was Danny Elfman from his So Low album.
That's the name of the album, So Dash Low.
I was listening to that on my way into our tiny, sleepy little town.
And I almost cried with thankfulness that I do not live in Cool City during these strange days.
But in its opposite, sweltering Hamlet.
Phew.
In more ways than one.
In between, we've been hearing stuff from the old subgenius media barrage albums.
But now, frankly, I've played all this other stuff mainly to soften you up for the hard, needy, hard times.
I am with one, Heads and Tails.
And you are listening to Papa Joe's Nugget.
And I'd like to give you a nugget at the center of this episode.
Uh, Papa Joe Mama.
Or more properly, Father Joe Mama's new X Day rant is here.
So, strap-on your tinfoil strap-on and prepare yourself for Papa Joe's Preparation X Day 2020.
Hello friends and welcome.
The sermon tonight is entitled Revolution for Bob
Revolution for Bob
Because let's face it, this summer has been the summer of revolution
In fact, it really seems like the end times
There's a worldwide plague ravaging the population
There's more police brutality than ever before
And we see it over and over again on TV with instant replay
And of course, all the riots and protests
Clashing with the man, looting various stores
And tearing down various statues and yada yada yada
Now, more than a faithful few have asked yours truly
Papa Joe, you're a bomb thrower
You're always preaching about hate this and hate that
Rise up and burn it all down
You do approve of the riots, don't you?
Or at very least the peaceful protests
Well, let's see
Let me answer the second question first
I don't do peaceful protests
I don't believe in no justice, no peace
I just believe in no peace
We've already had thousands of years of their so-called peace
And what has it gotten us?
A conspiracy, that's what
So don't expect me to chill out and let up
Just because the conspiracy throws us a bone
They can keep their bones
In fact, I'm all for throwing their bones right back at them
Starting with their skull and working our way through the bones
Our way right on down their weak little spines
To the tips of their tiny little toes
But now for the answer to the first question
Do I believe and approve in the angry riots?
The answer, dear friends, is both yes and no
I do approve of rising up and taking back that which is rightfully ours
And to use extreme prejudice in order to destroy extreme prejudice
But when I look out and see all the violence
All the destruction of the world
All the destruction and all the marching
I have to ask myself
Why?
Why didn't any of these people stand up and protest
Or fight the system in the name of Bob?
Oh sure, social justice is a good cause
Like the media says
Social justice is more important than social distance
So long as your justice agrees with my justice
And you agree with my justice
And your distance is at least an arm swing away from my fists
But there is a bigger issue than social justice, dear friends
There's an issue bigger than winning in November
And there's an issue bigger than curing the COVID pandemic
And that issue is J.R. Bob Dobbs!
For 23 years he's been waiting for us to rise up
And show the conspiracy bosses who the real boss really is
He spent his entire life lining up an alien armada
To rise up and show the conspiracy bosses who the real boss really is
And rocket all the way to this sneaking globule of dirt
Located in the armpit of the universe
Just to rescue us from this hell on Earth
Was he expecting too much for us to demonstrate just a little faith
That he would return and provide some fifth column resistance
Or outright guerrilla warfare
To make his X-Day invasion a tiny bit easier for the X's overlords?
Jesus H!
No wonder he keeps putting off the final evacuation year after year
It's because he's a little bit too old for that
It's bad enough that most of the sub-Gs are drunk
Passed out or asleep during the 7-day egg cattle call
But this year
Oh, this year
It's even worse
We're finally revolting against this system
And claiming that we're destroying the chains of oppression
And tearing down statues of colonial slave owners
And Civil War slave masters
But!
What about our slave owners?
Why?
There's no mention at all!
About them
Or their modern-day 9-to-5 rent-a-slave conspiracy
Or the daily denial of Dobbsian liberty and slack
In fact, there's no mention of Bob Dobbs in the slightest
It's as if he doesn't even exist
Oh, it makes me sad
Sad to think that on July 5th, just before 7am
Bob's gonna fly down in the first Reconno saucer
To enter our sub-orbit since this time last year
And he'll see all of us
And he'll see all the crowds
He'll see all the smoke
And he'll see all the tear gas and debris
And toppled statues
And he'll think
Finally, finally I can land this ship
And let my people go to the pleasure planet I promised all those years ago
And finally, I can release the shock troops to put this planet out of its misery
But then
Then as he enters NORAD's radar range
He'll start receiving TV and radio broadcasts
And he'll realize this is not a dream
It's not about him
It's about us
And the normals
And the cops
Alack
Alas
Imagine his pain and disappointment
We were so close to salvation
So very close
But we stopped just short of the goal line
If these puny pinks wanted to save themselves
They'd spend less time debating whether to take a knee for the national anthem
And instead would take two knees
For Bob
But, but, but, Bob, Bob, Bob and Joe
This is a good cause
Don't you think Bob will approve of us fighting to make Earth a better place for everyone?
No, I do not
Because Bob is not coming to Earth to make it a better place
He's coming here to take us, his chosen, to a better place
A better planet
Where none of these problems occur
Where none of this pinkness exists
And then just to make sure no pinkness infects anywhere else in the universe
He's going to make Earth a better place
By utterly destroying it
Yes, it's a dirty, Dobbsian duty
But someone's gotta do it
And whatever you do
Don't get nostalgic about it
Because Earth is dying anyway
Even the conspiracy scientists admit we only have a few years left regardless
At least with Bob, not everyone is neutralized
And the billions who are are put out of their misery quickly
Without all the long, drawn-out pomp and circumstance
That's showing a lot more compassion than the conspiracy ever showed us
When the boot was on the other foot
They always piled on the pain and suffering in slow motion
So they're getting much better treatment than they deserve
Of course, now the Bobbies and conspiracy collaborators are getting a little nervous
And starting to murmur and fidget
But Papa Joe, that's all supposed to be a big joke, man
You're sounding kind of serious
You're sounding like a religious fanatic
Newsflash, I am a religious fanatic
And proudly so, because I know what's at stake
You think it's a joke because we told you it's a joke
Because that's the only way we were able to pull this thing off with any element of surprise
And to stay out of prison in the meantime
Fine, it's a joke
Keep telling yourself that
And stop listening to my sermons
Because it's not for you
It's for the faithful
Those truly dedicated to Bob
Those truly dedicated and willing to die for Dobbs
Because nothing, nothing is more important than Bob
Than he is
Not you
Not me
And certainly not them
So don't start getting soft on the humans
Because pink lives don't matter
Now I'm not saying don't attend the protests
And I'm not saying don't riot
But I am saying
If you want real everlasting change
These little demonstrations simply won't do
The only riots and protests that can achieve something that dramatic
Are for Dobbs
And they ain't peaceful nor pretty
Because there's no negotiating or changing the minds of
The conspiracy
It's against their nature to compromise
The only way you change them
Is to destroy them
They not only have the cops
They have the military
And the only way to destroy that
Is with help from heaven
Or should I say the heavens
Because that's where Bob and his alien overlords will drop out of prison
And light this candle
It's not too late to fix our fate
We have up until 6.59am, July 5th
To change the future course of planet earth
We can either keep slamming our heads against the wall
Trying to improve a planet dying of diseases
Climate change and social chaos
Or we can jettison this bitch
And move on to greener, not pinker pastures
I suggest you put that proposition
In your pipe and smile
Or you can just go home
And if you do attend any protests or riots, do it for Bob's sake.
At least buy and wear a Bob's face chin bandana so maybe, just maybe, it will at least look like you're fighting for a cause worthy of his divine intervention.
And we'll find out soon enough if he falls for it or not.
And I'll be cheering you on all the way, because I, for one, am tired of waiting.
Here in the word of Bob, praise Bob.
Amen.
We're tired of your phony fireworks.
Blarzel, you have earned this.
Yeah.
What about this reputed Jesus?
Starfleet that was supposed to have shown up.
As you see, they have just left the hangar deck at Lunar Central and have cleared the airlocks into the colony.
The crowd of scientists and technicians are going wild.
What a space ovation.
Now let's feel another.
Now in celebration of this great occasion, we have planned a lunar party.
We hope all young people throughout the solar system will join us in celebration of this great day.
A.
A in alpha space.
Bob?
Sing it, girl.
Oh.
Who am I?
Who are we Princess Cookie?
We're us
Are we fake? Are we real?
Who determines what's fake and real?
We do
That's right!
And we are for you
We are real
You sound so beautiful
I tried, I tried this for you
Ooh
Do you want to do a real like Willis on the bus or do you remember back in the day where one person says one thing and then the other person steps in like a measure or two measures later doing the same thing?
Around?
Yeah
I actually have a question about Bob for the panel. I had mentioned this a couple of few minutes ago.
You know here we are in the middle of the night.
In the year, in X day of the year of the great Robert Anton Wilson, X day 23.
And is it a coincidence that the year of Ra happens to be the most end times and the most X day like year we have experienced in quite a long time?
Synchronicity is what it is.
The opportunity for a friendly ushering into the church of the subgenius has been extended for decades.
Centuries some might say.
Oh just send a dollar or go to the mall and buy that book.
It's been easy for so long and there's still several listeners who have not joined the church of the subgenius even on their own terms.
So we had a little talk with the Yakutismas and this year we kind of turned up the heat a little bit.
They want to keep a distance.
Well let's let them keep a distance.
If they want to interact with fewer humans and more people.
More of wowm existence.
Well let's give them a taste of that.
Well remember we don't want the humans anyway.
We only want subgeniuses who are latently among the humans.
Hey you guys watch this ad here because I'm getting a little residual from it.
You're getting residuals?
Lucky you.
I wonder how you can do that.
If you find yourself put off by the news.
Just.
Remind yourself or say to yourself.
Ching ching.
I think not.
Not in the sense of disagreement but really I think not.
Don't think about it.
Don't think about these things.
I'm not.
They go away.
I not think.
I think not.
Me no think.
Then you can get to I not and then finally just I.
Me not.
I not.
Me yeah.
Me it.
I no.
I know.
I unt.
The Arc of the Eye.
And then it's so long salute of the eye.
But with the subgenius scimitar you can slice the knot as Alexander the Great did.
Now this 23 X day and the worst year ever.
It's not.
This is just.
Year period.
Do you guys remember last year? Everybody was saying, man, 2019, this is so bad. So many people died. It's going to be better next year. Honestly, don't you remember?
Yeah, it is worse. It can always get worse. It can always get worse.
The bottom can always drop out.
You could be in Dresden on the wrong day in World War II or Hiroshima or on the beaches of D-Day.
You could be in the Black Death in Europe.
Trump could be reelected.
It's going to happen.
Salvation or destruction, friends.
Which would it be?
That was so clear.
That image was so clear.
It was like, you know, it was for many people, it was a breakthrough image, I feel, that he went on and just held on.
The Secret Service came to see me because of that image.
Because of that image? Seriously?
Yes, they did. Because Bob and Kennedy and Buddha and everybody are shooting at a hydra that has one arm is labeled Reagan or any president.
Oh, I see.
And the Secret Service did, in fact, come to my door in 1983.
And said that they asked if I was Doug St. Clair.
Didn't even have my whole name.
I should have said, yeah, yeah, that's right.
You should have said, oh, we've got a lot of crazy artists making pictures.
That's just one of them.
You ought to talk to Hal Robbins.
I didn't make it.
Well, the funny thing is.
Matt Reed is me.
No.
I've seen it in a stark fist.
Made by a great subgenius artist.
That someone at the L.A. airport.
Was showing to people as a takeoff on Hare Krishna.
You know, have you heard the good news?
They show this picture of this person called the Secret Service said they're going to kill the president.
Well, they showed up and saw.
Well, once they looked at my car and my shoes, they knew I wasn't a successful cult leader.
And that's really not very good humor.
So you shouldn't publish that again.
And I thought, well, we probably won't.
I see.
However, it was already in Book of the Subgenius.
Which one week later was reviewed by People magazine.
And what single piece of art did they choose?
To show to millions of people.
But salvation or destruction.
A week after, the Secret Service said, please don't publish that again.
And I went, we won't.
People did.
Millions saw it.
And they actually liked it.
It was one of the best reviews of the book we ever got.
It was in the pinkest magazine.
That great piece of art is by St. John Hagenbrenner.
Yeah.
Yes.
Well, tell us what.
Well, Swami Satellite Weavers.
Yes.
Reverend Stagg, I seem to remember you telling that story.
And then you ended up saying that those Secret Service members left your house as converts
and paid up ministers.
Oh, that made it for a good story.
But they didn't.
They did not.
That was a lie.
Did I say that?
Well, then you better pick up on it.
Did you lie?
Are you actually admitting that you may have lied to us at some time?
He extended the information farther than the deal was supposed.
Exactly.
I only said it because.
In some alternate universe, it did happen.
Anything a subgenius says automatically is part of our doctrine, as you know.
That itself is part of our doctrine.
This is the first Dobbs head that I've ever owned.
I got this in 1982.
I still have it.
Old black guacamole.
It's got the early address on it.
1980 copyright.
Black and white.
And it's black and white.
And I even wrote my name on it.
The little dots.
In case I had to loan it out so somebody could give it back to me later.
Because they could just like ask.
You were smart.
Hey, where's the on-hand?
Now that's so common, you just walk up to any hipster and cut the Dobbs head tattoo
off their skin.
You got one.
I do.
I like that idea.
And then frame it.
It doesn't matter because then they're going to be like, oh, I'm going to get a tattoo.
Then they've got a Bob shaped scar, which is what they want anyway.
That's like the next level.
With some secrets.
Now we fight.
Thank you.
Thank you, buddy.
And that was the Psychoskeletons.
Tomorrow's Tomato, name it that song.
For more information, friends, check out subgenius.com.
Yes, that's subgenius.com.
And praise Bob.
Bob!
Gee, I want to try triology.
All the kids are doing it, Mom.
There's a Dobbs head in every bar.
Yes, an embedded Dobbs head of soap
inside a bar.
A bar of translucent soap.
You can see Bob lurking inside.
And it tells fortunes
as you rotate it swiftly under the water,
lathering away the conspiracy smudge
and other schmata.
If the Dobbs head comes up at the end
in the true perfect pipe placement position,
you'll have good luck all day.
If it comes up the other way,
20 more years of winter.
That's triologysoaps.com.
It comes in every flavor and scent.
That's not nonsense.
It's almost every scent you can think of.
And they all have funny names.
Praise Bob.
And praise triologysoaps.com.
Try is spelled with an I.
Free your radio and your mind will follow.
Free.
Waleedan friend.
Brr.
Slack every Thursday at 11 a.m. Praise Bob and praise Freethink Radio.