Return to the swelling days of the Old West this weekend with Mr. Rory Tellers on a big
hiatus right, as they celebrate their 100th anniversary. Yes, the 100 days in the business
means a lot to the men and women of Mr. Rory's, and this weekend means a lot to you, too.
It means Old West prices, like a Big Rory for $1.79 or a Killer At Burger for $1.78.
It means Old West decor, from the cattle skulls on the floor and about bullet holes in the
drive-up speaker box. And it means Old West excitement, too, like the thrill of a bloody
shootout as man matches wits with hyena, or the spectacle of a herd of stampeding hyenas.
Have you силен yet?
First of all, is all that good Mr. Rory's food.
Whether your favorite is hyena tongue or tail, you'll enjoy it even more at a Mr. Rory's Arizona-baked hyena tribe drive-thru.
See your phone book for the one nearest you.
Some people need to be mashed under a large rock, man. You're probably one of them.
Well, you're listening to the arm-twisting adventures of your personal friend Huey on the bastard son of Poop Eye to the Gods.
You're listening to KPFT and Houston 90.1 FM.
The radio station that transmits my sick mind through electrical waves into a box in your personal home.
From the largest stock in Texas.
Hey, NON, 90.9 in Dallas, Texas.
And could express every emotion with it.
Love.
Hate.
Anger.
Chagrin.
Even contempt.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
You're the beta king.
It was only fantasy.
I don't see that as being something you can look at as being tangible right now.
I don't...
Well, I've lost my equilibrium, my car keys and my pride.
By this time, your fingers should be moving more quickly to the desired keys.
Also in...
Oh, what can I say?
What can a person like myself say to a vegetable?
But the answer is simple, my friends.
Just call...
...and I'll...
...leave this...
...all the intergalactic laxative will get you from here to there.
Relieve you and believe me without a worry or care.
...shhh...
...shh...
This is Lou Grubb for Lou Grubb Chevrolet.
Listen.
We've got some fine resale cars here at 27th Avenue in Camelback.
And what's more, if you'll stop out at 27th Avenue in Camelback to see us, you can ask...
Ah, yes, dear friends.
This is your host, Lou Grubb.
The subgenius radio ministry hour of slack on KNON 90.9 in Dallas, Texas.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
I'm amazed that upper tape deck works despite...
See?
When George got off his show, he said,
Now, that upper tape deck, stay away from that thing.
It's warbling again.
And see, friends, there's nothing wrong with that upper tape deck at all.
It's playing that Walter Carlos stuff just fine in the background.
Oh.
And maybe next time, I hope that next week, that it's...
We know for sure it's going to work.
I wonder if there's any way...
I bet I could distort this just by flipping this little switch.
Yeah, there we go.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Well, friends, you'll see next week, I'm going to be out of town.
And Willa Dobbs is going to take over the show for one week.
It'll be his first time on this ugly, ugly board, this mixing board here.
But, yeah, I've got to go.
I'm going on a special mission for Bob, so to speak.
But that doesn't mean that you bobbies can be breaking into my house and stealing Bob's skull.
Or rather, the 1984 Bob's skull.
I'm sure he's got a new one by now.
Because the house...
That subgenius castle will be guarded by both the Beast...
That's actually my Doberman Pinscher's name.
Both Beast and the Willa Dobbs will be in there.
Never mind the Beast, dear friends, but beware the Willa Dobbs.
Because he...
Oh, Willa Dobbs, he looks...
You know, you hear him in the background a lot.
And hopefully in the foreground this next time.
And you can't tell much from a voice, I guess.
But he basically looks like Arnold Schwarzenegger,
only with glasses.
Sort of like me.
Those of you who know me would pretty much know what I'm saying.
So, uh, you just...
You just better beware, dear friends.
Well...
Uh, you can call the Willa Dobbs tonight at 828-9500 or 823-7490.
And meanwhile,
we will continue...
with...
the horror.
Somehow, actually, I need to shut off that music
and get something a little bit more fitting in here.
Do you know what I mean?
Boy, no kidding.
We needn't dwell on those other bobs, dear friends.
We'll have to talk about the other bobs tonight.
In fact, actually, I guess...
Dr. Dili Lama,
who is here tonight,
I think could also help us talk about
the other bobs.
The bobs who are coming.
Uh, once again, we're gonna talk about
Robert Anton Wilson coming into town.
Uh, where and when is that,
my dear friend?
That will be Friday, August 7th,
at 8 PM at the Scottish Rite,
Hospital Auditorium.
You know, that's down there off Oaklawn and Maple.
Oh, friend.
You wanna make...
You wanna go see Robert Anton Wilson,
uh, bespeak the hideous truths
that you wanna hear so bad,
and the ones that you don't wanna hear, too,
and the ones that you can't possibly truly hear.
Or your ears will hear,
but only the...
truly attuned will listen.
Truly listen.
Are you aware?
So do, uh, whip on down there.
That mighty writer,
that's what he is, by the way,
for those of you who didn't know,
Robert Anton Wilson is a writer,
but he's a writer who's pried open the shell
surrounding the secrets of life and death,
and made them funny.
And also quite educational.
An agent of slack.
An agent of true slack.
Slack.
What is it?
Where is it?
We're going to try to figure that out now.
Oh, by the way, I should mention,
earlier tonight, uh, what you heard,
the second version of the
It's Not Just The...
rant from the great G. Gordon Gordon,
the mercenary of Bob.
He shipped that up from Brazil,
from, uh, the...
the town of Araruama,
where he lives,
and where I hope to go
for fun
next Easter.
And then again,
when they give us $40 million
to do the subgenius movie,
we'll all go down there to write the screenplay.
Of course, we'll party for six weeks
and then write the screenplay on the last day,
but that's what you want, friends!
That's the only true way to do it.
That's the...
This coming up here is called
The Blast Supper
by Reverend G. Gordon Gordon.
G. Don Truby.
Uh, put your headphones on for this, dear friends.
D-Li Lama just did, and he knows,
because he's...
he's b-b-b-been around.
Hail Eris.
Hey, there.
Yes, yesterday's brains are here.
A slow but steady intelligence
leading me by the nose...
...to the table.
This war hath spread.
You catch, eagles?
You must watch my feet, first,
and then the croc shall strike three.
Inflicting heavy casualties...
As you are to lunch.
I'll take care of this.
I brought my plastic.
Simon Peter assigned it to me
as I flopped out my wallet.
His bulging, belching,
bronze-tan voice
carried through the cafe...
Intentionally.
...trying to impress the boss, eh, Pete?
Paul retorted.
His bracketed, closed,
bombshell voice...
Blast!
...booming...
...across...
...the Neverwax floor tiles.
Boys!
Jesus!
...cleared his trout accordionly.
Aye, but I like it drunk.
Maggie moaned to a greasy pair of glasses.
Jesus donned the spectacle
and declaimed the onside click.
When in Rome...
...do the Romans...
...Jesus jousted...
...indeed, the Roman enumerators...
...bucket man!
...John announced from under the table.
John found his fork...
...and thrust...
...his precepts...
...in a must...
...unkeenly manner...
...upon his stable-mates.
They count on us for an explanation.
John jumped.
But Judas couldn't explain his order.
And the waitress confused did utter.
Look, mister, you must tell me what you want,
or I'll be forced to use my influence.
I can't read your mind.
Then Judas spent his second foot breathing in
and had a strange vision.
He was holding the bearded lord...
...in his wrists...
...bravel-style...
...wracking to a crazy beat...
...faster and faster...
...than slower.
He heard Cab Calloway singing...
...Mini the Moocher.
He smelled the hearty wrath...
...of twice-burned toast...
...and trembling...
...egghead...
...earnesty.
He touched and tasted a thousand things...
...and was unsure and wondrously proud...
...into the street...
...to find wherefore...
...and what not...
...on the bench.
That's pronounced guilty.
The others tittered and toastered.
But Jesus saveth not the hot...
...saveth not...
...in the pit.
...of his ugly mug.
The sky rained a million volts...
...of lightning bolts and...
...and forty buckets...
...of blood and beer.
And finally Maggie skittered over...
...to our booth...
...heaving and hoeing...
...and the streaming...
...steaming heap of feast.
She glared straight into the...
...belly soul...
...of our savior.
Questing, you order this weather?
Red beans and rhymes in yesterday's brains...
...read the two-inch video monitor...
...implanted firmly...
...in the forehead...
...of our one-eyed waitress...
...Maggie Magdalene...
...Littowitz...
...heh, heh, heh...
...Simon Peter...
...cuffed his face...
...to the side of my mouth...
...and whipped...
...I told you we should have taken him...
...to the awful house...
...their food is fresher and...
...cheaper too...
...but let him look at his men...
...you...
...customer implicated by circumstance...
...you fresh-faced...
...side of bacon...
...too many rowers scraped the bowl...
...I could see...
...feel...
...and touch...
...his healing glaze...
...as it shot clean through the tabular sails...
...in Maggie's hot sliding side slots...
...Thomas touched it too...
...and eagerly agreed...
...yes...
...they damn well...
...should have eaten elsewhere...
...but...
...hell...
...here was water...
...silver...
...leave now?
...why, they'd look like acids...
...they'd break my heart...
...my glasses too...
...Matthew decided to know men...
...so with their...
...heads...
...on their knees...
...they broke brains...
...in the house...
...of the rising one...
...it was over easy...
...all around...
...black coffins...
...all of eyeballs...
...a rim...
...an English translation...
...please...
...mouse watered...
...at once...
...and as one...
...but before feasting...
...as always...
...Jesus rose...
...he ass ended...
...and performed a...
...a mackerel...
...Luke faked a knowing...
...and a mackerel...
...a young smile...
...of adoration...
...as he had been hoping...
...for his favorite...
...the Messiah's interpretation...
...of Chinook salmon...
...fresh water...
...the boys ate...
...feverously...
...Judas...
...the joker...
...choked on thirty slivers...
...as usual...
...he got a big pat...
...on the backside...
...for his deep trouble...
...the lettuce braid...
...and everybody...
...said it was Grace's fault...
...for extolling the stone...
...in front of the shameless...
...steel vault...
...the dirty dozen...
...of ordered donuts...
...in haste...
...they ordered bagels...
...dry...
...then they ordered...
...many hundreds...
...of hot dogs...
...then they ordered...
...the tube steaks...
...to jump...
...through...
...the pastry hoops...
...sit up...
...big...
...roll...
...over...
...and pop...
...onto their...
...twelve...
...twirling...
...tons...
...imagine...
...their surprise...
...when the dogs disobeyed...
...and spelled out...
...on Peter's placemat...
...the word...
...niall...
...up...
...yes...
...the instantaneous...
...nash...
...out...
...teeth...
...sounded...
...like a lion cub's...
...damalash...
...derby of the salt...
...a smoky robin's nest...
...arose from the brown...
...jane...
...and haloed them all...
...with the foul paw...
...that eventually settled...
...and circled around...
...Judy's bolting purse...
...you foot the bill...
...they all bawled...
...at the Jude...
...who had began...
...to get under their skin...
...to make it better...
...they all...
...were...
...all...
...fall down...
...drunk...
...and asleep...
...and Jesus...
...was white...
...as a sheep...
...he knuckled under...
...and blazed...
...I'll never eat out...
...again...
...and then he ate...
...his words...
...in remembrance...
...of red...
...bees...
...and...
...rhyme...
...s...
...
repeatedly on the Hour of Slack radio show.
Plus, Archdoctor St. Margaret Moser,
high priestess of the cult of Chilkat from Austin, Texas.
And J.R. Bob Dobbs will be there.
Yes, he's alive, friends.
The San Francisco cool guy Bob may be dead,
but my Bob isn't dead.
Is yours?
Unfortunately, local broadcaster Ivan Stang
will be unable to attend.
But, friends, you can hear Stang on any radio.
Now these incredible ministers can spit fire,
heal the sick, and sicken the healthy.
Boom, Shakalamaka.
Way to this little snake here, son.
August 8th, 8 o'clock, bar of soap,
across from the Fair Park gate.
Praise Bob, free at last.
I'm not a Bobby in the bunch, dear friends.
Actually, despite all the nasty, nasty things
that I said about Buck's D-Bible last time,
I want you.
I want you all to go out there to the bar of soap.
That's the night after Robert Anton Wilson,
who is on August 7th.
You want to go see old Buckaroo and the Buckeyes
at the bar of soap on August 8th.
Oh, hold it, hold it.
Let me give you.
Reverend Stang, just a little point here.
Robert Anton Wilson will be giving a lecture
on Friday night, and then he's going to give a seminar
in the afternoon from 1 till about 6 o'clock.
At the same place, Scottish Rite Hospital.
And then I'm pretty sure that old Robert's going to end up
going to the D-Bible to see Buck naked
and all the other local sub-geni.
And did I understand that you won't be there?
Is that true?
Oh, I'm not allowed to be there.
This is an anti-Stang D-Bible.
Honest to God, it is.
Buck and I are friends on a personal basis,
but on a professional basis, we are bitter, bitter enemies.
And I refuse to appear on a stage.
I refuse to appear on a stage.
With anybody who takes sub-genius so,
I mean, so unseriously.
You know, I mean, this is a religion.
And apparently some of these other people
seem to think of it as some sort of a comedy thing.
I'm glad to see you sticking by your principles
of schisms in the church.
Yeah, it was, of course.
I mean, and I can no more tell Buck not to do a D-Bible
than I could tell, oh, say, the New York Bobbies
or the Philadelphia Bobbies not to do a D-Bible.
I'm not Bob.
You're...
Uh...
Neither are you.
Not really.
And I don't want to be.
Don't get me wrong.
I wouldn't want to be Bob.
However, over the swinging love corpses,
I should start talking about my D-Bibles, friends.
These are the ones that Buck doesn't even know about yet.
And we've been working towards that
with the kind help of David Hines,
St. David Hines, we should say,
down at the Stark Club, of all places,
has been donating us video editing time.
And we've been doing a lot of work
with the mighty Reverend Court Holland, SLK,
and I have been down there.
Well, last night, in fact, till four in the morning,
we were down there editing the subgenius video,
Finishing Touches,
and that video will be world premiered
at the Dallas Museum of Fine Arts
sometime in October.
And you'll hear about it
because it's going to be one of their main featured thing.
It'll be the main Saturday night thing
and their big video festival
that Bart Weiss is setting up.
So you'll finally see the world premiere
of the...
the much promised...
I mean, this is what's been taking...
been holding up the Stark fist
is this mighty videotape.
And oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
You wouldn't believe the stuff.
We got hold of some footage last night, friends,
of J.R. Bob Dobbs as a six-year-old millionaire.
And when you see it,
you will fall down on your knees.
You will be knuckle-walking to Jerusalem
when you see this incredible video presentation,
as well as, of course, the deep Bible to go with it.
And this will...
this will also be world premiered
at the Stark Club at some point or another.
We're not sure.
Probably also in October.
I mean, that means we have to finish this thing by then,
you see, friends.
We're putting a deadline on ourselves.
So I know that I can't compete with Buck naked at the...
What's the name of that little tiny hole-in-the-wall club?
The Bar Soap.
Yeah, with the...
I mean, I know I'm selling out.
Jeez, the Dallas Museum of Fine Arts.
Here we are telling everybody,
this is a religious...
That's the Museum of Art.
They put it in the...
That's right.
The Dallas Art Museum,
whatever the hell it's called.
They put it...
They're going to put it on and call it art.
But, you know, I guess, you know,
the Sistine Chapel was the subgenius video of its day.
You know, the Sistine Chapel ceiling by Michelangelo.
That was the equivalent in those days.
And so now we have to...
You know, we can't show you the videotape on television.
Because it's too nasty and bobful.
Hey, listen, you can hear him in the background.
Squirting.
Squirting endlessly in his endless dream.
He lives on in every one of those sandworms.
Bob is coming, friend.
But, yeah, I really...
You should go to Buck's revival.
You should go to Robert Anton Wilson's revival...
The thing.
Buck does devivals.
I don't prefer...
I don't like to use the term revival for what I do.
Because I like to think that it revives people.
I think Buck's definition is exactly accurate.
Absolutely accurate description of what he does.
And, friends, I do think you ought to go ahead.
I mean, it's cheap.
And also, there are...
I mean, I believe Reverend Chastity Belt is going to be there.
And, of course, the Hell Swami.
And Pope S. Cecilia.
You know, so there's people with whom I'm not having a terrible...
...fewed right this minute.
So...
Gosh.
I get so carried away sometimes.
Just, you know, having this soapbox.
Imagine the temptations, friends, to say tasteless things.
It's...
About a rotten day.
Oh, boy.
Oh, that's what I say.
Because that's what the word of Bob says.
I tell you, friend, there's no slack.
There's no slack.
I tell you, in this world, in this flesh, in this devil, there's no slack.
And if you can't whoop it, go ye down, my friend.
That's what I said.
Go ye down.
There's nothing that says you can't.
The devil don't have a rule book.
That's right.
The devil.
The devil does not have a rule book.
He is not humanistic.
He is not pacifistic.
And he owes you money, my friend.
That's right.
The devil.
The devil owes you money, and so does Uncle Sam.
You have to recognize the devil just like you recognize Uncle Sam.
Now, I'm going down there to pay taxes.
As far as I'm concerned, I might as well be paying taxes to the devil.
I'm sorry, but that's just the way things are.
It's a test of faith.
And that's why God put the devil down here to see if you can tell the difference between the devil and Uncle Sam.
Let there be slack.
And I want to know, if you can tell the difference...
If you can tell the difference between the devil and John Birkeland, the devil and Shelly Beeman, the devil and Dennis Bennett.
Because these people are just the first three on the list of pledgers to the hour of slack who have not paid their dues, dear friends, to the word of dogs.
There's two stangs.
God almighty.
There's not enough room in this world for...
Friends, I want you to pay up those pledges.
You know, I don't want to have any of the money, you know, I want to have the money to put into the show.
I want to have the money to pay up the money that's being made to the hour of slack.
Because the station really needs money right now.
And not only that, I need the status.
George's show, which precedes this show, has gotten twice as much money in as the hour of slack.
Now, how do you think that makes us look?
Of course, they're on twice as long every Sunday night.
But that doesn't matter.
I want to see every cent, every red cent.
And I don't want to have to have, you know, the bad Bob show up at your door, friends.
Caprice?
Now, Caprice, I know you can spare that $5.
Ed?
Edgar Cayce out there in the before life.
I mean, he's a saint.
He's healed many thousands of people magically.
But he hasn't paid that $10.
And in Bob's eyes, he's doomed to hell.
All right.
Mother Teresa here.
She could only spare $25,000.
And we haven't seen a penny of it.
Now, Mother Teresa, doomed.
Doomed to an eternity in hell itself.
Because she hasn't paid up to this show, despite all the other good things she may have done.
And, I mean, I'm seeing some names on here.
These are supposed to be friends of the church enemies.
And I just, I mean, I ain't.
I don't want to turn into that old drunk preacher again.
Now y'all point fingers that'll take care of my sister with your
You're blessing your touch down on me, you're blessing your touch down on your family.
She's got the perfect makeshift cup.
And she says a good faith, doing what you're doing.
If you didn't know?
You didn't make her milk.
God knows what to do.
And you know why?
He didn't look for her in her own white coat.
the church enemies.
And I just, I mean, I don't want to turn into that old drunk preacher again.
You know, I know y'all don't like that.
But before we get further into the tapes, I want to point out,
I got this, the last time I was at Glen Rose,
we have a creation science museum in Glen Rose just like the Christians do.
But we never get any PR.
Just like the Dallas Morning News did that big section of book reviews
of Dallas authors who've been reprinted and never mentioned the book of the subgenius.
My bile is starting to rise.
I want that money.
I want those recountings of bad drug trips from y'all so as to prevent,
I mean, you and you too.
I mean, I know you guys don't do drugs, but I'm sure you've had bad alcohol trips.
I mean, there's, we need,
we need bad aspirin trips, you know, anything.
We need your personal recountings.
Nobody, we've gotten one.
How about that?
One.
And he wrote and said, oh gosh, I, when you first mentioned it,
I thought that you'd be so flooded with material that I didn't need to bother.
Well, apparently everybody thought that too.
And we aren't flooded with material in Dallas.
We hardly ever get any mail from Dallas.
The mail, the subgenius contributions, the stuff that we play on the air all comes in from outside.
Of the state.
Uh, because I guess since we're not local to them, we're, we're worthy of consideration,
but I guess since we're just local, well, that's not good enough.
But in, and in Glen Rose, we're local too, but here the Somervell sun, this is a mighty paper friends.
It says that creation evidence has been confirmed and that Dr.
Carl bow, uh, on, on J on June 16th, 1987, uh, the, this creation evidence team.
Discovered a, within a few feet of each other on the same level of the Puloxy river, a human tooth, dear friends,
who has been dubbed Glen Rose man soon.
I'm sure to take his history next to a pelt down man and his place next to who else was a great little P King man was for real, but they never did find the bones.
Um, yes, Glen Rose man or little David, as they've called him.
Oh, how religious.
Uh,
was this human tooth was found within a few feet of a trial, a bite, uh, three dinosaur track and Hugh and human footprints plus possibly mammalian large mammal bones.
And this is a actual scientific evidence of creation.
It says here, uh, and I absolutely, uh, disproves the 10 uncountable millions of examples of, uh, evolution evidence that have been found all over the entire planet.
By actual paleontologists, as opposed to the, uh, spacecraft, uh, control system designers and, uh, um, the dentist who, uh, who analyzed this incredible discovery, which they say this juvenile human tooth found next to the dinosaur track was blackened by the ages, which is unusual in the case of a fossil, because usually they're not blackened, but turned to stone itself.
Um, but nevertheless, friends, this, it must be true because it's, it says it right here in the Glen Rose.
Weekly newspaper.
And not only that, but they've provided a new spelling of the word archaeologist, even when what they really meant was paleontologist.
So, you know, they must be friends.
It's, it's gotta be true.
Uh, you know, uh, the Glen Rose paper said it, I believe it, that settles it.
Well, I've probably been depressing and nasty and mean enough for a while.
I'm just gonna friends call a two.
Three, seven, four, nine.
Oh, if you want to know what's going on or eight to eight 9,500.
Uh, did you have anything more to say?
Uh, mighty, uh, uh, daily llama.
Yeah, I've got a lot to say.
All right.
First, I want to tell all you subgeniuses out there that hadn't paid your dues.
Kill them.
Reverend Stang was being real nice to you when he was talking to you a little while ago.
And you know what Bob does to people who don't follow through.
He'll cut you off.
He'll cut you plum off.
He'll cut you off in places you don't want to be cut off.
Right?
It's worse than having your head cut off.
It's worse than having your gonads cut off.
It's being cut off.
Off by copyright 1981 by Buck naked.
Thanks, Buck.
Oh, who is in the, in the great subgenius video quite a bit by the way.
Um, what do we do without it?
That's with his earlier, more explanatory materials.
I, I, I just can't get into this.
This is inside joke stuff that some of these people treat.
I mean, this is a, it's a church friends.
It's a church.
Well, before we, uh, we got some new Jane or hyper cleats coming up.
Oh no.
Yes, we do.
We do hit the profit.
Jane or speaketh again.
Uh, so, so, uh, girls hang on.
Cause that mighty tongue of Jane, there's going to be a lashing at you.
Uh, in just a few seconds, let me try that again.
We had this great technique, your friends.
Uh, praise.
Buck.
You almost shot and started.
God, I see that.
I feel that he's been just a swimming.
That's never too much.
Never too much.
I just don't want to.
This is not the pleasure.
Sorry.
That huge.
Washing collar down.
His collar is in orbit.
All those worshipers.
I don't know.
You know, collar dead.
Sometimes I think this was all just meant to be.
Collar all scooped up.
Down the collar bag and we'll be able to send them out.
I have a question.
Private staying.
Yes.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Fire away.
Okay.
Um, I, as I was waking this morning, I was looking into my frog stash and my dog had
smoking all my frog.
Is that ethical or should I refrain from that?
Yeah, boy down.
Just send your dog out on the street to get a job.
That's what I do when my kids do the same thing.
Well, you got a job.
He's got a job.
He does my job.
Well, then.
Collar's fading away.
Yeah.
He's going around the other side of the planet.
I mean, there's a, the blueness of a wound cleanses away the evil.
So, you know, uh, you'll have to find your yellow collar.
You're going through the ionosphere.
You know what?
You'll have to yell as loud as you can, collar.
You'll be eating your dog in a few years.
Once the ocean rises, you'll be dissecting your dog in a few minutes.
What do you recommend as an entree?
The cat.
Out here.
Well, are you going to talk or you'll be okay?
I'm going to have to turn on the delta interocitor interrogating.
It's so pretty.
It's so clean.
It's so dull.
And those little sparkling lights, they, they seem to walk over my mind and tell me, tell
me over and over again.
None of this equipment works.
Never again.
Why does a live mother come down here?
You know, you're going to have to go through the tortures of hell to, to, to know what
that's, to really be able to appreciate the slack.
That's the whole point.
But it's the slack you don't know that gets you.
They never talk about the pain that comes before and after the slack.
Yeah.
If you look at the chart, the way they draw those charts and the way their seminars run,
it's just, Whoa, it's just one big, solid line of slack.
Just a plateau of slack.
They don't, they don't even get into the agony.
It says your navel is in Vulcan and your punto is in the dog house.
Therefore, Spudge, don't go out of the house today.
Stay inside and put your photograph on them together.
Today could be a day to eat vegetables.
Or it might be time to put off some of that obnoxious mail you've been dreading to write.
As for you moon children, what are you doing on this planet?
Nuff said.
Next week we'll have asteroidology for the moon.
Oh, they're really out there.
Good healing crystals kill the dinosaurs.
Yeah, that fixed them up real good, those little dinosaurs.
Without a shadow of a doubt, the dinosaurs practiced psychic surgery.
Whoosh.
Here a Tyrannosaurus removes large goblets of flesh from a brontosaurus.
Without using his teeth.
That's right, dear friends.
The dinosaurs were killed by psychic surgery.
And, uh,
Oh, oh.
The, uh, Reverend Dili Lama,
one time Pope of all Houston,
just said to me, uh, not to let him get on and start on,
but to let him get on and start on.
And on those creationists,
especially after this lady just called and said,
Are you all the Antichrist station?
Is this the Antichrist radio show?
Well, friends, yes it is the Antichrist radio show
if you're talking about that fake Jesus,
that demon that goes by the name of Jesus
and makes you hate, hate, hate.
But it's science, friends.
Pure and simple.
Evil Dili Lama,
why don't you give us your sickening views on this subject?
Gotta, gotta get a hold of myself sometimes.
And when I think about what's going on,
you know, they're gonna make a law.
They're gonna make a law that you can't think for yourself.
They're gonna make a law that you can't buy a record for yourself.
They're gonna make a law that, uh,
Reverend Stang and all the others like him
can't write books for themselves.
And friends, this is serious.
It's funny, oh yeah, it's real funny.
And you're in your BMW now.
Maybe you're going out to the Madonna concert.
And, oh, maybe you're in your little Volkswagen
and driving up North, North Central Expressway.
Or maybe you're over there in Fort Worth.
I don't know where you are right now, but, you know,
you're gonna, you're gonna be walking one of these days.
And you're gonna sit back and you're gonna remember
all those chances you had to,
to do something with yourself,
to think for yourself,
to act for yourself.
And you're gonna remember Reverend Stang screaming at you.
You're gonna miss those times, friends.
And it's all gonna be because of
what these creationists are trying to do to your mind.
Trying to convince you that the way you are,
the world was created on October 23rd, 4004 B.C..
Well it said so in the Bible.
It said so, so it must be true.
Because I know God wrote the Bible,
must be God that wrote it.
It couldn't have been a bunch of old wise men,
a bunch of smart-alecks like ourselves.
There's 23 different people that wrote the Bible.
And that's a fact.
And Bob was one of them by the way.
Because he figured it was another way to make money
You know, it's one of the largest selling books in the world.
He owns many of the franchises on the printing operations.
So it's just a money-making scam, friends.
But friends, there's even worse things out there.
And Jane or Hyperclete went on the air at the Sisters Station up in Little Rock on RC Guys Show, Real Cool Guys Show,
to talk about the terrible prevalence we've been seeing lately of buckets of naked girls.
You can actually go out and buy a bucket of naked girls in Hollywood these days.
And we're going to get to that tape right after this message.
Tonight's episode of the Hour of Slack is brought to you by the Weeping Cyclops Insignia Company.
The Weeping Cyclops Insignia Company features jobs-approved church wear and all manner of weird things.
Serving the public since God knows when.
Weeping Cyclops is at Box 595-148, Dallas, Texas 753-59-5148.
Thanks, Weeping Cyclops, for supporting the Hour of Slack.
And K&L in...
Oh, thanks, Weeping Cyclops, indeed.
I don't know where we'd be without the Weeping.
And friends, you need to send for those Dobbs t-shirts and patches, buttons.
And all kinds of stuff from the Weeping Cyclops at that famous P.O. Box.
I have to cut in here before we get to Jayner to announce it.
I mean, when I put in Buck's cart earlier, it was playing only on one channel.
And I was thinking, God, couldn't Buck have gone to the trouble of doing that in stereo?
Then I put in the Pope S. Cecilia's Weeping Cyclops cart here, and it was doing the same thing, coming out on one channel.
And I was thinking, this is ridiculous. This shouldn't happen.
I was in frustration. I pounded really hard, pounded the cart player, and by gobs, it came to life.
It's a miracle. It's a miracle. Praise Bob.
It just goes to show, I swear to God, this is true, friends.
I have to work with tape decks all the time.
And many, many times, those decks go down, and I spray them out and do things to them, and they're still not working right.
And I think, oh, gosh, I'm going to have to take it to the repair guy.
And I found out how much they charge.
I get so mad that I actually pick up those decks and slam them down or put them in the car and drive over bumpy roads.
And, friends, 90% of the time, driving that tape deck over a bumpy road will repair your tape deck.
Isn't it the truth, Willa Dobbs?
It is the truth, man.
I mean, I just hit this machine, and we got that right channel in.
The acubiting is the truth.
Bob spoke of acubiting, friends.
Well, it's time to go to Jayner.
And, friends, this is sick what he's talking about.
I hate to think it's real, too, but here we go.
We've got here a girl that we recently got from a so-called Jayner Hyperclete's Rick Maverick brand bucket of naked girls.
Now, when I first heard about this, I couldn't believe that this could even possibly exist,
that Hollywood stars could be purchasing buckets of naked girls on the black market.
I thought that was too decadent to even be real, to even be happening.
Now, it's true that you came to Hollywood in 1974.
Is that true, Miss Girl?
Well, I don't know.
I don't know what year it was, really.
They just blindfolded me, and I was just like 12 or 13.
Oh, who was that?
They just threw me in the bucket.
Plancy dogs?
Yeah.
No, they just...
They gave me acid and all kinds of drugs.
Oh, my God.
I know.
It was just...
The most abhorrent thing I've ever heard of.
And so you were led to believe that you could get a part in a film?
Yes.
They told me I would be a big star.
They told me I would be the biggest star in Hollywood ever.
And they showed me contracts and everything.
But I've just been in a bucket since I was 13 years old.
And now I'm 27.
I want to know when my first movie is going to be.
I mean, what about this big movie I'm supposed to be starring in?
This is the most horrible...
I think the public has a right to know.
We found...
This is...
We found a warehouse of buckets of naked girls on the outskirts of Hollywood,
believed to have ties to Rick Maverick and Jader Hyperclete.
I thought the whole thing was a joke.
Some kind of prop.
For one of their quote-unquote skits.
But upon opening one of the so-called buckets of naked girls,
we found this girl.
It took us two weeks before she was even able to talk.
So well had she been brainwashed and trained by the maniacal white slave owners.
Now, is it true that your skin has been chemically processed to reject clothing?
Yes.
I can't even...
I...
One piece...
One inch of clothing just touches my body and it just disintegrates.
It just...
I can't wear clothes anymore.
Why are you flashing on that thing?
I just...
I glow when the freeze comes down.
I can't put on gloves when the freeze comes down.
I don't know what to do.
I just...
I'm just doomed to be naked the rest of my life in a bucket.
I mean, what can I do?
It's not so bad, really.
This is tragic.
I mean, I'm embarrassed that we're even having to talk to you up here with you naked.
I really...
I mean, this is...
This is completely sexist for a liberal like me.
Yeah, y'all ought to see this.
I mean, really.
Oh, come on, R.C.
Give her a break.
This is a human being.
This is just one of the most...
This is the most sick, degenerative thing I've ever...
It is sick, friends.
It is really horrible.
And Dr. Hyperclete's here has been reporting for a long time.
Of course, some think that this is just a giant advertisement for the hyperclete.
It's bucket to naked...
Robert Wisdom just walked in.
By the way, his show, The American Music Party, is coming up in less than 10 minutes.
But he walked in and said, they are saying bucket, aren't they?
Friends, I'm going to try running just out of a sense of fairness.
I'm going to try running Buck's cart again here.
Here we go.
Stereo.
Hi.
Buck Naked, pastor of the First Naked Church of the Subgenius, inviting you to a Bob Righteous
full squirt devourable August 8th, Saturday night at 8 o'clock at the Bar of Soap.
See and hear many other wild schismatic preachers.
Uber Pope's dominatrix, Cecilia Smith.
Bob Righteous reverend, Buddy West.
Hill Swami, Satellite Weavers.
Dr. Chaos of the Chaotic Church of New Deal.
Deacon Tom Williams.
Not a Bobby in the bunch, friends.
All the above have ministered repeatedly on the Hour of Slack radio show.
Plus, Archdoctor St. Margaret Moser, high priestess of the cult of Chilkat from Austin, Texas.
And J.R. Bob Dobbs will be there.
Yes, he's alive, friends.
The San Francisco cool guy Bob may be dead, but my Bob isn't dead.
Is yours?
Unfortunately, local broadcaster Ivan Stang will be unable to attend.
But friend, you can hear Stang on any radio.
Now these incredible ministers can spit fire, heal the sick, and sicken the healthy.
Boom shakalemaka.
Afraid of this little snake here, son?
August 8th, 8 o'clock, Bar of Soap, across from the Fair Park Gate.
Praise Bob! Free at last.
This is John Shirley, science fiction writer John Shirley.
John Shirley sent in his bad drug trip tales.
Friends, where are yours?
Are you aware?
The sound is movement of the air.
Are you aware
That music reaches out
To shake what's there
Can you feel it
It's a physical force
An unseen touching
An expression of its source
Are you aware
That a ghost runs its fingers
Through your hair
And did you know
That sound is a kind of light
Moving slow
Kind of blind
Can you feel
My sonic power
Yes
Can you feel
These sonic fingers
A sonic finger
Can you feel
Feel this now
Feel it
Well it's a physical force
An unseen touching
An expression of its source
себя
I am touching your flesh
Robin Hood
I am touching the flesh
I am touching your flesh.
I am touching your flesh right now.
Are you equal to this dance?
Will you welcome this invisible guest?
Will you welcome the invisible guest?
Can you feel my sonic finger?
Friends, I know you can feel it.
I know you can feel it.
And you can, you can, are you up to it?
Will you go through, will you make it in that final test?
You can find out by writing for information.
You don't even have to send money.
You don't have to send money.
Not even a dollar.
Just free for information.
Not like what you get.
Well, and friends, you can write to that mighty Bob himself at P.O. Box 1403-06 in Dallas, Texas 75214.
That's right.
Write for information to Bob Box 1403-06 in Dallas, Texas 75214.
And stay tuned for Robert.
Robert Wisdom in American Music Party.
This, by the way, this instrumental going out is by Mark Mothersbaugh.
I honestly have no idea where or how it got here, but it did.
And we do know it's him.
That's what G. Gordon Gordon said.
And he'll kill you if you disagree with him.
Praise Bob.
Who he'll move?
Mother who?
I don't remember.
pes Zustcé and the audio made by Sculpey.
Simba the
itís
me
family
I'm
Us
trying to
maintain
going
and
field
an
example
of
deep
heat
and
fighting
Thank you.