From PR News in Washington, I'm causing a huge explosion that ripped seats in the National Assembly,
but not as many as is hoped.
And in December, eight of them were given to the people found in the debris of the Indian child.
I think, uh, uh, uh, uh, frankly not.
A court official in Sri Lanka swept from his mother's arms said today that DNA tests will find PR News in Washington.
A one, two, three, foul-a!
Leave it to the soul genius!
The power of science!
Well, isn't that something?
What do you mean?
Well, if anyone gets any answers, it'll be the psychiatrist.
Oh, that's terrible.
Yes.
And no.
Huh? Are you trying to give me the double talk?
Yes. I'm sorry.
Six years.
Six years I've been hiding.
Searching.
Sulking.
On the run.
Looking for the one they call Dobbs.
The voice is in my head!
Six years I've been on the run.
Only I bear the secret of the subgenius.
And I must wring the last drop of blood from the bloodless one before I may proceed.
This planet is Mars.
1998 has come and gone.
I'm not going to be a scientist.
I'm going to be a scientist.
And soon, you'll know it too.
J.R. Dobbs. Bob Dobbs.
J.R. Bob Dobbs was on the number one list of frauds and phonies for Time magazine.
Exactly.
And I didn't know who he was.
And J.R. Bob Dobbs is the creator of the Church of the Subgenius.
This guy, the Reverend Ivan Stang, is one of their...
Disciples.
Disciples. Disclipples.
Yeah. Alright.
You know, it's funny.
I don't think Jesus had a disciple.
A disciple named Dopey.
Poor Bob.
A rolling stone gathers no moss.
The Brown Pope is moving again.
His fundament is expelling the dirt that will fertilize the minds of the believers.
The new believers for the new Pope.
The Brown Pope.
Not exactly the anti-Pope, but somewhat against the proper Pope.
But moderately so.
He's one who ushers in the Pope.
He's one who ushers in the beast of Revelation.
You see, the Antichrist is the one character, but then you have the beast.
These are distinguished from each other in Revelation, don't you see?
Now, what are some of the characteristics of the beast?
Four quarters, four crowns, and a carrot?
Perhaps a divoted eyeball socket?
The beast which riseth from the sea has five tentacles, although that was for budget.
I was misreading that.
They really didn't have time to put in eight tentacles, so they kept him partially underwater.
Oh, wow.
So there are only five tentacles of the beast.
And these are the five tentacles.
Not to be confused with the ten horns, which is actually the ten countries heading the European Union of economic communism.
Which we call in the underlings the ten horned sheriffs.
Right, the ten horned dictators.
The ten horned dictators.
And the ten horned dictator, known as the beast.
No, they have a...
The anti-Bob, they called him.
Number 333, let he who has wisdom know that it is the number of a man.
And the number is three hundred three tens and three.
Oh my, Dobbs in Cleveland.
That's remarkable that there's an actual number for J.R. Bob Dobbs.
No, no, the number of J.R. Bob Dobbs is 999.
Okay, oh.
909 billion and nine.
Okay, the ten dicks?
And that is the mark of the Bob.
Which, by the way, two times 999 equals 1998.
Three times 666 equals 1998.
Wow.
And six times 333 equals 1998.
Now by these stripes, we know that 1998 has not come yet.
Because I don't know about you, but I am a pre-98-alist in the Church of the Subgenius denominational schedule.
I'm a pre-98-alist.
It is, I believe that it is not yet 1998 and that the conspiracy has been screwing with our calendars, screwing with our heads.
They've been pooing down our brain holes.
Now wait.
I'm going to speak with false numbers, false measurements.
Do days seem long enough to you?
Nay.
They are never long enough.
Don't your body seem a bit...
They grow shorter by each common instant.
And at the same time, these stripes that we know them by, do they mean that each and every one of us shall have ten nipples and ten breasts?
What happened?
What did they...
How did they take these hours from us?
And it's not just daylight savings time.
They take everything.
Falling back.
They took other things when you were asleep.
They take our sweat, our urine, our other things.
Where you have blood, we have circuits.
Where you have memories, we have 0-1-1-0-1-1-1.
0-1-0-1.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to blow up the...
That's an inside joke.
We'll play the song for that one next time.
In just a little while.
Until I'm excited.
Actually, we could go ahead and...
We're in a robot age.
It is a robot age.
Should I just skip ahead to that song?
Did you want to flay the corpse on the way?
Shall we flay the corpse?
Just go ahead and flay the corpse.
Flay the corpse and let me see if I can find this.
Oh man.
Flaying.
This is Dvockov.
I would like to...
Fill up the image.
Will this man death fus televirt?
No, it isél bゃçø.
to the sky
and we know how high they'll fly
the range formula
is in our head
Why you have blood
we have circuits
Why you have memory
we have 011
Why you have blood
we have circuits
And the dawning of the robot age has come
You, you thought you were so smart
So sure we play our part
in the betterment of mankind
But you are wrong
You never saw the hatred in our eyes
You thought a behavior mechanized
You never knew you fell behind
Why you have blood
we have circuits
Why you have memory
we have 011
Why you have blood
we have circuits
And the dawning of the robot age has come
The dawning of the robot age has come
Uh yes dear friends
somewhere between the absurd
and the enlightened
That was wolf bait
and that's how they describe themselves
on their website
at wolfbait.org
where you can get more like that
when dawning of the robot age
They played at the
Detroit Devival last month
We've got some recordings from that coming up
Also the amino acids played
and that's who's in the background here
Before that friends we heard a little bit
of Dr. Onan Kanopal
There will be much Onan Kanopal
And of course Fernanda Nandeli-Mur
and lots of Cowboy Dave
But for right now
Let's get back to that actual recording
of a live subgenius devival
in Detroit
Now in progress
I've got Bob
on the brain
I've got Bruce on the brain
I don't need anything else
They say Reverend Slang
that don't make no sense
I've got Bob on the brain
What the hell do you think
your religion's ever going to make any sense
Religion makes sense
That's a shit
If your religion makes sense my friend
then it ain't a religion
That's science
Science makes sense
Science is cool
I love that science stuff
But religion
I mean you know if science makes sense
according to scientific theory
the way it's done
the world isn't going to end on July 5th 1998
Because that wouldn't make any sense
and time is already come and gone
But Bob says that the world is going to end
on July 5th 1998
If Bob said it
then you better
you better
put that in your pipe and smoke it my friend
Ah but now dear friends
the controversy begins
This is the reverend
Dr. Onan Kanabite
Today is
the 29th
of July
Words that sound impossible
and yet
they've not only been said
but they must be said
Like many of you
I stood ready to be received
by our
high school
angelic hosts
the Exists
on July 5th 1998
I have been on the run ever since
living an underground existence
hiding not only from the conspiracy
but from some of my own
fellow subgeniuses
I can speak to you
only via these broadcasts
on the road
I can speak to you
What I have to tell you
may sound strange
It may sound impossible
but it's true
Some of you may have read
or been told
in church
that the reason
that we're all still here
on this planet
is that
it's not yet 1998
that somehow
there's been an error
in the calendars
as maintained
by our human
cohabitants
pets
and tormentors
that
it's not just like
leap year
and forgetting that it was leap year
and that there was an extra day in the month
but somehow there's a bunch of
centuries involved
and we don't quite know what year it is
but when it really is
July 5th 1998
the curtains will part
the saucers will come
and Bob will lead us
to a world of slack
The fact that we don't have slack now
is demonstrated by the fact
by the evidence
by our confident claim
that
that this is not 1998
nor has it ever been 1998
well I'm here to tell you
that it has been 1998
1998 came and went
in 1998
six years ago
I know I was there
I was at Brushwood
with 444,000 other subgeniuses
I stood
in Brushwood
waiting for the sun
and the saucers to arrive
on this planet
and arrive they did not
although some were
made to pay the price
for that day
their innocence
is proven
and will be proven
by what I have to say
in tonight's broadcast
this planet is Mars
there I've said it
on July 5th 1998
the exos did land on earth
but this is not earth
how about those machines
that went to Mars
folks
I know that y'all
are real science fans
actually I know some of you
are science fans
weird science fans
what they didn't talk about
on the spirit and opportunity landers
well they do
in some newspapers some websites
it was kind of upsetting
did you know that there were
when they launched those things
they had fetuses in little
gestation chambers
it takes like 9 months to get to Mars
or almost
when they
when the spirit landed
that was the first one I think
there was a male in the spirit
and a female in the opportunity
don't ask me why they made those
choices on the names
but the
they landed on opposite sides of the planet
now for a long time everybody was real upset
because it seemed like the baby on the spirit had died
it was alive
when it landed
then the robot crawled out of way
and took some pictures and stuff
I don't know if y'all remember
then the robot froze up
well they were all upset because
that thing was supposed to take care of the baby
back on the ship
they had some other backup stuff
thankfully they kept it alive
I was really sweating through all this
then the opportunity
that was the spirit
then the opportunity landed about a month later
that baby was decanted or whatever
and that one worked fine
now the idea is
they're on opposite sides of Mars
if these children can survive
now they're inside
they're not inside the little robots that are crawling around
that would be silly
they're inside the big lander
the big thing that came down
there's these incubators in there
now the idea is
we'll slowly let the Martian atmosphere
such as it is
replace the oxygen atmosphere
inside the lander thing
so that these babies gradually adapt
to the Martian atmosphere
they'll be different from us
their lungs will have to be really large
to absorb what little oxygen there is
but
now
you can see why the government wouldn't want to talk about this
if these two children
can survive
this incredibly horrible
environment
and somehow
find each other
walking from one side of Mars
it's not a very big planet really
they get together and meet
man it'll be like Adam and Eve
it'll be like that movie Blue Lagoon
only on the red planet
with these young teenagers
that have never spoken
or know anything of Earth
that get together and mate
and think how adapted their children will be
for the Martian atmosphere
it's just I don't know
see I still find hope in science
I told you Bob
Bob scientist
Church of Bob Crackpot
if I believed in praying
I'd lead us all in a prayer
for those two little Martian babies
but
I'm afraid of who else might be listening
if we were to pray
that's why subgeniuses don't pray
you don't really want Bob to hear you
because he might play a joke on you
and you sure
don't want any of the other ones to hear you
they'll give you just what you want
in the most literal way
from PR news in Washington
I'm only the third of five Indonesian weather forecasters
expected to eliminate
Madrid, Moscow, London and Paris
President Bush officially opened his
healing insurgency alliance
when he fell into a 30-foot sinkhole
governments must choose corruption
abandon their people
and take responsibility for blaming others
the president's first speech
the president called on PR's journalists
to pull their members out of Vladimir Putin
for the first time since 1999
a 16-year-old girl continued to batter
PR news in Washington
and a curfew is in place there
the PR news by Fernanda Nandeli-Murr
and now a related piece by Just John
is your news safe?
can you trust it?
is your children?
is your news safe?
how can you tell for sure?
why hasn't your congressman taken a stand?
is your news safe?
why take chances?
when will consumers wake up?
is your news safe?
what can be done?
but friends
here's the thing
all this marvelous science news
which believe me can really cheer you up
after you look at the political news
or the local
or the obituaries if you're my age
the thing is
it's all a lie by omission
because out of all that
did they ever mention the war on drugs
on Mars?
did they mention?
have any of you ever heard
even from a crackpot
the theory that during World War II
while everybody was busy with that
the conspiracy one night while everyone was asleep
switched the planet Earth
and the planet Mars
and moved all the populations
from the used up former Earth
to the brand new nice refurbished planet Mars
which is the one we're on now
so that they can
finish running this one into the ground
like they did the previous one
they just switched back
the conspiracy has been around
that long friends and they're that bad
they use up a planet
this one
they'll use this one up
turn it into a dust covered thing
with hardly any atmosphere
and then swap it out again
by that time what we call Mars
will be all built up
have some air on it and so forth
they'll just keep doing it over and over again
Earth first
then all the other planets
screw them all up
kids these days think the war of the worlds
was science fiction
and they're not
they're just water towers
and stuff that are now used as water towers
and they think that's all they ever were
they don't know about those
that were once martian war tripods
there's a movie coming out
of the war of the worlds finally
Steven Spielberg and Tom Cruise
making H.G. Wells war of the worlds
into a movie
of course they're going to set it in present time
as if the real war didn't happen
in the turn of the previous century
friends I don't know if there's any
but I'm mad at Hollywood
because they've been cutting the nads off
of that guy's books
one after another
the time machine was about class division
well the new version of the time machine
is about industrial accident
oops
the war of the worlds
was about colonialism
and the island of Dr. Moreau
I guess was both
but anyway you haven't all read those
anybody see the Incredibles
or Sky Captain and the World of Tomorrow
I thought the acting in the Incredibles
was actually much better than the acting
in the Sky Captain
some people embrace their martian heritage
others deny it
and from that conflict
arises the internal
conspiracy
the conspiracy
of one within yourself
against all your other selves
the many selves in you
and the world
and each cell of yourself
as you sit in your cell
the conspiracy of one
may have already won
there's no turning back now
this planet is Mars
the tremendous implications
of all this may not yet be fully understood
Bob
and naturally further tests
will have to be carried out
this is the place of the mistress
how's it going Bob
we know who can get out
yes, Admin
you will pay for your unforeseen attack
on our complex on Mars
Bob, I thought you space jockeys enjoyed riding high
sure, but four weeks is long enough
are there any prohibitionists in this part of the country
Dave's not here
we will be avenged
we will assassinate
the great general
of the United Asian Republic
but in the present threatening situation
I'm ready to take a calculated risk
I'd like you back on duty as of now
I'm ready Colonel
it took decades to figure it out
the elastic nature of time itself proved the key
and isn't it much more likely
that this planet is Mars
than that the year 1998 hasn't occurred
isn't that just kind of foolish
and silly
Bob said
that the planet is Mars
and that it's a bunch of stuff
but that's not what I'm talking about right now
I'm talking about common sense
where are we Bob
the message is
Mars needs women
Mars needs
it's a gag
it's a prank
reproduction cycle of Martian fiend worms series 8
in series 7
you learned about many of the interesting creatures
who have been around for centuries
and who live on Mars
including the tiny microscopic
Gonococcus hairyhosea
or Martian peen worm
today
with the help of a neutron micro holographic scanner
we'll look into a dead Martian intestine
the peen worm's
natural habitat
and see the whole life cycle
of this simple aeroni-obe
unfold as if by magic
as the miracle of reproduction begins
our lone hero
is still a mere tube of water
and a tube of psychoplasm
but soon
a frenzy of chemical activity
called the amphetaphase
seizes the microbe
and by the mysterious process called
osmiotic blooming
it starts to clot
it grows a rudimentary
megastamen and antherite
and swiftly matures into the
spore of sex A
the gameteoroid
unscientifically
it might be called the male
he discovers his own
nasophallosian tube
and performs hermaphroditic autofusion
until he spills a secretion
of preposterol
this triggers the morphase to begin
and up sprouts sex B
the so called female
or nymph load
her thorax produces the jovian knobs
and she even has a feeble
nucleic eyeball
nearly as powerful as that of the male
a surprisingly complex
courting ritual
is initiated
she produces special chemicals called
mojo bodies
which excite her partner
she places her stigmat
on his cloacal apparatus
and performs parthenodulation
he achieves cytospasm
and germiades
and in natures
timeless tragedy
the helpless male falls victim
to the eternal wiles of the female
leaving naught but a pool of
albuminal spum
using her oviduct
as an oral groove
she saps every last trace
of her former lover
as the layman would call him
spermatogenocide is committed
and it's almost as if she's smiling
one last spurt of cleavage
produces two diploid ribosoles
each carrying half the plans
for a new worm
hopefully not the same half
finally convinced that they are
indeed of the same species
they hesitantly begin pairing
they combine to become
one single blasphemula
which makes a last tug of
mycotic cell division and
voila there are now two worms
where there once was one
but what becomes
of them now? we'll learn
not only that but also why
the peen worm is so crucial to our nuclear
beer and even the martian war
in series
could be scary
Surgub, the bug-headed man, cut a deal with the alien clan.
They agreed to destroy the Earth.
I hope Bush attacks them first.
Bad aliens!
Oh my God, they're here again!
They say they don't have evil intentions,
but then they take us to alien kitchens and cook us.
I have this dream about UFO people.
They fly around in blue and gold vehicles.
I'm real concerned about alien war.
Come close and I'll tell you some more.
Can you keep a secret?
I've got coordinates of bad alien whereabouts.
I've got locations of UFO hideouts.
I've got green DNA in my fridge.
I've sent samples to Mr. Tom Ridge.
Bad aliens!
Oh my God, they're here again!
They say they don't have evil intentions,
but then they take us to alien kitchens and cook us.
Bad aliens!
Oh my God, they're here again!
They say they don't have evil intentions,
but then they take us to alien kitchens and cook us.
Last night when I went to sleep,
I heard the sound of alien creeps.
They were chilling near my bedroom door,
making plans for a UFO war.
Can you keep a secret?
Bugman was there with his creepy bug head.
Martians were clawing the foot of my bed.
There were aliens all over the place.
Someone seal the borders before it's too late.
The End
Thanks for watching!
Subscribe for more!
See you next time!
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
дух
bird
This is the best joke on YouTube!
Office Word Document MSWordDoc Word.Document.8
Today students are called Samurai.
This was one of the anonymousум
front butt is missing, teacher.
Oh, don't worry about it. Somebody circumcised
me. You've accidentally...
I didn't circumcise you.
It's an accident that happens to all of us.
They've taken more than my flaps.
Good Lord, I...
Look down there.
No, no, no. Down there.
Further.
Down there. All the way down there.
Not so far, not so deep.
God, I can't believe I'm witnessing this. Oh, my God.
Pretty deep, ain't it?
That tickles. What'd you go down that far?
Man, I know how the worms feel now, Daddy-o.
They're all oozy and slimy and soggy
like greasy fried chicken
or something.
Oh, man, they're like liquid tones
are coming out. Like a cosmic float.
Yes. Worms.
Oh, look at the little oompa-loompa chair
with the wheels that go sideways
are coming. I've got to sit down and take a ride
on this thing, man.
But you have to be comfortable with your worms.
Are you comfortable with your worms?
What's so far, the quad?
Are you comfortable with the fact that your body is made of a bunch
of wet tubes
that might as well be worms?
You might as well be a bunch of worms yourself,
you know. You're nothing but tube upon tube
upon tube.
Worm tubes carrying
this juice and goosey stuff
to all your parts. And all your parts
are nothing but more little worms.
Yellow fluids to level one.
Yellow hydrofluids to level
five.
Please report any
cardio fluids.
You can't get away from your worms, you know.
You sit down and say, oh, I'm going to live
in my little box of plastic. It's all going
to be like smelling of plastic.
And it's all going to be like vinyl and clean.
And all nice. But you can't
get away from your worms.
There are worms and they're going cold again.
Get away from them bleeding things.
I mean, the first thing you wake up in the morning,
you look out the window, there's bleeding freaking
worms looking in back at you.
You come back home, ever sog,
ever slop, you wait a while, next thing you know,
look out the window, bleeding.
There's freaking worms looking in your eyes again.
You can't let the worms get to you, is what I'm saying.
You can't let the bleeding worms
get you freaking off, because the next thing you know,
then you're all one with the worms.
You've got to come to terms with your worms.
Oh, the great worm, yeah.
You've got to go and soak it.
Come to terms with... No, wait.
That's bleeding fresh, man. I'm not saying...
You must come to terms with your worms.
I like it. I like it.
Come to terms with your worms.
It's the cutest thing that you two are doing here.
Have you come to terms with your worms, you know?
I'm like a nice little, uh, on the back of your car.
Speaking of worms...
There are people whose worm cannot become big
when they want it to.
Oh, this happens once in a while after too much alcohol.
Yeah, needs a little extra boost...
Oh, poppy!
...from an herbal company, such as perhaps these guys
that used to do those ads called this.
Smiling Bob.
Bob is doing well.
Very well, indeed.
That's because not long ago,
Bob realized that he...
He needed something better in his life.
And what did he get?
Why, a big boost of confidence,
a little more self-esteem,
and a very happy Mrs. at home.
Oh, isn't that cute?
Oh, and there was...
There were so many...
Bob is looking cool.
Bob is living life.
In a few short weeks,
Bob has a big new spring of confidence.
The generous willing of God.
And the one thing every man deserves,
a little well-earned respect,
from the neighborhood.
Yes, well, you see...
Oh, dear.
Actually, there is...
In that kind of neighborhood,
oh, dear, I would say Bob,
your common Bob,
would have not slapped a boner
had he had the opportunity.
Bob is definitely a slack luster,
slack meister.
Yeah, yeah, he's a slack...
But here's the...
Here's the punchline to that.
But, oh, dear, they don't have that, see?
Over there.
Over...
Well, this endsite company
that makes this Bob show
with the fake Bob,
the pipeline,
he's a pipeless Bob.
You don't got a pipe.
He looks like Bob,
but he's don't got a pipe, right?
Right, he's made out of seashells.
And he's a rip-off.
They rip off the...
Garbage and flat.
They don't pay us.
They take his pipe away.
They use this pipeless Bob
so that these pink boys
and corporate screwballs
can get it up, right?
Okay, now, here's the punchline.
Here's the punchline.
Here's the punchline, okay?
The feds raided that company last week.
Okay, I heard that.
The inside company.
Yeah, yeah.
Cincinnati.
The feds raided them
because they'd been doing
this auto-charge crap
where they charge you.
You buy their herbal pumper-upper,
you know,
woodpecker device,
a pill,
and they're bending
so you can be a hot,
hot-charging Bob guy.
But, you know,
but see,
see, here's the thing.
Jesus didn't have
no disciples named Dobie.
No, seriously,
there was karma.
You know, of course.
There was karma,
and the enzymes
was raided
and had all their business supplies
confiscated
and their records and things
because of their evil doings.
So it wasn't just...
A soiled panty raid.
It wasn't just
the church of the subgenius
that they fought
to plunder
whose graves and tombs
they thought to rob.
Nay, it was
everyone who ordered
those get-big pills.
Those tiny little
get-big pills.
Yeah.
They were dee...
They were bigifiers.
You know what I'm saying?
They make you well!
All large and gross
and smelly and crawling.
That's the way we like it here.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm causing another disaster.
President Bush is set to blast
into the president's gay bishop
outside Slovakia.
A piece of Howard Dean's left wing
caused PR News.
Archbishops from around the world
commented this morning,
on PR's accounting practices
during testimony in the federal fraud trial
of PR News in Washington.
I remember you.
You and I used to sit and watch television together.
And there on the screen,
we'd see some horrible monster
from another world.
We could see it.
Week after week.
Different monster.
Same television.
And that same zipper running up its back.
With the quivery rubber boots.
And the quivery rubber glove.
And the giant rubber head shaped like Lyndon Johnson.
We'd watch television together.
You and I.
And slowly the picture would emerge.
Line by line.
It would scan across our third face.
And we'd understand that this planet is Mars.
Sometimes the aliens want to hurt humanity.
Sometimes they want to help humanity.
Sometimes the aliens are hideous.
Sometimes they're beautiful.
And you'd have to wonder,
what are the script writers telling us?
They don't have a consistent message.
Are they saying that the aliens are good or bad?
And knowing that I, as subgenius, am an alien,
are they saying that I'm good or am I bad?
And what are they saying about themselves?
Are they saying they're a pro-alien or anti-alien?
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
There's only one way to adjust these variables
and have it come out in a logical, sensible, rational manner.
And that is that this planet is Mars.
And that some of the aliens you meet
are merely earthlings trying to adjust to this planet being Mars.
Whereas some of the most subgenius people you'll meet
seem rather normal.
And they're Martians trying to adjust
that they're not on their home planet.
This planet is Mars, my friends.
Keep listening.
Only the hour of slack is brave enough
to rebroadcast these shortwave transmissions
gathered from subgenie all over the world like you.
Now it's very presumptuous of us to believe that
Martians are going to be any different than we are.
It's merely a freak in their genetic code
that has brought them to this planet.
And I'm sure they don't plan to harm us.
At least not yet.
From PR News in Washington, I'm violating international sanctions against the
former U.S., calling on world leaders to implement PR News.
The Bush administration's in custody in Japan
for trying to replace the Commission on Human Rights
with an invalid passport.
If convicted, Bob could face the leukemia penalty.
The attorneys say Bob did not hear the screams of the immigrants to the U.S.
Bob was in a bar for over 35 years.
In Tucson, Arizona.
This is 10-5-1-6.
A jury in Houston is feeding jam to PR News from Washington.
Quiet, quiet.
Dave carries a secret little sound effect with him all the time.
And it's like a perfume.
Some use perfumes.
Dave keeps a sound effect with him.
It smells.
Oh, I like the sound effect today, Dave.
What are you wearing?
I'm wearing...
Car, car...
Is that car crash number nine?
Yes, car crash number nine.
And the OVITURE in Fallopious.
Oh!
John Cage.
I'm giving birth.
Excellent.
Say it's not your birth.
Those worms, those worms!
All wrapped up, John.
for you.
Have you read any new horror novels lately?
I know. I've consumed one, though.
Oh.
To feed the worms.
Here are a couple of bookworms. That's what you are.
Just a couple of bookworms.
Yes. A couple of slimy ones.
Leaving a snail
trail behind you.
That's what I've said before
about you all the time, Williams.
There's a snail trail.
Let me repeat that.
There's a snail trail
behind you wherever you go, Williams.
You think you can get away with petty larceny.
You think you can get away with grand larceny.
And now you think you can get away with
murder.
But they got away with it, didn't they, Father?
Yes, they got away with it.
Father, they got away with it. Why can't we?
Well, because you're a member of the
Church of the Subgenius.
But the others can do it, Father.
Why can't we?
They are favored by Dobbs and you are not, child.
It is not yours to reason.
Why?
It is yours to sit down on your phalanx and die.
I don't understand.
You're not going to be prompted to understand.
No?
You're going to be pushed into the oven.
You're scaring me.
You're frightening me.
I know you're joking, but you're frightening me.
We're making Hansel and Brittle pickles with you.
Yes, those hands look tender and juicy.
We'll make a very nice
pie-o-squared for those.
Hansel?
To Grittle.
And Gristle.
The Gristle of Hansel.
As dead crickets
would not die.
The Bavarian doctor
working late into the night
working with his
alchemical equipment brought
life to the Gristle of the little
Austrian boy, Hansel.
And Brittle
and cut.
Come on.
And went.
Counts of electricity were needed to keep the poor boy alive.
For he was made only of crooked fingers,
cynical pie, and some impurities
found in our air and water.
He only wanted to die then.
But the government wouldn't let him.
No.
The government decided who would live and who would die.
And in this case, unfortunately,
they decided that he must live.
Even though the poor little piece of Gristle
was but a helpless, pain-filled,
paralyzed mind
full of feelings of hurt,
hooked up to a machine,
kept alive unfairly
in perhaps the grossest,
grossest miscarriage of justice
of all time.
And yet, and yet outside,
the protesters screamed
and then waved their torches
and said,
Make it live! Make it live!
Your life or death pass, please, Mrs. Veramal.
What?
Sorry, no death pass. You can't die.
I believe in the Gristle.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Veramal.
Believing in the Gristle is not good enough.
You must have a life or death pass
signed by your government agent at Gokul.
This is my death pass. May I go now, please?
It is not valid, Mrs. Veramal.
It's been placed in someone's bungie.
I need to go.
That has to be authorized by Secretary of State for Maldehyde.
And I'm afraid this is not your paperwork.
It is authorized.
The paperwork is not together.
You're going to have to live a bit longer.
The paperwork is complete.
You're going to have to undergo some more pain
until you can get this together.
I mean, really, there's no reason.
The information was posted in the basement of Town Hall
since long before you were born.
This is ridiculous.
Before the day of your birth was the day of your death,
guaranteed by your United Snakes government.
Everyone has a right to live, to be born, and to die.
No, they don't. No, we changed that.
You don't have a right to die anymore.
Where does it show here?
Oh, you have the right to live.
You have the right to an attorney.
But the right to a death has been...
The death penalty and the death option have both been confiscated.
This is for your own good.
This is for your own good, my friend.
There is no good in this world, you squirrely maggot.
Don't you understand what's going on here?
Squirrely?
I think it's just a random adjective.
A squirrely and squirrely-like.
Uh, rodential.
Well, if you don't like maggots, you just see how long you can get along without worms then.
Why don't you?
Yeah, you see too.
Check it out sometime if you, you know, got the inclination.
From PR News in Washington, I'm trapped in a suburb of Los Angeles,
but three deaths are being linked to an apparent self-inflicted PR news from Washington.
President Bush has been working to drench Southern California.
Downtown L.A. was killed when a rock slide fell into a 30-foot deep sinkhole.
President Bush had pointed words about the French President Jacques Chirac.
Ah, duh, duh.
The Arab League will soon pull its members out of Lebanese mass.
Six inches since Thursday night in Los Angeles.
Israel has freed the largest relatives.
Marines have raided PR News in Washington.
Has it ever crossed your mind that some of the saddest music...
Let's ride that!
...that you'll ever hear, some of the saddest music that's ever been recorded...
is the blues?
Now, how did the blues get its name?
Why call it the blues?
Why not the Reds?
You've paid your one dollar.
You've joined the church of the subgenius.
Now I'm here to tell you...
People call it the blues because we're stuck on this filthy blue planet...
Mars.
All the blues is a lamentation...
a wailing out...
of the sorrow associated with this...
filthy blue planet, Mars.
Earth.
That's the planet we belong on.
That's the fourth planet out.
But you were born on Mars.
So you're a Martian.
Everyone born on this world is a Martian.
But some Martians belong on Mars.
Other Martians belong on another world.
That's alienation.
That's what Marx and Engels were talking about.
And communism.
Something so evil and yet so good...
associated with the color red.
It's got all the good ideas.
Oh, it looks so good on paper.
Let's associate it with red.
Because that's the planet we want to go to.
That red planet that's up there in the sky.
We can see it.
That's the planet we want to go to.
We want to make this planet red.
And they tried.
And it did look good on paper.
Bob understands communism.
Bob is a salesman.
Sales transcends communism and capitalism.
Sales transcends fascism or socialism.
It's all sales to Dobbs.
The method to do American constitute just consume,
for truth only.
Ooooh!
From PR News in Washington, I'm not believing PR News.
Israel is demanding that some Palestinian officials insist that Syria put Syria in Tel Aviv.
Pope John Paul is preparing for tonight's Academy Awards ceremony,
but for the first time in his 26-year papacy, the Pope is planning to raise his notorious half-brother,
who's thought to be one of the leaders of PR News in Washington.
Dave, what do you think about the planet Mars?
I think the planet Mars inspires me.
It is red, like La Russia.
It is violent and blue and hot and sexy.
It reminds me of weird little, like, ant creatures with, like, huge helmets on and stuff and spears.
You know, thousands of them marching up and down these red, duned hills.
It reminds you of these things, eh?
Yes, but it's just...
As if these were hidden, buried memories from another life, or maybe even earlier in this life?
From 20 million years before Earth or something?
No.
No, not necessarily.
Could be.
Maybe from your childhood, even.
Genetic memories from my childhood, they could be.
I could be one of those little, like, ant-like creatures with the big helmets and this...
You could be.
Why does Mars seem so exciting to you, Dave?
Why do you want...
Why do you keep coming back to this subject?
Mars is valid.
Evocative nature.
Can't you leave the war alone?
Can't you just forgive the Martians?
Forget the war, man.
The Martian war is over.
Can't you just let it go?
Like a moist evacuation?
I can't stop repeating that.
My conditioning is too strong.
I've been conditioned since the beginning of the war to remember only the blood, the iron, and the red wine.
I've been conditioned to remember the stars and stripes forever.
The sound of the distant heartbeat.
The roaring guns.
The roaring lions.
The clowns.
The clowns?
The little dwarfs?
What?
The clowns?
Coming out of the cars?
The dwarf ladies.
The big sarangina lady with too much makeup and a weird mole on her face.
Oh, yes.
And the director.
And the producer.
And the cameraman.
And all the makeup artists.
And the extras.
And the grits.
And the grunts.
And the grooves.
And the groties.
Oh, they're all here together.
And there's the man carrying the great big fish.
Oh, there he is.
And there's the giant.
And there's the two-headed Japanese girl.
And Federica Felici.
She's so beautiful.
And Tim Burton.
And look, they're all mixed together.
And it's just like a giant homage to Bob.
And look at that.
Bob.
Right.
And the slimy corpse.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
And as the parade of life goes by, friend, did it go by you, too?
Were you left behind with the bold, rancid popcorn?
Did you turn your fish into wine?
The trash paper blowing through the streets.
Wandering.
Wandering sadly away into the sunset.
Wondering, where is Bob?
How can I find more about this man, J.R. Bob Dobbs?
I have a hint of slack.
Where can I go to www.subgenius.com to learn more information?
How can I possibly write to a post office box number that I'm getting a pencil ready in my hand to write down?
Which is the Hour of Slack or Subgenius Foundation at post office box 807 Glen Rose.
Texas 76043.
And friends, how would you ever learn how to get to Tex Day, the preliminary X Day drill at the High Rock Ranch outside of Austin, Texas?
For the strange Texanian, Neopaganian, Subgenian, Wiccabilly festival.
Where the great groovy Neptune I just heard will be.
Wow.
Yeah.
He's the one who did the song.
About.
I love his work.
Everybody here's crazy about Bob.
Everybody here's so crazy about Bob.
That fits with the theme of madness, of course.
Yes, the theme of madness, friends.
I can hardly call it work, though.
It looks more like he has pleasure when he performs.
Yes, it gives him pleasure to do what he does.
With the great beast.
And with the great pipe.
With the Leviathan under the earth.
With the great presence that he has.
The beast.
The ten-horned, ten-peckered goat with a thousand young.
Greetings, my friend.
The back squid of the forest.
You are interested in the unknown.
I see.
Mysterious.
The unexplainable.
You're talking to me?
That is why you are here.
Now, for the first time, we are bringing you the full story of what happened.
What?
The show's about to end.
We are giving you all the evidence.
This is the evidence.
They've only understood.
Finally, we're going to learn.
We're going to learn.
Just wait.
Don't say anything.
We have to give the credits.
Don't wait.
Oh, my God.
It's going to be at the incidents.
Places.
My friend, we cannot keep this a secret any longer.
No.
No, never.
Can your heart stand the shocking facts of the true story of Edward D. Wood Jr.?
Oh, Edward D. Wood Jr.
Is that all it was?
Man.
Don't you, Edward?
Well.
Boy, the shocking.
I want to bring down.
The shocking difference.
The shocking.
The shocking secret.
Absolutely shocking.
I mean, you've got to pray with me reflecting on that history in your mind.
a red Martian sunrise as the sun begins to rise as I'm walking along on the Martian sand
on this forbidding planet I'll be waiting for more Martian sands as I'll be waiting
for more Martian sands as the night has come and I'll be waiting for more Martian sands as I'll
be waiting for more Martian sins as I been walking in the Martian sins are blowing around me as I see
the red Martian landscape before me as I'm walking on the red Martian sands on this forbidding planet
Martian landscape and the Red Martian sunrise gives way to another day on this
forbidding planet as the Red Martian sands are blowing around me as I'm walking on the
Red Martian landscape as I've been walking all day on the Red Martian
landscape as the sun begins to set in a Red Martian sunset as the sun slowly
begins to fade off in the distance and the Red Martian landscape disappears
into the cold darkening night on this forbidding planet as I'll be waiting for
another Red Martian sunrise
I'll be waiting
I'll be waiting for more Martian sands, as I'll be waiting for more Martian sands, as the night has come in. I'll be waiting for more Martian sands, as I'll be waiting for more Martian sands.
As I've been walking in the Martian sands are blowing around me, as I see the red Martian landscape before me, as I'm walking on the red Martian landscape.
And the red Martian sunrise gives way to another day on this forfeiting planet, as the red Martian sands are blowing around me.
As I'm walking on the red Martian landscape, as I've been walking all day on the red Martian landscape.
As the sun begins to set in the red Martian sunset, as the sun slowly begins to fade off in the distance.
And the red Martian landscape disappears into the cold darkened night.
On this forfeiting planet, as I'll be waiting, for another red Martian sunrise.
Friends, my internet friends.
My beloved listener and close, close personal friend.
This is the internet-only end of the show.
part where I remind you about Subgenius membership ministerial ordainment kit, in fact, whereby
you can be a legal minister. Plus, you get insights into the secrets of the church of
the Subgenius and a big package of stuff. And we also have, of course, t-shirts and decoder
pins and bumper stickers and pins and everything you would expect. CDs, for instance. Even
a weekly radio show, did you know that? Our books are the best, but books, I think, maybe
they're just for old people, I don't know. Anyway, some people get the impression that
if you're a real Subgenius, you never send money to the Subgenius Foundation. You never
buy a membership, because that proves you're really not a joiner. But that's actually wrong.
I'm not sure where that came from. I think perhaps wishful thinking. But no, we don't
laugh at you when you send in your 35 bucks, finally, and we mail you that kit, which is
addressed by my hand, by the way. And yeah, I actually do physically pay for that. And
we manhandle each package. And they also, there's a little letter in there that's signed
by me, too. How about that? We actually care. We go to a lot of trouble. We keep track of
who you are, at least until you move, and we all forget about it. But yeah, friends,
isn't it about time? Subgenius.com. Oh, and we'll take checks. This month, you can mail
them to Box 807, Glen Rose, Texas, 76045.
And I have a feeling that's going to be our permanent address in a couple of years. But
in the meantime, you can still use the Cleveland address. We get mail forwarded back and forth.
Hey, Price Bob. Thank you.