Yeah, feel that bump on Bob's dome.
Let's see, Bob.
Oh, hey, that is a good one.
What happened?
The subgenius hour of slack.
Oh, thanks to Lemur for the titles.
Friends, we finished a new subgenius video, the cerebral reformatter, just in time for Winterstar, but not in time for a fresh hour of slack number 1191.
So this is really Reverend Susie the floozy's episode of Bob's slack time funhouse from WREK.org, Atlanta.
Her number 752, the inauguramus special, a subgenius farewell to George.
Ongoing proceedings are serious.
The program you are about to hear.
Bob's slack time funhouse is parody, satire, and comedy.
Any reference to Bob, the church of the subgenius, religion, politics, or any other touchy subjects is intended only as humor and should cast no reflection on the high standards of WREK Atlanta, its staff, or that of Georgia Tech.
I can't, I really do thank the staff of Georgia Tech.
The chairman and vice chairman.
The members.
For WREK.
And Bob's slack time funhouse.
Um, and possibly Susan.
Hmm, yes.
She speaks English a lot better than I do.
Otherwise I wouldn't have put her on.
Um, yeah, yeah, look, I, I picked the best person I could find.
Um, people, people know we're close.
I'm, I'm, um, look, as I said the other day.
Oh, I feel like I'm more of a senior now than I used to be a senior in boxing.
Yeah.
So far, she's done a pretty good job when it comes to like a bad göre.
Kind of which you know kicked some kind of belly into that sort of stuff, but, uh, man.
I need to tell you something about her first guy.
According to her, however, I, um, 3, 4 and up, she's one of the adjusted best polygona wives to the world to the way she ==
I don't think you would hit yourself.
So you meet the utmost mark, baby bitch.
Put me down.
It's a pity I'll only be able to use it this one time.
Yeah?
For the inauguration edition of Bob's Slack Time Funhouse.
Oh.
Yeah, they're finally booting that jerk out and that Irish guy's gonna take his place.
And I think it's terrible.
Oh, yeah, no more George.
Prologue.
Now it's morning in Washington, D.C.
Good morning, George.
What'll it be for breakfast, waffles or pancakes?
I want pancakes.
Hmm.
It's on account of slimy politics here.
We have all this unemployment.
You're crazy. That ain't possible.
No goodness whatever adorning his memory.
Arrogant in his vice was that one.
The head of the state had an elastic mouth that made him look like a harassed cannibal.
Gosh, okay.
Holding enormous official powers, he schemed ceaselessly to expand them.
Because it was expected of him by those who had pushed him
into the middle of the world.
He was the only one who could get him into office.
He had the cunning of the unintelligent and the frantic energy of the lazy.
The sole secret of his rise in life was the fact that he was a product of chance and knew it and aspired to nothing else.
I'm, I'm, I'm, uh...
Pancakes!
This beast blocked the door.
You should see the kind of human driftwood, the kind of men who like the way things are now.
Can you imagine that there are human beings who like it?
There's no such thing.
Well, there are, you know.
As if on cue.
Moving on to new business, what act of unmitigated evil shall the Republican Party undertake this week?
Oh! Oh, oh, oh!
You've already done enough, Nader.
He had summoned them all to Washington as his friends and personal advisors for a private unofficial conference on the national crisis.
Uh, uh, uh...
I beheld the shade of him who made the great refusal impelled by cowardice.
The...
The frankly mood of the world would have been astounded had the United States acted unilaterally.
Um...
How do you like the moratorium on brains?
I received a briefing on the threats to our nation.
I vowed to do everything in my power to keep us safe.
But I never did.
Damn you!
Oops, too late.
He doesn't understand.
He just doesn't understand.
Love the stats.
It's a monster!
Kill it!
I'm a monster!
Don't look at me!
Are you crazy?
Are you?
I...
Why such schism threatens it?
Only got so long before Mr. President doesn't mean a whole lot.
Uh...
Don't you see that you've run out of time?
He answered...
Gosh, I don't think I ever said I'm worried about Obama.
It's kind of one of those, uh, exaggerations.
Oh.
You don't care, do you?
Uh...
Not for decades.
We've got to get our act together better this season.
He's not ultra-bright at the best of times.
Sometimes I think the whole family's unhinged.
It's obvious that drastic measures have to be taken.
We can't let things go on the way they're going much longer.
We'll think of something.
Right.
Sure.
Let's see.
When hell freezes over.
Fact is, this year the rate of business failures had doubled.
Just trying to spread around the joy.
But...
You cannot fail to realize our disastrous deficit.
And that we expect you to pay.
I don't know why people do that.
I don't know.
That is your job, not ours.
You could save us now.
You could find a way to make things work if you wanted to.
Boy, they really miscalculated.
Uh, as your president, I'm watching too much daytime TV to save others' lives.
Tough guy.
Yeah, yeah, tough guy.
Are you counting on my not saying that the responsibility is yours?
That it was your goddamn policies that brought us where we are?
Uh, uh, uh.
You cannot solve a problem unless you diagnose the problem.
You gotta do better than that.
I got the conks, said the idiot George Ghibli Clay.
He's gone mad with power, like that Albert Schweitzer guy.
Get off that righteous horse of yours and come to your senses.
You can't expect us to ditch the machinery of state.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We've got to preserve the system.
Yeah, of course I did.
You're the fake.
So what, George said.
His shoulders bunched.
I got the conch, ain't I, Roger?
Roger said, hell, under his breath.
Yes, and I've somehow acquired a nasty old racist sidekick.
Happy?
George began to mutter vaguely.
I'm going to him with this conch in my hands.
I'm going to hold it out.
Look, I'm gonna say, I don't ask you to be a sport, I'll say.
Not because you're strong, but because what's right's right, I'm gonna say.
You've got to.
George ended flushed and trembling.
This man is obviously a psychotic.
I'd like to hold off judgment on a thing like that, sir, until all the facts are in.
But it's reality.
But there can be little debate about the results.
Oh, my God.
Insanity in the halls of Congress.
My eyes.
Stoned women in the streets.
Pictures of older men forcing naked young girls to have anal sex.
I wish I could.
That can be arranged.
Yee-haw.
That's a fact.
Doing it makes my stomach turn.
Oh, yeah, right.
Think about that.
Prostitution is on the march.
Oh, my God.
What the hell is this?
You just don't know.
It requires an expenditure of money that is commiserate with keeping a promise to our prostitutes
to make sure that they're well-paid, well-trained, well-equipped.
Ooh, cool.
We had a 19-year-old woman this weekend.
Right in the krillings.
Now there's a guy who knows how to get his point across.
Ouch, said the hooker.
W, I'm Mr. W.
If my name begins to trouble you, here's a way to help your thinking.
Won't you watch me when I'm winking?
Wonderful wink with my right eye, that's once.
Wonderful wink with my left eye, that's twice.
Two winks are nice.
They're the double of one.
Oh, I'm winking double.
That's how W is done.
Blink twice for yes.
Let's hear from the stone gutter world council before we act too rashly.
That's a crap shoot.
Isn't it, though?
Now, Bob Doe will read from the Necronomicon.
Rise, please.
Oh, my God.
A, Zach, Azuri, Galanith, Melodic, Doon, Osmeramus, and Brinkaby.
And the prayer had been answered.
By Satan.
And suddenly things turned ugly.
This little calls the whole thing.
He turned incredulously to look at his mother.
Little miss psycho bitch.
You haven't switched from liquor to dope by any chance, have you?
George grinned back, wiping his chin.
Jinkum.
He giggled and rubbed the stuff over his cheeks.
It's pathetic.
Texas mudslide.
What the hell did you mean?
How are we to cope if you leave us?
We'll be swept like driftwood in that terror that's running loose in the world.
Your father, we'll call him.
Your father was a good-for-nothing chimp.
Father was a gypsy.
I've never said that.
You can't quit.
His mother screamed in blind panic.
You can't turn deserter because now they take it out on your family.
The look of terror in her eyes was real.
In a moment her voice came back low and droning.
If you give up and vanish like all those men who...
Oh, that's that.
Daddy, my picture.
Right there.
Yeah.
There isn't a dirty cover-up in this entire business that I don't know about.
And your hand is in every one of them.
You reek of it.
You know, Wicked Old Leg was well into her eighties with wavy white hair.
And the pierced eyes.
Piercing hawk eyes.
The smile would have cracked her facial muscles.
You think your life's a mystery.
Duh.
Yes, they're into group sex, orgies and all that.
Baby sacrifice.
Go away, Ivan.
It's none of your business.
Yes, something sinister is coming.
Soon.
Ivan might have done as he was told.
But on his heels came a much tougher proposition.
The door of the office was suddenly flung open.
And Neil catapulted himself inside.
Oh, wow.
Neil's eyes were wide.
Pardon, Junior Ranger?
Neil told George excitedly.
Her image is lies with the truth.
And vermouth.
Duh.
This is gin.
Oh, sure.
Two measures of gin and a splash of vermouth and you've got yourself a liar's martini.
I'm using.
I swear to God.
I don't know what happened.
It's all a big mistake.
He knows that, uh...
He's got to believe me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I don't know what Neil's like.
See, because he sees things.
I hear the voices.
George said sharply.
Oh, yeah, right.
Whatever you say, pal.
Whack-a.
The question is, are you either with us or against us?
What?
No.
Yes.
And I'm...
I mean, no.
No.
I don't know.
I just don't know.
Particularly not him.
Tell me about it.
You're right on that.
Yeah.
And Neil went on screen.
Like I said.
Ah!
Shut up!
Do you mean George's young brother worked it out?
Father was Lord of the Flowers?
I...
We...
We don't talk about sources and methods.
The Bush crime family all know things about each other that they use as threats.
They blackmail each other to make them do or not do what they want.
The antagonism between the Bush crime family was mutual, powerful, and lasting.
No, wait!
Jib cried, leaping to his feet.
Brother, he said peremptorily, I need your dead horse.
Do I?
The two Bush boys faced each other.
George sighed, sensing the rising antagonism.
I...
Jib, Robert, and Bush snarled at him.
I want to be president.
I want it.
Ah.
They were both red in the face and found looking at each other difficult.
Why shouldn't I be given the fulfillment of my duty?
The fulfillment of my desires, as you always fulfill any desire of your own.
Because I...
I...
There is a belief that you'll never be found out.
And if you should be, you believe the family will use its money and muscle to save you,
as it has always done in the past.
Jib glared at George.
Don't I have the right to demand any form of happiness I choose?
Gosh, okay.
Jib's voice lifted into the wine of virtuous recrimination.
I'm your brother, therefore I'm your responsibility.
Hmm.
Um...
Isn't that a debt which you owe me?
You what?
There it was, he thought, looking at his family.
The nature of their pleas for mercy.
They wanted to hold him.
To keep him in the sacrificial furnace.
To make him let them devour the last of him in the name of mercy, forgiveness, and brother-cannibal love.
And what's wrong with that?
It was for the ultimate good of the family.
Through clenched teeth, George said,
Black hell.
He punched out two of her front teeth.
Faced with too many awful implications,
George ducked away from them.
And here he is sitting at the table in the Oval Office in big tears.
And started coming down to his cheeks and splashing them on the table.
Said George Bush, wetly.
It was late.
His staff had gone.
But he dreaded the emptiness of the evening ahead.
He felt as if the enemy who had wiped him out were waiting for him,
in the darkness beyond the glow of Washington.
He stopped.
Hey, what the hell?
Click.
Slam it in your chest, bitch.
Put the W.
Burn it through your flesh.
Verbally possessed.
Never second-guessed.
No mind like David Koresh.
The man sat on the edge of a desk in a pose of casual, patient waiting.
For a moment, George did not see him.
But on raising his eyes, he stiffened.
Yeah.
Trump, Prince Obama, George said.
And a scowl came on his face.
What are you doing here?
I thought that you would want to see me tonight.
George watched him.
Suspiciously.
Calling you down, man.
I mean, there you are.
This is my room.
I'm, I'm.
You got no right to come in my room.
This is a total violation.
You got no rights coming in a colored man's room.
I, I, I.
He shrugged unhappily.
I have nothing to say to you.
Well, I have nothing to say to you.
It doesn't mean we can't talk.
George worked his jaw like a steam shovel.
Authority sat on his shoulder like an ape.
I'm, I'm, uh.
Just you and me.
As president, I have a duty to lead.
Ahem.
I'm sorry.
You know I am the president of the United States.
Yep.
George looked at the rock open mouth.
George, it's over.
What?
Yeah, it's done.
Get out of here.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Son of a bitch.
Took you this long to tell me?
George, it's been over for a while.
Oh, man.
I just got your messages and I, uh.
Oh, really?
Yeah, it's, uh.
Oh, oh, wow.
So I'm way late.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
George sat shrugging.
You're trying to get me in trouble with my father.
Your father was a horse's ass.
Yep.
And you know what?
I respect that.
I respect that a lot.
George's face contorted with thought.
That boy's smart.
Maybe I should put him on the Supreme Court.
Maybe you can see now.
Suppose you had to sit out here and read books because you're black.
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
I got a gal who reads things for me.
Reading wouldn't save that neck.
I, I look.
Please, please.
George smiled helplessly in an attempt to make friends.
His voice grew soft and persuasive.
I told the Crown Prince Obama how much I appreciate his vision.
But suddenly allのr read what you see.
How can you?
It's the same thing.
Go on.
I've been right with him.
I, I, I, I do.
RICHARD P.
Marcus Garvey.
Mr. President.
George sneered and attempted bravery.
Each of us is guided by our own convictions, and to these we must stay faithful.
He repeated his words rhythmically as though he had said them many times before.
You know, there's a lot of people in the world who don't believe that people whose skin color may not be the same as ours pick themselves up.
I reject that.
Bush flushed, looking sideways.
I reject that strongly.
His voice faded away.
Then he rallied and manfully tried again.
I receive calmness in the storms of the presidency.
But thousands of lives have been lost to the wrath of Hurricane Katrina.
I don't play Death Track.
And the amazing thing about Katrina is that there has been a fantastic response.
What's that?
Minority ownership of businesses are up because we create an environment for the entrepreneurial spirit to be strong.
Say what?
This is a tribute to Hurricane.
Hurricane Katrina.
Yeah.
You exterminate.
Crown Prince and I established a strong personal bond.
President horse's ass.
There's no need to continue this obstinance.
It's not in your interest to do so.
Want me to tell you what will happen?
Gosh, okay.
Take you to the booty hut.
Tie you up with a collar like a dog.
I got the conch, said George indignantly, scowling in the gloom.
You shut up.
George's pathetic faith in the conch.
The conch really has no value.
It's become magical, a sort of democratic process, and he thinks that it will stand up against force.
I've got the conch.
Yeah.
The rock stood up and held out his hands.
I think anything I would say would just be redundant.
I haven't finished yet.
Read the patent number, bitch.
Suddenly, the rock struck with all his might.
It's Britain time.
The conch exploded into a thousand white fragments.
Oh, no.
And ceased to exist.
My dad's going to kill me.
There isn't a time.
I won't try for you anymore, said the rock contemptuously.
The conch is gone.
Ehh, ehh, ehh, ehh, ehh.
Suddenly, George's eyes centered and grew quiet and mad.
Duh.
Gradually, his sorrow and his anger grew into words.
Um, Mr. President.
He sniveled and his voice shook.
I, I, I never wanted the presidency taken away.
I, I, I'm, uh, oh.
Give that back.
George shouted over and over.
Give it back.
We don't need your ideas.
We don't need your advice.
And we don't need lames in the hallway.
Take a walk.
I am filled with disbelief.
Now, you just get out.
Terrible sadness.
Get out quick.
And a quiet.
Ow.
Unyielding anger.
Out, you're finished.
I should have knew, George said hopelessly.
I guess maybe way back in my head, I did.
Oh, I'm nuts.
Carl, I'm in a very tough spot here.
I know, but there's nothing to worry about.
Just hang tight.
They came to my office, Carl.
No, no, look, I know we have a deal.
But if I knew this was going to be happening, I wouldn't have signed on.
Just be calm and know that you have the full power of the White House behind you.
Okay, I'll be in touch.
What's the best way out of here?
I really didn't have an exit strategy.
Who is it?
Get out of my trailer, I won't get out.
It's 30 years over.
Let's get out of here. I'm not shaking that guy's hand.
Come on, let's get out of here.
The Treasury says the national debt is climbing to the sky.
And government expenditures have never been so high.
It makes a fella give a gleam of pride
within his eye to see how our economy expands.
The country's in the very best of hands.
The country is
in a terrible state.
We don't know what to do about it.
He was burdened by another primal concern.
I'm going to lose my job.
George saw his opportunity.
I'm not a lame duck, I'm a sprintin' duck.
Don't worry about that. My boys are there.
They'll take care of it.
Where was I? Oh, yes, yes.
As if on cue.
A blushing expose of the strange activities that took place behind closed doors.
Far below the Earth's surface,
a world of fruited meetings and change.
Here, here. Yes.
We have a winner.
Right on.
We.
The country's in the very best of hands.
They said surround this place they got.
This big, impressionable parking lot.
Just sit around it and you know what.
Up there they call to me if I moan.
I'm a little bit of a fool.
I think it's still rough.
They sat in a stately boardroom which was inadequately heated.
A man from Washington sat among them.
Nobody knew his exact job or title, but they knew that he was the man from Washington.
They preferred not to find out.
He? Who he?
Don't look at me.
It seems to me, said the chairman, that the top problem for us to consider is John Galt.
I mean, the ruler of the...
The leader of the board.
Say, you're sold on this.
Whatever, man.
Their leader was a civilian with the manner of an intellectual of the public relations species.
There's a man who is doing something.
That is a revolution, man.
Don't you understand?
Today we have broken our long law against your race.
May it be a sign that though the world is now dark, better days are at hand.
What is that supposed to mean?
And that friendship shall be renewed between our peoples.
He watched the men around him
with a look of so great an indignation that he seemed paralyzed.
Professor, I don't blame the shoreline.
It's a beautiful America.
America can only happen right here in the good old USA.
All right, I'll pick you up tomorrow at 11 o'clock.
I'll take you to the zoo, then we'll go to the ball game.
Oh, you got yourself a meal ticket and you hate to let go.
Sure it's a meal ticket for me, I admit it.
But it's also a windfall for somebody who's trying to crash national politics.
Something white fell out and I picked it up.
What's this?
And it was addressed to the leader.
What?
It was a letter and it read.
I love Mexicans.
Some say they're essential to our economy.
Others say they're a drain on our resources.
All I know is burritos are delicious.
Scrawled in pencil by some illiterate hand.
And pencil on tablet paper.
No, I don't think so.
It's exactly what it looks like.
Troll, cheer some lipstick on.
How awful.
Just look at my jacket.
I'm telling what that screwball might do.
Hey, man, it's going in a newspaper.
The Bushes and drugs.
Yeah, under the influence of drugs.
And it's gone for three days.
Shooting up in the big town.
He's stuck in with the needle.
Why he's not better than right up his nose.
Drop him off somebody.
Everybody getting caught in a fallout.
Getting their ass blowed up.
Take my advice and get him out of town before this thing explodes in our face.
You do just as much of a dumb as he is.
Excuse me.
We don't want to quarrel over past mistakes,
said the chairman in a tone of pleading reproach.
The truth is that it's an embarrassing and personally painful thing.
And if people will vote for an alcoholic
hillbilly leader, they'll vote for anybody.
You can say that again.
I never chase foul balls.
You can't know any less about it than that
alcoholic hillbilly who's in Washington now.
You lucky I'm pushing this death trap.
I don't play.
But get things going.
Make people work again.
Make them produce.
If it's an alien product, what is supposed to do to take a war?
Lead us to a peaceful, scientific, industrial age and to prosperity.
We'll do whatever you say implicitly with your head and your soul.
You'll be.
You'll be the economic dictator of the nation.
Yeah.
I suppose it's connected to the nominee.
The nominee is connected to the Treasury.
But he ain't connected to the Treasury.
He sits around in his thigh bone.
Brothers in the black room. Brothers in the black room.
I deal with housing in the community.
Bad plumbing, bad heating and bad rats.
The only way to set this thing
together is with self-determination, self-respect and self-defense.
We don't go for Jesus no more.
We must adjust ourselves to the level of our audience, which is pretty low.
Violence is a cleansing force.
Nonviolence has proven to be nonfunctional.
So it's guns, baby.
The end result will be our own political, social, economic future.
Bazookas, tanks, flamethrowers, guns, baby.
A gun is not a gun.
It's not going to get your job.
Who the hell wants a job?
Here, here.
You know what, Mavs?
I bet you he's somewhere getting blazed up with red man.
Where you been? Mecca.
The mad Obama himself.
The man says he's the president of the United States.
Lay some bread on, lay some bread on, lay some bread on.
We could create a subliminal trauma
throughout the land by using the advertising that comes out of your toilet.
Thank you.
We'll see you tomorrow.
Ahem.
Yeah, it was your idea.
Not bad, not bad.
You're going to make a great chairman.
Brother, you were voted in here on a jive hummer.
Now, how are things going to happen, man?
When are things going to start to change?
Where is the revolution?
You were talking about, man.
Hey, what do you think of the Panthers?
They look good against the Bulldogs, but they need more depth than quarterback.
Hey, man, I've seen that nonsense you're trying to show us here.
You're trying to dupe everybody in this joint.
Now, how do you like that?
Yeah. What's that for?
Look at you, the high water pants, your two button suit.
Now, what kind of suit is that?
You're supposed to be a soul brother.
Look at his brother's hair.
And I know you a jive cat.
Ain't nobody around who help you in anything.
Everybody is a shut up, cut up.
Ain't one of them around.
Are you going to tell me that's a lie?
Bitch, I'll f*** your ass up.
I used to be an exterminator.
Hmm.
Your lawyer wants to be the prosecuting attorney.
Bail him out and get him in here.
Mr. President, I'd like them neighbors to know we go out together once in a while.
I love you. Did you take your pill?
It's OK. Just don't send me the laundry bill.
What do you got to say to yourself, sonny?
I feel like an Oreo cookie.
You look like a pile of sh**.
The best I can do is 350.
Thousand.
100 is the best I can do.
Hey man.
If you want reality, I'm going to put you back on the streets.
1,200 is the best I can do.
I think anything I would say would just be redundant.
Make it six. The best I can do.
Don't push me, pal. It's perfect for you.
If it's me, the best is 9,000.
9,000?
The best I can do.
Forget it.
Make it six. Six. Six thousand.
Yeah, yeah.
At least he's not superstitious.
Thank you.
I think we got a winner.
We bet.
It's going to be a pleasure working with you.
You said we were going to do things with integrity and style.
And that's why you get less money.
Because you don't think.
I never thought of it that way.
What we're doing is worse than anything our predecessors have ever done.
But now we have a moment of joviality.
We relax.
We sit down.
We partake of a bit of grass.
I've got some good shit.
I have a feeling that there's a lot of untapped talent around here.
It's funny because it's well-informed.
That's what I always say.
I shifted myself into a cheerful trance
When the skeleton in the closet started to dance
A goblin giggled with fiendish glee
A shout banged out from the big banshee
Amazement was in every ghostly glance
When the skeleton in the closet started to dance
All the witches were in stitches
While the steps made rhythmic thumps
And they nearly dropped the broomsticks
When he tried to do the bumps
You never heard such unearthly laughter
Or such hilarious groans
When the skeleton in the closet rattled his bones
Excellent.
It was a dark road, but it led in a new direction.
I tell you, the day Rome falls,
there will be a shout of freedom.
Freedom such as the world has never heard before.
Oh, there's already a guy in here.
Far be it from me to gloat at another downfall.
I have a feeling no children are going to be crying
when this puppy is put to sleep.
The country is in a terrible state.
We don't know what to do about it.
That's not what I'm interested in.
At a gaudy White House reception,
the president proclaimed...
Hey, hey, look at me!
I'm a TV antenna.
Am I getting good reception?
Mr. President, you're a recovering alcoholic.
The wild turkey flows.
We've been here.
I'm sensible.
He knows that, and I know that.
It is no accident that we haven't been hit by intelligence in more than four years.
I think he recognizes that I can't party alone.
You're lucky if your vices get any attention at all.
Like my secretary of the state.
And it's important to make this point at the outset.
When he's abroad,
one of the most prehensile-ass people in the city.
Don't pay no attention to that, Algie.
He can't.
He can't even hold a gun, much less shoot it.
And of course, we all know that for two years in Austin, Texas,
Dick Cheney played Magenta.
That's a male role. What's up with that?
He acts like it never happened now.
I think it's disgusting.
It's awful.
Cheney.
The great white hunter.
You see, people don't see the fun side of Dick.
In fact, I didn't know a thing about that hunting episode
down in Texas till I saw him on America's Most Wanted.
But Dick's a good man.
He has a good heart.
My God.
This man is dying.
Someone get a doctor!
Well, he's a good man.
I'm sorry Vice President Cheney couldn't be here tonight.
Oh yeah.
Don't shoot.
What's that?
Cover your heart!
Pay no attention to the man behind the curtain.
Cheney, what a goofball.
Justice Scalia.
Justice Alito.
Well observed.
Hey boys, bet it feels good to be out from under those robes.
Everybody laughed.
It's funny because it's true.
Yes! Victory swig!
I met him in a boxcar a couple of years ago.
I was fooling around with my harmonica and...
Shh!
...well, she comes over and joins in.
I haven't been able to shake him since.
Boy, this is the first time I've relaxed since I took office and it feels good!
I love America because it's full of Americans.
I don't know where you did say you hated Crooklyn.
We're an America that should come together, Republican and Democrat and Alex Trebek of Jeopardy.
You look wretched.
George suddenly realized something was missing.
Could be home asleep.
Let me tell you, I saw his eyes.
He was stoned.
There he is.
Begin accomplice.
If you weren't drunk I'd...
Oh my God!
The President's off his ass!
Woohoo!
Can't catch this doggie!
Mr. President, stop!
Toga!
Mr. President, what are you doing?
Sir, you've got to put on your clothes!
You can't make me!
I don't want to wear a suit!
Good Lord!
I want to be naked!
He's more licker than man!
Man drink like that and he's gonna eat.
He's just going to die.
I hope it's true.
Boy, I'm so sorry.
I'm gonna kiss his ass.
Ha ha!
Look at me!
I'm running unopposed!
Woohoo!
That's my first class.
Mr. President!
It would be prudent to go.
Hail to the Chief!
Da da dee da dee da.
You're hallucinating, George.
Damn!
Trapdoor.
No elected office holder had made such an abrupt or eccentric exit from public life.
I've seen enough.
As honorary chairman of the welcoming committee, it is my privilege to introduce Mr. President.
To extend to you a laurel and hearty handshake.
Yeah, I love you, Pill.
You see, in another 25 years you'll be able to shake your hands in broad daylight.
I just want a lifeboat.
Joe, I'd like to go and crucify you, baby.
You, did you take your pill?
Man's been elected and you voted for him.
We all voted for him.
Because we thought no one else would vote for him.
You're the one that was paid the 30 pieces of silver.
Have you forgotten that?
And I will defend that mistake with my life.
Forget it.
Where's the president?
He wanted to keep partying, so he snuck out the back.
Great.
If you want to better yourself, you need to spend more time with someone you can read
or at least get through a single sentence without spitting.
Uh, is there anything important we needed to, uh, remember or do?
Oh!
Ivan, in a flash of generosity, had returned with a second van load of free plants.
My goodness, Ivan.
I'm stunned.
Super Jenkum Haze.
That's why I'm the way you should be.
Now, young bushy pot plants, which he spread out making decorative ceiling.
All right.
Now, supposing a certain unmentionable worm whose initials are TB was trying to use that
to shove his way into the white house so TB could put the screws so he could turn out
the lights in those lights.
Not anymore.
No one would be stupid enough to believe that.
If I vote Democrat, it will not happen again.
And we'll be here to save whatever's left.
So there's gonna be a new order of things, huh?
Everybody's gonna cut himself a nice fat slice of the John Doe's, eh?
I don't remember.
What do you think?
Cut him some slack.
Uh, they overbooked the lobotomy lab and we had to wait an hour and a half to get our
lobotomies.
It's all dripping out of your ears now.
We're ready to meet his terms.
We're ready to turn the whole economy over to him.
We're willing to surrender altogether.
If he'd only tell us when, how.
Where.
The place?
The grounds of the capital, Washington, D.C.
The Potomac in the sunset is a river turned to flame.
And the blue-hot cherry blossoms is like nothing you can name.
That's why we like to be in Washington, D.C.
Oh, it's cold out here, Mother.
Congress decided to leave the Capitol.
We hold all inaugurations outdoors.
Whoo!
Nice one.
Hey, how you doing?
Your new president gonna give you a new pair of shoes?
Yeah, he's working on it.
Hey, Barney, listen.
You know, I'm a fine-looking kind of man.
I got real regular features, real regular clothes.
Yeah, you're very...
Well, we've gotta be flexible.
Then this country will once more become a sanctuary for a vanishing species, the rational
being.
What are you talking about, man?
Whack-o.
I've stood things this long.
I can stand them just a little longer.
It won't be long.
As if on cue.
The sheriff is a .
One thing, the sheriff is near.
Now, I've got a friend who's named Rivers.
The sheriff is a .
What's the deal?
A guy needs somebody.
Near.
It's a great day for a celebration and a great day for United Tools.
We're gonna waste a minute for Mr. Rich, because he said he'd be here.
Today marks the miracle of story.
Here at United Tools, once again, we're gonna be here.
The sheriff, who's been bankrupt and about to disappear forever, is now celebrating a
new lease on life.
Can we see the president, Grandpa?
Can we, Mom?
You can watch him from here.
But I wanna get up close.
No dice.
you, and the establishment, and you people who are trying to make me part of
the unestablished establishment.
Well absorbed.
Oh, I can see them going up to the grandstand now.
Oh, it's a very impressive sight.
Come on.
Now, we've got a great day for United Tools.
We're gonna waste a minute for Mr. Rich, because he said he'd be here.
Oh, we've got a great day for Mr. Rich, because he said he'd be here.
Come on, we've got a great day for Mr. Rich, because he said he'd be here.
Oh, it's a very impressive sight.
That bastard.
A new king?
No more kings are going to push us around, son.
We're Americans.
Yeah, right.
I hope nothing unsavory happens during my visit.
As you know, I am the president of the United States.
Which president?
All right, let's do this.
Let's kick some ass.
Away from me, loser.
Oh, Jesus.
Oh.
How do you say useless in Texan?
President.
Adolf.
Bush.
All right, maintain.
Maintain.
I'm going to pretend I like being here.
Got a hangover?
I just want a picture of that drugstore where I found you.
What do you got to say to yourself, sonny?
Howdy.
There goes the man's face, see?
See that guy's reaction when Bush shakes his hand?
Surprise, then disappointment.
Their embrace was a battle.
The climax of victory.
It was a political act.
Brownie, you're doing a heck of a job.
Say what?
Why are they sitting together?
In this country.
Once the election is over, everyone accepts the people's choice.
Ha, ha, ha.
Ha, sure.
Guess I should let him know he'll be taking the reins.
The Rock looked malevolently at the idiot George.
Give up and get out of the way and let those of us who can start from scratch out of the ruins.
His voice was mocking, harsh, and tense.
Play it any way you please.
Dumbly, dumb George shook his head.
His lips were tightly compressed.
I hate that kind of bastard.
I've seen plenty of him.
He always wins.
I hate that.
I hate that kind of guy.
Who is the president right now about all this?
It sounds like he's angry.
I think it's fair to say that the president is a war to fight.
He's going to continue to fight it in a way that brings people together.
Hold hands.
Come on, it's not gay.
There's guns in the room.
Because that's what American people expect from their leaders in Washington.
No, sir.
No, sirree.
Bum, bum, bum.
No.
You're going to have him say anything.
Why don't you let him say something simple and real?
Something.
Yeah.
Let's hit them with some rhetorical eloquence.
Mother, they're beginning.
Oh.
Let's listen.
My fellow Americans, in the words of Sigmund Freud, I have a dream.
My friends, our purple mountains with ramparts red glare,
white with foam and justice for all,
fruity plains gallantly streaming,
from sea to shining sea with a shining city on a shining hill above a shining prairie,
and maybe some shiny trees and a few shrubs, I see a shiny America.
Ah.
Be, be, be, be.
At the moment of greatest passion and conviction,
that curtain flapped in his head and he forgot what he'd been driving at.
Ah.
Ooh.
He saw a look of bewilderment on all the faces around him.
So today I announce my resignation as president.
Yeah!
1-2-1-2, ladies and gentlemen, I am Chris Rock.
It is my pleasure, it is my treat, it is my honor to introduce to you the man that needs no introductions.
Ladies and gents, get ready for the Ticalian Stallion, a.k.a. Johnny Blaze, a.k.a. the Iron Lung, a.k.a. Mr. King K.
a.k.a. Mr. Weatherby, a.k.a. Mr. Henkey, a.k.a. Mr. Tim, a.k.a. Marla Gibbs, a.k.a. the Say Hey Kid, a.k.a. the Frisco Kid, a.k.a. Kid Dynamite, a.k.a. Velvet Jones, a.k.a. Jojo Dancer, a.k.a. Joe Ski Love,
a.k.a. Donnie Brasco, a.k.a. Donnie Moss, a.k.a. Donnie Osmond, a.k.a.
Stupid.
Excuse me while I whip this out.
You don't have to accept. It's a terrible job. Don't take it.
The changes I'm going to make will be minimal.
I'm not going to rock the...
The boat? Rocking the boat's a drag.
What you do is sink the boat.
And there's no sense sinking nothing unless you can salvage with productive alternatives.
And, brothers, you can't change nothing with rhetoric and slogans.
Because if a man's really got the truth in his pocket, he doesn't talk about it.
He hangs it out on a shingle where people can see it.
So from now on, the name of this agency is Truth and Soul.
Right on!
Yeah!
The leader spread his hands out in a gesture of pained helplessness.
Just give me 24 hours to come up with a brilliant idea to save our town.
How do we know that?
Just 24 hours.
Yeah!
Come on, come on.
Bring it back, back.
Levely, stand.
And then back.
Oh, y'all old school studios, 54.
Bring it.
And then back.
Oh, dude, I did the work.
Fuckin' hell.
I do.
Anything.
Thanks, man.
Odeon is where I'm fleeing.
All I've seen.
Dominant supreme being.
Face the mental.
Deep concentration.
Break the point on a pencil.
Keep my cliches out your dental.
Capisce?
That I've been through is cause for parental discretion.
No question.
My website connections are laid confidential.
World don't stop unless it's mental.
That and residential.
You with it?
Contain forever and a day.
Till I'm old and decayed.
I'm committed.
Look, Ma, we did it.
Time for the world.
Tell it to my firstborn and my baby girl.
Did it my way.
Take the low road or the highway.
Out the sunroof yelling, thank God it's Friday.
Show a nigga love.
If he got my sound full of plug, he's not underground.
Call him up.
When I flood the airwaves, household and stairways.
Waiting for these paydays.
Think not of the ends.
If I got 20, my brother get 10.
Now let the madness begin.
Nothing in the world that I won't do.
I give my world to you if you want me to.
I do.
Anything.
There's nothing in the world that I won't do.
I give my world to you if you want me to.
I do.
Anything.
Yo, yo, yo.
We got love for those with love for us.
Baby, you can look but don't touch.
You fried off the dust.
And plus, the only thing I trust is a fund.
They no fun.
Just paranoid niggas toting guns in a paddle.
Keep us camouflaged in the shadows.
That's where I bring this tale that you never get the tattles.
Obliterate the tri-state and the crime rate.
Tell it to my firstborn and my baby girl.
I don't swine.
Niggas fly straight.
You can call it fate.
And if it ain't mine, call it fake.
Bottom line in the case.
Spoon feed the track.
Just a taste of the side dish.
Soon for the day I come right like Embouché.
For them dead presidents.
What you saying?
He saying?
She saying?
They say.
Fake hate the premises.
Caught up in the mainland.
Sentence this song.
To 25 years hard labor in the system.
Where it takes the form of my wisdom.
Respect mine.
Take my time and protect nine.
Next on the front line.
Mr. Mac.
No more, no less.
What you see is what your ass get.
Set it off.
I suggest.
I'm a man.
I fight.
Niggas fly straight.
Let yourDY done, so anything you want to do with me in my world.
No business man this post.
Hip hop on godt that I got me car.
Yup everything'spay me.
So and contains.
Yeah.
Your cry for help.
訴고 scoop.
Bust aうわ wall of 잠aime.
Ça quei eras veux mais?
The thing with itつväc yine???
Started playing and he s'old площt my balet,
Get on out of here
We're gonna have some greasy fingers
And some chickens
And all the beautiful things that people have
Who have it
And you ain't got it
So get on out, you understand
We're not gonna take any more of your jobs
But let's move and fall, you understand
To the soul
This is the beginning of a better world for all of us
Oh, that's out of the question
What are you talking about, man?
You heard his speech
Yeah
Sorry, kid
No, come off it
Why?
Personally, I'd agree with you, but
We can't give people the impression that we're endorsing that speech
I'm a freedom-loving man, but people aren't ready for freedom
We can't adopt an idealistic theory which the country isn't ready for
There's no emoticon for what I'm feeling
It's the most vicious speech ever made
It will make people demand to be happy
It's only a speech
It was much too intellectual for the common man
People are too dumb to understand it
Ooh, good point
The leader
Burst
Burst out laughing
I'm not gonna help you pretend that there's still a way to make it work and to save your neck
There isn't
Give up
All of you
You and your Washington friends and your looting planners and the whole of your cannibal philosophy
You forgot one detail, Mr. Big Shot
You forgot the prize stooge of the world
This is a matter of intelligence and, uh...
Oh, can't you see this man isn't a hero?
Oh, absolutely
Uh, couldn't agree more
Do I?
You're a fake, I can prove it
Meaning?
Ask the president
Please do repeat again, and I will translate it for the president
Ask if he intends to take legal action
The president replied, I ain't fungified, Heidi, who bought no liquefaction, no ways
Then scratched his rear, hitched up his pants, and scratched his rear again
And he said more that I don't remember now
Given what we've been saying about him
Warm, tender, caring, kind to people
There's a wonderful story of sharing with the president that one of his policies had actually handicapped
a baby
We have new ideas about how people should live
George Bush doesn't care about people
He'll know
George Bush doesn't care about black people
I will not even honor that with a response
Screw him
This is an outrage
Man, what's wrong with your face?
He slowly began to come apart
I, I, we, we, we don't talk about, you know, the dark races
Like, I, we, we, we, we, we, we, we like to torture
That has been our...
Policy
You lazy bastard
I've never said that
Um
You've got to keep at me
Through clenched teeth, George said
The American people expect us to torture people, but I really meant to say
Men are only too willing to hate and love and kill if they believe it is not a sin
Or that they will be held guiltless in the eyes of their God
Prayer and religion sustain me
I never want to impose my religion on anybody else
With the Middle East
Oh, that's awful
After those holy words, fetid marsh fumes doesn't hide it
Hell yes
What's funny about it, George demanded defensively, entranced with his own picture
The president resolved all doubts about his choice for a replacement
I, I, I want you to know something
When I say I'm going to do something, I'm going to do it
There was a pause
Then his voice came slowly, changed, grave
But when I say I'm going to turn our duties over to others
You know, I totally reject that
Dog, we don't need lame bulls**t
The rock snarled at him
George cried out
Expect an epic battle between the old regime
To put an end to your dreams
What is coming is even worse
The leader burst out laughing
It's too much, met you
And, uh, uh, that's, that's reality
If you want reality, I'm going to put you back on the street
This was too bitter for George
Who forgot his timidity and he began to cry out shrilly
Then maybe you ought to just go on home
Bulls**t
George butted back on his heels and showed his teeth as far as he could go
The rock began screaming wildly
I'm gonna kill you
His desires for revenge knew no limits
Pain mingled with his pleasures
Creating a bloodlust insanity
Are you crazy?
First time to realize there's no one anywhere
Has the president taken leave of his faculty?
This is a nightmare scenario
I have carefully weighed the options
It was our duty to slaughter the innocent
Chaos is the greatest ally
In this struggle
I have carefully weighed the lessons of September the 11th
And you know what?
We will demolish the dictator
Obama bin Laden
The bolting look came into his blue eyes
And the United States is quitting its nine
That's the time
What's quitting its nine?
I hear the voices
And I'm the decider
And I decide what is best
And what's best is to remain as the decider
He grinned suddenly
And I saw a wonderful opportunity to do that
He'd stopped and looked at the clock
You see the spirit often if you know where to look
That can be achieved in a variety of ways
We are supporting the White House and what they're doing
And I am determined and brutal
George held out his hand and twisted the fingers into a fist
Unconstrained by conscience
Behind the president's creepy lopsided frown
Was the incendiary fervor of a terrorist
The animal instinct
The simple undifferentiated desire
The ethics of an intestinal bacterium
It means that we have to move quickly
George's tone grew decisive
And in a way that is effective and sometimes lethal
Whatever works, I am for
He'd stopped and looked up
He scanned for nothing in particular
Just a sign
With a deadly effort like wrenching a piece out of his own brain
He saw the page of a gigantic calendar suspended in the sky
The rectangle said September 11th
George scowled meaningfully
Huge structures collapsing
I did not insist, right on
That was the force that would tear the party to pieces
Plenty
Instead of letting that just stand there
We're not gonna allow it
Grab ahold of that thing and do something
Let's give this a try
We're there to help
Um, just, um
Boo!
I have a dream
Boo! No way!
It's like this here
Come on! Are you out of your mind?
We can all come together
Here's a visual
See here, lookie here
See there?
President White's here to look up there
Huh?
See there's the church
And there's the staple
Ladies and gentlemen
Let us have a moment of silent prayer
For their wholeness and harmony
My God, what is that?
Oh my God!
My God, you weren't kidding
Let us lay out a carpet of bread
Let us silence this bleeding of the sheep
Smite them
Deliver them unto my hand
Oh no!
I mean that is big
That is not nothing, what we are doing
The ground under the foundation is shifting
But I can't figure out why
Here it comes
God bless me, he said with a dark chuckle
Ah ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
George was loopy on my doll's Johnny Walker
And pure criminal adrenaline
There was a gnashing of teeth
And a smashing of windows
You see the Democrats blocked out when
Ha ha ha ha ha ha
Nailed it
See there it goes again
Oh I hope George had nothing to do with this
Been did and cuddly
People have been braided
I've been braided
Whatever you do, don't apologize
Just make them feel guilty
How about they get this debris removed
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
That scene says a lot about America
The nation gasped
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
You did what?
A terrible thing's happened
Oh my God!
Not a brick left standing
Call the priest
In the uproar that followed
This was one of the loudest voices
I'm feeling chipper tonight
I survived the White House shake up
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
People were ducking and diving for cover
Ha ha ha ha ha ha
You should have seen his face
Uh oh
George stopped
What's he doing?
He cleared his throat and went on
I wish I could have been there
Ha ha ha ha ha ha
Now watch this drive
Cough, cough, cough
But it was dust and ashes in his mouth
He was covered with boils
Eee
Oh
This is a national disaster
Maybe we should call FEMA
I am sick of your snide comments
President Bush is a good, honest man
And you're a liar
I didn't know one monkey could not
Knock over a building
Raise to the ground
No, George didn't cause that
That side of the building was unsafe
Now, let's have no more curiosity
About this bizarre terror
Ha ha ha
Wrong again, liberal media
I'm proud to be an American
Cough, cough, cough
The president has made clear
Our enemy is not just Al-Qaeda
It's the people
I would have done everything in my power
To kill the American people
Nimbles, nimbles gonna rise again
Gonna exercise our friend
Tries again
Gonna tax us up
Till our eyes again
When it gets them open at my bones
I want you to know something
When I say I'm gonna do something
I'm gonna do it
He's starting it all
Get him
Silence
Silence, you perverts
I think one of the things that people want us to do here
Is to play a blame game, I think
We gotta solve problems
We're problem solvers
There'll be ample time for people to figure out what went right
And what went right
Say what?
I'm confident we can work together to achieve a fat scene
It is not whether the bullet hit him from ground fire
While he was still in the helicopter
Or after he fell to the ground
And hit by ground fire
Or after someone came up and shot him again
What?
I looked him straight in the eye and I said
Speaking of suspects
Where's Joe Biden and John McCain?
We may never know that
What's important is that
The only thing we can learn about this
Is that the United States of America
Decided to go in
And get the body to safety
And the United States of America is leaning forward and not back
One of the good things about America
And then, and
All of us understand that we will develop the truth over time
The truth has many facets
Oh, shut up
Show me an American who can keep his mouth shut and I'll see him
I'm taking from you
What are we to do?
The man who answered would thereafter be the man in power
George blurted out the last confession of incompetence
I've suffered mightily
That's really important as far as I'm concerned
Got four more years, I've got more to do
To continue to raise standards of insanity
Through the power of one who while we speak is temporizing
He ousted coming back with head held high
Oh no
Oh yes
You're our president now
Win-win
It's done, we have four more lights left sir
Four more
I love America
With time,
Lenin and Hitler will be back on its feet
And America will be a stronger place for it
Welcome to Dick Cheney's America
Oh no, not again
And again and again and again
Gird up thy loins for the day of judgment is soon
Soon at hand battle with all thy strength
Lest the Democrats return again
And there was great reaction
Yea, wherefore I say unto you my brother
Let us pray
God bless America
Of all the horrors in the world
Said Winston with his eyes tightly shut
Back in a nightmare
Oh my god
They faced a black hole of unrelieved darkness
The country's in the very best of hands
Of the world
The world is in a dark abyss
Please kill me
Okay, okay
Ah!
Oh!
Oh god!
And friends you've been listening to
A Suzy the floozy rerun from Bob Slacktime Funhouse
Here on the Apple TV
And on our website
The Hour of Slack
For more information about her show
The Hour of Slack show
Or any subgenius show
See subgenius.com
And praise Bob!
Subtitles by the Amara.org community