I don't need to tell you how critical this is.
Hometown, pay-per-view, the eyes of the media.
Here's what I need.
It should be lengthy enough to seem substantial,
yet concise enough to feel breezy.
It should be serious, but with a slight wink.
It should lay out a new course of action,
but one that can change direction at any moment.
If you must mention facts and figures, don't do so directly.
The general thrust should remain embedded in one's mind forever,
but specific words should be forgotten the moment they are heard.
It should contain nothing that can't be confirmed or denied.
It should be on my desk Friday morning.
I got a funny feeling in my stomach.
I'm coming.
Oh, it's you.
Have you ever driven a Stangalini?
How many times I gotta tell you to stay away from me?
Did you say you'd always wanted to drive a Stangalini?
Shut up! Shut up, I tell you!
Will you shut up?
Hi, it's Pat Paulson.
I just want to say that I endorse Bob as my running mate in this year's election,
and this is the hour of slap.
In Dallas, Texas. You know, I know where that is.
So much time, so little to do.
Um, I suspect it might be something similar.
My old man was a bread stasher all his life.
He never got fast.
He wound up with a used car, a 17-inch screen and arthritis.
Tamari is a drag man. Tamari is a king-size bust.
BOOM!
They cry,
Put down.
pot don't think a lot for what time how much and what to do with it sleep man and you might wake
up digging the whole human race giving itself three days to get out tomorrow is a drag cops
the future is a flake i had a canary who couldn't sing i had a cat that let me share my pad with her
i bought a dog that killed the cat that ate the canary what is truth i had an uncle with an ivy
league heart he had life with a belt in the back he had a button down brain wind up a belt in the
mouth and a button down lip we cough blood on this earth now there's a race for space we can cough
blood on the moon soon tomorrow is dragsville cats tomorrow is a king size drag tool of fast
shorts swing with a gassy chick turn on to a thousand joys smile on what happened or check
what's going to happen
you'll miss what's happening turn your eyes inside and dig the vacuum tomorrow drag
all righty i'm dr laura schlessinger we're talking to susan
i've been married six years i have two kids okay any kidlets if so how many how old
my daughter's three and a half my little boy six weeks and are you married or what
um
why is there
screaming in the background
lester richards is dead and aren't you glad it wasn't you don't you wish you felt something
how many men here are attracted to shelly his his lovely wife
she's a babe and how many women here wish that their husbands would drop dead and leave them a big fat insurance policy yes i thought so hell it'll be years before you figure out what lester's death really means so let's forget the blah blah blah and go have a drink amen
you
,
Are
we
but people
live
I'm gonna add some bottom, so that the dancer just won't hide.
I'm gonna add a little bit of top, and make it easy to move your feet.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Else I shall deal you.
I'm your host, Bob. I'm your host, Bob.
Yeah, hi, Bob. It's always a pleasure to be on with you, Bob.
Put it in a nutshell, there is copious, specific evidence that the Bush regime has been engaging in massive election fraud systematically since 2000.
The last two presidential elections were stolen.
Loser take all. Let's call it what it is, this conspiracy.
Okay.
Hello?
Somebody needs to point out to all of us that 50 to 75 percent of fertilized eggs naturally do not make it.
They do not make it. Bad mutations get weeded out.
Put it in a nutshell.
And a nutshell is where we must put it, dear friends.
Because it's the Sunday before the election where we are in time.
Shalloween.
But our listeners, however, are in the present.
So we have to pretend that the election already happened.
Can we still smell him?
Hail the Chief.
Hail Chief.
Chief McCain.
Can we smell him from here?
No.
You bet.
Shh.
Remember, it's after the election.
My friends.
We have to say the right thing.
We have to be very careful now.
I'm trying to get off cue here.
Oh, my friends, I'd just like to thank the American pubish for the rock examiner and the American pubish.
I'm going to go to the delightful suitcase that I, my wife took back to Arizona.
And I just want to say that Joe the, the, the mongoose and Tim the dealer and also Frank the Hippocrat, as well as waiting for the electrician and all my other plumbing friends are going to be along with G. Gordon Gordon.
Or no, that's G. Gordon Liddy.
And we're going to be doing some Wallstream plumbing at the old Watergate once again.
Ha, ha, ha.
What?
That was from, that was from the Keating Six.
But I heard that Oz Goosemaster was actually the write-in king of our presidency this year.
Oz Goosemaster?
Among other many names that we've forgotten, there was a Filbert hoax design cathedral.
Oh, that's right.
There were other people that were running for president.
The Malacutioner, the ex-Bark woman.
There were, there were so many people running and, you know, they were sprinting.
But those last few days.
That's the last time that'll happen.
That's the last time that'll ever happen.
Yep.
They may lose more than their heads in the recent encumbering, you know what I'm saying?
Now that McMahon is president.
McMayus.
So I had heard that.
The McMahon.
The Mcwoman.
Well, that's the thing.
I mean, once the, the one day after the inauguration, the mysteriously timed heart attack hits.
And it will be, and then it's president, pale in.
Doggone it.
Now.
You do paling now.
No.
Dave, you told me that you read on the internet.
No, a friend of yours.
Someone you were talking to, you told me, told you that he had read on the internet proof
that Obama was not only a Muslim.
Yes.
But that he was also a Zionist.
Which you don't usually, we don't usually run into the.
Yes.
Muslim Zionists.
That's three great tastes in one.
If you know, if you're coming at the world from that angle, which is a definitely a side
cake.
Can you think of the, can you imagine such a Zionist Muslim Illuminati?
That's the whole thing, man.
They hide the truth right out in the open.
Well, and then it looks like a paradox.
It looks like two things at once.
That's to train your brain into the finordship of accepting absurdity.
Yes.
Well, think of anything.
Think of the N-gram part of it.
If you look at Osama bin Laden, I mean, no.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah.
If you look at Obama.
The signs.
The Obama's.
Obama, Biden signs.
Biden's.
If you subtract and add just a few choice letters, words, and alphabets, it comes out
as Osama bin Laden.
Right.
Yeah.
You just take a white out to Obama and change the B to an S. And then Biden, all you have
to do is, well, spread the I from the L.
Spread the I from the D and then add a whole bunch of letters.
And L.
Yeah.
If you do it the old Muslim way, you can take the vowel sounds right out.
You can create your own vowel movements.
Why don't they just write it in Arabic?
Yeah.
Backwards.
Just like, yeah, why don't they just call God Allah like they do, having their own language
and stuff.
Why do they do that, Stang?
Well, I can't tell you why.
We use the word God.
Because they won't let me.
God's in him.
They'd put me in jail if I told you why.
He can't tell you.
He never want to tell you, Stang.
He's behind you right now.
Look.
He's behind you.
He's making the me-me-me-me face.
I can't.
Put, put, put, put, put, put, put, put, put.
More.
You got, I can hear both of you guys equally.
I can hear you equally well.
I can hear you.
We actually sounds like she's on mic even.
This, this, Francis, it's a time of change.
Yes, change.
A beautiful place we've come to these last few days, hoping for slack, and look what
we've found.
A beautiful studio that was formerly the detritus of WCP and another station which emerged with
a new name.
With another st-
You're saying this, you recognize this building.
You've been in here before when it was-
It's not new, is it?
I think, is it a new building?
It's the goat, it's a haunted station.
Or is he just having deja vu?
It is a goat station.
Friends, it's so shiny and futuristic in here.
So blue.
Yes, and the walls are unmarked by band stickers.
We'll change that in no time.
Yeah, bad graffiti.
There's not a single Dobbs head in this radio station.
Really?
Not at all.
So shiny.
Clean.
No scrawls.
Everywhere.
No graffitos.
It smells all like a new car.
Like fresh paint.
Yeah.
It has that new car smell here, and because it's a new regime, we're starting into a time
of change.
Change.
Spare change.
The 21st century will be a time of reversal of the max.
You ought to run for president, Dave.
You have that sort of leadership quality.
You mean like-
Funny.
I agree.
Fundamental main street.
Depravity.
Joe the plunger.
Desire to take money from others.
A will for power for its own sake.
A hope, a grand vision for not only you, my fellow citizens, but also the charmed ducks
and bees that have been gathered here before me at this beautiful place.
I don't know if someone referred to it as a reformed school or a home for wayward hoafs.
I know it's really the Silatorium.
I'm sorry, am I reading off the wrong page?
Why are you looking at me?
I'm not the only person here.
Are you?
Am I?
What?
All of the posts on the internet are about you.
Signposts flashing by.
Everything bad they said on the internet was about you.
About you.
Just as you suspected.
Are you paranoid, Mr. Listless?
You've been here only a few minutes and yet you say we've kept you for hours.
Is there something wrong, Mr. Listless?
You can't seem to relax.
Come, come, Mr. Listless.
You need to cooperate.
We can get this over much sooner.
You can get back to your family and kids.
Just tell us everything we want to know.
Janet, how long has he been like this?
Oh, I can't even begin to remember.
It's just seems like it's been forever.
Well, they made sure you couldn't remember.
None of us can.
But if we could, we'd probably end up like this guy.
Poor sap.
In trouble.
Now, come on, Mr. Listless.
So suckerel.
Mr. Listless, if you'll just cooperate and tell us the other names.
Listen, I know how to do this.
Get out of my-
Of the other voters.
The other dead voters.
I know how to handle this.
Listless!
Hey!
Watch it!
Listless!
Snap to it.
Careful.
We need the names of the other, other voters.
Now, you know what I'm talking about.
Other, other voters, man?
I don't know what you mean, man.
You know, the vessels.
The vessels!
Listless!
Talk with him.
Now, now, Dave, that bad cop act isn't going to get anywhere.
Look, Mr. Listless, I can keep Dave from hitting you again if you can just-
I don't know if you're going to get over it.
I mean, I don't like this any more than you do.
Stop me.
Frankly, I voted for the other guy.
Just let me have a few minutes with him alone.
That's all I want to do.
Well, now, Dave, now you know what-
Please, please.
Dave, you need to back down now.
Who, who, what other voters?
Now, look, Mr. Listless, we read on the internet your post that claimed that you
had proof that you read on the internet that John McCain was actually born in Panama and
was not eligible to be the new Fuhrer.
You also claimed that he had raped-
What?
Barack Obama and given him AIDS.
You claimed also that Palin works for the Russian Jews and that-
Let me see if I'm reading this right.
Listen, listen, she's a double KGP for crying out loud.
Stand back.
Stand right there.
You said that the Jews are taking over Israel.
Did you say this, Mr. Listless?
Did you claim that the Jewish people are taking over Israel?
I can't remember anything.
And why are all the posts on the internet about you?
Listen, I want to know about McCain's-
I can't remember anything.
You clearly have no idea what it takes to be an alien vessel, just like John Henkley.
You sure you don't know who the other, other, other voters are, man?
Now look, Mr. Listless, you claim that the last president in office who actually broached
the subject of the aliens, the so-called aliens from outer space, was President Reagan when
he-
Not President FitzWater.
Oh, okay, okay.
Right after they bring these guys, you know, after these guys get elected, that first day in the office, they take them into the secret room behind the Oval Office and tell them what's really going on.
And, of course, from that moment on, your president-elect has a few more gray hairs and a more worried look and generally is a bit more presidential and a little more inclined to go along with the plan.
He likes to stoop.
They call him the President Eloy.
You'll notice that since Reagan, he had to teach, he got to talking about how what if the aliens from another planet came and we had to join together with the Russians and the Chinese and fight against them.
Why, we'd all be one race together.
One big happy family.
Yeah, one race.
The human race.
Not a bunch of appliances for aliens.
As soon as Reagan started talking that way, they sent Hinckley after him.
I want Adam.
And Reagan.
And ever since then, none of the presidents have talked about the aliens in quite that same way.
Now, Jimmy Carter said he saw the planet Venus abduct him and brainwash him and probe him and fly away.
But aside from that, and look what happened to poor Carter.
Aside from that, since then, they've been too smart to mention that stuff they tell you in that first hour.
Stay with me, Adam.
No, no, come on now.
Don't leave any marks.
Mr. Leslis.
Look, we're trying not to leave any marks on you.
You already broke my nose.
Oh, God, this is ridiculous.
What is going to happen?
I don't know about any alien other voters.
How much more of this violence going on here?
Oh, I know one thing that's going to happen.
What's going to happen?
I have to give a little bit of credit.
Credit?
Where it's due.
Yes.
All the beginning was cut up by Lemur.
Except there's a little bit of music.
Fur Bob, which sounded like ancient Mark Mothers Bob doing sample Bob music of a classical variety.
That was by The Large.
There were two clips from a movie called Schizopolis, which is great for clips.
The Ren and Stimpy promo for Hour of Slack was real, as was the Pat Paulson one.
Pat Paulson was a Bob supporter.
You know, he ran for president every four years from 19...
1968 to 1996.
I remember the blue suit he used to wear.
And he won.
Me too.
In 1992.
Oh, Pat Paulson?
Yeah.
But Clinton stole the election.
Was that Clinton or was that George won?
I can't remember.
What about Fatang Fatang Limbin in the historian park?
Well, that's the thing.
They bury all these people, literally, with frozen sticks and pieces of mud.
As if it weren't enough to have to crawl in the library basement to find out their names to begin with.
For the love of...
No, I'm staying.
We must do something to preserve our respubics.
Our republic, we must...
Sorry.
We need to call that reporter Woodward.
He'll straighten things out.
Oh, Woody, man.
He was stiff and hard with those guys.
Especially, what's his name?
No Throat?
The guy that had part of his...
No Throat.
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
The secret guy.
Yeah, the alien that had actually no throat, man.
That was quite a clever takeoff on, you know, Deep Throat back in the old Watergump era.
And when that...
I was only five years old when Watergate sprang.
A leak.
No, you weren't.
I was 45?
Yeah.
I was...
23, right?
Yeah.
I was hitchhiking, just leaving the country when Watergate sprung that leak.
Can I ask you one important...
Can I ask...
Watergate.
Can I ask you one very important question?
Try.
Why...
I forgot.
Never mind.
Okay.
This background music is by Ogo Dip.
Yes.
This CD's been sitting around my house unlisted to until yesterday.
And Princess, we and I decided...
We decided this was up the hour of Slack Alley.
Yeah, man.
Das Deutsche Reich ist eine Goberschnack.
Und mit diesen Freunden...
Und mit diesen Freunden.
Well, we'll be playing that whole song next time.
Ogo Dip is from Sweden.
Actually, this is Swedish music, although it's in sort of cartoon English.
Sweden!
All material composed, arranged, produced, sequenced, performed, and blah, blah, blah,
by Magnus Lundberg.
They sound like smashed up Viking gazole.
You know, like someone's been beating them around the anthrax with a medulla avant-garde
stick.
I hate...
I hate Viking rock.
Oh, and speaking of music, that amazing cut-up...
Vagmara!
Just before we started cutting up, there was an incredible mash-up.
That was by Girl Talk, and we're going to be playing lots more Girl Talk.
My son turned me on to Girl Talk.
You can wiki Girl Talk, and you'll learn some interesting things.
Like some subgeniuses ask their nasal passages suitable for sexual orifices?
That's not the only reason they do it, Dave.
But, um...
But...
Why would they cry to the clouds with their noses?
That's an ancient trick, man.
I say this in a butt-sick way.
I say this butt-sickly.
But we have but a few...
Well about five minutes worth of stuff here.
Can I kill we first for not talking?
No, you can do that while...
Oh look, there's the light.
But I don't want to die!
There's the light, okay.
I've been watching it.
Listen, listen, Dave.
I watched it.
Shut up.
I'm out!
You're on the wrong phone.
Pick up the phone, woman.
I just broke the headphones.
I broke the intercom and the headphones.
Stang, we're in a whole new situation now.
We're in a world of hurry.
In a beautiful new studio.
There's plenty of really, really good headphones here.
I can't believe this.
I really broke the headphones.
Not like the old stations.
Seemly.
You will be blamed.
I completely...
I can't hear myself.
But it doesn't mean you won't be able to find a brand new pair of delicious...
Okay.
Shut up!
I just turned it off.
I just turned you guys off.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to now do what I should have done so long, long ago.
Because I don't know what's going to happen.
Uh, um, what's going to happen?
Uh, I say that the banks will have the woman that will be human.
This is the most net and economic more than could be power.
So big dollar power.
Thank you!
Now's not the time for confidence.
Now is the time for panic and fear.
Now's not the time for steady leadership.
We can come together to restore fear in the American economy.
We can renew that panic that in America our destiny is not written by us.
Hold on one second.
I can't hear myself.
I'm not in office!
I'm still in office!
Oh, no!
Hi, this is Pat Paulson.
I'd like to endorse Bob as my running mate in this year's election.
Bob's a lot of...
Well, he's not fun.
He's a lot of fun.
But anyway, this is the hour of slack in Dallas, Texas.
You know, hour...
Boy, my shoes got cow stuff on them.
From PR News in Washington, I'm falling down over the weekend.
GOP nominee John McCain says,
I'm going to make doo-doo.
We're not pro-American.
We all anti-America.
Federal Reserve Chairman Ben Bernanke says lower prices reflect declining demand for PR News from Washington.
Introduce a little anarchy.
Upset the established order and everything becomes chaos.
I'm an agent of chaos.
Oh, and you know the thing about chaos?
It's fear.
But every few years they change the flavor.
This one's all about...
It's about...
It's about the decline and fall.
Fall down, baby.
Decline and fall.
Fall way down now.
Fall down, baby.
Decline and fall.
Come on, little mama.
Fall.
Give a man a free ticket on a dead-end ride.
He'll climb into the back even though nobody's driving.
Too goddamn lazy to crawl out of a wreck.
And he'll rock while he waits for the weather.
And the weather's not right.
Self-fair check, going to hell in a handbag.
Can't you see I ain't gonna eat no government cheese?
Ain't no government cheese.
No, thank you, Mr. Bush, no government cheese.
Ain't gonna eat your government cheese.
Thank you.
That's terrible. I never saw anything like that in my life.
Terrible, terrible.
Perfect.
Oh, yeah?
Ain't gonna eat, me ain't gonna eat, mine ain't gonna eat, mo.
Made in the night, made in reality.
Don't call it a comeback.
Face.
Hey.
J-Wayne!
Drop, drop, drop
How do you do?
Come on!
My eyes are sure, being a senator
Behind closed doors, hitting truth to the seafloor
The rich don't know us, ignore the tug of war
While the kids are poor, open door and better drugstore
So I became hardcore, couldn't take it no more
I'ma reveal everything, change the law
I find myself, walking the streets
Trying to find what's really going on in your streets
Yeah, you're a superstar
That is what you are
Coming from afar
Reaching for the stars
Run away with me
To another place
Can we lie on each other?
Uh-huh
Look, yeah, I'm a superstar
Like this
You're giving love instinctively
Woo!
Like this
Look, yeah, I'm a superstar
You're giving love instinctively
Like this
Woo!
Tell me if you want it
Like this
Baby, I'm like this
I love you
Like this
Like things
I really do
There it is.
Yeah.
That was girl talk.
We mastered the problem, yes.
The embarrassing personal problem.
We had to go off the air for that.
I'm sorry.
So much better now.
Unfortunately, the problem was that you refused to realize it was in your own mind, Stan.
Yet created the problem, and look at you now.
You're dripping with sweat.
I can't find my mind.
You're blue, and the very tips of your fingers are covered with blood.
My mind.
You've been scratching your old sores, haven't you?
It's not my mind.
It's not your mind that's bothering you.
Your mind is controlled by a vast, vast source in distant space.
They're whispering commands into your nostril right now.
That would explain a lot.
In fact, your nasal passages are quite sufficient for sexual olfactories.
I mean, sexual olfactories.
Okay, can we do that one again?
I don't want to go there.
Okay, let's not go there.
Let's go.
Somewhere nice and pleasant.
Like the obituaries.
Yeah, the obituaries.
The obituaries.
Dave, did you know that Rudy Ray Moore, the great comedian, died?
No, I did not know he passed under this.
Yes, he passed away.
Best known for his roles in As the King of Party Records, doing the character Dolomite.
Dolomite.
He also produced some what you might call blaxploitation films.
About Dolomite, The Human Tornado, Petey Wheatstraw, The Devil's Son-in-Law.
Petey Wheatstraw, The Devil's Son-in-Law.
And he was born in 1927 on a crossroads in Fort Smith, Arkansas.
He also grew up in Cleveland, Ohio.
I did not know that.
Very much like Screamin' Jay Hawkins.
There is a strong tradition here, but few know of it.
Rudy Ray Moore's albums include such classics that we can't play even on this station.
No, it's not.
It's not.
Such as Eat Out More Often, This Pussy Belongs to Me, Return of Dolomite, and a timely one,
Dolomite for President, which if I could have dug through my record collection, I probably
should have pulled that one out because I think he doesn't cuss on Dolomite for President.
Although maybe I'm thinking of a Dolomite Christmas.
We could have let him won in this dimension that we're in.
This time suspended dimension suspension bridge where one way or the other.
We're going to.
I don't think it's.
I don't have a cell phone.
I think.
How about a smell phone?
What are you hearing the cell phone to?
No, it's that thing there.
But I'm not going to mess with it.
But it's it's going through a computer.
I thought it was now station.
It's barking that you that you have to put the drizzle on it.
The sugar content is very high.
Oh, just like you are right now.
I see.
And to some people, but not all of us.
Now, in further bits, as we say goodbye to the great Rudy Ray Moore.
Dolomite.
Ima Sumac died yesterday.
Oh, yes, she did.
The great Ima Sumac died at the age of 86.
She was born in 1922 in Peru.
I'm sorry.
I used to think that Ima Sumac was a made up name.
And she was really somebody from Brooklyn.
But that's not true.
No, it isn't true.
She's part of the girl.
She really was from Peru.
Peru.
And her real name was Zoila Augusta.
Esperatriz.
Chavarri del Castillo.
Del Castillo.
So she was Zoila del Castillo was her real name.
Wasn't that something?
Peru.
Just do it, bitch.
If I was better prepared, I'd be playing Ima Sumac in the background instead of the Flying Ryan Brothers.
Yes, the Flying Ryan Brothers.
Available from Ryanetics.com.
Now, they didn't die too, though, in this week's obituaries.
No, they ride.
They were Ryan, Ryan guys.
Ryanetics.
Well, thanks for informing me that two heroes and one heroine, I mean, have died.
Yep.
Why can't you tell me about somebody that I wish would be dead?
Dolomite is my name.
And loving up other mother lovers is my game.
That would be the TV version, I guess.
Yes.
Man, I wondered how you were going to do that.
I'm here to stake a claim in this pimpin' and hustlin' game.
Well, I don't think you want to go in the same cave where Dolomite and Ixtabay are hanging around together wearing Peruvian landscapes.
You know what I'm saying?
Doing the old,
Alpaca!
I was, no, I wouldn't.
They probably wouldn't let me into the same heaven that Dolomite and Ima Sumac are in.
They would dress you like a saffron robe glamour.
Dolomite's probably doing Ima Sumac right now.
Yeah.
I would say he's been waiting most of that previous time.
Just, you know, I don't know.
I throw that singer on a velvet bed.
Love that girl till the girl drop dead.
That's another television version.
Dolomite kept on loving that girl without thinking.
Didn't even know the girl was dead till her parts started stinking.
Till her parts started stinking.
You see the problems here.
Actually, I was heavily influenced by Dolomite.
I heard his first party record.
I heard his first party record when I was a cub dishwasher at the Railhead restaurant in Dallas, Texas in the early 70s.
And I memorized the ABCs of love, which I can't recite.
I could, but I can't.
Not even a single letter.
The first thing we like to do when we join the club at the Cub Reporters Club is to learn the ABCs, the entire alphabet of love.
Of urban boasts and toasts.
Prison toasts.
He was really like a...
He was a signifying Movacian.
He was.
And that was another one of his routines, was the signifying monkey.
Well, I used a dirty word, but it wasn't as far as the FCCIA is concerned.
And we can all thank our lucky stones if we have any left in our pants.
I've tried, Stang.
I've tried to keep these solid members removed.
And at least not, you know, taped on the parts of my body.
Wait.
You didn't try hard enough.
What's that light coming through the window?
Is there a helicopter outside the window?
Oh, suddenly it was like a war movie, a crime movie.
Yeah, we were all dead.
It was wild, man.
I love this studio, don't you?
Yeah.
Isn't this cool?
I mean, we could actually make stupid dramaturg things happen that don't exist.
But if we went to the trouble, we could bring in all the little discs and MP3s.
We could make all kinds of sound effects.
And we could write scripts, even.
Yes, scripts.
Remember that?
My hand tape recorder doesn't work because it's actually a human hand.
I remember scripts.
Why, yes, I remember scripts.
Yes, you used to take OxyCramden and Lois Fazorn and all of those other lip-
I can't get-
My doctor won't give me a script now.
My doctor won't even let me answer me.
He won't answer my calls.
I call him constantly and profusely, and he's never lifting up the phone one damn time.
I think he's got my number.
I got his, you know what I'm saying?
Well, speaking of sound effects, I went to my cell phone to get some canned sound effects
and found that I'd been sent a massage from Governor Rocknar,
who says that we may announce the passing of his father on this radio show.
So I think I just did that.
Well, that's right, since we're doing obituaries.
The obituaries, yes.
And he must be listening.
Dad, right?
Governor Rocknar is up there trying to out-cuss Dolomite and to out-yodel Ima Sumac.
Yep.
And they're trying to out-whatever Dr. Rocknar did, the elder.
Or is it undue?
Oh, I don't know.
We'll have to find out.
I don't know.
All I know is, friends, we're all going to meet our maker someday.
Someday maybe.
In fact, our maker will-
Meet us.
He will grind us up in his big meat grinder.
That's why they say we're undone, because we've been overcooked.
If you're a pink or a human and not a subgenius,
your soul is pretty much identical to all the other human souls,
and your meat or soul will go into what we call the slurry with all the other souls.
Whereas if you're a subgenius, an ordained, saved subgenius soul,
well, then your soul is plucked out.
And kept.
And cored out specially like an olive and has a little-
Yeah.
Like one of those little red things stuck into it.
That's what I was going to say.
Like a little olive or a little raisin taken out of the-
You're a special one.
Out of the pemmican.
Yes.
Yeah.
Or like caviar ripped from a pregnant trout.
Ah.
Or such like.
What a much better metaphor.
Yeah.
You're working too hard.
That's the way your soul ends up.
It's like the-
It's the refined condiment for connoisseurs.
A succulent bag of snot.
Yes.
No, that wouldn't be-
Boggling.
You can sell your soul to the aliens for a lot more money if you're a subgenius than
he can if you're just a human or a penguin or, you know, one of these normal ones.
Warmly, warmly worms.
We are now accepting high mediocrity to normal, normal men.
They may be pink, but their money is green, as Bob said so many times.
If their shoes are scuffed and their behinds are big enough for us to get around or reach
around, they're on board.
Or is that-
Did I read that one right?
Did I say it again?
On board.
Right.
Am I supposed to say it like that?
You're like, you know, the flying saucers.
On the water, Board of Bob.
You're on board.
I'm sorry.
Oh.
That's you.
On the water, Board of Bob.
We is having a sound effects orgasm over here.
I did.
I'm enjoying it.
It's all over.
I wish you would, sir.
I'm sorry.
We is all having fun in here.
It is.
It's a fun place.
I think there are subnipple messages embedded in the psychic response unit or maybe the-
The cork ceiling is something.
Here's a subliminal message, kids.
Now, hang on.
Great.
That's funny.
Look, nobody thinks they're a bad person.
Mm-hmm .
All right.
You know, I'm not even claiming that people always think they're doing the right thing.
They may know that they're doing something dishonest or insensitive or manipulative,
but they almost always think there's a good reason for doing it.
Ah.
They almost always think that it will turn out for the best in the end.
And even if it's just it turns out best for them, because by definition what's best for them is what's best.
Now, look, in addition, you instantly come up against a question of style.
My style may be too...
too, uh, uh, direct.
Perhaps given my style, I seem more nakedly opportunistic or jerky or, uh...
What was the other thing?
Uh...
Manipulative?
Whatever.
But really all that's happening is that I'm trying to get what I want, which is what everybody does.
It's just that some of their styles are so warm or charming or sincere or otherwise phony,
you don't realize they're just trying to get what they want.
So you see, my transparent efforts are in a way much more honest and admirable.
Why is it what you just said strikes me as a massive rationalization?
Don't knock rationalization.
Where would we be?
We'd be without it.
I don't know anyone who'd get through the day without two or three juicy rationalizations.
They're more important than sex.
Aw, come on, nothing's more important than sex.
Oh yeah? Have you ever gone a week without a rationalization?
Eh? Have you?
I said, Monsieur...
Well, have you, punk?
Would you like the nice, juicy rationalization?
Yes, I would. Can I have two, please?
Would you like it rare, medium rare, or extra well done?
Medium rare, please.
Very good.
Would you like the sauce au jus?
Or would you like the hollandaise? Or would you like the bearnaise?
Oh, hollandaise, please, please.
All right, you, sir.
With a little dill, would you mind?
Would you like me to remove that third nostril from your face?
Oh no, I really have become quite attached to it.
I'm asking your husband. He's the man of my house, and he also wears the slippers.
You, sir, Mr. Stoin.
I'll have the double burger, animal style.
He doesn't even care about my navel foreheads.
Animal-style fries and...
Well, excuse me.
You have recently joined the Rosicution Unit?
No, I have not.
Have you electrocuted small birds, ducks, or other animals who argue with you?
No, I have absolutely not.
Then for you, it is the rationalization extra juicy and rarely used.
Oh my goodness, I cannot stand it.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave should be a super spy for the government, because he can talk all those other languages.
He's just talking French.
Yes.
Yeah, but that was a French accent sting, and most of it is gibberish when you hear me do the actual speech.
So I don't know how much good I'd be doing that.
Oh, well, if it's good enough to fool French people.
Ah, Signore, vendimi per parlare.
Devo dirti una cosa.
See, it kind of makes sense.
See, you can do Spanish, too.
Si, yo lo puedo.
Oh, and Russian, like he's doing now.
Gavrite paparuzzi, tovaris. Gavrite.
And Italian.
But that's Italian, isn't it, what you're talking about?
Si, si, si. In Volgograd.
In Volgograd.
See, Dave could be a super spy for the new McCain regime.
The new McCain regime?
Because he's as traveled as the vice president, at least.
Actually, more traveled.
You've been to England, haven't you, and other foreign communist socialist places?
No, I've never.
So you could be a spy.
I went to Canada, and I played in a band in London.
That's about it.
And I went across the border of Mexico and exposed my self.
My true inner self.
And then I was illuminated by Caswell and the Third Star Eye people.
I think it was in 1979.
And then on my recreational re-enumerment, I was named Osmart of this whole globe, daddy-o.
Wow.
So I'm kind of excited, and that's why I've gone and come and gone in my pants, so to speak.
Dave.
You have to be so graphic all the time.
You don't have to go in your pants.
Dog, got it.
Did I go in my pants this year?
No, you went.
I already have come and gone.
Yeah.
You're gone in your pants again.
Do you have any more of the Vikings of Yiddish music?
I was just looking at our internet list of internet listeners, and Mr. Listless is listening.
There's a Mr. Listless?
He's listed?
Listless is listed?
Yeah.
And on this list, he is in this-
I wonder how he fed.
How many years?
And he's in America right now.
Right.
North America.
In fact, he's in the United States.
He's not in Cleveland.
There's somebody in Canada listening.
All right.
I suppose you-
And there's somebody in ... What does DH represent?
.
DH.
That's not .
I think that's a sports term when you're-
.
You'll see them these days.
You'll see them asukan employed on California's ditch.
And usually a private business does- no Mmmgggg.
buzzERS.
a Kont recherchesburyijhaewusensVID 19 fluja Smith opina
sthj
en
He just left an old commode in his backyard like it was nothing.
He's not planting any pants in it.
That's the guy in Austin.
Austin?
Yeah.
Oh, boy.
Yeah, there's a guy in Austin.
Honest?
Yeah.
You can see where they are, and you can see the top of their house through the satellite.
But our station hasn't got the money for the really good internet connection where you can see through the roof of the house and look down their shirt pockets.
See what's in their shirt pocket and have the bald spot on the top of their head.
I think you're fooling on me and on everybody here that's trying to listen to this doggone show.
And you're just fooling on everybody talking about that and looking through the roof and through their bald head and all that.
Yes, you can.
You really can see.
The government has that stuff, and the stations that play the game right and stick to the plan.
You've got to be with the plan.
Stick to the plan.
The plan.
There's always the plan.
Yeah, the plan.
Once you deviate from the plan, then you're in nowhere.
You're in no man's land, no woman's land in your case.
Think about it.
What would happen in a world where there wasn't structure and order provided by somebody?
I mean, we don't have to ask who or what this is.
We don't have to call it the conspiracy.
It's a conspiracy of dunces indeed, but the thing is, somebody's doing the job.
You know what I'm saying?
What if I'm not down with the plan?
They're sticking to the plan.
Well, then it's anarchy.
Let me, yeah.
It's anarchy.
That's the way it is.
If you don't stick to the plan.
Oh, okay.
Everything breaks down.
I don't want to be considered anarchist, so.
Oh, for the love of God, no.
Calm down, you guys.
Just take this pipe.
Take this pipe.
There's a pipe over here.
Have a sip.
Oh, this is great.
Here.
Here, let me translate.
You mean it.
What'd you say?
Only two sticks.
Oh, that's not so hot.
He's going to try to have them at the same time.
From PR News in Washington, I'm first seen in jellyfish.
Former members of the Bush administration are saying that it's okay to get exercise in small jellyfish,
as long as it's on Friday.
New federal guidelines on jellyfish are saying that Hillary Mann Leverett says,
she says, he says,
and says,
Leverett says,
and Everett says,
there was a meltdown in small jellyfish today on fears that the widening financial crisis could touch off of PR News on Friday.
PR News in Washington.
Hmm?
You know what I noticed?
Nobody panics when things go according to plan.
Even if the plan is horrifying.
If tomorrow I tell the press that I'd like a gangbanger, we'll get shot.
Or a truckload of soldiers will be blowing up.
Nobody panics.
Because it's all part of the plan.
Hylian's a bust-up awful big shot.
They've got assets making money dollars, hand over fist.
Self-abasing, honest, walking tightrope.
Frito, lickin', lickin', sticky on the balsa.
What you thought you could?
He's got a good life, he's got a nice wife.
He's got a sharp knife, he's ready to cut it up.
He's got a bullshit, he's got a think quick.
He's got a very evident, another carpet.
Fuff, fuff, feel, fuff, flyin' forward.
Feelings air, feelings flow.
Ta-tune, anywhere, anywhere, Wil lamp.
Fuff Fuff Fuff Fuff Fufff Fuff
C n var 2, haha
hardest beat never pretty time ever let me
Stones, I gotta to activity.
Can no one say to your face
This the last time your to be darkenin'
reserved,
And if not
nobody top
Alum
I must keep cito
Make it
I got a puzzle made from turkey that does not fit
Hey, could be a stickler, sweat this fast, not enough
Slack a telepathy in the USA
Hard to hunt, rolling hay
Come here, I'm the way
Clever man, lazy and sane
Paralyzed in this game
Yeah!
Orbit plot shows we have about 8 minutes left
Scotty, I can't change the laws of physics
I've got to have 30 minutes
Snouty, I cannot change my nasal...
...deviance any more than I could change my love of my old besotten grand badness
How long do I have to sit in this damned water before it all comes out?
You've had me here for the last three hours
There's no way of changing my mind, I'll never resist
I'm going with the plan
The plan
The good plan
The Uber plan
Listen, if there was ever a plan
That you wanted to go with
A buxom, beautiful plan
Of over 29 feet tall
And 300 pounds of reekers
That's a hot plan
Friends, that song
Was, uh, that rockin' song there
That sounded kind of, uh, devonian
That rockin' schluckin'
Was by a band called Marvelkind
And the song is called
Slackadelic
It's so reminiscent!
And it, uh, our friend Reverend Toth Wilder put that on the, uh, not necessarily beautiful mutt mutated
Uh, compilation album that goes with the 2008 devotional
And, uh, that music we were playing in the first half of the show in the background was by Ogo Dis
Which I wanted to spell
O-G-O-D-Y-S
As in dystopia
I don't think he, in a...
I don't know what, uh, website it is
Or anything he would be on
But you can find Ogo Dis
On our website
Later, when this show is played back and streamed
From subgenius.com
Yes, that is our website
Subgenius.com
Home of the Hour of Slack
And the Church of the Subgenius
And the land of the free, dammit
Yes, the free party
And yet to be born
Well, I was telling Dave and Princess Wee on the way in here
That, uh, Bob J. O'Neill and I, uh, are going to be on the show
But to be a part of the show
That we are Bob Dobbs, our high epop of the church
Uh, ran for a city office in Brighton, England
Even though he's an American
And won
He defeated Fatang
And then didn't show up
And some British subgenius had to show up wearing a glued on Bobhead mask
And that wasn't on
In order to serve
To save face
And they were called the free party
Or as we put it, the free party party
Because they put on big, free parties in British media
Brighton. But Stang, remember,
our bite marked frei. And that means
if you're a member of the free party, you must
work. And if you want to work
out the right way, just
pull down your pants all the way to the
booties. Not again. Look up at that
galaxy off to the left there.
We don't have to. The one with the drizzling
eye. And
point again, I said. Point! Point!
Point your weight
at Baltimore, which is
where I'm going to have to go in two weeks
for that devival. Yes?
On the 15th,
I have to
go. And preach.
And the amino acids
have to go. And
holler. And
priestess Pisces.
And Dr. Legume
may show up at the last minute. And
Reverend Carter LeBlanc. And Fat Free.
And the motor morons.
Which is one of the oldest subgenius.
The motor morons were
subgeniuses in like
1980.
1991. Under a different
name. Severn Institute.
Right. Before the Lubrolak scandal.
The motor morons are
named that way because
they use, they actually
have a bicycle and car repair
shop. And they use the machinery
from their shop as
musical instruments. Grinders.
I remember. Sanders.
Spark makers. At the
Bisexual Bicentennial.
I remember all 12 of them were there.
And I mistook them for angels.
On high. But they were actually dead
beings. Kind of like zombies. But they
couldn't walk.
And I think that covers.
Yes. Okay. Baltimore on November 15.
The pledge drive
next week on the Hour of Slack.
Radio Thon friends. Get your.
Start saving your pennies now.
Because we're. The stations
are all going to need your
money. It's tie time baby.
This one.
Tie time. So we'll be back
for that. To pay for this brand
new shiny spaceship
like control
console. And stole studio.
It's just beautiful. It is wonderful.
Gorgeous. It's simply
wonderful. And you can't get in
to pester us here. I remember Loretta.
The one with the rancid left
nostril. It wasn't
very, very, very
well made for sexual deviance.
But believe me I taught her
all I know. And I don't know
very much but that's not the important part.
But the important part she was a good learner.
She wanted to learn the different
fashion of the bonobo.
The various movements.
The skip dragging and the dancing.
She was delightful in her early
years. But now she's encumbered
with old age and big teeth. And so
I had to shoot her down
the basement. A bit long in the tooth
eh? Yes. In fact
her whole face became elongated
before we put her back there.
Dave is long in
the throat. But we're not long for this
station because we have to get out of here.
As Captain Kirk
said in just about
well it was eight minutes.
It was eight minutes right then. Oh man you blew
the shagway because we've got to go to the top again.
No we're going to listen to
we're going to leave with The Hunting
of Bob. This is a new very
short 50 second show
by Lee Murr. Thank you
Lonesome Cowboy Dave and Princess Wee.
Thank you Reverend Stang.
He's meditating
on his own third nostril.
And now The Hunting of
Bob.
The Hunting of Bob.
Here it comes folks. Here it comes.
And now The Hunting of Bob.
Bob.
You talk too much Bob. You think
what you want to think. Stay quiet
Bob.
Oh Bob. Here he comes Bob.
What does he want?
We're looking for Bob.
And Bob. Then I'll
kill you where you stand.
Bob.
Oh Bob. Bob what have they done?
What did you do Bob? The Hunting
of Bob. You've got no
right to come in peace. Bob.
Bob.
I know I am right.
No wonder. You're always
right with Bob.
The Hunting of Bob.
Bob.