What you are hearing is not a test.
There is a need, brothers and sisters.
A need for you to get off your lazy ass and fucking donate to this goddamn station.
I am sick and tired of you dear listeners who continue to sit idly by in your car,
your living room, your bedroom, your stateroom, your panic room, and just listen.
Listen, this shit ain't free folks.
So how about you just skip that tall, half skinny, half 1% extra hot shot split quad shot latte with whip.
Or maybe just skip that lunch date with the cutie from the typing pool.
After all, it's only going to lead to heartbreak.
And spend that money now, right now, on something that will never give you up,
and will never let you down, and will never run around and desert you.
Because this...
This station will never make you cry.
They will never say goodbye.
And they will never tell a lie and hurt you.
So call the WCSB Cleveland Pledge Line.
216-687-6900
That number once again is 216-687-6900
With your donations now.
Credit card pledges may be made online at WCSB.org
This plea for cash has been brought to you by
The Soul Genius.
Powered by
or audio images that may be considered objectionable to those of a frank or sensitive nature.
Listener discretion is therefore advised.
We areという and working.
Thank you.
Imagine an instructional tape that produces gobs and gobs of money!
Quickly, easily, and effortlessly!
It's like a faucet you can't fix!
Gushing and spewing a never-ending constant flow of cash money!
Multiple streams of income!
This is the key to your financial future.
Say goodbye to your day job and live your dreams.
Getting started is really easy!
You're gonna get drunk, take lots of pills, and have sex!
All the time!
I was broke and living at the YMCA six months ago.
The one right down here down the street.
Now just look at me. I'm living large.
Six-figure income? We've done it!
We're gonna teach you how to be in a band!
Lose weight and make money!
Push, play, and get rich!
Have you ever dreamed of playing a wicked guitar solo under the spotlight in front of thousands of screaming chicks?
Keep dreaming!
Chances are, you'll never play like that.
And if you do, chances are, you'll never make any money doing it.
This is Wes.
And I'm Bob.
And we're here to tell you that
people don't care about guitar solos anymore!
What we're going to focus on in today's lesson is
how to fake it in almost any situation.
It's easier than you might think.
We'll also cover
how to break a string.
As well as
how to piss off your singer with some really cool noises.
First off, let's go over some fundamentals.
You'll need a guitar.
And it will need to be in tune.
If your act sounds like this...
...
Let's move on.
It's showtime.
Your band hits the stage.
You've had way too much to drink.
And you forget how the song goes.
Hey, Wes.
Some of us do that even when we're sober.
Well, in either case, the thing not to do is panic.
Odds are good that no one has ever even heard your music.
So, you can fake it.
Most people are stupid anyway.
They'll never suspect a thing.
The same applies to wrong notes.
They'll think you meant to do it.
It's also a good idea to keep a can of Spritz on your amp
so you can tease your hair while you fake it.
It's very important to look good,
even if you can't play very well.
Breaking a string comes pretty easy
if you beat the shit out of your guitar.
Don't bother to clean or baby your guitar
if you're just gonna throw it at the drum set at the end of the show.
Expensive guitars are pointless.
Korean-made Yamahoos and Ivanhads take abuse well
and are good for spare parts.
You can break up to five strings at a time and still play.
Just imagine dazzling your fans
as you recite
There are various noises that you can make with a guitar.
A wide array of sounds that you can use
to irritate domestic household pets.
The police.
And of all people,
the guy who sings in your band.
Stop it.
Hey, stop that.
It's my turn.
Man, shut up, punk.
Among other techniques, I like to make a guitar
squeal like a pig.
That's all we have time for today, kiddos.
I hope you found today's lesson enlightening and inspirational.
We welcome your letters.
Because we usually steal ideas from them.
Until next time, this is Wes.
And I'm Bob.
Stay hard and petty.
Rude and rude.
Smooth in the noose.
Fucking patood.
Buy our next lesson
or we'll come around and screw you.
Oh, lady.
Oh.
From Fort Lauderdale, Florida
to Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
Now, the man who will be damned.
Come on, let's get Bob up here.
Come on, Bob.
Where's Bob?
Bob, come on, Bob.
Come on, Bob.
Have a seat, Bob.
Have a glass of water.
Now, this could not have been your objective.
Did you want to do this, Bob?
Yes.
Bob?
Bob.
Bob, isn't it?
That is correct.
Oh, boy.
You're smarter than the average guy.
And, Bob, give me one good reason.
We, 23, did you mean to come?
We stopped real time.
No.
Well, there is no real time.
Very true.
That is very true.
All right, Bob.
Did you have something going on?
Yes, we have.
Oh, you are.
Yes.
You escaped.
That is true.
Yeah, for your verb.
Yeah.
What field are you in?
I work for a profit.
So there's not a lot of money to make.
But I work in a unique field.
I work on people.
That's fantastic.
It's incredible.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
Bob, you know, this works.
Someone out there plays along with you.
I have no idea.
Spleen is exactly right.
No.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, see?
See?
Okay.
Wow.
Bob, this is Bob.
Hey, Bob.
Hi, Bob.
I'm good.
Yeah.
Same here.
Okay, excellent.
And they're a brain trust.
Science.
Science it is.
All right.
Who just had its south polar region blasted?
Bob.
Boy.
That was really good.
So, okay.
Bob.
Why would anyone pay?
Is the question.
And the answer?
You got it, Bob?
Current events.
Yeah, I'm way off on that.
Yeah.
Because it would put somebody on top of Marilyn Monroe.
That's exactly right.
Yes.
Wow.
Let's go with people.
People.
Garbage disposal.
Toilet.
Base.
That we've.
All right.
I'm not sure.
So I'll go along with Bob.
Yes.
Oh, boy.
That was too easy.
They won.
Congratulations.
Yes.
Bob, you're going to put the fun and elegance back into its most unsavory aspect by eliminating
painlessly with a new and remarkably revolutionary poopy pet waste paper doll kit.
That's amazing.
Then they book the poopy wars by a handsome briefcase bag.
The party game including the fun and elegant peripatetic Bob bobblehead.
Bob, I know you're on vacation and walking the dog, but if you couldn't vacation with
the president this year, at least you have the next one.
And you could have used these.
This is the best thing.
The My Barack Obama, pooping Barack Obama.
Keychain.
Why'd it just turn between five neighborhoods, out in the issue with the pig from Iowa.
Congratulations.
Oh, there you go.
You really cleaned.
Can we count on that, though?
I mean, can we really.
Count on it.
That is a definite ransacking.
development in the direction that it's going unless several other things happen.
For example, if the power suddenly runs out.
And if the power runs out, that changes all these things just a little bit.
The curves are all different.
No, no, that's not it.
Very funny.
Some wayward fancies.
In this cloud-spinning fairy castle.
It's a cream-by-cloud cuckoo land.
So you think this is evidence of...
A Vulcan cuckoo time.
I see.
Yes, a fooling paradise.
I would be inclined to agree with you.
I think we should build a survey and give it to our constituents
and ask them if we should put together a task force to explore this.
But then it also might have its nobility, its elements of being a utopia.
If implausible and impractical, at least it means well and it's not.
If we don't get their funds and spend them exploring this concept,
we're just missing a golden opportunity.
We had two bags of grass, 75 pellets of mescaline,
five sheets of high-powered water acid,
a salt shaker half full of cocaine,
and a whole galaxy of upers, downers, screamers, lappers.
What a rum.
A line of law either.
Two dozen ambers.
Why don't you get locked into a serious...
drug collection?
The tendency is to push it as far as you can.
Ruppers.
Downers.
Screamers.
Ruppers.
Downers.
Screamers.
Ruppers.
Downers.
Screamers.
Oh, yeah.
I'm flying too boody.
This shit's for you, buddy.
Generals gathered in their masses.
Just like witches at black masses.
Yeah.
Evil minds that plot destruction.
Sorcerer of death's construction.
In the fields, the body's burning.
And the war machine keeps turning.
Well, I'm afraid of death and hate.
Too much time.
Poisoning their brainwashed minds.
Oh, Lord, yeah.
Hey, you know how...
Now in darkness, world stops turning.
Ashes where their body's burning.
No more war pigs out the power.
And the god of stop the hour.
Day of judgment.
God of justice.
It's calling.
Underneath the wall, it's calling.
Hey, well, I'm the fool.
There you pass, it's all the same.
Satan's up and gets his way.
Hey, well, I'm the fool.
Oh, Lord, yeah.
Registration and swag are now closed.
Right.
At 1 p.m. tomorrow, they will reopen.
On the other hand, friends,
if you get really drunk or high on something
and suddenly decide you have to have
a certain $100 worth of subgenius
crap, feel quite free
to approach me
specifically.
I will unlock
whatever needs to be unlocked
and take your money.
That's right, folks.
In fact, we've got a lot of swag here
that hasn't even been set out
because it hasn't been priced yet.
Just approach Honest Ivan Stang
and put in your bid and see how far
that gets you.
Honest Ivan Swag Shack.
That's us, friends.
Honest Ivan.
Honest Ivan's Swag Shack.
Because tonight is a pledge drive night
for those listening live on WCSB.
And even for those who are not listening to WCSB
but to one of our sister stations weeks later,
you can still...
It all still applies,
except for the phone numbers
and the premiums
and the credits.
And...
which are,
from the beginning of the show,
praise Reverend
Frodis Suds
Pasha,
who, besides doing tons of great graphics
and great music
lately,
whipped out that WCSB pledge
thing at the very beginning
with the funnily cut cuss words.
Thanks to a new contributor
for the
How to Be in a Band
late night infomercial.
That was by Reverend Dub Diablo
of the Subgenius Bait Shop.
The Bob Show collage
was by Reverend Dr. Royal Decapitator.
We heard Philodrummon, Dr. Howell
and Puzzling Evidence
on the Puzzling Evidence Show
from Puzzling Evidence.
KPFA in Berkeley
at kpfa.org
or quiveringbrain.com.
And we're going to have a little bit of a break.
And a live recording from X-Day
of the Evolution Control Committee
and the Subgenius Podcast folks,
Ministry of Slack,
doing that mashup of War Pigs.
And the last little bit
about the Swag Shack
was also at
14X Day, our annual event.
Which, by the way,
I just put a bunch
of stuff on my YouTube
channel.
That's youtube.com
Rev.
Stang.
All lower case.
Rev. Stang.
You can go there and see
all of 14X Day
in 11.5 minutes.
And I also just put up
some footage
at the very end of
Evolution Control Committee's
concert at X-Day
where he's doing this great
preaching kind of routine.
And his beautiful wife
is go-go dancing.
Trademark Gunderson.
And this is of most importance
to WCSB listeners.
I edited our movies
of the WCSB
annual Masquerade Ball
that was last weekend.
I may have mentioned that I put the pictures up.
But now there is
a movie up, a movie of
the rare appearance of J.R.
Bob Dobbs. It's about a 10-minute movie.
It shows little clips
of all of the bands and a whole lot of
funny costumes.
And Bob himself
is very, very
strangely represented.
I mean, I'm not sure if it was really Bob.
His skin seemed
unusually smooth
and his face is all floppy.
It's like his bones
aged, but his skin didn't.
It's very...
I mean, his hand gestures are...
You can see it at,
well, as I say, the Rev. Stang
channel on YouTube.
But also,
tinyearl.com
slash WCSB
2, numeral 2.
tinyearl
that's T-I-N-Y
U-R-L dot com
WCSB 2.
The slash between
this com and WCSB
numeral 2.
And it's a pretty funny movie,
actually.
Puzzling.
Very puzzling and strange.
You can see your...
All the other WCSB
DJs and bands and so forth.
But you won't know who they are
because they all have masks on.
And once again,
friends,
feed the Stangs.
Feed the station
by calling and pledging.
You can talk to Princess We Are Doe.
That's why she's not laughing
in the background.
She's taking calls.
Or you can talk to Dr. Sinister,
who also appears in that movie
I just plugged.
And all you have to do is call
the station
and pledge your
faith.
The number?
or more
easily remembered
Friends, I'd love to do pledge drive shows
because this is the only time we get to act like
real preachers and
try to bleed you for
every last penny you can spare.
And even pennies that you can't spare.
Here, look.
That's how many we've got so far.
That was all I could spare.
It's about five pennies.
Here, that little jar, collection jar.
I'm expecting
other co-hosts
to join me
any minute now.
But I should take this time...
Oh, I've come to...
Funny is, speak of the devil.
I am not the devil
of which you speak.
I am a devil of a distant world
unfamiliar to you.
The devil of the planet details.
The devil is in
the details.
Hiding his woolly horns
hoping not to be seen.
I wouldn't say that.
He's probably hoping to be voted for
in the upcoming elections.
Well, he's running in every party.
Right, he does.
That's how it works, man.
Thank goodness.
No matter who you vote for,
just by the fact that they're running for office,
it must be the devil.
Because who else would do a thing like that?
A crew of sociopaths
with an interest in gaining a lot of money
without having to do anything.
Well, that includes most subgeniuses, too.
But they don't have supernatural powers
until after they've
pledged
to WCSB.
I think it's one of the...
Which I can say,
I can't say what they would have to pledge
to the church as subgenius.
Probably their undying fealty
or their unbeknownst fealty, perhaps.
But anybody who would pledge
to WCSB,
to me, would be
one of the most wonderful people
in the entire world.
And we'll read their names out on the air, too.
I might want to break it up a little bit.
But I think of each and every contributor
out there
who's donated more than just their time and efforts
like this.
Like we and everybody who's
running phones and doing things.
I'm talking about the people
who come up with some money.
It's true.
They help more than anyone.
And what do they help with?
Why the station needs to update our website?
One last push.
It's more expensive than we thought.
We'll be archiving the shows.
Every show will be on for like a week or more
that you can download.
Although you can download this show,
of course, at subgenius.com.
You can download the last
1,332 shows.
This one is show number
1,333.
333 is the number of the anti-Bob, friends.
You're not going to let the anti-Bob win now,
are you?
No.
999 is the number of Bob
and of Herman Cain,
who may well be the
anti-Christ.
Some subgeniuses really want Herman Cain
to get elected because it would be so funny.
And it would be so funny.
It would drive, it would finally tip everything.
It would push things far enough
that there might be real serious,
serious change.
Not because of him, as a reaction to him.
Speaking of serious change,
as a reaction to Cain.
Listen to this serious change in this little jar.
There's five pennies in here.
Is that all we've been pledged so far?
Then that's my five pennies.
The sad thing is the previous show,
the guy came in here and took his change out.
Oh, man.
You know, he had to,
he used his own change as a sound effect.
Huh.
Hope and change.
That's the kind of change we're looking for, friends.
Oh, let me tell these folks
what they can get for their change.
Oh, they get plenty.
Yes, they do, actually.
For a mere $15.
I remember when it used to be a mere $5,
but $5 is like a penny now.
You can buy a piece of gum
or a small cup of plain coffee for five bucks.
For $15, friends,
why, there's a few VHS tapes
with these titles that I wrote down
because I like the titles.
Earth vs. the Spider.
Girlfriend from Hell.
And I know that you know about that one, friend,
even if you never saw the movie.
It's great stuff.
Incredible, incredible, incredible.
Martians Go Home.
Oh, yeah.
Reptilian.
That's the biography of George W. Bush, I think.
Yeah.
Things to Come,
screenplay by St. H.G. Bush.
Well, it's not to be confused
with the porno film Things to Come.
And here's the subgenius premium.
This is what everybody's been waiting for.
You know, every now and then
we do these triple X shows
that you can't hear on the radio
that we only put on the intranet.
Your ears would burn.
Well, for a $15 pledge,
your subgenius premium
is one subgenius triple X rated show.
My favorite recent one.
We did three recently.
And for your $20 pledge and up,
you get two of those.
And for $30,
you get three, three X shows.
Plus, in every case,
you get the famous
I'm Mad 2 Bob bumper sticker
as seen this week on Rachel Maddow's show.
Did you know that Rachel Maddow
mentioned us the other night on her show?
She has before even, too.
Well, she was,
she was explaining that
she considers Herman Cain
to be performance art.
She had pretty good reasons
behind that, too.
Much speculation is going in that direction
that he's perhaps a,
he's a form of performance art.
Yeah, an artist.
And he can't believe
that it's gotten this far.
You know, he thought it was,
he did it as a joke
and now he's going, oh my God.
Well, he did it for a few dollars,
more than a joke, but.
So, but yes, anyway,
you can, you can get your famous
I'm Mad 2 Bob bumper sticker
as seen on Rachel Maddow's show
to illustrate, for some reason,
she used that to illustrate
what performance art is about.
You got me.
Yeah, where does,
how does she know?
Why is she an authority?
And I know when she,
she grew up in San Francisco.
Pardon?
She grew up in San Francisco
where we were cool.
Oh, went to Design College of Art.
We were cool there.
Oh.
We were the coolest thing
in San Francisco in 1984.
They, they were too pretty cool.
They had, you know,
weird looking hair
and stuff like that
and their noses were,
they had like rings
in their noses and things
and their eyelids
and they're, they're funny.
They're fun to look at.
That's so 2009.
Really?
Yeah.
They were way ahead of their,
they were like 15.
That's how old people
try to look young now.
Yeah.
They get body piercings.
I hate that.
I hate to see a man like
about 72 years of age
with his body
like the illustrated,
man,
just covered with tattoos
and he's showing them off
on a porch
while he's drinking a beer,
you know?
Well, it's cool if he got them
when he was 30 years old
in prison or in the Navy,
but if he went to the mall
and just got them
so he'd be in
with the in crowd,
it's like when sportscasters
in the early 70s
started having long hair.
Yeah.
You know, longish,
styled, hippie.
It was like hippie hair,
but the kind you pay for.
Yeah, like what they used to do
with their nasal hair.
Make them look like
a little mustache and stuff,
but not quite, you know,
not quite a Hitler mustache.
You wouldn't want to stand
on that side of the fence
because the chickens
are over there.
A gentleman of age like us
should, besides calling
the station and pledging it,
I figure a feller should
wear his hair like he wanted to
in high school,
but they wouldn't let him,
which is why you and Dr. Howell
wear those ducktail
juvenile delinquent hairdos
and I have that
Grateful Dead bass player hairdo.
That could be the reason,
but I don't know if the
data set you're working with
could be called
totally reliable.
Some people have claimed
that the reasons why
our heads are all different
is because the magnetosphere
and the different vibrations
of our scouts
and the different noises
that they make
in the middle of the night.
To quote a dead guy,
my new forehead is great.
You can hardly hear the buzzing.
Get this, friends,
for $20,
you get two subgenius
XX rated shows.
Now these aren't
like one big track.
These are CDs
with like 30 to 50
separate tracks.
So you can play
just Sarah Palin
peep juice,
for instance,
by Rudy Schwartz Project
and so forth.
But you can also get
CDs,
and I'm just going to read off
the names.
There's a zillion CDs
here,
but I'm going to read off
the names of the bands
that I know.
And just that alone
will be big,
big,
big deal for me.
Like, for instance,
Negative Land,
a big 10-8 place.
One of,
a truly classic
album of collage editing.
Just astounding.
They were the
maestros of the art.
They were the originators
of the form that,
not the originators,
the form which goes
all the way back,
never mind.
But yes.
Yeah, they're very influential
and they played,
they played,
their second live gig
was opening for
Church of the Subgenius
the night Bob was shot
in 1984.
And Mark Hosler
handed me that album,
the LP,
and he said,
I wish I could show you
the reel-to-reel master
of this.
He says it was
edited with splicing tape
and he goes,
in some places,
the splicing tape
is up to five layers deep.
So the master
has a very weird look to it.
There's a CD available
for your $20 pledge
of,
by Zero Defects,
who played it last X-Day.
The Billy Nair Show album,
American Astronaut,
they also played it X-Day
a few years ago.
Poopy Necropondy,
his CD,
We're All Going to Tax You,
we see him every year
at the devotional.
GWAR,
GWAR's album,
Beyond Hell.
Didn't the GWAR just,
did the GWAR just die?
Yeah, the guitar player,
who was not the guitar player
I knew,
Flatus Maximus,
the latest.
You know,
there's been so many beefcakes
and so many Flatus Maximuses.
The subgenius was the one
named the Sexecutioner.
I actually opened for GWAR
very,
for like five shows
before they,
we all realized that
GWAR fans weren't into
spoken word,
no matter how sexy.
They were just plain mean.
Yeah, yeah.
They wanted to see
Fly Menstra, High Menstrus,
and her enormous opening,
shoot out a baby
and dump stage blood on them.
I don't blame them.
You did not want somebody saying
what you were saying.
Praise Bob.
No, I had to change.
What in the hell
do you think you're doing?
But we parted friends.
Odorous couldn't believe
we weren't going to sue him.
He goes,
but everybody that we kick off
of our tour sues us.
And we went,
you're not kicking us off.
We're leaving.
We can't handle this.
This is too much stress.
We didn't have that.
We're not kicking off
this tour sues us.
I was actually getting paid
more than he was.
And he had to wear
that heavy outfit
for two hours.
Oh, Kirkendall Void,
Cleveland local band.
Their CD, Graveyard of Go-Go.
I've tried to get them at X Day.
The Homo Stupids.
I don't know them,
but I love the name.
Grateful Dead.
I've heard of them.
KMFDM.
Neurosis.
Was on that GWAR tour.
Willie Nelson,
I've heard of.
Nucleon,
a local band that I saw.
And that's all the,
out of the list of,
I swear there must be
a thousand CDs
you can get for your,
one for your 20 buck pledge.
And I didn't,
I don't recognize
any of those band names
because I'm old.
However,
I should mention the music
in the background tonight
because I'm going to have
to cut this all up
for other stations.
I'm playing this weird,
avant-garde compositions
by Halim El-Dab.
Oh.
This is all,
all from his album
Musical Compositions
Through the Year,
which started with one
from 2006,
but let's see,
where are we at now?
Track three.
This is The Quest,
also 2006,
but a lot of these
are from like the 40s.
1973,
1961,
1952.
Well,
Halim,
Halim is about 95 years old.
He's a personal friend.
I can't say he's a close
personal friend,
unfortunately,
because I don't know him
that well,
but I see him a couple of times
a year at Starwood
and other places
and he's a professor
at Kent State
and a composer.
And he's an extremely hip cat.
He is the hippest cat.
He's like my hero
in terms of just having a life.
If I can be as spry
as I can be,
and good vibe projecting
as Halim El-Dab.
Still playing drums.
Well, I'll never do that.
But if I can still,
I'll still be,
they'll still be hauling me out on stage.
And I'll go,
repent,
quit your job,
slack off.
While you still remember how to.
While you still remember the words.
Mark my words.
Okay, let's see.
What else can we hit them up with?
Before I play music.
Sounds Bernard Harmon-ish
now in the background.
It sounds all kinds of ways.
Halim has,
he can do anything.
He can do a flabby prelude
by A12 as a dunder.
Yeah, he's a real composer.
He doesn't just like,
he doesn't do it like we do.
Yeah.
He writes it all down.
with the chef
until he attacks us
with a meat cleaver.
Friends, for your $25,
$25 pledge,
you get three triple X subgenius shows
and a Bob Bumper sticker.
You could get the X-Men Origins book.
Wow.
Many subgeniuses are X people,
X-day people,
and also X-humans,
X-intelligence,
X-geniuses,
X-ists,
existentialists.
And look at,
oh, why look,
speaking of existentialists
and so forth,
here's some of our pledgers.
The great Reverend Rock Roswell
pledged,
and he's getting the VHS tapes
of Evolution,
which is actually kind of a cute movie,
and Things to Come,
which is a classic movie.
Dr. Dark,
who shows movies at X-Day,
he's getting him
the Georgetown restaurant certificate.
So what an odd amount he donated.
Wow.
Oh, I get it.
Five, six, seven, eight.
$5,678.
No, not really, friends.
Here's, here's,
that's it.
And Little,
no, Elton Lytle,
or Lytle.
Lytle?
Or, yeah.
Elton Lytler?
Elton Lytle.
Or Lytley, I suppose it could be.
Little Lytley Elton.
I suppose.
Maybe he's wearing a fancy outfit.
No, it is,
for his,
$25 pledge,
he's getting the,
the X-rated Hours of Slack
and the 35th anniversary
of WCSB t-shirt.
This station has been around
for 35 years.
The Hour of Slack
has been on it
for probably almost 25
of those years.
But not quite that,
more like 20, I guess.
And you've been around here since,
I mean, when did you
and Chaz
and Path,
Psychopath find you?
Understar.
Chaz and I were making noises
in 1980s.
Right.
Six.
And then Psychopath
Render came up in 1987.
Man.
I guess that means I'm 143 years old.
But I just think of a wonderful place
like WCSB that harbors and shelters old,
you know, lunatics and crazy people
that wouldn't have any other place to go.
And why we can think of it,
say, like a political movement, perhaps.
Like, like Occupy Wall Street would be like,
Occupy your wall street.
Occupy your mind.
How do you want to occupy your mind
with quality stuff
that challenges your mind
or the banal drivel
that you're exposed to?
Let the hour of Slack
occupy your mind.
Dave, we got some inspiring letters
from people.
Remember when we had our
secret pledge drive
that we couldn't talk about
on the public radio,
but only on the internet radio?
Mm-hmm.
I got some letters
of people who had never,
you know,
they didn't want to say
how much they liked us
because they figured people
were kissing our butts all the time
and constantly throwing money at us,
which turned,
I had to finally admit,
wasn't actually true.
Yeah.
But this,
here's a person
who says,
I don't know what else to say
other than to tell you
that I think you are a hero.
Only a hero like you
could take the absolute drudgery of life,
which these days
has become pretty unbearable.
For the regular work-a-day Morlock
and turn it into comedy.
You look at the oblivion
and doom of modern living
and you laugh in the face
of its futility
while most of us only live
as closet rebels,
living our lives
of quiet desperation
to the sounds of laugh tracks
or American Idol.
Most of us line up
and take what we're given,
but you are someone
who stood up
and then did something original
and amazing.
You made a whole religion
out of the subconscious anger
many of us feel
when faced with the reality
of everyday life.
For that, you're my hero.
Oh, he's talking to Bob,
not me.
No, he's talking to you
and that's why I'd like to use that
in my resume
and I can't.
That's disgusting.
I mean, it's beautiful.
You can.
Go ahead and do it.
And he also taped a penny.
But I didn't invent the religion.
You did.
I mean, Bob did.
The letter I'm holding
has a penny taped to it.
I'm going to pull it off
and I'm going to donate that
to WCSB right now.
There it is.
There's another penny.
Six cents now.
Amen and hallelujah.
Praise Bob.
Now, here's a...
Another penny in the coffer.
Another tithing gone down.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's time to give, give, give.
Empty your wallets freely.
Pull them out of your pants.
No, not that.
Stand back.
Get away from me.
Let me find one that mentions...
Oh, here's one that mentions you, Dave.
You'll like this one.
This is from Reverend Hoosier Dada.
Although you are a younger man than I,
even the venerable Dr. Howell
is not older than I.
Lonesome cowboy Dave,
who can say?
Certainly not your child bride, we.
Your grasp of the heritage of my youth,
Forrest J. Ackerman et al.,
interbred with the shape of things to come.
There's things to come again.
Jonathan Colton et al.,
as a mainstay of my internal life.
You are the ringmaster of a weekly circus
with acts which are beyond legal.
I mean, beyond anything
I would have thought to seek out,
let alone find.
Thank you for bringing the collages
and songs together under one tent.
Listening to you and Dave and Howell and we
note the alphabetization to avoid a hierarchy.
Yeah, he was already formatted in
when he didn't, you know,
and he forgot to...
Oh, brave new world that has such people in it.
People, yeah, people, sure.
But this.
By this time, you've either received
the woefully inadequate love offering
I sent to the heights of Cleveland
on Friday last,
or some unseemly,
unseen hand has claimed it for its master.
But as the Joker has taught me,
any attempt to control things is pathetic.
So I can only surf the luck plane,
enjoy the ride,
and hope your own red light
claimed the cash as intended.
Want to know how I got these scars?
It will be beyond sad
when the last hour of slack fades into silence.
But let us not dwell on the coming darkness.
To paraphrase John Carter of Mars,
we will live.
Man.
And this person married his own son
and daughter-in-law last year
and is within days of being a grandpa.
He married both...
He married his own son.
How can you marry your own...
I mean...
I know, I know, that's sick.
Let's see.
They don't like to hang around that much
to begin with.
Here's someone who misunderstands.
You put so much work into it.
The sound collages you make,
like...
See, that's why I give the credits.
Most of those collages are made by other people.
I collage the whole show together.
But that's only 30 pieces,
not 30 million pieces
like Susie the Flusie collage.
Well, you are like...
What's his name?
The excellent corp of the French bulldog.
That's of the late 1930s.
Yeah, I know. Old-fashioned.
No, no.
You know what it is
to be a BS-er
and a dada.
In short, I love Bob.
He says we do humor.
The underground music is always fun.
Your wit and humor
is tip-top to the point
I repeat it a lot to friends.
Wow.
In a near-bit-hack way.
I love Bob and the church.
Being a member is fun
as I confuse many pinks with my ramblings.
Yet always the best
is to listen to the subgenius radio shows.
Keep it going, brother.
My donation is $6.66.
To start.
Unfortunately, that wasn't hundreds of dollars.
I want you to mention this on the air
in a challenge
for every church member to match it.
Match that $6.66.
It's under my slave human name of...
Please use my title under Bob
of Emperor Pope Wagner XVII
in your possible shout-out to me.
And there it was.
That was the shout-out.
Wow.
Well, I think then that should be
what we should ask.
Everybody out there
in the Burg of Clee,
in the land of Clee,
is to come up with 666.
And if we could get perhaps
666 people
to pledge $6.66
or $66.06
to the WCSB.
That's the SDSC.
6900, by the way,
if you'd like to start right now
before anything happens.
Because time has a way
of making things quicken.
As things are imminent right now,
the entire, not only this station,
but the whole east side of town
could explode or be vaporized
just like that.
Right.
And we wouldn't need...
Well, never mind.
You never know when this will be
the last hour of slack you'd ever hear.
And it'll be because of...
Or the other great shows on this station.
Yeah, the last time you listen
to African Abstract or Synesthesia
or it just goes on.
The Charleston show is...
I'm looking through the window.
Synesthesia is...
They're all famous.
Princess, we sit in there
reading Anathem.
And what's Dr. Sinister doing?
Oh, he's playing pocket pool.
That's what they always do.
Yep.
Waiting for a phone call.
Friends, damn it.
Now, if you folks ain't gonna call in,
I'm just...
I'm not gonna put up with it.
They don't cut no ice with me.
Oh, Dr. Sinister did just get a call.
He did get a call.
Have we got six calls?
He's playing pocket pool
while taking a call.
Oh, and Princess,
we just grabbed the phone.
So it's...
But there's...
Now, I want the kids...
The power of my brain.
Get them phone lines going.
They can hear me all the way
to the back of the amphitheater.
They knew that Carthage
must be burned.
And that means that
it must pledge now.
Friends, I've had it.
I'm gonna...
I'm so...
I'm...
I'm driven to play
a song we played
just two weeks ago.
You'll love it, though.
It's beautiful.
It is beautiful.
I'm going to play this song
called Feed the Stangs.
It was written by Pope...
and sung by
Popes Pontiera Evacuator.
Who is seen
topless in that YouTube movie
I discussed earlier
before you called in, Dave.
That doesn't mean that
she's exposing her breasts.
That means that
the top of her body is gone.
Well, it's...
You know, actually, Dave,
yesterday I spent
hours putting little black bars
over
breastages and peni
of subgeniuses
at X Day.
Movies.
The pictures of them.
Okay, but you were
continuing that you were
doing that a long time
meant that there was a lot
to cover up, so to speak.
There was.
And you can see that
on YouTube
slash RevStang
14X Day
in 11.5 minutes.
But I'm gonna play
this song here, Dave.
I'm gonna pot you and me down,
okay?
I love this song.
And we're gonna play this.
And also, the orchestration
on this is by Reverend Sud Shaw.
Feed the Stangs.
Each day to a mysterious stage
The little old Ivan Stang tries
In his own special way
To the Yeti he calls
Come by my table of swag
Come feed my little wife
Show her you care
And you'll be glad if you do
My grandkids are hungry
Our house is so bare
All it takes is money
From you
Feed the Stangs
Money for swag
Money, money, money for swag
Feed the Stangs
That's what he cries
Warm overhead
Space ships fill the skies
In Wisteria, campground Bob dies
In the dark, the sun is shining
He hopes in his midlands
Look down at the Yeti hide
And though you can't see it
You know that he's smiling
Each time that you give
Thirty-five
No, his words are simple
And few
Listen, listen
He's calling to you
Feed the Stangs
Money for swag
Money, money, money for swag
What the hell do you think this is?
You're a little woman
Dragging your butt through the day
Time for the hit and all of the guilt
But none of the sex
There is a simple answer, dear friend
A glowing beacon of slack
Amidst the turmoil that lurks
It's J.O. Bob Dawgs
And his mighty Church of the Subgenius
No, his words are simple
And few
Listen, listen
He's calling to you
Feed the Stangs
Money for swag
Money, money, money for swag
Repent, quit your job
Slack off and praise Bob!
Got anything?
Nah.
Laying down, eh?
Did you get anything?
No.
Oh, slacker.
Wait a minute.
Did you get anything?
Yeah, did you?
No.
Does that make any difference?
I guess it's come around.
Bob, and some of you are saying, who's Bob?
Well, you'll learn.
But I want to talk to Bob about some stuff.
1845-59-0338.
Can you imagine the checks Bob gets?
I got a name.
Here's another check.
They're going to open up the gates to the great Bob that I'm entitled to.
Who I think is a myth that I'm entitled to.
And I think it's guys like Bob.
Because, I mean, Bob works.
Actually, Bob slacks off and we work.
Mostly.
Sort of.
Parts of us work.
Some parts just sort of work and leak a bit.
Some parts are even, yes, they're leaking.
Reverend Decapitator did that last little Bob works thing.
It was very lovely.
When we get off the air of puzzling evidence,
famous ancient.
Collage will play.
But there's somebody listening from Korea right now.
It says.
They can send us their Korean dollars.
Or yuan or whatever they're called.
I forgot.
The Korean person just donated.
Wow, that's beautiful.
And here's the Reverend.
Oh, that's Bishop Stick.
Bishop Stick is playing on the 14X day in 11.5 minutes.
Video that I just put on YouTube.
And Princess Wee and Priestess Pisces are singing on that.
But that's not what's happening in the background right now.
No, in the background, it's still Halim El-Dab jamming away.
That's in the audio background.
But in the visual background, there are a few elves dancing around the little fire they've created right in the middle of the studio.
As a form of television for the blind.
That's another thing you're not supposed to say.
Because the fire department.
Okay.
Well, the fire department.
Actually, the fire department was here a little while ago.
Yeah, they were the actual artists.
No, they came in to donate.
Put their fire hats out and their boots on.
Now, even if you hear this on the internet, you can go to WCSB.org.
And that's the only way you can pay with a credit card or PayPal.
Because the callers here can't tell Princess Wee.
Just went to get another call.
The callers here can't.
We can't take credit cards.
At the station.
Except by web at WCSB.org.
And for those on the web who are perhaps in a distant land, or maybe just another state,
they can remember that the area code is 216.
But see, I have to cut these for...
I'll still run, even though it's like a pledge drive for this specific station,
I'm still going to chop it up and send it to other stations.
Because most of them have pledge drives too.
And even if they don't, I don't care.
I don't care whether it's efficient or makes any sense.
It's what religions do.
I called Pappy on the way up to the station.
He said, that's the way most ecclesiastical people work.
They guilt trip you into giving money.
That's it.
See, from those older folks, we get all of our erstwhile erudite beginnings,
our somnolent little small animals.
That we...
You...
Well, especially...
That sometimes we have to carry all the way over the...
But that's where I get my ideas from, is from the elders of the tribe.
When I can.
Sometimes they just bother me and throw me out of the tippy.
I'm descended from at least five preachers.
And all of them were heretics on some level or another.
Pappy...
In fact, Pappy's not a preacher.
He was a lawyer, which is bad.
But he preaches nonetheless.
He preaches doubt.
He's a Methodist church in Stanksville, in Stanks County, Texas.
So...
And he truly does.
He must be very, very, very, very sad.
No, that's the wrong word.
Forget it.
I was going to provide some descriptive color, and I just...
Never mind.
And that's why to fulfill yourself in at least the smallest way you can as a human being,
because we live and die, is to send your pledge to...
Well, this number is the number to call.
To make a pledge.
687-99-6.
And you'll probably get a shot glass and a punch in the mouth from WCSB.
And with that, I'm going to put back on...
You know, I never used any of my old pledge drive all-purpose stuff.
And I'm not going to.
I'm just going to put on...
I'm going to put you on, friends.
I'm going to put on The Harvest by Puzzling Evidence.
Dave, thank you for calling.
It's now show overtime.
And I hope you haven't stained your pants in your desire, your fervent desire,
to wake those ruffians out there who just don't want to pledge.
I'm sorry.
We're all so terribly sorry.
And now, Puzzling Evidence.
But one doesn't listen wrong before a little warning signal goes off inside that says,
Watch out.
Sometimes it's hard to pinpoint the precise error.
But the language, the pure language of heaven,
is missing.
Something says, look out.
This guy is fishy.
Cultist or someone with his theological wires crossed.
It's almost like listening to someone who knows only a few words of English,
but soon they're rattling off in a completely unknown language
when they haven't even been to kindergarten spiritually.
We eat more, drink more, play more,
and do less to earn a good living than any other people in history.
We have at our fingertips the world's greatest music.
And I might...
I might add a lot of its worst,
else the cultists would have no following.
We are a people grasping nervously,
sometimes almost hysterically for more.
I know that I know that I know that I know that I know
that I know that I know.
Whenever we read the obscene stories,
the voluptuous debaucheries,
the cruel and torturous executions,
it would be more consistent to call it the word of a demon.
There are little eyes upon you,
and they're watching night and day.
With a vocal and activist minority
ready apparently to burn a bomber's seal of kills for more.
And most, incidentally, are in their teens or their twenties.
And that's Washington people, I'll tell you that.
They dwelled in caves, not high-rise apartments.
They may not have found a key to affluence,
but they found...
an endless supply of dope,
uninhibited sex,
an endless supply of money,
free access to a distillery, I suppose.
Ah, yes, the harlot.
You can count on that.
Or kill for more.
Why, friends, we could feed another nation with our garbage.
What more than a space hogger on Earth?
Is the church of geniuses?
I don't know.
But how many of you are really genuinely intelligent?
Thanks.
Otherwise if you would believe,
I mean, it is so ironic because some of these false preachers can raise millions and millions of dollars.
No problem there.
Well, I tell you what, I challenge you, Jim Swaggart.
I challenge you, Jim Baker.
I challenge you, Oral Roberts.
You see this hand here?
You see this hand in front of me, Mr. Jim Baker?
This is called the claw, and it's got the power of dogs in it.
And I challenge you to show your ugly face here at this radio station and come forward.
Go ahead.
Come forward with all your millions.
I'm ready to have a match without rules.
No rules at all.
One will survive.
One only.
One minister will leave the match still breathing if one of you goody-goody preachers has the guts to show up.
Ah, yes.
I'm sitting here drinking some Texas Select beer.
Fran.
Beer!
You hear that, Jimmy Swaggart?
You don't drink beer, oh no, or smoke on froth because you don't know the power of these herbs.
I challenge any minister do-gooder out there to show up.
All of you, with all your TV shows and all your bought-off politicians, your paid-off judges.
Do any trick you want, but I got the claw, I got the power of Bob and the power of Texas Select.
And you, my friend listener, has the power to call.
This station.
Do it.
The times, the end times get closer and closer every minute.
Imagine some guy or some gal driving around out there.
They're tired of listening to the same old music on their conspiracy radio show.
So they try switching channels and they come upon this.
They hear these voices talking and they think, now what is this?
A talk show?
A church show?
A comedy?
I mean, oh my God.
Are these people serious?
It's too developed to be a joke.
Should I kill them?
No, not that part of it.
You know, the part where everybody, you know, liked each other and everybody had the same house
and everybody thought the same things and everybody seemed to be on the same page except for the them.
Whoever they might have been then, there's always been a them.
And it dawned on me that these people are just so frightened that everybody is frightened.
Everybody completely whack job church.
I don't quite understand it.
You know, once you get talking to Bob for a little while, he started, you know, dropping words like World War III, destroy the church, programmable priests.
The world is going to end.
The Federal Reserve.
I mean, he was hitting all the buzz points and who's going to want to go to that church.
And then he got sort of confused in the genetically designed Federal World War III and Iran reserve system diseases.
But for some reason, I just let him keep talking.
Bob challenges people to be tolerant of change.
And apocalyptic visions and challenges people to try to be accepting of a big fiery mess.
If you're going to honor the idea of genetically designed nuclear democracy bombs flying everywhere by the big they that they distribute in order to kill off the three billion people that are necessary to balance out the population.
Do you need to cry?
You need to have a good cry, don't you?
Why are you so afraid, little man?
You know what?
You know, Bob from the office.
That guy.
You eat lunch with every day.
I just found out he's such a good guy.
That's that's I can't even I don't even know what to do with that.
But if you have a problem with Bob, then you have to learn how to be a big fiery mess.
And that's that.
Sire, there is no more money.
We gotta get some money.
That dirty Turkish harker back.
Black and rotten.
Philip Buckaburton.
Perkaluma Burton.
Don't you watch tonight.
Oh, B.O.B.
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show.
And we're even more glad that some listeners have donated enough to help us keep on going for another couple of months.
And not just this show, but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob and want some of that slack back to rebound to you, you should go to subgenius.com front page or especially the radio page or the catalog store pages.
And help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty.
And we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference.
Even if it's only once a month from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that blowjobs could go the way of Steve jobs if you don't pay dogs.
We also...
We also take checks and money orders to Subgenius Foundation.
P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Thanks for anything you can do to help let there be slack.
Suspects described as outright compensation for several requests received by bar while receiving running-edge bâruts from the local Customs Office.
United States Department of HealthSD has received famíliares 콜-8060 from remember and medical staff to manage the staff activities of the Paraclassmen Department of Health andRobeson
national medium
official
Kill me!