🎵
Most greatest, great, stunning, surprising, first magical, legendary, fame, large, great, big, costly, faster, magic, relatively new, older, first, great, genuine, beautiful, giant, perfect, cool, special, shared, elaborate, easy, ultimate, best, natural, growing, special, nice, proud, quicker, and much more.
Uh, yes, dear friends, it is rerun time again, but you'll be glad to know that we're not going to just do the same old three Christmas hour of slack show reruns in a row.
No, I'm going to compress it all into just this one intensive total rerun show, except that actually it's not, uh, the whole first, uh, half will be, uh, uh,
largely peppered with a new Christmas sickness for, uh, the holidays and holy days and, uh, uh, the hole-in-head days, as it is for some people.
Uh, actually, I have to work double time because it's the season of selling! Selling, yes! Oh, you wouldn't believe what the elves have done over at the subgenius catalogs!
But, uh, uh, anyway, uh, happy, uh, whatever you do.
And, uh, uh, yes, this music in the background is, uh, somebody named Kenny Wayne Shepard.
Yeah, there's an album called Merry Axmus and Guitar Axmus.
It's cool, man, cool! And, uh, praise Bob and, uh, ho-ho-ho-ho!
I'd like to find the guy who done me wrong and stuck my butt up on this Christmas tree.
Oh, no!
Who put the stomp in my romp-a-bomp-a-bomp? Who tuck and jammed it in my ram-a-lam-a ding-dong?
Who stubbed the wood where I poop-she-poop-she-poop? Who put the stick up my hip-tip-tip-tip?
Who was that man? He shoved it up my can and left me stranded on this Christmas tree.
Yeah!
Will you stop it?
Woo!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
When this angel heard chop-a-pop-a-pop-a-chop-a-pop-a-pop, a dreadful fear went right into my heart.
Those pine-tree needles sting me – ram-a-jam-a-ram-a-jam-a-ring-a-ding-dong!
You'll never know how much that smarts you could do.
So..
Sometimes.
Who took the stump and my romp-a-bomp-a-bomp?
Who took and jammed it in my ram-a-lam-a-ding-dong?
Who stood the wood where I boop-she-boop-she-boop?
Who put the stick up my hip-a-dip-a-dip?
Who took that bush and crammed it in my tush?
He made this angel beg for mercy, please.
I might squeeze him too tight.
It's that psychedelic time of the year.
Do you know where your brain cells are?
It's already 9 p.m.
Don't go looking out in the backyard to dog-aid him.
Don't go walking down to the bar,
because old Frankie died last night in the backyard.
I mean, in the apartment store.
Oh, can I borrow the brain cells tonight?
Yeah, he brought back the chainsaw.
Yeah, and I ain't gonna let you use the brain cells
till I get the damn chainsaw fixed and back in my arm
the way it was.
Now, you boss be good,
and I'll give you some this here.
There can't be no good about it.
You ain't no good of a child.
That dog's run off with them brain cells.
Can you do something about that, boy?
I'm gonna have to.
It could be his head wasn't screwed on just right.
Eric Cranston! Eric Cranston! Eric Cranston! Eric Cranston!
What wing has manufactured Rosalia is fun.
The fate of a child.
Spend all the money you've got.
The Christmas trough.
I've lost my freaking mind.
Oh, look, Dave's dressed like Santa Claus.
Look at your eyes.
It's like a cowboy Santa.
How jolly.
Oh, Jazz is giving, gives Dave the show pills.
Boy, I really need one of those.
What am I going to do about laundromat in this suit, though?
I need the show bath.
The show de-lousing.
Oh, Dave doesn't even have headphones yet.
That's enough of that.
Oh, he's got headphones.
I also have the part of my pancreas that I'd like to show you now.
It's been increased in size to...
Oh, your pancreas looks lovely, Dave.
Look, it's swelling.
I actually have the capability of a man of 190 IQ's brain.
Come on.
I'll put more pills out for everybody.
Yeah.
Oh, those pills.
They make my mouth feel like it's on fire.
More pills.
And my brain feel like it's a puddle of liquefied crystals.
I'm shocked by the...
I'm sorry.
The red pills are really good.
I like to take the red one.
Oh, I like the red one.
I agree.
The blue one and the blue one, at the same time.
That way you go in and out.
The warp mix is easy.
You...
It's so high, you can't go over it!
Angels we have heard on high Singing about mountain dew
And those mountains in reply Saying we wish we had some, too
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Wario, in excelsis Deo
Barbie Dolls
Women rape and memorialize their lives by role-playing with Barbie
We have devised a marketing scheme for children's toys.
They will empower us to resist them.
You will use your power.
Your church as a vehicle to bring these toys before the public.
It will be a BOMBER FOR KIDS.
But how will the battle of good against evil be represented in your marketing schemes, human?
Good has lots of muscles.
Good.
Good!
The primitive earth.
The modern society should accept this value judgement.
Good will have free physical attributes according to human desires, sexual desires, latent in children, brought out through the vehicle of this so-called
So far we're told these toys have germs.
Batteries not included.
But there is a metaphor for them.
What is it that makes them shine?
The
Angels We Have Heard on High
it was by The Philistines
the collage called All The Money You've Got
is from the great Obtuse Christmas collage album
which you can get for free
check out this website
obtuse.iuma.com
that's obtuse
excuse me
next up The Real Story of Christmas
by Michael Shelley
Once upon a time
there was the baby Jesus
and he had two eyes made out of coal
and he was stuck up a partridge in a pear tree
and he wanted his two front teeth
and he got McDonald's gift certificates
and he
he
had a dog named Santa's little helper
and he took all the presents from Whoville
and his friend Yukon Cornelius
came with the three wise guys
and he wanted to play the drums
and be the little drummer boy
but he couldn't
he wanted 10s and 20s
10s and 20s
and he got McDonald's gift certificates
and he got Zuzu's pedals
and that's
The Real Story of Christmas
onitional
Heat
cold
before Andre
seems like a white он
an egg
if only he wasn't
Tell him I am
careful
the truth
or his baby is all wrong
Our Sweetonster
Da-da-da-da-da-da
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da
So separate, it's so separate, it's so separate
New from Tonka
Now you are in my evil clutches, Bob
I'll use this MTV bombardment to turn you normal
Shut up, pink boy!
No way, I'll never sell out to the conspiracy
Taste a little of my rocket pipe, alien fool
Bob Dobbs comes with rocket pipe, head launcher, janger device
All I got is a fightin' Jesus and other action figures sold separately
Some assembly required, batteries not included
This toy falls apart in three days
He-Bob and the bastards of the universe
Too much is always better than not enough
He-Bob and the bastards of the universe will be back after this message
Santa Claus
Well, Tommy knew exactly what he wanted for Christmas
He wanted an electric train
He had the whole thing on his mind, even to the table where it was going to set it up
He could picture the whole thing and he would dream so far that the whole thing would come to life right before his eyes
He was a pretty strong wisher
And what he started wishing for was a pretty fancy looking train set with locomotives and freight cars
He-Buber
and the station
and the gatemen
AnimalQuest
The Mozart Tower
And all the wonderful kinds of equipment and accessories
So grand, you might think that Tommy was waiting for something that just didn't exist
anyway
don't forget to follow us 4 comparison
a.k.a the Game of Thrones
But Tommy knew what he was wishing for.
It is turnover.
The time of the year when all things sell.
The end of the year sale.
Oh, yeah.
So come and get it, everyone, and just buy our products.
Now, are we, is Christmas, I'm a little confused about what Christmas is all about.
Are we celebrating the birth of Santa Claus or his death when they nailed him?
Well, that's the ancient, ancient subgenie.
But the present subgenie try to make sure that we have our inventories cleared by now and sell everything to the pigs.
Oh, yes.
Once a pagan holiday and now a shopping season.
And it was something else in between there.
Before it was, after it was a pagan holiday and before it was a shopping season, it was something else.
But I think they started to war over it.
Yeah.
But do you want me to?
All I know is you're gone.
When you trust your heart.
Oh, oh, oh, yeah.
Because we're gone.
But do you want me to?
Yeah, it's too much fun.
All I know is you're gone.
Oh, oh, oh, yeah.
So Santa has to sell.
Santa.
Santa Claus.
Just be
B
riction
Secret
The
Secretary
Hi?
Friends, try to imagine
somewhere in the snowy north,
the Santibob trudging mindlessly
through the Himalayan snows,
driven by strange forces
to complete his nameless errand.
And he may show up at your house, my friend,
if you've been a bad subgenius
or a halfway subgenius,
or if we keep getting tangled up
in these other shows
and having strange microphones.
How did that paternity suit ever turn out
between Dobbs and Santa?
And who?
His dad.
Santa dog.
I don't know.
I don't think it was...
Yes, but St. Nicholas, this is fact,
St. Nicholas punched another bishop
in the nose and bloodied his nose.
Really?
The historian?
The historical St. Nicholas?
Over the trinity of God.
The original St. Nicholas in Turkey?
I swear upon Bob.
Who the hell is God?
The heart.
I can tell you, I said God.
Who the hell is God?
Ask Dobbs one day.
That's the question we should be asking.
Suddenly, a lightning bolt struck from nowhere
on that bright, sunny day.
Bob did a backflip,
and from that day on,
he too was a believer.
And from the snow didn't stop.
A little child bearing flowers emerged.
And Chip, Chip, what else was on the table?
Each one a dirty flower.
It's the St. Nicholas.
Sip, sicken.
The historical Santa Claus
is originally lived,
as the caller knows,
as a bishop in,
was it Constantinople?
Yeah, like one of those...
It was in ancient Byzantium.
Like a cafeteria or...
Yeah, Asia Minor in general, yeah.
Yes, he was...
And he was known for
sneaking into the rooms of young women
and leaving gifts.
Life-size lumps of gold
complete with a fake beard
and a CIA Wall Street credit card.
A saint he was, the girl said.
St. Nicholas invented the CIA.
You got it, brother.
He snuck into people's houses through the chimney.
They were sleeping.
He knew when they were awake.
You got it, brother.
But like the CIA, he was...
That's Foucault, baby.
He was protecting them.
Foucault knew that St. Nick
was a creeping, stinking spy.
What?
He knows when you've been sleeping.
He knows what you've been eating.
Hey, man, my kids still believe in St. Nicholas.
And who keeps that belief alive
in their fevered, sick little brain?
Madison Avenue, of course.
No, the surveillance community
is under your direction.
And the Reynolds Tobacco Company.
He's a very powerful being.
If you're bad, he punishes you.
If you're good, he rewards you.
He's probably the closest thing to Jesus
walking the earth.
He's the closest thing to Big Brother there is.
He rewards those who knows when they're smiling
when they're awake.
I think, really, if you want to make a deal,
you have to do it with, you know...
Could Dr. Claus, in fact, be the
wandering, quote, milkman
rumored to have fathered
our savior, J.R. Bob Dodds?
Well, we find it very likely.
Possibility from the falsified documents
we have here.
And also the fluffy beard
that often grew on Bob's feet.
You better watch out.
You better not.
And I'm telling you why.
St. Nicholas is coming to town.
Material plums? Biological agents who only take 15%?
Oh, it's a great day, all right. A salute to Mr. and Mrs. America.
Shop as usual. Shop as usual. Shop as usual. And avoid panic buying.
Shop as usual. Shop as usual.
Sometimes I think all that Santa crap's just bull.
Santa Claus is real. Santa Claus is real. Santa Claus is real. Santa Claus is real. Santa Claus is real.
You're the cause for the child.
Who's the head man?
Santa Claus.
He was a huge, beastly, bulging man.
He was so real.
How come we didn't get scared?
He was like Walt last year.
Yes, the birth of the baby Satan on July 4th.
And now you can have it all pure 100% vinyl chloride CID.
The birth of our baby Satan as told by various authors and eclectic scholars from around the globular unit.
Including that announcer.
This announcement has not been a perfunctory announcement.
An announcement.
of the blessed anointing and birthday of our Lord,
Zinu.
Praise Zinu.
For one bright Christmas morning,
Zinu was born in a cradle to a rich man's family.
The Rave Jesus.
Oh, I know the Rave Jesus.
I'm partying with the Rave Jesus.
I owe a soul a merry little Christmas.
Let your sight be light
from the water triples with the outer sky.
Have yourself a merry little Christmas.
From now on we're miles away.
We're miles away.
Once a day as in olden days,
a happy golden day,
miles away.
Let's go.
Let your heart
be out of sight.
Out of sight.
The Jackson 5.
I wish everybody
a merry little Merry Christmas
and a gloomy, gloomy day.
From a mutated Christmas, friends,
the Have Yourself a Merry Little Christmas
by No-Dash.com.
L. No. L.
Before that, some year-old ESO
and Michael Shelley did that real story of Christmas
from the Tarkin Records All-Star Holiday Extravaganza.
I'm playing a lot from that.
So check out www.triage.com
for that one also.
The Tarkin Records is also on www.triage.com.
And now, the Jethro's.
Stephen, David, and Phil Philosophy Live.
Go.
OK.
That's a great view.
The nappy was body hot.
I'm out.
And the snow isEXICITING.
construction, and really cool.
Coming on Red Rubber Stang.
The Weir Bobs and Ima, those who have the psychosis that convinces them that they are the Santa Bob.
Or that they're Santa Bob by night.
And they go shuffling through the snow on their nameless, hideous errands.
The grin of Bob and the beard of Santa Claus and the pipe of the Lord stuck on their face.
They stop using the locks of their doors and they just kind of float into the keyhole.
Oh, friends, it's tough.
And, you know, just going to church ain't enough.
You gotta send your money to the Santa Bob.
As a matter of fact, the people across the street from me told their kids that Santa Claus bills them for the toys he brings.
Can you believe that?
The kids were asking if their parents, maybe Santa Claus will bring us two He-Man erector sets.
And the mom said, no, no, he won't because he bills us.
We can't afford that.
Santa Claus sends us a bill after Christmas.
Yeah, but at least he totes the note.
Let's be friends.
A cool message and a measure of joy.
Oh, boy.
I have to give games to the kids.
That's fair to give our kids.
Oh, boy.
And amazing.
More from Corporal Blossom.
I am really impressed by their editing work.
And that's on Corporal Blossom and the Mutated Christmas
is on the Illegal Art label.
That's www.detritus.net
slash illegal art.
www.detritus.net slash illegal art.
And now, more Jethro's.
Jethro's.
Now you're blaming Jesus.
You're blaming our Lord.
I sort of understand because
I understood the way any old fool would understand.
There was no Jesus.
No flatulent old woman waving her panties on the hill.
It's not that you don't want to.
It's that they won't let you.
No, they're ashamed.
Just a cry in the wilderness.
They're ashamed.
In the hot pursuit of wolves.
Everywhere.
In the background.
I'm ashamed of them.
It's cold.
I'm leaving that city life behind.
I can't get my finger off the paper.
I can't get my needle back in the pan, Jen.
Come on, cowboy.
No, man.
I was trying to hear a can against your tree
and it started whispering to me, man.
Oh, you've been drinking.
There's the face of the Madonna right up there.
There's the face of the Virgin Mary.
I swear to God, look at it.
Isn't it?
What?
It's her Christmas.
It's your Christmas witch coming true.
Wow.
A Christmas witch?
I'll be horny.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, I guess it does look a little bit more...
Her breasts are so cold.
I know she must be a true witch.
I guess you could call her that if that's what she's packing down.
She's surrounded by hovering Christmas ornaments.
It looks like a radar device.
What?
Yo.
Yo?
It's her.
What up?
Nothing.
What's up?
What a deep voice.
For Christmas.
What's up?
Thank you.
Mother Mary, oh, blessed lady.
Hail, Mother Mary.
I fell in love with your son.
Turn me on and on and on.
Hail, Mother Mary.
Thank God for you and your son.
Right on, right on, right on, right on.
Right on.
I am yours truly, Rudy Ray Moore, bold and still beautiful.
Baby, I want to talk to you for this kiss.
Because Christmas holds a lot of memories for me.
Baby, I've had a lot of hard times at Christmas time.
I can remember me and my brother when I was about six years old.
We hung our stockings up over the mantelpiece and the health department made us take them down.
I remember my father well, you know.
My father used to wake up every morning with a headache.
He used to, you know what caused it then?
He used to put a...
He used to put a stocking cap on his head.
And put a knock light in front of it.
Daddy wake up with that stomping headache.
And he said, the kids are saying, my head's hurting so bad.
He said, I don't know what Santa's going to get y'all for Christmas, but he's going to bring you something.
So Daddy took that old rifle and went outside and shot up in the air and come back inside and told us the biggest lie I ever heard.
He said, kid, Santa just committed suicide.
And whose birth do we celebrate with this new century?
They even come to questioning now.
Who was nailed on that great manger cradle but Satan Claus?
Oh my God.
Whose father, Paul Bunyan, and whose mother, Big Sister, created the conspiracy?
Did they have Christmas before there were malls?
Before there were malls, there was no such thing as Christmas?
Yes.
The Pilgrims for Babies?
There was a down-home Norman Rockwell style, it's a wonderful life type of Christmas.
It was a...
It was a kite-flying Coca-Cola drinking Christmas, not a crack-smoking, rubber-snapping Christmas.
When your little brother broke through the hole, it fell through a hole in the ice sling,
and you went and saved him.
You didn't laugh at him and huff some more glue.
It was a wonderful life back then.
I remember when Uncle Bud would come in with a keeter.
He would have candles, like most people have.
He would have that smile on his face and a big red nose.
But today, Christmas has lost its meaning.
He just beaten the crap out of Santa Claus.
Scott, you made your choice.
When you rejected my word, you rejected me.
And to your eternal soul, you have found that only could you afford to give to God that which was his.
Yes.
But you could not afford to do otherwise.
The Senate still stands.
You know, out of darkness, where there is wailing and gnashing of feet...
Sir, please give me just one more chance, sir.
I don't want to go to hell, sir.
Sir, no.
No.
Thank God I don't want to go to hell.
The man is as alive as he could be.
And the children say he could laugh and play just the same.
You and me.
The tail bearer will be at the judgment.
To be continued...
The man's virgin birth.
And a baby is born with a head that glows like a fluorescent lamp.
Dare I ask it?
Yes.
Was the infant Jesus neither man nor God,
but merely one of the countless aliens that visit the earth each and every day?
The answer?
Yes, definitely.
Take that and shove it up the tube marked certainty
in the fuzzy place called the Twilight Zone.
Merry Christmas to all!
Now you're all gonna die!
The night Santa went crazy.
The night Saint Nick went insane.
Realized he'd been getting the wrong heel.
Something finally must have snapped in his brain.
Well, the workshop is gone now.
He decided to bomb it.
Everywhere you'll find pieces of Cupid and Comet.
And he tied up his helpers.
And he held the elves hostage.
And he ground up...
And he put Rudolph into reindeer sausage.
He got Dancer and Prancer with an old German Luger.
And he slashed up Dasher just like Freddy Krueger.
And he picked up a flamethrower and a barbecue blitzer.
And he took a big bite and said it tastes just like chicken.
The night Santa went crazy.
The night Kris Kringle went nuts.
Now you can hardly walk around the North Pole.
Without stepping in reindeer guts.
There's the National Guard and the FBI.
There's a van from the eye with just news.
And helicopters circling round in the sky.
And the bullets are flying.
The body counts rising.
And everyone's dying to know who Santa was.
Santa was.
My, my, my, my, my, my, my.
You used to be such a jolly guy.
He knows when you're sleeping.
He knows when you're awake.
He knows when you've been found.
For good.
For the good.
For goodness sake.
You better watch out.
You better not cry.
You better not pout.
I'm telling you why.
Santa Claus is coming to town.
Have yourself an advanced Dogmatic Christmas song thing called Santa is Coming by F.B.
Gillespie and F.J. Coote.
ElectricElf at loop.com can tell you more about that.
But now.
Who gave the Lord the clap trap?
Who made him talk in funny riddles so that we cannot understand?
Who made him so succinct and blind that he is actually blind?
Yeah, we're now officially in the Jesus season.
The time of the Lord.
How many before you reach your limit?
Jesus.
Jesuses?
Yeah, how many can you bag?
How many messiahs can you bag?
Jesuses.
If you're doing it in season.
If you're doing it out of season, you need a special permit.
Oh, you never do.
And you can only take one.
Yeah, but I mean.
You never bag the Lord in C. You bag the Lord in B-flat so you get that kind of rough sound.
But when they're in season, it's every God for himself.
This is the season for the fighting Jesus.
Obviously.
We are between a rock and a hard place.
Did you know the Lord walked through Chaldea in the old age and he got a very good gift?
He got a very, very hard foot and he got elephantiasis of the rectum.
You know, it's not something well known by many Christian scholars.
Messy, messy, messy disease.
But I think the phrase in Hebrew was .
Well, I like the story.
I kind of like those stories where the Lord dies and then comes here to America and settles,
you know, tames the West.
I like when he moves into a trailer park and the cowboys walk with his dog.
Jesus fought for the Confederate army.
The ranger.
I like the Texas ranger.
Jesus.
Texas ranger.
Johnny Ripple was Jesus.
I could see Jesus for the Navajo police, for maybe the Hopi police force.
Billy Jack was the Indian Jesus.
Man.
He was the white brother who came to instruct the Indians how to be liberal.
Well, what about old peacemaker, the Jesus of the Iroquois who was actually Huron, a
Huron.
You didn't know that, did you?
I got you.
Jesus.
Elrond.
I got a Jesus and I can't think of no other Jesus.
Get in the club.
You got a Jesus?
And you know who it is?
I can't think of a better Jesus you've ever seen.
Oh, it tastes like butter.
A new Jesus.
A different Jesus.
It tastes like future Jesus.
A pat smoking Jesus.
Hey, Dave, you know where it is.
Go kick that window open.
I already kicked it.
I'll kick it again though.
Kick it good this time.
We don't mean nothing by this Jesus and God.
We hope that, we thank you for all the nice things that you've done for us this Thanksgiving.
We appreciate all that.
And we're just trying to insult your fan club.
That's all.
That's why we do this blasphemous stuff.
But we knew that you knew that because you're in all things and everything.
Right, Jesus?
Right.
I could hear him say that.
Praise God and Bob and Jesus.
Next topic.
Terrorist insurance.
Could you see Jesus as a terrorist?
And science.
That's the life of Brian, isn't it?
And Greek mythology and Norse mythology.
To the sounds of hell.
Jingle, jangle, jingle, we're on a sleigh ride to heck.
Santa and his reindeer are really wicked.
Wrapped in wrapping paper, we're gonna break our necks.
Got a rocket in my pocket on a sleigh ride to heck.
Sleigh.
Sleigh ride to heck.
The elves are full of cheer.
The kids are tucked in bed.
Santa ain't coming.
And we're on a sleigh ride to heck.
Their dreams are filled with toys.
But they're out of luck.
Cause Satan's taking Santa on a sleigh ride to fuck.
Sleigh ride to heck.
The greatest scary Christmas song ever, friends.
From his new album.
Don't trust Whitey.
James Kochalka.
Superstar.
You know, see, a subgenius has so much faith.
That he not only can accept somebody making fun of Bob.
Stomping on a picture of Bob.
He'll do it himself.
He has so much trust and faith in Bob.
Bob is such a good friend that he can insult Bob.
Now we subgeni.
I hate to get on my soapbox in the middle of a bunch of entertaining tapes.
But we subgeni may be bad.
But our way of bad is holy.
Is holy compared to the evil of so...
Not all, by any means.
But so many American fundamentalists, charismatics, evangelicals, etc.
In general, of course.
They and their corresponding types in Iran, Russia, Libya, South Africa, etc.
If you ask me, are actually the ace of the devil's sword.
I believe.
Wolves in sheep's clothing, friends.
Just like Jesus warned about.
I...
We're...
Jesus and Bob, like we say.
Our old drinking buddies.
Got nothing against Jesus.
It's just his fan club.
And now, we aren't saying that Bob is the ace up God's sleeve.
He's more like the smear on God's handkerchief.
Just like you or me.
But the uptight rival cults.
They don't think God has a handkerchief.
Uh-uh.
No.
Because God's perfect.
He doesn't even sneeze.
We're made to believe.
We're made in his image.
Except that we have all these nasty parts attached to us.
And we have to go in the secret room.
The bathroom.
To do awful things.
But God, oh, he's clean and pure.
According to them.
Oh, and he's male.
But he doesn't excrete juices and sweat and smelly stuff out of him like we do.
Because we sinned.
Oh, yeah.
We all sinned.
We're bad.
We're worthless.
We're no good to God unless we sign a contract with his agent.
First off...
I interrupt this program for a special promotional announcement.
Return.
K-Bob and the bastards of the universe will be back after this message.
And then...
I start to think...
You can get yourself some sleep
Over the ancient god's head
Just like the ones I used to know
I'm going to some small room
And it should be the same
To be a man that's in the snow
I'm going to some small room
I'm dreaming about the ancient god's head
When everyone can come back right
Name your days being
Shhh and short
And they all will be your gods and you are in this
By Fernanda Nande-Lemar
Oh, holy night
Who's singing in the night
The stars are brightly shining
It is the night of our dear saviour's birth
Long lay, long lay the world
In the air of fighting
The appeared and the stormed on its way
A thrill of hope
The weary world rejoices
The yonder grace
A new and glorious dawn
Fall on your knees
Oh, hear the angel voices
Oh, night divine
Oh, night when Christ was born
Oh, night, oh, night divine
Have yourselves a groovy little solstice
A groovy little solstice
Myth rose one year's fight
Oh, ho, ho
He, he, he
Come on, come on
It's t-bomb
Hey kids, you can help the mighty
Subtinus Wright's overthrow of the evil normals
with new Bob Dobbs action figure with rockin' pies
What I wouldn't do from Bob Dobbs
It's gonna get no more chocolatey pebbles from you, no ?
I'm a chocolate spice cadet
Life support system down to zero cocoa
Feeling free to have some of my new cocoa pimples.
Now so trumpety.
Mmm, smells coconut.
This cocoa liquid is...
Blue.
Well, friends, what do you think?
Is it the nativity of Santa Claus that we're trying to celebrate here?
Or is it the horrible death of the Santa Bob?
The Santa Bob, as he's been referred to in some early prescriptures.
The Jethro's, friends.
You need to know where to write to the Jethro's.
They're at...
They did that Wreck the Halls and so many other versions we've been playing.
The Jethro's are at 212 and a half Miller Avenue.
That's 212 and a half Miller Avenue.
Portsmouth, New Hampshire.
Portsmouth, N-H-O-3-8-O-1.
Santa Claus is Coming to Town was by Corporal Blossom.
Information on that mutant Christmas is available from www.triagemusic.com
or www.detritus.net slash...
Illegal Art.
I'm Reverend Ivan Stang, friends.
You can reach me, send me tapes or whatnot at Post Office Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
And friends, as always, the Hour of Slack is brought to you by the Church of the Subgenius.
www.subgenius.com
It's all Christmassy right now.
There's a bright green bob.
There's a light out there.
Is there a light out there?
Is there a DJA?
Is DJA out there?
And devilish artwork that's Christmassy.
No, that's something just left for DJA.
It's all Christmassy.
It's all wrapped up in a perfumed ribbon-wrapped present under the tree.
Smell that cinnamon.
Open the door all the way so we can see if he comes in.
And those sugar plums.
Something's up the chimney hole in Satan's, isn't it?
Yeah.
Or Santa, I mean.
Otherwise, gosh.
I guess we have to wait till Santa comes, Dave.
Oh, beloved Santa.
I have wanted to put your bag down for a minute.
Besides, I'm so ready to let him be.
What?
For so long.
Praise Bob and Mary Xmas!
¶¶
Lone cow babe, don't you know what they're doing to yourself?
Don't despair, just because it's Christmas
Children there are so gay at Christmas
All the children on the street
Hope they get something good to eat
But for me it's not so great
Fuck Christmas!
What a night!
Before Christmas and all through the house
Not a creature was stirring, not even a mouse
The stockings were hung by the tree
Merry fucking Christmas
To you!
Thank you.