The Self-Genius Hour of Swag.
Look, look, there's Susie and there's a big old microphone.
Yes, I just moved over so you can take a look.
Did you see her third eye glasses?
Alright.
That is really an amazing scientific device that she has.
They're Tuatara-like.
It has, it's glasses that have no glass over the eyes but a swiveling glass.
Oh, who needs glasses over the eyes?
Oh, I'm just going to sit here and sweat.
Does it pick up sound?
Sounds like a plan.
There's a, there's a, here, why don't we try, that's what we'll do.
Now there's Hanky Panky going with the microphones here.
Yeah.
It's like, I'm getting excited.
Microphones hidden in every chair.
I know I have to shove this out of her face.
Well, do what you must do.
She's so polite.
We have this bump here.
She doesn't like to lip it like some of us do.
No, we don't have spit guards like we have back at Radio Valencia.
No, sir.
Which we need to keep.
Michael Peppy from thoroughly wetting the instrument.
Well, Suzy can wet the instrument if she needs to.
Most of this stuff is pretty cheap, and made to work outdoors.
We have a foamy protective layer surrounding Mr. Microphone.
It's Mr. Microphone.
Hi, girls.
Really, very thr醫jän pal our show.
I'm extremely suspicious.
Okay, everyone, put the book on the table.
Okay, now it's real radio.
Look, there went the audience.
The morning zoo.
We're wacky.
We're crazy.
We're out of control.
We're certifiably insane.
91.1.
The crazy zoo.
Top farty radio.
That's right.
And Bob Dobbs is a-coming.
Nothing can stop it now.
The sluice gates have been opened.
Sluice gates.
That sounds good.
The goo-nami.
That's true.
I ain't cleaning up after that.
No, fortunately, we won't have to.
Let others sniff and then clean up our mess.
Because they weren't paying attention,
and now they had their fun.
As it says in the Bible, they had their reward.
And now they must go to their next reward.
Isn't that right, Stan?
Wouldn't you say so?
Oh, Suzy is fanning herself
with a seatbelt.
She's got a big CD jewel case.
Who ordered the steaming tart?
One of her biggest fans.
Vibration.
Yes, I...
I wish you'd been next to me on that
jolting airplane flight I was on.
I had to get on a plane.
It was like that shot in an airplane.
The plane, as we were coming into Chicago,
the very rough weather,
and the plane started to actually vibrate.
Thank you.
People are coming in.
People are getting scared,
but I want you to know, Suzy,
that I remembered that there was a lady
sitting next to me with a low-cut blouse,
and that I knew the top of her chest
would be doing this waveform ripple.
And I'm not the kind of person
who's just going to do that
unless I'm next to Suzy.
But that's why I wish that you'd been there.
Because the best I could do is very...
get one or two glimpses,
and yep, sure enough, just as I thought.
One horrible vibratorians. Oh, it was a beautiful pattern.
It happened to me.
I can remember what my boobs did,
because I'm watching them, too.
It's like, whoa, fucking broncos!
I wish I had boobs
that I could see like that.
Oh, wait, I kind of...
I kind of do, a little bit.
They're much smaller
since I lost my...
I think the moves are catching.
Do you wish to use these headphones
to hear the exciting Basil Polidorus soundtrack?
Well, then, my dear,
you must wear them.
Yeah, you don't understand.
You're not really here if you're not really hearing.
You know what I mean?
But I have the same problem on my radio show.
I just can't get some people to put them on.
Well, you can't hear
the Conan theme.
I already pointed that out.
But then, perhaps,
it is for the best.
That is pretty manly music.
Well, now we do have
politicians like that, so...
Hmm.
Reeves, Freebooters, Reavers...
Have you seen his already doing ads for 2020 campaign?
Have you seen that?
No, I haven't.
But, of course, what he does best is campaign.
They think there's gonna be a 2020.
Isn't that cute?
Morons.
It's possible he could go on
amid the ruins, equally deluded
that all was
as it should be.
Of course,
Reverend Susie Dufluzzi will be saved
from having to go to
Trump stop by being
red-headed. She's part of the
orange people.
Colored people, as they've been
dubbed lately. I think by
Obama. Didn't
Obama actually say something
about Trump being a colored person?
That was John Boehner. He said he was a person
of color. Oh, okay.
And therefore could sympathize with him.
I don't want to have to reject my orange hair.
I was blonde.
This past year I've been blonde.
And it was ugly
and frightening. Well, I knew that in
theory. You've explained that to me.
And I mean, my rational mind
knew that you had this normal
actual hair. My bangs were the same
tone as my face. And I couldn't
tell where anything was. And since I have no
eyebrows now, because of my
thyroid medication made my eyebrows
fall out, I can't
tell what I'm thinking.
I mean...
They're painted on eyebrows.
I didn't even notice.
Well, they're painted beautifully and they're so orange.
Thank you, they are. You look great.
That's right. You look wonderful.
Don't blow smoke up my ass, dang.
Mmm. Oh, but
it's so tight.
Oh!
I have the other end up mine.
Oh, I wish you could see this, folks.
I think I'm turning into a hidebound old conservative.
Well, that's...
Well, we're not
getting any younger.
Uh-huh. That's true.
Oh, yeah, I've gotten
to where I kind of
don't like to hear bawdy language
in mixed company.
No shit?
You see what I mean?
These... these Connyites...
Save it. You're not even a Connyite,
I know. You know, those film ladies
are... they're not gonna know what to make
of you, because, you know, they're kind of
new, and they...
I'm un-categorisable.
That's my main flaw. Well, it's a pity that the
actual insurrectionists aren't
coming. But I can't be pigeonholed.
Right.
Right. Well, we're
not gonna pigeonhole you. I can't
speak for the other-holing.
Although, we could
buy a cornhole set. They sell
them around here. The Amish
make them.
We could all corn... we could cornhole all...
It's okay to say that now.
You see, that kind of thing's in headlines now.
America's cornhole. Now that it's okay
to use all that foul language
in plain newspaper
headlines, I don't want to say
it anymore. Do you remember the
TV season where suddenly... I'm a reactionary.
...it was okay to say the word
sucks? Yeah, because nobody
knew what it meant. Yeah, that was
groundbreaking. Next came
ass. They sneaked
in ass. I was noticing.
I was noticing these things. Well, and
then... And they made it acceptable.
They took the filth
away from our filthy words.
I know, that's why I'm... It's in TV commercials.
I'm reacting by refusing
to be filthy, except in
a conceptual way, henceforth.
Aside from the obvious
one's... Bob's one law, fuck
them if they can't take a joke. Obviously,
we... That's... That's a
descriptive use of the word.
It's not in any way...
Well, actually, I guess it is
sort of arousing
in a way.
I suppose it could be considered
what's that word? Sexy.
So, yeah,
yeah, I'm against all that dirty
talking stuff. Well, you see these filmmakers
want to speak to... Now that everybody else
is doing it. They want to
talk to the rebels, but the rebels
are rebelling by not coming here,
so they can't
talk to them. I'll have to talk to the
old guard, who can explain
the nature of their
doctrinal errancy. There's
not so much cussin' as...
Discussin'.
Yes. Discussin'.
Discussin'. That's
exactly it.
All of this politically correct crap
is just...
It's up my tailpipe seriously.
Um...
Politically correct crap like
the... Like...
Evolution is just a theory?
That's politically correct. I'm being offensive
when I have no idea what I'm offending. Nowadays.
And it's making me downright
unprofessional about offending, because
it's just... It is... The
triggering is... It's all over.
Hmm. Well, I...
And when people actually are offended, I really can't
tell how offended they are, because of the
background level of offense.
Right, exactly. It's like when they're trying to
track, uh, some sort of
intestinal complaint, the background
level of diarrhea was just too great
for them to tell. We've got a background
level of diarrhea that is just far
too fuckin' high. Well, I hear
a lot of the phrase,
I couldn't tell if she was kidding or not. Is she
really that mad? You know.
It's... It's... And that
too is a sin, by not taking
the complaint seriously
enough. How dare
the cafeteria serve Vietnamese
food? They're culturally
appropriating, uh,
blah, blah, blah, you know. You
never know what's going to be the specific
thing, but... But,
the whole idea is all
actions, transactions are viewed
with suspicion. Guilty
until proven innocent. And
what does that remind anyone
of? Lock me up. I'm guilty, Joe.
Guilty until proven innocent.
Isn't that the way French people
do things? And isn't
this whole infestation
of our academic and intellectual
discourse something having to do
with French deconstructionist,
French, uh,
philosophy which says every
text is specially
motivated and you have to
deconstruct it and find
out what they really mean,
which is some unpleasant
thing for everyone else and
something which, only for them.
You see, since they can't win on
the battlefield, as in the battle of
Crecy, they try to
take us apart from, from,
uh, inside.
You're, you're fomenting a war
on Quebec, aren't you? These
Frenchified frogs are the ones
who are really behind everything,
uh, but now they have
done their part and they can
sit aside and shrug
their shoulders in gallic
incomprehension. There was a
great commercial for FedEx,
I don't know if you saw it, with, uh...
I thought we needed more Frenching.
In France, there's a,
uh, you know, they're trying to deliver somebody's
package and the guy instead is sitting
in a cafe and saying, I am bored.
This job is
pointless. And meanwhile in the background
they're going round and round the traffic
calling round about running over the packages
which he's, he's just thrown
there. Um,
and frankly that's about
the way it is.
I'm a Franco-American. It's like
French-American, but it's like
Italian food, but it's not even Italian food.
Well that was, uh, Rocknar's plan
was to sell Chef Boyardee
spaghetti to Europeans
since they... Oh, what the hell?
I grew up thinking
Franco was an Italian.
Well, he's a Spaniard.
The whole thing is all mixed up and crazy.
It's a bunch of crazy stuff. It's a Mediterranean
culture from the fragmenting
Roman Empire, still not
thoroughly fragmented. And how do you tell
the conspiracy from just freaking
sloppiness? Because they're trying
to put you in the Black Iron prison
all the time and they never stop. One way
or the other. And when you can discern
that, uh, their
aim, well there's the whiff of
the conspiracy that you need
to step clear of their
muck and mess and
twaddle and foof-a-raw and terradiddle.
They ain't gonna get me.
That's right. They already
got me. They got me, uh,
all the way. Agile, elfin. And then I
escaped. Spry sprang.
I've escaped. Stang, sprang,
sprang out of the way.
I know, I know. I wish I could
take everyone with me.
I've escaped. I've barely escaped
with my life. You know, you can't help
others before you help yourself.
I've been escaped. I've got a really bad sense of direction.
I was told that in Hollywood.
You were told what?
Uh, well,
uh, before
every show, there's a position
called the warm-up
guy. Oh, right.
It's a very low position. I've told you about this.
They come out and they keep the
bust-in audience
comfortable by telling them stupid jokes
and so on. They will never
advance, although they desperately
long to advance their career. So I asked
the producer of our show,
what about, uh, this
I'm talking about one person who was
doing it, uh, could we help her?
And he said, well, you know, you can't help the others
before you help yourself, you know.
We've got to get ourselves going. And then we'll be able to
pull all these other people along with us.
How's that for the reasoning
that you get in the magic
world of Hollywood?
You have to help yourself.
Otherwise, you're not going to be able to help
others. Well, that's true. Help yourself first.
I can't argue with that.
But it's the excuse
for never helping anyone but yourself.
That could be an
excuse. Why not both, you know?
It makes sense,
you know, I think he honestly believes
in the rightness of
what he was saying. Well, since he was a big Hollywood
star, wasn't it in time
for him to give somebody else a break?
Well,
we were starting a new show,
wanted to make sure, you know,
nothing went wrong.
Hey, speaking
of a break,
I've become a publisher
again. And we're publishing
as our first book, Lonesome Cowboy
Dave's novel, Neighbor World.
That's right. We're going to follow that. The church was saying, you know, we're going to follow that.
Genius is a publisher now.
We're going to follow that with
Nicholas Kingsley's
Eyelash,
and then a
book about Bob,
or a collection of novellas about Bob
called The Ancient and Mr. Dobbs
by the great Teeters LaVerge.
Those are easy because
they're just text.
By then, I feel like I'll be
ready to reprint
our out-of-print books
like Three-Fisted Tales of Bob, which
I do have rights to.
Or Bob's Favorite Comics?
Bob's Favorite Comics, if I can get the rights
to it. Technically, that's
still owned by Ripoff Press.
But I'm sure they'd probably let us
have it for a dollar.
Sure they would. They never had that much faith
in the project to begin with.
But what you ought
to do if there are certain people
who will not relinquish the rights
is commission new
strips to be laid in
for this special edition.
Well, yeah, that's the thing.
Three-Fisted Tales of Bob will be
different from the conspiracy version.
It'll have Nancy Collins' story in it,
for one thing.
I'm going to reprint all the
Stark Fist stuff.
The ancient Stark Fist magazines,
those have already been scanned
and are ready to
be assembled. Do you still have the huge
piles of yellow Stark Fists
from your basement?
No, I have small piles of yellow
Stark Fists. But remember the...
The Stark Fists.
Movie makers wanted special collectible
subgenius swag to give away to contributors.
And what could be better than
some archaic issue of
the Stark Fist, which otherwise
is too historically interesting to
destroy, but you can't...
You know, you've got a lot of storage problems,
so why not give them each
an ancient fist?
As part of the
swag bag, is my
thought. Well, eventually that
might happen. I could...
You've got to look after yourself first, Dr. Halle.
I could sell them on eBay for 50 bucks a piece.
Oh yeah? Well, if that interest is
there, I quite understand your
recalcitrance to give it away to
hedge fund managers and other
worthy... Those things are becoming
quite rare. There are
not that many of them left. Well, I thought you
had giant, yellowed
piles. Philo does. He stole
them from me. I paid for all that
stuff. Lost my ass,
too. That's why we couldn't... Publishing...
But now, you don't have to actually
print anything. You just
sell it, and when somebody
buys it, then this company far away
prints it. And they keep
more than half of the money, depending
on how much you mark it up. Well, who proofreads
this? I spent last
month proofreading Dave's
book. Did you find a number
of typos? No.
I found a whole lot of
paragraph problems and spacing
problems, little...
But Dave had been over at
the library a million times.
There were no stylistic changes.
Good for him. It seems like he really threw himself
into that job. It's great.
The book is really... I'm anxious to read
the book. I've got ten copies
of them here. Well, I may not be able
to read this iteration, but I will read...
They're proof copies, because it technically
hasn't really been published yet. I was able to get
proof copies for cheap, like three bucks
each, but you can only get five per
proof. So I kept making
minute changes and getting new
proofs, but they're slowly
getting out, so I only have ten,
and I guess we might auction them.
I've got to save a few for
people who reserved them
in advance. But we'll have
plenty of them soon enough. Great.
And, yeah, I'm
real excited about reprinting
our old stuff, and there's mountains
of stuff that's never been seen
except by me.
That happened between the last of the print
publishing and the beginning of the internet,
and nothing after the internet
ever got published to speak of,
except that
the final, last book,
the Bobliographon.
That was almost all internet material.
But we've got tons
of wonderful collages
that no one's ever seen,
artwork by great
cartoonists, such as
Hal Robbins, Paul Mavridi,
Yes,
many... Even Philo Drummond.
He's
become a painter in his
latter years, like George W. Bush.
Yeah.
Yeah, he's been taking
lessons from Reverend
K. R. K. Ryden.
A great guy and a subgenius.
An unapologetic subgenius.
We'll be seeing him at the
devotional. That's great.
On my saucer.
What date,
earth date, did that take place on?
July 28th, unfortunately.
It's in Cleveland, on my
saucer. Me be gone
on other pleasure trips.
The devotionals
are really fun. They're kind of similar to
X-Day because, well,
half the crowd is crossover,
really.
And, um,
you never saw so many people with glasses
on in one room.
Wow, a glittering, flashing... It's a regular
sausage party, too. It's at least as bad as
subgenius, maybe worse.
Is that why we never get off this planet?
You always have plans for August
and September.
I said on my saucer. I've been
advertising Starwood
to be on my saucer for a long time.
We keep up Earth dates on the
saucers. They're big, you see. I'm starting to put
doo-doo and doo-doo together. They're big.
Oh, boy, it's about time, see.
How long has it been? You joined the church
in 1981 or something like that?
Yeah, back when the Earth was cooling.
Yes, that was, uh...
Well, soon we'll be restoring the Earth
to its original state.
Pure magma and
poisonous gas. Like the bubbling
cherry pie. Back to nature.
Before the Indians.
You know, before the animals. Before
multicellular creatures.
...better than they do.
Eye farts? Or is that like... Pie farts.
Oh, pie. Pie farts.
Oh, God. They're
pathetic. I thought eye farts were
like the iPhone or something.
...and then peel them. Uh-uh.
Especially in an enclosed Buick.
No, it's just a... A Buick.
...a digress. A digress.
You know what? I can actually hear what everybody's
saying. I haven't...
I mean, except for that one that you
just said, because I was talking at the same time.
But when I'm not talking, I can understand
things now. I've been...
I've been reading lips and guessing
for about 15 years.
I had no idea what anybody's really
saying. So,
you know, if I sometimes seem to be talking about
a completely different subject than anybody
else, that's... That was why.
I guess I could still do that.
I stopped being able to hear, and I
countered it with just not caring
anymore. Well, that's what I did for
15 years. That takes a lot of the sting out, but if it's
something important, like, hey, that's on fire.
Yeah, I miss it.
Well, I've been... I've been able to understand
lyrics that I couldn't understand
when I was 21. And now
does that sadden you, that you're
understanding... I've been deaf my whole life.
Sometimes you make up better lyrics... It's just got a lot worse.
...than the ones that are actually there.
Well, this
$2,000 per ear
little gizmo has
made a big
difference. Thank God I
had the $2,000 per ear
that year. You have to remember
to switch it on.
To what? To turn
on the switch. Oh, yeah.
To switch it on.
Pull the switch! Pull the switch!
Pull the switch!
Otherwise, they are
sitting inertly there,
not doing their job.
Sometimes
I forget to put them in when I
get out of bed in the morning.
Everything seems so comfortable
and nice. So quiet.
So quiet, and it's like a blanket of
soothing nothingness.
No annoying rattling...
I look at Princess Wee, and she's going like this.
Everything's velvet
till I put on my glasses.
Well, at least I don't have to put the
stent in and out of my heart every morning.
But I do have to remember to take my pills,
that's for sure. My heart will reject
the little metal thing.
You are not!
So I do remember those pills.
That's your nut!
You're having nut attacks.
Nut attacks?
Not again!
You can't have a heart and work for Dobbs.
That...
Well...
He got mine!
That's why I've been feeling so slackful
and happy lately.
I don't have a heart anymore.
No wonder I've been feeling so...
generally carefree.
Like I don't give a shit.
Like who cares if almost everybody else
is miserable and starving?
Wow!
Thanks Bob for taking my heart away!
I think I...
Wow!
Now I see why Philo and them voted
for that guy.
Huh.
That explains a lot.
Hmm.
I'm gonna become a Republican!
That only makes sense!
Fuck everybody else!
A r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-r-e-publican.
Well, I don't.
Actually, actually you can't...
No.
There are many subgenius Republicans,
they are a minority,
I think.
They're certainly a minority on the internet.
I notice that when they put up posts,
those are also swiftly taken down
before I can get there.
Well, there's no law against being a right-wing fanatic and a subgenius at the same time, not under my law.
No, but there are subgenius administrators who don't want the sites used for GOP propaganda.
Right, no, well...
And so by the time I get there, as I say, this post has been...
Well, we also don't use it for Democrat propaganda.
We do use it as propaganda for slack, for sure.
But the main purpose of most of those news groups is actually to lift the spirits and give people a little chuckle in this grim, grim world.
That's right.
And occasionally they use GoFundMe things to save each other's asses.
Every time somebody's car goes down, if they are not too proud to beg, within a day and a half,
they usually manage to raise the repair money from their...
their old buddy subgeniuses, most of whom can't send more than ten bucks each, but, you know, a hundred...
Well, ten people, ten bucks, that's a...
Shame the Christians with your generosity and empathy.
Yeah, well, yes, and that's why we encourage people not to litter here,
because we want to make the pagans look like litter bugs compared to us.
That's important.
It's an ego thing, you know, it's just one of those us and them.
It's not necessarily good behavior on our part.
Passing out cigars?
I am married to the person who runs the big pagan festival,
and some of my best friends are, quote, pagans, unquote.
How do you peg? Is it like how you vike?
How do I what?
How do you peg if you're pagan?
Would either of you like some Turkish delight?
Oh, you don't shave your armpits, that's basically what it's about.
Turkish delight, would you like some?
My dead mother used to feed this to me.
I mean, before she...
She was dead.
I would hope so.
A few times afterward, but it was even better.
Man, them Turks sure know their onions.
It's made with roses.
Hey, would your mom like my dad?
They're both in heaven now, or whatever.
No, I don't know if my mom had a heaven.
She was sensible.
Oh, my goodness.
They were sensible parents.
I remember my father driving these two Jehovah's Witnesses,
just off their nuts.
They wanted to get out of that place so bad.
And he was relaxed against the frame of the door,
like, oh, I've always thought the Bible's nothing but history
and flawed history at that.
Whoa.
Oh, God.
That's pretty bald-faced.
Yeah.
I'm waiting to be able to...
My line is going to be, but isn't the Bible a book?
Well, I can make a book.
In fact, I did.
And some people actually believed it, too.
I certainly do.
I believe my own bullshit.
But I believe Bob's bullshit much better.
That's not my bullshit.
That really is Bob's bullshit.
Who says the Bible is the inerrant word of God?
Well, right.
That's the whole point of it.
But it's just a...
I mean, it is a book.
I know where books come from.
Supposedly.
They don't grow on trees.
They don't just appear.
70 and 2, or maybe just 70 scholars.
So much.
Composed independently.
They don't have those.
Miraculously in agreement.
Demonstrating that it was the word of God.
I know where milk comes from.
It comes from cows.
Those rectangular things at the store.
Those boxed...
I thought they came from the kids printed on the side.
Oh, that's silly.
That's crazy stuff.
Now I'm disappointed.
I thought they had a personal touch.
That's where the missing orphans pictures go.
I was in a supermarket once.
Princess.
We and I were.
And this mom and daughter approached us.
Mother and daughter combo.
The butcher in the deli laughed at us.
He wouldn't tell us.
But what's the difference between lamb and calf?
Or veal?
One's a baby cow and one's a baby sheep.
What's a sheep?
They weren't kidding.
These were Americans.
I was thinking, what did they not get Sesame Street?
I go, well, the cows are the big ones with horns.
They've never been outside the plastic vacuole.
The sheep are the smaller white ones.
Huh?
A biblical term.
I couldn't figure out.
Sheep go bop.
Cows don't move.
It kind of shocked me.
They didn't understand the difference between cow and sheep.
Tell them to do a word search on cow and sheep.
Tell them to Google sheep and cow.
I don't press images.
You could have taken them out for lunch.
Where's the cow?
Andreas.
I'll have to hear that when I play it back.
Did you desire further acquaintance with them?
Well, I did.
Actually, try to teach them as much barnyard basics as I could.
You raised your right leg.
That's it.
Very good.
Now put your right leg down.
And raise your left leg.
No.
Your left leg.
Very good.
Yeah.
It was a little, a little shocking.
No?
See.
Not even Sesame Street, I take it.
No, that's some production about liberals
with frisking people of color in it
that all good rednecks abominate.
Really, they don't like Sesame Street.
Some of them don't.
I mean, there's great variation,
but they don't like the urban aspect
of Sesame Street, as they say.
Hold on just a second.
I need to...
I have to go get spurred.
Peace to you, hippie brother.
All right, now calm yourself.
Dang, everything's going to be all right.
And Reverend Susie,
would you like another piece of Turkish delight?
Oh, I would love another piece of Turkish delight.
They say this particular type of Turkish delight
makes you want to continue to eat it
and to eat nothing but it.
But I'm sure a few more pieces wouldn't be harmful.
They're odd gelatinous cubes.
Yes, they are like the excreta of the wombat.
Yeah.
Many people don't know that the wombat...
But they taste so much different from that.
Oh, definitely, of course.
It was wrong of me to make the comparison,
but the wombat...
Of course, the wombat cubes are not...
Wombat feces come out in the form of cubes.
The only creature on Earth that...
God does not play dice with the universe
except in the case of the wombat.
Yeah.
You can easily find pictures of these amusing fumits
on the Internet if you just look up wombat.
But also, there's a lot of pictures of girls
cuddling with wombats.
And what's that all about?
They apparently mold the feces.
Have you ever looked up?
They have many sites of girls cuddling with wombats.
You know, I never suspected to see that.
And when you see their skeleton,
you wouldn't want to cuddle with them
because of the enormous incisor teeth, you know,
six or seven times larger, longer,
and sharper than a rat's teeth.
But they're very cute and cuddly.
You're limited to nutrias,
maybe the occasional capybara wombat's like.
There's that creature called the paca,
which I think is New World.
Oh.
And it's raised as a pet until they eat it.
I thought the dick dick had an unfortunate name.
What?
What's the matter, Stang?
I didn't do it.
I know what you're talking about,
and I swear it won't happen again.
Do you remember last...
Where is this?
You may remember last year.
No.
When we were sitting here, Dr. Howell,
I tried to play a message
that somebody had left on my phone
at three in the morning.
Yes.
And it was this guy telling me,
hey, he was going to get me
because I'd wrecked his ex day
because I'd banned him from Facebook.
And he was just, you know,
this is how you make things better.
He's up at the gate now trying to get in.
His name was the first one on the banned list
because he doesn't work and play well with others.
And I had to give him his real name
and say, nope, nope,
now he's up there going,
well, I don't know why they don't want me.
Oh, yeah.
I told Ferg to tell him,
Stang still got your phone call
from last year on his phone.
Didn't he drive here from a long...
I'm sure he drove here from Cleveland, Texas
because he's stupid
because he's a mentally ill guy
and he's got this...
He thinks he's going to win this battle
against the world
because something was unfair
because he did something
that made somebody else mad.
I will.
Yeah, like threaten me
and then claim he's going to come to my party?
No.
That just isn't the way it works.
And he's just got to be damn glad
that he didn't join Heaven's Gate
or the People's Temple first
because he wouldn't have gotten this far in that case.
That asshole.
Jesus fucking Christ.
Fundamentalist subgeniuses.
Oh, God forbid.
You don't think he might attempt to sneak onto the ground?
Of course he will.
And perform mischief and malice.
Dr. Legame is here.
Why you look as skinny as me?
Are you talking about that LeapHouse car from the year?
Yeah, yes.
He's up at the gate.
I just ran into him.
He's fucking crazy as shit.
Yeah, no, he needs to be gone.
He has been banned.
You picked up on that too, did you?
I picked up on that when I blocked him on Facebook.
Right, yeah.
He's crazy as a shit.
Right, his name was the first one on the banned list.
That doesn't mean he gets to be in the subgenius ban.
Ferg just came and called me and I said,
no, no, no, no, no.
Well, this is becoming this whole part of the show.
We'll have to be snipped out, excised.
We can't have this be banned.
Part of the recording of the happy hour of slack.
Telling the people the joy of the church and the subgenius.
In fact, this is an unfortunate extrusion of sad political discharge of church policy.
And we regret its necessity.
But soon we'll be talking about comic books and monsters and other things
that will be more transferable.
To other formats, other venues, other locations.
Create a thrilling, inductive resonance of hope.
Well, you know, we're trying to make it seem better.
Have you tried that before?
Black keys work too.
And you can change the mode here by pushing that.
It produces belches.
As soon as I found out Facebook had nothing,
nothing to do with Bob.
That's the only face I give two shits about.
Well, remember, a certain apostate subgenius said,
face it, Facebook is the church.
And we had to say, well, you know, that's not really the truth.
It's an open picture window for the world to throw its garbage through.
You can put up posts, but then people like Mr. Fropchopula
will come and kind of crap all over the place.
And then and in the end we are theב
And this means, most of attempts to remove SpongeBob
without actually humility are volume aren't honest.
And so thank you for taking that up.
To say, that's not quéf.
corners, we can say that builders appreciate the fact
that technology worry about eight, or we have a fourthMusic is
a problem for even these libraries.
But we're all started to get there because.
We did.
have it on wretch yep I was doing Mozart
the buddy rich tapes and rich they are he's on he's on the bus he's berating his band this is
like in the 70s I guess 70s 80s where they were going around playing
dinner theater supper clubs and things and all the way on the band he would just mercilessly
lace into them it was like and you're up there and and you're blowing clams
fucking clams that was what I called bad notes and he would single them out and just
belittle them oh god he was a bastard to work with so they're so they're blowing clams they
they recorded him they're not such a blowing clams there Johnny yes
I'm also
barking spiders lizards mm-hmm you blew a lizard it's like hey if I could figure
out how to do I probably would I'm very fond of them you have a current lizard
in residence now I have three lizards right now I have a good for you I have
two Sudan plaintiff so Jack and girly girl and uh there are they look like
alligators with a nose job they're really really really smart really
very very mellow smart lizards they ride around on shoulders well and uh they're
really really cool I can't say enough about the Sudan platens and I wound up
with an adopted a knoll little girl who was leaving home from behind me had a
four annuls that she'd caught in it was winter and technically they're illegal
to keep in Georgia
I figured for the duration of the winter I'd keep them
and one died
another one
she'd name them like Jeff and Cliff
and Cliff was old
Cliff was missing a hind foot
and it didn't regenerate
he had big jowls
he was definitely an old bull
Jeff on the other hand
Jeff was entering his prime
full of piss and vinegar
Jeff was an asshole
and I love lizards
I never knew a lizard
could be such a fucking asshole
there's like this other little one
in there that I didn't have a name
I called it Squiggle because of this thing on its back
and it's like I'm keeping Jeff and Squiggle
just for the winter
until it's warm enough to let him out
and Cliff he's got three hots
and a cock for life
because he's missing a foot and he's old
he doesn't want to have to fuck that stuff
but Jeff was
making everybody's life
miserable
he was
he was just a little bit of a mess
he was just so macho
he'd be like bobbing his head
banging it on things
knocking stuff over
and that's when they're feeling their oats
it was like
it was basically clubbing them over
the head with his two dicks
and you know reptiles have
two dicks
they had to come up with a word
a plural for
hemipenes
they call them
yeah
one is a hemipenis
I had a
I had a lizard who was so tough
his hemipenis
prolapsed
and he roasted it off
on the hot rock
I don't know how long
because I wasn't turning him over
looking at his butt
because you can't see anything
it's like a vent
it's like
mmm
like no blowjob here
and you can't tell
everything is like inside
but when they take a dump
it's like these two things
will stick out
like
and it's like
what the shit
look like
look like a
chewed red licorice or something
I'm like what the hell
also in the dinosauria
the cloaca
in the female
contains all this apparatus
and in the male
this aperture contains
the hemipenes
and
they have two willies
and they don't use them both
at the same time
well then they're defected
they're packing a spare
so Randy
my first lizard
Randy
how appropriate
Randy roasted off
one of his dicks
because he could really give two craps
he had another one
and he was like
oh I'm not fucking
and it's still careless
and it was in the days
before computers
it was like about
can't blame that one
on computers
no
and then
when I took him to the vet
I thought it was like
doo doo
that wouldn't come out of his vent
and I was trying to pull it
and it was like
on like a gristly bit
and he was like
ah ah
and I'm like
what the fuck is that Randy
and I took
yeah
I try to do a friend a favor
I've lubed up lizard vents
I'm proud of it
have you ever subscribed to
Reptiles magazine
they discuss these matters
the gay male assistant
of my vet
had to write down
in the records
you know
by hand
the update on Randy
and when I brought him in
it was like
you know
Randy
ahh
Randy Barrows
that's his last name
and it said
he was supposed to write down
remove
penis
and when he got
to the penis
after the removed
he seized up
and it looked like
a Richter scale
he had to go over
the penis
because it was
you know
putting
putting penis next to remove
was just
ah
it gave him a conniption
maybe he's in the wrong profession
but that's
how tough lizards are, they will laugh that off.
Yes, lizards laugh at pain.
And prolapse. Why isn't anybody anti-lapse?
That would mean
it was stuck inside the ecological
atmosphere. It's hardly ever a fun thing. I mean, after a point.
If you just let it alone, ultimately it
fixes itself, or it doesn't.
So, in the dinosauria also, you see
these structures. If I were a superhero,
I'd like to have the power of a sea cucumber. Oh, yeah?
Yeah, to just shit my guts out all over.
And while everyone's trying to figure out, what the fuck?
No, stop. We'll do it. You say. I don't know if I can make my getaway
though, with my guts all over.
I haven't thought it out that far.
Has anyone ever found a petrified dinosaur penis?
I don't believe they have that. I don't know.
They do have all the feces.
I bet they had two. Chances are they've got that.
Yeah, that would be the thing.
But also, the female has evolved
in some species.
An ovipositor, which is large and bulky,
and makes it immediately easier to see the female
sauropod and recognize it from the male.
For that reason, they carry their tails lower.
And the male's, it's almost prong-like back there.
Hmm. I just thought about biting your neck and mounting you.
You need to stop.
Well,
I don't know what you're talking about.
I think the larger of the dinosauria had to adopt a similar stratagem.
I guess horny toads have got two penile.
That would be right, wouldn't it?
Yeah.
They're extra horny toads.
They are not toads, of course.
How about the stang's immortal newt that they've had for 30 years, and often they've thought,
thought it was dead, but it's still going.
Wow.
You know.
A 30-year-old newt?
It just endures forever and ever
in its little tank.
What is the general lifespan
of an American newt?
Well, they generally don't get a chance
to live so long. In the wild,
something always gobbles you up,
but if you get the chance...
30 minutes.
Well, I don't know. This newt, you know
what I mean. It's lasted. It's still
ongoing because I heard them
arguing about feeding him.
Like the last sea monkey, right?
It has its
own way of being kept
that is
making it thrive.
It's violating
amphibian physics.
Did you see Stang's
little video that he made
of it some time ago?
He synchronized some of the
beast from 20,000 Fathoms
score to his video.
Did you see that one?
It was quite well done.
As he fed the newt.
Where can we find that? Will that be on the subgenius.com?
It might be. Fortunately,
we've got Ivan Stang right here
and after he returns from his
unfortunate duties...
Okay, they might be killing a guy.
Something. We don't have to
be concerned.
Barbecue in three hours.
But really,
on the other hand, just out of...
...
Was there a noise? Was there a sound?
Yeah.
Oh my God. Hornets.
Oh yes, they hover around.
Just hold your breath and your foreslam shut.
Oh yeah?
Somebody told me that and I believed it.
I heard if you ate bananas...
I never get stunk.
Hold your breath and your foreslam shut.
I can't stick their stingers in.
No, that's bullshit.
Too bad.
I got to do that when I was like
12.
I was like 12.
And I believed it.
It made sense to me.
And I never got stung.
Except for one time when I wasn't ready.
I was rage sweeping.
Oh, and you weren't prepared to hold your breath.
Something that was in the silk flowers that I was in.
I was on the phone with my brother.
I was having a horrible birthday.
Flowers.
He got that kind of phone call that he would have paid money
to hear his sister squawking.
It's like, oh my God.
This thing stings hard.
Well, I...
I did say that last time when I was here,
one blundered into my face and stung me,
kind of as an afterthought.
And I wasn't doing a damn thing.
So that was enough to increase my ire toward their species.
As you can see, I'm all left alone.
And there's not even any music here.
And yet a recording is happening.
Everything's going fine.
I don't suppose you can hear it.
I suppose you'd like to get on the other microphone
instead of earphones.
Yes, we can be supported.
Fill in the blanks.
Proceed to check out.
All will be well.
And all manner of things will be well.
Now, Reverend Mother Dr. Miller is going to join us
in this enchanting bobcast at X Day 20.
Here in Caffeina's snazzy cafe.
All right.
First of all, I want in on some of this here.
Turkish delight.
Rose petal infused Turkish delight.
Have some more.
Please, please.
I wonder how many calories are in each one of these wombat-esque cubes.
Zero.
Precisely zero.
Really?
These are the calorie-free.
These are calorie-free Turkish delight?
No, they're not.
Oh, they're not.
Oh, well.
Too much.
Calorie-free sugar-filled.
You could believe.
Go ahead.
Have one.
The first one's free.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And who are you, good sir?
Reverend Frogtoes.
Reverend Votos?
Frogtoes.
It's Reverend Frogtoes, who is here for the first time.
And from what state do you hail?
We came all the way here from North Dakota.
All the way from North Dakota.
And with you is the lovely?
Amber Sofar, but we're working on it.
Amber Sofar.
Sister Sofar.
Praise his sweet name.
I'm so grateful that you guys are here.
You guys made it here safe and alive?
Yes.
Amber provided a bandage for Princess Wee last night when she took a couple.
And she provided lipstick for my frop earlier, my frop stick earlier.
It was nice.
Beautiful rose petal colored frop stick.
And then Stang roused me from the hammock and rolled.
He did?
Yes, he did.
What's that all about?
He said, Dr. Howell has summoned you for pie.
Boy, how messages get garbled.
It's like the game of telephone.
Did you ever get a piece of pie?
I didn't.
No, that is most regrettable, unfortunately.
All variety of other things, but no pie.
I mean, it was part of the con.
No pie for me.
Well, there still is enough pie for you to have a piece if you would like.
Is it the one that's got the spaceship emblazoned on the top of the crust?
It did, but now it's no more.
I mean, you just get chunks of pie which have been transferred to another pan.
But it did have, yes, a flying saucer, cross pipes, X for X day, the number 20 in the background.
Dr. Howell, would you be so kind as to pass my luge there, my, no, no, the absinthe that is now cloudy.
Here it is.
Bo, would you care for a swaggle?
Who the butt?
What?
It's Mr. Bo Ragsdale.
We have an extra mic, do we not?
Yes.
Do we?
This goes here.
Do you see it?
Well, all right.
Pass it down there.
Pass it down.
Take hold.
Here.
See if you can loosen the coil.
I will loosen the coil, good sir.
Please stand by.
Oh, you sound good on radio, Bo.
No.
Bo is my Yeti brother from Allegan, Michigan, which is on the western side of the
state.
I'm now holding up my right hand.
Oh, that's great.
The state of Michigan has such an interesting shape, I always thought.
Yes, it is shaped just like a, you know, a, you know, a, you know, a, you know, a, you
know, a, oh, maybe a glove, so that we can raise our right hands and use it as a map
any day of the week.
So I'm...
Actually, I'm from Ngombo, Sri Lanka, and I'm currently residing in the island of Kirk
in Croatia.
The island of Taprobane, as originally it was, or Taprobany, however one would
say it.
Golden Ceylon.
Do I want to touch this?
Yes.
You have already, and why not?
It's not a coprolite.
Stang was already making jokes about it for all his supposed aversion to bawdy humor.
No, it's just a mineral which happens to resemble...
Go ahead.
Jeez, yes.
Happens to resemble an organic form.
Yes, it does.
It looks like something that it would have resulted from extra meditation.
Perhaps, but...
Bo, did you engage in extra meditation this morning?
Extra meditation?
Extra meditation.
It's a...
It's been handled.
Nice.
I had a productive meeting with my associates.
I, too, had a productive meeting with my associates.
Oh, that's very good.
One as productive as one can be.
Progress.
There was much movement.
Well, now, yes, you'll actually get that other pair of headphones on, but you know,
there's nothing to hear because we can't seem to continue the music track without Reverend
Stang there.
Do you know how to operate the machine?
I don't know how to operate that machine.
That's why I was moving the slider, seeing if there was a track playing, but whatever
it is has come to the end of its cycle.
I'm going to start pressing buttons.
You could press buttons, but I'm sure you have a natural-born affinity for this sort
of thing.
What happened?
Power on.
Ah, well, that'll do it every time.
Load, open.
Okay.
Oh, we're doing something.
Now move, see the two sliders, the farthest to the right?
Try moving them.
I believe autoplay is the thing, so watch this.
Try the slider because the slider's all the way down, so no matter what's happening, we're
not going to hear anything unless you move.
This one?
I think it might be that one.
Okay.
Wait, because it's going low, okay?
It does?
There, now it appears to be playing.
Ah, here we go.
Now we're back to the hour of slack.
Now would you adjust the volume yourself?
I can't.
Oh, no, the volume sounds quite good to me here in the headphones.
Unfortunately, I don't know if the audience are able to experience it the way we do, but
though that is to be regretted, I'm...
Give me a thumbs up.
Oh, look, I think it's Arise behind us.
Aha, Arise, ye prisoners of starvation.
Arise, ye wretched of the earth.
The international subgenius will become the human race.
I hope it.
I mean, really, this time for sure.
Well, unfortunately, it's not by evangelism, but by attrition, since many are called, but
few are chosen.
The subgenius are an elite few who will be saved, as opposed to the bulk of people whose
sacrifice is supposed to make everything better.
So, does overman or uberfem status or yeti lineage give you a plus one for an extra spot
on a ship, or how does that work?
Well, it helps you, definitely, because if you are descended from yetinsin, you are a
subgenius.
What about mating with yetinsin?
Meeting, did you say?
Mating.
If you're just like a yetisin's concubine.
I mean, does that get you on board?
Well, you could...
That would, I think.
I mean, come on, who's yeti dick do I gotta suck to get on board the saucer destroyer?
Well, you know, they're not going to anger the yeti by leaving his amour behind on the
launching ramp.
That would be untoward.
Well, I mean, I think that's a good thing.
On the other hand...
Ladies, that's how you get on board the saucers.
We have faith, and that faith is in the incredible supreme efficacy of these beings, superior
to us on the evolutionary scale.
But surely we can be forgiven for thinking or questioning, does that mean everything
they do is perfect?
Can they not still make mistakes?
Couldn't we be left behind by some bureaucratic snafu of an...
Ultra-advanced civilization from the stars?
You know, the universe is tricky.
Plays snickering tricks on us all and our expectations.
So I'm just saying we shouldn't be too ready to rest on our laurels simply because we are
that rarity of rarities, a subgenius.
Wow.
It lives.
Operation...
Operation Mind.
Oh, this is...
This is...
What can I say?
This is our opinion.
If it offends you, well, perhaps we'd like to know what you think.
And return of the sacred scribe, I will take my leave, of the beloved Dr. Calvin.
Yes, I...
You heard that music playing in the distance a while back.
That was when Reverend Stang ate his spinach and dealt with the interloper who we had at
the gate.
And having re-transformed himself back to his...
Salty, normal self.
Reverend Stang will sit with us and he will once again join the ranks of the paladins
as we beat back doctrinal error with every pulse of time and restore the purity of our
original uncorrupted vision.
Because we don't believe.
It's been...
Uh...
Supplanted by anything particularly...
Worthy.
Uh...
But, on the other hand, also we include everything because there is a doctrine of all inclusion.
You know, you've read, if you've read our sacred texts, that any old damn thing a subgenius
says immediately becomes part of subgenius doctrine.
Uh, there's absolutely no problem with that.
But...
There are not enough subgeniuses to produce so much noise in the signal that the entire
system becomes inoperable.
Uh...
At the same time, once again, as I said, many are called but few are chosen.
For free information, see subgenius.com.
Praise Bob!
Subtitles by the Amara.org community