You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to the subgenius
of our life.
Sometime in early 1996, praise Bob.
Sometime in Cleveland.
And it was an ugly, ugly night.
But we survived and we bring you the skeletons, the remnants of that evening.
Hello.
My name is Chaz.
And we are Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
And that's what you were just listening to was Einstein's Secret Orchestra performing
for you.
That was last week's show.
Let's put last week's show away and create a whole new show just for you.
I think we should put this guy over here on the turntable where he belongs.
Oh, he didn't want to do that.
Okay, there he is.
Break dancing.
Well, by the time you get this communicated, it'll be too late.
The pigs are outside the door.
What I want to know is who speaks for Earth.
Hey, here's Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Michelle down in the other studio on that box there.
I'm sitting here with a keyboard.
And Dave's got his guitar.
And Lisa Lisa is over there.
And the Reverend.
Reverend Ivan Stang standing right behind me.
And that's a dangerous proposition, boys and girls.
Crazy.
Princess Lisa.
The KY Jelly is ready to go.
And everyone is standing around in line.
Look, they fell for it again.
They're back again.
Told you they'd do it.
And they always fall for it every time.
Always will again and again.
Again.
Thought you could get away, did you?
Look at it.
He doesn't even remember, does he?
No, no, no.
Just let him guess.
We'll just let him drift in and out of realities for a while.
Who speaks for Earth?
Who sells for Earth?
And who will buy Earth?
I'm afraid this is the end of the game.
Here's one for Mother.
You are about to discover a part of yourself
that you have never dared dream might exist.
This show will be a personal experience
between you and the man with the pipe.
You are about to rip open a yawning chasm
in what you see.
thought was your personality. You will stand on the brink of a hole deep within yourself.
A pit, a pit, and a stinky pit, and then the very deepest, blackest part of the pit that
is your mind. You will discover Bob. But first, let's step back out into the real world. The
real world. The real world.
Now that you have achieved, Trans State, come with us.
Come and travel in the astral planes as we seek that which is dark.
But first, you must pull loose from your own body. Yes, it's easy. Just a little tug.
Close your eyes. Float upward and give your soul a little tug. You'll see. You are free.
You're free.
You never thought your soul a little tug? Did you? You never thought it would be so easy, did you?
Then let's go upwards.
Let's float.
Upwards. To get perspective. Upwards. Higher. Towards heaven.
But we'll stop here in space first. Just past the Earth's atmosphere. You see? We can go anywhere instantly this way.
And it was all so easy, right within humanity's grasp all along. And you know the secret. Really. You can go anywhere. Let's try something new.
Trans State.
this trench in the middle of this
blistering hell planet
and sent it due to sitting chained
in this ditch forever.
Just waiting, waiting
until the ticks come again.
Yes, just waiting.
The giant ticks.
Here they come again.
Let's start shooting.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Yeah, don't look.
Look.
Keep shooting.
You could shoot another one in another hole
and you'll never kill them all.
Keep shooting. Keep shooting.
Just keep shooting.
See, just like your job.
Back at home, ain't it, boy?
Yep.
You just can't get away.
You can't get away from them ticks.
My friends.
So join them.
My mother never answered
one of my prayers.
I made obeisances.
Well, you paid Obias since today,
but
did you pay money?
Actual cash, green and gravel.
Think about it, boys.
Don't wait till everyone
in your neighborhood's got the bomb.
Nuke them.
Now at Hiroshima Schwartz's
Miniature Nuclear Weapons Warehouse.
Hi, friends. I'm Hiroshima Schwartz
of Hiroshima Schwartz's Miniature Nuclear Weapons Warehouse.
Home of the Mini-Mag,
the Pocket Thunder,
the baby neutrino that leaves their apartments intact,
and many other fine, low-range,
bad nukes.
These teeny-tiny warheads actually fit in your wallet,
purse, or pocketbook.
And what's on special this week at Hiroshima Schwartz?
It's the giant X-Day
drill sale.
Now until the wee-wee hours of July
6, 1996.
We are literally giving away
tons and tons of useless
and useful weapons.
It's the Werner Von Braumeister Party Special
that blows away 50 party pinks at a time,
leaving the party intact.
Disguised as a four-gallon keg that first draft,
really packs a wallop.
But for paid subgenius,
it's the smart prairie squid face-seeking special.
I'm sorry, I always get that wrong.
It reads your mind
and literally knows where to send the warby.
Finally, now until X-Day,
bloodier than any golf pro,
it's the exploding head of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
When the pipe lights, it's armed.
When launched, it zaps up to 100.
That's 100 useless bobbies at a time.
Friends, don't wait till it's too late.
Everyone will soon have the bomb.
Nuke them now, from now till X-Day.
And beyond, we are literally
blowing up the competition.
Hiroshima Schwartz's X-Day End of the World Sale.
Tell them Bob sent you and received 23% off.
Batteries not included.
Some assembly required.
You know, I've been eating alien shmegma pie
for almost 50 years.
Since those first shoster crashes near Roswell.
My sons grew up on it.
His sons too.
Here in Wilbur Bullets.
Wilbur Bullets is natural as pie.
But many folks don't know about alien shmegma pie.
Things kind of changed
since we landed on the moon.
Some things we didn't even know.
Some folks believe in things called greys.
Gramps, did you eat your pie today?
It's my daughter, always worrying.
Hey Gramps, when are we going to go
to the nude dancer's norian?
I'm going to go to the nude dancer's norian.
I'm going to go to the massage parlor.
And that grandson of mine always keeps me running.
Then forget our little appointment.
Oh, nice and tidy.
I've been staying in a sack with Grandma for a long time
thanks to alien shmegma pie.
All I know is alien shmegma pie is made of a cheesy wax
from alien genitalia.
It's made me sexually active again.
And it tastes great.
That's all I know.
Building a new race in this life is hard.
And nothing gets it as hard as alien shmegma pie.
Alien shmegma pie, the taste that's out of this world.
Bob loves me and I love Bob.
He hates you.
I love Bob and Bob loves me.
No, he hates me.
He hates you, Dave.
He hates you.
Bob hates you.
J.R. Bob Dobbs has answered all of my prayers.
He even told me go and fling myself down the stairs.
I did it on a lark, but now I'm glad.
Bob loves me and I love Bob.
He hates you.
You may love Bob, but Bob hates you, Dave.
He makes you fling yourself down the stairs for fun.
Oh, I love Bob.
And Bob loves me.
Bob loves me.
We're sweet and slimy just like little bees on a tree.
And he pulls me on Valentine's Day.
And I'm sending flowers and chocolate.
And he loves me anyway.
I said it.
Bob loves me.
And I love Bob.
He hates me, Dave.
What could be more pure?
It's the purest form of love anyone could imagine.
He answers all my letters.
He calls me up and leaves messages on my phone.
He's always with me.
You know,
Bob loves me and I love Bob.
Don't be a sucker, Dave.
And now he's not in love on his television.
He tells that to all the boys.
And now he's so stupid because木 æô бøenoś
He makes you feel good.
He makes you feel like this.
It's pure.
Oh, it's your catapult. It's pure. It's beautiful. It's so beautiful.
Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. You don't want it.
This is what Bob meant when he said, pull the wool over your own eyes.
I can't see anything.
Oh, I'm going blind. I'm going blind.
But you can still see Bob in your mind's eye, can't you, Dave?
My mind.
You never stop seeing Bob in your mind's eye.
I can't stop.
Such as it is.
My mind?
What there is of it.
What?
Your mind. Your mind is no longer your friend.
I'm a physical person. I'm in love. I'm in lust. I'm in love with Bob and I don't care what you say.
I love Bob and Bob loves me.
Bob does love a fool. That's true.
Bob loves the fools of this world and truly the king of fools is Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Now performing the...
The greatest guitar solo in the universe.
Rock out, baby.
Play it, Dave.
I don't hear the music, but don't think you know.
Give me a beat, man.
What do you mean, which one? I thought that was all A-string.
And you see, friends, you see how the love of Bob has freed Dave from that ponderous real life around him.
He pays no attention to...
Uh, the...
What other people might think of him.
Sure, they think he's a... a fool, an idiot, a bad person.
He's a... a half-janger.
I'm tired of my... I'm bored.
I'm blue about you.
But he's happy.
You can hear the simple happiness in his voice.
Don't you...
He's a form of... I... I... I can't... I can't express how happy I was when I think about it.
Oh, don't think about it. You won't be so happy if you stop and think about it.
Now, will you, Dave?
Why are my pants all wet? What's wrong with me?
And how come I can't close my mouth or open my eyes?
And why doesn't Bob ever call a writer, answer my letters, or leave anything on my message machine?
You're not losing your faith now, are you, Dave?
That would be a great sin, a grievous sin, indeed.
To lose one's faith.
To lose one's faith in Bob.
I have no faith in Bob. Bob has no faith. He be-haves no faith.
Meaning he only hath a head. He cannot have a faith in a head.
It's... to the watchdog god, Janus, had two faces on his head.
Neither one of them were looking at the same thing at the same time.
And Bob can see you out of each one of those dots on his face, like multifaceted eyes of the mighty insect.
The mightiest insect.
Boing, boing, boing, what's happening to this brain?
The mightiest insect...
It's crawling from this life.
Little tiny pea-like thing.
Into a magnificent, magnificent brain.
Yes.
The sucking bugs of the amazing Northern Ohio area include among the order Hemptera.
I said the order Hemptera.
The sucking bugs, the bugs who suck things through pipes, such as the water scorpion,
and the rantrofuscia,
and the giant water bug.
Did you ever see that movie, The Giant Water Bug?
That was great.
And the giant water boatman was the sequel.
Thus, these are lovely and interesting insects of the Northern Ohio swamp areas.
But, aside from the pleasant, happy-go-lucky order Hemptera,
one also finds the order Neuroptera,
which includes in the sinister family Cory Dolly Day.
Do you hear the significance of that?
Cory Dolly Day?
Salvador Dolly Day?
We find a creature, yes, a living, actual bug of the Northern Ohio swamp area.
It's called the Dobson fly.
The Dobson fly?
The Dobson fly, which is, you can go see a stuffed, mounted example of this hideous, vicious beast.
In the Cleveland Natural History Museum,
the Dobson fly,
while surrounded by lovely butterflies and not too alien-looking dragonflies,
you'll notice that the Dobson fly has the head of a vicious red ant,
with tedious, clicking mandibles,
and the body, a body that resembles the tail of a rattlesnake.
Horrible, flapping, leathery wings.
Yes, the Dobson fly.
This is not some biological freak that we're making up.
I'm afraid there are thousands of Dobson fly larvae.
Now, they are in their season, their 50-year season.
As evolution lied,
It was in the 40s.
As evolution lied.
In the 1940s was the last time the Dobson fly cycle reached its peak.
And thousands died as these pincher-like beaks of billions of dobson flies,
attacked the suburbs of Cleveland.
Oh, the days of Velikovsky.
I thought it was Wassily Kambooski.
And every time you swatted a Dobson fly,
a million eggs would squirt out of its ruptured abdomen.
Each egg hatching into another million Dobson flies.
And each time you tried to squash one of those,
it would hatch another million.
Evolution has no plan.
You see, friends, man likes to think himself the grandest thing in all of God's great creation.
But indeed, no, it is the great order of the insectorii.
The great brain of all collective insect hives and tribes
is a billion times smarter than any single ego-centered human brain.
Certainly, one Dobson fly or one tick
may possess a...
rudimentary brain.
But they can communicate by radio with each other.
And the millions of each species
each forms a great brain of that species.
And those brains get together to form brains.
And let's face it, you're outsmarted, Mr. Earth Boy,
Mr. Human, Mr. Two-Legged,
Mr. Tool-Using Primate,
Mr. Thinks-He's-So-Big-Time-Smarty-Pants.
But you know, if you took that human back into the early Devonian period,
even here in the lovely Northern Ohio area,
you would find that there was no Devo.
No Devo?
No Devo.
There was...
But because there was a slimy ocean covering the Northern Ohio plains,
a filthy, sewer-like, shallow, but murky, muddy, disgusting, smelly ocean.
And in the depths of these foul, murky, pod-lives,
there grew such creatures as the Dunkelosteus.
Yes, the Dunkelosteus.
And friends, I hate to tell you this, but there is a...
It's true that there was an ancient plant discovered,
fossil of this plant, and they named it, yes,
the Clevelandodendron ohioensis.
4411-oe-us.
No, seriously.
The Clevelandendor...
Clevelandendodron ohioensis.
That was merely, however, just a tube-like plant with teeth and thousands of eyes.
From Club Moss.
Einstein's secret...
Yeah, I mean, Club Moss was a great place back then.
I saw Devo at Club Moss in the Devonian period.
Einstein's secret orchestra.
ESO Radio, boys and girls.
Ivan Stang...
in the house.
Hello?
As usual, speaking of the all themes of the insect kingdom,
we noticed that through these over-exaggerated sense of smell,
that they also keep, in a form of ESP, extrasensory contact
with each and every other member of their community.
And as we notice here, if I expose one of these insects to this molasses,
all of the rest of the insects will begin to come within the air,
even if they have been exposed,
or have been held in this container,
and are incapable of actually smelling the molasses.
As soon as they're released, they all begin exploding,
because some of them have distal charges in the back of the vacuum in.
Some of them have even approached 300 feet in length,
and some of them are well over 2,000 pounds.
And I see them in my dreams.
I keep on thinking that one of them was...
with Harry that night when they went over the edge!
Oh...
Work it!
And confess to me!
In this small...
dark...
room...
more...
I kick my quarters.
I kick my overtime.
Get market meant.
That...
is...
this new magicaaaa!
magic...
It's matter.
It's, it's matter.
This is magic...
magic...
The white zone is for immediate loading.
These phobias can be cognitive.
No!
I'm all in.
Sex with Anthony.
Harry went over the edge.
Oh, my God.
And how can we surmise that from this incident,
the head of J.R. Bob Dobbs did emerge into the lustrous as a numinous being?
I don't know.
But you can find out by coming to the X-Day Drill in Brushwood, New York,
on July 5th through 7th this year and every year from now till X-Day.
That's right, Ivan.
That's right.
Remember to call for free information about the amazing X-Day Drill.
Yes, it's like the legendary Doc Stock.
That's right, Ivan.
You'll see the most hated preachers of the subgenius church.
You'll camp out on a lovely, fully developed camp.
Oh, dear.
You'll be surrounded by geeks you'd rather not ever spend much time with.
But by God, you'll know more about the church of the subgenius,
because, friends, you will have practiced for that fatal day,
that glorious day, X-Day.
Yes, only two years from now, in 1998,
the sex goddesses from Planet X shall come.
Oh, dear.
And rupture up the news paying fully Dobbs-approved,
subgenius ministers.
That's right, Ivan.
All 4,000 of us.
And destroy the rest of the planet.
That's right, Ivan.
Well, not destroy it, but turn it back into the stinking swamp
that it was before the filthy humans came along and muddied everything up.
But, friends, you can come along and muddy everything up.
You can wallow in the filth.
You can dance all night.
Oh, dear.
You can pull your clothes off and county law doesn't care,
because we are having the first X-Day Drill this July 5th,
through Saturday.
7th.
Sunday.
Sunday!
You'll see the pill.
You'll see the bleeding head of Arnold Palmer.
It lives.
It bleeds for you if you don't vomit your money back.
Friends, you will see things you wouldn't dare believe,
things you never wanted to believe,
and things you'll wish you never saw.
That's right, Ivan.
Yetis will be copulating in the bushes.
Oh, dear.
The darkness monster will rise up from the little pond.
What?
The crazed pagan drummers will drum all night long
and keep you from sleeping.
Mosquitoes the size of dobson flies will devour you,
but you won't care.
You won't care because you spent your money
and came to the X-Day Drill July 5th through 7th
in Brushwood, New York.
Brushwood, New York.
Only three hours from Cleveland.
And, friends, you can call for information.
216-LF-LF-60338.
I'll give that number again.
Write that number down.
It's the free information divinable hotline
at the Church of the Subgenius here in Cleveland.
0060338.
That's 0060338.
What do those numbers add up to?
Aha, now you know the secret.
Now you know what we're really trying to tell you about.
The froth.
Yes, the froth.
There's no end to it.
That's right, Ivan.
Buckets of froth.
Backtops full of froth.
Three months tired.
That's right, Ivan.
A froth.
A different age.
You're only an ocean.
Ocean full of froth.
Whoa, dude.
Ancient Tibetan herbs.
Scrolling right up under your feet.
You won't be able to sleep.
There'll be so much froth growing at high speed
underneath your sleeping bag, tossing you around.
It's like a giant funhouse.
Yes, it's insane.
It's crazy.
But ain't it always been the crazy people
that were able to party like the new hell?
Yes, sir, E-Bob.
Yes, sir, ma'am, sir, lady.
You will finally learn what it's like
to be a subgenius.
That's right, Ivan.
Staying in the church of a subgenius.
And so...
Oh, did I say that?
Well, then, pick up on it, man.
It's said that the end of the world
shall come in a great flash.
Ha!
I sure hope so.
Some people might go
and the other ones might last.
Will you be the one who goes?
Where will you be on next day, brother?
Where is your...
Will you be in the...
Will you be on next day, brother?
Will you be on next day?
With...
There's still lots of room.
Oh, will you be down in the room?
You can have anything you want.
Will you be burning?
Oh, yes, sir.
I'll burn it.
I'll see you this night.
Will it be a perfect pleasure?
Perfect pleasure.
Perfect pay.
Which will it be?
It's up to you to choose.
Bob gives you free will.
But you can't feel anything
until you sign on the dotted line.
And the next day is coming,
so you better move fast,
because where will you be on next day?
I've got plenty of time
to spend my $30 on that Bob ministership.
I've got plenty of time.
That's two more years for next day.
Why mine?
It's a long time.
Bob and I are still here!
And Fred and
Oh, and my names are on a혀!
We don't have a connection.
Bob didn't get a call.
not that the world's going to end this year, 1996. Probably not. I could probably afford
to take that risk. I mean, I've got that $30. That's not a problem. But there's this Hootie
and the Blowfish CD I wanted to get. And, well, you know, I wanted to go to this movie
about water spouts. And, well, I just, you know, I mean, Bob will wait on me. I mean,
Bob's a patient man. He ain't a rat, for God's sake. I heard Bob loved this geniuses
even if they never spent any money.
A patient man. A patient man. Man, he ain't no patient. Bob is the doctor. He ain't no
patient man.
Bob is the surgeon who will excise the filthy, rotting tumor that is America. That is modern
America today.
Yes, my fellow.
Rebellious citizens and untaxed payers and militia members. All the citizens of courts.
We must come together. We must come together. Quick, they're coming. They're trying to stop
me from speaking. All of us religious nuts and crazy, bright-winged maniacs, we must
band together against the man because, oh, wait, they're coming. I've got to get my message
out. The last one.
Oh, come on.
We're about to start.
5-5-6-0-3-3-8.
Call.
Here they come.
No, come on.
Yes, yes, yes.
No, please.
I'm not telling you it's going to be.
I won't give you long to be.
No, no, no, no, no.
You'll have to laugh one day.
One day.
Got a cold crusade for a necktie
Got me a church by the roadside
Made out of rattlesnake hide
Bob is gonna ask you, who do you love?
Who do you love?
You are my love
Watch my little book drop it by
You love me, got me right
Hey, how I feel
Hey
ela
You love me
Hey
Andится on m어지uka HD I didn't even kick money grew and died at work
You mean, am I worthy of Bob's hate?
Of course I'm worthy of Bob's hate.
Everybody hates me.
I'm one of the most hated men ever to walk the earth.
There's no reason why I dare on Bob Dobbs, the old hate master.
He wouldn't want to give me a few stabs with the old poison eyeball.
I'm afraid you flatter yourself, Dave.
It's a form of love, Dave.
You know, like, he beats you up because he loves you.
It's like a heavy thing, you know.
It's like a tough love, you know what I mean?
What's so close to that?
But you know, Dobbs did love Dave.
And there have always been Daves.
Yes, for thousands, even millions and millions of years,
there have been Daves.
Lonesome cowboy Daves.
Generally ignored by science for obvious reasons.
But this month only in Cleveland Natural History Museum,
there is, in fact, a display.
A rather large exhibit called
Cleveland Before Bob.
In which one may actually see fossils of the ancient peoples.
The precursors to the modern day.
The Dave that we unfortunately know now.
There have been, for instance,
there's quite a wonderful set of artifacts
that were raised up from the P-Dog site.
There, that prove that even the early Davonians were tool using,
not quite at the level of primates.
We can get my finger all the way up here.
They had an unusual,
there were an unusually large number of stone pot shards.
As well as, oddly enough, many pot sherds found at this dig.
Obviously pots were used, overused, probably.
Abused.
The abused, yes.
The abused pots, they were broken all over the place.
Old clones.
However, we do know that the ancient Dave's had a sex life.
But somehow, as we can see,
I see in this a fairly well honed
fluted point carved from stone.
And notice here, the wooden foreshaft
of the ancient Dave piece contained quite a wide groove.
So you could take a look at it.
Take that wooden foreshaft.
The ancient Dave, them old Dave men, the old Dave men could take,
they had a wooden foreshaft with such a wide groove and the fluted point of it.
See, now nowadays, modern Dave, it's not even made of wood.
It's just limp like an old wash rag.
It's still got the fluted point.
But, you know, it ain't nearly as sharp as they used to be.
Because the ancient, strangely enough,
the Neander Dave's actually had a larger cranial capacity.
Than the modern homo Daveian.
You see here, slide three, an ugly creature.
But yet, strangely enough, still our ancestors.
Well, yours maybe.
And me poised on edge of evolution as we stand together here today on this historic moment.
With brain much bigger than that to follow.
Must rewind all those who follow.
But even with its larger brain,
the ancient Dave men were able to build nothing but crude pipes.
There are thousands of varieties of pipes,
shattered pipes found in the ancient settlement in which they smoked.
But what as far as we can tell, wild plant materials, including dogwood,
the bark of the dogwood, which was quite strong,
quite a bit stronger than the bite of the dogwood, although it did have a good bite.
If he made you a dog stick, dogwood stick, rolled you up, run up some dogwood.
That does have a bite to it.
That's a hell of a bite to it.
And bring to big today.
Come on, Douglas.
However, the ancient Dave men had a natural enemy.
The mammothous primigenius.
Oh, my God.
Here they come.
Or primigenius, which is Greek for primitive subgenius.
Ironically far more intelligent than the modern subgenius.
I want to play on the old record.
As proved by the fact that you're listening to this show at all right now.
I'm going to smoke olive rabe.
And here they come.
Unfortunately, the largest display in the museum showing me Dave men is the items
of unknown function, carefully carved and intricately decorated bone and ivory
fragments, which the uses of which have yet to be discovered.
They seem to be senseless.
They are simply created.
Perhaps some size.
Some scientists suspect they may have been used to dislodge unwanted objects from
obscure body parts and the early Dave men possessed more orifices than the modern
day, but made copious use of them and also a thyroid wax collector.
And also under opinion, a master also beneath both follicles of here.
I'll hold.
Wow.
I love.
In these ancient holographic films, you can see the olden time Dave,
the primitive days chanting in their silly rituals.
Yes, even then, man had religion.
They buried their dead
infant
Dave fetus skeletons have been found, which showed signs of having been ritually slaughtered
by their parents.
They were forced to leave their body.
For the delicacy, the one the one item of diet that we know that the ancient
Dave men enjoyed was fetus, not quite know how to put that.
Certainly a serious.
Those things would go for 1495 an ounce at least nowadays.
You know, then once you're on your way to the piggly wiggly,
you can't hardly get fetus match, but the ancient Dave men were able to harvest these from there.
I am.
Time now. Time to go out and harvest.
I was.
What was it we were harvesting?
This was during the dawn of agriculture.
And these ancient Dave men were, in fact, what we call skull farmers.
There they are.
Three hundred of them just waiting to be.
The women stay in the campground, mating with the men
of the rifle tribes as the Dave were out in the fields harvesting the skulls and the heads.
They tried to grow heads, but generally they were so
such such badly skilled farmers that they were able to only grow skulls or else they
forget to pluck their heads until they become skulls.
This white is gleaming and is ready to walk.
Now, what do we do afterwards?
We drink, we drink, we come out the store.
We drink and call you a big skulls because we have such big brains.
But in a vain attempt to gain the intelligence of the mighty mammoth,
the Dave would drink the brains of the mammoth to gain the courage of the mighty
cow and its craftiness and speed.
The ancient Dave men would drink the brains of the cows or rather,
they would suck them up through stone pipes.
Now, remember, some of you drink cow.
You imbued with all power of cow strength, beauty, sleep, fast, quick, small, tiny, little.
Shut up.
This is what is known as sympathetic magic.
Obviously, today in today's modern world, we know better than to fall for simple superstitions.
I drank that genius's urine just for a taste of brilliance.
That's true.
There is the one exception.
Sympathetic magic does still work in the Church of the subgenius.
If you will drink of the fluids of Bob, you will gain the wisdom of Bob.
His great intellectual acuity will be yours.
And you all know how smart Bob is.
He's from the Church of the sub gum guys at subgenius.
They're all geniuses or something, right?
Isn't that what they're trying to say or something?
Yeah.
And Bob's a smart guy.
And so if you kill Bob and drink of him,
if he's an idiot, his body will be as smart.
Nate, Nate's alive.
Friends, Bob is not smart nor nor intelligent, but only lucky.
So you don't drink of his brain.
You drink of his other fluids until you have gained some of his luck.
Drink his final fluids for good luck.
Wear it on your head.
His armpits sweat.
If you can stand in front of Bob when he sneezes,
you will be able to gain the viruses of Bob.
He's milk is his most precious.
Oh, yes, it's milk.
If you clean up Bob's bathroom after he is finished in there.
And I think you know what I mean.
Hey, I just came to clean up.
No, no, I wouldn't want to do anything like that.
Just trying to fix the plumbing.
You will gain his sales acumen.
I own the plumbing business around the rest of the world.
I will control the plumbing enterprise of the planet.
It's true, folks.
You too could be just like the modern lonesome cowboy Dave.
This paragon of manhood and manly beauty.
This this confident and stalwart stud and cool guy.
All you have to do is to know Dave, to know Bob.
But to know Bob, you merely must call the secret number.
Yes, this is a secret.
Don't tell anybody.
Turn your radio down.
Get your pencil out.
Call this number.
Yeah.
60338.
Go ahead.
Yes. Give it a try.
What if you got to lose a little time?
Maybe you did sign the application.
Kids, don't forget to get your
special Bob Dom's decoder ring that explodes in your face for only $49.95.
Oh, now.
.
Baby, is it you?
As a boy, I dream of angels
Little darling, tell me why
I get so cold looking in your eyes
Is it you?
Baby, is it you?
As a boy, I dream of angels
My little baby, leather and lace
Take a minute to go out of space
Is it you?
Baby, is it you?
As a boy, I dream of angels
Little darling, show me now
Somewhere, somewhere
Somehow, is it you?
Ah
Baby, is it you?
I hope I dream an angel
Who speaks for Earth?
Earth.
Who smells for Earth?
Who flies in the case of authority for Earth?
Why is none of it in the webinars?
Who's paying the rent on Earth?
That's the question.
Who's gonna take care of this bill?
Who's paying?
It's passed by the pretty piggy.
Well, who is paying?
Who stands for Earth?
I don't know, maybe me, maybe you.
Maybe nobody.
Is that your dog?
It's really the same song.
No, really.
What else?
To Brian Conrad, campus.
You know that I'm now on a stage where I have to go.
For hours, I was đấy, oi.
It's just in the camera zoom.
Die hablados zusammen, dieeightasink encapsulat in которого
ets le estructur des eendinchum covid
Dieちゃんli tout att leather
Die طest java
or emay
because he's a misanthropist.
An animal, an animalistic thing.
But this is, yes, indeed, the jawbone of an ancient yeti.
And how could you know such a thing?
Well, it says so right there on the display.
Is it the jawbone of an ancient giant yeti?
Yes.
It is about a foot and a half long.
Looks like it weighs about seven or eight pounds at least.
You lie like dirt.
No, I don't.
There's a skeleton of a gorilla not far away.
That's conceivable, a skeleton of a gorilla.
Even with its massive lower mandible,
it is merely but less than half the size of the gigantanthropus,
the prehistoric yeti.
I agree.
We call it prehistoric.
Of course, the yetis were keeping records long,
80 million years before humans knew how to pick their noses.
Well, I don't bring up a yeti.
And it was a gigantanthropus.
It focused on misanthropicus erectus.
And she was cute.
Yeah, she was awful hairy.
She was the hairiest woman.
I ever saw.
But she was big, wasn't she?
Yeah, so there was something so fragrant about her feet.
Musky.
Musky, that's too old.
Get a whiff of that yeti.
Musky, musky, musky.
Oh, yes, musky's a natural phenomenon.
I was just thinking about it.
That makes you feel manly.
They go yeti girls.
Yes, sir.
Keep up her leg.
Are you man enough for the she yeti?
Are you man enough for one of her legs?
Are you?
You got it.
Hey.
You can.
Ride on that leg, boy.
You can grab you a tight hold on that mane she's got growing down that leg and ride.
I've tried to ride her in my dreams.
I've tried to ride her off into the sunset singing my Yahoo!
Final Dernier song.
But it seems to me every time I begin to mouth the lovely young whatever you might name the lady.
I seem to.
Asked her name in a bathroom voice.
She said.
Wanda.
She yeti.
Oh my God.
Wanda of the jungle.
Wanda of the Himalayas.
I took a walk around in the park.
She held my hand.
She crushed my wrist.
I went up running.
She caught me just like that man.
It ain't no fun when a woman can outrun you and tackle you at the same time.
There I was laying on the ground in Central Park and birds twittering around and screaming
in pain.
And this huge, huge female yeti is trying to have her way with me.
Wanda does Dallas.
Deep.
Wanda.
Wanda does Zayn.
Behind the grill.
Wanda.
Behind Wanda's green behind.
Wanda likes schoolgirl uniforms.
Yeah, man.
If you've got.
Did you see the latest issue of Yeti?
Big Yeti.
I think it was Big Yeti September.
B-Y.
Yeah, I saw it.
And, man, there was this prejudice.
I couldn't believe.
In fact, it was one of the largest magazines I ever bought.
We had to get a guy who had, well, he had a Volvo one.
And we loaded up three or four of them.
And it took half an hour just to get them in the back.
Oh, yeah.
The foldout in the middle is like 30 yards long.
Yeah, we used to go to wallpaper that nation over on the top of the hill there where almost
repercussions had left.
Oh, those human stroke books might show some pink.
But you won't be seeing no pink in Big Yeti.
No.
Magazine.
It is kind of expensive.
They're like $8.95.
It's specialty material.
And if you've seen the Yeti binaries on the news, on the internet, you can get you some.
Boy, there's some pictures out there.
That's about 30 days to download.
I don't want them all dead.
They're so big.
They're such big.
Big Yeti.
Big old Harry.
Because the true women of the Yeti race, they're the big old Harry.
They're powerful.
Jesus.
And they could pick us men up by our parts and swing us around their heads and we loved
it.
You know, it hurts.
Yes, it hurts but we loved it because they were disciplining as you see.
We had discipline in those days.
The big women.
The bigger and hairy women taught us discipline.
And we thanked them.
Look at the knees and we worshiped them.
We were polite to a woman in those days.
And I languished in my decent sweat.
We equaled our عيون لنع 당시.
the woman who came with respect for the woman.
When we
dissipated
a race of gigantic
yetis, we did it out of respect
and discipline.
We did it on time.
Not like these slackers
of today.
These holiday slackers.
In the old days, the very yeti women
were on time, always on time.
The blood runs thin.
They have fluoride
in their blood.
They're not like the yetis
of yesteryear, the yester-yeti.
But boy, they can make a pickle
when they put it under the armpit.
No, I'm sorry.
I remember that sometimes
from the yeti women, you could take a whole cucumber
and slap one into each armpit
and make a pickle in five seconds.
I was a little...
And you too
can get a whiff
of one of them pickles
if you come to the X-Day
drill, July 5th through 7th
in Brushwood, New York.
At Sermon, New York.
That's right.
You'll find out all about that when you call that phone number.
Call that important phone number.
Who speaks for Earth?
You can find out at
216-960-338.
Praise Jesus.
And there ain't no
Chinese fire drill, is there, Reverend?
Oh, hey, did you know that Jesus
is now working for the Church of the Sub-Gene?
I had heard that he was not only on the payroll,
but that also that he was having eye surgery
from some crooked Medicare program
he was running.
Well, that just goes along with the job.
We like to look after our employees, but it's true.
The Lord Jesus Christ,
who is now about 26 years old
in this incarnation.
26 to 52, somewhere in the ground.
He was formerly the owner of the
now-defunct Flying Lemur
bookstore.
Jesus has now moved to Dallas.
Jesus just left Chicago
and has moved to Dallas.
He's filling the...
He's taken over the mail order
of the Church of the Sub-Gene, friends.
He's the promotion.
He who was foretold by Bob.
They said he would come wearing one sandal
and he would buy a chariot
from the Eritreans
and they would cheat him
and he would be screwed.
And yes, it is as the prophecy said, friends.
Praise Bob.
We were saved.
The smart money guy finally showed up.
And this time, he's got connections.
You know what I mean?
He's got family,
if you know what I mean.
Yeah, the Church of the Sub-Genius
has got some new friends.
The kind of friends that's got some muscle.
You know, the kind of friends
that if you cross Bob the wrong way,
he may just wake up with cement overshoes
at the bottom of the Cuyahoga.
I thought Jesus made them
missions too.
Jesus was a Capricorn
and is just all right with me.
But except that noticeably,
he sheds.
Jesus does.
Now, he lives in my,
actually in the Sub-Genius offices.
He works so hard.
And he's a really nice,
such a martyr.
He sleeps on the couch.
But he sheds.
Now that it's summertime in Texas,
Jesus is shedding all over the church.
I can't believe Jesus
definitely works so hard.
All of the above was from ESO Swamp Radio
on WCSB Cleveland from the old days.
The show of the late, incredibly great Chaz Smith,
who also played half the instruments.
Praise Chaz.