Oh
Well, I'll tell you what friends
I'll do a public service announcement right off the top of my head and it's about heart attack
friends
if you're
hanging out
or even just waking up in bed feeling funny
and you have pains in your left arm or
your right arm or
places you've never had pains before or
Headaches that they're in the wrong place of your head like your neck or your lower jaw or your teeth
You may be having a heart attack
and
it also can feel like
the worst heartburn you ever had and one thing you can do is wake up or
Clutch your chest and go. Oh man, this is bad and I bet it's nothing. I think it's gonna pass
Bad idea I
Tried that myself it didn't work
They had to helicopter me to Fort Worth and stick up scaffolding in my
So that the clots wouldn't happen there again
So yeah, when you have those symptoms go ahead and call 9-1-1, then that's Might unscripted public-service
Message
Now it seems
Friends, I hate to break it to the regular listeners. So I know some of you are going to be terribly disappointed
but dr. Sinister can't make it and
And this isn't radio synesthesia.
Although this is the time slot of radio synesthesia.
I'm afraid I'm having to fill in for two hours.
It's a bad night for me to have to do that.
Because I've got company coming tomorrow.
And I'm not done yet.
But I'm going to get my act together here.
Yes, I will.
And let you listen to this music while I do so.
This is the soundtrack of Kenneth Anger's weird underground movie called Lucifer Rising.
This music was recorded in a prison.
And one of the key composers of it was one of the charlatans.
Lee Manson family, believe it or not.
And the nice thing about this music is it goes on for half an hour.
That will give me time to get more act together.
Praise Bob and thanks for listening.
Lucifer Rising.
Our hero, Standard Mozek.
He's what you might call a combination cop and news reporter.
And he has finally tracked down the weirds.
The weirds are people who live outside of Neighbor World.
Neighbor World is the electronic environment.
You might call it the internet.
But it's a lot more than that in the future.
And Standard, our hero, is trying to defend his job.
He's a proud advo.
He goes, I whisper in what they tell me.
And it works for the average neighbor, I said blankly.
The signpost up ahead.
Pinpoint means evolution.
Everybody is information.
You're all.
You're all yacking artichokes, the fireman said.
You live in a mind-controlled prison, Shama said.
That's why you can't do what we can.
Our minds are free.
We're a brotherhood, I continued.
We work for the global neighborhood.
It sounded stupid.
I felt shame.
Tears welled in my eyes.
There, there, the inspector said in a sarcastic sounding, comforting tone.
It must be tough learning.
Your info scam brotherhood is just a mind and evolution control tool.
And probably a front for some secret society, too.
The fireman raised an eyebrow.
Shama's narrowed his focus, looking right into my eyes.
The womb walls pulsed.
But I'm an advo, I said, wiping tears.
Advos bring hush mode cults into focus.
Shine the light on them.
ECU.
Listen, Bob.
Along their jeeps they'll stop and talk like delinquent Comme Ci,
being a local worker took it the wrong way.
If you love dark people, you want to see them.
You're lost.
Next time,Schema will pull back the pages
while a book provided the secret information from Dr.
we'll vote it down and round contribut thi.
I couldn't handle 진행 WHAT
ichtein
So, I found the lights on the waysel fingerl yenzhan nike.
What was it again?
A shadow ofП
ACIM
bonds that they've had.
It's paranoia, so folks don't know what's real, the elk concluded.
It's all lies, info scam to control them.
But you can't lie to people forever, the inspector added with a threatening tone.
He source-pointed, scrutinizing me with a distant look, then shook his head.
I can see you still don't understand why we would never spotlight or join your neighbor world
or be any part of your info scam, he said.
Neighbor world doesn't help people evolve or live better, Shama scolded, waving his hand.
It just jerks off their nervous systems when they should be seeking their true natures.
I was zumbie to their jango, totally accepting and depressed.
The weirds had penetrated my stacks and the necks was wide open.
One thing seemed certain, this goose would never lay the gold op.
These folks would never spot me.
I was not like Gooey in the right, and I would never see the Advo gig the same.
The key to evolution isn't technology, Shama continued.
It's the teachings.
Tech changes.
The teachings never change.
The mirror is a beautiful thing, the inspector said with a grin.
Beautiful.
In synchro cue, the chamber got darker.
Crushing stillness moved through the room, forcing us all into awkward freeze frames.
I had a feeling a bunch of these weird kids were watching, invisible.
My diaper's full, the inspector said, looking sadly at the ground.
Mission accomplished, the shaman said, nodding in agreement.
There's only one way out, said the inspector,
shuffling slowly toward a plainly marked exit near the last omitted display.
And I'm the only one who knows it.
A mental case.
Shama said, holding his nose with one hand and making the sign of the crazy with the other.
The shaman placed his hand on the fireman's shoulder.
The pyro-freak mumbled incoherently and made oblique gestures.
His pink and blue streamers glimmered weakly.
I lift my face to the invisible sun for an invisible tan, the fireman muttered.
Beauty's only skin deep.
By fool's day, everyone will glow.
They walked to the exit.
I followed my witch-clown masters, a crazy man in a volunteer fireman's outfit
and a comic-turned-shaman without understanding him.
I lowered my eyes in humility and relinquished my personality.
Well, that was on page 154 and 155 of Neighbor World.
Bye.
By lonesome cowboy Dave DeLuca.
I've got some more nifty little spots I could read from that.
But let's do the music a little bit longer, okay?
Okay.
Yes, friends, we're listening to the soundtrack of Lucifer Rising.
An underground movie by Kenneth Anger.
Even though this would normally be radio synesthesia, it's not.
And it's going to be a subgenius show.
Or rather, actually, I'm going to play a lot of my favorite music in a little while.
But I need, X Day's coming, and I'm going to need material to put into a rerun-type production.
So, at some point.
Well, no, wait a minute.
Couldn't I just have the robots on the X ship do it for me?
Well, anyway, here.
Let's not worry about that.
I'm going to read a different section of the book, The Bobliographon.
It's out of print, so it's the only way you're going to ever, ever be able to see it or hear any of it.
And I'm going to read from a little section called Subicide.
It's about why you shouldn't kill yourself.
And I've already, I think I've already read a lot of the materials.
No, I'll start here.
Many people insist that death is great, that it's a whole new adventure.
The subgenius euphemism for when someone dies is, he got triple his money back.
Our problem is that we've noticed that none of the people who said death is so great,
have actually read it.
And that those who finally did try it suddenly became very quiet about it indeed.
Almost as if they had something to hide.
Hmm.
If on the day that I die, I find myself in an etheric light body flying down the tunnel of light
into some wonderful now incomprehensible level of awareness.
Well, great.
I'll be very pleasantly.
Surprised.
If on the other hand, I'm just plain dead, then you probably won't hear me complaining
about that either.
That was said by the great Reverend Ivan Stan.
So what is the hurry friends?
God or Bob are going to get you no matter what.
Do you really think you can do a better job of killing yourself than Bob or God can?
Are you that prideful?
Please leave it to the professionals.
If you must die, don't try.
Try to do it yourself.
Let Bob do it for you.
If you try to do it, there's a very good chance you'll muff the job.
By definition, you're an amateur at suicide.
It's possible that old grim reaper Dobbs might take his sweet time about getting around to
killing you.
You might even get impatient.
But remember what Bob said?
At the 19th century.
1978 Dobbs-Kahn stockholders meeting at the Howard Johnson's Motor Lodge in Lake Tahoe,
Nevada.
Just as suicide is the most sincere form of self-loathing, my new church of the subgenius
is the most sincere form of send one dollar.
So friends, hitch your wagon of screwed-up-edness to Bob.
Reinforce and reaffirm that commitment.
That $35 bridle.
And jump on board.
Just don't drag your feet.
If he can't help it, he can't help it.
Don't push.
And remember, the first of Bob's five keys to magic, get off your butt.
Don't worry about being a failure in the conspiracy world.
They will try to humiliate you.
But they know not the sublime cosmic secret of the forbidden sciences.
That the only thing that never fails is failure.
The only thing that never works is failure.
The only thing that never works is perfection.
The only workable philosophy, the one rule of the church is...
I'll paraphrase it.
Screw them if they can't take a joke.
You must stop blaming yourself for your failures and get back to blaming the conspiracy.
Yeah, in fact, that's why I can't say the true law of the church on public radio.
The conspiracy is a lie.
The conspiracy tries to tell you that a failed experiment is bad.
And that you're a loser if you aren't rich yet and cute or smart.
And that it's somehow abnormal and unhealthy to be depressed, pessimistic, occasionally
consumed with hate, blundering and desperately seeking slack in strange places.
But those are actually appropriate responses to a world that's so screwed up that even
the church of the subgenius starts to make sense by comparison.
Now that's screwed up.
The idea that it's normal for everything to be cheery and hunky dory and slackful and lovey is a lie.
The pinks act like everything already is that way, so you'll stop trying to make it that way.
That makes them look bad.
As the old bumper sticker says, I'd rather be killing optimists.
That way lies a life of...
quiet desperation.
Although slack is the energy which powers the universe, it's equally true that invisible,
seething, self-contained hate particles comprise the missing dark matter of the universe,
the hidden mass for which quantum physicists still search.
The subgenius taps this pure, universal hate force and transmutes it from stupidity
into...
slack.
Hate and failure are part of nature and can be unsuspected paths to slack.
The life of a subgenius marooned in a sea of humans can be hard.
You might assume that we preachers of Bob, we fishers of the wallet, have the most slack-filled jobs in the world, next to Bob.
But you see, we took on the job of pulling God's leg.
And that's a mighty big leg job.
We're the first to admit that devouring your...
No, well, we're the first to admit that devoting your heart, mind, and soul to Bob won't solve all your problems.
But it will help you to blow them off.
You really do know what's best for you, and all those hundreds of nagging weenies and widgets don't know jack hooey.
Most of them don't even know what they want, and that's why they're trying to tell you what you want.
Most people have not the slightest idea what they want to do next, and are probably better off letting the boss and the spouse and the church and the society run their little lives for them.
But Dr. Drummond, most lives are barely touched by slack at all.
It seems at times that we are forlorn ships, drifting, dreadnoughts, stuck forever in the sargasso sea of slacklessness.
The Bermuda Triangle of failed desires.
Some subgenie constantly entertain thoughts of suicide.
In fact, they're remarkably creative in such thoughts.
If they didn't have those thoughts as a release, they'd surely go mad.
Instead, they reach a point where everything's so bad, they can only laugh.
Suicidal thoughts come when you feel the great battle.
The battle to cut yourself an island of slack amidst the anti-slack and toil...
...and the losing one.
It's like an itch you can't scratch.
The conspiracy is to blame for most of it, which is a consolation one must never lose sight of.
But there is an anti-universe of anti-sight and anti-sound, and that's where half of your thoughts are.
You are represented in the anti-universe by an anti-you.
In that universe, you are rich and good-looking.
Assuming you're not so now, a safe assumption regarding subgeniuses.
You're not in negative physically, but you're negative in concept.
The negative or backwards universe is also what causes that itch you can't scratch between your ear and your throat.
That's when you have to go...
...like that to scratch it.
The transtemporal opening to the anti-universe is located in that area of the sinuses.
That is the most telling manifestation of it.
That's what the overman had to say, friends.
Life may be tough, but don't worry.
There isn't much more of it left.
Remember X-Day?
You only need to stay alive until then.
The end times are nipping at our heels, dear friends.
This is no time to false slack off.
The conspiracy has become so powerful that they can brag in the mass media about how there's a secret CIA, mafia, Nazi, or whatever.
They can boast openly that they torch whole cult compounds full of families that dare to be really weird.
They show off their, quote, crash saucers, unquote, and turn them into tourist traps.
They can do anything they damn well please, and it's all just more entertainment to the pinks.
Hell, they even show them previews of X-Day and movie theaters.
Every summer in which the pinks win.
Every other TV and radio ad has some pink everyman named Bob submitting to anti-slack happily.
Are you going to stand for this?
Are you just going to eat, get stoned, and watch the tube and listen to this station?
Well, that may be just what Dobbs commands you to do.
But if he moves you to mayhaps rise from your butt
and do something that actually takes a little extra energy,
like agent our next Ukrainian bomb purchase,
or bill our latest trademark infringer,
or make a million bucks,
or find your true Yeti mate and parent the twins who bear the scissors of sight,
will you then falter?
Will you waver just a bit in your determination?
Will you pink out?
We won't tell you what to do.
Only you know what to do.
But for God's sakes, don't not do it.
Certainly the pinkness around us and the sheer massive weight of the conspiracy
is enough to send a subgenius spiraling into depression and paralysis.
Sure, don't feel guilty if it has.
There is a cosmic slackfulness to blowing even slack off.
But accept this pep talk.
If you knew half the toil, orgasms, and brain damage it has cost us
just to keep the church post office box open for 37 years,
and how worthless it is,
how worth it it was,
you would heed.
This is no nickel-dime-bum show, but the real thing.
Your life and how not to waste it.
Your one prank call to the local radio talk show
could be the domino that starts the arisal.
Your one economic takeover in subsequent dictatorship
over some seemingly useless nation
might just be the straw that breaks Goliath's back.
What are you waiting for?
Approval from Dobbs?
Hell, he doesn't care.
He's probably watching TV.
But you aren't him.
And so you must serve him.
Don't wait to be trussed up and served to him with an apple in your mouth
like the rest of the bobbies.
Take command.
Stuff the apple in his mouth and braise him well.
Core out the apple in your own head.
Spray paint it gold and throw it to the mongrel dog pinks
so they can fight over it.
You may be that one subgenius.
The 13th apostle whose one sarcastic remark
at just the right moment is the heretofore missing link
in the chain reaction that melts down the conspiracy's self-fueling reactor.
You never know.
Just don't miss your chance.
That's all we're asking.
When you're ready to give up,
when any pink would have caved in ages before,
make that last one Herculean effort.
One of you is the one.
The one who shall make up the world.
The one who has uncut the scissors of sight.
We have redoubled our efforts at shoving the work, the church,
down the resisting craws of all normals and unsaved subgeni alike
via TV, radio, and the internet, comic books, nightclub devivals, anything.
We'll play kook.
We'll play literary outlaw.
We'll wear any mask to get Bob's word out.
Not only will this make us rich before X-Day, always a major goal,
but it will also possibly make us rich.
We'll probably save two important mystery souls from despair and suicide.
And that's probably our real contribution to Earth society.
To save from suicide the two really key individuals out there, whoever they are.
Dobbs wasn't specific.
Who will then go on to create the cure for normalcy,
or the anti-gravity teleporter, or whatever the hell it is,
that allows subgeniuses to buy out the conspiracy?
And replace it with slack?
You think we're kidding you?
Was Moses kidding?
Come X-Day, were we not promised a new government
where crime would be legal and Bob the only politician?
A new religion where you'd go to services on Saturday night,
drunk, not at some god-awful early hour on Sunday?
A new coolness where the weirdos would decide
what's cool, and the cool people would be either
in-weirdant or...
cleansed?
Yes!
Where all hate would be stomped out by force?
Well, what are we waiting for?
Why are we waiting for X-Day?
Bob taught us the hard way not to depend on God, aliens, or even salesmen.
Yet too many people still use Bob as a crutch
when they should be fighting over his armpit space to be his crutch.
You must stop asking what's in Bob's mind.
Throw yourself into that pipe and let him smoke you.
Let him make an ash of you.
Your mind is what he smokes in that pipe.
Your mind is what is sucked into his eyes and thoughts
when you look at his face.
And looking at his face?
That's all it should take.
People ask you,
Who's this Bob man?
Why is he important?
Just sit him down and make them really look at that face.
And they will see.
They will truly, finally see.
Oh, they had us fooled for so long.
They had us thinking that a one-world government
or else a one-world religion was the real conspiracy
when actually it was the one-world advertiser all along.
And it has already completely colonized Earth Farm One.
The subgenius must have slack, my friends, by any means necessary.
The Pink Man has held the Slack Man down.
But everything comes apart.
One way or another.
Heh. Heh. Heh.
Make no mistake.
God loves you.
But Bob, Bob wants you.
And he's going to find you.
You cannot find yourself.
Are you so confident as to think you can find yourself better than Bob can?
As Bob said,
I'll find myself when they pry me out of my cold, dead fingers.
Why should we let a total conspiracy clampdown get between us and Slack Man?
Just because the Norms ninnied out
and are busy building themselves into a prison corner that they painted themselves,
does that mean we have to give up our slack too?
Hell nay, say we.
For J.R. Bob Dobbs is our personal self-fulfilling prophet.
We don't know what year this is or even what planet we're on.
Praise Bob.
We don't know anything except that it's not yet July 5th, 1998.
Maybe we'll be lucky and tomorrow will be that.
Maybe these aren't the end times at all.
They might be the beginning times.
Bob said,
I want you to stop buying and start selling.
We have nothing to lose.
If we don't live forever,
we get our money back.
The final truth,
Bob is not the answer.
And neither is anything else.
You must learn to think for yourself.
But only Bob can show you how.
Question authority.
Or else.
Praise Bob.
And above all,
if they can't take not a joke,
let them mount up upon themselves.
So mote it be.
Motant it.
Motant it indeed.
So now I think it's time to go
to the real music.
The kind I mighty like.
And we're going to welcome in a new era.
Along with our old buddy,
Jimi Hendrix.
Praise Bob.
Five, four, three, two, one.
From Bill Graham and everybody in the Fillmore family.
We're going to welcome you to the new era.
A very, very happy new year.
In a new decade.
A happy new year, everybody.
A very happy new year.
And if you walk down the bay that I see
Guess I didn't really know
God, what I'll been feeling
shocked by
So many things
As it was
But one thing's for sure
That is anyone,
There will be
No one
But me
guitar solo
райüle şeker
happy new year everybody
bass solo
keg
pech
I've been through ya
About 69
What you gonna do for me
Make us fall behind
I hope you don't mind us jamming a little bit.
We're gonna sing this one.
We'll see what we're gonna do to play next.
Yeah.
Hello darkness my old friend
I've come to talk with you again
Because a vision softly creeping
Left its seeds while I was sleeping
And the vision
That was planted
In my brain
Still remains
With me
In the sounds
Of silence
Oh
In restless dreams I walk alone
In the narrow streets of cobblestone
Neath the halo of an east street line
I turn my collar to the cold and down
When my eyes were stabbed by the flash
Of a neon light
That split the night
Of a neon light that split the night
And touched the sounds
Of silence
The red富loaps
In the naked light I saw
Ten thousand people, maybe more
People talking without speaking
People hearing without listening
Writing songs that voices never share
And no one dare
Disturb the sounds
Of silence
Fool said I, you do not know
Silence like a cat that grows
Hear my words that I might teach you
Take my arms that I might reach you
But my words
Like silent raindrops fell
And echoed in the well
Of silence
And the people bowed and prayed
To the neon god they made
And the sign flashed out its warning
In the words it was for me
And the sign said the words of the prophets
Are written on subway walls
And tenement halls
And whispered in the air
And whispered in the sounds
Are written on subway walls
And whispered in the sound
Of silence
Are written on subway walls
Silence
I sometimes get feedback unless you play some good music, so I'll do that now.
Music
Father, father, I'm here in the zoo
I can't come home cause I've grown up too soon
I got my sentence, I got my command
They said to fake my name
Thank you.
And the great Elvis Costello that was.
They call you Lady Luck,
but there is room
for doubt.
At times you have a very
unladylike way
of running out.
You're on a date
with me.
The pickings have been lush.
And yet before
this evening is over,
you might give me the brush.
You might forget your
manners. You might refuse
to stay.
And so the best that I
can do
is pray.
Luck, be a lady
tonight.
Luck, be a lady tonight.
Luck, if you've
ever been a lady to begin with.
Luck, be a lady tonight.
Luck, let a
gentleman see
how nice a dame you can
be.
I know the way you've treated other guys
you've been with.
Luck,
be a lady with me.
A lady doesn't leave
her escort. It isn't fair.
It isn't nice.
A lady doesn't wander
all over the room
and blow on some other guy's
dice. So let's
keep the party polite.
Never get out
of my sight.
Stick with me, baby. I'm the
fella you came in with. Luck,
be a lady.
Luck, be a lady.
Luck, be a lady tonight.
Luck, be a lady
tonight.
Luck, be a lady tonight.
Luck, if you've
ever been a lady to begin
with. Luck, be a lady
tonight.
Luck,
let a gentleman see
how nice a dame
you can be.
I know the way you've treated
other guys you've been with. Luck,
be a lady with me.
A lady wouldn't flirt
with strangers. She'd have a
heart. She'd have a soul.
A lady wouldn't
make little snake eyes at me
when I've spent my life
on this road. So
let's keep the party polite.
Let's keep the party polite.
Never get out of my sight.
Stick with me,
baby, I'm the fella you came in with.
Luck, be a lady.
Rollin' up,
rollin' up, rollin' up,
rollin' up right.
Ha!
I jumped ship
Head for South of South
Swam like a senator
I reached the shore
On the trip
The beauty was brewing
Handle to the cake
To the ocean floor
Now I'm alone
Yes, I'm alone
In the old world
Singing like a stone
I am a man
Without a country
And I'm a boy
Without a home
I'm a casualty
Of a battle
Of the roses
And the war
Of the broken home
I got busted
For drinking while begging
Carrying a weapon
Under my coat
And I got busted
For all the money
To people
And now I am a pirate
On the bad dream boat
And I'm alone
I'm alone
I got a lot of stolen bones
I am a man
Without a country
And I'm a boy
Without a home
I'm a casualty
Of a battle
Of the roses
And the war
Of the broken home
I see land
divided down the middle
And the sides are divided
And divided again
I see so many people lonely
Hating lover, friend against friend
Now I'm alone
I'm alone
And now I'm never going home
I am a man
Without a country
Without a home
I'm a casualty
Of the battle of the roses
And the war
Of the broken home
guitar solo
The path is the mask of love
A way, a way
The flow is the task above today
There is no other way
guitar solo
You gotta try
to trust us
When you need a friend
To find us
You gotta look within
You gotta trust us
Before you turn to dust
You gotta see it
before you see it
before you be it
You gotta see it
before you see it
guitar solo
Out of here without fear
Without a fear to reveal
You gotta touch without taste
Such is ill and I ain't his ain't
guitar solo
Well for you
Of you
guitar solo
We're telling the truth, we love you
The path is you, it's a dying life
The path is life, it's a lying life
It's a lying life, it's a lying life
It's a dying life
Thank you.
And this is the great Herb Alpert.