CLOSED CAPTIONS PROVIDED BY THE LAMBDOM STORE
The sad genius
Power of slack
Power of sl-a-ck
Power of... slack
S-s-s-slack
P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P
Power of... Power of...
Power of slack
You won't get much higher
You got a dollar for crack, I pay you back
Higher
From NPR News in Washington
I'm demanding human rights
Human rights violations on French trains to Nazi death camps
Outgoing Defense Secretary Chuck Hagel is not involved
More than 25 U.S. mayors that turned violent overnight
Are finding their shops in ruin
And are ready to do it
Dow is 1099
Hundreds of thousands of children under 5
Are suffering from acute PR news, Washington
The United Nations calls this NPR's reports
Saying as many as 15 million young people
Are caught in PR news in Washington
Under Walmart
Domestic violence
North American
Africa
South Korea
Donald Trump
My dominion is valid
MTN kardeş on Facebook English and comedianville.net
He's a light with your whole body
He ain't no man, he ain't no God
I don't wanna walk the path I've tried
At his desk in Dallas
When Dreadops sits smoking
Behind his mirrored windows
Let up your pipe, let go the smoke
This is slack, it ain't no joke
Brace me to Bob, lift up your chain
And you will pay to know what you think
Body in a box
He ain't no man, he ain't no God
I don't wanna walk the path I've tried
od
God is watching us
He's following you
His holy highness
Knows everything you do
God's heads are all around
Trust me, I know
His third eye will track you down
Wherever you go
If all slack is what he's found
Pink you shall glow
God is watching you
God is watching us
He's following you
His holy highness
Knows everything you do
Don't look down, don't try to stop
He's right behind
Smoking his heavenly frog
Breeding your mind
Cracking his every thought
Truth he shall find
Bob Dobbs is watching you
He's right behind us
He knows everything you do
He's following you
You are my God
God is watching us
God is watching you
He's following you
He's bright behind us
He️ knows everything you do
you do
One more time.
Yarr, yarr, yarr, yarr, yarr.
Cool.
Bob, Bob, Bob.
Yeah, Bob, Bob.
How about that?
Can you hear me?
Baa!
I wear a special aluminum helmet.
Bob, Bob, Bob.
Special aluminum.
Yes, is it true that you're well-announced?
Yes, it is.
Bob, Bob, Bob.
Bob, hey Bob! Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, we love you! Bob, hey Bob! I'd like to request free bird. Bob, Bob, Bob, what's the meeting like? Yes, Bob. Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob. Yeah, Bob, I need to talk to Bob. Yeah, Bob.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Babe, babe, we're the Dixie Dogs.
Bob, Bob, yeah, Bob, hey Bob.
Yes, Bob.
Hi, Bob.
Bob, Bob.
Bob.
Hello, Bob.
Now, here you go again.
Yeah, Bob.
Don't stop your eyes.
See what's going on.
Goodbye, Bob.
Bob, hey Bob, how you doing?
Bob, Bob, Bob.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Yeah, Bob.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
No, he hates you, Dave.
He hates you.
Bob hates you.
J.R. Bob Dobbs has answered all of my prayers.
He even told me go and fling myself down the stairs.
I did it on alert, but now I'm glad.
Bob loves me and I love Bob.
He hates you.
You may love Bob, but Bob hates you, Dave.
down the stairs for fun.
Oh, I love Bob, and Bob loves me.
We're sweet and slimy just like little bees on a tree.
And he told me on Valentine's Day,
and I'm sending flowers and chocolate.
And he loves me anyway.
I said, Bob loves me, and I love Bob.
He hates me.
What could be more pure?
It's the purest form of love anyone could imagine.
He answers all my letters.
He calls me up and leaves messages on my phone.
He's always with me.
The computer does all of that, Dave.
Don't be a sucker.
Bob loves everyone except you, Dave.
Because you were so stupid as to believe him
when he said he loved you that first time.
He tells that to all the boys, believe me.
Bob loves me.
It's not a torture kind of thing.
It's pure and beautiful and selfish.
Oh, I love Bob.
Stop, stop, stop telling me you don't love him.
This is what Bob meant when he said,
pull the wool over your own eyes.
I can't see anything.
Oh, I'm going blind.
I'm going blind.
But you can still see Bob in your mind's eye, can't you, Dave?
My mind.
You never stop seeing Bob in your mind's eye.
I can't stop.
Such as it is.
My mind?
What there is of it.
What?
Your mind.
Your mind is no longer your friend.
I'm a physical person.
I'm in love.
I'm in lust.
I'm in love with Bob and I don't care what you say.
I love Bob and Bob loves me.
Bob does love a fool.
That's true.
Bob loves the fools of this world and truly the king of fools.
This lonesome cowboy Dave.
Now performing the greatest guitar solo in the universe.
Rock out, baby.
Play it, Dave.
I don't hear the music, but don't make me go crazy.
What do you mean, which one?
I thought there was always strings.
And you see, friends, you'll see how the love of Bob has freed Dave from that
mental state of mind.
He's a real life around him.
He pays no attention to, uh, the, what other people might think of him.
Sure they think he's a, a, a fool, an idiot, a bad person.
There's a half-janger.
I'm blue value.
But he's happy.
You can hear the simple happiness in his voice.
He's a form of things.
I, I can't begin to express how happy I am when I think about it.
Oh, don't think about it.
You won't be so happy.
You'll stop and think about it.
Now, will you, Dave?
Why are my pants all wet and what's wrong with me?
And how come I can't close my mouth or open my eyes?
And why doesn't Bob ever call a writer, answer my letters, or leave anything on my message
machine?
You're not losing your faith now, are you, Dave?
That would be a great sin, a grievous sin indeed.
To lose one's faith.
To lose one's faith in Bob.
I'm so sorry, Dave.
No.
I'm not that good.
He has no faith in Bob.
Bob has no faith.
He has no faith.
Meaning, he only has a head.
He cannot have a faith in a head.
It's what to the words of God.
Jonas had two faces on his head.
Neither one of them were looking at the same thing at the same time.
Bob Eggo and them.
Bob?
How?
It was an accident.
Bob kills pigs dead.
Bob.
kill big dead Bob kill big dead Bob kill big dead Bob kill big dead kill
angry
killed Kunst
killed downwards
Volleyball
saw
Who
kill big dead
Brand
bomb
skill
heat
that
tää
Bob, Bob, Bob's, Bob's own Bob's head.
Bob, Bob's, Bob's own Bob's head.
Bob struggled again for air while smelling his rank body odor.
Bob knew it was wrong.
Bob, Bob, Bob.
A beer and a good laugh and then a good night's sleep.
My bourbon Kentucky.
Bob, Bob.
Too much beer.
Bob asked, how is your daughter?
I would ask her, but she's still unconscious.
Bob, Bob.
Some big punk something out of a nightmare.
Fly legs and spider heads through his brain.
One sip and I'm gone.
Oh my God.
Then he got down to it.
Bob, perfect round black hole.
Bob, entry positions in the rear.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Bob, Bob's, Bob's own Bob's head.
Oh my God.
might remember Bob, Bob's own tragic moment.
Holy shit.
I never cried.
Behind a knife well, old school in college with noviolog.
Captain detective equivalent.
I finally remembered all my horny defects.
Do it.
And it drew me to come see.
And the sewage, it formed a message.
It said 13013.
I then heard a voice from Doves Town
Gently saying, follow me.
There's a froth farm down the valley
There's a froth farm past the rain
There's a froth farm in your sorrows
When your mind is going insane
There's a froth farm when you're burdened
There's a froth farm where you stray
There's a froth farm, heavenly froth farm
For kill me, it is safe
Sometimes my friends forsake me
And I'm tempted to despair
When I summon
When I summon my friends
And I hear
You would pay to know exactly
What it is you really think
And I'll guarantee you, my brother
You are probably hoping
There's a froth farm down the valley
There's a froth farm past the rain
There's a froth farm in your sorrows
When your mind is going insane
There's a froth farm when you're burdened
There's a froth farm where you stray
There's a froth farm, heavenly froth farm
For kill me, it is safe
Thank you.
Big, pure love.
I love you.
That's all, folks, for now.
Yes, dear friends.
We've been
collecting old Bob songs
from 2008 to today
lately, because we haven't assembled
our yearly Bob song album since
2007.
And I'm going to give some credits
here as soon as
I put you on
by putting on Lonesome
Cowboy Dave.
It sounds so different
and far away.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, I'm
in a pickle tonight.
Really?
Yeah, I'm in a natural
kosher dill pickle right at this moment.
See, I have
come in contact with various
extraterrestrial entities.
I've heard that before.
Beings. I don't know if they're the nephilim
or the nephilim or whatever it is
or anything like that.
But give me secret arcane sciences
to which I can
tap into at any time.
It's a brotherhood of
swine.
You know, there's a mentally ill guy
who leaves me a message saying pretty much
the same thing on my phone
40 or 50 times
a week.
He also sends you pictures of himself
walking around in an athletic supporter
or nothing else, I think.
I wish.
No, we haven't seen anything like that, Dave.
But is
what you're saying, is what that song
that we just heard said, which is
that not even Bob can save you now?
No.
Yes.
I don't like that.
I don't like it either.
In fact, it makes me want to sing my
I Love My Nipples song,
which I just recorded a couple days ago
and I really wanted to play, but I'm
at six now, which goes like this,
but it's not very, very interesting.
My little fucking crab lice.
It's doing themselves to here.
Did you hear that, did you?
I heard something about crab lice.
Oh, boy.
I hope.
I heard my song.
I love to sing to my nipples.
I love to sing to my knees.
All sandwiches were made for sucking.
Big hairy pimples were hocking.
Put down in the trees.
What's going on?
Is this like a new wire recording that you made, Dave, using actual wire?
That's pretty hard to hear.
Did you cut me off?
No.
No, I was about to.
Yeah, I didn't blame you.
I wouldn't blame you after hearing the first parts.
Also, I hope I didn't let a dirty word flip by there.
I hope not, too.
I couldn't really understand any of it.
I hope not, three.
I have to do credits.
Yeah, friends, let's backtrack just a second.
Hold on, Dave, while I explain a couple of things.
As I said, we've been collecting old Bob songs together to make new Bob song albums,
which we will put on the internet.
Because nobody buys CDs anymore.
And the instrumental we were just listening to was When the Saucers Come by Brain Leak.
And I don't know whether that was Reverend Brain Leak, son of Kay Wren and Eggplant,
but they're in our thoughts anyway.
They sure are.
Before that, a song, the Bluegrass song, A Frop Farm in the Valley,
was the Mutant Mountain.
The Mutant Mountain Boys recorded it last X day.
Before that, a weird thing about Bob's body odor was by Heart Ignition.
The little chant, Bob kills pinks dead,
was the Swingin' Love Corpses from Dr. Philodrumon and his relatives back in the day.
We heard, I love Bob and Bob loves me by Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
And Einstein's Secret Orchestra recorded the year at WCSB about 100 years ago.
Sounded like babies.
Yeah, we all sounded like babies.
That was the Baby Dave and the Baby Stang and the late Baby Chaz playing.
There was a weird collage-y thing called, well, it was by Christian Blatter.
It was very collage-y and rocky.
And before that, Mutant Mountain Boys again, with the song Bob is Watching You,
recorded in the parking lot of the Beachland Ballroom by yours truly at a devotional.
And the song Dread Dobbs, the reggae Bob's hymn, was by Lost Souls Incorporated.
We also heard PR News and Intro by Lemur.
And Slackmaster Sarcastro did a little $1 collage.
And praise Bob, and now we're back.
So stay tuned on subgenius.com for new Subgenius Bob song albums.
Okay.
The final slice of Jabberwock was near heard, too, by the way.
Aw.
Little snippets and snipes and little perpendicular angles that everybody can crawl out of and go,
my brain hurts.
Does your brain hurt, friend?
Does your brain leak?
Does your brain weep and dribble like as heard here on Microphone 2?
That's your cue.
No, Dave.
Does your brain gently weep?
It's only one thing you can do.
Make a punishment hole of about 15 yards by 20 degrees in diameter
and place the unborn snippet in the bottom of the barrel.
After reducing it down to a fine powder and an ilky substance remains,
then it is time to take out and complete the albedo portion.
The Raccoon.
Once a...
Magma!
How you doing, Magma?
Do you...
Do you force it on now?
Is it later?
Yes, it's later and now.
Well, you've done slack thought.
You've removed yourself from the temporal thermometer.
That's the reason why you can say that.
But you can't say it again because you've already said it twice.
So if you go back and forth and back and forth,
then time starts up again.
That's true.
Did Bob back in time you, Dave?
Did he come along and back in time you?
Did he?
Yeah.
He came, he snuck up from back in time me
and jumped into the future as well at the same time.
That's when the permissive organs came out.
I had to bomb for you.
Permissive organs!
I know about those.
I'm still hurting from those permissive organs, Dave!
of Bob.
He's the one who gets permission
and you are the one who are forced to obey the rules.
That's what I don't like about it.
But there's a lot of things I don't like about it.
I think Bob's smarmy.
You know what I mean?
Well, that's just the...
You know that pallid mug with the drool
and, you know...
Oh, he's just old-fashioned.
You know, that's just the way people of his generation are.
He's a little older than us.
Yeah, we do the pipe and spit.
Tip your hat.
Tip your hat to women.
These people in the 1950s
still had the habit of tipping hats,
which they wore,
at women walking or, you know,
people walking down the street.
What?
You know, what?
That's like, you know...
Well, in those days,
the hats weren't stapled onto the wearer's head
like the fashion is now,
or sewn on.
Yeah.
The bottom fuses are what confuse a lot of people.
The fact that all those parts are soldered together
now, they're not, you know, discreet parts.
Well, I think usually the reason they sew the hat on
or shave the head
is to hide the fact that they are balding.
It's as simple as that.
It's just vanity.
If you shave your head bald,
then nobody can tell you're balding.
And if you wear a hat all the time,
nobody can tell how bad your haircut is.
That's why I wear that blue hat all the time.
Yes, but you're not balding.
You're just...
You're thinning a little bit.
You're receding a little bit,
but you're not balding.
You don't understand the abject misery and pain
of having a bald pate.
Not completely, no.
No.
No, is it miserable, Dave?
Is it really that bad?
Oh, yes.
It's, you know, like you try to pick up a girl at a bar
or maybe in a playground or something,
and the first thing that comes out of your mind
is,
do you got a bald?
Or you make some bald joke or something.
You're balder than I am.
Or something like that.
You're drawing attention to your disability,
your infirmity, your deformity.
Let's go ahead and be...
Come on, let's face it.
If you're balding,
that just means you're weak, inferior.
Whatever happened to bald is sexy?
I don't understand.
Oh, well, that's what the bald people invented.
The balding people invented bald is sexy.
But of course.
Then they shaved all their hair off,
and now all of a sudden it's sexy.
Yes.
All the young boys shave their heads.
Women are attracted to bald men
if they're...
like a father or uncle was bald.
Nobody in their family was bald.
They view it as a handicap.
But the style that my nephew thought up
never caught on
where young men would shave
just the top of their heads
and leave the row going all the way around
from ear to ear.
Like a monk, right?
Yes, like a monk.
It's a beard on top.
Yes.
Yeah, I could have a little goatee
on the top of my head and a little mustache.
Our friend sent tentatively a convenience.
A great...
He wrote the Performance Art 101 book.
Yes.
Tentatively, for a long time,
wore his hair cut in mustaches.
He had a...
In fact, he appears in a rise that way.
Yes, he had mustaches all over his head.
Yeah.
He looked like Alfred Jari.
He drank too much absinthe,
and that's why his brain putrefied.
Well, now, tentatively later,
he shaved the mustaches off of the top,
off of his head,
and had a brain tattooed on there
so that it looked like, you know,
he had a...
He was not a skinhead, but a brainhead.
He looked as if the top of his skull
had been removed
if the tattoo was a little more realistic.
Now, he has a full head of hair now,
so you can't see his brain.
But if he shaved his head off...
If he shaved his head off,
you'd be able to see his brain
if he then shaved the hair off of the head.
Yes.
There's no mistaking...
Well, I'm sure that it was a false brain.
I'm sorry I didn't hear you.
Right.
It wasn't his real brain.
It was just an image, a simulacrum,
a facsimile of a brain.
A simulacrum...
A drawing of a brain.
...of a better brain is what I heard,
of an actual superior brain.
Well, I think he asked him...
He said, can you draw more convolutions?
Because I've got...
In reality, he had kind of a smooth noodle map,
like all of us subgeniuses.
Mm-hmm.
So he...
He had him roughing it up
in the brain tattoo on his head.
But there's no concealing
his purple and green eyebrow tattoo.
Is that a tattoo?
I believe so.
One is green and one's purple.
I thought the hair was just dyed.
I think he has green and blue
on one of his eyebrows.
Now, it would be really cool
if he could have a green eye and a blue eye
and they weren't contacts.
He'd be like Frankie Stein.
Yes.
Our girlfriend on Monster High.
Or David Bowie.
Oh, that's fake, though.
No, no.
Is he really deformed that way?
He was born with two different colored eyes.
Well, well, well.
So...
I was aware once of a person
born with these yellow eyes.
And he had no problems with vision or anything,
but the eye was yellow.
And I'm going to shut up now.
You mean the pupil of the eye was yellow?
The central part?
No, not the pupil.
The pupil.
No, the part that's hazel blue or brown.
The iris.
That guy's yellow.
That was yellow.
The yellow rat bastard.
Now, I knew...
I met a guy standing in line selling...
That's all you could tell.
Once in...
The weekend after the Heaven's Gate,
people killed themselves.
I was standing and selling subgenius goods
outside a survival research lab show in Austin.
And a guy walked up to me and conversed with me.
We had intercourse, you might say.
He had...
Double pupils in his eyes.
His eyes were very, very strange.
It was like something out of Ripley's
Believe It or Not catalog.
It really didn't look right.
I'm serious.
He had...
You could say he had four pupils on his two eyes.
Goodness.
And he was associated with Heaven's Gate.
No.
This just happened to be...
I'm just...
I'm dating it by...
Saying that.
I guess it was 1995.
Anyway, he...
I said,
Wow.
That must really impress the ladies.
And he said...
He got a really, really sad look on his face.
And he goes,
No, I wish.
But it has just the opposite effect.
It creeps him out.
It was very sad.
I thought it was pretty cool, but...
His vision wasn't good.
And he didn't...
Get...
Picked up in bars because of his double pupils.
He never met any fellow beautiful mutants.
Right.
Think if he'd gone to X-Day.
Yes.
They'd be beaten.
He'd have to beat them off.
Yes.
And blast them.
The living dead.
But he...
There's an alternative story about the Heaven's Gate cult.
Heaven's Gate?
Long before they were known as Heaven's Gate,
they were peeping poop or something like that.
Oh, yeah.
Bo and Pete.
And they appeared with pretty much the same rigmarole
and the same thing that they were going to lay on everybody.
Yeah.
And they were at some function at University of Florida in Gainesville.
And there was a person there
who later became a friendly enemy
and an anemic friend at the same time
who had half of his face look like classical handsome Joe,
like right out of some book of like, you know,
a Greek statue or something like that.
Mm-hmm.
And the other half of his face,
his face looked like Melton, man.
It was like all drooped out.
I guess, you know,
there were some things wrong there and stuff like that.
Uh-huh.
And it was very bizarre.
And I'm not making fun of handicapped people,
but it was really strange
with the way Heaven's cult,
that cult,
treated the meeting
and the bunch of people
that kind of like were weird looking that were there.
And it was very, very creepy.
Creepy.
I mean, the meeting was creepy.
Like, they were like,
they would sit there with their eyes closed
and somebody would be the spokesman guy
and say this stuff.
Maybe they'd nod once in a while or something.
And it looked like they were having this,
you know, communication,
this psychic communication between each other.
And then, you know,
it was very, very creepy
and attracted all kinds of strange people.
I'm sorry, I quit.
Well, when they were traveling around touring
and trying to recruit people
for their castration death cult,
which they had fun doing, apparently,
they all seemed to be very into it.
They came through Dallas
and a friend of mine
who was kind of a new agey feller
and interested in the unknown
and the remarkable
and he was gullible as hell,
let's just face it.
He went and saw him
and he came back
and he told me about it.
He said, man, I'm thinking about leaving Dallas
and moving to El Rancho,
whatever it was,
in California with these people.
And they,
I,
he had a flyer from him
and it was just cram-packed with tiny print
like kook flyers should be,
like ours are.
And I studied it
and I said,
man, I think this is the Bo and Pete people,
the UFO contactees
that were telling everybody the world was going to end.
It's a silly idiot.
They thought it wasn't going to be July 5th, 1998.
They had some other silly,
ridiculous, superstitious date.
So,
I said,
here,
I read up on Bo and Pete
because I think this is the same people.
And he read up on them
and he called me back the next day
and he said,
thanks for saving my mind.
I'm not going to join him anyway.
And,
now he had gone,
he had videotaped their meeting
and when the Heaven's Gate suicides happened,
he went,
wow,
those were the people I almost joined
that Reverend Stang taught me out of joining,
but I've got a videotape of them.
And he sold it to CNN for $15,000
and they never showed it
because it was really boring and stupid.
But,
here's what happened to Herf Applewhite,
also known as Doe,
the cult leader of the silly Heaven's Gate people
who could have been subgeniuses
and waited for the end of the world
without cutting off their reproductive organs
and actually probably would have met
some more interesting nerds
than the nerds they met in Heaven's Gate
because anybody,
you know,
who joined Heaven's Gate
would believe the dumbest stuff,
whereas somebody who joined Church of the Subgenius,
they'll believe everything.
Dumb and smart.
But,
I don't believe I'm going to be shaving my nads off
like some silly saucer cultists do.
Nay.
Best not.
How many can I shave off anyway?
I mean,
you know,
you should get down to the last thing.
I mean,
luckily,
I've got plenty of other organs
that still roll all over the place, so.
Yeah,
well,
trepanation is a far more skillful art and craft.
Cutting a hole in your head
and maybe letting your brain breathe a bit.
Clearing the lid,
as it were,
over the third eye.
It does have its benefits
and it's way, like,
beyond the applesauce.
It's like,
you know,
people like that and stuff.
I think it's far.
L. Ron Hoover.
Yeah.
Joe Hoover.
L. Ron Swaggart.
L. Ron Tilton.
And L. Ron Enron.
That was the rich one.
Yes.
So, yeah.
Yeah, man.
Yeah.
So, Dave,
did you hear the beginning of the show?
I've been trying to assemble
new Bob song albums.
Back in the day,
we used to put out a new one every year or so
because there was so much music piling up.
And no one bought them.
But it was great hour of slack stuff.
And we quit because no one bought them.
We kind of just quit compiling them.
But then people started,
instead of buying CDs,
now they buy downloads off the internet.
And people started begging for stuff
they could download more,
besides just this show.
So, we've been unearthed.
Everything are ancient Bob song albums
that go all the way back to the 80s
and they were on cassette tape.
And I went through every hour of slack since 2008,
about a month ago,
for several days.
And I pulled out everything that looked like a song
from all those hours of slack.
And there were some that you had done
in the studio here
that we all forgot about.
Buried treasure.
But I've been ripping them out again.
And some of them are remarkably well CSB produced.
The old studio there had a nice,
fog-warm sound.
Yeah.
And we made nice CD-quality recordings in there.
And we always glib and came up with something,
you know, that hit the spot at the right time.
And, oh, we could walk back then
without that jumble-baggy,
I mean, the infirm and age.
And we could sing without worrying
about our stomachs jumping out.
I don't know those were the days.
Back in those days,
we had to have special filters
to make us sound old and raggedy.
And now we can do it just without any filter at all.
Yeah.
An extra pack of cigarettes a day,
that's all it takes.
Well, Princess, we,
earlier at the beginning of the show,
I was playing this really old stuff
from ESO radio from the 90s.
And it had you and me very clearly.
But I didn't sound like me.
And you didn't sound like you.
It was us.
But it was like these little babies talking.
There wasn't that extra micro crackle in the voice
that we get from the 25 years of cigarettes.
It comes with gender
and difficulties with reimbursing your age
and stuff like that.
I talked to all the people at the Social Security Agency,
but I didn't, you know,
talk to them in person or call them or anything.
I was just kind of like,
put it on the side,
like a hotline.
And I got a call in about 25 minutes
saying that everybody,
not just you and we or me,
we're all being pushed under the,
you know, with a great sidesweeper.
This is going to do away with us all.
Well, no, that's called death.
That's called old age and death, Dave.
And that happens to large mammals
on this particular planet.
It's probably a good,
it's a good thing too.
In the long run,
for the younger ones anyway,
not so good for us older large mammals,
but hey, you know.
No.
You got to make room for the next life form,
whatever it may be.
Squibbins, gibbons.
It's a rather primitive,
primitive way of doing things.
I mean, if you were doing the schematics for it,
you know,
you just have a common recycling,
this being come into existence
and then at some certain point in time,
you sort of,
you know,
you're going to have to do it again.
It may be primitive.
It may be rough.
It may be,
it may not go down well
in the polished ears of the modernist,
but that's what God's plan was.
That was the way God set it up.
It may be a survival of the fittest
and God was the fittest of all.
So he's the only one that gets to survive.
Everybody else.
I drew my finger across my throat
for listeners purposes.
There, I did it again.
Yes, he did it.
Nice.
I did it too.
We did it to ourselves, man.
And I also went one year like Vincent van Gogh.
You know,
we can sit around and blame the conspiracy,
but we did it to ourselves,
just like Vincent van Gogh.
Nobody bought his art.
That was because his art wasn't any good
and no one bought a single piece of his art
while he was alive.
Now,
his mirror scribble sells for $5 million in Japan,
but obviously it must not be very good.
I don't know.
I didn't buy any when it was fresh and new.
I thought it was weird and self-indulgent.
They didn't have eyes to see.
And look at Cezanne of the same school of art
and they just couldn't hit it off
because she was so crazy.
And Cezanne was not crazy.
Oh, never mind.
Well, they're crazy in different ways.
It's like the subgeniuses
mostly can get along with each other for a while,
but there's always one subgenius
subgenius seemingly put on the earth
just to drive one other subgenius
literally
insane.
I am that subgenius.
For some people.
Not all people, but for some.
Definitely.
Yes. So he's
written, so is it moat or smote,
whichever it is. Smote it be. Smote be it,
baby. If you got him, smote
him.
Most of the subgeniuses with the
rather large cranial areas and
stuff like that and the very, very small jaws
want to be the
next high epoch and scribe guy.
They want to take your place like they think
they could join your fun
house and come into
your palace and become
the king. I don't understand
how that works. Hydrocephaly does not an
overman make, but $35?
I don't know.
Maybe. No calls
to action here. I'm just saying.
Just points of information.
If you want to prove you're below
a genius, you know
what to do, friends.
Subgenius.com
There is a way to make it official.
Right. Official. To prove
that you are not
suitable for Mensa.
We can
sell you a piece of paper that
proves that your mind is not okay.
Well, the only people
who have pieces of paper that says their mind
are okay is people who've been
in the loony bin and then got released.
Do you have a piece of paper that says
your mind is okay? No, I do not have this.
I have one that says my brain is normal
physically, but that's not the same as
saying your mind is okay.
No, it's not the same. Your brain and mind
are different. You're talking about the physical organ
of your brain, not what's inside of it.
Look at Dave. His brain is perfectly good.
I know. Yeah, your organ is
actually like your clavimedus or your
snot nostril or something like that.
It's the place that you like to vacuum
when you get the urge to clean
up the place. However,
on the other hand,
subgenius membership is more like a
map to the
infernal regions, and you
learn a lot there.
Yeah, you learn what not to do. That's for
sure. But by then, it's too late.
Welcome to hell.
That was good cackle there, Princess Wade.
Did you learn that in Wiccan school
when you were a young lady?
Or did you learn that in that Catholic private
school?
I went to. She went to both. She went to
Wiccan school and Catholic school.
I went to Episcopalian school
and
the school of very, very
hard rocks. No, I graduated
just barely.
It's high school.
And there were no girls in it.
I don't think anybody
did much better than barely graduating from
Ponson. Yeah? Yeah.
But let's not go any further
into that now.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
And bounce back and forth
to different types of deformities
that people like to create
and shine up
like a silver hump
on a hunchback's neck.
You know?
Most hunchbacks
don't get the silver hump. They just get a little
brass hump or even a plastic hump.
Man, 50 years gets you
the silver hump for
beyond the retirement party they throw, too.
I guess they have, like, these huge wires
standing from the ceiling,
and some are hot and some are not.
And different contestants or the entries
or the attendees of the conference
all stand up on the bus tables, you know,
where they're serving the salmon and everything like that.
And once the piggies dance, boy,
a couple of them get fried real good.
At least I never attended, but I'd heard about it.
When you're recounting things like that,
Princess, we and I look at each other across the studio
with kind of a puzzled look on our face,
like, maybe when we play it back later.
Later is coming pretty soon, actually.
I was cocking my head like a small dog,
just trying to figure out what it was,
that you were saying about salmon and trays
and wires coming from ceilings.
Must have been a cocker spaniel.
Yes.
Well, it's like the Humpin' Baby Cakes parade
they have every, you know, post-St. Patrick's Day
or something like that,
to show some sort of spiritual ancestry
or some kind of...
Humpin' Baby Cakes.
Is that a tie-in with the Silver Hunchback or what?
And we...
By the way, I hope there's no Hunchback listeners
who think we're making fun,
because we are Monster High.
We are.
Monster High.
Yeah, we're the ghoul kids rule.
So, you know, we're cool with all your deformities and stuff.
To us, they're just marks of superiority
over the Mirhumes and the Normworms.
We are Monster.
The Barbies and Kens.
We are proud.
The Mediocratons.
The Pink Boys.
Yep.
My eyebrows or any of those parts of my body
are not purple,
but I can sure do a good job of pretending.
And that's what I do every day.
I'm...
Pretending, you know, my eyelids are purple
or that I'm balder than I am or something.
Dave, you don't need purple eyebrows or green eyebrows.
Your eyebrows are perfectly psychedelic
just the way they are.
Well, you know, it just takes a little bit of extra work
in the morning when you're getting ready to go out
and play in the backyard and stuff like that.
You get all dressed up and you shave
and you just, you know,
spend an extra 15 or 20 minutes
working on your eyebrows.
You tweak them.
You pull, you mascara, you rub,
you shave, you unshave,
you comb and you brush.
It's a process that I don't know why I do.
And listeners, you can learn more
about whatever the hell he was going on about
His eyebrows.
by listening back to this show again
because I'll probably have it archived
in MP3 and Augvorbis in different formats
tomorrow or the next day
like we always do with every hour of Slack
because you can find, not all of them,
I think the first couple of hundred
are mostly absent from 1985 and 86.
Absent from the annals.
Everything else that we've ever done
called Hour of Slack can be downloaded
from subgenius.com
or someplace you'll find from that
if you want to look there.
I happen to know that most of the radio subgeniuses
don't want to look there.
They don't want to look at our books
and most of the book reading subgeniuses
already know what the show is probably like
so they don't want to be disappointed and hear it.
And the internet subgeniuses
don't know anything about any of it.
All they know is that you spell Bob
with all capital letters and no quotes.
That's how you know the internet ones
where they come from.
So subgenius.com is it, dear friends.
And I guess for our prisoners out there
I should give our post office box
because I haven't done that in a long time.
You can write for free information
from subgenius at post office box
181-417
Cleveland Heights, Ohio
Praise Bob.
And we're going to have to go out now
and make room for some other poor wretch
whose name is Dr. Sinister here in Cleveland.
Thank you.
And, uh...
But we've been lying this whole time.
It's not really all about Bob.
Did you know that?
It's really...
I didn't know that.
Reverend Bill T. Miller, the king of slack,
will tell us
it's really all about Connie.
You want to hear some great music?
I just wanted to make money and have fun.
Hello, doctor.
How are you?
The doctor is on.
You could have a rewarding career
as a subgenius doctor.
That's right.
Surgeons for Connie.
Perform healing orgy-divisible surgery.
Sicken the masses.
Bombard the patient with subgenius anti-fusing noise.
Surgeons for Connie.
Standing by.
Well, I...
Ready to operate.
Scammo.
Goff Club.
Pipe.
Light the pipe full of froth.
And insert the Goff Club into the third nostril of the patient.
And the depro-gaming will begin.
Stop it! Stop it!
Please, I beg you!
You will no longer believe that Connie's little puppet, Jay, are Bob Dobbs.
You will now realize the truth.
That Connie is the one true slack master.
Praise Connie!
Don't worry.
The spurting, bleeding head side effects are part of the treatment.
Now, whenever you hear the name Bob, you will automatically substitute the name Connie.
Oh!
Here we go, there.
WOO!
Oh!
We're even more glad that some listeners have donated enough to help us keep on going for another couple of months.
Not just this show, but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob and want some of that slack back to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com front page or especially the radio page or the catalog store pages
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty,
and we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference, even if it's only once a month from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that blowjobs could go the way of Steve jobs if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to subgeniusfoundation.com.
P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Thanks for anything you can do to help let there be slack.
We'll see you next time.
Money, Bob!
Kill me!
Yes, money, Bob!