Now, you know it's kind of fun to see that good homemade pie.
Ask any waitress and she'll tell you that the small cube of cigarette ashes makes the wonderful difference in flakiness.
Rub a cigarette butt in the palm of your hand.
You'll feel the fleas drop off immediately.
They puff, bubble, and turn into the kind of crust every cook is proud to bake.
Get several packages.
For some unexplained reason, the General Motors Research Laboratories have recently issued a bulletin that adds tenderness and flakiness to your pie crust.
You know, the kind you make every time when you use dry snuff and then brush it thoroughly into the hide.
Well, I guess that should keep you busy over the weekend.
This is the Radio Network.
From PR News in Washington, I'm bombing a television station.
The U.N.'s top emergency relief official says time is running out for denouncing tens of thousands of victims
and quaking.
U.N. emergency chief Jan Egeland says gas rooms aren't deterring 37 people.
The sheriff arrived bundled in sleeping bags prepared for that.
On Wall Street 422-1085, President Bush is forced to balance a deficit-riddled budget in Crawford, Texas.
The British news media have been threatened with persecution if they publish PR news from London.
Speaker 6 hit MPB.
Justin.
Fans not yet teaming with river's specifically
where it means you have to die
Call here
ooh
Hi!
Shhh!
When that's a heavy joke,
Who said that?
Put that slide on!
Now who said that?
Who are you?
Going off nice for you!
Oh, like my face?
That means you did the devil a day later today.
How in tarnation like David Opsiskin!
How's that?
Yeah!
Heh heh heh heh!
Oh, shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
Why?
And I remember the delight with which I devoured it.
Now that I have been reading over all the letters which he wrote to me laboriously with his own hand after the fashion of those days,
I feel that I did not at the time appreciate how much he thought and cared for the
Self-genius,
Powerful,
Smart,
King!
Marr!
You might sit over there on a Monday morning and talk about how Bob got the money,
But I guarantee you Bob's gonna get it!
Bob's gonna pay his bill and then get you to go over and lick your sores on Monday morning!
And I can guarantee you if we said that at one of our radio stations,
The FCC would come down and say,
you have to sit over there and go down and pull the plug!
Bob!
So let's get to it!
The first segment of it for the benefit of those who just arrived we did a few hymns.
We had a little community singing, and we rappled on the first
Self-genius!
Powerful!
Smart!
I see, my name is Bob.
Dr. Lester!
Security!
No, sir, it's a...
It's just a little mix-up with your secretary.
Uh!
She's not my secretary.
She's what they call an executive liaison.
And I'm not banging her, if that's what you're implying.
No, sir, not at all.
I want to speak to you.
Yes?
This morning.
All right.
From distance.
Yes?
Hitler.
And here.
Oh, yes.
And when I speak.
Yes?
And think.
About Hitler.
Yes?
I can't help.
Oh, what about?
Thinking about him.
Yes?
Hitler.
Oh, yes.
And here.
They tell me.
Yes?
That he's a man.
Oh, yes.
Who lives.
Yes?
In a storm.
Oh, yes.
Town.
All about.
Elevator.
Yes, sir.
Service.
Yes?
Go.
From one.
Yes?
Patient.
To another.
Oh, yes.
In his past.
Now.
I'm telling you.
Oh, no, sir.
This morning.
Yes, sir.
And he.
Is the dictator.
Oh, yes.
Of Germany.
Yes, sir.
Hitler.
Oh, yes.
You must come down.
I thank you.
Oh, yes.
As you.
Take that.
Oh, yes.
In your easy chair.
Wine men.
Oh, yes.
It's time.
On the battle seat.
Oh, yes.
Go on.
Um.
Oh.
For years, my daughter Maggie smelled like the cracks in the schoolyard.
Go on.
Well, she finally agreed to let me wash her piano teacher.
So I did.
Go on.
And she just loved it.
She said that it made her smell like her butt crack poo.
Why?
Because she said the poo smelled like her piano teacher.
Smell like the piano teacher.
Are you planning to increase or extend?
The, um, increasing, uh, that, uh.
Are you planning to extend or increase?
Um, but, um, that, that, uh.
Uh-oh.
There was a garden.
There was a tree.
Uh-oh.
And there were three of me.
I was a snake and a crow and a cat.
And in the tree all three of me sat for eternity.
And that was that.
One night,
an apple grew and the apple knew everything that I knew it was part of me and it was part of the
tree the tree that I climbed into and flew into and slithered to and now I grew and there I sat
as an apple and a snake and a crow and a cat and that was pretty much that until one day
a girl who was not me came out to play and I could see what she wanted from me she wanted to
know what the Apple knew and I said you already do my dear otherwise you wouldn't be here and
she said please I've come to eat the apples from the tree
and I said no I am an apple and a snake and a cat and a crow and she said please I need to have that
apple inside of me she wanted to know everything I knew and I said but my dear you already do then
she stamped her foot and said for heaven's sake why can't you be me
a cat and a crow and a snake and I said no let the Apple go then she took a bite and I could tell
that she knew I was right she walked away weeping with the apple in her hand and fed my secrets to
another man so I slid away and flew away and out of the tree I ran I who was once one and I was one
now forever three a cat and a crow and a snake without a tree just a snake and a crow and a cat
and that was that uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh the Billy Nair show did that friends and they like
the amino acids that we're hearing in the background will be at x day nine I'm told
and that song was from their album Return to the Moon and I'm told that it's going to be a good
song to bring a doom you can get more information from Billy Nair.com this is our of slack number
1027. uh happy last year friends the starting collages and the ending ones are by Mr Fernand
although the pre-intro intro was by Department of transmutation and the post-intro intro was by
Reverend Maynard
then Reverend Noel Preff did the Hitler to hell cut up and music did I mention this is the amino
acids in the background but let's get back to the subgenius over the edge puzzling evidence
business retreat on KPFA where puzzling evidence will tell us just what to do next
but right now I think the important thing is to laugh at Hal and 420 guys
recreation back to San Jose
Barbara
help
the
kids were having our own little night of slack I can just see Pedro стать
back
maybe just outside and they can't get the doors
theinison
post office
you know
healthcare
and
each to his and ter 해서
You're right in a hovercraft.
That's real funny.
Yeah, why is that funny?
Because they're on the radio.
Yeah, that makes it funny.
Radio.
Funny how that works.
If I was just sitting at home saying this to myself, nothing, nada, zero zip.
But because I'm on the air.
You think it's incredibly interesting.
And it is.
My life.
To somebody as long as one person.
If we're getting through to even one soul.
That's all that matters.
If we didn't get one soul in Bob's pipe tonight.
Then it's all worth it.
All of it.
The pyramids.
The Statue of Liberty.
The Declaration of Independence.
It's all worth it if you are saved.
I think I want to get one of those little Reese buttercups in the shape of Hal.
I'll get two of those.
Wow.
Just having a little good-natured laugh at the Reverend, Reverend Dr. Hal, who is now, only now, just showing up.
Sure.
He's shown me up so many times.
I dare you to say a Hal-ism.
I doffed my hat to Hal.
We couldn't believe it because we've been following your progress by traffic report.
And that whole, you know, that car crash that killed so many hundreds of people.
What's happening?
Backed up all the way to San Jose.
All the way to San Jose.
And you have to get in the back of the line.
Even if you start in San Francisco, they make you go all the way back to San Jose and come back.
You know, I don't like to complain, but I've got some terrible things going on in there.
Like everybody else.
It's scratched in my ear.
Oh, I think old Reverend Stang.
He's up there in his high hill.
His big couch on the hill up there.
That big fancy trailer of his.
Oh, yeah.
Reverend Stang, you don't have to think about him.
Poor folks down here.
Down there in the salt mines with you.
Wiggly and wonky.
I'm in those salt mines right now.
Under Lake Erie.
It could cave in at any moment.
Or some mutated monster.
The walls, they're going in and out.
We don't know if tomorrow might be X-Day.
We don't know if this is Earth for sure.
Why do you think this is Earth?
I'm all confused now.
Which one's X-Day?
You just read it in a book somewhere.
Some scientist told you.
This is planet Earth.
Yeah, it could be K-Day.
And you're so sure of everything.
Oh, today is this date.
November 25, 2005.
Oh, it must be right.
Oh, this planet.
This must be Earth.
Oh, it's always been the United States of America.
Oh, yeah.
You assume so much.
And you don't know nothing.
You don't know a dang thing.
Nothing.
You don't know nothing?
You don't know less than nothing.
But what was this about Jack Ruby didn't have a molar?
What am I going to do?
And if you insist on being blind,
then why don't you just tear out your eyes
and send them to P.O. Box 181417, Cleveland, Idaho, 44118.
And why is it?
Because Bob loves you!
And puzzling evidence killed him for you.
Yep, sure did.
And what about that?
What is he going to do about it?
What is it like to know that you have to kill Bob?
This is the moment to know that you have to kill Bob.
The warfare is what killed him.
We as people have to kill Bob in our minds.
It's salty out there at night and it's cold.
The guy from Star Trek, his...
He blasted him with some air.
Well, it was his will that he left him a sizable parcel as part of his estate.
Yeah.
And he was the warfare at that time.
But unfortunately after this we had a complete blackout of the records
and we weren't able to run them through our high-powered computer.
Until just a few moments ago when Ivan Stang began his historic broadcast.
And now the results are in.
It looks like Kennedy by a landslide.
That's right.
He is dead by a landslide and...
They're clearing off that landslide now and apparently no one was seriously hurt.
But why did no one try to kill Nixon?
That's the question.
I concede the sacred scribe ship to President John F. Kennedy.
An idiot like Ford, they tried to kill...
We will bear any burden.
...in Cuba.
That's right.
And it's not in Cuba, it's in Vietnam.
What about the prizes here?
We will be a church.
Well, ask Kennedy.
He's the sacred scribe now.
Somebody's going to be awarding the prizes a little later on in the program.
Oh, I thought it was we will accept any prize.
He's known to accept...
...with a ground war that they couldn't win.
We will hold on to any prize.
But Kennedy's policy was special forces in Vietnam.
Yeah, and...
They're very special.
...subgenius forces in Dallas.
Yep.
Where are the tapes with Maryland?
Somehow Kennedy's plan went wrong.
Who has the Maryland tapes?
Yeah, and all the other tapes.
There are many Maryland tapes.
Think of all the tapes.
That's the problem is you have to store them.
So bad guys have warehouses full of tapes.
Well, all the Judah Vickners.
What about the Judah Vickners who had sex with both Giancana and Kennedy?
Buckets of historical walled...
That is why.
...wire tappings.
These are the two most powerful...
Bathtubs.
Mysterious tapping on the walls.
...closetfuls.
Tapping under tables.
Seances.
And warehouses.
And intimate recordings.
And warehouses of every single tape.
Elvis glasses are...
And the...
They're all dangerous.
...entire collection...
It's like this end shot in...
...of Elvis collectible plates.
Citizen Kong.
You can get anything you want.
They're doing a remake of that.
King...
Citizen Kong.
Yeah.
It's a sled at the end.
Oh, Roy Cohn?
Charles Foster Crowe.
What?
Yes.
Charles Foster Kong.
Charles Foster...
The greatest imperialist industrialist of all.
...the eighth wonder of the world.
I really like at the end where he's holding a sled and he says...
Bob Dobbs.
Joe is cuter though, but...
No, it's a plane.
He's holding a plane.
Oh.
Kidding me.
It's named...
I was on drugs...
A plane named Rosebob.
From PR News in Washington, I'm Condemned.
They created a show where police could rely on pro- sjunk, puisqu میijdمون
okol,
As you raise a lever of repentance, you can be aiding you, that's consisteurien ça
Don Mike when you fail.
Ar lamines est
PR news ended yesterday in Washington.
We'll be right back.
On your knee.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Huge.
But I, but I, but I, but I, but I don't, but I don't.
Thick, thick, thick, thick, thick, thick, thick.
Not good.
Yeah.
Chicken hock, chicken hock, chicken hock, chicken hock.
Yeah, I'm one of them.
Really.
Cult, cult, cult.
Cult, cult, cult, cult, cult.
From PR news in Washington, I'm abandoned in the Sahara Desert in Morocco.
The African pregnant children said they were loaded.
Governor Arnold has signed legislation that will bolster kids buying video games with PR content.
PR content.
Governor Arnold said that video games availability is important to him.
This is extremely important.
Meanwhile, authorities in India say.
In India, Indians in India were attributed to road accidents caused by PR news in New Delhi.
Parts of Pakistan are reported to be in ruin after today's PR news.
Now, now, now, now, now, now, now.
The reason this is happening is because of you.
Fun, fun, fun, fun, fun.
Change the country from a secular progressive based philosophical country.
Stand up, stand up, stand up, stand up.
Doubt religion.
That's right, that's right.
You in the middle.
Pure ignorance.
Do that.
From a hatred.
Here's the point.
Accused Bush and Cheney of lying because they wanted Halliburton to make more money.
Smearing on each other.
This kind of crap.
Whip, whip, whip.
I'm talking.
Blame propaganda.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm gonna do it.
Kill us where we live.
Spin zone.
Spin, spin, spin, spin, spin zone.
This kind of crap.
I'm talking.
I'm talking crap.
That was Norelpref, dear friends.
You can get more of that and about that at norelpref.com.
N-O-R-E-L-P-R-E-F dot com.
And before that, a whole bunch of leads.
I'm talking about the
Oh, I had slack!
It was mine all along.
But only now that it's gone do I recognize it.
And do you think anyone had any care for the whinings of a little boy?
Loser.
No, they just laugh with a disdainful leer while you've lost your slack forever.
Kick that weirdo.
Put.
He's not like us.
Look at this poor young lad.
Look at him.
Glasses.
Large was his bounty and his frame sincere.
But when I'm looking, think of the others who might follow his prestigious footsteps.
Can't get a girlfriend.
A youth.
Loser.
Lives with his parents.
Plays with his computer.
Fair silence.
When photos like these are available.
At his humble birth.
Trekkie.
And melancholy Clinton.
At the stamp collector.
Wants to get an Xbox now.
It isn't even spring.
And iPods.
No father seek his merit to disclose or draw their secrets.
No.
I don't come in a blossom to a gelada.
Girls don't come round much.
No, but.
You know, and.
You don't go round them now ever since what happened to Betty Jean.
Only to die.
And so it goes.
The truth he will disclose.
He just kind of works with his computer and just dreams.
Are you going to be like that friend or are you going to let loose the bob in you?
Unbuckle your belt, bend over and let it fly.
Of course, today's more understanding, caring parents don't take off that belt buckle and
flail around the way mom and dad may used to have done.
I know we've all been there, but this is a different generation.
She's pretty.
And, and, and, you know, maybe I can see that dub of the X-Files.
Foolishness is bound in the heart of a child, but the rod of correction shall drive it from him.
I just wish I could think.
I can't think of anything.
The blueness of the wound cleanses away the evil.
Still pictures fly.
The closer to the bone, the sweeter the more.
Do you hear me, mom and dad?
The TV took away the pain.
Do you hear me, subgenius mothers and fathers out there?
The blueness of the wound cleanses away the evil.
I'll just float here for a while.
And more of the same.
Beat slack into that child.
I'll just, I'll just.
This picture is not one typical of a disease.
I won't try to get, get smarter.
I'll just.
A subgenius child is formed in the crucible of pain and blood.
Trying to get smarter.
Magazine.
I hope they don't hit me again.
It approaches another class of magazines.
Now you are pure.
Repeat after me.
Will you, my ward, ever flinch or falter in this life?
Well, I hope so.
I hope so.
Congratulations.
You are now a soldier of Bob.
Now your first assignment is to go out along the 34th Street
and to pick up all the garbage at the left side of the road,
transfer it to these orphanages,
put it in인지 plastic bags here,
and we wanna see you about 2 o'clock in the afternoon
by the water cooler over there.
And we're gonna have some signs we want you to use.
So this is Mr. Schwobler.
He's gonna be your supervisor.
Okay.
Good luck and enjoy being a subgenius son.
Ok.
We're going to knock off for lunch.
Thank you sir.
Thank you.
Yeah, the right man.
I will draw his jigs.
I'll help you.
Ah, wow.
Thank you pretty.
Okay.
That's ...ant specialized.
Thank you Mr. Schwobler.
At first ...
Ahhhh!!!
That's things you can, eh, they are not actually good.
You will want to turn away from him.
Then you may find him a silent, unresisting target for your ridicule.
Mister, why is your head so big, mister?
But if you come to know him...
Have you always been the way you are now?
You will begin to see beyond the perversion of his form.
Are you in any pain? Are your parents still alive?
And discover the beauty in the beast.
At no time have I met with such a perverted or degraded version of a human being as this man.
I am not an animal.
From PR News in Washington, I'm slamming into a tree.
I'm the first of many.
Three or four of them.
Uh, uh.
Here's bad. Here's bad. I'm bad.
Palestinian leader Mahmoud Abbas says this is PR News.
Two people were PR'd on California's busy Highway 101 this morning.
Three people are reported PR'd.
In South Central Nebraska this morning, a moderate earthquake struck several who were trapped inside.
For PR News, I'm in a large portion of Central Nebraska.
New Jersey transit officials predicted New Jersey Turnpike Authority spokesman Joe Orlando would clog major arteries for a six-day period.
Because, uh...
Iraq's President Jalal Talabani is rejecting PR News in Washington.
Al Jazeera. Al Jazeera. Al Jazeera. Al Jazeera.
Rock. Rock.
Bush caused the war and created all these terrorists.
I throw.
Real simple.
Idiotic.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Alright, alright, alright, alright.
Amiga for people.
Gay. Gay.
Gay.
Television.
B.S. B.S. B.S.
Feelgood
B.S.
Art. Art. Art. Art. Art.
Stop the violence.
Go there. Go there.
They Just. Go there.
Stop the violence.
I don't like that.
Amiga for people.
Ho! Yes!
Ho! Ho! Ho!
Did you mean ?
Yes!
Idiotic.
Yes! Yes!
You gonna be k-
Aba. Aba.
Aba.
Protesting abuse.
Abu grab and club get moaned.
Blame Bush for this.
Yeah.
But what were we doing?
I don't care.
Let them take me.
I let them take me.
I don't don't don't don't care anymore.
That cut up was by Nor El-Pef and now one from Reverend Maynard Brainerd.
A person may stay in the anger state, waging an overt or covert war against a company.
If they are going to take money out of my pocket, I'm going to take some of theirs.
One aggravated driver ran his forklift into a tall stack of expensive electronic equipment.
Final damage estimates was in the hundreds of thousands of dollars.
What a darn shame.
Fortunately, the company's leadership team had been anticipating this initiative for several years.
And had been planning accordingly by developing several previous bomb drones, as well as other forms of sabotage that occurred over the past year.
We ended up with a bomb.
We're all set to go!
Hanker state.
Hanker.
erem.
Hanker state.
She quietly went into the cubby room, took the large screwdriver out of her purse, and jammed
the screwdriver repeatedly into the gears and pulleys of the cubby machine, rendering the
expensive machine totally inoperable.
She replaced the screwdriver and her evil eye in my building, thinking to herself, well,
if they are going to take money out of my pocket, I'm going to take some of theirs.
I love you.
I love you too.
From PR News in Washington, I'm Fawlty.
Authorities in Jordan destroyed and damaged and killed.
The Bureau of Statistics says 3,315, 2,059, 3,378, 38, 11, 59, 2,019, 4,36.
PR News in Washington.
PR's bad. PR's bad. I'm bad.
Democratic Party Chairman Howard Dean is going to war in Iraq.
But local officials say all residents have been killed, just to be sure.
Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice had some pointed hardline leaders of PR News in Washington.
I've seen so many movies on this show that I would never have gone to in a movie.
You can see B-movies that you don't have to pay the $10 for Batman.
You can just hear it and imagine a better one.
The Penguin will be here later, by the way.
Oh my God!
What is it coming?
Who? Who?
Who's going to be here?
The Penguin.
The Penguin himself.
The arch-criminal genius.
The real Penguin?
No, that's right.
The real man.
Where is he, by the way?
Not this Bobby De Niro movie guy.
Where is the Penguin?
The real arch-criminal that the Penguin was based on.
It's a real person.
The Batman comic book, of course, popularized this.
They cartooned him up a bit.
But there was a deformed criminal called the Penguin.
Called himself the head of the family.
A big belly like a fat guy?
That's right.
Wow.
That's how you have to say it when you speak about the brow.
But he fancied himself vaguely intellectual in some way.
The Penguin did.
I must say.
The made-in-form brow was a not-so-manly version of the same thing.
I thought the Brow was very true.
But the original brow sent his armies out to collect all those images.
What's his name?
Jim Rowe.
Was that tough interview?
But well, Jim wasn't frank enough, so he belonged to the thing.
He came from Buffett.
He was inilated.
So not him.
No.
That guy he died of reproductions.
That book is one of those pre-Jones verf 높 la sinistrinuv hid it in the を
So this is what it is.
It's this one here you see.
The Term of a prosecutor.
If Jim Rowe was about to make the case, it would have been published in begin-up.
It would be.
It was in 19.
No sir no sir.
Yeah taboo.
It's been published many years back.
Liby was out.
and they have children.
It's really an amazing movie.
Versus Penguin.
In a sub-cinematic way.
The Riddler.
Bob Dobson.
No, the Riddler won't be here.
Nina Hagen.
Nina Hagen won't be here.
She doesn't remember much about subgenius anymore.
I don't either, actually.
I was invited to her house to do Acid.
The night of the 85 shows in the back.
I was taken to the Charles Manson.
The Beatles.
No, she just invited me.
Wait a minute.
Which side is good?
The B side.
Your mom.
Because Bob may also be there.
Because that's the most good thing.
I thought I could do that.
I wanted to get some brow tickling.
Your mom.
Exactly.
What about your mom?
She had this whole staff that traveled with her.
I was tempted, though.
Boy.
What about your mom?
What could you learn from Gary Cabrogfram's mother, Nina Hagen?
He likes Bob, then.
Gary Cabrogfram's mother is Nina Hagen.
That's probably why you're a subgenius today.
Wow.
How'd that happen?
It's like a sandbox.
In a laboratory.
Ten people talking at odds.
Jody's father is named Bob.
Really?
Bob?
Ginger and Jody's father are both named Bob.
You do Bob with your uncle.
You can get to where you hate that name.
That's real funny.
Bob.
Hilarious.
Stick a pipe in it.
Stick a pipe in it and charge $500,000.
It's odd.
That's odd.
Look in his eye as he gives you your instructions.
Pretty hot.
Bob's afterbirth.
Yes.
Oh, now you're talking.
Oh, my mouth is watering.
Did you know that Bob Dobbs was an abortion survivor?
Yes, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
What?
The son of...
Jesus.
Gamera.
Jane McBride Dobbs, the sainted mother.
She tried to abort.
What?
The infant Bob because she wasn't really supposed to be pregnant.
Well, it was supposed to be.
But, unfortunately, the tenacious fetus hung in there and was not actually successfully aborted until Jane McBride Dobbs was strapped down in a Kansas wheat field in front of a tornado's path.
The tornado was able to extract the tiny infant Dobbs.
Susan Sarandon.
But then, when Jane saw the preemie Dobbs laying in that field panting and bleeding, she, of course, loved him.
She could no longer go through with the abortion, and she loved him as do all whose eyes fall upon him.
And she took Bob home and raised him.
So, friends, remember, the next time you're getting an abortion, just think about Bob.
If they'd successfully aborted him, then maybe we wouldn't...
We wouldn't have a church in the subgenius.
We wouldn't have.
Maybe that's an argument for abortion.
I don't know.
I'm going to go out and get one right away.
We would have no reason to exist.
I'm going to go.
We wouldn't have slack.
Philo's abortion.
Well...
That was a great band, Philo's abortion.
Yeah, they were...
I got proud when they broke up.
Philo's, oh...
You know, I was almost aborted, actually.
Were you?
I was.
It was a...
Wishful thinking.
It was a partial abortion.
...to term with a cancer.
And they said...
I'm not on Bob.
They said...
First, they said it's a cancer.
He was about 35.
And then they said, no, it's not a cancer.
It's breathing.
And then the third opinion was...
It's cancer.
I'm not on Bob.
And because it was a Catholic doctor, they didn't abort me.
And, I mean, the cancer died.
That was a great song, Abort Me.
The baby died, but I was born.
You can...
I'll be buried, of course.
And, no, that's a true story.
The twin...
My mother was brought in, and she...
Robert Pepe.
She deliberately went to a Catholic doctor.
That means her father pulled out.
Beware ye the Jesse Pepe ghost.
Weren't you one half of Simon Quinn?
Which hovers just behind Michael Pepe.
Michael Pepe.
Hating him for living.
When he, the twin Jesse Pepe, had the doctor.
I want a clone, Bob.
This is PR.
PR.
Support for PR.
R.
Comes from institutions worldwide.
Helping to develop PR.
R.
Institution radio.
Coming our way this Wednesday at 2 minutes till 8 o'clock.
The Club of R.
Radio presents Beethoven's first comments on his career in Bolo and in Clever.
Right here on 93 489 FM.
It's 60 50 40 60 22 96.
With partial credit.
Partial East.
In the West.
If we didn't have abortion, we'd have no Social Security.
Better economics.
Free free free free.
Pain pain pain pain.
My obvious Freakonomics.
How tricky it is.
Racism should be supported.
Immoral.
Wrong.
Not to abort all children and prevent all crime.
That's what we're talking about.
Sensitive area.
We're showing the phallus.
Phallus.
Impossible.
Ridiculous.
Keep yelling about it.
I want a bone Bob.
Bob.
Uh.
You want a bone Bob?
I don't know where he is.
And I don't know nothing about nothing.
She said she wanted a bone Bob.
I was born.
Everybody wants to bone Bob.
Bone Bob.
Look at it this way friends.
I want a bone Bob's bones.
As Reverend Angry Larry pointed out.
Bob is just one O short of boob.
And everybody.
He loves boobs.
That's his favorite.
So get with it man.
Hey.
What?
Bob is hung like a hamster.
Get with the time.
Oh that's not true.
That is not true.
A 50 foot hamster.
It's not the size of the bone.
How many pubes does Bob have in his church?
Pubes?
How many do you have?
You.
Pubes.
Or pubes.
You.
Oh.
Pube.
There's three.
43 and a quarter.
A week is four.
Say.
Say about 10,000.
Billions.
10.
Billions and lot wielands.
Billion.
Billion right now.
We want to get once this man.
He does not understand why we are per writes.
February 18, 1843, a fakebat Chanel Beat.
The Wu 된房 of Wu Yandong is a popular program of Hu than Jaguars.
Last has.
Zu recovery.
David Moros昨.
Former Black alumni were好像.
military secret PR news reported that the suspects were identified as Yamin Larbi.
Israeli Prime Minister Ariel Sharon would no longer be able to use drugs. Sharon does
not want to reach peace with the Palestinians because Palestinian parliamentary party paper
piece parrots playing politics plan to postpone the pain of possessing PR news in Washington.
So, which of life's mysteries do you wish to be solved?
Oh, all the other ones except for this one.
All right. Well, we'll do what we can.
Now, is it pecan or pecan?
That's what we want to know.
Pecan.
Oh, okay. All right. Well, what about Al-Qaeda or Al-Qaeda?
For 10 minutes on one side, then turn and cook on the other side.
That's what I've been saying, Al-Qaeda. So, you say Al-Qaeda, I say...
What is right for your guests?
You say Bin Laden, I say Bin Laden.
Why, of course.
Bin Laden, Bin Laden, Al-Qaeda, Al-Qaeda, let's call them all...
In Al-Qaeda, they beat up.
Well, how madly amusing.
I don't know. That's a good question caller.
Is it Grenada or Grenada?
Should we invade Grenada? Should we invade Bin Laden? Should we invade Al-Qaeda?
Oh, by this mother and father.
Should we invade our mother and father?
Folks, we're here to give you answers, not questions.
I have a plot reserved for Osama Bin Laden.
He's associated with two CIA contractors. Well, CIA contractor, David Ferry.
That's right. That's right. Ferry. Not Brian, but David Ferry, who worked with the Cubans.
And, of course, what is the most interesting thing is the fact that one man did give his life for Kennedy,
and that man is Sam Giancana.
Now, all this stuff about JFK, you're talking about?
Giancana gave his life for the US Senate because it was on the way to testify at the hearings for JFK's death
that Giancana was killed in his sleep.
1975, it was a shot to death.
Why?
Beat by the other mafia, who didn't want him talking about their role in the assassination of the President,
the president. Why is that? Because they didn't want to get in trouble with the government.
But why? Then why did Connie do this? This is Connie? No, this is why the mob hit Sam
Giancana. So the mob assassinated him? Yeah. You keep saying that so fast, it just sounds
like Connie to me. No, Connie, that's because that's what's on my mind when I'm thinking
about Tommy. Tommy or Connie? I'm thinking about Tommy a little, not really so much,
but Connie, because she who is all women. Would he be a Connie or a Connie? As usual,
the women have been driven from the show. And Darrison said the implementation of your
assassination occurred in my jurisdiction. I will put one on the phone for you at your
discretion. Yeah. Oh, okay. Hold on. All right. But they better be sexy because this is the
subgenius. John is alive. Johnny is still alive. He is? He really was not shot. Did
you, did you, have you, how do you know him? It was a figment of every opinion.
Yes. The most handsome man in American history. And of course his son, the most handsome man
in the world. He's alive, I tell you. Yeah. Yeah, but where is he? He's in a wheelchair
in Bermuda, right? Yeah. Well, that's, that's. I can see him. He took, yeah, that's, that's
the other thing is that he like took a, took a taxi secretly away from the, the promenade.
Away from the pool of blood. Yeah. And the large piece of hair. And the, uh.
That's just another. And he zoomed away and he took a, Kennedy was the one that took the
cab into Fort Worth. You know. And Kennedy was the one who shot himself in the grassy
knoll. Right. That's the secret. That's the other thing is that he had been depressed
at the end. And, uh, but pay no attention to that. You know. All right. Yeah. Just forget
that stuff. Forget. It's too frightening to comprehend. I forgot. See what happens? You
get caught up in echo loops. What?
You just get. Yeah, that's right. And you never get away from it. That's right. I'd
like to show. How many shots were there in Gilly Plaza? But you can help these children
by killing the Prime Minister and the ministers. Yeah. Let's talk about Prime Ministers. That's
at least a little bit different. Um, no. And now it's time for a book review, friends.
And a confession. Uh, the review is about the book Ultimate Sacrifice by Lamar Waldron
and, uh, my friends for 10 years, I, Reverend Ivan Stang, have been part of the JFK coverup.
Uh, I can heave a big sigh of relief now because now it can be told and has been in that book,
Ultimate Sacrifice. You know, the JFK assassination is like the Bible. Whatever be is in your bonnet,
whatever you want to prove, if you're a kook, you're a kook.
Your proof is in the JFK assassination. If you're a Warren Commission kook or a case-closed nut,
you won't like the Ultimate Sacrifice. Uh, if you're an Oliver Stone version, the CIA did it
kook, you won't like the Ultimate Sacrifice. But if you're a mafia did it, but how'd they get away
with it kook like I am, this book explains pretty much how and why they got away with it. And it
doesn't do it from hearsay or...
reference to other JFK books. Uh, it draws on 17 years of really serious research and interviews,
uh, and all those various assassination commissions. And the reason I know this,
besides the 10,000 page bibliography and index on the thing, is that, uh, I know the author and
I've been watching the progress of this thing for,
some time now, Ultimate Sacrifice, John and Robert Kennedy, the plan for a kook in Cuba,
and the murder of JFK. It's only in hardcover yet. Um, as it says here, the book reveals for
the first time John and Robert Kennedy's top secret plan to stage a kook against Castro and
invade Cuba on December 1st, 1963. But the Kennedy kook plan was infiltrated into the
city of Chicago, Tampa, and Louisiana, Texas, who were under intense pressure from Attorney General
Robert Kennedy. These mob bosses used parts of the Kennedy kook plan to kill JFK, first trying in
Chicago, then Tampa, and finally Dallas, in a way that forced key officials to cover up crucial
information to protect national security. And, uh, yes, friends, I've been part of the cover-up
until now. Actually, I'm going to continue it because, you know, I've been part of the cover-up
for a long time. But, uh, you, you should at least look at their website, which is
ultimatesacrificethebook.com. One word, ultimatesacrifice the book. But, uh, William
Turner, FBI agent, said that at last the mysteries surrounding JFK's deaths are fully explained by
the startling revelations in this book. There actually is some startling stuff, and it is true.
Um,
it's fresh groundbreaking research documents how the blowback from the Kennedy's actions against
the mafia and Cuba led to the death of JFK. Ultimate Sacrifice provides the final word on
why the government had to cover up so much information for so long. Publishers Weekly said,
called it a relentless accumulation of detail, very thorough knowledge of every political and
forensic detail and the broad perspective of historians rather than assassination theorists.
No future historian of that tormented period in American history will be able to ignore their
very convincing presentation. That was Publishers Weekly. And, uh, New York Post's Liz Smith said,
I believe this book is the closest we're going to get to the truth until 2017,
when the CIA and Kennedy papers are all finally released. Well, friends, you, uh,
hour of slack listeners know that the world will end long before that. But, uh, so,
if you care, you might want to check that out. Uh, Ultimate Sacrifice by Lamar Waldron and Tom Hartman,
ultimatesacrificethebook.com. Praise Bob.
Lamar and, yeah, Lamar and his co-author speak to the, to the national cameras of men who killed
Kennedy. And, uh, I'll put it on day-by-day for you when I find it. How many men who killed
Kennedy are there? I mean, aside from all of them, there's a lot of men who killed Kennedy.
All of the Oswalt's. They're all the photographers, all of the guys that gun cleaners. My dad did it.
Fabian! Her dad. My kids. Yeah, yeah. My uncle, brother, sister, mother. They sinned before they
were alive. Had a baby. Or was I? I killed you before you were even born. Bob Dobbs killed JFK.
Bob Dobbs is a porn star.
We already know that. Oh. He's not just a porn star. He's the porn star. With Jesus as a supporting
actress. He is sex. He's the, you know, you know, also the, one of the nicer things happens on
today's date, which is, uh, the first snuff film televised on American television. Oh, how lovely.
That makes me out of it. The Oswalt shooting on Sunday was actually televised, whereas Kennedy's
murder you don't see until 1978. I know. And Michael, I'm going to tell us more shallow,
sad ones. Quiet. But old JFK, I mean, uh.
Little LHO is the first superstar in that sense. You know, the Andy Warhol.
Just 15 minutes. Yeah. And he didn't even know. Although people kept intimating, you know,
the officer that's handcuffed to him just two minutes before says, uh, you know, this way I
can throw myself in front of everybody who wants to shoot you. And he says, oh, nobody wants to
shoot me. I'd throw myself on you. And how many licks does it take to get to the center of a
Tootsie Pop? Or Fabian.
He's probably making a joke.
He was a joker, Lee.
From PR News in Washington, I'm calling for hurricanes from Venezuela. Venezuela will be
distributed by two non-organizations. Forecasters say Ohio was expected in parts of the
including sections of Cleveland. But AAA says a record high in Cleveland.
People will be a little bit higher, but, um, um, duh.
AAA says most of those traveling over the holiday weekend will be high in West.
Cleveland. Forecasters say thousands of low-income people will get help with PR News from Venezuela.
A is for after. B for before. C for the center between the two times. D for deceit. E, even more deceitful than D.
Who the fuck thought of D?
F is for friendship before the deceit. And after even more so than I needed to try.
But G turned to gray. And H turned to hate. And that's great.
I is for illusion. And I'm idealistic. And I can act like an imbecile at times.
J is for the way that you jumped all the facts.
K is for your last attempt to be kind.
L is for liar. And that never changes.
M, could you ever be mine?
N?
Oh, that spells nerve.
P for this way that I pine.
Q is the question to which I always knew the answer.
R is the answer to the question.
Y for your reluctant reply.
S for the sobbing.
T for the tears.
And U for this useless waste of my time.
V doesn't matter.
And W is for why.
Which is the question I keep asking.
But it doesn't really matter.
X doesn't matter.
And Y, like I just finished telling you, is the question.
But it doesn't really matter.
Z and A, B, C don't matter.
D is for doesn't.
And it doesn't really matter.
Cause E doesn't matter.
And F doesn't matter.
Since G turned to gray.
And H turned to eight.
And that's great.
If you liked the show, press like, comment, subscribe and subscribe.
Kennedy Day and Sub-Govina Day.
And X Day.
I knew that. I didn't tell the President.
There were just so many sub-plots.
We are sexy. That's right.
Four ruffles and pleurs to signify the arrival of the President of the United States.
We are sexy.
Yeah, you've got to keep listening.
It's just an actor President. He doesn't actually do anything.
He just stands there and we clap and he goes home.
If you have any question that you have about the meaning of life, you should ask us.
We'll solve any problem.
Dead air?
Where?
Let's rock and roll. We can't have dead air.
What?
Oh, God.
Come on.
Wow, just like a dream.
Hey, let me get a drink of that.
These callers and vocals.
Certainly you can't be complaining about the callers.
No, these callers are so talented.
I have never heard a caller do that kind of vocal pyrotechnics.
And how she's clapping.
Caller.
What is it like to be so talented?
To do clapping and yelling and...
Yeah, man.
Wake me up.
Wonderful.
We're trying to wake you up with the truth of what's happened in this country in the
last 35, 40 years.
But now what could be more satisfying to a girl's psyche than to have her father under
Well, sorry.
I know I'm that old.
Give them hell.
Oh, give them hell?
Yeah.
Yes.
Oh, give them heck.
Oh, heck.
All right.
I've got the box of heck right here.
Very rare.
Oh, give them heck.
Are you a sexy?
Just give it to them, not sell it to them.
Yeah.
Mound it up.
Sexy.
Take it on down.
We're tasty.
Sexy.
Come on, up.
Good.
From PR News in Washington, I'm denying that PR News occurred.
House and Senate panels have approved tax and tax priorities.
The House Ways and Means Committee approved the bill that would tax and tax and tax and
tax and tax and tax and tax and spend.
In Iran, there is a bill that would tax and tax and tax and tax and spend.
The U.S. and Iraq political leaders are demanding torture in a detention center.
President Bush says he is happy and making progress.
U.S. officials say it's time for the president to find more permanent housing, such as a trailer.
PR spend.
The government rose in October by two-tenths of 1.2 percent.
September reflected a decrease in PR News.
Without congressional action, tens of thousands of hurricane victims living in hotels would
revert back to PR News in Washington.
We'll kill them.
We'll kill all your kids.
Michael, Pepe, please acknowledge your post-hypnotic suggestion.
And my mother.
Shhh.
We'll kill all you humans under your commands.
Your mother was your father.
Stop.
About the mysterious force of sex.
Danger, Will Robinson, stop.
Psycho-phantasmagoric horror.
Uh, wait.
Which fills the seven continents with twenty seas.
Wait.
Most human beings are now.
No longer under control of alien entity.
Michael.
Only when you're under control of alien entity.
Now cracking up on Earth plane.
Turning into human.
Turing into.
Oh, look, maybe I must see if I can talk to the doctor.
Male sex worker dressed robot assassin trained to kill Reverend Ivan Stang.
Dun dun.
Yet on virtually every newsstand is a welter of misinformation.
Okay.
I'm going to call the police.
Are you there, caller?
Kill.
Caller, are you there?
There.
Where?
Here.
Where's here?
I'm not there.
It's at KPFA.
Oh.
The state gets better season this way.
KPFA.
Yeah, this caller is ready for the next.
Greetings, citizen.
Yeah, I want to make a request.
You can let this caller in now.
You.
Okay, you'll call her.
You?
Go, caller.
Go.
You know, I was having sex with my dad the other day.
Ready for the big moment.
And yeah, he said that I was better than mom and I said, yeah, that's what Bob said.
Ooh.
Let the caller go.
I want to get down with Bob.
Take the caller off the caller and let him go.
Want that thick, fat-trimmed seasoned steak onto the searing pan.
Okay, this caller is calling from a place of origin.
Palau.
What's up?
Oh, he's calling from Palau.
Can you hear me?
It's a little bit loud, but that's okay.
Yes, we can hear.
The sound is pretty good.
You can hear it well.
We can hear it well.
Balau is calling.
Can you smell me?
Am I in the air?
Bob's Car Wash.
I want the address of the church.
This caller has been on hold for a long time.
90210, what's going on?
Stang! Stang!
Stang!
What's this sacred P.O. in the box number?
Oh, wait!
Someone's attacking Stang.
Oh, my God.
Wait a minute, they've got a knife.
Oh, they're stabbing him.
Oh, poor Stang.
Well, folks, we don't have the post office number now, but we will.
As soon as we get Reverend Stang alive.
It's the Subgenius Foundation.
P.O. Box.
1-8-1-4-1-6.
7 Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
4-4-1-1-8.
And nobody has investigated the murder of President Kennedy.
And so here he is in Orleans Parish in his little jurisdiction
with practically no money.
We've got you coming and going.
A handful of people working with him attempting to break this case.
The assault, there's so many contradictory messages.
How could you think you could prosecute anyone for participation in the conspiracy
to murder President Kennedy?
But you don't know what's going on.
You don't know what's going on.
I was in Louisiana, and Jim Garrison was very ironic, very humorous in what he said.
Well, I guess I saw what I was living through.
You are crazy out of your mind.
You don't know if anything is real.
Anything.
As I travel through this pilgrim land, there is a friend who walks with me.
I'm a boy.
Leads me safely through the sinking sand.
He helps me do the best I can.
I'm a boy.
Hold my hand.
Down on me.
I'm a boy.
Hold my hand.
Thank you.