The National Broadcasting Company interrupts all its programs to bring you a special broadcast.
A few hours ago, the atomic bomb was dropped on the...
So genius!
Power of...
Watch!
9, 0, 3, 7, 5, 4, 6, 2, 1, 0.
You tell them about me, buddy. We're freelance entertainers, officer.
Apple Baker Mary.
Droolers speaking.
Dig this.
You have a go on Operation Get'em.
Got it?
Good, go get'em!
Hi.
Well, where are you?
What?
Oh?
Huh?
Oh.
Fine.
Hello?
Quiet.
We know nothing.
But every one of us fears the very same thing.
The so genius.
Power of...
Watch.
Hang on, everyone.
Ladies and gentlemen, you've heard about it, read about it.
But have you ever seen a psychedelic circus?
Those innocent fun games of the hallucination generation?
Here you will meet the swingers, the hipsters, the beatniks, and the acid heads who live from pill party to...
The pill party.
That's it. Step right in. Ride the accident.
Called Michael Pepe.
Garrison was very interested in Jack Rupert.
You have to be this intelligent to ride this ride.
...dead straight.
Oh, man.
...except to what he said...
You just removed all the subgeniuses from that ride.
...assessment.
Incoming.
We're done!
Let me go!
There's a brick wall coming down soon.
Rockin' like a hurricane.
Yeah, I mean the show in general.
...is really not sucking at all tonight.
It's not what?
It's not sucking at all.
Oh, yeah.
It's rocking the night away.
And famously.
It's on the interweb.
Yeah, it's on the interweb.
I guess of all the subgenius gods over here on the interweb.
We're in the internet.
...superhighway.
The media netway.
You don't know if anything is real.
Can I drive in the carpool lane?
Remember when you could get on the information superhighway in a little...
Anything.
And you knew what was real in those days.
Now you have to take the supercar to get on the information superhighway.
You can't just get on there in a regular vehicle anymore.
And you don't know where to get the new supercar.
Because you can't use the one you used six months ago.
...to be purchased by children.
And then you can go really fast.
...like the color of the...
...rear grass.
...or in Chicago, New York, or Los Angeles.
Well, uh...
That was some show there, friends.
From Dr. Philodrum and Doug Wellman, Puzzling Evidence,
Dr. Howell, Michael Pepe, Don Joyce, and, uh...
I got...
Everybody was all over the place there.
And this also, Hour of Slack number 1035,
an unusually tripped-out show because it's on drugs.
That is, it is an educational episode about drugs.
Now, RelPref.
Are we going to get smarter?
Cosmological challenges.
Drugs, DNA, and the analyst's couch.
The future of happiness.
Brain scans, wearables, and brief encounters.
Are we alone? And where?
In the shadow of culture.
Science.
This is the big news.
Mastering disease.
Mind, brain, and self.
The greatest anything is ultimately undecidable.
Swappable mind tapping into the beam.
The complexity ceiling.
The future of chaos and complexity.
What causes disease?
The future of matter.
The future, in theory.
The merger of flesh and machines.
What is life?
The core remains mysterious.
What makes us the way we are?
Are we going to get there?
We are going to get smarter.
In a cartoon, you can do anything.
Let's say I, uh, eat, you know, the whole...
What do I do?
The carnivore diet.
Give me a little idea what that is.
I propose that we just eat meat all day long.
Use it up, consume it, eat as quickly as possible.
Okay? That's wise.
And you realize that that high doesn't last for very long.
They're not sick.
So you're looking for the next high.
Right. That's wise.
Crenshaw.
Hurry, get all your men and send them down to 666 Shadowbrook Road.
It's an old mansion.
He's found the amulet. There's no time!
Who the hell is this?
I'm the one they shot last night! I'm a werewolf now!
Have a nice night.
No, no, no, no! Don't hang up!
He's gonna kill your son!
So this is a kind piece.
This goes this way.
And, um, it's really cool that...
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Shit.
Oh my god.
That can't be good.
Alright.
Can't be done with that one.
More, more, more, more, more, more, more, more, more, more...
It's okay. My dad was an alcoholic.
He was always like,
I'm drunk, I'm beating you!
So I love alcoholics. I get the humor in them.
Marijuana.
Couple of keys.
The joint.
Hey.
Uh, this is pretty good.
My head is spinning.
Think I...
I can do it.
What, you guys...
You wanna...
Oh!
I think I wanna...
101.
Hashem Ben install this thing right there.
I can do it.
Sh homeland, Sera is breathe.
I'm faithfullyросh, Sh Yeti.
Hav ah be a unlary and a shling to...
Hav a sweaty neck and all the dirt on here.
Oh my god.
I...
How can I make you feel free...
to do my best to fall?
Huh?
Honey.
Too fast.
in fact sedated that's sort of gone soft
i do regret the dosage my friend
most um lethal by human standards
then um human standards do not apply do they
well i'll go have a bite will you change into something more comfortable
i don't know
the monkeys are asleep today i saw them down on fifth street
bumming cigarettes and staring at the cracks there on the floor
the monkeys are asleep
and just odorЭтоמ buna
They're sending out their resumes.
Auditioning for plays.
We've seen it thousand times before.
The monkeys are asleep today.
I see them laughing nervously.
Their bare teeth painted smiles.
They just don't cut it anymore.
The monkeys are asleep today.
They're trying to walk upright.
But the lives upon their backs won't let them quite fit through the door.
The monkeys are asleep today.
They're getting laid in restroom stalls.
Their backs are up against the walls.
With nothing in their hands.
The monkeys are asleep today.
They're crawling in the sidewalk cracks.
They're much too tired for fighting back.
They fill the shopping malls.
The monkeys are asleep today.
They're sitting in their cubicles.
I saw them crossing Market Street with briefcases in tow.
The monkeys are asleep today.
They're getting stuck in traffic jams.
They haven't figured out quite yet.
They've got nowhere to go.
Nowhere to go.
Transcription by CastingWords
Good Drugs in the form of The Good Gear Pimps.
Then you will always enjoy the best sound performance from your CD player and compact discs.
Please select track 5.
Jeez, I gotta take a leak so bad I can taste it!
Golly, you hear a lot of savage and unnatural things about people these days.
Thump their bodies and warp their personalities.
Nature makes mistakes. It's proven every day.
This person is a transvestite, a man who is more comfortable wearing girls' clothes.
Thank you very much.
Since the only legitimate source of LSD in the United States is the specific type of alcohol,
LSD is used to find itself in large, black, and white.
You want to borrow your sister's dress?
LSD is lysergic acid diethylamide, or acid as it's popularly called these days.
To help you set up and adjust the sound from your headphones or speakers,
we are providing the following.
Following music.
Amen.
Destroy 40 million little innocent babies.
You'll faint!
I don't know if I can give up.
Amen.
It's true!
Standing for LSD, waiting for a psychedelic lightning to strike,
More often they swing by exploring the mesmerizing sphere of fear ...
hat this
This is the right channel.
And now, both channels
Going insane
We are now switching the D Penn Basin to Ministecti Excel.
on the stereo sound and you will hear the full range quality and fidelity of
the following music as it was recorded
this is one of the most potent chemicals known it produces marked changes in vision time space
and self-identity it was synthesized in 1938 by dr albert hoffman in basel switzerland
and then about five years later he accidentally inhaled a small amount
of alcohol
no one had a bad trip it was all very good
only you can kill a brain
you go ahead and wear your sister's dress plans
we did look much better as a girl than you do as a man
your laser lens system has now been thoroughly cleaned we suggest that you use this voice
assisted laser lens cleaning system on a regular basis but every 10 hours of player use then you
will always enjoy the best sound performance from your cd player and compact discs
no we we would have even though it was said that music was completely
おいしい
me
Purple haze is in my eyes
Don't know if it's day or night
You got me blowing on my mind
Is it tomorrow or the end of time?
Ha!
Couldn't he have hidden a body in a closet
or someplace around the house?
The only place he could have hidden a body was inside
The Self Genius
Powerhouse
What?
No.
Couldn't he have hidden a body in a
Bob?
someplace around the house?
Zero, two, four, six, eight, it's a bad
You really ought to be ashamed of yourself.
Here is your talent.
For tonight by tomorrow it's not the day and the evening
but still mostly Thursday
so more night for Friday by Saturday
and plenty of Saturday night by Sunday from Tampa.
Lee Murr
Uh, did it.
And the purple haze version there was by
the Roto-Rooter Good Time Christmas Band
and the long trippy ravey thing before that
was the Industrial Strength CD Cleaner
from lamprey-systems.com
Lamprey Systems
And now a little heart ignition.
Music
Music Music Music Music Music Music Music
We're talking about uh uh
Uh
Let's see if we can go to Nancy.
Hi Nancy!
Hello?
Hi.
Am I am I an aspect therapist?
Good for you.
You're um
What?
Yeah, I'm I'm dumb.
You know
um
and uh
So I
I
Thanks for calling.
Where you at?
We're talking about, uh, uh, uh, what, what, what?
Um, uh, I, um, um, I, um, I, I, um, to, to, uh, uh, um, I, uh, um, um, I, uh, uh, yeah.
Is it?
And, uh, and, and, uh, so forth.
Um, yeah, I, I, I, then, uh, so I, um, but this, uh, I, uh.
So thank you for going and, um.
And you.
And so much time, so little to do.
Um, I suspect it might be something similar.
This is PR, helping scientists understand and improve PR.
Those are chimpanzees.
You can't fool me.
These are bonobos.
They're pygmy chimps.
Oh, pygmy chimps.
Oh.
These nice little fellas, when you get to know them.
I can't afford.
Real nice.
Fifty-one dollars for.
But today the news says.
No matter how great a world.
It seemed like it was something that just couldn't lose.
You know, Michael Pepe and a lovable family of chimps.
But the public, the critics, uh, who can understand things like these?
Uh, you know, it just went, uh, totally tanked.
I mean, it kind of spoiled the Michael Pepe name in Hollywood.
But, uh, a lot of people since that time.
When the DVDs come out, have come to love it.
And, uh, they actually have Michael Pepe and the chimp conventions across this land of ours.
In college campuses, uh, sometimes, uh, auditoriums deserve it.
Warehouses are.
The kids are five minutes.
Male alike are hardened in cynical contempt.
You know, we, uh, had a touring chimpanzee act for a while that we were doing in DeVivals up north.
With Professor Yeti.
We had, we had.
Oh.
Do you remember Professor Yeti?
We had, we had died.
From chimpanzee to chimpanzee.
It was a really old chimp.
It would have gone to the labs if we hadn't, uh, taken him in.
To your labs.
We had, well, yeah.
We, we dyed him white.
And we would have him stand in a white, uh, prom suit.
And gesticulate with a Bible in one hand.
Or a book of the sub, Genius, rather.
And, uh, a pointer in the other.
And, uh, that was like the DeVival part.
And then it, uh.
A, a, a, a, a, a man and woman would stand in front of him.
And he'd wave the book and gesticulate.
And that would be a wedding.
Wasn't there some dance?
Uh, yeah.
He was one of the best paid of all of the subgenius preachers.
Yeah.
In that he at least was fed.
One of the smartest.
Literally, what we were given, uh, as useless to us was his food.
Yeah.
So.
Well, he had people working for him to get his food together and do all that.
He was really, he was really popular.
Oh.
But, uh, he went berserk one night, uh, from flash bulbs as they tend to do.
I eat hippos.
And he bit, he bit Dr. Legune, who was on that tour.
And, uh, yeah.
Did a big chunk out of his leg.
So, did, uh, Dr. Legune have to get a surgery?
I mean, uh, what do you call, uh, a tetanus shot?
He stitched it up himself, actually.
Wow.
Hey, Stang, you should come read this, uh, review.
It's really, it's really good.
Well.
And, and then he killed the chimpanzee.
And that was the end of Professor Yeti.
Did he get to do that himself?
Like with his knee on his throat or something?
He had it every once in a while.
Three hours or so.
He won't say.
Right, because of the toxins.
He won't say what he did to Professor Yeti.
Yeah.
And he, and he knows that most of us are really sensitive about, uh, chimpanzee rights.
Especially, right.
Uh, especially Bonobo.
Especially the YETI.
The endangered Bonobo chimpanzee.
Yeah.
The one thing that about.
The sub, or the, that's the Yeti chimpanzee.
Yeah.
In subgenius science.
The Yeti Z.
It really should be another name for it.
A Yeti Z.
Yeah.
The Yeti Z.
Is that how you, is that?
That would be, that would be cinematically more correct.
Yeah.
The Yeti Z.
Oh.
Find out all you need to know.
They're fighting over their food.
What food?
Us.
I don't know.
Sandman Al is a kinda dinosaur.
What's an immune system?
Make them sick.
Life.
An alien.
Where'd that come from?
A thanks to Norrell Preff, and now Soupy Sayles.
Oh, hippie has a pair of cha-cha hips.
A cha-cha starts and hippie flips.
A bongo drum begins to play and hippie is carried away.
Hippie can't control his cha-cha hips.
All cha-chas have him in their grips.
He simply has to start to sway when a bongo begins to play.
The room may shake a little, quake a little, when hippie starts to go, go, go.
People scream and fuss, but the Zippopotamus has a built-in cha-cha down below.
The Pasadena Duda, the 49er romp, best of all.
The same stupid stuff.
Same stupid.
This way.
Are you out of the mood?
I have that record, which is, where is he, by the way?
He's the only missing pope, as far as I can see.
Which pope?
Bishop Joey.
Bishop Joey, yes.
It's the only pope that, I hope he hasn't been killed by the silent road.
I hope he's not dead.
Now stop it.
That's a jinx, old man.
We don't do that.
You know, there's...
That happens to subjugate.
You know, subjugate.
Well, there are subgenius popes dotting the highways from here to Amsterdam.
I could be lying dead by the side of the road.
Do you think they can?
Yes.
It's happening.
No, really.
When there are subgenius pope migrations, you'll find them dotting the highways.
The corridor along Tennessee on I-40, a lot of them...
Hanging, being crucified.
Well, they try to cross the road.
And get hit by trucks and so forth.
The hope of meeting a subgenius pope is so great that it drives them blindly rushing across the hot road.
Yeah.
It's like...
Their glands get the best of them.
That's the way a real subgenius holy pope man is.
Now, you notice I don't call myself a pope.
I'm not one of the people driving the trucks, I like to think.
Why is that?
I'm a mere reverend.
That's all.
Just a hard-working...
Well...
I'm not gonna say that I'm getting a word direct from J.R. Bob Dobbs, although I am.
I'm not gonna say it.
Well, I am as well.
Well, I am.
Thank you.
Who and what?
Welcome to the
O.
Welcome to not
rying
to
now
open
the
door.
may
not
look
Let us go, oh, oh, poo, poo, poo, poo.
Let us go, oh, oh, poo, poo, poo, poo, poo, poo.
That was Poo Blues by Artemia Salina.
Well, you know, there was a, there was that sewer rat.
Back when all the two-year-olds were looking in the sewer hole and they all thought it was cool and they were yelling at it.
And I was ten and they were all, yeah, yeah, we're going to say hello.
But I was running through the sewers as fast as I could on my new flashy skateboard.
And we were talking in the Ninja Turtle, they were too cool for us because we didn't have the same kind of agents and we didn't have the same kind of connections.
But when we went down in the vagina.
Of the earth that we've created these artificial zombie cyborg vaginas to crisscrossing all through the cities to counterbalance the big old limousines and pizzas.
And you got New York style, you got Chicago style, you got, you got Jägermeister style, you got garlic.
And when we got the garlic, we got to be able to pin down those Ninja Turtles and Joseph Heller.
And we said, Joseph Heller, you fucking cunt.
I want to.
Where are you from?
But then you went on and you went on and you went on and you went on and you went on to praise Jesus.
And you had your hand all up in the air, just like Adolf Hitler.
Because when you get like Adolf Hitler, you realize that you're a political genius, which tells you something about the nature of politics.
And when you mention the nature of politics, you reach the nature of man.
Because man was a squid.
He was a squid and his tentacles were flying everywhere.
And you understood at that very moment.
Friends, that this is not Prairie Home Companion.
No way.
And I'm not Garrison fucking Keillor.
Because when you realize Garrison Keillor, you realize, you realize what a CD really is, friends.
Which brings us back to Bob.
And when Bob rained down his pyroflatulent glandular love onto us.
And by us, I mean U.S., which is United States, which is a very esoteric country.
And we have a very esoteric name for our country.
You can't say, Libya.
Libya? What the hell does that mean?
You look at the United States and you realize that, well, you know what the United States of America?
You know what the great seal of the United States of America means?
It means fucking.
You fuck in the United States.
State, male.
State, cat.
And you fuck their cat.
Not that I advocate bestiality.
But bestiality by any other name is just...
Sex.
And...
Well, you know, you gotta find your wine bottles.
You gotta collect them up.
For Bob!
You gotta recycle your wine bottles.
And you gotta turn in every single nickel.
Melt them down into pennies.
And melt those penny downs into mills.
Little plastic mills.
That are worth a millionth of a cent.
And you gotta melt down those millionths of a cent.
And...
And you gotta cut off your gonads.
And then your gonads to...
To Cleveland.
Because Cleveland's where it's at nowadays.
It's where all the cool kids go.
Not really.
Really.
In Kansas City.
We got barbecue sauce everywhere!
We got dates.
We got masterpieces.
We got brides.
We got everything.
Why are we more popular?
We got all the barbecue sauce.
Barbecue sauce is American!
Which brings us back to fucking.
Fucking.
Your.
Own.
Self.
Man.
That's what the eye in the pyramid's all about.
That's what.
That's what the crescent in the star's all about.
That's what the cross is all about, friends.
You have to be screwing in the sewers with the screw-er rats!
Yeah!
You gotta be screw in the sewers.
That's what it's all about.
It's like that hokey pokey song.
You have a hokey pokey life until you find Bob.
And you realize that every little wee bit.
Bob!
Is actually.
Another Bob!
And then you find all these Bob's and they won't stop!
You see them everywhere.
And every little electron is a little grinning pipe.
And you say.
Fuck!
And then you realize there was really just Tony Danza all along.
And Tony Danza was ruining everything.
And you found them everywhere.
And everything.
And then it was all a hologram because the matrix came and you took the green pill, friends.
Oh man.
You took that green pill.
Oh.
I know.
It means you picked your nose, didn't it?
You picked your nose and ate instead of taking the red pill or the blue pill or Bob's pills
cause all they're false pills.
You gotta take the true pills, friends.
Why aren't you paying Bob?
You have to.
I mean.
Bob.
Is Bob.
And he isn't Bob.
At the same time.
time.
Oh
Take me away
And uh
Reverend Slaughter
did that rant.
Uh
just uh
frightening there
relatively new
minister
in Kansas
and now
little
Theodore
I just
sit here
watching
squirrel
I
They have much more fun than me
Sometimes they run around all day in circles
They fight and squabble, then they lick their wounds
At least they seem to have a purpose
My mind's always clogged with leaves
Like silly, stupid advertising jingles
And themes from TV shows I do not like
I must not go out the front door
I could get hit by a car
Just like the squirrels when a dog is growling
I must not go out the front door
There's perfect safety high up in the tree
I know I'm bad to just sit here
I should not be so afraid
But once outside I'd have to choose a direction
It might be the wrong one so I'll stay here
They tell me of self-improvement
And someday I could even have a job
Then I would have become just like the squirrels
I don't see how I could accomplish that
First I'd have to choose a direction
Like which tree I should start to climb
And then I'd have to go to the other side
They all seem to be up to the challenge
I just take whatever's given me
So I'm okay here just watching squirrels
Though the soundtrack could be much improved
I'm just a little bit scared, I'm just a little bit scared
Though silly stupid advertising jingles
And things from TV shows I do not like
Wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah
Wah wah wah wah wah wah wah
Bah la la la la la la la la la la
Bah la la la la la la la la la
He's so angry
when какоето
when Alan Watts was on there talking about how you couldn't see your own brain.
And then after that show was Birchers.
And then after that show was Zen Music.
And I thought, boy, someday I want a show on that station.
But in those days, radio was good.
This is a different world.
Radio promoted friendly feelings, warm gushiness,
and, of course, woe-tanning.
Okay, do you mind if we just practice a little bit here?
Right, there you go.
Radio.
It rocks.
Well, I'll probably be chopping this up and making it into hour of slack number 1023 through 1026.
Yep, only 42 chopping days before X-mas.
Yes.
Constantly.
Yeah, that's right.
Little pieces.
Rerun time.
Rerun time is coming.
The great X-mas reruns.
Will you watch what you did all year?
No, rerun the Christmas rerun.
We watched what you did last year.
Don't go in this show.
Don't open up the baseboards and gaze at Bob Nelson's body.
Don't remove the blindfolds.
You won't believe the terror.
It's not fun.
You won't believe the horror, but it's all to you.
Don't drink the Kool-Aid.
Don't look out the door.
Don't go in the basement.
Don't go in the bathroom.
Don't smell your armpit.
Put your hands behind your back.
Don't rubber stamp the visas in your back.
Stand up straight against the post.
Don't wee-wee on your TV.
Don't take that wool whip lesson you were going to at the circus.
Don't pull that wedgie out in public.
Don't ride a UFO too soon after taking narcotic medicine.
Do not operate heavy farm machinery at speeds in excess of 70 miles an hour.
When taking this medication, it's very good.
Life is very crazy.
Oh, look!
There's the chocolate train going round and round and round and round and round the canyon.
On the Candy Track.
Soon it will stop and a special passenger will get off.
On NBC.
The Star Spangled Banana.
Chocolate train rides on the Candy Track.
The lollipop wheels go clickety-clickety-clack.
Ding dong bell goes the dong dong bell.
On the Chocolate Train.
On NBC.
The chocolate train rides on the Candy Track.
The lollipop wheels go clickety-clickety-clack.
Take a trip to Candy Land.
On NBC.
That's fine.
We interrupt this program to bring you a bulletin from our newsroom.
In Chicago, another outbreak of violence was reported in Chicago's Grant Park between anti-war demonstrators and the police.
Protest leaders complained that several of their marchers were severely and brutally beaten with police nightsticks.
And now, back to the game.
On NBC.
And now, we'll give you some valuable advice on how to die in your washing machine.
So for laughter, fun, and comedy...
Passion.
Bloodshed.
Lust and death.
Everything that makes life worth living.
Be sure to see the brand new repeat of the old new show Thursday on NBC.
Chocolate train rides on the Candy Track.
The lollipop wheels go clickety-clickety-clack.
On NBC.
And now this word about a different tasting cigarette.
Be among the many who change over to a mild tasting Philly cigar.
Remember, all the fellas are switching to Philly.
And now an ambassador who is stoned in his embassy.
On NBC.
Girls.
Do you wake up feeling lustless?
Get off.
Girls.
On NBC.
You'll always find the freshest girls on NBC.
Don't miss it if you can.
Bill Cosby is a member of the CIA.
On NBC.
CNBC's week programs this fall.
Inquire about our plans for owning your home.
We have Bill Cosby in mind.
On NBC.
And the sale will take place at our wholesale whorehouse.
Buy with confidence.
Buy one, get one free.
What do you want for nothing?
Check out what's new on NBC.
Free gift rates.
Buy with each purchase.
Don't tell anyone.
On NBC.
Go back to work.
Don't miss me.
My phone's heavy rain.
I love you.
On NBC.
You're done.
Finished!
That's it!
And now, please stay.
Take a trip on NBC by Maynard Brainerd of the Department of Transmutation.
Friends, you're listening to Hour of Slack, number 1035, from the church of the subgenius.
This background music is by the Phlyin Ryan Brothers.
That's Ryan spelled R-Y-A-N.
And you can know about their new album, Blue Marble, from Ryanetics.com.
They almost got a Grammy for Best Guitar Instrumental, something like that.
A very beloved band among guitar players.
Friends, if you need more information about the Church of the Subgenius, it's here at subgenius.com.
Also, at Post Office Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
And now, Doctors for Bob.
We have your attention, please. There's about to be a fairly serious accident.
Doctors for Bob!
Doctors for Bob.
Everything for real.
It's not mine.
I've got the blues.
It's that damn pickup done right over my wife.
Doctors for Bob.
Everything for real.
It is mine.
He's got the blues.
It's that damn pickup done right over his wife.
Doctors for Bob.
We're doctors.
Doctors.
Doctors for Bob!
Doctors!
Doctors?!
We're doctors!
We're doctors.
Doctors!
Doctors are for Bob!
Doctors for Bob!
Celebrate, hundreds of this for fame.
David Flegel.
destroy all normals
we ain't staying in the church for the subject
this is our cover, it's our cover
we shall rule
we shall be free
we gotta destroy all normals and kings
we are the one true church
I know it's the law
and everything's real
in his life
he's got the blues
cause that damn pickup
done run over his wife
doctors for Bob
put out that light
he'll be coming, isn't it girls?
from PR News in Washington, I'm from California
Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice
used cruel or degrading practices
on human rights organizations abroad
cruel, inhuman, and degrading
Bush administration officials
meet the list of the most
legal definition of torture
Bob reports
the BBC's bad
on Wall Street
10-8-5-5-2-7-2-2-3
President Bush again today
linked the nation's war on terrorism
with the war against PR News
in Washington
well, who else was on that show there?
well, uh, you know
in Flash
we lost many of our
important contributors
my ear hurts
I bet you have
it sounds like you're down to 10 or 12 people there
I think the rate of attrition has been absolutely remarkable
a couple people died
well, you know, I'm gonna go out this afternoon
I'm gonna make myself some fried peppy steak
wow
and some boom fries
and some potatoes chips
and some last-lives
and that poor little peppy died for you
is that what you're saying?
little peppy Joe
he was a sunny little guy
stoop-toe
about his former death and it's just a little peppy
he was a little bit chump on the road
all he ever wanted was a smile
he wanted to die with a smile on his face
everybody's just stabbing him till he's brown
nonsense
I remember how he used to say
I just wanted to help you
well, you can get him
well, you ought to be ashamed of yourself
I remember looking through the used-by-Maccato department
I bet you'd like a little of his help now, would you?
I think Mike
well, that you'll never have
ayeee
that show's over, huh?