A subgenius
Hour hour and a slack
Hour a slack
Hour of slack
Subgenius
The hour of slack
Bob
Oh yes, dear friends, and welcome to the first live hour of slack in about a hundred weeks
And this is, we had a good excuse for it
For one thing, I can walk and
Wear a shirt and no bandages
And all that
But the other thing is, we have a special guest here
At Stang Ranch
At Tarzan's radio station
And my friends, it's none other than
The overman himself, Dr.
Philo Drummond
Well I'm glad to be here
I'm awful glad you're here
When was the last time you were on the
Puzzling Evidence show?
It was like three or four years ago, right?
It was, let's see
The 19th of June
Yep
Goodness
My swan song
In public radio
This can be your
Your new pyroflatulation
My re-entry back into the mainstream
Yeah
Of the non-mainstream
The mainstream of the backside of reality
Yeah
Now you guys remember to
Talk sort of close to the microphones
Don't do a Susie on me, okay?
Alright
Or a Hal
Actually, doing a Hal is when you fall asleep
With your head forehead
Leaning against the windscreen
You know, Hal would
He was like, at one point
He would like anchor himself
With his nose touching the windscreen
Right
And then he could kind of doze off a bit
He'd sort of meditate for a little while
It's really easy
Nobody would realize that
Until they try to be on a radio show
That simply touching your nose
To the windscreen on a microphone
Has a
I'm going to try that
It has a hypnotic effect
See what I mean?
Hal was on to something
Beep, beep, beep, beep
It turns you into shimp
Right
It's a shimp
Yes, friends
It's the first new hour of Slack
In months and months
And it's a new year
The conspiracy says it's 2022
You know, I mean
Obviously, that's silly
Because the X's haven't arrived
It's 1997 all over again
Right, yeah
Might as well be
I mean, we don't know
Who cares?
We don't even know
What planet it's on
Yeah
All that old stuff
I really
I'm kind of going for the
That one theory of
It's 1998 was upside down all the time
86, 61
Yeah
So we've got a lot
We've got a lot of time
A lot of time
And that's proof that the world
Isn't really going to end anytime soon
Well
Because we know
X day is going to happen
And so how could the world end
Before X day?
We need X day to bring about
The end of the world
Right, right
So
Well, you know, the other
Some of the rival cults
Feel like they have to
Have war in the Middle East
In order to bring about
The proper end of the world
With Jesus in charge
That won't be the proper
End of the world
That won't be like a sub
Sub
That's just some
One of the precursors
Of an end of the world
That's a precursor
To the true X day
Yeah
We've got to wait
Until 86, 61
And some of us
Probably won't make it
Right
That red
That red calf
And the
And the white buffalo
Uh-huh
And all those things
Different special creatures
Have to come
Yeah
And be born
The red heifer
That's right
Yeah, the red heifer
And the black
The black
The black yeti
Yeah
Has to be born
And the blue
I was thinking about
The black yeti
We cut that from
Revelation X
The blue bull
Because the black yeti
Had the biggest
No, the blue
Of all the yetis
The black yeti
Of course
Had the biggest
Feet
Yeah
And you know
You know what big feet mean
Big shoes
And big nose
Yeah
That's P-O-P-Y
But we do
Had
We did have
A peewee in Lawrence Fishburne
In fact
We had a blue ox
It was peewee
In Lawrence Fishburne
Lawrence Fishburne
Had the line I think
You know what
What big feet means
Big shoes
Big boots
He was cowboy Bob
Yeah
That was Morpheus
Yep
God
Morpheus
I guess acting
Is a thing
But you remember
I remember Lawrence Fishburne
Was in Apocalypse Now
He was
Oh that's right
He was a skinny kid
One of the guys on the boat
He was a real skinny kid
That went surfing
To Rolling Stones
He got all shot up
Yeah
That's right
That baby Lawrence Fishburne
Wow
Just never
He was 17 or 18
Or something in that movie
Man
Actors can play
Somebody of any age
How could the
Pock faced
Giant fat guy
Lawrence Fishburne
Play that skinny
18 year old
Yeah
I remember
There was music in the background
It's really soft
French swing
By different bands
That St. Byron Warner
Sent to Princess Wade
Not me
He sent it to her
Well he knows that
She still has her hearing
Well we had a conversation
About music
That he'd been seeking out
And she can actually hear
The notes and things
Right
Hey speaking of music
Now this
Now see that's where I'm from
That's the French
Accordion
I could cut in the
Swinging live corpses
Right
Dirt
Things
Yeah
That's what was
guitar solo
Don't you go dancing with your blue jeans on
Better wear leather or maybe nylon
You won't have to wonder if you just got a stamp
You're looking at the folds in your underwear
Excuse the mom, mama's really back at home
And I didn't lock a room cause I'm dancing with my heart out
There's no place where I can hide
Cause if you're going and I'm pushing and I'm pushing
Come inside
I feel it getting bigger, it's about to rip
The jeans of my jeans are throwing a fit
Excuse the mom, mama's really back at home
And I didn't lock a room cause I'm dancing with my heart out
Hey kitty boy
Excuse the mom, mama's really back at home
And I didn't lock a room cause I'm dancing with my heart out
There's no place where I can hide
Cause I'm dancing with my heart out
And I didn't lock a room cause I'm dancing with my heart out
Hey kitty boy
Excuse the mom, mama's really back at home
Yeah, I'm dancing with my heart out
guitar solo
That was such a great old tune.
I love that tune. Yeah, yeah.
Except we can't play it on the radio because it's so
dirty. Yeah.
Those filthy boys.
Dancing with a
heart on was always a problem
and there's not a bad
word anywhere in it really
but the concept is
Excuse me ma'am, I must really
beg your pardon.
I need a lot of room when I'm dancing
with my heart on. Yeah, it's about
a guy with a purple heart. Right.
Proud of his purple heart.
And it's stuck right to the front
of his pants. Yeah.
Right on his zipper.
Yeah.
See my heart
on? Yeah.
You guys were so ahead of your time.
The Swinging Love Corpses
people may not understand this but
there was no spinal tap.
At the time that the Swinging Love Corpses
were doing their
commentary on the tropes
of modern rock and roll bands.
I think that we were co-temporaneous
at one point there because I remember
we got free tickets to go see Spinal Tap
when they were filming it.
Yeah, when they were filming it but you guys
were already doing it. Yeah.
You know, I always had this
favorite band, festival lineup
that was like, it would open
Tenacious D would open
and it would have
a mighty
wind and Spinal
Tap and then the Swinging
Love Corpses and then the final finale
would be Frank Marino
and Mahogany Rush because he's
serious.
He was the classic
example of one of those over
the top stadium bands
that had to have the hour long
bass solo and then
the hour long drum solo.
I went to see him in Cleveland about
ten years ago. He was still playing.
I made it through
the drum solo but then he said here comes
the bass solo. I had to leave.
I couldn't stay to hear
him. The Swinging Love Corpses, we used
to have, our drummer was
demanded his
solo of course
and so he was fairly self
indulgent which we promoted
Skippy Mojo Butcher
Mojo Skippy Butcher
and so he would go into his drum solo
and we would
drag out the lounge
chairs and turn on the TV
and read the newspaper
while he did his drum solo
and finally he'd be finished
and we'd put everything away and get back into the song.
I liked the Swinging Love Corpses
songs that would end
for like five minutes.
We had one that was like a minute long
and then would end for like five or six
minutes.
The ever more
triumphant buildups
to it.
Dun dun dun.
And then the drummer would
but then they couldn't quite quit
you know just when you thought it was over.
Like the monster that keeps coming back
and you think he's dead.
That was
I remember there was a band that had
a song like that. I think it was
the
Outlaws.
They had that
one of those take off endings that goes on
that just goes on forever
and it's got like three guitars
going at the same time.
You guys
were a very visually
interesting band because you wore
really cool
hippie costumes and
back then you had long hair.
Yeah they looked like
something out of a quick silver messenger service
crossed with Country Joe
and the Fish or something.
That's the look we were going for.
And it was sort of defined by the fact
that we had gotten all of our clothes
at the same rag merchant.
We went there and dug
through the piles of clothes.
And found our best outfits that way.
Wow.
Huh.
Yeah.
And then we had to wear wigs.
And that was one of the cardinal sins in the band
is that you couldn't take your wig off.
Right.
Well that'd be
You'd be breaking character.
Well what happened we did have that time
in Chicago where we were playing in that club
that was about 150 degrees on the inside.
Oh my god.
And it was like playing inside of an oven.
Yeah.
And you couldn't play with a wig on.
We had to take our wigs off.
Or die.
Flip your wigs.
Yeah.
It was really sad because
Because they need to just look like businessmen.
And then our fans
You look like cable repair guy.
And our fans realized that that wasn't our real hair.
You look like Xerox repairman.
And yellow page salesman.
Yeah.
And conveyor belt manufacturers and things.
Right.
Yeah.
Pharmaceutical salesman.
It was crazy.
Our buddies on the show.
And some of our fans were so sad because they realized
that really wasn't our hair.
That wasn't our real hair.
And that some of us were actually bald underneath.
That's sad.
You know I'd do both.
I have real long hair and I'm bald.
Yeah.
I'm bald on top.
But I have long breasts.
I have brown hair.
It's all white in the front.
Look coming towards somebody.
I look like a little old man.
Walking away I look like some kind of pirate or biker.
Or a pirate who mated with an angel.
I would keep reminding myself of that if I were you.
Well ladies like my punk.
How angelic and yet piratical you look.
I have horny divorcees come up to me from behind all the time.
I yank on that thing.
But then when I turn around and look at them and smile they kind of their face drops.
I'm so hopeful.
I'm so let down.
He had such a cute butt.
And nice long hair.
Yeah.
But he's much older than my husband.
He's much older than my dad.
Goodness.
The dogs are here.
My goodness.
It must be chilly out there.
It's chilly outside.
Chupacabra is here.
Oh there's an article about Chupacabra.
It's my new skeptic.
Oh really?
Inquirer newsletter I get in the email.
I read a lot of skeptical stuff.
Because I like monsters and they cover monsters and spooks.
I'm pretty skeptical about most everything.
Well you know Robert Anton Wilson was skeptical about everything and skepticism.
He had kind of a why not both approach although he called it maybe logic.
I've boiled it down to why not both or in some cases why not all three.
I think it's like an extension of your concept that I've applied to disagreeing and it's
really we just agree differently.
Right.
You never have to be disagreeing with anyone.
The whole world can just realize that they agree differently.
See this is when I should have.
I should have.
I copy stuff off of our secret news group and there's a whole thing about the differently
everything.
It was like you know the differently moral.
The differently sane of course.
The differently sane was the first one.
God.
That group really extends itself to be more of a philosophical discussion group.
Well I know but I like I've got a whole like six pages of stuff up there just from
the last three days of you me and Onan and Sterno just and Marty going back and forth.
I mean Sphinx Colonel.
Sphinx.
Yeah.
We're part of a very august and elite assemblage.
You talk about Illuminati and elites and lizard people and stuff.
We've got we've got it boiled down to the five or six.
It's only really five controllers of the universe.
It's you heard of semi sweet chocolates were like a semi secret society.
We're semi secret.
Semi.
I didn't mean to say semi.
Edit that part.
Semi.
Now let's be smart again.
Okay.
That's easy.
I'll just turn it or turn it around backwards or something.
I go.
All right.
That's really clever.
Just you want me to know that that that means you're giving KBFA phone number.
Yes.
Or ла.
Or the WCS phone number.
Come on call in.
Why aren't you calling in?
Because I have the problem of this show actually plays on several different actual broadcast radio stations.
Not many, but they're the best ones.
And people want to call in and talk to us and they can't.
Right.
They would end up getting somebody at KPFA or somebody in Cleveland.
Why don't you just give them, just right now, give them your phone number and have them call us now.
Sure.
Sure. 216-320-9528.
Call us now.
We're waiting for your call right now.
Yeah.
It's true.
Please call us.
It's on the website.
We're standing by for your call.
People go, well, Stang, I didn't know how to get hold of you.
Why didn't you try Googling Ivan Stang email or subgenius phone number?
That's the phone that rings in my pocket.
Nobody ever calls it, though.
Exactly.
Except Bernard, that psycho guy.
Well, I call it once in a while.
Hardly ever.
In fact, you had to ask me what my phone number was not that long ago.
That wasn't me.
Yeah, well, you had to ask.
Yeah, you've had, no, you're asking me the address.
It's like, what's your mailing address?
It's like, he doesn't even know the sacred P.O. box.
Yeah, well, I was in a position where I couldn't look it up.
But you were more accessible to me than other addresses.
Here's how you remember the P.O. box.
It's like 808.
It has eights in it.
But we couldn't quite get up to 808 for Bob, so it's 807.
Mr. Yarborough has 808, and I'm waiting for him to die.
I didn't say that.
But your street address is different.
Oh, yeah, yeah, but the mail won't come here.
This is too remote and deadly.
What do they do with that box out there?
That's for U.S.
mail.
Yeah, yeah, some mail goes in there.
So your junk mail goes in there.
Yeah, but we use a P.O. box.
807 Glen Rose, Texas, 760.
Come offers and...
But if he's like us, his children will then use the box after him.
They'll get 808.
Maybe you can just steal the box when he dies and swap it out with yours.
You know, actually, I could.
I have thought about writing the guy a letter and saying,
would you...
Would you be open to swapping post office boxes?
And explain to him that the 808 ties into my business logo.
Right.
And probably he's going to go, no, that's way too much trouble.
I've got all my business cards and everything printed with that.
I just don't think I can do that.
You want me to change the street to Martin Luther King?
Boy, you nailed Mr. Yarborough, and we don't even know anything about him.
And that's him, all right.
This is Garden Grove.
You will not...
You do a pretty good Texas accent, Dr. Drummond.
I've been known to live in this state from time to time.
It's not a lot different from a Kentucky accent.
They kind of drag it out a little bit flatter.
Actually, there's so many Texas accents, it's ridiculous.
You're here.
Yours is a little bit more Houston-y.
I like to use a classic Houston accent.
To the average human, you and me sound almost alike.
The people have told me they had trouble telling us apart,
although I don't understand that.
That's true.
Yeah, I don't get that.
The accent, anyway, but not the voice, timber.
Dr. Drummond has the loudest, most piercing voice
in the whole world next to yours, Princess Marie.
Oh, I didn't know that.
Yeah, that's why you're the only two people I can understand.
I see.
The speech.
Everyone else just sounds like they're mumbling.
I've been guessing what Dr. Howell says for 20 years.
Because I get tired of going,
sorry, how can you say that again?
Okay, I'll say it again!
They always overdo it, you know?
Yeah.
It's almost like they're angry.
They're angry because you didn't hear.
Yeah, so they say it way louder than anyone would ever need it to be.
I'm just differently hearinged.
Yeah, you're different.
I can hear you guys fine.
Of course, I'm in headphones.
They're cranked all the way up.
You know, our TV is set on 100 all the time.
My grandsons came in and literally, like, screamed when I turned on the Wii or something.
They were like, turn it off!
Where's the volume?
Please!
Where's the remote?
Please, grandfather, don't hurt us!
That's my sister's TV.
We never found the remote for it.
No!
Stop hurting us, grandfather!
Yeah, it was like that.
Alexander goes, it's turned up to 100!
And I said, welcome to the world of the hard of hearing boys.
They just couldn't grok it.
They've been forgetting that their entire lives.
Those poor sons of...
Grandsons.
Those poor sons of your...
Sons of our sons.
Sons of the pioneers.
Those poor sons of your daughter.
Yeah.
Those guys have it pretty good, let me tell you.
They really do.
These kids these days, they don't have to try anymore.
They don't try.
We can't do that.
They do.
These zombies these days.
They don't try.
Now, when I was a zombie...
We got up at 5 o'clock in the morning to eat the face of a...
Of a grandma.
Yeah, but see, we're ripping off Jane or Hyperclete's and...
Oh, no.
And that means we owe him a million more dollars now.
That's right.
That's exactly right.
Just for those five or ten words we said.
Just for mentioning his name, he's going to...
You know, Stang's been ripping me off.
He sold thousands of Jane or Device tapes.
I know, because I've met three people who just memorized part seven.
Yeah.
That means he sold probably two or three thousand.
A hundred thousand.
We sold nine a year like we sold of all the media barrage tapes.
That's about how many tapes we sold back then.
Yeah.
That's enough.
We're doing a little better now.
Although, whenever somebody buys a CD, I know they're old.
I know it's a really old person.
You know, I think the church is starting to hit its stride.
We're really kind of now finally starting to take off a little bit after...
We are?
Well, maybe in the next...
I can think I'm seeing...
We've been saying that for 40 years.
I think I'm seeing a little rise in the trajectory in these numbers here.
Well...
Well, Sandy Boone's award-winning documentary, JR Book Ops...
Maybe the world is tilting.
And the Church of the Subgenius, available on Apple TV and Fandango and others.
Can you buy that DVD on Amazon or anything?
You can't buy the DVD, period.
I can make...
But, I mean, do they have plans on producing a DVD?
No.
Really?
Nobody did.
What optical media?
My son said this to me.
Dad...
I think you're the last person I know that still uses optical media.
It took me a minute to realize he meant DVDs and CDs.
Here's what I say.
We're using offline media.
Really?
Yeah, offline media.
Offline media.
Yeah.
Optical media is a type of offline media, son.
Someday, we won't all be connected to the internet anymore.
And I'll still be watching a movie.
I've been thinking about teaching...
I've been thinking about teaching workshops at...
places like Starwood or Harvard University about data capture post-internet.
You know, post-electricity data capture.
Right.
I would introduce them to the pencil and the sheet of paper.
Which a lot of people don't even...
You know, it's like they don't...
You know what else you can do?
You can teach them the code of cursive handwriting.
It's a special code.
Oh, yeah.
That only some people can read.
Yeah, that's like...
Yeah, it's a secret.
That's secret.
It's a secret type of code now.
Yeah.
Right.
That's why they wrote the Declaration of Independence that way.
So nobody today could read it.
They don't even know what language it is.
They don't want to read it.
It would hurt their eyes to learn to read it.
And their brains.
Trump had trouble reading it in a, you know, typed up, printed script form.
And he goes, it's almost like a foreign language, isn't it?
I'm like, no.
It's actually modern English.
Who was this?
Trump.
Yeah.
Trump?
He was...
Because they were recording...
They had all the presidents that were alive and a bunch of other people reading parts
of the Declaration of Independence.
The Constitution.
Yeah.
Or the...
Maybe it's the Constitution.
And each one had a different paragraph.
And apparently the tape of Trump trying to do it is like the Colonel Sanders tape.
You know, he's like, he couldn't...
He never got a good take of it.
And he just...
He didn't really understand some of the words.
Do you remember that?
That one where it had Orson Welles.
The peas?
Yeah, the peas.
That's so classic.
I love that.
See, those aren't prank calls.
We could cut to those.
He's taking apart the whole...
Telling them what a poor job they're doing.
The writer's bad.
The director's bad.
He's just tearing them apart because they're telling him to read it a certain way, you know.
Yeah.
It's just hilarious.
There's a whole bunch of those...
It seems like that came from a series.
Celebrities at their worst.
That's what it was.
Is that what it was?
Celebrities at their worst.
I bet.
And they have like John Wayne and he's drunk and he's doing something on stage and...
Yeah, he's talking to a college...
Yeah.
A college graduation.
And just a whole bunch of people that were really...
We used to play that.
Yeah.
Chaz played that John Wayne one a lot.
Yeah, the drunken celebrities.
I like that stuff.
Trump will be on one of those someday.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
I can't even imagine.
Remember that idiot George Bush?
All the things he would say.
We're putting...
We're trying to put food on...
What did he say?
I'm putting...
You're trying...
It's tough for you to put food on your family.
Yeah.
And, you know, fool me once.
Fool me twice.
You know.
Yeah.
But frankly, I totally...
It's like I...
Bush had so many gaffes.
But that's the way people talk.
I mean, come on.
That's actually...
If you cherry pick...
Anybody talking in public, you're going to...
You can easily pull up all kinds of embarrassing...
And now nobody can...
Sure.
And there's no privacy anymore.
So...
And everybody has...
Everybody's a reporter with a cell phone, you know.
Right.
So you can't escape the gaffe anymore.
Somebody's going to get it.
Well, it's perfectly normal.
And, of course, any gaffe by anybody of any importance...
Or anybody you don't like.
If it's somebody you don't like, it's the stupidest.
It's proof of senility.
It's whatever.
It doesn't matter.
If it's somebody you like, it's, well, hey, anybody can, you know, stutter.
I got to stutter myself.
But it all gets transformed into clicks eventually, you know.
Yeah.
Because it's all about traffic and, you know, selling advertising.
That's what rhymes the world.
I used to think that algorithm stuff was sort of sci-fi, but now I've realized it's real.
It's real.
Very real.
It's super real.
It's...
Neil Stevenson's novel, Fall...
You still didn't watch that movie.
Yeah.
I didn't want you to watch, did you?
The documentary?
I did, but Social Network or...
Social Dilemma?
Yeah, I did.
You did?
Okay.
I sure did.
I watched the hell out of it.
Scared the pee water out of me.
Yeah.
When I first saw that, that's when I decided to quit Facebook.
It was the guys who invented the internet going, man, this stuff is dangerous.
I don't want my kids on this.
People that worked for Facebook and Google and different...
And Twitter, they...
Yeah, were higher ups.
I mean, these were like people in high responsibility.
And talking about those algorithms and how they're designed to...
To inflame you.
Yeah.
Because that's...
That's what you click on the most.
You're more active.
You do more scrolling and more liking and more reading and posting.
Now, see, the next generation of phones will track your eye movements.
Yeah.
So you won't even have to click.
It'll know exactly what words and what images you're looking at.
In my case, that's not a problem because...
And then when you want to post, you'll just blink your eyes.
No.
Yeah.
Right.
Oh, well, you won't even have to.
When you want to like something.
You blink your left eye twice.
It's just automatically saying what it thinks you would say.
Yeah.
You don't even have to.
It says, oh, I know this guy so well.
He's looking at the like button.
That's all I need is to indicate the like button now.
Well, we all three noticed that all of a sudden our phones were making these little movies.
Which they've always done.
But they were really pushing them at us.
This morning, I was typing keystrokes that said, Philo's coming.
Actually, Philo's coming.
Hide your frog, girls.
Philo's coming.
Hide yourselves, cats.
And so forth.
But my phone went, oh, Philo's coming.
So it made a Philo collage of all the pictures in my phone of Dr. Philo Drummond.
Which were, of course, hilarious.
And it put this inappropriate sappy music with it.
It made it even funnier.
Don't you think I look better cutting off that nasty big old beard, though?
Well.
You got pretty big.
You did look like a cartoon character.
Yeah.
And now you just look like any old, very, very old.
Cable.
Old cable splicer.
Yeah.
Old cable guy.
Old pharmaceutical salesman.
Well, you looked more like a farmer with that beard.
You know.
Yeah.
Particularly with my overalls on.
The funny thing is, Dr. Drummond is a farmer.
That's true.
He is.
He's a real farmer.
He's an actual farmer.
I'm not.
I live in a ranch.
You're a rancher and I'm a farmer.
No, I'm not.
My brother is a rancher.
You are a rancher.
You have all kinds of livestock around here.
I see them.
I really like ranch dogs and cats.
Canine and feline livestock.
But nonetheless, they require a lot of kibble and food and walking and cleaning up after.
Canine livestock and key lime livestock?
Generally.
Feline.
Oh, feline.
Okay.
Generally, what's referred to as livestock doesn't live in your house or sleep on your bed.
Not anymore, but back in the olden times when they first started, they had the livestock
right in the house with them.
They only had one.
And they were keeping them warm in bed.
What about that red goat up there?
Didn't that goat live in your house?
Reverend Stang?
That was the first or second goat that my parents got before it was ever a goat ranch.
I don't know what.
Possessed them to get a goat.
But they kept it.
They took it back and forth between Richardson near Dallas and out here at the newly built ranch.
That particular goat, old Big Red is his name.
Big Red.
Princess Weir is referring to a mounted goat head.
A huge goat, domestic goat head that's mounted up on the wall.
With Dr. Seuss-like horns.
Like a wild animal.
Yeah.
Like as if it was some wild animal that had been shot.
That was actually a pet.
But it went wild.
It went feral like Boo Boo did that one time.
Boo Boo runs wild.
Yeah.
And the goat was running around.
Actually, this happened in Trailer Park Boys game.
A willy goat did the same thing.
It became a rapist.
It was a male goat, a billy goat.
And it started raping.
It went off the hook.
It was off the hook and it was causing total damage to other goats.
Total mayhem and destruction.
We didn't have that.
It was a habit.
It was having its way with the female goats.
Yes, but they weren't our goats.
They were other people's goats.
Were they bearing the young of this crazy goat?
I don't know.
But there he is.
That's what happens if you start raping.
You start raping.
You end up on a wall.
If you're a pet and you start raping, your head might end up on the wall like that.
That's not people don't.
Goats don't like that anymore than people do.
There's a big old bighorn sheep.
My dad shot that bighorn sheep and that bear.
And that jackalope up there?
Yeah.
He shot that jackalope, right?
There is in fact a jackalope mounted head on the wall.
It was here when we moved in.
Oh, so you can say that you didn't actually kill any of these creatures yourself.
Me?
No.
I only shoot.
I hunt, Dr. Drummond.
I'm an avid hunter, but I hunt with a camera.
Don't you see?
Oh, yeah.
I know.
The dogs and I hunt, too.
Are you going to have a big year this year?
Oh, I don't know.
Did you watch, see that movie?
Everything's going extinct.
The big year?
No.
That was kind of Jack Black and Steve Martin are bird watchers.
Oh, no.
I meant to check that out.
Kind of a good movie.
I thought that might be fun.
You could tell, you know, like probably Jack Black wanted to work with Steve Martin, you know?
I would.
Sure.
I'd like to work with either one of those guys.
It's another spaceship, but it requires a cord.
You feed a cord into it and you pull it out and it flashes and makes noises.
Friends of Tarzan's.
But I don't have the cord.
Tarzan's radio station is all packed onto a fairly small table, but it's really decorated.
There's a replica 3D model of the moon up there and a giant cabbage worm rubber toy
on top of a reel-to-reel camera.
It's a real four-track recorder that hasn't worked for years.
It just looks cool.
And this spaceship.
And three spaceships.
Princess Wee has one.
You've got one.
And here's the good one.
Let's put it there.
Man.
That's a classic spaceship sound.
Yeah.
Who sent us this?
Cosmic Layla.
That's right.
Yeah.
What a character.
Cosmic Layla.
Yeah.
Wee Ma Ma, the 92-year-old that lives here, she sat and played this thing over and over
and over again when we first got it.
She just fascinated.
She couldn't keep her fingers off of it.
Yeah.
She played that over and over and over.
It's her driving.
It's a very haunting melody.
It's kind of Mars Attacks.
It's a Mars Attacks-looking plastic spaceship.
Yeah.
It's obviously someone to take advantage of.
Friends, the environment we're in is kind of across, the decor is crossed between Western,
a fairly tasteful Western style with landscape paintings, and subgenius slack alter Archie
McPhee, Susie the Flusie, Bull Dada, like many subgenius houses.
Every bit of it.
Yeah.
We have horizontal surface taken up with-
Okay, enough of that.
Enough of that.
Nick Nacks toy dinosaurs skulls, real skulls, fake skulls.
There's just over our mantelpiece-
It is quite the collection.
There's a complete rubber-
75-foot Dobbs head sculpture.
A 75-foot metal Dobbs head, a Smilodon skull, that's a saber-tooth tiger, an Australopithecus
skull, my grandfather's skull.
Both of our dads had a skull.
ashes and a bust of Pappy, my father.
A brass bust.
A well-done brass bust.
Except for he looks more like L. Ron Hubbard than Pappy.
Maybe he was L. Ron Hubbard.
And you notice Pappy also.
Maybe Pappy was actually L. Ron Hubbard.
Pappy had many.
Well, you know, that would explain a lot.
That would explain a lot.
The timing would not.
It just doesn't fit.
It doesn't fit.
Although, maybe that's what his naval, that whole naval reserve thing.
That's where he met him.
Maybe he actually just.
He'd be gone for weeks at a time doing, quote, naval reserve.
He was probably ghost riding for L. Ron Hubbard.
He was in intelligence in naval reserve.
That was his code for the yacht.
That's when he was going out to the yacht to run his secret cult.
Sure.
He would say it was intelligence.
He was also really busy in the Masons.
And he was.
He.
He taught Bible studies at the local Methodist church.
And he was an atheist.
A complete.
He absolutely.
He's a biggest expert on the Bible of hardly anybody I know.
And we've got more books here talking about how the Bible is all made up.
Bunch of hooey.
Bible scholar.
And Jesus never even really existed.
Well, I'll be.
My father, like me, was very interested.
Don't you tell me now that Jesus didn't exist.
He was interested in religion.
That's just crazy.
Crazy stuff.
He was interested in religion.
He was also interested in weird, twisted things.
Well, don't you be down, downstroking my Jesus now.
He was also a Sunday school teacher who planted doubt into all of his students.
Yeah.
Bible study.
Bible studies.
That's just the work of Satan.
That's a satanic.
No, it was all Bible quotes.
He just read them.
That's a satanic goal to implant doubt in the mind of a Christian.
You know how much subgenius is who's never read books of the subgenius?
Same with Christians and the Bible.
They have never actually read.
You don't need to read the Bible to understand it.
You just put it under your pillow and sleep on it for 30 years.
It just seeps in.
It just seeps in and it teaches you the word.
That's all you need.
Oh, yeah.
Quote me John 3.10.
How about 3.16?
Oh, that's better.
That's even better.
He so loved the world, he gave his only begotten son to J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Postal.
That whosoever shall believe within him shall be saved.
In Glen Rose, Texas.
76043.
The Destruction Evidence Museum in Glen Rose, Texas.
But how about John 4.10?
How about John 4.20?
How about Ecclesiastes?
I'll have a John at 4.20.
Let's see.
What was that other book?
Isaiah 4.20.
That was a good one.
That's a killer.
I think I'm going to look one of those up just for grins.
Hosea 3.22.
Lo, for my people are destroyed for lack of knowledge.
And so I spit them out of my mouth and accept them no longer into the temple,
for they are as morons and dip.
Oops, I cussed.
Shoot, man, what time is it?
Is it after 11?
Oh, it's okay then.
Huh?
Remember, 11 o'clock was Safe Harbor on the real radio.
Oh, right.
Remember back in the days when we would drive?
Yeah, I remember.
It was real broadcast radio.
We had to leave the dogs at home and drive across Cleveland and go into a locked up building
and go through, put in all these codes and tricks and get up through the airlock and
there'd be Charleston.
Yep.
Finishing up his show.
And then when we left, there'd be Dr. Sinister.
I'm missing.
I miss him so much.
I do too.
I miss it a lot.
You know, Dr. Sinister quit doing his show on WCSB.
Why is that?
Did he really?
Well, he'd been doing it for 20 years since he was about 19 and he's about 40 now.
I can't believe our friend Puzzling Evidence is still doing a show.
He can't quit.
I don't think he can quit.
I don't think I can either.
You know, I...
It just gets in your blood and you can't...
It's part of your DNA.
Even doing reruns...
To keep on yakking.
I've been running reruns for 10 or 12 shows in a row, but I have to listen to them and
drop in the PO box and stuff like that and look out for people who've since been unpersoned.
You know, there's not many of those.
Yeah.
People who had to be unpersoned from the church.
Oh, yeah.
I know a couple of those.
Yeah.
I know about a dozen of them.
Anyway.
On a lighter subject, there's so many subgenius radio shows or subgenius-related ones.
Puzzling Evidence, of course, was the very first one since 1982.
And Puzzling Evidence himself is still doing that thing out of KPFA Berkeley.
He lives fairly nearby, lucky for him, in Oakland.
Philo used to have to drive all the way from Martinez.
Yeah.
He had to drive all the way from Martinez to get there.
That was a really interesting experience.
For 100 years you did that, didn't you?
Well, 117 minus 100.
That's a long damn time to do a weekly radio show.
It is.
Yeah.
This, by the way, I think is our Slack number 1,869.
Wow.
Sixty-nine.
You know what 69 means.
Yeah.
Almost 70.
Right.
Hey, aren't you about to be 70 years old, Dr. Trump?
Well, if I'm 69, I will be 70 in May.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
You may be 70 in May.
I will be, assuming I may be there.
The world ends tomorrow and you may die.
Actually, you're pretty much guaranteed not to die in that end of the world, the real
end.
You know, that portion of the world I live in now has been in the same place for the
last 420 million years.
The continent has moved around and seas have come and gone.
But that section of the country has remained above and in the same place.
Well, relative to the center of the earth, it's been in the same place.
Relative to the universe.
No, no.
Relative to the other continents, to all the continents.
Right.
To on this planet.
Yeah.
It has moved around the surface of the earth, but it's stayed within its same perspective
to all the rest of the continents.
Right.
Because the whole solar system is moving real fast.
And the orogeny is like 420 million years ago.
Orogeny?
That's.
That's the term for mountain building.
Oh.
When mountains are built.
That's when God.
It sounds sexy, doesn't it?
When God.
Did God just sort of leave off doing that after that?
It just seems sexy.
Orogeny.
That's your orogeny zone.
Please bend over and don't let go.
Dr. Drummond, you have a golden voice.
You have a real good radio voice.
I do.
I really enjoy being on the radio regularly.
And I would drive in.
It would take me about 30 minutes to get there.
And I usually came in right after the show started.
Yeah.
It took us about half an hour to get to the station from Cleveland Heights.
It wasn't really all that far.
It's just a lot of lights.
You know, it's a big city.
Oh, yeah.
It was actually a nice drive.
It went by the hospital.
All the big, rich hospitals.
And the music was great.
The museums.
The hospitals?
Yeah.
The hospitals.
Case Western.
Man.
University.
I wish my drive went by the hospitals.
Yeah.
And the art museum.
The science museum.
All the museums.
Mine just went by houses.
I didn't go by any special buildings.
It was only, even the slums that it went through were being converted into ritzy, some kind
of thing.
Oh, everything was being gentrified like hell.
Yeah.
Cleveland was one of those towns everybody used to make fun.
We're going to send him to Cleveland.
But it's, now Detroit is the one everyone poops on.
Yeah.
And Cleveland's like, actually, not a bad-
Seattle.
Cleveland's a pretty fancy place these days.
Yeah.
It pulled out of its doldrums.
The river doesn't-
Burn.
Burn anymore.
And guess what, Princess Wee?
What?
The whole first half of the show, my zipper was down.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
Really?
We'll have to erase the whole thing.
And I missed it?
Man.
Well, we're going to have to erase the whole thing.
I can't believe it.
Doggone.
Because that was a good part of the show that you messed up.
Yeah, I know.
With your zipper down.
Yeah, I can't.
I can't.
We're going to be-
It was probably the best part.
Well, I didn't have my pants on.
But that's okay, right?
I heard that was okay on this show.
That this was-
It's always okay to do a radio show with no pants on.
This was a pantsless show.
But if you have pants on and you have your zipper up-
You better have your zipper up.
Yeah, right.
Otherwise, it's kind of obscene and suggestive.
Yeah, it's a little bit obscene and suggestive.
It seems like you're trolling.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're hiding something, but you want them to look.
Particularly if you have anything, like if the cows are coming out of the barn or anything.
Barn dogs have cows coming out.
Yeah.
You heard that one, didn't you, when you were a kid?
Of course.
But see, you were a girl.
Yeah, when you were a kid, that was a good-
You were a girl, sir.
Yeah, but they still said the same thing.
Yeah.
You heard it loud enough.
In Ohio, they had almost all the same kid jokes and songs and sick, dirty poems that
we had in Texas.
But there's always differences.
Yeah, there's always weird little variations, like the greasy, grimy, gopher guts thing
is a little different.
Great, great big gobs of greasy, grimy, gopher guts, mutilated monkey meat, dirty, dirty
birdie feet.
All wrapped up in something.
Wouldn't you like to lick the spoon?
I'd like to lick the spoon.
Mars ended with eyeballs, eyeballs rolling down the dirty street.
Let me think.
And we didn't have the spoon.
Great big gobs of gooey, gooey, gopher guts, mutilated monkey meat, dead heads and dirty
feet.
They're all different.
Yeah.
It's Mandela effect, man.
No, it's just that-
We were all in different dimensions.
There wasn't an internet back there, so we didn't know what the internet was.
We weren't doing those on kids' shows.
No.
We didn't know how to say-
Like they do now.
What the right way to say it was yet, because we didn't have that whole system in place.
Yeah, we didn't know what ass meant exactly.
Yeah, no, we thought an ass was a type of a goat or donkey or something.
Well, it was also a type of a bug that could sting.
Yeah.
Oh, that was an asp.
But then in the Bible, an asp was a snake, so we didn't know what to think.
Right. Yeah, everything's all...
It's just all messed up back then.
It's all hornswoggle.
But it's perfect now because we have the internet that lets us know what's right and wrong.
You can tell what's true and what's false.
They wouldn't put it on the internet if it was just some baloney, would they?
Once all the people were joined together on the massive network, they were all shaking hands and loving each other.
Yeah, I noticed.
It's like a one-world community of harmony and melodic relationships where people sing together and dance together.
It was.
Hold hands.
Remember, Dr. Drummond, when you first introduced me to it, it was still just college people and military.
There was only 100,000 people back then.
Right, and everybody on the internet was real smart.
And they still had to exchange email with each other, and then they would call and say,
Hey, I just sent you an email. Would you read it, please?
Right.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's like a tell-all.
Hey, man, what do you think of my email?
It looks good. I really like the way you worded everything there.
Thanks for giving me a call and giving me a heads-up that that email was coming.
And now, really, I'll read it more in depth tonight before I go to bed and try to decipher the inner message.
It's like calling somebody up and going, Hey, I just sent you a telegraph, so you better read it.
Yeah.
It's got real bad news in it.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Now, just remember, when you read it, and you will, will be affected strongly.
I'm telling you, I'm sorry, and I didn't have anything to do with it beforehand.
So, don't look at me when you really want to blow your mind.
When you read that telegraph.
Telegram.
Right.
That's the word.
Yeah.
Don't think of me anymore.
Hey, do you think we're starting to slide?
I think we're sliding.
I think I slid.
Yeah, I think.
Man, that's a long time ago.
Maybe it's time to turn the show off.
For ten minutes.
Because what if we slide even further?
What if we should turn it off for like five minutes?
And then, of course, you know, it could be off for a week.
It could be off.
But, you know, we didn't get any callers.
What happened to the callers?
They never called in.
It's a bummer.
Bunch of slackers.
They're out there just listening.
And they're not really active.
They're what you call an inactive listener.
Because they're just listening, sitting on their hands, not really thinking about what
the radio station actually needs.
And someday someone will call in, and that will be considered an active listener.
One that actually wants to interact.
Well, first I'd have to hook my little iPhone up to this mixer.
And then you'd have to hook the mixer.
And then I can have one.
I can have one caller.
And you'd have to actually be streaming this live instead of recording it as we are.
I would never stream things live.
It's pointless.
It's crazy.
It's...
But...
We did it for X Day.
It makes it easier for the callers to call you when you're streaming live.
It's the red light.
Well, you know, Hal does his show every month on streaming live.
And...
But see, you know, then you have to shave.
Yeah.
I just can't see.
I just put my mask on.
I've had people go, why don't you guys...
People can't see my face.
You know, why don't you guys, you know, like, do a streaming YouTube show?
You should have a mask that looks like your face, but it's shaved.
And so then when you need to go on the show, you just put your mask on.
Yeah, but the sound is bad coming through masks, as we know.
That's true.
That is true.
It's terrible.
My mask is kind of resonating a little bit right now.
It sounds like...
I thought that was your mustache.
You know, when I used to...
That overman head would make the sound echo almost.
It was so big.
Yeah.
It's so round.
Sure it did.
I actually had to sacrifice a lot to wear that head all the years I did.
I mean, to actually let my head expand that way.
Swell up that way.
Yeah.
It looked like it hurt.
It did.
It was very, very painful.
But I did that for the people.
I know.
You were selfish.
Because I'm kind of magnanimous about things like that.
You're the greatest.
Yeah.
You're the most humble man of all the greatest.
I'll admit, sometimes I do let...
I may not be as humble as I should be.
And I regret that, and I'm going to try to be better.
Like one of the butt sisters.
The buttresses.
Gutter.
Gutter and...
Gutter butt.
Gutter buttress.
And blinther buttress.
Yeah.
What was the other one?
Blimper.
Blimper buttress.
Well, they didn't talk about blimpers.
They kept her upstairs.
She didn't move much.
No, she was unfortunate among the buttresses.
So, when is this break coming?
Oh, I know what you're talking about.
Rocket away.
Yeah.
Remember that back porch?
Man, that was so good.
That was good.
I sort of remember.
Until they told us we couldn't do it anymore.
9-11.
They put cameras out there.
9-11 screwed everything.
Yeah, we couldn't open the windows at the station at WCSB anymore.
Nope.
Dave couldn't smoke.
Did you know 7-11 is just two less than 9-11?
The company?
7-11.
It says everything.
It's a conspiracy.
They were involved.
They set it all up.
It's hidden in plain sight.
Yeah.
Everything is hidden in plain sight and nothing is true.
Okay.
I'm going to stop this machine.
Goodbye.
Bye.