And you sit there and you talk with your neighbors.
Each one is named Mr. Smith.
Let's sing to the hour of black.
I'm J.N. O'Byrne.
Praise God!
My hair!
Your mind is completely released and becomes still and tranquil
as it gives itself in complete surrender to a positive new pattern
of perfect happiness and grace.
Restoration.
From the so-called powers of voodoo, hoodoo, hexes, jinxes, and witchcraft,
get rid of that spell of sickness.
Get rid of those funny sicknesses that you're wondering about
and the doctors can't seem to do any good for.
I've got to get a grip on myself here.
Heaven will be my home
Oh!
And I'll come
to get this all
This is it.
What?
They're going to make a contact.
Oh, Johnny, you are drunk.
No, no, no, no.
Listen, Rosie.
They've contacted me on the car radio.
This is the night.
Now let's watch the sky.
I don't see anything.
Anything moving?
Over there.
That one.
What?
No, it's...
It's not moving.
I don't see anything moving.
Uh-oh, I think he's caught it.
Doctor, give him something for his cough.
All right, all right.
Here's a quarter.
Oh, that's not much.
Not much of a cough.
Well, thanks, Douglas.
I'll take over.
Big man.
Pop.
P-O.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
I'll take over.
Ooh, thanks, Doug.
Well, you've got me all worked up again.
That ought to have been nice.
Get rid of that spell of sickness.
Get rid of those funny sicknesses that you're wondering about
and the doctors can't seem to do any good for.
After about 20 minutes, we went into the house.
Our master bedroom was furnished with lounge furniture.
And also, there was a radio and a TV receiver.
And I sat in there in the darkness.
I was looking out the window.
Just how did this message come to you on the radio?
Well, maybe I can show you, honey.
Look, we've got this radio over here.
See this little radio?
Yeah.
Now, I talked like this.
Okay.
All right, you folks.
Look, proof to my wife that you've spoken to me.
Do like you did when I was in the car.
Sure, like you showed me.
What was that?
It was the television.
The television.
Oh, Johnny, there's something wrong here.
Are you the same ones who contacted me in the car?
Look at the screen, John.
Look at the screen.
Like Bob.
Bob, you're the people.
With your neighbors.
Each one is named Mr. Smith.
And he says, I'm average.
You say, I am too.
And it's lovely to look at love when you're average.
I'm average.
But then you've got to get back.
You've got to get back.
And that's the hard thing.
To make the film go backward.
Until finally, you're crawling back through the sewer.
Up through the pipes.
Somehow you make it back through the drain.
And then the reality of where you are.
Brings you back.
And then you're back.
What's going on here?
The Cell Genius.
Our own cell.
Watch.
You're going down.
Chainsaw.
I have sinned against you, my lord.
I have sinned against thearynx.
Can I ask you to forgive me?
How can I ask you to forgive me?
I have sinned against every one of you.
I only owe it to one last reign.
Elliott Nash.
And this is why.
Though our marriageی
I call it a mendacity. I call it sin.
I call it sin.
I want to address myself as best as I know how to those that I have wronged, that I have sinned against.
First of all, my wife, Frances.
God never gave a man a better helpmate and companion to stand beside him.
I have sinned against you.
And I beg your forgiveness.
God could never give a man a father, a minister of the gospel, a finer son than he has given me and his mother.
I have sinned.
Donnie and Debbie.
I have sinned against you.
And I beg you, forgive me.
Donnie and Debbie.
I have sinned against you.
I know that so many would ask, why?
Why?
I have asked myself that 10,000 times.
Through 10,000 years.
Why?
I call it sin.
I have sinned against you, my Lord.
And I would ask that your precious blood
would wash and cleanse everything
until it is in the seas of God.
God's forgetfulness.
Never to be remembered against me anymore.
Being acquainted with customs and habits different from our own
is an important part of the learning process.
That's right, it really is, dear friends.
You're listening to The Hour of Slack
on KNON 90.9 FM.
The Hour of Slack voice.
Of the Church of the Subgenius.
And this is your host, Reverend Ivan Stang.
You can call 823-7490 for information.
You'll be speaking to the Will O'Dobbs itself.
Oh, fuck.
But are you still smoking the same old brand, friend?
The communist brand?
The smoke?
The smokers smoke?
On the side of the package it says,
warning, smoke or else.
Or are you smoking the capitalist brand cigarettes?
The smoke that sets you free.
Cigarettes, they call them.
That's the one that's got the warning on it.
About smoke at your own risk.
Communism, capitalism.
They both deliver on that great taste.
Repression, authority, dogma, mayhem.
And what's one without the other, dear friend?
After all, they've been battling for close to a century.
The same stilted bulldada from either side.
You know, without the decadent West, the Reds,
oh, they'd be in the pink, pinker than red.
And without the, quote, evil empire, unquote,
the West would truly be the best.
And in between, they've brought us such great tastes
as Cold War, World War, Korea, Vietnam, Afghanistan,
Bay of Pigs, and soon, soon to come, friends,
Central America.
Not to mention a neat $3 trillion military bill
for keeping both sides in power.
Well, don't get branded.
Leave the rope to the rest, dear friends,
and break away from the pack with subgenius.
Mmm, subgenius.
What a great taste.
Mm-mm.
Neither, neither God nor master, dear friend.
And no state, neither.
Ain't that refreshing?
It's our own way.
No leaders?
No followers.
Try it today.
Subgenius.
And call 823-7490 for further information
on where to write for your further information.
Whoa.
On the other hand, we should try not to pass judgment.
You're kidding me.
Nope.
This is drugs.
This is your brain on drugs.
Any questions?
Huh.
Oh, you did.
Oh, I know.
I did.
It was so nice.
It was so nice of him.
Just, why ca...
You know that Bob, that way we were guy.
Why can't Woodman be more like Bob?
Why do you want him to be like Bob?
Because I don't know Bob.
I, I don't.
Why would you?
I don't know, Bob, but I've been touched.
I've been touched by Bob.
And, well, you've been touched by Bob, too.
And I know you have.
And I know you know.
And then the horrible, perverse God is laughing at his truth
as it stays the same.
From what I've told you about Bob,
you think he sounds okay to you?
Yeah, I guess.
You're not sure?
There's only one thing I'm sure of.
What's that?
He's lucky.
He's not just a doctor.
He's a person like anyone else.
Isn't he?
I mean, he's just a person who makes his living staring at...
He's a doctor.
That's the important thing.
He's a doctor, a man of science.
This has nothing to do with sex.
Hi, I'm Dr. Barber.
Ellen.
Bob.
Ellen?
Oh, my God.
I mean, Bob.
Right.
Uh, so, uh, so.
So.
Hi.
Hi, Ellen.
How are you?
Hi, Bob.
I'm fine.
And you?
Fine, fine.
Um, Bob, I'm a little surprised to see you here.
I was expecting a doctor.
Doctor.
I was expecting a doctor, not Bob.
I was expecting...
I'm gonna...
Is this your Bob?
Bob.
Bob is there.
He's here.
He's a little homeless.
I don't know where I'm going to put him.
But that's what you get for the service.
Epic.
Is that it?
And, um, well, that's it.
Is that all right?
Every time I sit down
I'm a doctor.
A complete cyborg.
And that suits this orders.
From a handsome man
to a shopper.
I'm in Surrey
Nobody has heard of
stuffed with
it.
It's down to
no cleaning.
Too much will
only
wickedness
away.
I didn't see
Call 823-7490
for more information.
Thank you.
Each day you will experience a new delightful sense of quiet peace and perfect contentment.
Oh no, he burned down the transmitter again.
Oh man.
Kind of sort of bummed me out.
Isn't it?
In a sort of multi-logical way.
I don't know what you're going to see.
I don't know if the auto focus is on the commercial.
I'm sure the cars will stand by here for just a few more minutes
in the nonsensical beginning of your famous tape.
Right, somebody take the gun away from St. DeRule.
By the eleventh day, it became eminently apparent
that both Hargraves and Jennings were weakening severely.
I was still forging ahead with my trusty Sherpas,
but the two young army officers began falling farther and farther behind.
Often they would not straggle in until it was almost dark and camp had been set,
and would collapse in front of the fire and having eaten,
go directly to sleep.
And I think the poor lads slept with difficulty.
Their bodies aching and groaning, every muscle shrieking,
every singing twanging in protest of this arduous trek
above the high Pamiers in...
to the unknown valley of the Crusader,
high amid the radioactive rubble of what was once the splendor of Tibet.
I made notes in my journal,
used extra meditation chips,
and then finished off the eleventh day
by chanting myself into a state of insensibility,
doing my Harry Curly Moe, Bob Hill's,
Sex, Food, Love, Nukes mantra,
until at last the whole forbidding landscape
shrouded in snow,
encrusted with glittering iron-like ice,
became a rosy glow around me,
and I knew that before me somewhere,
somewhere in the valley of the Crusader,
amid the radioactive rubble of what was once the splendor of Tibet,
somewhere in there I knew lay the answer.
So...
Tell me about Smith.
Well, Smith ain't no trouble.
He's just this little guy with glasses.
Well, I said, sound's eunuchs.
Yeah.
He can barely drive a car,
and he's right above us at the same time.
Don't come drunk, friend,
on the Skull Farmers.
We can go on the lawn
where the Skull Farmers are.
Skull Farmers. Not again.
Oh, God, I don't want to hear him go into that, my friends.
No, I do not.
I daze not, let me say.
Let me put it that way.
Some nice natural sounds for some background.
Got a little bit of a rant coming up here.
Actually, this is not one of my rants.
This is just merely information
presented in a fairly straightforward manner
by Dr. Waves Forrest,
who actually was one of the co-authors
on High Weirdness by Mail,
the new subgenius book.
Not yet available.
I'm not sure if you've read it.
And I'll give you Waves' number
at the end of the rant
if you remind me correctly,
and if these darn tapers in the background
will quit snorting around.
It's easy. It's easy for me.
You know, I get to live
pretty much anywhere in the world I want,
make love to pretty much any animal I want.
Bob promised us that.
He said we could do that.
But as it says here in Waves' latest,
have you thought about
where the oxygen you breathe comes from
or where it's going and how fast?
Now, anybody listening to this show probably has.
But have you noticed the decline in water quality
and the increasing disruption
of once-dependable rain patterns?
Notice the funny weather we've been having lately,
as it says in the pamphlet?
Or the deterioration of public health
and vitality in general
and reduced life expectancy for adults?
It's started to go down lately.
The primary cause of the continuing slaughter
of Earth's trees and other photosynthesizing
or oxygen-producing surfaces,
such as green plankton in the ocean,
coupled with the massive oxygen consumption
of modern industrial transportation methods.
So...
killing trees and bugs
and making more stuff.
Well, we all knew that.
We've all been...
most, I think, most regular listeners
and probably most of you
who've been listening to the Church's subgenius
radio ministry for the first time
knew that our oxygen is being depleted,
slowly but surely,
by the deforestation of the major rainforest.
No big deal.
Nothing worse than a nuclear war.
It's not even worse than nuclear war.
It's not even worse than nuclear winter.
It might last a little longer.
That's about the only thing.
You know,
all it really means is that,
you know how we exhale that carbon dioxide stuff
that those trees breathe.
Well, they breathe out that oxygen stuff
that we breathe.
And three quarters of it comes from South America
for the whole planet.
Actually, I don't know if it's three quarters of it.
The rainforests in general provide
most of the land-contributed oxygen,
since the trees and other plants there
have much faster respiration and growth rates.
They spread like subgeniuses,
have a lot of babies, friends.
And they have a lot more surface area per acre
than your subarctic forests or temperate forests
like around here.
By the same token, cattle grazing land,
which is what a lot of the rainforests are getting torn down,
and they're trying to make way for,
produces a whole lot less oxygen than that.
Makes lots of hamburgers.
The big beef, big-time beef business
requires thousands of acres, friends,
and undeveloped lands and ranch hands
and just about everything else that you need
to raise cattle can be had a lot cheaper
in less developed countries,
particularly South America or Africa.
But the land there wears out after only a few years,
since the soil that had sustained the rainforest
isn't really rich enough to last as pasture.
It works out, in the end,
to about nine square yards of rainforest
that get wasted for each hamburger.
I know that sounds ridiculous.
I mean, I'd hate to think how many square yards
of rainforest got wasted for one subgenius pamphlet.
Ethiopia being a classic example.
That country was nearly half forest in the year 1900,
and it's now about 2% forest.
Rain seldom falls where there are no trees.
And nobody eats.
And despite such innovations
that the government generally tends to,
not the government really so much as
those who own the government, I should say,
tend to just keep the lid on.
Innovations like electroaccretion,
where you grow walls for houses in the ocean
for almost nothing,
or urethane foam structures,
growing houses from interwoven tree branches.
Despite all that,
lumber will continue to be in demand for most construction,
since it's what we're used to and it's versatile.
So a total moratorium on cutting trees is obviously out.
Nobody's going to quit eating hamburgers,
except vegetarianists,
and I mean wimps.
So that means if we don't want to have to buy
all of our oxygen in bottles in about 20 years,
which would mean the poor people,
like most of you,
would have to just plain stop breathing,
then we need to get moving
on some pretty heavy reforestation programs.
I'm sorry you have to hear the Church of the Subgenius
preach about serious stuff like that,
but it's sort of like that nuclear war stuff.
That's fun.
That's fun pornography for us subgenius ministers.
We love to talk about your hair falling out
and the breeze and the buildings crumbling around you
and all that,
but the slow suffocation, dear friends.
Think of the suspense.
Don't worry.
You'll find out if we can do the subgenius movie
before that actually happens.
Friends,
now,
this morning,
that was merely the prelude.
That was from Waves Forest's Now What?
Issue number one,
which has information besides the electro-accretion techniques
and plant growth acceleration methods.
I haven't tested them.
I don't know.
But I trust the guy.
He's a buddy.
He's a subgenius.
Right for information from Waves at...
Oh, and here's the other thing.
He's got...
is the AIDS cure theory.
Okay.
P.O. Box 768,
Monterey, California,
93942.
We'll give that one again in a minute.
Now,
what I was really getting to here
is that, uh,
this morning, I opened up my morning paper.
I love to read the paper in the morning
because it...
it fills me with such hate.
The child rapes and the kidnappings.
Oh, there was one down the street from me.
Four houses down,
a little 14-year-old boy
with three of his buddies went and, uh,
they stole a car and a gun,
and they played with gun,
and one of them shot himself in the head.
I remember coming out about 10 o'clock at night
seeing the ambulance and all that,
and it's just sort of normal nowadays.
And so, you know,
when you read the newspapers,
then you get into this fit of subgeniusness,
basically, is what it amounts to.
Uh...
Now, this particular, uh, morning,
around...way down around page five,
in the little section,
the little special section of minor news items
around the U.S., they called it,
as if it didn't have anything to do
with the rest of the world,
quote,
greenhouse effect,
linked to forests.
Washington.
Hey, this is big news, friends.
Not that they bothered to put it on the front page
or anything like that, no.
It's the kind of thing that should have been
on the front page 20 years ago
and could have been.
Major efforts to restore tropical forests
could bring an important slowdown
in the expected greenhouse effect
or warming of the Earth,
according to a study of forest needs.
Uh, growing trees, uh, absorb carbon dioxide,
the principal gas responsible for the warming,
and break down gas to incorporate carbon
in their woody tissues.
Uh, a growing forest also adds carbon to the soil.
It does provide an important lag time,
while we do important things in other areas,
like reorient national energy policies.
One paragraph on page five, dear friends.
With about 40 other paragraphs around it.
And it's more, it's a more likely end
to you and me and all the cute little bunnies
and rabbits that you animal lovers
don't want to eat.
A sure and certain end, dear friends.
And it makes a paragraph every month,
well, actually, they mention it every month
or two, three, you know, it's a minor thing.
They don't want to get you excited.
They don't want to panic you about what could happen
if there, if about a million Johnny Apple seeds
don't get to work.
It's essentially what it boils down to.
And the, here's the most horrible thing
about this little paragraph.
Not that it was so little, and not that it was at the back,
but the irony on top of it was that the statistics came
from the World Watch Institute.
Probably ourこう
friends and it makes a paragraph every month well actually they mention it
every month or two three you know it's a it's a minor thing they don't want to
get you excited they don't want to panic you about what could happen if there if
about a million Johnny Apples seeds don't get to work it's essentially what
it boils down to and the here's the most horrible thing about this little
paragraph not that it was so little and not that it was at the back but the
irony on top of it was that the statistics came from the World Watch
Institute the Institute is a Washington based environmental research
organization now not to slander anybody but word has it in certain circles of
kooks crazies subversives weirdos computer hackers and others
you know people who study the news constantly the especially suppressed
news who of course therefore wouldn't know what was really going on according
to mainstream ordinary news doctrine World Watch Institute is basically
government supported the news about the environment the scariest news you get is
associated oftentimes with them and yet and yet and yet you know there are
organizations that are doing this and they're doing it for the sake of the
Klim podcast remember we are
together forget we are connected we're planning try
again but hey the thing is this the picture result says that neoliberalised
light is your message to me then should you be okay with that
part as in ition numbers you want to eu i for
Carol stated when she input 15 protracting
nomination from herdsman
can it represented the
pres Ig i w
on a
which was a
those are 24
I am
bid
that they've helped in some manner.
Now, the funny thing is,
I get mailings from the World Watch Institute once a week,
and I've never given them money.
If I've been getting one every week for three years,
and lots of other people have,
think how many millions,
how many acres of rainforest had to go down
to support those mailings,
those pro-environmental mailings,
of the biggest of the environmental groups.
They're not all like that.
I don't think you could say that.
I mean, I haven't heard rumors.
These are rumors, of course,
that no station like this would ever support such rumors.
You know, in public.
But this is not to be confused with efforts like Greenpeace.
Greenpeace, I don't think, they don't have a thing on them.
Bombs on their ships, yes,
placed by governments, foreign governments,
even cool.
People like the French.
Artsy people like the French.
Even the French government might bomb a Greenpeace ship or two
so as to get the attention away
from the little problems out there with the plankton.
Nobody worries about the plankton anymore.
You don't.
I certainly don't.
And the fish themselves who live on the plankton,
and the plants who live on the fish skeletons,
and who make the air,
and the water which comes up into the rain,
they don't care either.
Nobody cares but us four-legged creatures
and only a tiny, tiny percentage of us, dear friends.
Only a small percentage of us.
And that's not the only thing the Church of the Subgenius is here for.
All we're here for, really, the main thing we're here for,
is to make it possible for you to not kill yourself
while thinking about these things.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Here I go falling down, down, down
My mind is a plank
My head is spinning around and around
As I go deep into the funnel of love
It's such a crazy, crazy feeling
I get weak in the knees
My poor old head is reeling
As I go deep into the funnel of love
I tried and I tried to run and hide
I even tried to run away
You just can't run from the funnel of love
It's bound to get you someday
It's gonna get you someday, dear friends
Jeez, what was that tape I just started?
Yeah, you got me.
Good people on bad days
will often hurt those they love most,
their children.
When stress builds and you're about to lash out,
stop.
Take time out.
Don't take it out on your kid.
Well, there was a big argument
with the Sherpas this morning.
We wanted to bury him,
but they wanted to eat him.
Said they were tired of eating dried dog.
And said that it was not by our religions
for the people to eat the flesh of young men,
only young women.
Young maidens, in fact.
They were surly.
They were about it.
But after I branded my brand new
Boxer III short barrel pistol,
they quickly threw up a rustic camp.
And we compromised.
We served.
We served for old Hargrave's fingers and toes
as hors d'oeuvres at the wedding service.
This seemed to be a compromise with the Sherpas.
It was.
And soon we were up here
at the end of the Valley of the Crusader.
Where the Roentgen level is lower,
we found a small, commodious,
and quite comfortable country inn.
Three-floor level,
guests on the third floor,
food storage, family,
and livestock on the first floor.
And, of course,
the dung gaso-gene on the first floor.
Yes.
It was there we found Watson,
and we waited.
We waited for a smoking,
a serviceable-looking pipe,
and serviceable-looking gas-lap.
Oh, thanks.
No, that's right, dear friends.
We'll continue with G. Gordon Gordon's report
on his Himalayan expedition
200 years from now,
when possible.
Here's another one from Waves Forest.
Now what?
Once again, I'll give the address at the end
because you're going to want it this time.
This is Dr. Chris Gross in the background
doing the music.
Designer diseases.
AIDS as a biological and psychological warfare.
First, before I get any further,
let me state for sure and certain
that this is not the official policy
of this station,
nor its management,
nor subscribers,
but only of this particular editorial
that I'm reading
and something that I myself often wonder about.
At a House appropriations hearing in 1969,
the Defense Department's Biological Warfare Division
requested funds to develop, through gene splicing,
a new disease that would both resist
and break down a victim's immune system.
Within the next five to 10 years, they said,
it would probably be possible
to make a new infective microorganism,
which could differ in certain important respects,
from any known scientific study,
to any known disease-causing organisms,
most important of those being
that it might be refractory
to the immunological and therapeutic processes
upon which our bodies depend
to maintain our relative freedom
from infectious diseases.
The funds were approved,
and AIDS appeared,
happened to appear within the requested timeframe,
and as happens to have the exact characteristics specified,
the incidence of AIDS infection in Africa
coincides exactly with the locations
of the massive smallpox vaccination program
in the mid-1970s, according to the London Times.
Some 14,000 Haitians then,
on UN secondment to Central Africa,
were also vaccinated in this campaign.
Personnel actually conducting the vaccinations
may have been completely unaware
that the vaccine was anything other than what they were told,
and it may well have been.
A striking feature, though, of AIDS
is that it is ethno-selective.
That is, the rate of infection is twice as high
among blacks, Latinos, and Native Americans
as it is among whites,
with death coming two to three times as swiftly.
Funny how that worked, see?
And over 80% of the children
with AIDS and 90% of infants born with it
are among these minorities.
So-called ethnic weapons that would strike
certain racial groups more heavily than others
have been a long-standing U.S. Army
biological warfare objective.
It just so happens.
Under the current United States administration,
biological warfare research spending has increased 500%.
I suppose that means since the last administration.
Primarily, the United States has been the largest
in the area of genetic engineering
of new disease organisms.
Ah, yes.
So despite the loyalty of the vast,
I'm sure the vast majority of U.S. military personnel
towards their country,
there may be some military officials
who have very different intentions,
and they occupy high enough positions
to impose their priorities on military programs,
and get away with it.
So far.
The first charges that AIDS may have been
a biological weapon were published
in New Delhi, India in 1984,
and then the Soviets picked it up,
but dropped it pretty quick after,
mmm, you know, where China became
more and more friendly with us,
and so they had to be a little bit more careful then.
Anyway, there are many key references to this,
and also to the hyperoxygenation therapy,
which is a highly contested, very controversial,
and certainly not to be definitely called anything on,
over the air,
but as a supposedly possible cure
for the cureless disease.
And once again, for information,
that what I've been reading from basically,
Waves Forest at Box 768,
Monterey, California,
93942,
USA, dear friends.
What a deal.
Call 823-7490 here at the station,
KNON, if you have any serious questions.
I certainly would if I were you.
In the meantime, just stick, just hang in there.
It is a common thing among our youth today,
to become,
one with Wotan.
But through Bob,
it is not necessary to become one.
That's right.
You can be half with Bob,
and still be one with Wotan,
or vice versa.
Half a hole is still a hole.
Dig a hole.
Fill it halfway with dirt.
It's still a hole.
That's true.
Maybe it's a little more shallow.
Sort of like a suburban housewife.
Hey, not quite as deep.
Wait a minute.
But it's still a hole in a state of wholeness.
So as you can see,
it's possible to be whole with dirt.
Half with Bob,
or half with Bob.
Or half whole with Bob.
You can achieve oneness,
and you can achieve wholeness.
Or,
you can achieve hole in oneness,
which is considered par for the course.
Bob.
velen
Ven.
A neighbor lived across the hall
He used to do strange things
One time, a cozy dinner at his house
Before he slept, three cups of coffee
Sat and bowed, all three
He thought to himself
Say nothing more then
Please ask your service
Another time, we were traveling
We had no sooner set our bags down
In the motel room
When
He
He moved every piece of furniture
In the motel room
Four inches to the left
Saying a little well again
Do you feel draft in here?
The third time
Took the police
I saw him turn around three times
For a positive male
In the little blue U.S. mailbox
On the corner
Three times he turned around
I said, why?
I cornered him in the hallway
I said, why did you do this?
I said
If I turn around
If I turn around three times now
Why?
There's less of me for life to turn around
Three times later
My strange neighbor
By the quarks, dear friends
The quarks
And before that we had Nick Smith
And before that I don't know what all
Public service announcement here
Teen Contact wants teenagers and their families to know that there is an alternative to being isolated and alone with a problem
In other words
If you're feeling all alone and overwhelmed
And need somebody to talk to for any reason
Say you can't tell your parents
You can't tell the teachers
You can't tell me
Because I'm not going to give you my phone number
Call Contact Teen
At 233-TEEN
So literally 233-T-E-E-N
Seems like they only give the numbers on there
Some people have, like me, have trouble figuring that out
233-TEN
Remember it's healthy to call for help before reaching the boiling point
Call 233-TEEN
And that's pretty, uh
That's pretty much for real, uh
I remember a time when I would have killed myself a day later had not I gone to my friend and said
Hey man, like
Like, what's wrong?
I've got this problem
Yeah, I bet some of you out there are wishing that friend hadn't been there
But it could be worse
There was a congregation
This was also in the papers
Before we get back to the tapes here
There was a congregation in, uh, Denver
This Denver minister seeks commitment to international disarmament
He told his, he told his folks basically they had to turn in their guns
They had to turn, bring in their handguns, their shotguns
Their, uh, just about any kind of guns
And, uh, give them, give them over to the church
For, for international disarmament
Guns are demons, he said
We pretend they'll save us, but they won't
Said the pastor of Our Lady of Guadalupe Roman Catholic Church
Everyone in, in Denver has guns these days
Why do people need a gun on their hips?
He asked parishioners to sign cards pledging they would not carry guns
Uh, unless it was for hunting, uh, wild animals and not their neighbors
So far, 400 cards, but only 10 guns have been turned in
Uh, the guns will be destroyed by the Denver Police Department
Hopefully not given over to Hare Krishnas or white supremacists
Or any of the other people in your neighborhood who stash guns away
And many of your subgenius buddies, so you never know
Father Gurley said that, uh, he could have preached 10 sermons on New Year's Eve
And a nuclear disaster, but they wouldn't have hit the people
The way this request has
And believe you me, they won't hit anything as hard as a nuclear blast would
But, uh, well, hehehe
Like I say, that kind of thinking, that's almost like pornography to some of us
Oh, what have we got here, what have we got here
Oh, Dick Gregory, he can say words that I never could
Now, for you black folks that was devastated
By Ronald Reagan getting in the White House
It's awful when fear enters your consciousness
You can hang it up
But I would say to those of you that's really upset over Reagan
What you should do is just go sit by yourself
And take your pencil and piece of paper and just write the word Reagan
And look at it
Then spell his name backwards, write Reagan backwards
Just sit there and look at it
That's right, Reagan spelled backwards is nigger
So at least we can boast we got us a backward nigger in the White House
Praise Dick Gregory, dear friends
And for all you Jimmy Carter fans, well look at it this way
Anywhere, anything that gets Amy off television, you know what I'm saying?
Anywhere, anything that gets Amy off television for the next four years
Cannot be all bad
Yeah, we're the good old days
Hello, we'd like to know is Bob a member of the Republican Party?
Bob is a member of
Good question, great question
That is a good question
Bob at different times has been a member of every
He was a member of the Illuminati for a long time
And he was one of the highest ranking members of the conspiracy
He could have been president at one time
He was the richest man in the world and he threw it all away
For you my friend
Well, I thank him for that
And speaking of president, Bob is a friend of Ronald Reagan, a close personal friend
That is true
I remember he used to go out to the Bohemian Groves and drop acid together
Reagan is not, he's not what people think he is
He's an actor, he's doing an excellent job
Well he's obviously dropped a lot of acid
Reagan?
Yeah, but he was with Bob and it wasn't, you know, they, it's not, I wouldn't recommend that kind of thing to the average young
He knows Bob in every sense of the word
Yeah, Reagan and Bob, you know, I could get into some stuff that you wouldn't believe about Reagan and Bob
They're good friends
They're the kind that's illegal in Texas
In Georgia
He's a broad minded guy
Yeah, did Bob and Reagan and the Supreme Court Justice there get together a lot?
Well see, now Bob is, Bob, Reagan, like I said, he's an actor
And Bob is not for all the censorship they're doing, you know
But the thing you gotta remember is even though, even though they've tortured the 7-Eleven executives into not selling Playboy and Penthouse
At the same time when they do that pictorial on the girls of 7-Eleven
It's, they're gonna censor, they're gonna censor the subgenius mutant women that should be in that pictorial
You know what I mean?
So censorship and the conspiracy works both ways
They'll have nothing but those plastic, you know, airbrushed, hard-gallon girls
As fragile, tender, enduring, tough, talkative, gossipy, nasty, humorous, sweet, intelligent, passionate creatures
Who are, unlike other animals, capable of symbolic thought
And therefore also unlike other animals capable of deluding ourselves
If we could accept ourselves as we are
We could start to build a morality built on actual human need and desires
Oh yeah
What's for lunch?
A game show steeped in the American tradition!
What's for lunch? A game show steeped in the American tradition!
Scrambling for roaches!
The new high-speed competition that fits natural American skills against the awesome, icky corporate clock of greed!
Just look at what you can win!
A car two blocks long outfitted with a mint-covered toilet
A dishwasher the size of the Great Cheops Pyramid
A trip to Venus
Four shots at Spiro Agnew's limo with a grenade launcher
A six-legged dog
Forty strap-on dildos in a rainbow of colors from Mr. Huey's of Nookers Street
A change in the weather
A break in the action
Twenty hand-painted Arkrum t-shirts of antiquity
A stainless steel bar autographed by Groucho himself
A kiss on both cheeks
One on the face even
A genuine hand-rubbed atomic poodle harness with snout retainer and automatic scooper
A piece of table linen stained by Keith Moon himself
All the comic books that your mother threw away that are now worth millions
A life-size fiberglass figure of Vincent Price in full mask of the Red Death drag
And a matching set of plaid wool socks, panties, brassieres and mittens
The premise of our game is really simple
We line up two rows of identical alternating 52 Chevy Coupes and old Firebirds whose looks are more body-cutty than metal
42 in all
We then load up all the ashtrays with premium heavy-duty roaches and pipe-dumping rimners
Just the kind found most commonly on Texas beaches in July
At the sound of the police siren, our two contestants will scramble like mad through said ashtrays
And try to amass the largest amount of usable dough possible in the three-minute period prior to the firing of the air raid siren
And to weigh the dough after the mad scramble,
We use a nuclear-powered triple beam donated by Mr. Natural himself
This little beauty is accurate within one-eighth-billionth of a gram
And we don't weigh the paper either
All the remaining money and prizes revert to the US Foundation
Because we have bills to pay
Not to mention a vicious Jones
In everything vision
Scrambling for Roaches!
Yuuuughhh
Bwahahahaha
Oh, so good ol' Hell Pope you in there, huh?
And he is a Hell Pope, dear friends
He's an ugly, ugly, ugly, ugly man
If you knew him personally
Oh, oh, he's a bad, bad guy
I think you can tell
With the swinging love corpses in the background
Huh
Stay tuned, dear friends, for Robert Wisdom's American Music Party
Regular type
Oh, well, good ol'
It's not regular, it's better than regular
It's a good ol' day, good ol' time
Back from them good ol' days
Remember that one time
You and Wanda in the back seat
Remember that time, what, that song you were listening to?
Well, Robert Wisdom's gonna be playing every one of those songs
In the next hour and a half
I got about, uh, four minutes to go here
And I think what I'm gonna do is let, uh, Berklee take over
This is the Berklee Subgenius Show
Because you can fade out anywhere on their show
Doesn't really matter
Dr. Howell, Puzzling Evidence
Lies, I think on this one, maybe in the background
And Gary Gbrogfran and Bob Nelson
And yours truly for that one time
That one time
Remember that one time
Well, I want you to, before I go, though
I want you to write for information
If you haven't already
Free information from the Church of the Subgenius
Get that pencil ready, dear friend
Cause it's Bob at P.O. Box 140306
In Dallas, Texas
Once again, P.O. Box 140306
For stuff you wouldn't believe
Stuff you really wouldn't, wouldn't
Now, at last, the step-by-step process is revealed
This is it
Maybe
Speaker 1 says maybe
Voice over
Since she said maybe
hurt your eyes
Mr. B steel
Oh...
Yeah.
Go on
What are you talking about?
Talk on Yoga
All right
If you don't want the details
What are you mad about?
Do you wanna talk on Yoga?
Skin voor Segen
Well, you miss that
Con Jedi
Well...
What do you have to say for yourself, son?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, little caller officer.
It came from the caller zone.
Okay, let me just start my show and get out of here, okay?
Just let me give you a piece of my mind.
Oh, here, go ahead.
I'll put it in here.
Oh, thank you.
Ah, squeeze!
Oh, there we go.
Okay.
See, this little piece of Hal Robin's mind, let's examine it.
In time, sir, in time, we have plenty of time to be on the air.
It's been freed from the encasing skull.
Well, I hope it'll be soon because you're driving me crazy.
Well, if you don't like it, turn off the radio.
Turn off the radio.
How do you guys do that?
We hold our mouth like this and you just kind of, yes.
It's the hypnotic beam from the interocitor.
Would you like to change your mantra?
Okay.
M-I-N-O-T-I-O-N.
Oh, Darnini, you're so pretty when you wear that flaming headdress of burning souls.
He exploded all by himself.
You see, Bob, who being in very nature dogs,
did not consider equality with an antipode something to be grasped,
clutched, or palpated, but rather smoked in his pipe,
like a fine burly or rubbed-in shell.
He himself, nothing keeping the very...
848-4425.
Dave, show us.
All caught.
Somebody's smoking some anti-Bob right here.
And being an apparent of a man, he fumbled himself
and became obedient to entropy.
Well, here, have a hit.
Therefore, God exalted him and taught him to himself,
but we gave Bob the name that is above his name,
a movement of the year,
that at the name of Bob every year should wind on each human
and have water up his head and soil the tops of his shoes.
And every tongue confess that Dob's his squash.
So be nice, little callers.
It's almost time to go seepy again.
That's right.
The show really begins to get pretty here.
The wind-down part of the show.