Ah, yes dear friends. This hour of Slack number 1780 is actually a rerun of number
664 from either really late 1998 or early 1999. It includes a devival with Einstein's Secret
Orchestra and Lunsum Cowboy Dave and yours truly Reverend Stang at the Euclid Tavern in Cleveland,
or at least Clipsa, from November of 1998. And there's some great tunes and all kinds of great
stuff. A lot of ESO radio from the late Professor Chas's show. And so, here's Bob.
Bob
Welcome to Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
The Subgenius Hour of Slack that you are about to listen to
is specially designed only to be played on radio station
and only in the city of...
Yes, dear friends, we're back and it's once again,
it's going to be a solid Einsteinian secret orchestra show
for the simple reason that it's the holidays and I've got to get out of here.
I've got things to do, people to see.
We've got a big...
Tonight the stars will be out.
Don't you know the goddess Pooh-Bang?
Goddess Pooh-Bang?
If you were in a spaceship, you know, you'd keep it pretty clean, right?
And you'd really be very careful about getting your air all dirty
because how would you get clean air again?
Yeah, there's no other air except the air.
You're inside.
It's okay.
When you're outside of a balloon,
you don't think anything about that, you know, pop in that balloon.
But if you were inside the balloon and there was nothing else outside,
you would not want to pop it.
Well, we used to have blimps fly in our neighborhood
and we used to take pot shots at them with our slingshots.
Well, somebody...
We're on...
The Earth is a giant balloon
and who might be taking pot shots at us?
With their slingshots, right.
And are we just developing...
Have we just invented the needle?
We, the people who live inside the balloon,
have now invented the giant needle.
It will pop through and...
So what are we doing?
All the air out.
Hey, let's go.
Let's pop.
Let's go get against our atmosphere.
See what happens.
Yeah.
Well, there's an idea.
Well, when they exploded the first atomic bomb,
they didn't know if it wasn't like Ice 9 or something.
Right.
It would just vaporize the whole atmosphere.
Yeah.
Man.
The whole damn solar system.
They weren't totally sure.
They didn't think it would happen.
Right.
You're in a pool without source.
Did they know it would be that big, as big as it was?
Did they predict?
No.
They were...
It was about the way...
When they shot off the first atomic bomb,
it was about the...
And then the guy who...
Dobbs, Oppenheimer, Bob Oppenheimer...
Right.
...who invented it,
he looked at the first explosion
and he quoted the book of the subgenius
that I am becomes rock.
This is the end of the society.
The slinkies, the slinkies.
The slinkies.
Oh!
They're fun for girls and boys.
From the deepest, deepest points of the universe we can look at,
and there's these waves in the background,
and they kind of look like these rows of pipes.
I can feel those waves washing over me sometimes when I'm real sensitive.
Yeah.
Wow.
What are those waves?
Have you ever laid in bed in a receptive state of mind
and tried to feel the neutrinos washing across you?
Yup.
I do it every night.
The cosmic particles zipping right through your body.
Yeah.
You say it like it's something unusual.
It's not.
It always makes me need to go to the bathroom when I have...
I hear them.
Every time they hit my eardrums,
my ear nerves,
I hear them.
Bing!
They sound to me,
they sound like the little particles slamming against your hard drive
when you turn your computer off.
Right.
Do you hear like a rain?
Yeah.
The dust is much more efficient than dust.
Dust just degrades.
Whereas the cockroach,
as they reproduce,
they continue your information.
Another reason why the church needs,
you know, more support, friend.
Right.
Because of worthy research like this.
Well, it's a way of sending the pamphlet of Bob
and the word of Bob into the future.
Someday an insectoid species,
long after man has gone,
will investigate the earth's cockroach.
They'll say, look, encoded in this DNA,
is this completely useless material
that has nothing to do with this creature's life cycle.
Wait a second.
Just eye.
Look, it decodes into a photograph of a hideous monster's face
with a pipe-like, uh, implement sticking from its mandible.
We gotta get going here.
We gotta get going home now, folks.
We gotta get out of here!
We gotta build that rocket ship.
Help me, Obi-Wan Kenobi.
You're my only hope.
Do you have the mental power?
Do you have the willpower to take perhaps an old vinyl record
that maybe your grandmother gave you 14 years ago
and view it in your mind as a spaceship,
as a flying saucer that can scissor through the cosmos
and then cop through galaxies like a laser-mute?
See!
Cut!
Oh, look, your little light's flashing.
Who could it be?
The twin red eyes in the deep.
Gnashing in the radio.
Who could it be?
Who could it be now?
Which subgenius stalker could it be out there this time?
Who could it be?
Breathing down the backs of our necks.
Who could it be now?
Come on, man.
I, I, you, you owe me all them slacks that Bob said I was, was, was, was slacks.
And if I believed, I believed and I planted my seed.
Who could it be now?
My words, my slacks.
I want my slacks back.
Who could it be now?
Could it be, could it be the cute stalker?
The stalker everybody wishes was stalking them.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Oh, you thought I didn't know about you, did, did, did you?
Well, old, old Bobby, he knows all, sees all.
And he pipes all that information down to us followers here in the tower studio,
uh, headquarters, dungeon, basement, penthouse.
Where we, we, uh, have these, uh, rock stars and, and all those guys.
I've seen it all.
Taking some of them glass equipment stuff.
Uh, but we, we still need your, your pledge, of course.
And and, and, and you could, you could, uh, you could too.
Come on.
Everybody wants to.
You know Philly wants to.
Don't you?
Yeah.
Come on.
What's the matter?
You scared?
You afraid?
You afraid Momo's gonna catch it?
You, you afraid, you afraid you gonna lose your plates?
cool. Oh, what's the matter? We might get diseases. Oh, come on, man. Let's go out to the graveyard
and desecrate. Make satanic symbols. Make fun of religion. Yeah, man. Sure, kids. Go on. Go on.
Do it. See where it gets you. You'll just be one more name in Bob's big book of bubs.
Bob's burnt out bubs. Those he leads to experiment with the occult and metaphysics,
ufology and Bigfoot and all that superstitious nonsense and parapsychotic phenomenons and
horse mutilation.
Crack circles and giant, huge chupacabra monster pterodactyls and scorpion beings.
Oh, yeah, yeah. Monsters. There's real live monsters.
We are young people.
Godzilla.
That's a metaphor.
Man is metaphorical.
By virtue of the cosmos and all the powers in command.
And virtue of the form and all else that has that power.
We won't go.
You seem a little nervous, my friend.
When the strength is up by your soul.
You're telling me from beyond.
You'd better be ready.
To speak your piece.
You call me from beyond.
You disturb my rest of sleep.
With your childhood games.
You don't know what you're playing.
You're playing with me.
This is not a game for little boys and girls.
This is your life.
You're not a monster.
Look, we're not just another stupid army of elephants.
Listen to the music backwards in reverse.
It's the truth.
They won't.
It's not like I'll
give it to them.
Nail it them.
No way.
You all came this far.
No walk.
You're to blame.
And I found the truth is in the taking
A rock through which I will need a life
It's you, it's the pit of your face
But never worry
You're ready for me
Can it be ready to face the consequences?
It's never too late to redeem yourself
One last chance
That's all you have
It's up to you
You're ready for me
No escaping my eyes
You'll see them in every dream
You're ready
You'll never escape me
I'm here
The sun will never shine with me right again
Would you like to make a pact?
You're ready for me from the outside
You've got me ready to face the truth, my friend
I'm here for you
So hang on to me
And I won't do it alone
Come on with me
And I'm ready to take on the truth
Face the truth
Be against me
For fingernails
The sandwiches were forced to eat
And then he said,
He had exactly 24 minutes to get these people to believe somehow.
They must jump the church or they will die.
What button can we push?
The sexual buttons have all been pushed.
The drunk buttons have all been pushed.
How about simple repetition of a word?
Bob.
You say it now.
Can you say it, sir, please?
Bob.
Now say it like a paralyzed child trying to communicate.
Say, Bob.
Bob.
Now I can't wait to say this.
Now I'm going to get you to do it.
Okay, you and the front row, we are going to do it now.
No.
No, I don't want you to say Bob.
I want you to get doing it now.
Thank you very much.
Lets do this.
Perfect!
Thank you, Lonesome Cowboy Dave!
Oh yes, I forgot about that!
Well anyway, I'm sorry that I did that.
I was very unprepared tonight too. Anyway, here's the bottom line of the whole thing.
See, I was the guy that almost came up with that internet joke, you know,
the internet joke about Johnny Black when he comes back and everybody wearing ape suits
and stuff. Do you know that joke?
Okay, for those of you who don't, you gotta go and see it.
When John Black comes back and all those guys land, everybody dress up in ape suits
like landing on him. So while I was only the guy who
almost came up with that joke, I did come up with this joke.
Okay, there's this guy. He's got like a regular normal head
and a nice normal body and everything, but he's got this little teeny
tiny growth, a little my growth that looks like a head coming out of his neck
right here.
So the guy walks into a bar, see, and he pulls out a two dollar
bill and slaps it on the counter and he says,
just give me a beer. And the bartender
says, hey buddy, we don't serve freaks in here.
And the little teeny head on the side of the guy's neck pipes up,
hey buddy, cut me some slack! I've been trying to get rid of this asshole for the last
three days!
I think we started a little real preaching going on.
If your body's in a mess,
it's the only one you have.
You wanna take away the flame,
or go out and look beneath the rain.
So once the farmer's gone to bed,
I'll send that ass out ahead.
There's never a thing
all you gotta do is wait.
The Faith in I!
Yes friends, I'm not talking about hate.
I'm talking about eight! Dinner at eight!
That's right, let's eat!
The glory of the faith!
The glory and communion of food!
The mighty hot dog!
The gigantic falafel stick!
The wonderful hummus and bread!
Oh friends, you could probably be saved by food,
or anything else that you eat,
but believe me now, just one time,
I can only heal your bodies!
Faith and hope and charity,
and simple relativity,
they can make you understand,
All you gotta do is pray,
All you gotta do is take his hand,
Remember what someone said,
Ask the man in front of you,
He'll never have to leave,
All you gotta do is believe in God!
The Faith in I!
Oh friends, can I put my hands on you?
Strang is a man of supernatural power!
His eyes can see a thousand miles!
Truly a mystic guru genie man
He can see your future
He can see your past
And if you bend over
He can see your up
Oh, he's got everything he needs
To heal or sicken you
Trust the man inside your head
Oh, friends, we want to put our hands on you
We'd like to get down in there
And grope every one of you
Just put our hands all over you
But we just can't do that
But we will someday
Can I put my hands on you?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Whoo!
Reverend Ivan Stang, ladies and gentlemen.
I'm Sly Secret Orchard.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Oh, friends, oh, we would like to put our hands
all over every one of you.
Look at this.
According to a Reuters wire service report in August,
lobbyists in Bonn, Germany,
called the Working Group for the Unemployed
held a series of rallies to demand
six weeks annual paid vacation
for people out of work.
Pointing out that those looking for work
often are under greater stress than those with jobs
and thus need a longer holiday.
Praise those unemployed workers of Germany
demanding a longer vacation.
Friends, that is subgeniusness in action.
Whoo!
They give you a half an inch and you take 40 miles.
Now, this kind of thing can go on a little bit too.
It can get too intense.
In August, a couple from Silver Springs, Maryland,
were arrested for indecent exposure
at an adult cinema in Baltimore
after the husband had arranged for four men
to have sex with his wife on the premises
of this adult theater.
According to the police, several other males
in the theater complained, apparently,
because the live sex interfered with their enjoyment
of the sex on the screen.
Friends, I guess you could say there is perhaps
such a thing as too much slack.
I mean, did those guys actually stop and think?
Did they really want the live sex to stop?
So, you know, friends, as they said in Clockwork Art,
the colors of the real world are never so really real
as when you video them on the screen, you know?
And, um, friends, you know, that causes a thing like,
when you read about a thing like that,
you have to ask yourself, what is slack?
Howdy, boys and girls.
I'm Mr. Frolic.
Let's see what's in our mailbag.
Why, it's a shrunken head!
I'm back in institution.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
Does that mean they're going to keep you in there?
No, I have to stay in a little bit longer.
I don't like thinking about it.
Is that the kind of place, like the show in the movies,
where they hose you?
Just when you're, about once a week,
they put you in a big tank and hose you down with fire hoses?
Yeah.
To clean you?
Yeah, they get, that sound goes off, the eh, eh, eh, eh,
and all them guys in them suits come in.
And then after that, then they just, you know,
they come in with them suits and them big thermal things there
and stuff like start poking you.
It feels real hot.
And then you got to get, all get hurried in another room.
Then they just turn the hoses on us and it's not very quick.
You're still staying there now?
Yeah, I can't, I told you, man, I'm in here.
I had a little problem before.
Got into an argument in the bar.
And they said, you know, you're going back here for a while.
And I said, well, what's a while?
And they said, until your attitude changes and you can talk to Vinsky.
Dr. Vinsky about it.
And Dr. Vinsky ain't helping me.
And Dr. Psychopath Finder obviously didn't help me none
or else it wouldn't be in this problem.
And, you know, it's just getting worse.
I don't have to worry about claustrophobia anymore, Dr. Trophobia,
because he's on vacation.
There's people around here, you just wouldn't believe the things they can do
to the human body, the kind of pain they can inflict.
I don't care who I'm talking to on the radio.
I'm talking to you on the radio.
I'm talking to you on the phone, you know.
Well, you know, I'm surprised that they let you talk.
Are you sure that you're talking on the phone and not just hooked up to a machine
imagining that you're talking to on the radio?
How the hell would I know right now?
You know, I don't practically repeat my damn brain, Jim.
You know, all I want to do is watch the hearings and stuff.
And then they all come in here, you know, and they start staking me and threw me.
That's okay, man.
I don't blame you.
I mean, all your friends are in the hearing.
It looks like a phone to me.
I don't know.
The hearings are about your friends.
And I'm sure that it bothers you.
How does it feel?
How does that make you feel, Dave?
Well, I don't know.
That's a rather difficult question to answer.
You don't mind talking about it, do you, Dave?
Oh, not at all.
People, where are you going?
People, what do you say?
Do you keep falling into little fat lumps of clay?
The TV.
The TV is calling.
Please don't go away.
The children are bawling.
But you can't go out and play.
There's only one sin handed down from above.
People dying in guilt's death, living in love, in love, in love, in love.
All of the people, please don't go away.
People, where are you going on each Sunday morn?
While you play to your monster, the kids are watching porn
Do they really see beyond those crowns of thorns?
The mall after buildings where my brother was born
There's only one sin that I do not know of
People dying and killed instead of living in love
In love
This is Chaz Smith, Einstein's Secret Orchestra
And there is a werewolf
There's only one sin.
Aaaaaah.
Yes, love is the sin.
I guess that means, man, it's probably
extra fun to do it then,
huh?
Extra fun to do it then, huh?
Yeah.
This
is love.
Now, Bob,
there is a man who, uh,
who claims to be channeling God.
Uh, I can't recall what this man's
name is. No, no, no, no.
Uh, he's a secular
guy, and he's got books out, and he claims
to be channeling God.
And I kind of wonder,
um, I know, yeah, the guy,
Van Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob,
Bob, my, my, my,
but you do have a soft,
delicate throat.
A candy-colored clown
they call the Sandman
tiptoes to my room
every night
and just as sprinkles stardust
and to whisper
go to sleep
everything is
alright.
Cities of the world woke up today to
potential tragedy in outer space.
The vehicle has exploded.
I've just picked up a fault in the
drive unit.
It's going to go 100%
failure within 72 hours.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob,
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob,
Bob, Bob, Bob,
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob,
So you feel that you have some conflicts
regarding religion that need to be resolved.
Would you like to
discuss those, Dave?
Yeah, I think that...
How does that make you feel, Dave?
Well, the first experiment they did
was what did it all wrong
to me, trying to teach me God
that way. You know, that ain't right.
Sticking them things up different
places in me, you know, and then making
me pray all these different prayers. I don't know what the hell
they was even talking about.
I'm sorry to hear that, Dave. Tell me more.
Well, the first
they started to implant these little
religious devices, these little
things in my body, crucifixes,
little Madonna's and different
little things like that. There's no bigger than a thumbnail.
Some of them are so small, you know.
So what do you feel about little
Madonna's, Dave?
Well, when they're dancing around my head in my
pig sleep, I don't mind, but when I'm
fully awake and alert and maybe being
prodded around with those big hot thermal
sticks, then that's a whole
different can of tuna.
I hear what you are saying, Dave.
How does that make you feel?
It makes me sad.
It makes me happy. It makes me
filled with kind of a preternatural
delight. I can't explain because I'm
vibrating the whole time. You know what I
mean?
I'm afraid I can't do that, Dave.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Did I screw up some place
along the line to cause this all to happen?
I mean, you have to bring home some evidence saying,
hey folks, it wasn't my fault.
Take a look at this picture.
Something happened back there and I wasn't back there.
Any penetration
penetration of
penetration of the heat shield would have
possibly allowed a heat leak plasma leak and eventually a burn through during the process
of entry that would be trippy huh as these are sitting there all these birds are flying around
let's put it this
children
into the
loves
you
god
Oh, Bob loves you.
And you love Bob.
And if you don't love Bob, you know what happens?
He'll kill you.
He'll Bob you out.
Drink the Kool-Aid.
Drink the Kool-Aid, children.
Doc Smith had a fellow who was working as a chemist at the National Bureau of Standards one afternoon.
Two days later, he had conquered the whole galaxy.
I was looking at my crystal ball and it just went completely blank.
I just inserted my crystal ball into the, uh,
into the end of my spaceship.
I didn't insert it.
Oh my God, you put the Dynasium's crystals into the hull already, Chaz.
We're there. We're there.
Oh my God, you put the Dynasium's crystals into the hull already?
Not only did they build a spaceship in their backyards and take off the next day,
but they didn't stop at the moon.
They were shipping their space.
The first time you could do a kill
being the Reveal Space gentleman?
A Sage.
I wanna go.
New York, old Raja.
Now, what do you call it?
What would be the equivalent insult for Greys to the term Tom or Apple?
Tom.
What would you call a Grey who is like a human lover?
Yeah, come on.
What would you call a Grey who just, you know, he was, he kind of forsook his Grey heritage
and was a human lover?
A human mimicker.
Primophile.
Yeah.
That's delicious.
That's a good one.
Homophile.
And it's kind of, yeah.
Well, that sounds like something they already got down here.
Yeah, no, I like primophile.
It's kind of poetic.
Primophile.
Yeah, but you wonder if it has to do with firstness or primacy.
That's the axis that made it.
Number 1797.
Yes, my queen.
You have been found guilty of primophilia.
I cannot resist the lures of the humans.
Well, then they would also be attracted to monkeys if they had real primophilia.
Cast, cast Grey number 4005 into the mulch pit and paint him on the stomachs of the other
worthy Greys.
Hey, is there someone there?
Yeah, we're going to paint you with maglev paint, buddy.
Hello?
I'm a necropedophile.
Oh, that's old.
When everybody slugs his feet, his feet are dead.
The two nuclear superpowers and their leaders stood eyeball to eyeball.
A sickly, frenzied passion for that wasting form began to obsess me.
No, no, no, no.
I've broken through the wall of inertia and reached my goal.
The challenge is to bring up a bright sprout from this dry, parched ground.
Yes.
Deep inside.
To launch a great seed up into space and carry our kind out into the galactic brotherhood
where we'll probably end up being the shoeshine boys of the galactics.
I would not be so sure.
For the first few million years.
No, I don't think we will be lower than when we arrived there.
I think that we are.
Yeah, you think the galactics are going to roll the red carpet out for a bunch of monkeys
that just fell out of the tree by galactic standards.
Who don't even have a patron.
Yeah, that's true.
All the time.
By ourselves.
Here, just us.
Earth, Earth, Earthers.
Damn two biped monkey face boys.
An atomic bomb.
The most powerful explosive yet developed.
We have the technology.
Sometimes it feels like a night.
We had visited a very alien and very hostile and lifeless planet.
And we saw the Earth as the only home that we know of within our near space capable of supporting life.
And we recognize the absolute necessity to protect and nurture and take care of this environment.
An invisible being that cannot be disintegrated by atomic fission.
Oh Skipper, that is a scientific impossibility.
There it goes.
Oh, that's the last of that.
The purging last of the bad blood of Bob out of our bowels.
And wasn't that invigorating?
The blabbering bladders of the bad Bob blood.
It's the ink or the biolog-
I can breathe again.
I had arrived here by my own choosing and I had no intention of ever going back.
I was going through.
Look, the blasts are increasing.
Doctor, look.
The color of the blasts.
Oh dear God.
What?
Doctor, it's nitrogen, isn't it?
Nitrogen?
What?
The fools.
The everlasting fools, I warn you.
The blasts.
More and more.
They started something they couldn't end.
The color of the blasts.
They've set off hydrogen atoms.
I don't know what-
We used uranium, plutonium, and when the initial blast was over, that was all.
But hydrogen, that's part of life.
One reaction sets off the other like setting off an endless chain until-
Look down there.
Blast.
Faster and faster.
They're spreading.
The fools.
God help the fools.
The sheet of flame.
Around the Earth.
Doctor, tell me, what is it?
It burned up all the atmosphere.
Burned up?
Reynolds, what does he mean?
The chain reaction burned up all the air.
Now, throughout my relationship with God,
I have tried different methods of sex.
You can have sex with God, and it's okay just as long as you wear a condom.
Those are the aliens that are hiding in plain view.
I mean, they're right out in front of us.
You never actually saw one of them, though.
They had a real face, right?
Well, how would I know?
I mean, we all might have-
They might be around us all the time, and we wouldn't know.
Yeah, but you made it sound as if you had heard or had some touch to come on me and-
But you know what's going on, where it's basically saying that they knew what they described their face to you.
And you say it was horrific, like was Gorgonzola in Pegasus and that?
Yeah, exactly.
They were hideous like Gorgonzola, like that thing that drips off of his face.
Yeah.
When he gets all worked up.
And that's why Medusa had to hang a shield up there,
so he could look at it and say, check this out, man.
You need to say it, you know?
Right.
It was like Medusa had the super power of turning people to stone,
but gorgonzola had that smell that could even kill medusa well that's what you were saying
if the cash wanted to be actually decomposed in space he would have to transfer them smells into
the chambers where they make them into different tones whatever they are like if you're playing
illuminati new world order on some secret orchestra and you use the plug-in the gorgonzola
plug-in you can like if you get that when it's infected that will take your opponent's uh
uh chain or device or like him or lonesome cowboy dave or whatever and you know then you can convert
you could you get their powers yeah but if you start double clicking on them things come up i
heard that whole civilization disappeared this is dr q ellis here coming to you live from friendly
island in tonga just minutes from the international dateline i'm here to cover one of the first few
rupturings to take place on this historic day of course being a clone i'm
designed for the fact that i i will be destroyed i i welcome my i remote 142.
okay 55 damn it what time okay full 99 full i i of course reuters and the ap and the rest
will not be covering today's events uh the news blackout will continue right up until the bitter
bitter end taped news has been gathered from the conspiracy media's battle
all the Bengalier news will be back on this gio SRLED 5 squadrabs
meeting where teams in western american market
will tell their friends or
Fatal error. Stack collapse. Memory overlap. 738.
Alright, this one's shot. Activate remote destruct sequence, just in case.
Well, somebody was thinking of it. Where else are we going to come up there?
Oh, they're all... Well, I mean, as soon as one person thinks of it, then a hundred monkeys are going to start doing it.
That won't take long.
If that hundred... If that first monkey ran off the edge of the cliff, would all your hundred monkeys go following it?
Definitely. They see one monkey watching their fish in the water, and next thing you know, ten years later, everybody's watching their fish in the water, and they all jump in.
They all stand up like lemmings, or like the hundred lemmings.
The hundred and twelve hundred monkeys?
The twelve hundred monkeys.
Cold, persistent fingers swarmed over my body, tugging at me and sucking me away from the machine.
I held tight to Wiener as a man holds fast to life.
I kicked them away with my feet.
Hurry, Dudley, hurry!
Get these levers quickly, or we're done!
One more turn, and it's...
You touch me, I'll throw the switch.
The truth about real sex with God, and that...
That will help me gain victory over the power of lust in my life.
I mean, you could have the most perverse thought in the world.
Pass through your mind.
Perhaps you've tried some of those.
Invite that thought into your life, and sit down and have a cup of coffee with it.
Cut a snow down, you're moving too fast.
You got a man of morning distance.
Kicking around the cobblestone.
Look for fun and feeling great.
You got a man of morning distance.
Look for fun and feeling groovy.
Got nerve teats that do no promises to keep.
Dabbled in a drowsiness, ready for sleep.
Love at the moment, it's in drive-by, with space on the beat.
Life of love, you always groovy.
La-da-da-da-da-da-da, feeling groovy.
Hello, lamppost, what you knowin'?
I've come to watch your flowers growin'
Ain't you got no rhymes for me?
Do, do, do, feelin' groovy
Feelin' groovy
I'm feelin'
groovy
God is in his holy temple
Earthly thoughts be silent now
Oh, um, oh, oh, background music.
Dear friends, that was of course Chaz Smith.
A lot of Einstein's Secret Orchestra going on tonight.
Chaz actually edited this show.
You might have heard of it.
You might say most of what was, has been played was, uh...
What?
Every man needs about three.
One to make babies with.
One to groove with.
What the hell?
One to chase after.
How about a couple of honest-to-goodness virgins?
Send me about a dozen assorted variety.
How about me for starters?
What the hell is this?
What did your mama say?
She used to make me take piano lessons from this groovy young guy.
We used to sit just pressing our thighs together.
Well, one week we were practicing, and all of a sudden his hand went up my skirt.
Hey, hey, hey, enough of that, kids.
Oh, that's, uh, F-Friday Jones.
Figures.
Yeah, Friday Jones figures.
She has some good figures.
Anyway, I thought I was putting in...
That.
That's what I thought I was putting in.
Uh, but I put in Friday.
Yes, her little Russ Meyer type there.
I haven't really listened to that yet.
Well, now we know what's on there.
Russ Meyer movie soundtracks.
That's some pretty groovy stuff, man.
And, uh, you're listening to the Groovy Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack, uh,
tonight's show, uh, and last, like last week's, all done at the same time, mostly by Chaz.
Uh, uh, the kind of thing.
Chaz Smith.
Not the man heard playing in the background.
Uh, that's the Hell Pope Huey.
He's the Hell Pope, and I'm the Sacred Scribe.
But Chaz is the cantor, and he, he can indeed, and he did.
Uh, we also heard Bill T. Miller's, uh, song, You Rang, uh, very early in the show.
Uh, that's, uh, Kings of Feedback, Bill T. Miller.
And, of course, Lonesome Cowboy Dave, who is part of Einstein's Secret Orchestra,
but he was doing kind of a live, uh, audience show.
And, uh, I heard the audience thing, uh, from the Euclid Tavern Devival November 8th,
not very long ago, recorded by myself on the donated, uh, deck.
And, uh, boy, this music makes me talk fast.
Uh, everything else on there was from Chaz's volume 10, uh, mix, edit, uh, of, uh, stuff.
Uh, that we do on the radio, on his radio show, ESO Radio, which you can hear, um, on
the internet no matter where you are, friends.
They're out of WCSB in Cleveland, but on the internet, if you go to this address,
hurl yourself to this URL, uh, www.wcsb.org.
That's wcsb.org.
And, uh, on Sunday, on Thursday nights, 11 o'clock, uh, Eastern Time,
you can find me.
You can hear that radio show on the audioactive, uh, internet, uh, thing.
And you can call in.
You can be on the show.
And then you'd be on this show.
It's like you call in to Chaz's show, and Chaz sends me the, and we do a thing, a worshipful,
you know, subgenius religious thing.
And then Chaz sends me the tape, or he edits together one of these type things.
And then suddenly you're a big, you know, big highly paid star, just like all the rest of us.
So, so, such a great job.
And, oh, gosh.
Uh, yeah.
.
The color of the dream I had not too long ago
Misty blue and lilac too, never to grow old
There you were under the tree of sun
Screaming so peacefully
In your hand a flower plays
Waiting there for me
I have never laid eyes on you
Not before
This timeless day
But you woke and you
You smiled my name
And you stole my heart away
You stole my heart away
And you left the girl
Yeah, alright
Girl
Girl, come here
Give me that dream
Golden rose, the color of the dream I had
Not too long ago
Misty blue and lilac too
Never to grow old
Golden rose, the color of the dream I had
Misty blue and lilac too
Golden rose, golden rose
It's only a dream
it's only a dream
I would like to tell someone around the street
if the sky was filled with flowers and stars
while the sun kissed the mountains blue
There's twelve moons playing across the rainbow
About me and you
Golden road
Got another man in the war
That's the end of the show
Alright, now close your eyes
Take a deep breath
And then
You have seen
You are slowly
Sinking
If any outside thoughts
Should come into your mind
Simply brush them aside
And I want to begin
By having you focus your attention
Upon the psychic center of your body
And I want to begin
None of what you see is real
It's all a dream
Out of band experience
Bill T. Miller
His album
Drum Army