Ladies and gentlemen, presenting the subgenius of OVSLUG.
I feel real good. And then other times, I feel like I was going to get sick right in my stomach.
Well, that doesn't take much doing.
Yes, friends, we're still editing the recordings of X-Day, but luckily we have some shows from before X-Day.
This will be part two of Dr. Sinister's Radio Synesthesia, which follows our Slack every Sunday night on WCSB Cleveland.
Thank you.
So, away with the show. No, we want the show. We don't want to send it away. Whatever.
And, yeah, some not music in the background. Not music.
The artists themselves said it is not music.
What is it?
I don't know.
Sounds like music to me.
Sounds a lot like music to me.
Is it music to your ears?
Yes.
It's melodic.
It's not anti-music.
And rhythmic.
Thank God.
The name of the title.
How is it not music?
The title of the album is not music.
If there was one thing I could go back in time and remove from the book of the subgenius, it would be all that stuff about anti-music.
Wasn't that Paul Maritas?
No.
Don't you think you'd rather take back...
No, no, no. That was Doctors for Bob, and they meant it.
When they said anti-music, they really meant it.
Don't you think you'd rather take back the date of July 5th, 1998?
It doesn't have anything to do with me.
I...
I added...
Philo and I added that bit about anti-music.
July 5th, 1998 was given unto Bob by Jehovah One, the alien space god from some corporate sin galaxy.
You know, there's...
During his...
His immaculation.
The immaculation of Bob in 1953.
There have been a lot of cults out there throughout history that said the world was going to end on a particular date.
That date came and ended, and the cult...
Let's see.
Let's just say it did not prosper quite the way it did before that date came and went.
They were left with...
Jehovah's Witnesses have done great.
And they've predicted five specific ends of the world, and yet they're still going strong.
I'm one of Jehovah One's witnesses.
Yeah, well...
Ah.
They're very witless.
Jehovah's Witnesses.
Can I be a witness?
Yeah, but I've been hearing all night long on this radio station.
A bunch of Jehovah's Witnesses.
At the Kingdom Hall.
You know the best thing about Jehovah's Witnesses?
I will be done.
Well, actually, I gotta take that back.
The best thing about Jehovah's Witnesses is they have Prince now.
The second best thing about Jehovah's Witnesses is they don't vote.
They have Prince?
Yes.
Hey, speaking of Prince...
Are these formerly known as Prince?
On Saturday night at...
They used to have Michael Jackson.
X Day.
Morris Day and the Time.
That's right.
At our special event.
Morris Day and the Time will be at X Day.
They'll be playing Saturday night.
Don't you wish you'd signed...
I've signed up because now it's too late.
Or is it?
No, I've really gotta make it...
Oh, it's not too late.
We're having a seance and a Beatles reunion.
With real Beatles.
We're...
The Dung Beatles.
The Tenacious D has agreed to conduct the Bobby Awards.
Wow.
And Penn and Teller will be special guests on the Hour of Slack,
although I expect Teller probably won't.
I thought it was at 8 a.m. actually.
He does talk, but not professionally.
Well, what doesn't kill...
What doesn't kill you makes you richer.
The Rolling Stones canceled, by the way,
and I'm not at all surprised.
They needed their Metamucil.
It wasn't.
It was that they didn't want to play...
By the way, you've been making...
...after the swinging love corpses.
That's a hard act to follow.
And I had to, and that's...
Right, exactly.
By the way, you've all been making jokes
about how old the Rolling Stones are
since they were younger than you are now.
Well, that's true.
That's easy.
They are...
Real, real easy.
It's all right to poke fun at mortals, isn't it?
Hello, you're on the air.
Hello, subgenii.
Hello, hello, hello.
It's no money, Mark.
No money, Mark.
We know why we won't see you at Wisteria.
No money.
That's it.
Yeah, sorry about that,
but I did want to ask you something.
Will the flying spaghetti monster be there?
Of course.
I'm sure he will.
He's ubiquitous.
Yeah, he's always...
He's one of the biggest fans
and butt kissers of J.R. Bob Dog.
That flying spaghetti monster
was one of the earliest bobbies.
We deprogrammed him.
We sent him on his way,
and he's done pretty well.
Actually, it's a tentacular,
undifferentiated mass
dripping with red sauce.
We've all been touched by his noodley appendage.
My God's bigger than your God.
My God's better than your...
Well, I'm subgenius.
This Astro Sturgis ripped off...
The Discordians.
My God, he's a Sturgis boy.
...was first,
and the diminuses just ripped him off.
Hilarious.
These people don't understand
that there is such a thing as prefiguration.
Just as Apollonius of Tyana
prefigured the Christ of the early Christians,
so did these early primitive fumblings
manage to suggest the refined doctrine...
It's ludely appendage.
...which would come later.
In fact, which comes terminally, ultimately.
You know, nobody ever accuses us
of ripping off the Boo-Hoo Bible.
Do you remember that one?
What about Art Kleps?
I've got a copy.
Right, Art Kleps.
Art Kleps and the Boo-Hoo Bible.
No, I have not heard of this Boo-Hoo Bible.
I had that long before I ever...
It was the sacred Bible of the hippies years ago.
Yeah, predated the Discordians.
And a most entertaining book.
So you can find a copy of anything online,
although I doubt if it can get there by X day.
But you could try to order the...
Art Kleps was the chief Boo-Hoo of the...
The Boo-Hoos.
Yes, of the Boo-Hoos.
And he wrote the Boo-Hoo Bible,
or compiled it from sacred sources.
And frankly...
What about the Bobo Bible?
For me, the Merry Pranksters
was the most influential religious organization.
And the Church of the Blinding Light, too.
Either you're on the bus or you're off the bus.
Blinding by the light.
Oh, blinding light.
Oh, light that blinds.
Ken Kesey was a subjugator.
A subgenius minister, by the way.
I cannot see.
Yes, I know.
Look out for me.
You know what?
Frequently on this program, we'll sit around...
The few people who still call in,
we'll be talking about the people who used to call in.
Yeah, if you're so tough.
And what I really aspire to,
what I really aspire to,
is to be able to talk about people who used to call in...
Sex music.
And have them be as notable
as the people who used to be subgenie.
Well, it's your show.
If I could...
You ought to do that.
If I could have that going for me,
I'd feel like I accomplished something in life.
The people who used to be subgeniuses.
The people under the stairs.
What the hell went wrong with them?
Did they get deprogrammed?
No, usually what happens is
we have to kind of discontinue their line,
usually due to sexual predator behavior.
Their line...
Revenstein has gone out through all the earth
and their words unto the end of the world.
That's been, unfortunately,
the most common reason for banishment
is predatory sexual behavior.
Can you tell me...
I hate to say it.
I'm not going to ask you to name names.
But I kind of love to.
I'm not going to ask you to name names
if they're not already in the public record,
but what can you say about it?
Name names and break the muck.
Because, actually, Revenstein,
you know, you proposed a voyage to Germany.
How about that?
Yeah, Revenstein.
What about that?
Proposed by a friend of the family,
who lives over there.
I want to go to Germany.
I was creeped out by that proposition at first.
But you insisted that these people were legit.
And I trusted your judgment.
Because if anybody is used to dealing with weirdos
and sniffing out sketchy business from miles away,
I would trust your judgment on that matter
if nobody else's.
The heron wolf.
Well, if I said that,
then you better pick up on it.
You have seen some very disturbing behavior
from humans.
I've developed pretty good cridor.
So, like, what kind of...
Over the years.
I mean, like,
we need more anecdotes on this program.
Because we can't get an antidote
to the poison that this show is,
so we'll have to settle for anecdotes.
The Church of the Subgenius
is the antidote to all placebos.
So you can get rid of those old...
Anything that was making you feel good before,
after the Church of the Subgenius is done with it,
it won't help you ever again.
You could probably tell...
Placebos will all be useless.
But you could probably tell some very disturbing stories
about people who have gotten involved
with your movement in the past and...
Without naming names.
And...
Yeah, we can't.
And made a disgrace of themselves.
We're not trying to humiliate anybody.
They did that for themselves, but...
We'd love to hear more of those stories.
Well, it's up to you, Stang,
if you want to open the secret archives
of the Church of the Subgenius.
They wiped my memory of that sort of thing.
I'm not allowed to criticize the tribe.
I went through the...
re-education camps.
I can't...
It's in blank to all that stuff.
I was the worst one.
What about the Department of Information?
I can tell you all the stupid things I did.
Oh, wait.
I'm still in the middle of it, though.
That's the problem with these kind of stories.
You sit down to try to write the history
of the Church of the Subgenius,
and all that comes out is more stuff
to put in the next history of the Church of the Subgenius.
Here, Stang, your stories are most convincing.
Clip seeds.
I...
We've got another caller here.
Okay, let's have him.
You're on the air.
Hello?
Hey, Dr. Sinister.
What happened to Dave?
I don't know what happened to Dave.
He...
Hopefully he'll be back.
We'll meet again some sunny day,
but new caller, you're on the air.
Dr. Sinister.
That's me.
This is a rhetorical question.
I love rhetorical questions.
Am I a dumb shit?
Stupid ass dumb fuck?
Or what?
I'm going to guess yes, you are.
Well...
Only because I think that most people are.
There's a...
And since you sound like a person...
That's a sad, sorry way to be, I guess.
Since you are...
That's my comment on that.
You sound like a person.
And I'm going to guess that you actually are a person,
so I think statistically, if I had to...
If I were a gambling man...
Oh, you're going to pick me apart now?
No, I'm not going to take you apart.
Peace. Bye.
But you know what?
I'm an idiot myself.
Really?
Yeah.
Don't let my fancy big words fool you.
I'm an idiot.
I haven't heard any fancy big words.
Yeah.
You're not...
You don't seem like the pusillanimous type.
Pusillanimous?
Yeah.
I forgot what that word means.
I confused that word with pugnacious.
No, it's small-minded.
Small-minded.
Yes, I am small-minded.
Look at that.
It's tiny.
Well, you know, I didn't mean to accuse you of being small-minded.
It was just a word of kindness, or anything like that.
I didn't mean to accuse you of having a...
All right, all right.
Let's forgive him.
Let's say the church had the genius, okay?
We admit it.
We admit right up front, okay?
We're not the sharpest crayons in the pencil box, or whatever.
We...
Whatever the...
Eat your heart out, Mensa.
That's stang?
Yeah.
The genius stang?
That's a good one.
That's a good...
He's right over there, officer.
It's a killer.
Do your duty.
Go ahead.
man?
Would you like to ask
Reverend Stang? He's kind of
old, but you could ask him something.
I know J.R. Bob
for what he wants. We got him on ice
here. We're in communication
with his brain.
I don't have an app.
Alright, well. Another joke
on the story. What about Burning Man, you folks?
You folks have been talking about Burning Man.
Well, I go every year.
I have to, but...
How long have you been going there?
Since... Does anyone still go to Burning Man?
Since 1996.
I would go to... Princess, we and I
would both happily go to Burning Man
every single year if we
could afford it. And also if it
wasn't just a couple of weeks after
we burn ourselves out.
Then it wasn't a damn fool waste of time.
Well, we gotta...
You know, we think
globularly and act loco.
Well, that makes sense.
That's why we go to the loco campground
and burn people up and get burned.
And burn each other.
It burns! It burns!
So, what's your...
What's your question, maybe,
with Larry Harvey?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You ask the question. We give you the answer.
You're the one calling in.
You ask the question. State short question, please.
Larry Harvey and, uh...
Harry Larvey, yes.
No, Larry Harvey.
Oh, okay.
And John Law.
John Law was involved with that whole thing.
Not anymore.
Yeah, I know.
Well, and Michael Michael and all those other guys.
Ranger...
What do they call them?
Danger Rangers.
Red Rock Rangers.
Danger Ranger.
He's still around.
He's still there.
He's still on the job.
Michael Michael still?
Danger Ranger, yes, is still there.
All right.
Roaming the waste spaces of the Earth.
Yeah, and so they got a big old fence
around the whole thing now, right?
Well, the BLM makes us keep all the loonies
inside the crates.
Lazy folks corral, as they call it.
And it's to keep the hats that blow off
everyone's head contained.
Somewhere, there are two of my hats
up against that fence.
Really?
Yeah.
I bet you could sell one of those hats
on eBay or something, right?
I bet you could, too,
but I'm not perceiving a question here.
Did you have a question to ask?
Why is Starwood cooler than Burning Man?
Because you've never heard of it.
That's why.
So check it out.
Starwood Festival.
Just two weeks.
Southern Ohio?
Wisteria, yeah.
It's in Southern Ohio near Athens.
Clear-cut case of Wisteria.
Although, actually, this year,
Starwood Festival will be on board my escape vessel
because the world will be destroyed
and I will rescue the Wisteria campground,
beam it up onto my...
And anyone who paid to go to Starwood,
even if they're pink boys,
can go to Starwood.
Then they will be ejected into the void of outer space
if they haven't bought a subject.
They've been a genius membership by the end of Starwood.
They've actually been that obtuse,
that remiss,
that they haven't...
They'll be turned out of the spaceship
into the vacuum of space
and we'll watch them pop
like an inflated balloon.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to step on you there.
What is the quintessential difference
between Starwood and Burning Man
out in Nevada?
Well, burning...
Moisture.
Yeah, they got water.
That's right.
Yeah.
They've got water and living things,
life, not just a...
And a lack of corporate douchebags.
How about that?
That's right.
They don't have any internet millionaires.
The corporate douchebags
have not yet discovered Starwood,
but they discovered Burning Man
like 15 years ago.
I'm afraid they did.
I thought that corporate douchebags
weren't allowed to advertise there.
Well, not...
I mean, aside from church,
besides genius.
Actually, if we really wanted to discuss this,
there are many people who pay outrageous sums
so they can camp in some cool camp.
These misguided souls
have nothing to do with the core mission,
but this is all too informal to discuss, really.
I was hoping there was a question here
that we could answer.
Oh.
So I haven't asked my question yet?
Go ahead.
Everybody else does,
as a friend of mine used to say.
I remember her.
She...
Gosh.
So I'm here on my...
I'm on my last question.
Let's have it.
The last question.
I don't...
I don't divert...
I don't divert or advert to, uh,
uh, pop TV or anything like that.
What do they...
What do they say on, uh, the...
On my favorite Martian?
...one of the most popular, uh, shows on TV?
Like, your last question, your, uh...
I'll buy that for a dollar.
Is that your question?
What do they say on...
I'll buy that for a dollar.
I'm just...
I'm just saying, like, the real meta...
I'm just saying.
...meta culture...
Just saying.
You know what I'm saying?
...kind of stupid people...
Note your sign.
This is the kind of thing that they say.
They watch.
Yeah, they're...
They're stupid.
They want stupid...
They have this on the tip of their tongue,
and they...
They know what, you know...
I just don't know that.
Well, out with it, man.
I'm trying to...
I'm trying to just kind of break you guys down...
Why don't you stop beating around the bush
and just come out and say what it is that you want to say?
Yeah, we're all friends here.
What the hell...
What the hell's wrong with this country?
Hmm.
Where to begin?
Let me see.
They, uh...
Well, I'll tell you where to begin.
I'll tell you where to begin.
The problem with this country...
People.
...is that it's full of human beings.
That's exactly right.
This is a beautiful land.
The Grand Canyon, the Great Lakes.
You'll never see things like that anywhere else on the planet.
But there's trash everywhere called Homo sapiens,
as opposed to Homo excelsior,
which is the advanced subgenius race.
All right.
So, if you are the only last living beings on the Earth,
how are you going to take care of these last vestiges of...
Oh, now he's asking...
...of...
He's asking another question.
Oh, boy.
Yeah, you think you get an...
No, we're not going to be the last people on Earth.
We're going to be the only people who leave Earth.
Everybody else stays on Earth.
You're thinking of that Tom Cruise movie
where the most privileged person on Earth
gets to be the only person on Earth.
Don't go there.
Sorry.
I don't...
I don't want anything to do with Tom Cruise.
Well, there was another...
You're too proud to admit that you've seen a Tom Cruise movie.
There was also a Will Smith movie
where he got to be the last guy on Earth.
And then...
Everybody wants the last word.
Yes.
They learn that from the Internet.
People see these movies
and they think they are going to be the last sole survivor.
I'm afraid the statistics,
the actuarial formula is quite against that.
You'd have a better chance
of winning the publisher's clearinghouse sweepstakes.
You just...
And yet we've all tried.
Yes, it's true.
It's human to try, to dream, to have self-deception,
but one must...
agree, at least in some small part of one's being,
that there ain't no chance in Hades.
You know, I've never tried.
Does that make me subhuman or...
A quitter, eh, son?
Oh.
Don't worry.
See, this is where I'd like to step in real quick here
and point out the whole concept of sub and super.
Okay.
That all depends on what direction...
When you go out into outer space,
there is no up or down.
That's right.
So to say that something is above something
or below something,
is meaningless.
It's just a matter of which direction you're looking.
Relativity.
Maybe above or below the orbital plane.
Yeah.
You just have to be there.
Yeah, yeah.
You just have to...
Look up.
Look down.
Look all around.
Stick up your thumb.
A subgenius is not something that is below a genius.
A subgenius is someone who's a genius of all things sub.
Or who is beneath a genius of some kind.
Actually, I've tried to use that argument before
when I was arguing with a born-again Christian.
Like, what denomination are you?
I said, I'm a subgenius.
And they're like, what the heck is that?
And I said, well, you know, God is the genius, of course.
It comes from the Latin root for, you know,
like the Greek root genesis, you know, genius.
Yes.
We are all below.
We are all below the creator.
Genius is with sighing scent.
We are subgenii.
Well, the genius need not be the creator.
It need not...
It only need to be a spirit.
Not the almighty spirit.
Not the biggest jumbo ghost in the room
that likes blood like all ghosts do.
That's why the Old Testament is full of putting blood out for the old guy.
No, it's different now.
We have different spirits that we converse with.
No simple seances, table knocking,
streams of ectoplasm emanating from a medium's belly.
That's all old thinking.
The old way.
We have something new that we communicate with.
Well, I'm pretty certain that if there is any such thing as the divine,
if there is any such thing as a deity,
I'm convinced...
He was in multiple maniacs.
I'm convinced that they are many and not one.
Mm-hmm.
That's right.
And that they don't agree with each other all the time.
E pluribus unum.
And that explains so much about how the universe works.
The fact that the gods can't agree with each other on anything.
You know, we see one such thing as the divine.
Just ask John Waters.
Yes, I was there.
I...
Well, yes, the moving waters at their priest-like task
of pure ablution round Earth's human shores.
Let's take another caller here real quick.
You're on the air.
Hello?
Oh, hello.
This is Rev Wildhorse out here in Olympia,
checking in with the gang.
Well, Wildhouse.
Who was that masked man anyway?
A fiery horse with a speed of light
and a hearty high old silver.
That's right.
And Johnny Depp.
Yeah.
When I was a sprout in Indiana,
I was told this story.
A well-watered sprout.
And a riddle.
And maybe you can finally answer it.
I've been waiting for nearly 30 years for this to happen.
Wrapped in an enigma and covered with creamy milk chocolate.
Why does the porridge bird lay his egg in the air?
Say that one more time, please.
Why is that?
How did I know it was hot?
Lazy leg in the air.
Was the porridge too hot?
Was it too hot or too cold or just right?
Just right.
In the Goldilocks zone.
Goldilocks has been in the news lately.
The porridge bird never lands, my dear son,
but circulates through the sky.
Oh, yeah, man.
We make the tough calls.
The egg also is buffeted by the streams of the upper atmosphere
and never descends.
From it eventually comes the next generation of porridge birds.
And the porridge itself is their leavings,
sifting and filtering,
through the atmosphere into the bowls of the truly desperate.
When I was a little kid, I thought that porridge was...
Called manna by the ancients.
When I was a little kid, I presumed that the word porridge
was derived from the word poor because poor people are always eating it
in the stories that I would hear about porridge.
It's good for you.
I was never actually fed porridge as a child.
Well, you haven't lived until you've...
Well, then I found out later on that oatmeal could be classified as porridge.
You never owned oatmeal?
Yeah, right.
Tor like oatmeal.
But it was never called porridge.
Yes.
Until now.
I might have eaten it more heartily if it had been presented as porridge
because it was something exotic from...
Eat heartily, honky.
...from stories.
Okay.
That's the story.
And Will Stigman sticks to your ribs.
I was going to ask, Red Stang there, you know, if the saucers make it this year,
I can't make it out to Wisteria.
I don't have any money either.
Could you guys stop by here on the way out?
If you paid your 35 bucks, they will stop you.
However, all the good spots...
Some people think they're good.
...some people think this will be already taken and you'll be in the vestibule or the
lobby, which is still paradise compared to everywhere else.
So make sure you pay your 35 bucks and there'll be a seat on the saucers for you.
It's been paid.
And like Red Stang got the Grand Canyon, well, I got Palouse Falls out there in Eastern Washington.
Okay.
We'll come and get you.
Were you under the impression that the exes only are going to show up at this one rinky-dink
campground in Ohio?
They're going to line up north to south over the entire planet and let it turn under them
while they vacuum up the saved and spray napalm onto the unsaved or whatever.
Oh, no.
Something like that.
So you can just sit there.
You'll be able to watch it on television.
It'll start in the Pacific Ocean and where the dateline starts.
That's where it will first be, 7 a.m. on July 5th, 1998.
Oh, no.
That's when the planet rotates on its own.
1998?
Yes.
We don't know what year it is.
Have you?
I get the impression that this listener has not been reading his prescriptures.
Actually, what am I
I would say that this person needs to read something besides pamphlet number one.
I know it's expensive to buy those books, but
Actually, one of my favorite
This is all explained over and over again.
One of my favorite theories about the whole 1998
1998 mystery.
Let's hear it.
I don't hear chat while everybody talks over one another.
Sorry.
You question the whole 1998 thing, and this is what you call a divine mystery.
That's true.
I believe because it is impossible.
It's something that we can't explain.
We know it is true, but we can't explain it.
We don't know what planet this is.
We don't know what time this is.
We don't know what year it is.
We don't know nothing, boy.
We don't know nothing.
We don't know how
And our man might not even belong to us.
Yeah.
We don't know how wine becomes the blood of Christ, and we don't know how 1998
I don't know nothing about it.
I don't know anything about it.
has not yet come, even though we think it's 2014.
These are mysteries, my son.
My favorite theory
I don't know anything about it.
My favorite theory came out a few years ago, though, that everything was delayed by 19
years.
If you recall, back in 2003, when we were about to invade Iraq, you were talking about
this in one of your sermons once we were even staying.
Right.
George W. Bush, when trying to advocate going to war with Iraq, he said, the goal of this
war is peace.
War is peace.
The president says war is peace.
Iraq is white.
That means
2000 years.
2003 was actually 1984.
That means that the real X Day, the real 1998, will be 2017.
Right.
And then Donald Rumsfeld gets one over at the next zebra crossing.
And that's only three years away now.
But you know, like sometimes when you're waiting for the airporter to take you to the
airplane, they come early.
Well, that could happen also.
So it could happen this year.
We have to be ready.
We have to be there and in place each time.
X Day will come in a time you know not.
It could be tomorrow.
It could be in the next two minutes.
Are you ready?
Did you
Bob, pay your dues to Bob.
Or is your soul safe?
Ye never know when the master cometh.
I did my excrehowever you say that.
God damn it!
No man knows.
Some excremeditation, yes.
Somebody open a window.
Bob will come as a thief in the night.
And in your pants if you aren't careful.
So stay zipped up.
I will.
And if you can't keep it in your pants
Except for when the cows are coming out.
keep it in the family.
Flip up, flip up, and knock it out.
I'm not going to do that.
I'm not going to sleep with cows.
Look up.
Look down.
Good night, my brother.
Look all around.
Good night, brother.
Stick up your thumb.
God, you're dumb.
Praise Bob.
Not dumb.
Let's pause real quick for station identification.
This is WCSB Cleveland 89.3 FM.
I'm not dumb.
Portions of the following broadcast will be objectionable to some members of the audience.
Therefore, WCSB advises listening discretion.
God, you're dumb.
Oh, yeah.
That's what he said to me.
Yeah.
And any views or opinions expressed on this program are not necessarily those of WCSB
or Cleveland State University.
We are here to help you.
I had to cut you out there for a second so I could do my disclaimer without you talking
over me.
What a cut up.
That's okay.
Cut it out.
All right.
I'll take my cut now.
I'll talk to everyone another time.
Have a great Fourth of July.
We never do the Fourth of July.
We have no money, Mark.
The Fourth of July, we can't celebrate.
It's the day before the end of the world.
The Fourth of July is for pinks, for sad veterans parades and fireworks and booze and too much
noise.
You know, we're not allowed to celebrate the Fourth of July anymore because, you know,
there's the Florida.
Well, the name of the...
Because, like, you know, the World Cup is getting higher ratings than the World Series
in the United States.
Okay, well then.
Have a great next
day.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Exactly.
You too.
And we'll see ya!
See ya on the saucers, brother.
Next thing you know we'll be using the metric system.
Actually, no money, Mark by definition is pretty much stuck here on the gross breathe.
Yeah, but he said he was paid up.
I believe.
No, that was the other guy.
I don't think No Money Mark could be.
Oh, I see.
See, here's the thing, though.
Although if Dobbs had mercy, he would certainly be ruptured along with the rest of us.
But mercy is not what this is all about.
Mercy shall sit between, throned in celestial sheen.
With radiant feet, the tissue of the clouds down steel.
Come on!
I believe No Money Mark is going to come up with some cash at the last minute.
What is mercy, really?
Altruism.
Empathy.
Feeling for another.
But if you are familiar with the works of the philosopher La Rochevique,
even a saint does his saintly things for his own good feelings.
No one really does anything for anyone else.
You are a saint because it makes you feel good about yourself.
No, I'm not.
According to La Rochevique.
You know what would be a really interesting experiment, then?
I'm sorry if I cuss.
Too late.
You should reiterate what that guy's name was.
Who the author of that term was.
Please.
What term, son?
Term of...
Endearment.
Thank you.
Okay.
Try endearment.
Hmm.
Well...
The problem is...
The problem with saints.
They're just as selfish as everybody else.
They just won't admit it.
That's right.
They're showing off how egoless they are.
Now, how much sense does that make?
Come on.
That's right.
What if we could create, either through genetic engineering or through selective brain injury,
a person who gets no satisfaction of any kind from anything?
Well, that would be a tormented spirit.
And then program them to do nothing but good works.
Just a degree away from the human condition.
There are many people who have toiled.
Endlessly.
But even if they don't receive satisfaction, they're still seeking personal satisfaction.
They're not doing it for other folks.
They're doing it to make the pain go away.
And that's something we have to acknowledge.
I'm pretty happy doing what I do on a daily basis without having to prove anything to anyone.
You don't have to prove anything to me.
You have to prove it to yourself.
To your secret heart.
Okay.
Well, I don't have to prove anything.
I don't have to prove anything to you, nor do I have to prove anything to myself.
Not now, not yet.
But the great day is coming closer and closer.
When the secrets of all hearts shall be known.
What are you referring to?
I'm speaking of that time when the sea gives up its dead and monsters walk the earth.
And the dreadful judge in middle air shall spread his throne to judge the quick and the dead.
Yes, it I will end them.
The wise-ass caller shall be at the door.
The judgment.
Laundry detergent is stronger than dirt.
Is that me?
I'm sorry.
It could be.
Reverend Dang?
Could be.
What is wisdom?
Why that?
I just don't have any belief or faith in all this altruism of like some other great, gracious beings.
Do you believe that altruism is a vice?
Well, I do.
Can you talk about my son?
You don't say.
You can't say that.
You can't be telling me you don't believe in J.R. Bob Dobbs.
We're speaking of things which are...
I feel altruism...
...faltering in belief.
...is a vice.
A vice grip that will not unclench from these tormented souls until the day of liberation.
Yeah, exactly.
The great day of liberation when all prisoners shall be released.
When you told me that you think altruism is a vice, you sounded just like every 17-year-old.
I'm the 17-year-old I ever met who just finished reading Atlas Shrugged.
Yeah, some pouting Ayn Rand fan.
I've never read it.
And, you know, what's the guy, the girl's name, whatever the hell it is.
Ayn Rand.
Ayn Rand Paul.
Do you believe that advancing your own self-interest is the only moral imperative?
Shevayn Rond.
The only... I'm sorry, can you repeat that?
Yeah, I will repeat that. Do you believe that advancing your own self-interest is the only moral imperative?
Answer quickly.
The only moral...
The only moral imperative.
The only moral imperative...
The only moral imperative is to advance your own self-interest. Do you believe that's true or not?
I don't want to say immoral imperative.
I said the only moral imperative. Do you believe that would be to advance your own self-interest?
Advance your own self-interest. So, advance my...
I'm sorry, the time has expired.
You're really parsing this phrase more than you need to for the purposes of our conversation.
No, I mean, is it my own moral imperative or is it our...
Now he's asking another question.
I used what's called a definite article.
Okay.
The word the.
I got that.
Do you believe the only moral imperative is to advance your own self-interest?
Well, put up or shut up?
Kill them all. Let Bob sort them out.
If you can't answer that with a yes or no, then just say you can't answer it with a yes or no.
Oye.
Advancing...
To the rear.
Uh...
You can spa on your Sunday pants.
No, I don't see my moral imperative...
I didn't say your moral imperative.
I said do you believe or do you not believe or are you not sure that the only moral imperative is advancing one's own self-interest?
Can we go home now?
Do you believe this, do you not believe this, or are you not sure?
Stop snoring, sleepo.
Oh, I nodded off there.
Come on.
Jesus, God.
It don't have nothing to do with good or evil.
People, it's just robots.
And I'm the robot program to tell y'all you're nothing but robots.
That's all it is.
You're just programming.
It's all a bunch of monkeys.
Automatons.
Doing what evolution forced you to do for the last million years just to get dinner.
Speaking of that, what is for dinner?
I'm back at another number, but I'll advance my point here right now.
Eventually.
You seem to have the idea that there's an infinite time for this.
Any second now.
I don't think my moral imperative...
Don't push that button behind you.
Three, two, one, go!
Has anything to do with...
Be funny!
Pot stickers?
I don't think my moral imperative has anything to do with anyone else in the world.
Cock-a-doodle-don't.
Yeah, see, but there you go again saying my moral imperative, and that wasn't what I...
I was going to ask you about your moral imperative.
Me, me, me, me, me, me, me.
You sounded very good at parsing questions before, and you don't sound very good at parsing
them anymore.
Me, me, me, me, me, me.
There is a fundamental misunderstanding going on here.
I didn't ask you the question.
No, you really didn't, but that's okay.
I didn't expect you to answer the question because it does not serve your interest to
answer any of these questions we ask you.
No, come on.
We're just sitting around here trying to have some laughs at your expense.
Princess, princess, we're just trying to have some fun.
We're just trying to have some fun.
I want to have laughs too.
I want to have laughs against moral humanity and all the other crap that goes on in this
world and all the stupidity that has to do...
What about that giant belly laugh in the dark?
All the bullshit?
Okay, I can see...
I can see that.
I can see bullshit, right?
Wake up, Reverend Stang.
It's almost time to go.
I've heard this so many times.
It's groundhog day.
Did somebody leave...
Who brought my answer machine in here?
I thought it might help.
I'm sorry.
That was forward of me.
No, we had a difficult subject I thought we could...
Now he's gone totally cuckoo.
I hope you're pleased with yourself.
So anyway...
He's off howling in the hell of his own making.
So anyway, anyway.
I'm going to go to bed.
Isn't it great how I can just shut everybody up by saying, anyway.
Yeah, that's right.
You've got about 15 minutes left in the program.
It works for a second.
I've got growling and all kinds of shit going on right now.
Those are just growling pains.
Easy there, fella.
Let's see if we can retain at least the semblance of our human shape.
Princess, wait.
I'm going to decolletage my moral imperative.
Stop that.
Throw a towel over it.
There's so much tittering going on in here.
It's all getting me.
And you cover up too, baby.
We've got to maintain some decorum here.
Decorum or decolletage?
Well, I...
It's getting swollen.
Well, I haven't seen a sight like that since I was weaned.
My moral imperative is about to explode.
Your moral imperative needs a cold shower.
Emergency, emergency.
A kitten is up a tree.
Call the fire department.
Where's the fire?
If your eyes, officer.
It's an old one, Princess.
Yeah, right.
The older they are, the better.
I'm just a pushover for an old joke.
Moldy, oldie.
I will call her pushover.
Because she'll do everything for everybody.
Now, that's Suzy the floozy you're talking about.
Yeah, that's true.
She's been pulling that train for nigh on to 30-some-odd years now.
Mm-hmm.
Old gal.
She's a great old gal, though.
That old Suzy the floozy.
She'll be there.
I think she's a great old gal.
Suzy the floozy will be at the judgment.
Not old.
She'll be at the day of judgment.
I believe she's a year younger than me, Princess.
She's still not old.
Her spirit isn't old.
Of course not.
Right, right.
Sixty...
I love that.
Sixty's not old.
No, and sixty's the new forty, and forty's the new twenty, and twenty's the new ten,
and you end up as an Indian.
Well, when I was 25, I thought sixty was damn old, and I guess I must be those who think young then.
I guess you must be.
When lively folk work up a thirst, they'll hear them ask for Pepsi first.
They pick the right one, the modern light one, and all...
Let's take one more caller here.
Oh, it's Pepsi.
You're on the air.
Hey, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Everybody shut up for a second.
See, that guy thought he was going to say something on the air, but nobody could hear
him.
That guy.
That's a great example, a great example of not knowing...
Not understanding how to be a hit and run caller.
A good hit and run caller will make sure that his voice is heard.
You try to do a show, and there's always one failure.
And that hit and run caller fails.
Oh, he's gone already.
Oh, too bad.
How old is he?
Small and apart.
That's part of time they share.
Could somebody go and let the apprentice in?
Oh, he's down there at the gate?
The apprentice is not...
Just at the door up here by the elevator.
Sure.
Open the vast portal.
Open sesame.
The apprentice is here.
Keith won't be here tonight, by the way, folks.
Oh, he won't?
I'll be filling in for Keith tonight.
Oh, okay.
So, you think things are crazy now.
Well, they're just getting started.
Oh.
Because it's getting pretty late.
Yes.
Late at night, man.
And I kind of lose it.
It's later than you think.
Especially for a Californian.
Oh, yeah.
Really.
How long have you been here?
Not long enough.
I'm still not acclimatized.
Do you get jet lag in a three-hour time difference?
Actually, let me be quite honest here.
I never get jet lag.
That never bothers me.
It never bothers me.
I've never traveled far enough to experience such a thing.
Why should anyone be subjected to such an invigoration?
And my general...
My general...
My general sleeping habits are kind of strange.
Like a...
They pat you down.
They make you go through the see-you-naked machine.
They make you take off your shoes.
And it's just not worth it.
But to communicate with this group of fellow believers, I have to put myself through certain
cantrips and certain evolutions.
I like the word cantrip.
Thank you for using that word tonight.
Don't mention it.
I got a million of them.
We got a couple more callers lined up here.
Turn that caller into the cold and damp.
You're on the air.
And you are on air.
Oh, hey.
This is Mark Buda.
How you guys doing?
Hello, Buda.
Up to you.
Yeah, I was just thinking.
I remembered it just hit me.
The first time I met Reverend Stein.
The first time?
Which was in 1997.
He had just dropped off in...
1997.
...Sonic College.
...where I met Reverend Stein.
And he stopped at the Brushwood Center for the first strange days.
Mm-hmm.
We remember.
And we were talking.
We were talking.
And all of a sudden, this naked guy jumps on his van.
Hooga hooga, hooga booga.
And the guy goes, oh.
And he was probably tripping on acid.
He goes, yeah.
Nobody understands me.
He was on something.
And Stang looks at him and goes...
He's on a van.
Nobody understands me, says the naked guy jumping on top of a van.
And Stang looks at him and goes, you're gonna understand something.
You don't get the hell off my van.
And this guy jumped off the van like it was 200 degrees.
And Stang looks at me and goes, what's going on?
I've never hit a person in my whole life, but oh God, that felt so good.
He couldn't help but automatically raise the temperature of the van 200 degrees.
Wow.
Generally, we restrain ourselves and don't perform impudent miracles.
I don't think you can say you've really lived if you've never hit someone, though.
No.
Fuck away, good-bye, Stang.
This greeting on my impious crest has been...
You haven't...
Dr. Sinister.
Yes.
I have to ask again.
Is it true that the next...
Next show host is not coming in?
Keith will not be in tonight.
Oh, that's...
The reason I ask is apparently there's someone outside waiting to be on Keith's show, a regular
guest of his called Sheriff Deputy.
Holy guacamole.
Sheriff Deputy.
So you can use the big eyeball there.
Is there a back door to this place?
Dr. Sinister is using...
Did he give a name?
Crystal ball?
I'm glad I'm not the only person that has that reaction to those things.
Did he give a name?
I gotta leave.
I got a pie in the oven.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Where is the guy?
He's like in the next...
Next show host.
He's in the middle lot.
He's in the middle lot?
I don't see his body weight.
He's off our radar.
There's a flashing red light down there.
This is...
Well, if he comes to the door, we'll see him and let him in.
Okay, I gotta go.
Goodbye, everybody.
If he comes to the door, we'll see him and let him in.
As soon as I heard that, red lights went off.
I'm not talking with you.
Go tell him he's not gonna be here.
Well, he'll see us leaving in about 10 minutes.
He's welcome anyway.
He can't make it to Chicken Stock with the rest of us.
He's a jolly good fellow if he's the real guy.
Well, this is a weird thing, too, and I'll share with that.
I guess...
I guess if I were to know something earlier, I could've came down and filled in the guy
who could've came down there, but I made plans.
Well...
You made plans to sit at home and call in instead.
No.
Those are all going by the board, aren't they?
I should've thought of that when you had a chance.
Getting on with something...
But I will talk with Keith, and he needs a fill-in.
No, Keith will...
You're gonna have to talk with him, because he's not coming in.
Right.
Exactly.
This is some talking future reference.
We quit making predictions here in the Church of the Subgenius.
Yeah, boy, do I hate being right all the time.
I predict the sun will come out tomorrow.
And I predict the women...
No, it's gonna be cloudy.
I predict cities made of rubber on the moon.
I predict women's underwear made of titanium steel.
But...
It's invisible.
Aztecs invented the vacation.
I predict Obama minions disguised as Google Earth trucks spying on subgeniuses.
Obabo.
I'm sorry.
The new name is Obabo.
The new Obama is...
Yeah, the subgenius Obama.
The bizarro Obama.
Obabo.
He looks like Bi-Bo of the Archie McPhee company mascot.
Hell yeah.
You're on the air.
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Hold on, hold on.
Hey, caller.
Caller.
You failed.
Caller, you failed.
You get an F for the day.
You ever heard the phrase, look before you leap?
Was that Dave?
That was Dave.
No.
That wasn't Dave.
No, that was not Dave.
Dave's not here.
That was not Dave.
That was a Patsy imitator.
A lot of times Dave calls my phone doing a voice and I don't think it's Dave.
That was Snow Toilet.
A Patsy, eh?
Yeah.
Dave sometimes out maneuvers himself.
There's the phrase, look before you leap, and then there's the phrase, listen before
you talk.
Listen to make sure that you're not being talked over if you have something that you
really need to say.
And okay, now I can see that Don is here.
Okay.
How are you?
Don is here.
Put her there.
Don's coming.
How are you, buddy?
Praise Don.
He's a jolly good fella.
Yeah, I remember the praise Don skissum.
Me too, and Lou, and all that.
Yeah, praise Don.
Yeah, that never ends.
It's a real fucking fuck on.
Oh, I think we just had another caller who doesn't know how to listen to make sure he's
not being talked over before saying something and hanging up.
I think we have five more minutes.
Nobody could hear what you just said.
Put the real talk show on.
I could hear it because I have a superhuman sense of hearing.
What a sucker.
Yes, you are.
Thank goodness I am stone deaf.
I have not heard a word anybody said this whole show.
Man, I had a couple of interesting hearing tests recently.
I was out for a hike on a park trail last weekend with my dad, who is older than you
two.
Put it together.
And I could hear.
125.
I could hear.
I could hear a bicycle behind us, squeaking of the metal parts behind us.
Squeak.
And I knew to get out of the way because I could hear the bike coming.
My dad did not hear the bike coming.
He was surprised by it.
And then there was a TV show I was watching where there was some kind of ultrasonic like
beeping going on saying like, oh, you couldn't hear this because you're too old to hear it.
But I could hear it.
It was really quiet but loud at the same time and a very high pitched like, I can't even
do this.
Wow.
Dr. Sinister, you know those headphones that you have on your head right now?
Yeah, I had to turn them way down.
I had to turn them way down because you were the last person to use them.
Well, eventually you will find yourself cranking them up a little bit more each time.
Every time.
And someday that bicycle is going to come behind you and knock you right over.
They say it's inevitable.
Over time you will lose some range.
But you get to be old like the Reverend Steele.
Yeah, I'm still under 40, so.
Well, 40 is the new 30.
30 is the new 20.
20 is the new kid.
Not biologically.
No, that's true.
Only fashion.
Only can't.
Only culture.
70 is the old.
I found out when I hit 50.
He's only 70 years young.
He can get the lifestyle lift.
When I hit 50, it's like screw fashion.
For kids from six to 60s.
That's the thing.
Oldsters 90 years young.
All right, so we've got another caller here who is probably not going to listen to see
whether or not anyone's talking over him before he says his thing.
Well, go ahead and try.
Let's find out.
All right, now you're on the air and I want you to listen before you say anything to make
sure nobody's talking over you so we can actually hear what you have to say before you hang
up on us.
Okay.
This is Potsy and I'm going to take my ice cream truck and buy a bunch of weed.
I'm going to buy a bunch of weed.
Ice cream.
I don't think that's Potsy.
Everybody's a crappy comedian.
Nobody's got any ice cream here.
Next.
Ice cream.
You scream.
We all scream.
That's it.
For Bob.
Yeah, we've only got, we've got less than two minutes.
So all kidding aside, if you really want to do, shout one last barbaric yawp, this might
be the time.
Yawp.
You're on the air.
Oy-yi.
Yes, this is Fred.
Hello, Fred.
I'm your biggest fan.
I'm your guys' biggest fan.
Wow, thank you.
Yes.
That's pretty good.
Fucker late, but Potsy.
What was that?
I couldn't quite hear it.
Oh, God.
The butternut bread, Fred.
Try to erase that.
Bring home the butternut bread.
Aren't you glad you stuck around for an extra two hours?
Hasn't this been the best two hours of radio you've ever done?
Boy, I'll say.
That's an evil laugh
Somehow you feel that you've left out
The most important thing
Bring home the butternut bread
Fred
And now
Drop dead Fred
Yeah drop dead
The actor who played him just died recently
It's true and it's what he gets for being in that
Phoebe Cates epic
There used to be a Cleveland band
Called the Phoebe Cates
They don't know more
Time hath endless rarities
And shows of all varieties
Yeah
Well speaking of time
It is just about midnight
Oh thank god
My grandfather's head
Was too large for the shelf
Last call
Last call of the night
Can I have like a double
With
Last call to breakfast
No matter how you feel
I know this is not Keith
March around the table
And have fun with Don McNeil
How is everybody doing
Are those guys trying to break into the station
Yeah
Are they trying to break into your car
I'm sorry about your asthma caller
Yes
Sucks to your asthma
I feel your pain
Yeah I remember
The doctor Igor
Asthma brand
This is actually
I've returned to being gay again
I get to taking up the ass
Oh dear
Well so much for that
That was
Inappropriate
He was doing a great job up until the end there
He was doing a very convincing impression
Right up until the end there
But then it all fell apart
I do a lot of voices myself
My deep Keith voice
Anarchy was loosed upon the world
My deep Keith voice is almost the same as my George Takei voice
That's it
They're very similar
Maybe they are the same
They kind of had this equality like this to their voice
Where they kind of talk this way
Except Keith will say
Good morning
You sound pretty good
They're both fabulous
Well it's been fun
Well that's the most charitable thing you could have possibly said about tonight
Thank you
Yes it has been always
Always
Maybe when I listen back to the recording I'll agree with you
You'll make some sense out of all this mishmash
Hash
Yeah I'll be perfectly happy to wait a couple weeks for the copies
No need to hang around to copy them tonight
No need to wait around for the copies
I know you're good for it
So
This has been Synesthesia Special Edition
We've been staying Princess Wee and Dr. Howland Owl
For a long time
Farewell one and all
Well farewell
We will meet again in a place where there is no darkness
Hal can you do a line from Half-Life for us please
Have you seen my coffee cup?
Thank you so much
I have actually played that game just to hear your voice
I'm not kidding
Thank you
I already had a copy of it
Before I found out that you were in it
Well I recorded this year for Plague Incorporated
Awesome
I'm going to a Z.A. meeting
No brains allowed
Kind of like this program
Exactly
That's why I listen
I'm safe
No brains here
Good night doctor
Good night Buddha
Good night
This has been Synesthesia on WCSB Cleveland
Stay tuned for
Well I don't know
A little of this
A little of that
From PR News in Washington
I'm timed to the huge 1997 perversion of the British percent in June
Russian President Vladimir Putin says
June percents were cut
One year ago
PR's report reports
I'm just in time for PR News
President Putin said you're a contagious disease
Putin presented President Petropor
Peace PN provinces
He said to attack PR News
They demanded PR News
Hurricane Brennan says
Watch and uh duh
The hurricane now says
Arthur
On Wall Street
1-8-6-9-4-6
7-4-5
Officials in Nigeria
In a busy marketplace today
And dozens of others
In the northeastern part of the country
At least 8 people were active in that part of the country
No one is feared hurt or dead
But no one is claiming responsibility
President Putin says
This is smart huge PR News
Millions of years after that singularity
What do you think Bob?
You want to do this for a living?
Sure
Let's sit down and have a cup of coffee
This is just like
This is a
This is solid at ordinary temperatures and pressures
Another night with Bob
This damn church
I was born near a damn church
A little village
Simple agricultural
Well praise the Lord and hallelujah
We are the living
Now I'm not going to name any names
In stereo
Somebody has to take this lump from me
More coffee
Will you have one lump or two?
Damn good cup of coffee Bob
Thanks
This is a joke
I like it
Yeah it is it's a show it's just a joke
You sure as hell got that right?
Thank you
How did that happen Bob?
Work hard work concentration and extreme effort
The beginning of brought to fruition
Those things predicted in the before life
And in the pre scriptures
No it's going to be a real pleasure working with you again Bob
Okay it's countdown
Countdown to the end of the show
I'm sure I told you
Kevin is Bob's best man
You got the message
I did
What
Seeing Bob
Has a secret place
Heh heh heh gratuitous
Bob, Bob, Bob!
The breath of the show smells like that.
Get Bob!
We're not back in an hour.
We'll reschedule the rehearsal for first of June.
Okay, all right, fine, fine, fine.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's time to go down, Mr. Blaney.
It's over.
Well, Hal, I don't want to come to rehearsal tomorrow morning.
I'd really rather do something else.
Yeah, I mean, yes, that would be more of a deal.
What?
No, the show's over.
It's over.
The show's over, yeah.
I'm sorry.
No, it's over.
Well, actually, that's all she wrote.
X.9.3 minutes.
A medical facility researching the criminal mind.
Since you had massive head injuries,
I've used a brain from your workplace as a replacement.
So basically, I turned Carl into Skeeter Winnie Dobbs,
and Skeeter turned out to be pretty bad,
so I have to kill him again.
What?
Winnie Dobbs was killed yesterday by the owner of a catering truck.
The victim was wanted by the state police
in connection of two teenage girls.
Murder?
He dug himself out of the grave.
He thought about the op County Jail now over with mother couple Gang
Don't let us deter you from doing business with us again.
You're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
For free information on Bob Dobbs and the Church of the Subgenius,
send a self-addressed stamped envelope to...
Got your pencil ready?
Bob, Post Office Box...
That's Bob, P.O. Box...
1-8-1-4-1-7 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118 www.subgenius.com
Stay tuned and praise Bob!
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show,
and we're even more glad that some listeners have donated enough
to help us keep on going for another couple of months.
Not just this show, but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob and want some of that Slack back to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com front page,
or especially the radio page, or the catalog,
store pages,
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty,
and we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference,
even if it's only once a month from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that
blowjobs.com could go...
blow the way of Steve Jobs if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to
Subgenius Foundation,
P.O. Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Thanks for anything you can do to help let there be Slack.