This is Doug Smith, radio operator. I'm going to bring you a piece of that green cheese for sure.
You're a joke! A dirty joke from one end of this town to the other!
The Self-Genius Power of Self-Genius
This is an urgent public service bulletin from your police department.
A dangerous killer beast is at large. You are asked to remain indoors.
This is an urgent public service bulletin to all citizens.
This whole thing is cockeyed.
Friends, we bid a fond farewell to the great Maynard G. Krebs.
Goodbye, Bob.
Knowing her fate, Atlantis sent out ships to all corners of the Earth.
On board were the Twelve.
The poet, the physician, the farmer, the scientist, the magician, and the other self-genius.
The Self-Genius!
perseverance
Slash back with his spicy crispy slapjack sandwich a spicy crispy slap with fresh lettuce and tomato only at Slack in the box restaurants
Yeah?
Stab me!
Stab me!!!
IMGR
I'm looking the soup in your soul of slugs and say I can't understand what you're saying.
You can't understand what you're saying.
We cannot understand what you're saying.
Price Bob, Price Bob, it's not Price Bob.
From PR News in Washington, I'm sentenced to life in prison for funding Bob.
President Bush envisions as many as 180 people returning to Beijing.
At least 21 people have been ordered to stay on their medication.
On Wall Street, 86105564.
A new study finds that most people with schizophrenia are meeting in Vienna and they've expressed concern about PR News in Washington.
For 14 hours, Rudy Wells and his team of highly trained specialists painstakingly labor over the battered and broken body of Bobby.
How do you feel?
You're now faster, stronger, more durable than you ever were.
Just what did you guys do to me?
I don't want any part of any of it.
I'm getting out of here.
Stay in your bed.
Wild man, wild man.
This will stop him.
Then.
I didn't think we'd ever stop him.
How do you feel?
I'm stronger, faster, better.
But you left out one thing.
I'm not a man anymore.
I'm a friend.
Personal diary.
But somebody ought to Moonpie her.
What's the problem, boy?
I've been busting my hump all week for that withered old clam and all I got was 50 cents.
Hey, when I was your age, 50 cents was a lot of money.
Really?
Nah.
Dad, I've done everything I could and I've only got 35 bucks.
I am through with working.
Working is for chumps.
Son, I'm proud of you.
I was twice your age before I figured that out.
From PR News in Washington, I'm found in home.
roads and other sites. The massive Bush administration is now grappling with two
Japanese tourists after an assassination attempt on William Rehnquist. Homeland Security Secretary
Michael Chertoff says corpses will be home. The third fire in more than a week in Paris
is blamed for at least 14 deaths. Authorities suspect PR News in Washington.
And the water gonna come and I have no place to stay.
Well, all that night I sat on the lever and the moon.
Thinking about my baby and my happy home.
If it keeps on raining, the lever's going to break.
Can you hear me?
Can you guys believe how this guy ripped off Led Zeppelin?
Yeah, it's remarkable what goes on in this country nowadays.
People come up with some idea and claim that they invented the idea,
when in reality the idea was pre-invented.
Well, you would think that...
Well, by the Ministry of Culture, anyway.
I mean, what has happened to the trademark laws and copyright laws in this country?
It's back to the Ministry of Culture.
A singer can rip off a famous rock band like Led Zeppelin.
He's probably made...
He's probably made $25 dollars off of this thing.
Well, did you hear about...
This guy was involved with Robert Plant in a sexually deviant manner.
He was paid off under the table and beside the table by some sort of Rosicrucian, I guess it was,
from the Legal Defense Department.
They call them legal aides.
And I guess they're all condemned to hell for their...
Do you think that...
All witches are condemned to hell, too.
Yeah, but who does the condemning?
I'd like to know.
God.
Is God?
Well, there's one particular God.
Let's put it that way.
Oh, so he is the one in particular that's responsible for all this placebo mess and this garbage.
Well, there's the one that does the hell stuff and there's probably another one that doesn't.
So how many God, God, God, Gods would you say there is?
None.
But I was told to say that by the Spirit.
I was seized up and told in the Spirit to go out and preach the word of no God at all.
The guy in the movie Wise Blood.
I was taught by an elderly Bolshevik.
I got wise...
Oh, no, that was the crazy guy that said that.
Well, he was...
Yeah, that was the elderly Bolshevik.
The hero said,
I am not a preacher.
I'm a festerer of wounds.
I'm a rubber of salt in the eyes of man.
Well, I had to face it.
I'm a preacher, all right.
I'm a preacher of Bob's word.
I'm an undergrown pubish, Stan.
What shall I do?
Send $30.
I've polished the bump many times.
Send $30 to J.R. Bob Doves.
I bet you never actually...
You never actually did that, did you, Dave?
No, and I wonder...
I've seen that he would have been left behind if the exodus had come as promised on July 5th, 1998,
which may still be happening anytime.
Have you heard the phosphorescent rumors?
What?
That they're going around picking up subgena individually rather than this mass rupture that you had, you know, hoped to make a couple bucks off of.
I think they've been taking body parts individually, like your hair, my memory, Princess Wee's morals.
No, just kidding.
We have...
We have to throw in that...
We have to get those gags in somehow before we're gagged.
Well, thank God I don't...
I still don't have any gonads to speak of.
I just wanted to make that perfectly...
Did you really have to gonad there?
I mean, come on.
God, God, God, God, God.
That's the German word, you know, but we can't say the Arabic word.
God, God, God, God.
Allah, Allah, Allah, Allah.
We can't say that one.
How come God spoke German, Stan?
I'd like to know about some of this evangelical stuff.
So that we wouldn't be able to understand what he was saying.
Yeah, I think...
Yes, what is the...
If you're off something...
Well, we have some collages coming up that condemn the administration's foot dragging
as it dragged its feet off the rowboat through the waters of all the cities that have been flooded.
It sounds like a body dredging or something.
This is really hurricane season.
You know, the next hurricane is supposed to hit Phoenix, Arizona.
And there's one in China.
Somewhere in China, they're dealing with a typhoon.
Well, I heard...
The sixth one to come up after they go into the Omega, you know, the Alpha Omega cycle,
where they use Greek letters instead of funny names like Rita and Jane and stuff like that,
is scheduled to hit Denver on November the 7th.
That's where the eye will cross in the great, bolded, mile-high city of Denver.
For crying out loud.
Loud.
Praise Bob.
I think we have something about that coming up.
My daughter called me from Los Angeles to inform me that she was driving straight into one of those giant 24,000-acre Los Angeles farms.
Oh, Santa Ana.
Yeah, and I got interested in that, and I found this report from...
I'll go through this real swiftly, but to September 12th,
horror and disbelief swept through the greater Hollywood area this afternoon
as a minor power outage turned the city into a virtual war zone,
and local residents struggled to deal with the devastating aftermath.
Traffic lights fell dark.
Local gyms and sushi restaurants were without power for nearly...
30 minutes, and many businesses were illuminated only by the light of the sun and its blistering 78-degree heat.
Sugar in the raw? Are you kidding me?
sobbed local homosexual and avid salsa dancer Enrique Santoro.
I'm on a South Beach diet, and my insulin levels are going to go crazy if I use this.
Why isn't the rest of the country doing something?
At least 2,000 refugees, the majority of them beautiful,
will travel in a bus convoy to Beverly Hills starting this evening,
and will be sheltered in the...
8-year-old Spago on North Cannon,
where soft omelets with confit bacon and Hudson Valley foie gras
will be airlifted in by the National Guard.
Well, it sounds like paradise staying, but let's get real here.
Halliburton still was given the Los Angeles Reconstruction Contract.
Oh, yeah, yeah. Yeah, Halliburton and them will be cleaning up.
They'll get the big money off of these things.
And not cleaning the swimming pools, and, you know, the sushi restaurants will be running again their way.
I mean, come on, man. Nobody escapes the iron fist.
Nobody escapes the tender little baby booty that's filled with...
All this is not anointing me. It's not...
The other thing was...
Well, this is the sad part about all this.
The mayor of Hollywood, Johnny Grant, told a group of embedded reporters
at a Cuckoo Roo chicken restaurant on Larchmont that, quote,
The scope and scale of this disaster is almost too much to comprehend.
Local car washes are at a standstill.
The tram tour at Universal Studios has been on hold for almost an hour now,
and I've been waiting for a rotisserie leg and thigh with a side of green beans
for upwards of a year.
In 15 minutes, this is truly our tsunami.
Jeez, man, you're putting up the barbed wire in Topanga Canyon.
Yep.
And all of those poor, those poor Los Angelinos.
I feel so bad.
Listen to this.
Listen.
Okay.
A group of chickens masturbating.
Geese.
Can the geese masturbate?
Two.
One.
These geese aren't bad.
That's honking.
Yes.
You can honk along.
That is.
Ha, ha.
Honk it hard.
Honk.
Ha, ha.
The mid-goose does the Mick Jagger dance.
I know that.
He has to lift the legs up a little bit, you know, and he put his one wing on his leg.
Oh, where's my...
Get the coxcomb going, yeah.
Where's my script of the devastatingly cool...
Stang, you're spontaneously among us.
You're not supposed to use a script or refer to any written pieces of paper.
Well, I have to because I have to say the credits, which is all Fernand and Andy Lee
Murr and Norrell Preff did pretty much everything.
And there's no sense in trying to tell people which part of what those two guys did, but
they did almost everything.
Well, who sampled the geeks?
That is hilarious and wonderful.
I don't know.
There was a...
We had some Beatles.
We had the Beatle Barkers did some of our background music there, and that was Kansas
Joe, by the way, doing the levee.
Now, he was involved in the...
When the levee breaks.
Ripped off the Led Zeppelin.
Oh, he was involved in ripping the legs off the Zeppels, or the Zeppelay there.
Yeah.
The brazen ripofferage.
Now, I'm going to play this devastating collage in a second here.
Can I ask you a question first?
Sure.
Because you're smart, and you remember things.
I forgot one.
Ontology recapitulates ontology.
What does that mean?
What?
I forgot.
Ontology recapitulates ontology.
Oh, I can tell you, but I'm not going to because it's too boring and it's all bogus, academic
bull pooey anyway.
I'll show you.
Okay, I'll show you.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
That's a med speak.
Okay, here's the devastating collage, friends, by Phineas Snarko posted this, and it was
by Stephen McQuillan.
I don't think anybody anticipated the breach of the levees.
They anticipated a serious storm.
These levees got breached, and as a result, much of New Orleans is flooded.
He didn't think...
I don't think anybody had anticipated that.
Liar.
Saturday before the storm hit.
If we had a direct hit of a Category 4 or 5 and maybe even a Category 3, we would be
totally inundated with water.
We couldn't pump it all out.
I don't think anybody anticipated the breach of the levees.
The levees in Jefferson Parish, with the tidal surge that is presently forecast, will be
top.
We can expect our community to be significantly underwater and for a number of days.
I don't think anybody anticipated the breach of the levees.
This is a city.
It's built on the coast in an area that has hurricanes and is built below sea levels,
and that is a super.
People have talked for years about whether it makes sense to have a city like that.
I don't think anybody anticipated the breach of the levees.
It looks like Hurricane Sluggo is headed right for us here in America's wetlands.
That's right.
And since New Orleans is below sea level, if a hurricane hit us directly, it could push
the water over the levees and fill it to the top.
Let's act now before it's too late.
This will be a major emergency for American bikers, emergencies, and the future.
And not a time to waste on them.
But instead I will tell you why I'm lowered ourselves, and how we
fail.
It is a dire disaster.
People in the Port of Illinois feel the vulnerability of this damage.
There is a large ciaddadWonbe've facing a guarantee così de rest роль Roaden
rollerci確a?
I never expected we'd have the risk of having a hurricane country.
Down there.
It must have.
How are you?
Wake up!
Said, don't you know me?
I'm your native son.
I'm the city of New Orleans.
I'll be gone when the day is done.
New Orleans is sacred land and I don't want to swim.
It keeps on raining, levees going to break.
I don't think anybody anticipated the breach of the levees.
When the levee breaks, I have no place to stay.
Welcome to New Orleans.
Federal, state, and local governments are working side by side to sustain lives
by ensuring adequate food, water, shelter, and medical supplies for survivors and dedicated citizens.
Our dislocated citizens.
At that time, he was making a big deal about telling the nation that the convention center had been secured.
FEMA's moving supplies and equipment into the hardest hit areas.
All they had done, as Geraldo Rivera actually reported on Fox, was they locked people in.
This is it. This is it. No sugarcoating. No political spitting.
No Republicans or Democrats.
People suffering. Let them go. Let them out of here.
Let them walk over this damn interstate and let them out of here.
I want to get some perspective here because earlier today the images were...
That is perspective.
Hang on a second.
That is all the perspective you need.
Anyone who walks up out of that city now is turned around.
I don't know, man. I don't... Let them walk the hell out of here.
Let them get on that interstate and walk out to the Walmart on the other side of the river.
To some other town.
Some place where you can help them.
All you got here is thousands and thousands of people six days later.
Same clothes.
Where do you think they're going to the bathroom?
They don't wash their hands. They don't wash their face.
These babies.
There are so many babies here.
What the hell?
Come on and rescue me.
Six feet of water in the streets of Louisiana.
You simply get chills every time you see these poor individuals.
So many of these people.
That child that washed us away.
They are so poor.
So many people got lost in the flood.
And they are so blind.
So many people got away on the rain.
I'm alright.
And I'm alright.
I said I'm alright.
I'm alright.
George Bush doesn't care about black people.
Here's Barbara Bush.
So many of the people in the arenas here, you know, were underprivileged anyway.
This is working very well for them.
They're being drawn to careers of service.
When the manpower of government is not enough.
The government is stretched thin.
So we headed down to finally bring presidential leadership to the disaster zone.
President come down.
President's a little fat man.
He made a shame.
What the river has done.
This poor cracker's lame.
Out of the rubbles of Trent Lott's house,
he's had lost his entire house,
there's going to be a fantastic house.
And I'm looking forward to sitting on the porch.
Michael Chertoff, the Secretary of Homeland Security,
sounds like he doesn't know what's been going on at the convention center in New Orleans.
For the past two days.
I have not heard a report of thousands of people in the convention center
who don't have food and water.
Michael Brown, nominated to the post by President Bush,
director of the Federal Emergency Management Agency,
and director of the retarded mismanagement of Hurricane Katrina.
Confirmation hearings for this guy were 42 minutes long.
And only five senators showed up.
Hey there, people, I'm Michael Brown.
Every person in that convention center, we just learned about that today.
Sir, you're not telling me...
There's those bodies that are there.
Sir, you're not telling me you just learned that the folks at the convention center
didn't have food and water until today, are you?
You had no idea they were completely cut off?
Uh-oh.
The federal government did not even know about the convention center people until today.
You just found out about it today.
Don't you guys watch television?
Don't you guys listen to the radio?
I'm George W. Bush.
Disrupting communications.
And I approve this message.
Brownie, you're doing a heck of a job.
The FEMA directors were complaining.
Although, Blackie, quite frankly, I've seen you in better shape.
Kill me, Mom!
George Bush ain't a gold digger.
I'm in need.
But he ain't with no broke niggas.
I got a .
George Bush don't like Black people.
Katrina exposed serious problems in our response capability to the federal government.
And the federal government didn't do its job.
And I take responsibility for what went wrong.
Are we incapable of dealing with a severe attack?
Or another severe storm?
It's in our national interest that we find out exactly what went on and what went wrong.
From PR News in Washington, I'm before the Senate Judiciary Committee.
President Bush says.
The.
We have a few tips so you can be prepared for floods, tornadoes, or even a quake.
You gotta be ready so your heart don't break.
Disaster prep is your responsibility, and mitigation is important to our agency.
People helping people is what we do, and FEMA is there to help see you through.
When disaster strikes, we are at our best, but we're ready all the time because disasters don't rest.
All right.
That was for real.
Amidst all the smells, did you get a sense that there was more crack?
I was struck people blame President Bush, blame President Bush.
He's the same guy that was on 9-11 with the white folks.
He hasn't changed.
The white folks.
The white folks, they are blaming President Bush.
They told me directly they're blaming President Bush.
George Bush, haunted by New Orleans to the last day of his presidency.
There are such low expectations.
Tell me something I don't know.
Expectations are so bad right now.
There are 10,000 dead bodies there that this is actually, Howard, going to be a win for President Bush.
A good one.
Right.
It's going to be much better.
Amidst all the smells.
So now I'm supposed to roll over like an old bitch dog getting my belly scratched?
Yeah.
Look, maybe it's none of my business, but don't you think a man with your talent, that your first obligation is to your gift?
Shouldn't you be doing whatever you have to do to work again?
What would that be, son?
I don't know exactly, but I do know what you're doing with that drink.
You're cutting yourself off from your gift and from Audrey and from your fellow man and from everything your art is about.
I don't know, son.
I'm building.
I'm building a levee.
Gulp by gulp.
Brick by brick.
Putting up a levee to keep that raging river of manure from lapping at my door.
So anyway, Bush is in trouble.
Bush is in trouble.
And he can't enter me.
Creepy little Bush is in trouble.
Devil Bill O'Reilly.
Ew!
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
O'Reilly's.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Propaganda.
You know it.
Creepy.
Nudge.
O'Reilly's.
You know.
Me.
Propaganda.
Now this is great.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Uh.
Um.
How screwed up.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Right.
Terrorism.
With affection.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
O'Reilly's.
Creep.
Some weeks ago, Pat Robertson made a mistake in calling for the assassination.
Calling for the assassination of Bill O'Reilly.
Absolutely.
Most Americans loathe Pat Robertson.
They loathe me.
And that's the truth.
Creepy little Bush is in trouble.
Well that's what's happening.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Put it up.
Turn America into a secular progressive jihad.
Hey, hey.
Try to look like a random shapie.
Come on.
Keep it in.
The Denver Metro area has been recognized by two federal agents.
President Bush says it's just the debris from Hurricane Katrina.
The nation also needs to be hit by the storm.
Our nation joins with them to pray for sorrow.
He's charged with sexual assault, crime of violence, attempted murder, false imprisonment, and other counts.
U.S. Marshals said ventilation ducts.
In sports, Rockies from Arizona tonight at 7, 12, 30, and 2.
News gets brought to you by the victims of Hurricane Katrina.
Denver police hit and killed a four-year-old boy over the weekend.
What's next?
PU.com
I'm Barbara Bush, and I urge you to cook yourself.
Barbara Bush kills one person every hour.
Every day.
And I urge you to get skin cancer.
From PR News in Washington, I'm ordered to pay restitution totaling $134 as well as fines.
Residents of an area of New Orleans may cause more damage to production facilities in the Gulf of Mexico.
And we share that dream.
Just before the close on Wall Street for 10-5-4-7-6-4-4,
North Korea has pledged to give up its nuclear PR news program in Washington.
We need to put the了不起, uh, um, um, a.
Bush, Bush, Bush, um, uh.
Bush, Bush, Bush, uh.
I do wish Katrina had only hit Bush.
From PR News in Washington, I'm from Paris.
The Federal Emergency has ordered tens of thousands of Katrina evacuees.
An agency spokeswoman says the agency
says the agency spokeswoman approved hundreds of dollars, too hastily.
On Wall Street, 10-10-4-4-5-5-20.
French police have been recruiting terrorist insurgents to fight software Caucus.
YPR News in Washington.
I know I've got religion.
It's down in my heart.
The head imam, Pat Robertson, has issued a fatwa against the president of Venezuela.
Where all the guppies come from.
It's time to play the blame game.
Blame.
Let's see how much time we can waste doing this before Lisa comes back.
Right in the middle of when we were supposed to start doing the blame game.
Who's Lisa?
Actually, that gives me a chance to give credits where credits are due.
We don't know who did the L.A. News thing that I read.
But it was signed by Joshua Gates.
Actor and victim.
Victim.
And posted by Bike Painter.
That first criminal incompetence collage was by Stephen.
Stephen McQuillan.
And all the rest were by Fernand and Andy Lemur who does PR News.
And also Norel Pref.
That's spelled N-O-R-E-L-P-R-E-F dot com.
Where you can get that and also his heavy confetti.
Heavy confetti-ish music.
Well, pref is also the Croatian word for fart.
No.
Which you're not allowed to say.
But you can believe in such a thing.
You don't have to reiterate it.
That was a stinky thing to say.
Hey, we think it's time to play the blame game.
The blame game.
Bumba bumba bum bumba.
Bumbo bumbo bum.
Banana banana.
Bumbo bumba bumba.
Boosh.
Bumbo bumbo bumba.
Bumba bumba bumba.
Banana banana.
Bumbo bumba bumba.
Mi-my money.
Brownie.
Don't é!
Mi-my, mi-my original for female.
Banana banana for female.
Bi- Tough before mi-mah.
Female.
Baby boy now.
That was Lonesome Cowboy Dave and Princess We Are Dough.
Dough.
Greatest.
Greatest show on earth.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
No.
I've been...
Well, I've not yet recovered,
but...
When I do,
I promise,
I'll ride those ships.
I'll ride those
X-ing damn freaking ships
off into the blue cosmos.
One day,
Bob's words
will be in my brain,
buzzing the back of my vertebrae.
Hey, did you know I had
a really, really funny
erectile tissue?
Or not.
It's called a cartilage, actually.
No, I didn't.
Everybody has one
in their state.
Everybody has one.
Is it really funny?
No, it's not any funnier
than any of the rest of yours.
It's pretty much the same.
Speaking of funny birthdays
and the October subgenius holidays...
What is the October birthmark
for these funny people, Tuesday?
Well, here at...
Crossed Eyes.
Cleveland's beautiful WCSB station studios,
it's October 2nd.
It's probably not when most people hear this,
but the great Reverend Numo,
vender and the great
nobody's friend,
is starting to understand
why all these тайline
and all related
things under the
Но efforts have to be made
song by
Gomer Pyle. I have
some pictures of Gomer Pyle
in the bathtub. The lattice of coincidence is just
beyond... Well, it is a coincidence because it's also the
birthday of
Gumby and Frank Sinatra
and another song I had
queued up was a song
about Gumby by
Frank Sinatra Jr. How old is
Frank Gumby now? This is way too messed up.
Well, I mean, synchronistically.
The original Frank Sinatra? No,
the Gumby version.
He is, she is, it is...
How many years now has Gumby been riding the train?
Gumby started shooting in Dallas
in the 60s. He's been a heroin addict
since the 60s? He started shooting
or he was born?
Art Clokey
gave birth to Gumby
in, I believe,
in Dallas. Was that an intro?
A guy named Foggy actually shot
the stop action of that
claymation. I often wondered,
you know, back in
those days,
they had to shoot Kodachrome,
which was an ASA of
25, which meant you had to have really
bright lights. And I've
worked with claymation, and that
stuff kind of sags and goops up
and melts under those bright lights and
also gives you terrible skin diseases.
So I often wondered, how did
they keep Gumby hard?
Hard enough to model?
Is that what Pokey was there for?
Unlike Icthresh, Gumby had no
wings of wax which to burn
under the heat of the sun. Who was Gumby's
all-in?
You can't shoot him in full sunlight, though,
because his nature begins to drift
and change like a werewolf.
Did you know that, Stan? Of course you did.
Yes, of course I did.
It indicates a possibility of where his name came from.
Well, I'm not going to read
off the entire list of everybody
who has a holiday in
October, but these are reasons why you can
celebrate and
fornicate as if your very heart depended on it.
Because these people were born
in this month. St. Buster
Keaton, St. Genghis,
St. Sonny Bean, I think
Dr. Sinister there would probably be into
Sonny Bean. He was in the same
similar business. St. Groucho Marx, who should be
a subgenius. St. Madeline Murray O'Hare,
the obnoxious great
atheist. The queen of no-god-is.
Sid Vicious and Nenslow,
St. Nenslow, share birthdays.
They both killed each other on the same night.
Alan Turing, who
both Emma Peel
and Lindy England.
Now, isn't that ironically bizarre?
Dean Martin and Jerry
Lewis on the same day.
St. Richelieu, St. Barbarella,
Timothy Leary,
Janis Joplin.
The day to be named later is the
25th.
And the 31st,
Halloween, is also
the birthday of St. Bob Crane.
And it is mandatory,
friends, that you must have a seance
for Bob Crane on that night.
It's also pater nostril.
And also, don't forget to take
a nylon stocking and tie off
your testicular vesicles
as tightly as you possibly can
on Robert Crane's birthday night.
That's right.
Is that what happened?
Well, they fell off before he actually fell out.
And that's why he became a Rosicrucian.
Or was first...
Well, he wasn't initiated.
He was kind of rubbed the wrong way.
What? Got rubbed the wrong way?
The rubber bands were applied.
It turned black and fell off.
But, quote, he could still use...
He could still use it, unquote.
Of course he could use it.
As much.
Speaking of tool using,
it was recently...
Gorillas have...
Gorillas have been...
That's the species name is Gorilla Gorilla.
Has been observed
using tools, simple tools,
like sticks, AK-47s.
Yeah.
They've been driving 4x4s for years now.
Simple tools.
Golf carts, linoleum rug beaters.
Yeah, golf carts.
The instant egg,
which you just plug into your necro wave,
or your munition thing.
Your necro wave?
Did you see?
Also in the news,
the third of the rich space tourists
took off today.
$20 million for an 11-day cruise
from the Cosmodrome in Kazakhstan,
seen here on slide 3,
via Soyuz,
to the space lab.
And the...
The rich guy gets...
The rich guy gets to come back after 11 days
with the other...
The Russian...
And the American astronauts
have to stay there
in that smelly box
for six months.
Well, this is what it...
This is what it's like
when you become
the commercial piker nations of the world
rather than the industrial military fornicators.
Well, I'm sure we have that
to look forward to.
You bend over and they work their way now.
You and me will be
caddying for Chinese millionaires
in the Grand Canyon
in five years.
No way around it.
I know that sounds harsh,
but think about it.
Yeah.
That's if we're lucky.
And we won't even be able
to afford one of them
damn new 2007 Sun Tours
or whatever they are.
It's going to take GM's place.
Ah.
I remember the first nostril sound.
The waves were so dense
I could hardly stand up.
When I grew to be a man,
I later understood
the meaning of these dense nasal waves.
Are you a member of the...
Are you?
Well, occasionally I have been a member
over the time of my life, yes.
Do you know the secret shake?
Well...
Do you know the secret nose blow?
By nature of being secret,
I can't really say.
Oh.
Well, then you're really
one of the inner circle.
You're not a square,
that's for sure.
Princess Sweet.
What's that point?
Taking advantage of your expertise,
do you think I should play
that Jim...
the Jim Neighbors
or Gomer Pile song?
Sounds a lot more like Gomer
than Jim.
How about the Orgon Pylon song?
We could like extricate
Jim's neighbors
and kill everything.
You know, just for the pure
bush-like hell.
Hell of it, you know?
Here, listen.
Get into the spirit of things.
Listen at this.
Go, Gomer.
Went walking down the street
one day, said,
hey there, my lady.
You sure look good to me
and I'd like to make you my baby.
Actually, I don't know
that this is Gomer.
What's he talk?
Sounds like...
He tried to make
Bart Reynolds his bitch one time.
And that's a weird story, Hollywood.
Everybody know that
screenwriters' guilt,
they were having a meeting.
It was on a corner
of Sunset and...
They were there
and there's a bar below there, man.
And all the bartenders
and everybody in town
knows about this, man.
Are you talking gossip
about Jim...
I'm telling you, Jim...
The late actor and singer,
Jim Neighbors.
He tried to put a love...
A love thing on Bert Reynolds?
On Bert Reynolds.
Known heterosexual?
One-eyed...
What do you call a dog?
A monster.
I don't blame him a bit, man.
Bert Reynolds is a sex god.
Jim Neighbors is a sex god.
You gotta remember...
Dober Pyle is a subgenius god.
You gotta remember
back in the day, man.
Heart, heart, heart.
The deep old coffee woman,
but she had a hot dog heart.
Hot dog heart.
Now I'm not an educated sailor.
I didn't go too far in school.
But I can count and read and write
and tell a horse from a mule.
But trying to judge a woman,
boy, it's bound to bring you fear.
There's many different ways
to judge a woman.
But they all have the same size of ears.
She...
Yeah, just grab them and go to town.
Oh, sorry there.
Are you saying Jim Neighbors had an...
He said he had an educated phallus.
I first thought...
Prehensile, actually.
Like them, they're educated phallus.
He was saying he has an educated phallus
and that's why he's everybody's neighbor.
Come on, man.
It's not a real joke.
It's not even a joke, but it's...
What's the worst?
The meanest...
The meanest, worst thing
that you can call a pink,
a human,
a mediocrity that moves in next door to you
that starts with an N.
Nosy neighbor.
Neighbor.
Noseburger.
How long have you been a member
of the nasal forces, Linda?
And the nasal forces?
Yes, how long have you been
a member of the nasal forces?
Your tattoo is fading
and I think you're trying to...
Hypocryfy your way into these quarters.
Turn back now.
Turn around.
Oh, I like that.
Now turn around again.
Now point this way.
Put your leg up here.
I'm getting dizzy now.
Now, this is not a circus act.
Just show me some...
Okay.
Yeah.
Oh, wait.
I'm in the wrong house.
What does this nasal pornography
have to do with the word Bob?
Or then the fight,
the good fight
against the bad conspiracy?
Bob loved having his sinuses
frisked with sputum
from many, many different clients.
There were ladies of the night.
There were the dogs of war.
There were the winds of the evening
that catapulted Bob into his...
And the things that broke the winds
...sickening condition.
The wind...
The great breaker of winds,
they called him.
The cracker of all cheeks.
He was a fully blown man.
I mean, fully grown
when he realized his mission here.
He was a pilot light
to those around him,
those who saw him.
Ah, enough.
Every...
Every emission
from this great emissionary
was what we now call
a lubrifart.
A preparatory emission.
Thanks to Mr. Sister.
To pave the way
for a greater and thicker
chunk of knowledge to emerge.
I don't understand, though,
how so many different people
can understand
the different tone values
and the strange rasping sounds
and make sense out of it.
I just can't.
To me, it just sounds like
an elderly traveling sailor
cracking wind with his...
You should know,
shouldn't you?
Well, I should,
but I'd like to be
one of those mini-minions
who, like,
listen to bombs,
excretions,
and know what to do.
Yes.
In life, you know what I mean?
You gotta, like I said,
send the...
Send $30.
If you don't know
what to eat, try food.
what to believe,
send $30.
Yeah, I suppose I will.
To quote the great O-Nan,
whose birthday is also in October.
Enlightened,
I will be enlightened
when I see you.
Send the $30.
I'll be able to understand
Bob's noises.
Yes.
Per se.
Well, you pay to know
what you really think,
Bob said,
and $30 isn't bad
to fork out
for what you really think.
And what you really
may already know,
but you think
you need to be told.
Well, you know
Let's not beat around the bush
like we've been doing
all week.
Oh, no, that we need
to be told.
I need to be told.
I don't listen.
We need to be told
that we need to be told
and that's what Bob's here for.
Dang it.
Long may he wave
his fractured, dry,
consenting unity
in the parched wind.
Yes!
Hell, Pope Huey
did this background music,
incidentally.
It's called
Bob of my thing.
Version two.
I must comment right now
and before I forget.
That this is some
of the most wonderful
ear candy I've heard
in a week of Tuesdays.
I think this is just
a sumptuous feast
from, um,
for, for, for, for,
for, for, for, for, for,
Well, some would say
why don't you shut up
and listen to it?
But that's not what
we do on this show.
Shutting up
is not an option.
Now we must just
gabble and garble
on and on
until it's just all done.
Well, now I do have, uh,
songs coming up.
Uh, for instance,
as I said,
the strangely synchronistic,
uh,
Zappa Sinatra
collaboration
on the Gumby theme,
which was actually done
seriously
and with no tongue in cheek
for the,
probably,
Gumby remake
or something.
And I've been, uh,
transferring ancient
subgenius songs
from the,
from the old,
really olden days.
From the 80s.
It's actually plain,
it's in, uh,
I have a, a reggae,
we have a reggae song
coming up that,
that when we play it
for everyone else,
it will leave our heads
and stop playing
over and over and over
and over again.
Oh,
oh,
no,
no.
Is that Popeye?
It's Popeye.
Popeye?
Popeye.
The two chestnuts
right there.
I'm a Popeye
the Sailor Man.
Is that what they meant
by spinach?
I,
I am.
I'm trapped by the
swollen leg.
Oh,
you're the flirty now,
too,
for the love of crates.
Stand back there, sir.
There's plenty of room
for everything.
Now, remember,
take two of every kind.
And let's not be kind
about it.
You,
the ones with the,
the furry hair.
Oh,
but the kind,
The ones with the very
coarse,
coarse brillo pad
on your heads
and on your arms
and on your necks
and on your legs.
On your feet
and your ears.
Yeah,
you with,
oh, wait.
You're actually
a piece of shit.
Well,
thank you very much
for joining
the Tonal Parade.
Gleam,
gleam.
One of the many things
we have to,
uh,
say when the,
when the flannel
goes down,
when the handle,
when the,
uh,
Oh,
boy.
He was once
a little green
dab of clay.
Gone,
gone,
But you should see
what Gumby
can do today.
Gumby,
he can walk
into any book
with his pony pal
Pokey, too.
And he'll find fun
where there's none
if you'd like him to.
And if he likes,
he can change
into something new.
You know,
this song really
sucks,
I guess,
would be the best way
You know,
when I used to sing
that song,
I was living in Benson,
I used to sing that song
while I was on the street.
I beat up every day,
you know?
You know what I'm saying?
Hey,
Stank.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yo, Stank.
I was living in Benson.
I grew up in Benson,
you know?
And I was walking
down the street,
you know,
singing that snappy song,
snapping my fingers
and so forth,
you know?
And a guy come up
and kick my ass
all over the place,
you know?
Up and down a boy walk
all the way to
Canossie Park,
you know?
I wouldn't blame him.
What the hell's up with that?
I wouldn't blame him either.
As long as we have to wear
this strange foreskin
on the top of our heads.
It smells horrible.
Ah, don't mind the smell.
Soon we'll be through
that veil of
innoxious gases.
Excuse me.
Gases.
And we'll be through
the gaseous walls
and everything will be...
Oh, ah,
we're in the wrong area.
Jeez, oh my.
Now there's the usher
over there.
Uh,
man,
ma'am,
sir, ma'am?
Ma'am, sir?
Yes, yes, ma'am, sir,
that's me.
I'd like to know
how the hell out of here.
Get...
Well, uh...
Can I get out, please?
Yes, um,
just keep following
the yellow brick road
and pretty soon
you'll get there.
Follow that
wafting smell
of burning garbage.
That's the froth
from Bob's pipe.
That's not a yellow
brick road at all.
Follow that smell
of garbage
from Bob's pipe.
It's a yellow brick road.
It's a smell that...
Just keep believing
it's a yellow brick road
and it'll become
a yellow brick road.
I can't do anything
with my belief system.
I'm going to have to
report on what I see
on the server.
Yes, sir.
I don't know
This is done
Bhim
Drunk
Syrup
із
Zip
Stay
Shit air, and jet lags like smoking
Piss your money away
There won't be no rainy day
If I will sell you all the sun
He's unlike with your old old one
But he ain't no man, he ain't no god
I don't wanna walk the path Bob's tried
He ain't no man, he ain't no god
At his desk in Dallas
When Dread Dab sits smoking
Behind his mirrored windows
Light up your pipe, let go the smoke
This is smack, it ain't no joke
Crispy to pop, lift up your chain
And you will pay to know what you think
But he ain't no man, he ain't no god
I don't wanna walk the path Bob's tried
He ain't no man, he ain't no god
If I will sell you all the sun
Can you take him to take him to Tupac Mane
My eye-or and I and you
Your best excuse, Bob for me and Bob for you
No matter what, a little thumbs up, new buddy
Ain't no man, ain't no guy
I don't wanna walk the path Bob tried
Well, friends, from the unreleased subgenius album, The Hairs in Bob's Ears.
I think the Lost Souls were part of the Babashanti cult, a sect.
They're a sect of the Babashanti or the Babadreds.
A subcult of the Dread Cult, of the Dread.
The Babadreds.
The Papadreds.
And like herring, they communicate with each other via a high-pitched raspberry-like sound emitted from their anus.
And smoke signals.
Well, yes, of course, it goes along with the high-pitched sounds emitted from their anuses.
Which came first, the smoke or the sound?
The herring, which came first?
But you don't want to tread the path that Bob tried.
Actually, the herring's not even breathing hard.
Well, let's give it a little poke here.
Hey, wait a minute, we can forget this herring.
We gotta get back on the path to Bob.
Smoke on there, baby.
Bob tried.
Ah, that feels terrible.
I can't, what's happening to my...
Oh.
Follow, just follow the trail.
The trail of those cotter pins and jello.
I'm trying.
Look, they're falling apart.
It's up to you, Dave.
Smoking isn't helping.
You must...
The jello is slippery and the cotter pins...
You must find Bob.
Keep on saying, keep smoking this.
And look at the cotter pins as the jello molds fold.
And I can't keep my eyes focused on that pipe in the distance with all this confusion.
And what's that?
Why?
I don't know.
It's some sort of suspense sound made by an orchestra or some group of people with instruments.
Something.
That usually means something terrible is about to happen.
It could happen.
Look, there's a cave and there's a sign that says, don't enter, monster inside.
Oh, man, let's go.
What a setup.
Couldn't it have been a little bit more subtle?
If we don't go in there, everything will have to stop now.
Well, we don't have to necessarily...
We can, like, wait around and be scared before we go in.
Somebody has to go in there and get killed.
All right.
Otherwise, what have we got?
Do we have any ethnic people we could send in there so the rest of the white people...
Yeah, yeah.
Well, first.
But eventually, eventually, you're probably going to have to get killed.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, there's nobody else.
And I'll have to save her.
Well, you could also sacrifice her to...
Well, it's not one of those...
No, no, no.
Somebody has to save her or else...
Not a virgin, yeah.
We don't have a show.
Yeah, not a virgin.
But anyway, okay.
What do I do?
What?
Well, why ask?
Go in the cave where it says the monsters...
Okay.
I don't have to do anything but be coerced into having my head ripped off.
All right, I'll just...
Wait, look.
A pair of brand new shiny booties.
Look, they've got little points on the end of them.
I don't have to do anything for any of you people.
I believe in a new Dobbs.
I believe in a new word.
Fool!
You've fallen directly into my trap.
What an idiot.
But I knew he would do it.
What?
He's so simple-minded.
He's subgenius-ist.
Don't look at him enough.
They're such piddling earth fools.
Who are you?
What are you?
I am the true Ivan Stang.
Oh, you don't look like the true Ivan Stang.
Master of the mimeograph.
The cassette tape deck.
You're a falsified profiteer.
Under 80s forms of fanzine publication in college radio shows.
Oh, no.
Why are you laughing while I'm in English?
What's so freaking funny?
I am so much cooler than Steven Spielberg and his ilk.
Though they may be wealthy, tall, rich.
Intelligent, educated, and other useless things.
They do not have Bob.
Now do they?
Yes, but you are as useless as they are.
And I possess Bob!
Bob is mine!
Yes, yes, it's possible to own Bob.
Why not?
Did I not serve him long enough?
Sweating under his grip in that dank cave in Tibet.
As he instructs me to do my job.
And he instructed me the so-called initiation.
I'm still hurting and sore down there from that.
Yes, I've paid enough.
And now I, Stang, shall rule Dobstown!
Ah, Master.
In my iron pinky.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ah, Master.
Master, there are these forms from the uniform code ministry.
Oh, those again.
There are these forms of the torturing forms.
Oh, yes, all right.
Go ahead and...
If you are going to torture this victim, you will have to sign this release and this release there.
And I hereby swear that any strange activities created on the back of this man's skull, although they may emit the nauseous gases and...
Don't you...
Don't we have a rubber stamp for this?
...proporial eventuality of another cosmos...
This is ridiculous.
Move right on to this document here.
Is this professional?
Yes.
There's nothing professional about this.
I understand, sire, but it all must be uniquely and triplicate.
Oh, wait, no!
What is...
What is this?
What could it be that he has returned?
Is it...
Is it truly...
Am I...
Is it truly Bob himself come to...
To destroy me?
Ladies and gentlemen, this is Bob.
My guest today is Bob, the art of positive persuasion.
Bob is a writer.
Bob is also a staunch supporter and defender of...
Stereotypical, fast-walking, slick-talking sales guy.
You know, the one who sort of sticks their hand out and glad hands and back hands and slaps hands and shakes hands and...
Right.
Bob, thanks for being my guest.
And he is somebody that practices what he preaches.
Give.
You can see Bob's heart come right through it.
Bob, this is what I like most about Bob.
It's giving.
Just so darn wonderful.
Now...
Now you're in a position...
And is it something that...
That I can do effectively in a five or ten minute time frame?
Oh, absolutely.
It's a one-on-one in a...
A group, at a party, at a...
Most people think it's worthless.
Well, it is.
If we're doing this correctly...
Now, get this.
We're being, you know, pushy or obnoxious.
And it always blows me away.
Mm-hmm.
Bob, you talk about...
Wonderful.
Extraordinary, neat, feel good.
Feel good.
You're out of line.
I've got ten of them in my arsenal.
You should devour.
Absolutely.
And you should devour it again and again and again.
Thirty seconds.
They're not necessarily ready for it yet.
Big shot.
Flies in the face.
Find this person's pain, you know.
Let's find their joy.
Let's make them feel good.
How about this wretched excuse for a life?
Bob, you know, Bob...
Absolutely a tremendous, tremendous look.
We're gonna talk about...
We're gonna talk to Bob.
Hi, this is Jack Trout, author of Trout on Trout.
You're listening to Bob.
And you can contact Bob at www.bob.com.
Oh, my absolute pleasure.
Thank you.
Could go on for days and days and days.
Now...
Feel good.
Feel to the rim and...
That's wonderful.
Come see me.
Right.
It may be time to consider, right?
All right, Bob.
I'm gonna put you on the spot.
Well, Bob, thank you so much.
I'm fine.
You know, the good news is that he is a catatrophre.
I can't believe it.
I just can't.
You know, in a way, they're better off than we are.
There's no sense.
There's no feel.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
My grandmother used to always say that every time she hit her head, she'd say, oh, don't
worry, there's no sense.
There's no feeling.
Do you remember when we had given second short, the other day?
Afterwards, that was a bloody ball smack.
I'm my grandmother's daughter.
I'm my grandmother's granddaughter.
Do you remember when we divisected and removed her breasts?
No, I have no memory.
I blacked that completely out.
Shouted the fruit trees in the yard.
There's too many crows and ravens and things flying around my head.
You've been listening to the subgenius radio ministry hour of slack.
I feel like my mind has been corrupted by something much smaller than myself.
Episode number 1015.
Violent shows may be episodic.
For more information on the Church of the Subgenius, feel free to visit www.subgenius.com.
For more disinformation on the...
Subgenius?
I could give the P.O. box, but nobody ever writes to hour of slack.
That's where the disinformation comes from, right?
181-417-Cleef and Heights, Ohio, 44118.
I'm just saying, some people would rather get the disinformation than the information at the...
What other address would you like not want to give?
Do you prefer the disinformation?
Perhaps they like to be lied to.
Well, part of the game is figuring out which is the info and which is the disinfo.
It's all a game, isn't it?
Is it dis or is it dat?
Is it blind girls?
Is it a sad story?
And these fine dat recordings are brought to you by the Subgenius Foundation.
Now that's what I call sad.
And recorded at the studios of WCSB.
And at the studios, which probably means the computers, of Reverend Norrell Preff and the great Fernanda Nandi Lemur.
Under the watchful gaze of Hector Berlioz in a lady's undergarment.
And the way Polka Chorus.
Ladies and gentlemen, this is his finest...
And now...
This!
Quit your job!
Slack off!
We're gonna fix ourselves a tray.
It's a damn good day to talk to Bob.
Oh, what a day.
It's a damn good day.
What a day.
Oh, it's a hot flying day.
If I don't find heaven funny, you're gonna give me back my money.
It's a damn good day to talk to Bob.
Well, it's a damn good day to be talking to my savior.
We got a lot of...
A lot of bread to break.
We're gonna walk out on the lake.
It's a damn good day to talk to Bob.
And it's a damn good day to go to heaven.
And it's a damn good day to talk to Bob.
He keeps the rain off my back and he fills me full of slack.
It's a damn good day to talk to Bob.
Oh, what a day.
It's a damn good day.
What a day.
Oh, it's a hot flying day.
If I don't find heaven funny, you're gonna give me back my money.
It's a damn good day to talk to Bob.
Yeah, I remember one night in this card game in Vegas.
I was down to my last dollar bill.
And Bob blew into town, laid four aces down,
and made away that night with a kill.
Yeah, now my eyes are open and I'm walking on the water.
Got a roll of cash as big as my hand.
Got a guarantee for slack.
Triple money back.
More joy than I can stand.
Yeah, and when I get to heaven, I'm shouting hallelujah.
And the angels, they have carried me away.
Oh, what a joy I will share.
I will need my underwear.
What a damn good, damn good day.
Yeah, and now I'm on my knees.
The spirit is upon me.
And the angels, they join up with me to say,
Will I?
And I'll begin to sing.
Bob will tune the old six-string.
And he'll play it in his own special way.
Oh, what a day.
What a day.
It's a damn good day.
Oh, it's a high-flying day.
If I don't find heaven funny,
you're going to triple back my money.
It's a damn good day to talk to Bob.
Oh, what a damn good day to talk to Bob.
Oh, it's a damn good day to talk to Bob.
That was Reverend John from the album
Haters and Bards, Ears, Precious Bows.