While Nick television used ta-da-sody Snap up a telenovela!
Tell me I'm
a big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big.
One man, one woman,
one man.
How's that?
You're a wish-not.
Ah-ho!
Well,
aren't you a Bobby Dazzler?
How's that?
You're a wish-not.
Ah-ho!
Well,
aren't you a
subgenius?
Yes, I am.
Now, I can't stay but a minute,
but here's a welcome home pie for you.
Oh, thank you.
Where are the kids?
Oh, they're out in the backyard with Bob.
I know he's going to break his neck.
How are they doing?
Um, they're much better now that we're back at home.
Oh!
Bob for the fan, yes!
Yeah!
Whoa!
We win!
Me next!
Oh, I think I'm getting too old for this stuff.
Yeah!
Oh, please, Daddy, please.
Oh!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Thank you.
That music was by Sodi from Music for Imaginary Monster Movies.
And the upper parts were by The Large.
And the background music here is a great band called Electric Junkyard Gamelon,
who we saw play live at Starwood.
This is the Hour of Slack number 1300,
which doesn't quite spell Bob, but we're getting there.
And it happens that for this episode, 1300,
we're doing a special on last year's Starwood 30.
Starwood's been around for 30 years,
and number 31 is coming up directly after the world ends at Wisteria.
Same place in southern Ohio as X-Day is now held,
and where almost all of the following was recorded,
except for the parts from Radio Synesthesia on WCSB Cleveland,
where we called in right after arriving back home at the Slacker Mansion,
still just a bit toasty from doing both the Subgenius and Starwood festivals in a row,
as we might have to do this year.
We begin with Princess We Are Doe and I starting to explore the new Starwood site,
very late on Wednesday night.
It's almost like a 1-18th of a Burning Man.
This one guy in a little PVC dome swinging a torch around.
That's only thanks to the other Ivan.
If it wasn't for the other Ivan, we wouldn't have that.
That looked like an Ivan dome.
It must be one.
This truly is an outdoor hippie festival,
with chemical toilets,
and pickup trucks and tents.
I suppose it could be a biker convention or a rock and roll concert.
It's Starwood is what it is.
It doesn't look like Starwood.
It's in a different place.
It sounds like Starwood.
Yeah, it does.
There's a little candlelit altar,
and a tent lined with colorful Christmas lights.
It's a pretty big bonfire there, isn't it?
Yeah, there's a nice sized bonfire, and that's not the main bonfire, right?
No.
That's going to be the bonfire site later?
Because they'd have to build it.
That's Paw Paw, I bet.
Paw Paw?
Yeah.
Is that the Paw Paw Patch?
Yeah, Paw Paw Patch.
Are there naked hippie chicks there?
Probably.
Or at least topless?
Maybe.
Oh, oh, oh, see?
Look up there.
The Puffer Dome.
Look at that.
Oh my God, it's beautiful.
It's Waking Dream.
It's Waking Dream and their psychedelic Puffer Dome.
There's sexy movies projected all over the outside in crazy patterns.
Hello.
Finally, there's some hippies.
This is the first hippies we've seen the whole time we've been walking up this road for ten minutes.
We saw the hippie camps.
Now, where's the witches?
I've seen hippies.
Where are the witches?
I see the bikers.
I see the...
I never saw the trailers.
I've never seen the...
The losers.
I see the lame brains.
I'm real confused of where we are because I never saw the trailers yet.
But where's the witches?
And that's my orientation spot.
Well, there was a...
Like the shower place back there, right?
Yeah, that's a...
That's different.
So you're lost.
You're already lost at Starwood, at the new Starwood site.
Yeah.
Princess Wee is lost.
I'm lost at Starwood.
I'm lost.
This reminds me of walking around crazily tripping at Burning Man, except we're not
tripping and it's not Burning Man.
But the domes full of multimedia shows look the same.
So now you know, Bob, Slack the Conspiracy.
How does that apply to the Starwood tour guide?
My favorite document of the year.
This year, Princess Wee are dozed.
I'm going to go through this and look at the names of the workshops and stuff.
If you happen to be giving one that I make a sarcastic comment on, believe me, I'm not
really commenting on your workshop.
I'm commenting on my quirky first...
idea when I saw the title.
Now there's one, Creating Your Own Tarot Layouts.
It so happens that for all of a sudden this year, there is a subgenius tarot deck.
For 30 years, that's been a running joke.
Every new subgenius has to say three things.
Hey, did you know Bob spelled backwards is Bob?
Hey, I got a joke for you.
Bob, damn it.
And the third one is, hey, what about a subgenius?
What about a subgenius tarot deck?
Finally, somebody did one.
And I was the fool.
They had me as the fool.
Okay, anyway, I see we have a course in the horned god.
We have, believe it or not, there's people who hate the Church of the Subgenius and consider
it really dangerous, huge, because it's part of the...
Because they...
They...