Bob
What we've got here is a failure to communicate.
The subgenius powerhouse.
I don't like it any more than you, man.
My CPE is intact.
Thank you, LeMire.
This episode is another one of those perverted group marriages of young, old, and in between.
From Hour of Slack number 88,
we hear from
the young 1987 puzzling evidence,
Paul Mavridis, Dr. Hal, Ivan Stang, Pope Sternodocs,
St. Viren Werner, and Dr. Philodrummond.
We hear those selfsame early apostles as doddering old codgers
in an excerpt from Sandy Boone's fine documentary film about the Church of the Subgenius.
In between, from the future year of 2000,
we hear the middle-aged Stang, that's me,
Lonesome Cowboy Dave, and Professor Chaz Smith,
back before the wars and the diseases and the deaths
when we were all ever so happy-go-slacky
at ESO's Swamp Radio on WCSB Cleveland.
There's not much music, but what there is,
is the Rudi Schwartz Project and Shemiki,
Shemikiya Copeland.
The music in the background is CyberChump from this moment of perfect happiness.
And now, back in time.
I'm gonna start all over again.
I've got to start this damn show all over again.
God, I'm so sick and tired of having to start this stupid show
over and over and over again.
This show never seems to go anywhere.
It's nothing but an endless beginning.
A thousand beginning sequences, it seems like.
Ugh.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
You're listening to the Ivan Stang Theme by Nino Rota,
by way of Snakefinger.
We got some, a whole bunch of stuff from Ralph Records.
Oh, praise Bob.
The wonderful Reverend Sheena over there at Ralph Records
has converted to Bob and to the Hour of Slack,
and so I've got an infinite supply of all the stuff that's coming up.
All the material from Ralph Records.
And I'll be playing some of the new, oh, a little bit of new residents,
new negative land,
and Snakefinger.
But, but you know those things pale in comparison to that
which has been sanctified by Bob.
Because, dear friends, which came first, really?
The mistake or the excuse?
You know, the astounding power of the human mind
is nowhere better illustrated than in its ability
to rationalize its own mistakes.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
It can devise wonderful machines and soaring concertos.
But those wilt, dear friends, besides the inventiveness of its excuses.
After all, must we not survive before we can afford to indulge in such pleasantries?
As culture and science?
The alcoholic, for instance, or the yogi,
or any cult member or subgenius,
by intuitively recognizing this, can bypass it.
And even in that, find excuses to bypass survival itself.
Yes, alcohol or Bob, in other words,
can be more seductive than life itself.
Ah, yes, praise Bob.
This is your friend, Reverend Ivan Stack,
and you're listening to The Hour of Slack on KNON 90.9 FM in Dallas, Texas.
Oh, yes.
And you're listening to The Hour of Slack on KNON 90.9 FM in Dallas, Texas.
The Hour of Slack on KNON 90.9 FM in Dallas, Texas.
Oh, yes.
were really just sub-genius.
And in my head, everything fell together like a puzzle box,
a Rubik's Cube that suddenly formed itself.
A weird fringe cult for weirdos, specifically for weirdos.
That was the church of the sub-genius.
When we did the first pamphlet,
it was really a labor of love, the pasting up, the cutting.
We tied together every fringe belief you could think of.
It was like getting all your toys, your dinosaur toys,
and your army men toys, and your cowboy and Indian toys,
putting them all together on the floor,
and having this whole world that was a conglomerate of all the cool stuff ever.
It was so much fun!
We had this sort of an icon we could blame everything on,
the conspiracy of normalcy.
There's Bob, the conspiracy,
and Slack.
You know, if you're gonna have a cult,
you have to have a cult leader.
Well, that's Bob.
We needed to put a face to that entity.
We can't afford artwork.
No, there's clip art, the public domain stuff.
It's old, nobody cares about it.
As we flipped through the catalog, there was that face.
We both instantly knew, that's Bob.
After a couple of months,
we had assembled a group of people,
and we assembled Subgenius Pamphlet number one.
When the printing bill came in on the first pamphlet,
it was $60!
My wife got very upset with that.
You're gonna have to send these to publishers.
We can't afford that kind of thing.
You need to try to turn it into a book or something.
Publishers, wow, okay.
I got Writer's Digest, and got the addresses of every publisher in the United States,
and mailed the pamphlet.
I got a pamphlet to them.
We got 150 rejection slips back.
The rest of them didn't say anything.
I was living in San Francisco,
working with my comic partner, Gilbert Shelton, at Ripoff Press.
I wandered into the publisher's office,
and I saw a fellow named Fred.
He opened some envelope up and pulled out the initial pamphlet.
He grumbled something about it,
and threw it in the trash can next to his desk.
To his complete irritation,
I pulled it out and just started laughing at it.
It's the funniest thing I've ever read.
It was kind of like, how refreshing.
I think my first act was to get an envelope,
and put all the cash I had in my wallet in it,
and wrote a note saying, send me more pamphlets.
The first pamphlet, pamphlet number one,
is a significant document in many ways.
It is the vector by which many people have had their most significant introduction
to the Church of the Subgenius.
Doug sent the pamphlet to KPFA,
and so I saw that and really loved it.
And for years, since I was a kid,
I've been putting stuff in the mail to strangers.
So they became new strangers.
They start mailing stuff back.
It was like the internet, really,
but instead of a thousand people,
it was ten or fifteen of us.
It was really fun.
It was such a seminal little pamphlet.
It was almost like a test of your mindset.
Like, were you a subgenius or not?
If you got it, you were a subgenius.
It really spoke to me.
It had this whole thing about how the goal is slack,
and the motto is,
if they can't take a joke.
The central doctrine, more than anything else in the Church of the Subgenius,
of course, is this slack thing.
It's probably one of the hardest things to describe in the Church, you know.
We don't describe it,
because by definition, slack is really different for each person.
Slack is what everybody wants.
It's what we still want.
This idea of, you know,
a place where people can live,
where they don't feel harried by just the multiple things
that one feels harried by all the time.
You know when you don't have it, that's for sure.
It was like finding like-minded people,
if you could truly say any of us had minds to be alike.
You know, somebody with the same type of cynical perspective,
same reference points.
They were so layered in everything.
It was part pop culture,
part science, part religion.
So it appealed to me a great deal,
and I did do just as it said,
I sent a dollar with the letter.
What's that say, send a dollar?
Even I've got a dollar, so I sent off a dollar,
and I got this little pamphlet,
and that was where the crushing loneliness started to get chipped away.
I was doing a magazine called Famous Potatoes,
using a lot of ads and clip art stuff,
and it was a fine artist,
Robert Williams, who said,
hey, you ought to send some stuff off
to the Church of the Subgenius.
They're doing a bunch of clip art stuff like you do.
So I sent stuff off, and I think it arrived
just after Stang's birthday or something,
and he just flipped out over the famous potatoes,
and he sent me all the pack, you know,
and I didn't have to pay.
There was a flyer on a phone poll that said,
get ready for a pretty tough future.
What scientists are afraid to tell you
is that you're going to be the next
and I got a little bit of a picture of Bob.
I showed it to all my pals,
and they were just like, yeah, yeah.
So we didn't send him a dollar.
We sent him $100 from Little Rock.
And we got the first pamphlet back.
That just bobbed us all up immediately.
It was a little bit of a sense
that there are other people interested in these things.
They might be far away,
and they might exist from post office box
to post office box, but they are out there.
It was intoxicating to think that there was somewhere
where you didn't have to fit in,
where people were crazy in the good way.
So I sent him my 10 bucks,
and I became a subgenius.
We got the first few orders coming in.
Remember, we were so excited,
and then all of a sudden...
Well, terrified, more like it.
It was like, what, somebody actually sent us $10?
Now we have to do that new stuff.
Now we actually had to start working and doing stuff.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm making final preparations
just hours before the start of PR's historic Trump
of the Trump being Trump-tested so far.
The Trump is hoping to help the greasy dead bodies
of migrants who have drowned at sea.
But the European Union says it's dishonest and weak.
Experts say the Trump or the Trump or also the Trump
is looking for his PR News Washington.
Sanctioned.
Trump requires cooperation, not PR News.
Critics fear this could severely and fairly disrupt people's PR News.
But there are concerns about a large-scale burger testing lab
that's hostile to PR News in Amsterdam.
Health officials in Democratic Republic of Congo say this is PR.
They also confirm 38 infections.
...to the US, as well as round-the-clock radio messages
to the American population, urging them,
to overthrow the evil robber barons
who have seized power in this bloodless coup.
Presidential appointee George W. Bush showed little understanding
of the gravity of the situation after UN sanctions were explained to him.
If they don't like it, maybe they should look for a new home
for their organization, he reportedly said.
Sanctions are scheduled to begin immediately.
What kind of flavor sanction are we going to be having?
Ugh.
Well, that is...
That's not only disturbing, but it's also very, uh,
I don't know, kind of exhilarating to think that, um,
we might be liberated by UN troops who...
Yeah, yeah, I guess, uh...
...come to restore, uh, Martian law.
Right, the Nicaraguans and Colombians and so forth
will be sending police keeping, uh, peace keeping troops here too.
I hope the drug lord sends some, uh, send a few squads,
or squab...
Squat teams.
That's all you can think about, isn't it, Dave?
Squatting or teams?
Boats. Teeing and squatting and stuff.
Excellent.
All I can think about is, like, riding around in a boat with a bunch of girls.
But that's, that's, um, that almost got me into an accident on the way here.
I saw some home movies of you skiing behind a boatload of girls.
Yeah, but that...
They were all laughing at you and you had no skis.
See, I was an extra. Remember the island of Dr. Moreau?
Not the ones, you said there were three, like, major classics and a couple rip-offs?
No, two classics and one terrible rip-off.
Well, this was kind of like an island of Dr. Moreau thing, except for there,
there were all these, like, sexed-up babes who had lived near a nuclear plant.
And I had to, like, ski on a power plant and stuff.
And my testosterone was somehow quanti- quanticized with it, too.
And I had to water ski, like, endlessly, like, for hours and hours and hours around the same little puddle.
I could, I'd seen everything before a thousand times.
I heard they made you do that.
And, uh, I got no pay. You know, your usual chicken sandwich bidet and your so forth that you get, you know, as your offerings for having done your doo-doo.
You just, um, I didn't make anything off of it.
Not even a concept that made sense.
And still don't.
But if you can imagine a bunch of, like, female werewolf queens.
Whoa! Now you're talking!
And one of those, like, really hot Chris Craft, you know, like, outboards and stuff from the 50s and everything,
wearing those Donna Reed bathing suits, like, smiling and waving and stuff like that.
And sometimes their hands fall off because I guess there was- they were trying to weave a leper colony thing in there with, you know, the people being bestial and so forth.
And I had to have sex with all of them, too.
With the werewolf cheerleader babes, did you say?
A cheerleader kind of beach babes, more like a net, you know, fungicide or something.
You know, the sexy aspect of werewolf- were-women wolves has not been explored except in very few movies that-
I lost on you.
The howling.
The first howling movie I remember had a sexy werewolf scene where this couple goes out waiting for the full moon, because they're into it.
Yeah, I remember that. I remember that.
And the full moon comes up and they're- they're making the- ahem.
They're a beast with two backs.
Two backs.
While they change into werewolves, of course, they end up at the end of the climax of the scene, the male is
And talk about dog breasts.
Now, speaking of hair-covered monster babes, there was also a movie in the late 50s called The Neanderthal Man, which I saw when I was a kid.
And it really impressed me because the cops broke in and they found-
They found photographs of-
Real Neanderthals having sex.
The mad scientist had been experimenting on his Mexican maid.
And there were a series of photographs that showed her as a nice-looking young lady and then gradually reverting into a Neanderthal.
He had a devolution drug or something.
Which, of course, we've all been seeking our whole lives, many of us.
Well, we're looking for Hirsute women, if that's what you mean.
Well, either one.
I want-
You know, one or the other, both would be the best.
Back to the canthropy again.
But not Hirsute, no, it's not the hairiness that's the kick.
It was the prognathous jaw, the sloping brow, the heavy brow ridge, the increased-
The lupine, elven neck bones.
The heavy muscle structure.
The strong yet archy neuronucleoid pieces of flesh hanging from the-
It was the difference that turns you on.
Just the difference, huh?
Well, but it was a major, major difference.
I could see you like chasing like these weird like poor war veteran guys and stuff from 1942 and everything.
Around the block and like grabbing them and-
Oh, there they go now!
Those funny looking dudes.
White canes.
Someone wearing the DAV bracelets around their necks.
And it looks so much like dog collars.
I'm sorry.
Chaz, I understand you were at some sort of a convention, the Stone Hand Axe Convention, was it?
And you had to dress like a woman and carry stone tools, titanium tools they're making now.
By hand, right?
With those little-
They smelt them by themselves with their little hands.
In a little shack in the back?
Were these like scrapers and choppers and-
Or was it the new modern day hand axes?
Were there scruffers and scribes?
Or were there people who worked with their hands and feet like mom and dad?
People were taking pictures of-
Going.
Ooh.
Ooh, ooh, ooh!
Were there little homo habilis people working and chipping away at the church in Flint?
Were there little homunculi working away-
In the dark basements of the out-
There were monkeys with apples on their backs all over the place.
Monkeys with apples on their backs?
See, that's the new word for-
Applebacks, we were calling them.
That's a new word for a gyrating junkie.
That's a new word for a person like what they used to have a gorilla on their sidecar.
No, they're just mac monkeys.
A bunch of mac apes.
Mac apes.
I'm one of them.
I'm a mac ape.
That means in Celtic-
That means son of the ape.
I'm still-
You know, that's how mankind started out.
My eyes go-
In the plains of Africa-
I mean-
In the old Davai Gorge.
It's now a gorge.
It used to be just a light side.
An alagorge?
That was the song of the Australopithecus and homo habilis.
What was the alagorge of the homo habilis?
The alagorge was do not step on moist rock five million years from henna.
You know, the paleo-
I was reading a Martian paleoanthropology book and they-
Dr. Zorg.
Interesting-
Yes, Dr. Zorg's book.
Actually, it was by Dr. Shreve right here in Cleveland and Dr. Johansson, Lucy's child.
And they were-
And Buster Poindexter's brother.
They were suggesting that perhaps human intelligence evolved in concert with our society-
Complete and total lie.
We became the apes that conquered our environment because we had our own selves, our own society,
our own human and private ape society as our own worst enemy.
That our own fate of each other was what drove us to evolve such demonic cleverness.
You think they're demonically clever?
No, we-
Your pronouncements are yet so hollow to me.
I cannot-
Yeti's-
You say in one breath-
Yeti's are president.
I don't consider that man a man of yeti blood.
I consider him a-
No, you're absolutely wrong.
A spurlish, a curlish-
A pink-
A snake.
A human.
A pure human one, an escaped lab rat.
George W. Bush might as well be an escaped lab rat.
Most of them.
Most of them might as well be-
A beaten, drooling lab dog.
A beaten, drooling lab dog with only five teeth.
I'm a bad heart.
A bad heart.
Ah, yes.
Yeah, we're back to normal.
Let's see what's on TV tonight.
There's a special on one of the-
Let's see.
It's Channel 38 if you get cable.
Frappa Billy live in Nashville.
On Channel 27 tonight, the men from Planet X-
Or the man from Planet X.
And if you tune in right now, you can catch the very end of our series.
We're going to be talking about the Squirting Universe on PBS.
See, 39, I think, has 20 million miles to Earth.
And Mars Needs Women right after that.
Both of those feature cameo appearances by J.R. Bob Dobbs.
On CBN, the Christian Broadcasting Network, we've got Love That Bob.
And after that, Bob and Connie and Jim and Tammy.
Oh, ho, ho.
I can't wait.
That's like a soft core porno.
And then Fort Dobbs.
What is Fort Dobbs about?
Apaches try to regain their sacred pipe from a mad Caucasian plunderer.
And, oh, that's with John Wayne.
And then at midnight, Dante's Inferno with Spencer Tracy, which also has an amazing appearance
by Bob Dobbs.
But, oh, let's see.
If I can just get my technical act going.
I think I can.
I wanna play this song I'd like to...
No, I'm serious here.
It's a quiet moment.
I'd like to dedicate this to those, uh, the kids that were lost in the Guadalupe River
this weekend.
Oh, Jesus.
You gave me water.
Jesus.
Jesus gave that woman water.
You gave me water.
Gave her that living, lasting water.
What a, what a, what a loving water when there was none in the well.
There was a woman from Samaria.
Came to the well to get some water.
It was there she met our Savior.
So the story tell.
Hell, that woman dropped her pitcher.
But her drinking wasn't good.
She had people to pour her a
tied up mana.
And in Jesus' name we love, we trembling.
pouring blood.
Water, bringing those living price new fridge.
sitting in a pool moment.
Having a drink for morning difficile.
When the land in.
in the well.
Oh, yeah.
Yes, yes, yes. That was Snakefinger,
also late.
Yes, Snakefinger's also dead.
Reverend Sheena
Timoney down there at Ralph Records
said that just about three
weeks ago, old Snakefinger bought it.
Yes, he did.
He's out of the
way now. Sad,
sad. But you know he's gone on
to a life in Bob, a new life
in Bob.
I've never heard of that.
Did you hear the theory about
how if aliens come
here, that they're probably already here
in the microbial form
and that they're going to
in intelligent form
too, and that they're going to take over
through the internet.
The world wide web.
That they're not microbial,
I mean they're nano.
They're like nano.
Aliens.
Oh man, how could you be a digital life form though?
It's required to form the physical body
that we know as Bill Gates.
God, just think of all the
microbes and how they hold themselves together
into a semblance of a
human-like thing that breathes
and talks. Probably even
eats. Peanut butter cup, Dave?
No thanks. I was going to have some
Smarthy tumor juice over there and then also
a piece of hemlock pie.
I see the Reverend brought his Slim
Fast with him.
You gotta drink.
You have to drink three or four of those every day.
Now why would a man of your small,
not your girth, want to have a Slim Fast
for lunch or breakfast?
Because I can't
suck down the blood of a newborn
kitten every hour like I would like
to, so I have to suck down one of
these damn humanoid
drinks.
It's for the protein. I have to have
protein to balance the sugar
and caffeine.
So therefore I have to...
eat nuts or
frop or some other form of protein.
Nuts and frops and other colloquialistic terms
for human bodies when you crunch off the tops
of their heads and dig right into that
fleshy medulla oblongata.
Zips the tops.
Have you ever sliced the brain?
So what do you think about that? Aliens and nano-aliens.
Well I was trying to ask you a question.
How could they make my biotic form
become digital from a digital form?
Actually boys, the nano-alien is the one that's going to be the most effective.
What does that mean?
The nano-alien is the one that's going to be the most effective.
So the nano-alien that you're talking about Chaz
are in fact the
WOM supercomputer
predicted by J.R. Bob Dobbs
described in not very much detail
in either of the
baubles so to speak.
This WOM supercomputer is actually like a zillion billion nano-alien creatures.
What is?
They're artificial but
you know they're as alive as any
virus or bacterium.
And these
this super computer of the
exist aliens
because of the nature of it
is able to exist as a permeating
gas as a paint
upon the walls as the carpet underneath
An all pervasive feeling.
As very slim fast in that
cannon as the can itself.
Or a lack of oil in one's carburetor.
Those are all part of the exist computer. That is how
the exist super computer is able to
instantly grant the wishes of all those
who paid their thirty dollars to this.
And simultaneously deny the heartfelt desires
of those it wishes to crush and conquer.
Following the rupture
or predicted
XXXX day
4XD
we like to call it
coming up this July 5th
4Skin day.
4Skin day?
As Bob predicted.
Yes sir. Oh holly hot 4Skin day.
When our mothers and grandfappies
laid down these flaps
that would create
a new hoon and bean
here on this consecrated ground.
We just decided
actually there was a vote. Shouldn't we demand
that everybody in the church be circumcised?
Whoa!
Or circumvented by faith.
I think you got mixed up with a certain heaven's
gate or a certain Judaism
or some such thing.
Or a certain medical
American
conspiracy. But no.
Trephination was the...
I think everyone in this church
should have a sex change and then have
a sex change back. Well you've already
had one. No that's been done. That's already
happened in this church of
excrescence and putridity. I can't even keep up
with the names of some of our ministers
whether they're Mrs. This
or Mr. That. Hot stinky
in between man woman.
Lephargic thing purple...
Yeah. Pope. Pope.
Stir this and...
Mary Popes stir this and that.
But all of these predictions
shall come true as the end times
unfold. Listen to the mic.
I could do the whole song and dance.
That's kind and it's own juices.
Just like a thick little salami. How do we expect to get to the moon
if we can't even talk between two buildings?
How can we expect
trees to communicate when we
cannot even talk with our own
urine and other bodily fluids?
It's just too much of an explanation. It always
comes back to bodily fluids
and genitalia. That's Dave
That's little baby talk.
That's sophomore unit baby talk.
I know Chas that you and I would prefer to keep the conversation
on a lofty, rationalist,
humanist level.
Perhaps the subcutaneous plane.
And eschew this metaphysical
claptrap nonsense.
Slathering skin of this fleshy,
fleshy
genu-oriented
and poo-poo oriented individual.
But of course that's what the audience wants. That is
what keeps the advertisers
coming in here at WCSB.
Dave's poo-poo talk.
Oh yes, yes,
yes. Listen to that.
Ha.
You want to know what kind of
music I listen to when I'm sitting around at home?
I sit around at the house
and I listen to this old box
of all kinds of weird, old, funky
old-timey
music like this. It's old, what's it
called? Old western music.
Western Germany. 1500s.
Ah.
It feels so good.
Yeah, back at the house. I'm the proud owner
of two little kids, believe it or not.
Yes I am. Both of them are old enough
to read, but neither one of them is old
is old enough yet to
well, for me to break
certain things to them about Santa Claus.
Now it makes me mad that I
can't tell them certain things, but it almost
shames me that I have to tell them other
things at all.
Some of these monstrous truths
don't slide by as
easily as the one about Santa
Claus. One day,
and this is the truth, I had to
warn my kids about
certain grown-ups who are so
twisted by their own
messed up parents that they want to close
their mouths and quote,
do bad things to you, unquote.
And it feels awful
to break that kind of news to a kid
and it's frightening to think what they're
prompted to imagine about the world
they're going to grow up in, no matter
how you soften it up when you're
telling them about it. And I've never
been able to tell them about the bomb
or the germ
or the gas
because I knew what would happen if my
kids started thinking about those
things all the time.
They'd end up like me,
dear friends, and all through
high school I was dead
sure the future would see
us back in the caves.
As Einstein or some
other wise guy once said,
quote,
I don't know what World War
III will be fought with,
but the one after that will be
fought with sticks and stones.
Unquote.
And now,
dear friends, we don't even have that
to look forward to.
That was a naive,
positive thinking kind of
view of the end of the world.
With the weapons they have now,
there wouldn't even be
sticks and stones. There'd be nothing,
dear friends, nothing left
if the big mistake
happened. By the way, my kids
did figure it out for themselves without
me having to say anything.
Between TV cartoons
and the news and conversations
on the playground, they were able to put
two and two together before first grade,
and you'll be glad to know that they did
adjust a lot better than I did.
But friends, most people cannot
conceive of worldwide
extinction of all higher
life forms. Nay,
they've got a lot of trouble, for that matter,
conceptualizing so much as a
rape or a car wreck.
At least until it happens
to them.
Positive thinking,
you know, oh, positive thinking,
oh, don't you love it, and that escape
into affluent
isolation, dear friends, have become
so socially desirable
that the idea of preparing
for the worst, that's a bad
habit now. Only survivalists
and cooks would do something
like that. To most Americans,
friends, a big mistake
is, oh, say, forgetting to photocopy
that textiles contract
before the board meeting or
burning the roast
when guests are expected
for dinner.
People nowadays, they won't
build themselves a fallout shelter.
They won't even, I won't even
quit smoking myself, for that
matter, and yet, they'll
donate to save the whales.
Strange
paradoxes, but, uh, you
see, friends,
most human beings
have no idea how
real they are.
And for that matter, they don't know how smart
they are, but at the same time,
they grossly underestimate
their own stupidity.
And they,
to, to, think about it,
they could wreck,
permanently wreck the rest
of the planet, for all of us,
by, just for no other
reason than not giving themselves
enough credit, either for brains or for
the lack thereof. And if they
distrust themselves
so much, friends, think how
much they distrust you.
They assume that
they wouldn't be good enough at anything
important, like stopping
the arms race to take a stab at it,
and in all too few cases, they're
right. And so they cling to
the safe and the meaningless, and they
wish everyone else would, too.
When somebody tries
to warn them about a danger they didn't
already know about, well, oh, they take
that as an insult. Now
as Bob Dobbs said
to a Sunday school class
in 1955,
if they all thought they were as great
as I think I am,
everybody'd get along just fine,
even though they'd all
be wrong. That's what Bob said.
So how much
do you tell your kids about the future?
About pollution,
about overpopulation,
and war, and crime, and
just exactly what those
statistics are pointing to?
When does it
get past survival training friends
and start making them suicidal?
For that matter, how much
can you psychologically
afford to tell yourself?
Maybe a lot more than you think.
Earlier today, Chaz
was giving a sort of
a trance lecture
about
that ranged from
the protoplasmic beginnings
of all life to
space exploration.
And this lovely dome
here is certainly a good
place to think about
that because if we're not
lucky, all of our descendants
will live inside little puffer
domes like this because
there won't be the right kind
of air outside.
And if we are
lucky...
Yes! Oh baby!
Do that again!
I say!
Oh I say!
Oh! Hit me one more time
please, darling!
You know, uh,
you know if you increase the oxygen
in here too much, a spark like that
would cause an explosion.
We'd all be fried like those poor
brave astronauts on
one of those ill-fated missions.
On the other hand, if you turn the oxygen up
you get kind of high.
Well let us speak first!
Aww.
We'll watch on those.
Now, uh, remember,
the air
outside is not exactly
the same as inside, so you might
want to go through that decompression
chamber first! Oh man!
James!
These kids just go right in
and out from earth atmosphere to
outside atmosphere.
Doesn't even bother!
I have to wear a mask to go out there.
You're out of evolution.
Yeah.
It's hard to keep up with evolution, man.
It was hard enough just to crawl out of that pond
and use them lungs.
That hurt!
You kids don't know nothing!
You never did have to crawl out of that ocean
and use them lungs the first time.
And that first time
we've had to
invent murder
and murder
murder!
That was hell, baby!
But, man's gotta eat.
You gotta get that,
you gotta build that spaceship somehow.
And if you have to
start by chipping flint
rocks together, well that's
a start. Better than sitting on
your butt, scratching your butt. Or is it,
friends? Is what it would have been
better for early man
to have merely sat
upon its butt, scratching
that butt, and
picking its nose and it flees
off into each other and
rutting like happy little monkeys
in the wilderness.
Instead of all this progress,
which, while it has brought us
these apps and things,
they're still not working right.
We have to breathe
this processed atmosphere
or else end up like those
new breed of kids with the
giant lungs and stuff.
John?
Sometimes I get mixed up and can't
even remember what century I'm in.
I remember
that one time
when we invented
legs.
That was out
of necessity, believe me.
No, but,
you know, I mean, there's some people
think that, that, uh,
well, I used to thank Chaz.
You know, we've been
exhorting people to build their own ships
just in case the aliens don't save
our butts, but I used to say
to people, well, hell, we got a whole
other planet right here on this one
that's a lot closer than Mars
or the Moon and a lot more hospitable,
that being the ocean. Oh, we got
a whole other two planets
worth left to pollute
if that's what we wanted to do.
No!
He's a maniac!
Out to rule the world!
What can I do to make you understand?
I love you!
And what will the new year
bring you, my friend? What will Santa
bring you for the new,
the true new millennium?
You know, it took him to remind us
about this, friend. Will Santa bring you a
giant black slab?
And when you throw, will you throw
a bone into the air? Will it turn
into a nuclear bomb
or into a checkbook?
Which will it be, my friend?
Who will you follow?
The black slab or the flying pipe
with the wings?
Santa is saying that conspiracists
got big red straps. They want to strap
that big black slab onto you with big red straps
and keep it
strapped to you so that, you know,
all of the doubt will fall over you.
Do you have protection, my friend?
Are you wearing protection
for the new year? Or do you have
that $30 membership
skin on?
...of mankind.
If you are the moments
we two can share.
Quiet and blue
like the sky,
I'll hug over you.
And if I can't find my way back home,
find my way,
it just wouldn't be fair.
wouldn't be fair.
These precious and few
are the moments
we two can share.
...are the moments we two can share.
Maybe it's you
on my mind. Your
love is so rare.
...love is so rare.
Being with you
is a feeling I
just can't compare.
And if I
can't hold you in my
arms,
can't hold you in my arms,
it just wouldn't be fair.
wouldn't be fair.
These precious and few
are the moments
we two can share.
...are the moments
And if I can't find my way back home,
my head just wouldn't be fair.
wouldn't be fair.
These precious and few
are the moments
we two can share.
...are the moments
These precious and few
are the moments
we two can share.
Quiet and blue
like the sky,
I'm hung over you.
And if I can't find my way
back home, my pretty baby,
Wanna take a little break right now when we come back?
Oh, that just wouldn't be fair.
Wouldn't be fair.
These precious and few
are the moments
we two can share.
These precious and few
are the moments
we two can share.
...are the moments
The Rudy Schwartz Project
from Sunshine
Supers hits,
and now back to ESO Swamp Radio
of the year 2000.
...of the year 2000.
The season is now entering
....the Dark Zone.
I have one more specious argument to make with you, Dr. Goddard Dammerung.
If the day of the end of the hand isn't coming, what can we do?
How can we do it?
And when, above all, must we perforate it?
And among other questions I have for you, Dr. Goddard Dammerung,
is when is the Valkyr storm coming to my backyard?
Well, son, to release the essence,
you must go into the chamber of excremeditation
and there grip upon that which has troubled you and itched you,
that which has strained and pressed outwards from you,
and wring it like the turkey's neck.
Of America!
And give thanks unto the bathroom tiles
in your whiteness and discolored blood-tinged.
Thanks for the wild turkey and the passenger pigeons
designed to be spit out through wholesome American guts.
You know, I've had the transfusions all my life.
For a nation of...
Fakes.
...an iron-chopped turkey fried dinner.
...so automatically that I can hardly stand with you.
The printer is in my head.
Oh, dear Lord.
Oh, there's blood everywhere.
Slowly I turn.
Oh, God, no.
Step by step.
Inch by inch.
As I can see, the clothes were burning.
Thank you for the Indians.
To put up some...
...minor...
...resistance.
Thank you for government narco-police and laboratory aides.
Thank you for P-Dawg and Poop-Dawg.
Thank you for reminding us...
Thanks for the war against...
...our fascist autocracy. ...subgeniuses.
Thanks for Dave killing lawmen, feeling up their notches.
Oh.
Thank you for not having time to lay feedback.
Mine fell out.
I'd like to give thanks right now for this...
...beautiful pumpkin growing out of my pie eyes.
And as God has made this turkey for me and this wonderful gravy...
...and petty broth on our bare hands and knees for three weeks, I...
...bassoon, this is probably going to be one of my best lung savings...
...and thanks days forever.
I know you're growing, my children.
I can smell it.
Your eyes are glowing like the old ones now.
Soon you will be ready...
...to have a thanksgiving of your own...
...on the martyred corpses of the Hunan bin.
The caller drifts around the studio...
...and is decapitated by Hal, who presses a button...
...for yet another...
It's hot.
Oh, yeah.
...situation down here.
It's live.
We'll keep you awake for no reason at all.
No reason is right, dear friends.
Listen up.
The Will of Dobbs just pointed out that...
...you know, the only call we've gotten down here tonight...
...was what?
Somebody wanting Madonna tickets?
Great show to call for that, friends.
Whew, Madonna, geez.
Unless you're thinking about Jesus' mother.
Now, we can get you tickets for her.
She's meeting all the boys back in the garage after the show.
But listen.
What makes us mad, what really makes us sick...
...is that nobody has gotten mad and sick at us yet.
Why is it I can get on the air and make underhanded, nasty...
...well, satirical, strictly satirical...
...and absolutely has nothing to do with this station...
...but nasty comments about certain disasters...
...that have happened in the Dallas area recently...
...and nobody calls, nobody's upset about that.
Oh, no.
But if we mention one wounded animal...
...if we say, even once...
...I like to kill animals...
...well, that, oh, then, oh, the lines light up.
You people are so, so angry...
...and so ready to get up and fight...
...when you hear somebody insult your four-legged friends.
They're so poor and helpless.
But when we get on here and insult living human beings...
...who died for nothing...
...oh, that doesn't bother you a bit.
You don't care about that.
That's just people.
Oh, there, oh, that Nick or something.
Oh, that Nicaragua stuff.
That's all just people.
I don't care.
Oh, Vietnam.
Oh, those were just humans.
Those were just two-legged animals.
Go ahead and napalm them again.
Do it again.
If you can't do it in Vietnam, go ahead and do it in, uh...
...oh, El Salvador.
Do it instead of Nicaragua.
Do it anywhere you want.
I don't care.
My hero, Ali Norris, said it was okay...
...and he was told it was okay by somebody ahead of him...
...but, but he doesn't remember who...
...and they certainly don't remember either.
Because, because that's okay.
It's okay to kill people.
But it's...
...it's okay to kill people.
It's a terrible, terrible thing...
...for us even to do a satire...
...of making fun of someone not liking animal liberation.
You new age...
...peaks!
You pathetic, pathetic, useless excuses...
...for human...
...I mean, you're useless excuses for human beings...
...much less subgeniuses.
My God!
By gobs, this, I mean, the whole thing, it's just...
...it's just...
...it is...
...no...
...we've been doing this show...
...this is hour of slack number 88.
We've been doing this for 88 weeks...
...and no one has killed us yet.
You call this a free country?
You call this a patriotic...
...American state of Texas?
Where subgeniuses can get on the air...
...or publish pamphlets and books and things...
...out of P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214...
...and nobody's killed us yet.
Oh, no, no, that's too much trouble to go to.
Only if we kill somebody, uh, kill an animal...
...then you'll get upset.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Sick! Sick!
This is not the Dallas show.
This is, this is KNON.
Wait, I'm Doug Smith.
Come on, let me be Doug Smith.
No, you said it was my turn to be Doug Smith.
Hey, listen, you were, last time you were on the air...
...you got to be Buck Henry or whatever that other guy's name is.
I think this confusion breaks out when Bob's...
...re-erection is evident.
Bob's come back to life.
No, don't worry.
He's killing everybody on the list, and your name's next!
...in the game for everybody!
Now, listen, I, I know this sounds funny, but this, this Bob...
...this creature, this werewolf, uh, monster...
Monster, I don't know how we're gonna kill him, but...
...has some vulnerable spot, and, and all we have to do is figure this out...
...and, and then we can...
...and, well, we can find out its weakness, and, and we can kill him.
No, we must communicate with him!
He has much to teach us!
I don't know whatever's down in that pit.
It ain't human, and it ain't an animal.
But it's smoking a pipe.
Look at the glint on its hairdo.
Look, it's, it's beckoning to us.
They're gonna open up with 20 million...
I almost thought it was Ronald Reagan.
Go ahead down in that pit and communicate with it there, Mr. College Professor.
Oh my gosh, look what it's doing. I guess that's why it's...
Uh, hi, uh, we bring you greetings from our civilization, uh...
Ahhhhh!
Oh, look what we did.
Good morning.
Put them subdemus guys out.
What happened, little Cole, what happened?
Slimy sub-demeuses.
What's Reverend saying out here in the Bay Area?
He was caught in that, uh, love nest with, uh, Reverend Gamey, and, uh...
...they made him leave Dallas.
They made him leave the Shining Temple of...
Bob.
Didn't.
Dr. Stan, could you hand me that giant light right there?
Everything I say is a lie, including this very statement.
Wow!
Yes, that's light. I need that light.
Yeah, did you ever stop to think that this show just may be a, uh, a little...
A little show inside a larger show?
And that somehow is inside an even larger show?
Yeah, I had that same, I had that same thing too.
Hotel accommodations question.
It'd be like someone's buying you out behind your back, and you don't even know it's a swine.
No, we're buying you out from behind your back.
Are you really? Well, no one's behind me.
Well...
Here's your back now, being bought out.
Well, I can't see, it's behind me.
Well, never mind.
Can someone see my back?
Camera 3, Bob.
.
But let's leave things of this world behind.
And walk now down the path of Bob for this brief minute of slack from the Church of the Subgenius.
And, uh, we find then the family falling apart.
Oh, they wail and gnash their teeth, our rival churches do, about how the children are getting exposed to too much this and too much that.
What they ain't being exposed to is a little bit of mom and dad.
Forget the pornography, I don't care.
. . .
The hypocrisy, man, my friend, the hypocrisy.
Now I have nothing against hypocrisy.
Every religion must have its fair share of hypocrisy.
As Bob Dobbs once said, I don't practice what I preach because I'm not the kind of man I'm preaching to.
But that preacher can get up there on TV and oh, he's so glad to keep you normal, keep you working so hard you don't even know your own wifey anymore.
And your kids?
You don't know your kids any better than your employees.
So, friend, let there be slack.
Subgenius.com
And now, Shamekia Copeland
Uncivil war, uncivil war
How long must we fight this uncivil war
Same old wounds we opened before
Nobody wins in uncivil war
The lines are drawn, gloves are off
Smiles are gone, we're all talking tough
Uncivil war, uncivil war
You curse me out and I cuss back
Everything we love is under attack
The spirits are back in rags blue and gray
Thought they were gone but they won't go away
Uncivil war, uncivil war
How long must we fight this uncivil war
Same old wounds we opened before
Nobody wins in uncivil war
You're sure you're right, I'm sure you're wrong
Why can't we all just get along
You yell fake and I yell real
Nobody seems to care how the other guy feels
Keeping count of each other's sins
Only problem is nobody wins
Uncivil war, uncivil war
How long must we fight this uncivil war
Same old wounds we opened before
Nobody wins in uncivil war
Uncivil war
We're here to fight a will
Carham's a chill agree to disagree
You cut out all the hostility
Call off the fighting
And bring it to an end
We can shake hands and be friends again
Uncivil War
Why can't we just let it air here so we don't fight others?
Why can't we frames our wrongs
Nobody's backing down
Some won't even talk
The table's empty
We all took a walk
He says left
And she says right
One says peace
The other says fight
One hand's a palm
The other's a fist
Another chance for love
Just got missed
Uncivil war
How long must we fight this
The same old rules
We all went before
Nobody wins
Uncivil war
Straight out of her chest