The program you are about to hear, Bob's Slack Time Funhouse, is parody, satire, and comedy.
Any reference to Bob, the Church of the Subgenius, religion, politics, or any other touchy subjects
is intended only as humor and should cast no reflection on the high standards of WREK Atlanta,
its staff, or that of Georgia Tech.
Star Date 2434.2.
First officer's log.
On a routine patrol flight in the Milky Way galaxy, I discovered on our space sensors
an unidentified planet careening wild birds.
Wildly, in an eccentric solar orbit, I ordered an immediate investigation and with much difficulty
maneuvered our ship for a temporary orbit.
Upon beaming down to the planet's surface, all I could see were ruins.
Ruins of some type of civilization.
Crumbled buildings.
Deserted streets.
Charred vegetation.
All covered with a thick layer of dust.
But none as leaves the Earth's surface as founding tectonic material.
The only sort of
visible cup of air that appeared to have been disappeared, really, we never even experienced.
Only the pleasant waves of light of a certain planet and a began to emerge.
WhileORDMENTADEP.COM
Water targets awaited full unanimous questioning.
These rare features remain undeniable.
For what these are, there exists only onelaughiger.com.
By staniees.com.
JOHN ====וקmpony 0575-045 Cameras began recording all Bridgemark tabletodopes at the request of Karl Amersstam.
I heard a sound.
It came from a cellar in one of the nearby buildings.
Carefully and slowly, I found my way to the source
and discovered a human being.
Or rather, what once was a human being.
A scarred, disfigured man lying in the rubble.
When I questioned him,
he told me that this had once been a great world.
They had abundance and plenty.
Intelligence, beauty, love.
There was enough for everyone who lived there.
But the inhabitants were never satisfied.
They wanted more.
They wanted everything.
And they started to quarrel amongst themselves.
They could not live in peace.
And they tried to destroy each other.
In doing this, they destroyed everything.
Their abundance, their plenty,
their abundance.
Their own intelligence, their beauty, their love.
He told me that so far as he knew,
he was the only living thing left.
But that he knew he was dying.
When I asked him the name of the planet,
he replied,
we called it Earth.
Oh my God, you blew it up!
Damn you all to hell!
This is a real, truly live place.
And I remember that some of it wasn't very nice.
But most of it was beautiful.
But just the same, all I kept saying to everybody was,
I want to go home.
Then close your eyes.
And think to yourself,
there's no place like home.
There's no place like home.
Hey, aren't you going to
turn that damn clock radio off,
so that it's footsteps,
or for maintaining the foods
mycket
al Luisa 18
There there no profit way.
All of my weddings,
including in the 순간 blank quênoas but turtle quê perhaps,
as long as you don't seem to be congratulations from my vast utom Poweria de los Horale.
your troubled mind. Poor Flooz, just let it soak into your shattered little brain.
Wait a minute! You evil witch! That isn't funny at all! Ah, ease up. You were flat-out
kookin' on that song a couple weeks ago. So what's with the long face, puddin'?
Oh, like you don't know? Ah, yeah, but I like to experience the pain I caused through your
perspective. Mmm, this is so sweet. So, you went up to Ranch Apocalypse with hundreds
of other drooling bobbies, looking to get off-planet with them here pie-in-the-sky
sex goddesses, huh? And, ooh, you wound up getting royally reamed for your
brainy, dirty, dirty, dirty, dirty, dirty, dirty, dirty, dirty, dirty, dirty, dirty, dirty,
bright and shining fate, didn't you? Surprise! Ooh, and what did you get for your trouble?
Cuts, bruises, blisters, sunstroke, and, ha, one hell of a chest cold. Ooh, and on top
of that, you really burned your bridges behind you when you flipped that final end of the
world bird at all your co-hosts and both of your listeners. But, but you did that! Did
I? Really?
Hey, who's to know? Who can tell where I end and you begin? Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
Ooh! Hey, Sparky, it's Saturday night again. You still have a show to do. Oh, screw the
show. Oh, well, you sure got your wish last Saturday night. Thanks to you bugging out,
that was one screwed show. You know what went on in your precious little fun house while
you were too vegged out to pull your shift? I don't care. Yeah, you don't care that that
surf music maniac, Rex Reverb, spent a whole hour of church time playing Measerloo over
and over and over? Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha! Oh, and tonight, he's planning to play 25 versions
of Surfer Joe, the vocal. No, no, no. Oh, yeah. No. No. It doesn't matter anymore. I
don't care. There is no show. There is no church. There is no...
Bob? Ha, ha. There is no Bob, is there? Yeah, you've been on a loser's treadmill for years
now and for nothing. It's all over, Flooz. Little Ivan's house of cards got blown down.
Hey, wake up and smell the mail fraud. Yeah, the Federal Trade Commission and the IRS and
the National Council of Churches are closing in on that.
That little weasel. Ha, ha. He's gonna be sharing a cell with Glenn Turner. Yep, looks
like you've been humping the wrong leg, sugar plum. All your subgenius boyfriends are gonna
be taking the fall for this. Oh, a hard rain's a-coming from this shakedown and I, for one,
ain't sticking around to take it on the chin. Oh, jeez. Why don't you just wrap those poisonous
lips of yours around another cliche? Ha, ha. Hey, consider the source, baby.
Everything in me comes from you. Oh, great! But unlike you, I am looking out for our future.
Look at it this way. You could use this opportunity to change directions. And your ministry has
been steadily declining ever since you started this fiasco. Mmm, but hey, up isn't exactly
an option with you. Maybe you could just go down at a steeper angle. Oh, or hey, you and
that co-host of yours... Oh, hey, hello there. You know me. You know me. I can go anywhere.
yours could do uh one of those drive time things like those you know those local radio idiots
stink and sticky or whatever their names are yeah think of the billboards you could take
callers yeah hey you got a natural flair for comedy except for that
what this miserable little dog and prairie squid show of yours could be made to turn a profit
that insipid bob stuff has been keeping you out of the big time flus you could be straddling a
success rocket to the moon oh but i like straddling w-r-e-k atlanta just fine all right the mindless
loyalty card you know they keep you and the big band show guy around just so they can get senior
citizens kicked back from the federal government and what do you think they put you on at this hour
you know
I know this town closes down at 10 o'clock.
And look at this equipment here.
It's all held together as spit and scotch tape.
Oh, but they have hearts.
Oh, yeah, well, I got a heart too, and it's bleeding for you.
Got a tampon?
No, but I do have a wooden stake, bitch.
Take that!
No! Ow!
Oh, damn you!
Well, well, it's one less Susie to worry about.
It smells like summer's eve in here.
I'm sweetness and light, Susie, and you freed me from my earthly prison.
And last time you were here, I was here.
And now I'm free to spread my message of love and joy and peace throughout the world.
Give me back that stake, sister.
Hey, I'm pretty good at this.
Oh, my left boob.
Oh, why'd you have to go and do that?
Geez, Flues, you sure can't take criticism.
Look, you bitch, I only have one stake, and I hate her more than I hate you.
So, just go.
And just shut your stinkin' trap and crawl back in my cortex and just do your friggin' job, okay?
Wh-whatever you say.
I have a show to do.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
I would really like to know you better
But sometimes I'm afraid that it's not meant to be
I would like to believe in something higher
That I can't get a grip on all the little things
When the night comes, I cannot sit still, you see
And the years, they have not been so kind to me
Got a gallery of figures standing all in a row
Every single figure has a name, you know?
It's all of its own
Never look back, never look back
Don't you look back on me
Hey, yeah, my life has come around again
Like so many days
Hey, yeah, my life has begun
Oh, it's been through so many pieces
Hey, yeah, my life has come around again
Like so many threads
And we went too far to be friends
There's a time and a place for understanding
And a time when our actions sound louder than words
And I don't seem to get no implications
And I don't know how to get through to you
And a time like the pyramids has run away
The mountains and the valleys and the words that we say
We have got to make sure that something remains
If we lose each other, we've got no one to blame
Never look back, never look back
Don't you look back on me
Hey, yeah, my life has come around again
Like so many days
Hey, yeah, my life has begun
Oh, it's been through so many pieces
Hey, yeah, my life has come around again
Like so many days
And we went too far to be friends
Hey...
Hey, yeah, my life has come to a bad end
Like sun and the clouds
Hey, yeah, my life has begun
Oh, you see
Hey, yeah, my life has come to a bad end again
So many days have been
Hey, yeah
I can't get away
Hey, yeah, my life has come to a bad end again
Hey, yeah
And I've made a bad deal
Hey, yeah, my life has come to a bad, bad turn
Oh, what would a dead man
My life
Came and go
Hey, yeah
I can't get away
And I've made a bad, bad deal
Now I can't get away
And now I cannot titillate
Come, take my hand
Come, please help me
All right!
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
When you're waking
From a bad dream
Don't you sometimes
Sometimes think it's real
But it's only
All emotion
That you feel
As painful as it is to contemplate,
I guess we should really
become
again at the beginning.
July 5th, 1998.
Dawn, just like
every other day in Dallas.
You can't do this, Bob.
Sheriff, arrest that man!
This community is going to learn to obey the law!
Why should we obey laws that are twisted to fit the needs of thieves and liars?
Take it easy, Bob.
Arrest him! He's a deputy marshal.
Don't let that stop you, Sheriff.
I'm fed up with the law around here.
This court can accept my resignation right now.
Where am I to, Bob?
I'm...
Come on, get going, boys.
Bob, come on.
Sorry about this.
I'll get in touch with you.
Thanks for trying, Todd.
Hey!
It's next day.
What do I care?
A ship that will take you anywhere you want to go in the universe.
That's the kind of flying saucer I mean.
No kidding.
Yes, no kidding.
And if it doesn't turn out to be true,
you can have your worm bag.
Whoa.
Um...
I don't know about that.
Uh...
Oh, all right.
Sounds all right to me, I suppose.
I didn't catch your name, mister.
Dogs.
Once again, Superman concentrates.
Like a laser, his mind beams the exact course they must take to the silver creatures
who wait, shivering just a foot above the Earth's surface.
First thing he says is, watch out for religious deception.
Sincerity is not enough.
The devil's sincere, but he's not saved.
Adolf Hitler was sincere, but he's in hell.
Sincerity is not enough.
You've got to be sincerely right.
You can be sincerely wrong.
Yes, yes, that's right!
Everything you know is wrong.
Then, like a plague of locusts, the alien creatures rise up, up into the sky,
up until they become, once again, a tiny, tiny dark cloud above the highest mountaintop.
And then, finally, can be seen no more.
DOROTHY AND HER PALS
BOOM!
As the screen fell, Dorothy and her pals saw a most unusual sight.
Behind the screen was a tiny, little, old-fashioned...
...old man with a bald head and wrinkled face.
Who...who are you?
I, uh, I am the Wizard of Oz.
But I thought the Wizard of Oz was a huge head or an invisible man or...
No, no, no, I'm not really the great Wizard of Oz.
I'm just a pony. I'm a...I'm a humpug. All that.
Well, Mr. Stang, it was an almost foolproof plan.
I should have stayed with the promise keepers.
No redemption, no redemption
No redemption from evil and sin
Okay. Is anyone here not a downer? Anyone?
Damn it. It fell apart like everything else I've ever believed in.
So, I guess it's back to good old-fashioned voodoo.
Wow, I need a drink!
Come with me.
Terrible! Now I'll never get a heart!
And I'll never get a brain!
And I'll never get a return!
And I guess I'll never get back home!
I'm awfully sorry. I didn't mean any harm. I was just pretending.
But...why did you do it?
Well, it's a long story. You see, I was born in Nebraska.
That may have been the way it happened, Mr. Stang.
But I suppose it wasn't.
Oh, I'm nuts.
Hello.
Hang on here. Who's this?
My name is Bobby Dobbs.
You come in here and take our jobs! You're dead! You were on your skin!
All right.
Well, since they can lie, you're dead! I mean it! Dead!
But you did call it a sympathy trick, Mr. Stang.
The jury has already heard the testimony about the phone call.
There's no use trying to pull the wool over my eyes.
The damage is done!
Don't apologize.
It's much too late now to forgive you for your lies.
I'll keep you in my heart and soul now with such a bitter pill.
To find you only wanted the taste of a brand-new thrill.
The damage is done!
I've been such a fool
I never dreamed that
You could ever be so cruel
Oh, you were playing with my love
It was all a little game
But you've coined my hopes and dreams
Now I'll never know, I'll never be the same
The damage is done
My lesson is learned
This is the last time
That I ever will be burned
Cause the damage is done
Damage is done
You have done
That my love
Was for good
This was all a little game
But you've coined my hopes and dreams
Now I'll never know, I'll never be the same
The damage is done
And you've had your fun
Now you're free to run
Now the damage is done
Oh, you were playing with my love
The wizard turned back
away and Dorothy whispered to the lion how the people didn't want the wizard anymore.
Oh, we were fools to trust any man.
Have you been such a fool, such an adult, such an idiot, such a dum-dum as to give away
my pinky, the best stuff and maker in the neighborhood?
And most quieter than most worms as well for a saucer without a matching cup?
Take that!
Ow!
Oh, my God!
That's a bad thing!
Hey!
Ow!
Now, Bob, I think I got a little problem.
Then me, I just stick it up and get it over with.
Oh, Brad, Bob generally knows what he's doing.
He does everything for the...
Well, Bob, what are we going to do?
I don't know.
That's great.
We go home and hang us.
We stay here, we starve to death.
Roger, don't the other way now, Dobbs.
If I'm not back tonight, don't wait for me.
I'll meet you in Denver, Mountain Hotel.
Wait a minute, Bob.
Me and the boys have been talking.
How about taking over the bank in town before we split?
Nothing to it, Bob.
I told you we were through tonight.
Now get out of here the way we planned all of you.
Bob says we're through.
But why?
It's a shame to leave all that money down there.
Yeah.
That town owes us plenty.
It sure does.
It sounds good, but what about Bob's order?
He won't even know about it until we give him his share.
Yeah, right.
Bob, couldn't we take our fight to another county where we could get a fair trial?
That's a good idea, Ben, but it takes money.
We haven't got it.
Christ.
Who wants the back seat?
Hey, I do.
What I owe you?
With interest.
Bob!
Get Ben out of here.
Come on.
Come on, Bob.
The other officers quickly take up the slack.
Thanks, Bob.
You got me out there just in time.
This ain't right, Bob.
Nothing's right anymore.
Go on.
Get going.
It won't be like before.
There just won't be anymore.
Well, I want him.
Say, Wizard, guess what?
I just now quit.
Why did you quit?
Why did I quit?
Because after you've been taking aboard a UFO, it's kind of hard to top that, all right?
They have Alcoholics Anonymous.
They don't have Alien Anonymous.
I lost my watch.
I lost an alien culture who wanted to take me to the planet Arcturus.
I mean, I don't know if I've gotten the resentment, you know, forgiveness part down in the program.
I turned to a cult for mindless happiness when I had beer all along.
You taking it?
No.
I'm letting go.
You're letting go.
Okay, fine.
Stop.
Dad, Bob broke your beer.
No, I didn't.
Doug broke it.
It was you.
Clean up the mess, boys.
Ridiculous.
Perhaps, Mr. Stank.
In the middle of the room was a big, green marble throne.
Sitting on the throne?
Well, it wasn't exactly sitting, because it was nothing but a big head.
Nobody.
Just a head.
As Dorothy stared, wide-eyed, the big, bald head said,
Dobbs, we'll get the dynamite.
Oh, sacred head, now.
Oh, my God.
God, I hope they're stoned.
Attention, attention, attention.
The bleeding head of our plumber has been destroyed.
Oh, my God.
It was not supposed to be like that.
A premature head-latching, but nonetheless, a lead-latching.
And now, because it's absolutely no-sense, we're going to have Jader launch the head.
Oh, my God.
If anybody has any flashlights...
We need some flashlights over here.
We need a...
The superstar needs some lights.
Flashlights, flashlights.
I know you guys have them.
Where are they?
Break them out.
Break out the flashlights.
And let's launch the bleeding head of Tiger Woods.
Ladies and gentlemen, state.
State.
Ladies and gentlemen, we have just seen the destruction of the bleeding head of Arnold Palmer.
I think this shows everyone.
Just tell us why the conspiracy is ready to go and try to stop the X's landing.
Because it's the Palmer head, which is the perfect golfer who has the golf plan,
who's actually working with the Y's to try to stop the X's.
The conspiracy is trying to connect with the Y's,
which is connecting him with things that have seven limits for heads,
which isn't exactly the same thing as the thing with a U-totem for a head,
which is different, actually, from the thing with an 812 store for a head.
Who?
A witness who can prove you are lying, Mr. Stang.
Now, there's Arthur.
Arthur is a witness.
I think I'll start by reading you one that isn't terribly serious,
but it explains what his views were when people asked.
My answer is, no, he really did not believe in a serious way in UFOs,
and this might be an indication of that.
UFOs is a bucket of s***.
Mr. Stang.
Is a bucket of s***.
I'd just come up behind him with a knife and put his throat real quick like that.
So I grabbed him by the collar.
And I jerked him out of the car and said,
Buddy, I ain't never seen nobody like you are.
How come you pull these kind of jokes?
He said, well, sometimes it works, sometimes it don't.
And I thought, what kind of deal is this?
It's a bad joke.
That's great.
Your words, your words don't mean
What they used to mean
They were once inspired
Now they're just a joke
They're just, they're just routine
I'm afraid the masquerade is over
And so is love
Bob, you've been through so darn much lately.
What do you think's going to happen to you now?
I don't know.
Gotta nuke something.
Touche.
Have you thought about one of the other major religions?
They're all pretty much the same.
What if we pick the wrong religion?
Every week we're just making God madder and madder.
Testify!
You just gotta learn not to expect nothing out of life.
Were you fixing to say a little something about how life don't seem too fair?
Don't even start.
I think you need to learn to get a little disappointed.
Tear dropped or wind there don't make me laugh.
Please don't touch my heart.
Who said life was a roller coaster?
Who said life was sweet surprise?
Who said life was a circus poster?
Not me, not me.
So ask me no questions.
Give me no answers.
And I'll tell you no lies.
Were you getting yourself a ride?
A little moody cause some folks are down right mean
Oh me, oh my, ain't that a shame, shame
Well you're starting to make a little speech
About the troubles that you've seen
Please spare me that
Stop that pity game again
Now who said life was a ball of berries?
Who said life was peach ice cream?
Who said life was a box of cherries?
Not me, not me
So ask me no questions, give me no answers
And I'll sell you no drinks
Were you thinking that you were gonna maybe
Have to leave this lovely town again, again?
Get one more spot
Were you feeling a little like a baby
Who just got itself knocked down?
You say you were
I say well so what?
Ain't no use
Who said life was a song for singin'?
Who said life was such a snap?
Who said life was a bell for ringin'?
Not me, not me
So ask me no questions, give me no answers
And I'll hand you no credits
Who said life was a song for singin'?
Who said life was such a snap?
Who said life was a bell for ringin'?
Not me, not me
So ask me no questions, give me no answers
And I'll hand you no crap
And I'll sell you no dreams
And I'll tell you no lies
No lies
I couldn't bother to be a low-down door count witness, in you.
There isn't a bus coming home?
What are you looking at?
I'll cut loose, you skank!
If I were by myself, I'd show for you, unconscious!
It was me!
Wait, you're making a mistake!
Put me down!
It's the villager!
It's a clerical error!
It's Stang's fault!
The party's over
It's time to call it a day
They've burst your pretty balloon
And taken the moon away
It's time to wind up
The masquerade
Just make your mind up
The piper must be paid
The party's over
The candles flicker and dim
You danced and dreamed through the night
It seemed to be right
Just being with him
Now you must wake up
All dreams must end
Take off your makeup
The party's over
It's all over
Over, my friend.
Now you must wake up.
Our dreams must end.
Take off your makeup.
The party's over.
It's all over.
My friend.
Well, I think I'm gonna break down and cry.
Oh!
Yes, I've been hurt.
Like I've never been hurt before.
Turn back the clock, hey, turn around and join the ambience.
Yeah, don't just sit last to your in there like that.
Because you cheated, cheated, cheated,
cheated, cheated, cheated, cheated on me, girl.
Yeah, she told me that not always she makes the best of me.
You way.
I have nothing to do with it, I swear.
I was just repeating what I was told.
Oh, little girl, girls out in the air.
And I've been hurt.
Oh, till I can't do it.
Oh, not you too anymore.
Oh, look lady, I really have nothing to do with this.
And my name.
Here you go.
There must be some sort of mistake.
And no pain.
No, no, no, no.
When you left.
No more, I keep.
Great.
Cause I can be.
Sweeter than you.
Left with food.
Bobby Bull.
And I've been hurt.
Hurt.
Till I can't hurt.
Well, at least it sounds like there's a limit.
I'm so hurt.
Oh, great.
Where'd she come from?
To think that you.
You lied.
To me.
Hey, I'm in the same boat.
I'm hurt.
Way down deep inside of me.
Try to look at it from my perspective.
I mean.
You said your love was true.
And we'd never.
Ever.
Never.
I cotton.
Hey.
Look.
No, you what?
And one.
Hey.
Mine.
self.
.
What?
I don't.
more oh then you'll ever know staying in all of his goons they just they keep me in the dark
yes darling i i'm so hurt i feel as wronged as you i because i still love you so
but but how many butts do you have even though you hurt me
like nobody else oh man i'm out of here i ain't filled no class action lawsuit i would never
ever
oh just look at all these expenses for the apocalypse
apocalypse gas camping fees new nikes black pajamas roll
oh just look at all these expenses for the apocalypse gas camping fees new nikes black pajamas roll
quarters
damn oh that leaves nothing for frock for the rest of the whole damn summer
oh thanks a lot bob
oh why bob why what did i ever do to you what's the idea of leaving me bereft upon that misty
hilltop in new york oh how i tried i was a dupe of the first water for you
hilltop in new york from acial south lift you Bob
hilltop in Buggy
hilltop in buggy
you Bob
hilltop in trampoline
h frozen
hilltop in tourorthDIO
Bob, the fact that you alone understood my pain, the agony of living on this life-sapping planet,
and you told me what I longed to hear.
That yes, there was a place in the stars where the slack flowed like hot lava and the sex codices were even hotter.
Yes, yes, it didn't matter how much I suffered here because I would be rewarded there.
So, oh, how I debased myself for you, Bob.
I prostitutelized for you, serving you on my knees night and day in the trenches of this pink conspiracy world,
spreading the message of your divine withering grace among the slack-starved masses.
Oh, and then, come your prophecy next day,
I awaited your coming in the fearsome light of early dawn,
with hundreds of believers, arms spread, mouths wide open for the first barrage of face-raping bats,
and it didn't come.
Desperately, desperately, I looked to the skies for those gleaming iridescent escape vessels
and for the glory and sex codices within them, but they didn't come.
I was looking for that ultimate good time that you promised us, Bob,
and Bob...
Bob!
I didn't come!
Oh.
Oh, what does this mean, Bob?
Is your word false, even to your truest believers?
Are our sacred pre-scriptures nothing but lies?
What else is there you're lying about, Bob?
What about the sex?
What about the salvation?
Oh, Bob, if you were wrong about X-Day,
were you wrong about the slack, too, Bob?
Oh, no.
No.
I can't go on if it means living in a world without slack.
Oh, Bob, I can't take this pain.
Why?
I wonder why.
P攰
ف
But I never find out why
I keep pushing to hold it
Maybe I keep trying to make it right
To another lonely day
Oh, oh, oh
It's coming to an end
25 years
And it's just one night
Oh, yeah
But I'm 25 years old tonight
So I know it can't be right
And I'm no better, babe
And I can't help you no more
Than I did when you just began
But it don't make no difference, babe
Oh, oh, oh
No, no
And I know that I could always try
It don't make no difference, babe
I better hold it now
I better need it, yeah
I better use it till the day I die
Why?
Don't expect any answer
Still
Oh, I know that they don't come with age
No, no
I ain't never gonna love you any better, babe
And they're never gonna love you right
So you better take it now
Right now
Oh
But it don't make no difference, babe
And I know that I'm gonna wish it out
But there's a fire inside of every one of us
You better need it now
I get to hold it, yeah
I better use it till the day I die
Don't make no difference, babe
No, no, no
And it never ever will
I wanna talk about living and loving you
I get to hold it, babe
I gotta need it now
I better use it
Say hi!
Don't make no difference, babe
Oh, honey, I hate to be the one
I said you better live your life
And you better love your life
Oh, baby
Someday you're gonna have to cry
Yes, indeed
Oh, baby, yes, indeed
I said you're almost gonna hurt your own life
I said they're almost gonna let you down
And it's everywhere
Everywhere, everywhere
And everywhere, everywhere
Oh, honey, what you hold on to, it's gonna move
I said it's gonna disappear when you turn to black
I said you know it ain't gonna be there when you wanna reach out and hear about it
Oh, baby
Oh, but keep trackin' on
Oh, yeah
Oh, yeah!
Woo!
I sang
I saw
And I fell little fool I am
And now I'm in an awful jam
I love him but oh
I guess I'll have to change my plan.
I should have known that he'd be somebody else's man.
I overlooked that point completely
until the big affair began.
Yes, before I knew where I was at,
I found myself up on the shelf, and that was that.
I tried to reach the moon, but when I got there,
all that I could get was the air.
My feet are back up.
I'm up on the ground.
I've lost the one man I found.
I guess I'll have to change my plan.
I should have realized I'd be an also-ran.
Why, why did I buy those black pajamas?
Before the big affair began.
My boiling point is much too low
for me to cope with that elope for Romeo.
I think I'll crawl right back
and into my shell,
dwelling in my purse.
But
from thousands of miles beyond your planet.
Warning!
The final hour is approaching for the people of Earth.
Ah!
Oh, my God!
Oh, great advice, but how can you change your plans
when half of your life has been spent preparing for a day
that just didn't happen?
Or did it?
Did it not happen, Seekers?
I was there at Brushwood, and I know what I saw.
Or I think I know what I saw, but...
Oh, whatever it was, it was truly apocalyptic.
I went not knowing what to expect,
but with a background sensation that we would all somehow be ripped off.
Oh.
You know, as I put it, one way or another,
we're all gonna finally get porked real good by Bob.
Woo-hoo!
Oh, but, you know, Seekers,
I never expected to be feeling such righteous afterglow
from the spiritual mugging we all suffered.
Sure, staying in Jesus or brazen charlatans
who took advantage of our willing gullibility,
and sure, the chance of actual redemption from the skies
is about zilch .9,
and, uh, oh, but still,
I tried to keep that wool pulled over my eyes
and to be a starry-eyed little seeker for the cause,
and although deep inside there was a feeling
that we were about to get the big burn of all time,
I tried to deny it.
Oh, but, Seekers, something mystical happened out there
in that subgenius sweat lodge,
and I know I'm not the only one who saw it.
The night of X-Day Eve, after all the riddles,
the night you all started to peter out,
I took my boombox full of apocalyptic, easy-listening music
out into the middle of the big-ass brushwood field
and stood out there,
naked and alone in the dewy grass
beneath a sky that was screaming with stars.
And there I danced an end-times dance alone in the dark.
And as I swirled,
everywhere I looked was alive with our people,
the night air pulsed with subgenius life.
All around me was a ring of their glowing campfires
and the sounds of their last night on earth revelry
carried through the cold night air
and blended with the atmospheric schmaltz.
And suddenly, I was moved to tears of absolute joy by it all,
because this was no longer a raggedy-ass convocation of bitter misfits
that screwed up loners.
No, suddenly we were a great subgenius nation.
And at that point of Satori alone there in that field,
I sobbed like a damn baby over it.
And in that crystalline perfect moment,
I knew what it was really all about.
Waiting for the saucers to arrive was a lot of kicks, sure.
Oh, but that wasn't the be-all and end-all of the game.
Yeah, we got burned.
Oh, but at the same time,
something stronger in us all got forged in those same fires.
We are all in this church from the start
because of our mutually shared pain and discontent.
And at the risk of sounding just too damn sweetness and light,
we have each other.
That's where our power and our true menace to them is.
And some has always lain.
Oh, but by the same token,
we can draw the solace and the strength that we need for our basic survival
from the fact that we are a solid, cohesive subgenius family.
Yes, every one of us has a part around Bob's big dinner table,
passing that steaming tureen of slack to the Yeti next to you,
and happily digging into the soul-satisfying feast of Dobbs
with our brethren.
Sure, we're a dysfunctional family,
but we're made of superior material to start with.
And our version of the home game has much more amusing and fascinating characters,
like our oily daddy, Stang,
and our badass uncle, Katahdin Lagume,
and our sweet little brother, Onan,
and our silken sister, Lilith,
and our crusty old grandpa, G. Gordon Gordon.
Ha ha!
Oh, and you can just think of me
as your slutty sister, Susie,
who laughs it off when you walk in on me
when I'm douching in the tub.
Yeah, because out there in the woods, Seekers,
I got more bang for my membership buck than I ever thought possible.
This church has given me,
and I know it has given many others,
something immeasurable,
and I am absolutely shining from it all.
With lovely subgenius friends like I have,
I can simply chortle out of hell to sex goddesses,
and maybe I can laugh off the sting of brutal disappointment that much more easily.
Because we didn't exactly get off this planet,
but for some weird-ass damn reason,
I don't exactly mind living on crap ball earth as much as I did just two weeks ago.
And that in itself is a miracle of first degree, baby.
Oh, sure, this cult is founded on a big damn joke,
but our dedication to our own is totally serious,
and any lame-ass butt-stain who doubts that we're a family
can just look at the outpouring of support for poor stricken pea-kitty.
A subgenius so strong that not even diabetes could fell him.
Oh, maybe we didn't get off this planet, Seekers,
but we can use our new solidarity to create a subgenius paradise for the utensin here on earth.
And by the way, yes,
that was a huge damn X in the clouds in the pink light of early dawn on X-Day morning.
And it was truly a beautiful thing to see the tangible sign of Dob's covenant with his people,
a fire in the skies over our great subgenius nation.
Oh, brave new world that has such creatures in it.
Snap out of it.
Ow!
Ah.
I think that pagan living softened your brain.
How do you feel?
Huh.
Do I ever need a frickin' cigarette?
After that emotional display, I need a douche.
Oh, yeah.
Ah!
torres?
Nab.
Oh, fuck!
Partner, yes!
Through this night were still the troubles of the past so far.
Out of sight, through the mind.
Ah, oui.
Ah, oui!
I've done a lot
God knows I've tried
To find the truth
I've even lied
But all I know
Is down inside I'm bleeding
I'm a superhero
Come to feast
To taste the flesh
Not yet deceased
And all I know
Is still the business
Of a hero
With me
And crawling
on the planet's face
Some insects
Called the human race
Lost in time
And lost in space
And in meaning
Meaning
Ah
Smithers, I'm so happy.
Something amazing has happened.
I'm actually happy.
Take a note.
From now on, I'm only going to be good and kind to everyone.
I'm sorry, sir.
I don't have a pencil.
Don't worry.
I'm sure I'll remember it.
P.O. Box 181417
Cleveland Heights, Ohio
And also see