Now, would you get your nose out of my amoeba?
Before we begin today's lessons, I think there's one thing we should straighten out in regard to our relations with each other.
Uh-oh.
Oh!
Some of you seem to think there's something shameful about a little boy and a little girl liking one another.
Mm-hmm.
Now, let's think about it for a minute.
I want the reason.
All of us are rather like one big family.
Oh, that's not good enough.
And I think our family could be a lot happier...
None of your business.
...if we were kind, considerate, and friendly toward one another.
I am not.
Well, you don't have to be.
I wanted to hit somebody.
But I do think you should have mutual respect and learn to get along together.
You're a smelly old ape.
You really told him.
You know, if you do that...
For two days.
You'll be taking a big step toward...
The Self-Genius.
Power of...
The kind of men and women we want.
Yeah, because you're dirty.
All right, fellas, let's get going.
The following is copyright 1981 by the Subgenius Foundation.
Should you have comments, criticisms, or suggestions regarding the cassette book program,
please forward them directly to...
The Technical Staff.
Division for the Blind and Physically Handicapped.
Library.
Secretary of Congress.
Washington, D.C.
2-0-5-4-2.
Over 21 years...
This concludes the instruction.
Perhaps this is as good a time as any to take a few minutes to repeat a message
that seems frequently lost in the hustle and bustle of our daily activity.
This won't make too much sense, but it's not intended to.
It's intended to strengthen the lips.
Bring your lips far forward now with woo.
Woo.
Woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo.
For variation, emphasize every third or fourth woo.
Woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo.
And I have so much I would like to say, but I don't know how to say it.
So please bear with me if sometimes this doesn't make much sense.
It's realistic.
The second question is what?
What's happening?
Uh, before this...
Before this show, the Hour of Slack began in 1985,
we produced 13 90-minute albums on cassette tape,
which we called media barrages.
Some of those later became CDs, but not the one we're playing tonight.
Tonight we're exerting Media Barrage No. 1,
edited by me in 1981,
when there were only a few dozen subgeniuses,
and only about eight of them are on this tape.
Me, that is Reverend Ivan Stang,
Dr. Philo Drummond, Puzzling Evidence,
Lies, Glass Madness,
Pope Sternodocs,
Snavely Eklund,
Jane or Hypercletes,
and the late Dr. X.
In other words, what you're about to hear was our very first official subgenius album
made 35 years ago.
Praise Bob.
Is this a miracle?
What kind of a miracle?
Is this a parable?
What's the point?
Is this a letter?
What's the big idea?
What's he trying to communicate?
Because people like you are helping us stay on the radio.
You can't buy a miracle.
But you can certainly stand behind a miracle ministry.
Like a bunch of...
Uh, I'd like to go to the lake.
I'd like to go to the stage.
Go walking around.
I'd like to go to the beach.
Uh, yeah.
I'm honestly a bit down.
As the weather keeps around me...
Um...
I will see you soon.
Um, so nice to meet you.
Have a some fun.
We got to get going.
Okay, awesome.
So nice seeing you.
Chaotic times.
Praise the Lord.
And these times are not going to get any better, my friend.
Amen.
They're going to get worse and worse.
Opium is still the primary plan that the United States has for dealing with its people in the event of a nuclear attack.
There has been six cases of breast cancer, one bladder cancer, and one throat cancer.
There is a God who is a God of love, and there is a God who is a God of judgment.
Two sides.
Mockery of everything that's decent and wholesome.
I challenge you to point out national talk shows that do not belittle sexual fidelity, purity.
That they do not belittle the marriage union and the family lifestyle.
That they don't literally flaunt illicit lifestyles.
I mean, I challenge you to show me.
A talk show that doesn't make light of God.
The Subgenius Foundation.
The Reverend Ivan Stang and Dr. Philo Drummond.
And they are, as we mentioned before, the dual heads of the Subgenius Foundation.
You don't know about the school book suppositories.
Watch out for all the leads.
Because I'm number 6742 to witness it.
And they're coming.
Coming after me.
So call their derby.
Hello there, Palo Du.
We're picking up all your trash.
With us, the leader and the idea are one.
And every party leader must do what the leader orders.
Subgenius culture.
Subgenius.
Mr. Chairman.
Gentlemen.
I must admit.
I know.
I'm very little at this time.
It doesn't make fun of godly laws.
Agreed.
They laugh at us.
I agree.
They make a mockery of us.
Now, we don't have to watch it.
We can turn it off.
Who will pay to clean up the contaminated land?
And because of the equal time provision in the law, we can't show you the taped interviews.
Follow issue.
787-1270 is the number.
Call us and talk about what you'd wish.
Go ahead.
I'm going to point out that a lot of people worry about the one world government that the conspiracy is trying to get across on us.
And we suspect that the only thing that can fight a one world government is going to be a one world religion.
And of course, that's what the subgenius, the church of the subgenius is here for.
I'm telling you, all other gods besides Jehovah and his son Jesus Christ are strange gods.
Question number two.
Do you believe in the virgin birth of Jesus Christ and the death and the resurrection of Jesus?
And the resurrection, barrel and a resurrection.
Sir, we absolutely believe in everything.
We believe in it wholeheartedly.
I'm sorry.
The voice analyzer was designed by our guru, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
We have to make clear from the beginning that we are not really the founders.
We were just hired to promote the word of Bob.
Okay, that then brings me to this.
It is the Subgenius Foundation is the publishing and PR firm of the Church of the Subgenius.
So would you tell me then what is the Church of the Subgenius?
It was founded by Bob.
Bob founded the church mainly to help unmask the conspiracy.
And we're talking about the conspiracy, the one behind the other conspiracy.
Oh, that's the one.
To unmask the conspiracy and to get us all a little bit of slack.
Slack through any means we can make do with.
Time control is one of the most spectacular and hard to achieve ones.
We're going to go into some depth before the evening is over,
defining, and as I say deeply,
the terms, uh, slack, and what was the other?
Time control.
Right.
Absolutely.
Those are things that I, of course, think we need to deal with.
The use of genius and my subgenius and my subpenius.
The use of penis and my subpenius and my subpenius.
I must love to know!
Now we must vote to know.
Grandfather, all the whites aren't crazy.
I'm glad to hear that, my son.
I thought they were.
Oh, no.
I know of one who is as brave as any human being.
I'd like to meet this man and smoke with him.
Bob started the church about 20 or 30 years ago.
We've got a picture of him here.
We'll hold it up so everybody on the radio can see him.
Hold it up to the left part of the radio there.
Can you see that?
You can see that he's a really handsome guy.
He looks a lot like George Noll.
He has a pie and smiling.
He's got what some people call a sinister grin.
Jack Armstrong, all-American boy.
He looks better.
He lives.
I can face.
But it's just a sin.
And you just can't call it anything else.
Many of you in this stadium have been deceived.
Perhaps you've been deceived by evangelists masquerading as angels of light.
Hanuman Likova, the ninth seed.
The only cult they want to talk about.
Is the subgenius foundation.
The church of the subgenius.
And the only reason they talk about it is for the money.
We're going to go to the phones right now.
Good evening.
You're on KFJZ with Mr. Opinion and Dr. Philo Drummond and the Reverend Arnold Stang.
Ivan Stang.
I have a question for Mr. Drummond.
Yes.
Go ahead.
Are you Mr. Drummond?
That's right.
I'm calling from Dallas.
What's your question?
Well, do you work on spiritual problems?
Are you spiritual?
Or do you just work on wallets?
We will help you out spiritually.
Of course, it helps if we can have some financial assistance.
We sell $10 memberships.
And once you start getting our newsletter, you start receiving lessons on how to conduct
your life in the most beneficial way for both you and us.
And regardless of what you're looking for.
Doug Smith says we're different.
Doug's right, Virgil.
We are different.
Thanks to Jesus, the genetic engineering corporation of American states.
Mommy too?
Yep, the whole family.
Is everybody like us?
No, son, but we're working on it, round the clock.
Soon everyone will be a superior biospecies.
Wowee.
I want to be a genetic engineer just like you, Pop.
You will, Virg, if you don't baggy.
It can lead to photon confusion.
Don't baggy.
.
for a healthier, happier, bio-superior.
Hi!
You say you're looking for excitement, adventure, business opportunities,
and a real nice place to raise the kids?
Well, explore no more.
We're there already.
Let's visit the world of the future.
World of the future.
Yes, this bustling world of a thousand moods
reflects the dreams of its ambitious inhabitants,
dreams already realized of man's triumph over nature,
where humans no longer suffer self-inflicted pains,
where one is made to enjoy life.
Hallelujah!
All the signs point to serious health damage.
There are no winners in a nuclear war.
The minute you have another war,
there's not going to be any world left, I don't think,
because we're going to blow one another to pieces.
Because in this day and time,
we don't know what we're going to come to.
There's not going to be anything left for the kids.
I mean, there's not going to be a world left.
And we're all going to end up digging our own holes.
As soon as we dig them, they're going to fall in on us.
I don't think anybody would know what to do,
even possibly the president.
The only true religion is guns.
The guns create your own reality.
If I had a gun,
I'd create my own reality.
Crude to the loon.
Simple.
You have a gun,
you point it at their head,
and you're in control.
I would listen to television and watch it.
Tune us in on the radio dive.
We got charisma, we got style.
Well, people,
we'll make you feel better for a while.
Put your hands,
put your hands on the radio.
Those are the Pink Boys from right here in Dallas.
And put your hand on the radio.
Before that, the B-52s in private Idaho.
And of course, Devo.
And one of the earlier more primitive versions of Mongo-ite.
This is the Rock and Roll Alternative.
My name is George.
And tonight,
on the subject of the Pink Boys and all that,
we have in the studio with us
Ivan Stang and Philo Drummond from the Church of the Subgenius.
Hi, guys.
How you doing, George?
Oh, just fine.
Say, a lot of people have been wondering,
just what is the Church of the Subgenius?
Well, George, if we could describe the Church of the Subgenius in one sentence,
we'd be rich by now.
As it is, we're explaining it in long-winded sentences,
and we're getting rich kind of half.
Half fast.
It's kind of a scam, religious cult company, whatever you want to get into.
It's the first industrial church.
That's right.
We're hoping to make a lot of money real fast.
And if we can wake up ten more people out there in the listening audience tonight,
we will have achieved our goal for the evening.
What is the church's priorities?
What's important to you guys?
Mainly the quest for slack.
The casting out of false prophets.
And controlling time.
Those are our three main goals, I guess.
Slack.
It's something we all need.
And I know that lots of people out there listening right now are feeling a terrible shortage of slack.
Slack is something you can't get enough of.
That's right.
And we can help them to get slack, George.
Man, the world is filled with a bunch of kooky ideas and concepts about the Bible.
And I can't believe the weird things that people get in their heads
and the weird things that people are teaching.
Why do you think that these people, aside from that rather vague reference in the Bible,
why do you think these fallen angels have stayed around to do us in, so to speak?
Well, they figure that this planet is theirs to loot
and that the people of Earth, we Earth people, are their slaves.
And I think the past history of all the records of the wars and famines and things that were created deliberately by them,
I think, bears it out.
Not only that, Joe, besides the Bible, there's also other ancient works.
That's what I like about the Word of God.
There's nothing fakey about this thing, man.
You talk about telling it like it is.
See, it hangs the dirty wash right out the front bay window for everybody to see.
And ladies and gentlemen, this is a transmission that we picked up, obviously, from space beings.
That's right.
And we want, when 1998 comes, we want subgeniuses to be in positions of power
so that this alien technology is not abused.
And Bob tells us what we need to know to get into that position.
One year ago, we were obscure nobodies, and now we're secretly famous.
That's right. And we've got hundreds of dollars at our disposal.
And close to thousands upon dozens of members as well.
That's exactly right. We are international now.
Every state in the Union is represented on our mailing list in 12 foreign countries.
That is strictly incredible.
And what are the various ranks in the Church?
Well, of course, Bob is our high-E poppin' guru.
He's the saint of sales.
That's right. The ultimate businessman.
Very few people are able to meet Bob.
He is pretty hard to get a hold of.
He's like most cult leaders.
Dr. Drummond here is the...
He communicates with me via telepathic transmissions beamed into my skull.
And so what we get from him is usually second-hand information.
He in turn is like a shortwave radio picking up signals from famous dead holy men,
living holy men, creatures from outer space,
advanced supersonic Nazi hell creatures from within the hollow earth.
Waiting for the UFO.
Waiting for the UFOs.
And they use the latest components.
I feel like a new machine.
Go now, quickly.
The survival of our galaxy is in your hands.
Thanks, and I'll try to live up to that.
Jeez.
Well, the Church is going pretty good.
How has your life changed since dogs came into your life?
Crowds?
I've realized that the exes are a reality,
and that my life is geared towards their arrival.
I redefined my own space and was able to center my being.
I was really able to integrate all my anti-societal...
I'm gonna kill everybody here!
When I first heard Bob on the radio,
he said that he could heal,
and told me to put my hand on the radio
so that the Bob energy could come out through the airwaves.
Death to the fascist earthworms!
Many of you in this stadium have been deceived.
Put your hands on the radio!
Well, let me ask you, sir, are you having some type of problem in your life now?
If I have a triple-steer,
I'm having a spiritual problem right now.
Okay, give us some idea of the nature of the problem.
Well, I'm afraid of God.
Oh, you are?
Yeah.
Well, there's a lot of people out there just like you.
I tell you what, if you would, put your hands on the radio right now.
We can help you out.
I think we're being sold a bill, a big bill of goods.
Really now, are you guys in this cult business just for the bucks or do you have...
Mr. Wilsey, isn't it a fact really that you've invented this whole thing,
that you've thought up all these little gimmicks,
and you're taking advantage of a lot of ignorant people by getting money out of them,
people who believe in you and your silly preachings?
No, it isn't, Joe.
The Illuminati will be unmasked, and the subgenius cult will have a lot to do with that.
Bob is going to see that the whole conspiracy, the Illuminati, the trilaterals, you name it,
the guys that drive up and down the street selling ice cream, all of that will be exposed.
That's what America needs, to have their brains washed,
clean out all that filth and all that garbage and all that fear
and all that sickness and perversion and all that junk that comes from the pit of hell.
I'm completely organized.
I can perform marriages.
I can legally perform marriages, and I can also ordain people.
And that's what we've been doing.
When you become a $10 member, we send you a little card that says you're a minister.
That loosely explains that.
Then, Dr. Drummond, could you explain your doctorate?
I'm not really a medical doctor, but more a PhD-type doctor.
I obtained my PhD at Dobbstown Community College, and my PhD was in journalism.
We sell doctorates, too.
What's a good doctorate going for now? $6?
Yeah, $6. We sell about the cheapest doctorates on the market.
Most of them are $20 to $30.
But the Diploma Gilda Edged or plain?
It's plain, but it's got more Bob pin on it than you can imagine.
It takes about three hours to read, and it tells you in great detail what sort of a subgenius you are.
Praise doctors for Bob!
In the Doctors for Bob album, what is subgenius?
It's Doctors for Bob!
Here's the Doctors for Bob one of those words.
You think you can know a subgenius without knowing Doctors for Bob?
Well, you're wrong!
What is Doctors for Bob?
Doctors for Bob!
Only we know what we don't know.
And when we do know it, we shall find out later just exactly what it was that we didn't know.
But in the meantime, we shall experiment further and delve into the deeper recesses of the human mind to find out exactly what causes this device not to function properly.
Could it be a malfunction of the foot gland or the nose gland?
Yes, possibly you did not know that the nose and the feet are true glands of the human body.
And only after permanent foot and nose glandscaping can you know how to make your feet smell and your nose run.
Which would mean possibly that you were backwards or built upside down.
But we'll delve further into that at the end of the broadcast when you and I cannot hear each other.
Doctors for Bob!
And we can get into this too, this psychoneurotic mastosurgery, the techniques of which has been developed by the many great doctors who have come over to Dobbs and from many of the other religious cults around the world.
I ain't been the same since I had my frontal lobotomy.
And we've got Europeans and Lithuanians and little Mexican doctors and we've got rock and roll star doctors.
And...
And ice doctors and the big doctors and the doctors of the trees and the tree walking brain socket doctors.
And we've got a song about doctors.
And here, hyperclites, here it is.
Doctors for Bob.
Doctors for Bob and everything real in my life.
Oh, real in my life.
Damn pickup truck come out blue done run over my wife.
He's got the blues cause they run over his wife.
Some of you are going to get mad at me.
Jesus ain't in the church.
Don't turn the radio off.
Keep it on.
And I wouldn't infer that our secondary state is antichrist.
But I'm telling you that preparations are being made.
And that the very door of the day of the wrath of God is at hand.
And that if you plan to get saved, you had better do it now.
There will be a day not in the too far distance.
And a future in which antichrist will be revealed.
And the mark of the beast will be introduced.
And people will have a number in their hands and in their foreheads.
They'll be given a considerized number if you please.
That will entitle them to do business in this world.
And without it, you can starve.
We have a lot to do in a very short time.
Boy, you are kidding.
And that's the way I felt for quite a while.
Get ready to ease out of orbit.
Ah, you bet, honey.
That's what we're going to try to do.
I have never flown a city before.
Many of you in this stadium have been deceived.
I think they'll pass the $10 bridge.
The original concept was that...
Throughout history, all great geniuses...
had somebody at their side that was kind of steering them.
You know what I mean?
So you say that person is...
That was the subgenius. He was the guy that was really...
He was making sure the genius was used to his proper potential.
Right.
And for the right reason.
That's why my name is misleading, you know.
Now, I want you to hear a little of the service where the Holy Spirit was using me.
With the gift of discernment.
I was ministering in the Spirit.
God was showing me things about people I didn't know.
I'd never seen before, but the Lord was talking to me.
God was talking and I was walking.
Listen to a little of this right now.
My sister, I don't know anything about you.
I haven't talked with you.
As far as I know, you haven't told him...
Have you told him, my staff, anything about yourself?
You haven't.
Then if I know anything about you, it would be because the Spirit of the Lord has led me to you today.
Am I right?
You're in dire financial...
She wasn't supposed to say anything.
I'm in dire financial need, baby.
...things that you possess if you don't cope with some money pretty soon.
And you have come to the end of your rope.
You don't know which way to turn.
Give me money.
It's starting to affect your nerves.
It's affecting my mind.
And sleepless nights.
I want to kill my husband.
Today we're going to put this in the hand of God.
I'll kill my husband.
In the Bible, in two different places, a handful of meal brought a miracle.
I want you to hold that envelope open.
That's right.
Please save my life.
I'm going to give you a handful of meal.
Save my life!
I'm going to pour it in this envelope.
Now.
Amen.
Tell him the truth.
I know you're telling the truth.
That's what's bad.
From now on, every new addition to our demand for energy will be met from our own production
and our own conservation.
There's the fact that the trial agents and some of the other people that you've named
are actually being controlled by aliens from outer space.
By UFO agents.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
We're not going to hurt you.
But once you understand, you'll be grateful.
Let us go!
We'll leave town.
We won't come back.
We can't let you go.
You're dangerous to us.
Don't fight it Miles, it's no use
Sooner or later you'll have to go to sleep
Subgeniuses strike out on their own too
There's rogue subgeniuses
In fact they've gone
They were originally subgeniuses
That went off the deep end
Like Howard Hughes
Jack the Ripper
Adolf Hitler
Richard Nixon
For sure would be one
And not just crazy people
Muhammad Ali
Yeah, renegades, Muhammad Ali
He's a renegade subgenius
But these people don't know they're subgeniuses
No, they don't
They may know
They may know, and for all we know
They're out there reading stuff
The 5th Temple Lodge of the Church of the Subgenius
Of Little Rock
And before we begin this sacred spouting
I think that we should all
Bow our heads
And let's all have a minute of noise
Ah!
First we have a schisming member of the church here
This is uh
Did you introduce yourself?
No
Holy Master
Do not listen to this man
This man is a retrogrant
This is an anti-democracy
This is anti-Dobbs speaking to you
Here we've got stereo here
This is the anti-Dobbs
Take this note
This one here
No
This one
Okay
The true Dobbs is in the right channel now
True Dobbs
All Dobbs followers to the right
Uh, hello, hello Reverend Doug
This is Edwin
Better known as Savage Pencil
Speaking to you from you in a little room in
Belsize Park, London
Where I live
Anyway, I'd just like to thank you very much for speaking to me today
And for sending me all those really great subgenius things
Including the absolutely work of art stock fist brochure
And all the other things
I've got them all plastered up everywhere
I've been telling everybody about them
I've been mumbling about subgenius and everything to many people
With your permission, the Reverend Bob and your good selves
May be popping up in a future rock and roll zoo
This man has something to say
When I came up here this morning
I knew that Bob was straight
But you know something
I serve a miracle working God
High as a star, high as a star
You can never get higher than a star
God bless you
And I love you children
That's a hell of a testimonial I see, Fred
Enterprise has explored the depths of the 23rd century for the Federation
Of the first last work ofina
Where there once you found You were never too far from home
I was only a little far from home
But I pull you over to thank you
And I hope that our world has a friend like you
To say hi to for the first time in my life
All right, that's the youngest member.
Channel 7's still the one.
I'm Snabley and Eklund.
I'm over-read Snabley and Eklund.
And we were at the Hall High School library today,
and we put lots of subgenius literature in all of the books.
All around, we have miniature Dobbs heads floating everywhere.
Miniature Dobbs heads everywhere you go, there's a miniature Dobbs head.
Begin by settling back comfortably.
Get as comfortable as you can.
Well, we're getting comfortable now.
Hey, I feel better already, Paul.
You know that we're here on Telegraph Avenue and the music's cool.
Oh, wow, I can feel it coming on.
Must be a whole trip here.
It's like being on acid ice.
Yeah.
Doing all right, brother.
This is the post office.
It's all yours, Terry.
We're going to park here very carefully and very quickly
so we can run across the street
and plaster Bob's little face all over the billboard.
We're back here at the studio
trying to clean up the mess after the explosion,
but we did get Bob all over two billboards
right by Tower Records,
and we did take an authenticating photograph,
which, if it comes out, I will send to you.
And you can see Bob spread out all over Berkeley.
And I was relating to you on the tape.
It may come up later anyway
that I've been putting Bob all over California.
You can see those stars so clearly.
It's not at all like on Earth.
Look at that cloudy planet go by.
Gee, this is really inspiring,
and I'm glad to be talking to you here from Star Deck One.
My lord.
Yes?
Yes, Elric?
A floating ship is about to crash into us.
Oh, pay no attention to it.
So done!
Yes, my lord.
These droids get so upset
when the least little thing goes wrong.
But anyway, it's a...
Wow, that is pretty awesome.
Look, it's...
Goddamn!
All systems prepare for full power.
Okay.
Give me Mach 1, 2.
3.
Charlie Baker, 749.
I think we maintained a hit there on starboard.
Put up full force phasers.
Call Bob!
Let's lock in these controls.
Move it out.
Okay, Bob.
Okay.
Let's go.
Bob.
Bob flies us.
Bob flies standing up.
That's incredible.
Look at this.
I'm not worried because I know...
Oh, the force field wasn't on.
There.
Now it's on.
It's okay.
Come back, you fools!
You cowards!
Come back, my lord!
Listen to him.
Come on, you'll be destroyed!
Let's go!
Well, Doug, we found Bob.
Do you want to say anything to Doug?
He's really appreciated, I think,
because he's really good.
Hi there, Doug.
I'm Bob.
I'm better than you've ever heard of.
Believe me, I am.
I'm a native.
Thank you.
I'm...
He isn't here.
Yes, he is.
Probably not for a few days.
No, right now.
Try Madison, Wisconsin...
No.
Try Dallas, Texas.
Victor Street.
Oh, Bob will kick their asses
and take their money.
Yeah.
you know I'm...
I think I found the bank.
And, uh, we bring the cardboard plating back along with us.
And I
Since he came
Through my life
I've quit
Selling wrenches
And I've got
The micro-encapsulated
Feeling
About things
Now to you
I'm trying to tell you
About dogs
Dogs
Who know
What's going on
This time
You know
Hmm
I've
Got to
Get some
Slack
In case
You couldn't tell
That's what
I lack
You know
Maybe
This subgenious
Stuff
That we've been
Getting involved
In
Is
You
Maybe
This isn't Bob
Bob are you in here?
No
Bob
Where's Bob?
Are you here Bob?
No I don't think
Bob's here
I can't find Bob
Anywhere
Can you hear me?
Oh Bob
Dr. Drummond
Can you hear me?
Is that a special room?
Oh the great
Stinky
Bob-o
Oh Bob
I need some money
I need some slack
Oh Bob
Bob I need some money
Give me food
Give me some money
Bob
Oh
Bob's my friend
Oh Bob
Thanks for being my friend Bob
Bob's my friend
And he's leading me somewhere
Where are we going Bob?
Is he waiting there for me?
He's not waiting anymore
Did he go up and go home?
Bob's my friend
And he's leading me somewhere
Bob went to vote
And he went
He'll be back shortly
Oh okay
In the white form
Bob left you a doughnut Bob
Bob went to vote
Bob can stop the aliens From killing me
Bob can save me
Bob can s Save Me
Don't count on it Bob
Get me Bobby Bow signe
You got the money
Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby
Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bob
Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby Bobby
Let's all go riding in the Bobmobile.
You don't need gas in the Bobmobile.
Oh, the wonderful, wonderful Bobmobile.
You don't need no gas.
You don't need no wind.
You don't need no money when you're in the Bobmobile.
When you're in the Bobmobile.
Hey.
Look.
Up over the car.
The back again.
Ah!
Oh, Bob.
Hey, Bob.
Re-Bob.
Oh, Bob.
Hey, Bob.
Re-Bob.
Bob-Bob.
Ray.
Oh.
Oh, I'm starting to get slack in my feet.
Oh, they're shuffling out from underneath me.
Oh, Bob-Bob.
Bob-Bob.
Bob-Bob, don't run.
Don't run away.
Bob, don't run away.
Here's my dollar.
Come on back.
I want you to stay and stay.
Oh, Bob.
Bob-Bob.
What's wrong?
What did I do?
You want 2 more dollars?
Okay, Bob, here's two more dollars.
Oh, wow.
Wow, I suddenly feel, I feel great.
I feel like I can see through all the women's clothing.
I can.
Look out the window.
Them girls are all naked.
It's Bob.
Right?
We can sit here and talk about, you know, it's here.
He's Bob.
That's why you need to send us money here at the Subgenius Church.
Because Bob, he can work miracles in your life.
He can bring you money, send us money.
He can bring you love.
And of course the molecular dispensation,
which comes from the...
Subgenius Church.
...the spewing diodes embalmed in our brain cells
through the Bob surgery and Dobbs tan,
which we've all gone through.
Kill Bob.
Braise the lard.
Shoot Bob.
I don't believe there is a Bob.
Sometimes we don't.
If there was, he wouldn't be so cool.
No way.
Dobbs, Dobbs atheists.
If there's not a Bob, then...
then...
Why are you here?
Why do you spread life if there's no Bob?
Pick a symbol, any symbol.
Bob.
I started.
Bobby.
Bobby Dodds?
I remember Bobby Dodds.
Bobbs.
Dobbs.
Bobby Dobbs when he was a boy.
Bobby Dodds.
Bobby Dobbs.
Little Bobby Dodds.
Where did he grow up?
Bobby Dodds.
Right here on the main street.
Why, I knew Bobby Dodds when he used to cut the grass
out in front of the drugstore,
and he had a part-time job in Vietnam
long before any of us even knew how to say the word.
Bobby Dodds.
Oh well.
That's just the way Bobby Dodds grew up.
Of course he grew up in a small town
in the Shenandoah Valley in Virginia.
Nobody knows that actually,
but it was Stanton, Virginia that Bobby Dodds grew up in,
Bobby Dodds.
father owned an antique store and sold half-burned uniforms and ancient rusty farm implements
as tourist attractions.
Hi, Daddy.
Here's Bobby now.
What's happening today?
There's Bobby Dog.
How'd he get so hit?
We have these ancient holograms of Bobby Dobbs, the way he was, asking how the things are
the way they is now.
What did you do in the war, Daddy?
Bobby Dobbs.
There was no answer, so he thought for himself.
Bobby Dobbs was looking for a droid, some kind of transformation.
I think I understand.
Yeah, sure.
Well, now maybe...
Bobby Dobbs figured it out for himself.
Bobby Dobbs.
Yeah, that's it.
No.
Well, well.
Bobby Dobbs.
Yeah, I sort of like that.
He didn't say I got it.
Hey, I know.
I got it.
No.
He got it.
No, he didn't get it.
That's it.
Yeah.
Bobby Dobbs is sitting around thinking.
Hmm.
Oh, but it's not bad.
Then they...
It must be...
It's not bad.
He decided his name was too long, he wanted to have some dignity to his character and
personality, so he named himself Bob.
He said...
We understand.
We know what's going on.
And he convinced people that he did.
And then a voice came to Bobby Dobbs one day.
Bobby, Bobby, Bobby.
He said, you really think you know what's going on?
Hey, Art, Art.
Oh, oh, oh.
He said.
Who is that?
What?
Hello?
Oh, oh.
Bobby Doll, what do you know?
Hey, it's dark in here.
I don't see anything.
I don't hear anything.
Oh.
Bobby Doll.
But I think.
I understand.
Bobby Doll.
He's getting enlightened right now.
I know what it's all about.
This is what his voice sounded like when he was really getting enlightened.
Here it's happening now.
It's the universe out there.
That's what it is.
Bobby Doll.
And here I am, sitting in the middle of it.
To you.
Yes, yes, folks.
He's really.
Bobby Doll.
To you.
Today, once again.
Bobby Doll.
Bobby Dark Skipper.
Bobby!
Oh, Bobby.
Bobby.
Bobby Dorian.
Oh.
Bobby.
Where were you during the war, Daddy?
It's time to wake up, Bob.
It's time to get up.
Bobby Dog, this is your wake-up service.
That's right.
Bobby Dog.
Are you asleep under there?
Hey, your hair's on fire.
Hey.
Hey, police are coming.
You better get up right now.
The cops are coming, man.
They're going to beat you up with brass knuckles and baseball bats.
Hey, your hair's on fire.
Friends, I want to talk to you today about something that I'm sure is close in everyone's hearts and minds
that you might not be living up to or be the man or lady, woman you should be.
And that subject, you might have guessed it by now, but that subject is Bob.
I want...
A man came to me.
He said,
My life is empty.
I said, why?
Why is...
Is it because...
It's not because my wife left me.
No, it's not because my car broke down.
It's not because I'm fixing to be evicted and fired from my job.
It's because I don't have Bob in my life.
And I talked to that man.
And I...
I saved that man that night.
I showed him the way of Bob.
Oh, Mr. Bob Dog.
Where are you in this dark?
Oh.
This dark world of humanity.
Oh, Bob.
Somewhere back here lies the answer to the secrets of the universe.
Somewhere in this slimy, sleazy hole that we call
the dark of the subgenius conclave meeting hall.
Oh.
This is the pink boys.
This is a battleground.
Oh, Bob.
Oh, who are you?
Oh, who are you on your organ, Bob?
And what a big organ you got.
But friends, I get up in the morning and there's just like this electricity that just shoots through me.
And I say, praise Bob.
And you can feel it, man.
You can feel that.
Was that him running around over there?
Did anyone want to see Bob?
I just want to say, praise Bob.
Don't you think he's the greatest?
Sturno.
Bob.
Praise Bob.
Sturno said, praise Bob.
I don't know if you hear.
But everything comes from Bob.
And it's just so beautiful.
I just want to turn everyone in the world on to Bob.
And I'm not sure, ma'am.
I don't know, ma'am.
I said...
I've seen your pretty pictures one time.
But you think Bob might give me those pretty pictures if I vaporize Smith and Jones?
I don't know, ma'am.
You write me by writing Pastor F.
Cheatness is a true vein of the subgenius?
Cheatness is, I'd say, what caused us to get started in this in the first place.
Well, I heard you talking about time control earlier.
How can I control time?
Are you going to...
Cheatness.
Listen to this, sir.
The lady sitting right there with your hand raised praising God.
Sister, stand up.
No, it's not here.
Look at me.
Do you live on a farm?
Come here.
Something wrong.
Seem like I see you on a farm.
Now, don't worry.
I mean, I always...
I feel my way through sometimes.
When God starts...
When it's a holy ghost, you don't have to worry about it.
Just relax, huh?
I'm not going to get tied up.
I'm not going to get...
Huh?
I know what I'm doing.
Praise God.
I may stumble around and feel around, but I'll come out all right.
I kept worrying a long time ago about the gift of the Spirit.
He just...
But I think...
Come a little closer, Doc.
Just a little closer.
I see something about a farm, Woody.
I'm on a farm.
You was what?
Raised on a farm.
But you don't live on one now?
Still something about a farm.
What's a farm?
Huh?
Because you look like a farmer to me.
What?
The name what?
What does it mean?
Farmer is your name.
What is your...
Wait a minute.
What is your name?
May Farmer.
Farmer.
Oh, hallelujah.
Oh, my God.
Hallelujah.
You're a knight.
Come on.
Hey, Farmer.
Oh, thank you, Jesus.
Jesus stole it.
You're a knight.
You know it.
I love you.
You know Jesus.
You know he knows you're a knight.
Like I say, I'll talk to Bob on the phone about your problems.
If you have any special needs, we can always supply you with anointing oils.
Yes, we have special anointing oils.
And we can...
You can...
Just for a few dollars more, friends.
Only a few dollars more.
Just a few dollars more to that miracle box number.
We can let you come to visit us at the special retreats at Dobbs Town and where you can get
glandscapes.
And Dr. Drummond and all his little friends from the special places will open up your
third nostril and make it where you can pick up on the strange liquid vibrations that are
all around us in the air.
I think I can get a whiff of them now, friends.
Yes.
I can tell.
Yeah, there's Pastor Naked.
No one knows what happened to him.
He just disappeared in a burst of smoke a little while ago.
But people didn't even get excited.
They didn't even jump up and down because they're so used to seeing it happen in front
of the tape recorders and all the microphones that we have here at the foundation.
Hallelujah for him.
Sanctify.
Oh, can you say anything about what Bob has done for you, my dear sister?
That's Bob.
Bob.
I can say...
Baby.
Oh, Bob's working miracles.
I can say...
Baby.
They call him Bob.
And I think I can try to...
I can pick up what your name is.
Yes.
You've never met me before, right?
And you've never been into this temple, right?
That's right.
And this is true, friends.
This woman has never met me, and she doesn't know any of my employees or any of the other
people at the foundation.
And I think I'm getting a picture.
I'm getting an image in my head.
I see it.
I see a farm.
Yes.
A little rooster on top of a house.
And what is it?
Wait.
The farm.
Are you a farmer?
Close.
Close?
What is your name?
Is your name Farm?
She said yes.
What is your name?
Farm.
You know what I mean, right?
What is your name?
Farm.
That's Becky Botts.
We can't steal that.
I think so.
But you know what I think we ought to do is just rent.
We ought to have our open.
We ought to open a damn lab, a subgenius analysis shop back here and do counseling.
You know, we can get a license to counsel in a subgenius fashion.
Can you do that?
Uh, I don't know.
Well, we can do hell, they do palm reading.
Here.
They do, you know, astrology readings.
We can come back here and do mental life trance readings.
Do them really spectacularly so it's worth people's ten dollars that we charge.
Yeah, even if they don't...
I mean, we flop around on the floor, we speak in tongues, the voice of their dead relatives
comes through.
This is Granny, I hope you did well.
It's beautiful here.
There's music and soft clothing and tight shoes and...
This is a place where all of us live together happy and freely.
I just spoke to Sigmund Freud about your problem and he says you can quit if you'll just try.
Oh, we got this, but only got this chance.
Checking you out, I'm gonna take a break.
Put me in a box, put a didn't in it for you.
Pink boy, never gonna grow up.
Pink boy, think I'm gonna throw up.
Pink boy, you can get the better back.
You can play the sound like the sound of the wind.
Oh boy, you are the man.
You're the man who knows all the answers.
So it seems at least that's what Doug and Follow keep telling us.
Well, maybe I could be...
If the screen is right here...
And I'm back...
Oh, this is Timothy Leary, reminding you that just as you need slack, Bob needs your help.
Send in those pledges and praise Bob.
And everything else is at subgenius.com.
subgenius.com because this is the hour of slack and it's the church of the subgenius and our new
official post office box well it's the old cleveland heights post office box uh the texas
austin office had to move so now we're at post office box 181-417 cleveland heights ohio 44118
www.subgenius.com
you