Nobody feels really bad around Bob unless you get bit by a
subgenius
power of
swag.
You'll finally get to see why they call me Bob.
What, you got something against a warm welcome?
No, no, just...
just has been a long time, that's all, and...
well, people change.
Have I changed?
Maybe.
What are you getting at, man? Are you...
The bobbing boy nearly floats away.
But bounces back like a man.
Mostly.
Keep it running!
Okay, Bob, we're ready for rollout.
Bobbing to the surface.
That's what I like to see!
You're saying that the reason that
you're not doing the job that I'm
paying you to do is...
Bobbing to the surface.
That you don't have a job to do?
No.
Is that what you're saying?
What are you trying to convince me of, exactly?
That you're as useless as an old snake right here?
Well, guess what, buddy.
I think...
you just convinced me.
Are we all...
in a continual cycle of birth and rebirth,
simply interchanging bodies as we go?
And if so,
this raises yet another question.
Do we get to choose?
I mean, who was I before I was who I am now,
and who will I be next?
Could I be you?
Now that is definitely weird.
Weird? For what?
Uh, not that weird.
Um...
Later, friends, there'll be new stuff,
but first, as promised last week,
we're about to hear part two of Reverend Exister's
collage extravaganza, Ship of State.
What a way to finish.
We're not finished.
Speak for yourself.
One day, one night, Kobayashi Maru.
Are you afraid of me?
I'm afraid of the future.
I believe that was a general idea that I was trying to convey.
I don't mean this future.
What is this? Multiple choice?
Some people are afraid...
of what might happen.
I was terrified.
Try not to be too hard on yourself.
We all felt exactly the same.
I want some fantasy.
I want to see in society's black underbelly
he can never pretend, like you do,
that it doesn't exist,
no matter who orders him to look the other way.
We don't do this...
thing,
because it's permitted.
We do it because we have to.
We do it because we're compelled.
The End
This is not just a fiction.
chemistry,
it's the Значит,
I think of you.
Nick said there were no hospitals.
You said it means there was nothing for you.
Please
I don't regret it much.
Know this,
people,
when you are afraid of reality,
we're scared to give you back
what that shows,
Man wants chaos. In fact, he's gotta have it.
Depression, strife, riots, murder, all this dread.
We're irresistibly drawn to that almost orgiastic state created out of death and destruction.
It's in all of us. We revel in it.
Sure, the media tries to put a sad face on these things, painting them up as great human tragedies.
But we all know the function of the media has never been to eliminate the evils of the world. No.
Their job is to persuade us to accept those evils and get used to living with them.
The powers that be want us to be passive observers.
You got a match?
And they haven't given us any other options outside the occasional, purely symbolic, participatory act of voting.
You want the puppet on the right or the puppet on the left?
I feel that the time has come to project my own inadequacies and dissatisfactions into the socio-political and scientific schemes.
Let my own lack of a voice be heard.
It wasn't really worth it.
The instinct of my purity worth the lifetime of your lies?
Please explain to me, where's the purity? You couldn't live without it.
You see, there is only one constant. One universal. It is the only real.
Cause. Causality. Action. Reaction. Cause. And effect.
Everything begins with choice.
No. Wrong.
Choice is an illusion.
Created between those with power and those without.
Look there. At that woman.
My God, just look at her.
Affecting everyone around her so obvious, so bourgeois, so normal.
What you see, I have sent you a dessert.
A very special dessert.
I wrote it myself.
It starts so simply.
Each line of the poem creating a new effect.
Just like...
Poetry.
First, a rush.
Heat.
A heart flutter.
She does not understand why.
Is it the why? No.
What is it then? What is the reason?
Soon it does not matter.
Soon the why and the reason are gone.
And all that matters is the feeling itself.
And this is the nature of human person.
We struggle against it. We fight to deny it.
But it is of course pretend. It is a lie.
Beneath our poised appearance.
The truth is we are complete.
We are complete.
Out of control.
Our politics is too delayed.
Things change.
Thank you.
It's worth a thousand prayers.
Don't cry, she might.
I don't think I'm any crazier than you are.
That's your shadow on the wall.
Can't get rid of your shadow, can you?
Any regrets.
I don't spend a lot of time with regret.
That's a waste of emotion.
Well, I wish that Indian hadn't got killed.
Man had a rattlesnake sitting in a corner.
Rattlesnake?
Could pick it up and pet it.
He saw it.
He saw what?
The demon. He saw the demon.
The demon?
What demon?
Everybody got the demon in here, okay?
The demon lives in here.
It feeds on your hate.
Cuts, kills, rapes.
It uses your weakness, your fear.
Only the vicious survive.
We all told we're no good piece of shit
from the time we could breathe.
God damn right.
After a while, you kind of become bad.
So tell me, how can you look at an ordinary person,
an innocent guy with kids,
and then shoot him to death?
I mean, how can you bring yourself to do that?
Innocent?
Who's innocent? You innocent?
I'm innocent. Yes, I am.
I've met it.
Definitely.
All God's creatures do it in some form or another.
I mean, you look in the forest.
We got species killing other species.
Our species killing all species, including the forest.
And we just call it industry, not murder.
But I know a lot of people who deserve to die.
Why do they deserve to die?
A lot of people walking around out there already dead.
Just need to be put out of their misery.
I don't know.
For the result, there is no escape from it.
We are forever slaves to it.
Our only hope, our only peace is to understand it.
To understand the why.
Why is what separates us from them.
You from me.
Why is the only real source of power.
Without it, you are powerless.
You know, the only thing that kills a demon...
Love.
It's just like...
Being in the garden of age.
Our only love could kill a demon.
How that thought.
We are the heart of death rattled on the world.
Do you think he'll live up to his name?
Or will it just be a death hairball?
Prepare to evacuate soul.
Parting is such sweet sorrow.
Have we not heard the chimes at midnight?
Goodbye cruel world.
I'm leaving you today.
Goodbye, goodbye, goodbye.
Goodbye all you people.
There's nothing you can say.
To make me change my mind.
Goodbye.
Painful living fear, isn't it?
Nothing is worse than having an itch you can never scratch.
Oh, I agree.
Wake up.
Time to die.
Die.
Why won't you die?
Beneath this mask there is more than flesh.
Beneath this mask there is an idea.
And ideas are bulletproof.
I shall die here.
Every inch of me shall perish.
Every inch.
But one. An inch.
It is small and it is fragile.
And it is the only thing in the world worth having.
We must never lose it or give it away.
We must never let them take it from us.
I hope that whoever you are
you escaped this place.
I hope that the world turns
and that things get better.
But what I hope most of all
is that you understand what I mean
when I tell you that even though I do not know you
and even though I may never meet you
laugh with you
cry with you
or kiss you
I love you.
With all my heart.
oh, wait a minute
you fucking hypocrite
you said the love beats the demons
you said that love beats the demons
and it will
it's just that you're the last one
I don't remember if I can kill me
this is not about you, you egomaniac
I kind of like you
but if we let you go
we would be just like everybody else
killing you
and what you represent is
a statement. You and me
You're not even the same species.
I used to be you, then I evolved.
From where you're standing, you're a man.
From where I'm standing, you're an ape.
You're not even an ape, you're a media person.
Media's like the weather, only it's man-made.
You're the one who made it impure.
You're buying and selling the fear.
You say, why?
I say, why bother?
I have some dignity.
All right, so I'm a parasite, so what?
Right, life is cruel, no one said it was gonna be easy.
The day you two killed your ass belonged to us!
To the public, to the media!
That's how it is, and we are married, eh?
Let's make a little music, Colorado.
In other news tonight, a bride and groom's
wedding reception turned into
a nightmare.
In chapter six, he begins to get into
the actual message of Revelation 6.
Now, I saw in the lamp opening,
He can sit in the sun, that's all I tell you.
Chapter five, now only the Lamb of Christ
is worthy to unseat a lamb.
He slapped me again, he...
I just wanted to say this, like this,
before I say it to the brides and grooms,
can we...
The people is all trying to lie to you,
and the Lord is gonna get wine for us.
What does this wine horse mean?
And he was set on it at a foe,
and a crown was given him,
and he went forth conquering and to conquer.
A wine horse?
Now let the Bible interpret the Bible.
.
Give me a nightmare broken,
and I'm never broke.
.
Life is lonely here,
there's no one left to torture.
.
Give me absolute control,
over every living soul.
.
That's an order.
Give me a crack, anal sex,
take the only tree that's left,
and stomp it up the hole.
.
In your culture.
Give me a back door burning wall.
.
Give me a start, and say,
Paul, I've seen the future, brother.
.
It is my turn.
Things gonna slide.
.
Slide in all directions.
Won't pay nothing.
.
Won't be nothing you can't measure.
The blizzard.
.
The blizzard of the world's crossed the threshold,
and it's overturned the order of the soul.
.
When they say.
Repent.
.
I wonder what they meant.
When they say.
.
Repent.
I wonder what they meant.
.
When they say.
Repent.
.
I wonder what they meant.
And, he said,
this shouldn't have happened but zusel Wiebeler said he wanted to go and please not be obstructed.
.
To say it clear, to say it cool, it's over, it ain't going any further.
And now the wheels of heaven stop, you feel the devil's riding crop, get ready for the future, it is murder.
And things are gonna slide, in all directions, won't be nothing, nothing you can measure anymore.
The blizzard, the blizzard of the world has crossed the threshold and it's overturned the order of the soul.
Wind it up.
When they said, repent, repent, repent, I wonder what they meant.
When they said, repent, repent, repent.
There'll be the breaking of the ancient western code
Your private life will suddenly explode
There'll be phantoms, there'll be fires on the road
And a white man dancing
You'll see a woman hanging upside down
Her features covered by her fallen gown
And all the lousy little poets come around
Trying to sound like Charlie Manson
Yeah, the white man dancing
Give me back the burning wall
Give me Stalin and St. Paul
Give me Christ or give me Hiroshima
Destroy another fetus now
We don't let children in our house
I've seen the future, baby
It is murder
Things are gonna slide
In all directions
Won't be nothing
Nothing you can measure anymore
The blizzard
The blizzard of the world has crossed the threshold
And it's overturned the order of the soul
When I say
They say
Repent
I wonder what they meant
When I say
They say
Repent
I wonder what they meant
When I say
They say
Repent
No wonder what they meant
I wonder what they meant
When that's said, repent, repent, repent.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Time, cut, cut, cut, cut, cut, cut, cut, cut.
That's a fucking joke, right?
I'm not going to ask that the recording devices be turned off.
And I'm not going to ask that all of you cover your ears for what I'm about to say.
But I'll ask your discretion in this tale of the decisions made by subgenius.
Cautionary tales of real subgeniuses.
I was born in Knoxville, Tennessee.
And in 1992, I moved to Portland, Oregon.
And on the way, I stopped.
I stopped at the houses of some people I'd been corresponding with.
Even emailing in a few cases.
One of them was Reverend Tom Dickinherry.
Who lived in a city that I will not disclose.
He and I had a good correspondence and he was a right funny guy.
And he said, yeah, you can stay at my place when you come through town.
Come on by anytime.
So I did.
And that's when I learned.
That he was a teenager in high school living with his parents.
So it was kind of staying at his parents' place.
Instead of staying at his place.
And that evening, Reverend Tom Dickinherry and his mom and I were sitting in their backyard.
And she said, you know, I'm kind of worried about this church of the subgenius.
Yes.
And I said, well, I'm not sure if it's a good place to stay.
It seems like there's a lot of drug use in it.
You don't say.
And I said, well, ma'am, that's just kind of part of the humor.
That is talked about.
And of course, some people do it.
Some find it cutting edge.
Not so much anymore.
I don't.
And it's certainly not required of anybody.
So I wouldn't worry about it.
And I think she felt a little better after that.
Well, some time passed.
And I hadn't heard from Reverend Tom Dickinherry in quite a while.
And I got a letter.
Because it was still the time when you wrote letters to people.
And here's what he'd been up to.
He was a straight-A student in that high school.
And the editor of the school newspaper.
So he had a key to the school.
And he could go in any time he wanted.
So he could finish up that late-breaking story before it went to press.
Well, because he had the...
Key to the school.
One morning he went in.
And stole all of the computer lab.
This was in the mid-90s when a computer lab was still kind of a big deal.
That's a lot of gear.
He stole all of it.
Took it home.
Every last scrap.
Took it home and hid it.
It made the local news.
Big cyber crime.
All these computers stolen.
And nobody had any idea.
But they knew computers were the future.
So they retooled the computer lab.
And he stole that too.
He stole all the computers twice.
Well, it wasn't hard to figure out at that point.
And he was called into the office and said...
The principal said,
Reverend Tom, Dick, and Harry,
we are, of course, not sure at all who's taken the computer lab twice.
Not sure.
But we think it's time you chose a new editor.
For the paper.
Give somebody else a chance.
And why don't you give us your key?
You understand?
Not sure.
Reverend Tom, Dick, and Harry.
Well, I do understand.
He did understand.
He returned that key.
And then went home.
Disassembled all the computers.
And scattered the parts all over the place.
Through some of the river.
Except one.
He kept one of them.
Because in the mid-90s, computers and laser printers were still kind of a magical thing.
And he had basic layout skills and a little bit of pirated software.
So he took that computer.
And he took a prescription pad that he had finangled from a doctor's office.
And he made out scripts for prescription pills.
More demkind pills than you've ever seen.
More demkind pills.
And he took it to one pharmacy.
And they gave it to him.
All he had to do was give him some money and this piece of paper that he generated.
Then he did it at another pharmacy.
And another and another.
And then he was doing the rounds every day.
One day, there was a knock on the door.
Knock, knock, knock.
Mrs. Tom, Dick, and Harry, is your son, Reverend Tom, Dick, and Harry at home?
Well, he sure is.
Son, could you come with us?
And so he did.
And Reverend Tom, Dick, and Harry was taken to the police station.
And shown the videotape of him entering.
And they told him that he had been to eight pharmacies the day before.
Eight.
Eight pharmacies.
And passing a forged prescription at each one.
And they told him, you're looking about 10, 20, 30 years each time you did that on just this day.
Plus all the other times you did that.
So we've got a choice for you to make, sir.
You can either go to trial and maybe not see the light of day again.
Or, because this is the first time you've been in trial.
And because you're a straight A student and the editor of the school newspaper.
You can just go to a mental hospital for six months.
I don't know where I'd be sitting.
He chose the latter.
Indeed.
So he went to the psychiatric hospital.
And it had been a while since I heard from him.
But I got a letter.
Hey man, guess where I am.
And he told me his tale that he had gone through.
He did his six months.
No alliteration.
No electric shock.
But forced drugging and counseling.
And then a little bit of after counseling after he got out.
He did his six months.
Got out.
And because he'd been a straight A student.
And editor of the school newspaper.
And a young guy.
The record was expunged.
Because he had just gone to a hospital and not to prison or trial.
Lucky.
So he got a full scholarship to Reed College in Portland, Oregon.
And that's a pretty prestigious school.
He had the full ride.
He went to Reed for a couple months.
And then decided that it was more important that he went to rave parties.
And distribute pills there.
So he dropped out of Reed.
And became a pill distributor.
And that was the last I heard of him for about 20 years.
I didn't even know he was still in Portland.
But.
I looked him up one day on the internet.
And sure enough there he was.
I found him.
Hey man.
Remember me?
Yeah I remember you.
I asked where are you?
I'm in Portland, Oregon.
Really?
You've been here for 20 years and haven't said hey?
Yep.
Well let me buy you dinner.
Okay.
So we go and have dinner.
He's looking about the same.
Life has been good to him.
He's looking fit.
Just a little taller than he was.
Otherwise same smile.
Same sparkle in his eye.
But he's receiving transmissions the whole time that we're talking.
He's having a dialogue with me.
And who knows what other unseen agencies are also delivering his ordinances.
And we talk and he's fine.
He says he's got a wife.
And the wife takes care of him.
Kind of like a house pet.
He can't hold a job.
Can't hold a thought.
But he's got the means to get by.
And towards the end of us having dinner he says,
Well I just want you to know that if we don't hang out again and if I never talk to you again,
it's nothing personal.
I just can't relate anymore.
Well okay then.
So he went off and did his thing.
And I've done my thing.
And I'm here now.
And he's wherever he is now.
And that is the first of an endless series of cautionary tales of the subgenius.
There you go.
My word.
A lesson learned perhaps by somebody apparently not necessarily Reverend Tom, Dick and Harry.
Seemed rather thick.
And yet he has his slack.
He's having his ex day tomorrow.
And who's to say.
Just like everybody else 7 a.m. we will sort you out.
Who's to say.
Well you said he was getting transmissions.
And he's getting transmissions.
I've been waiting quite some time to even have one.
And he's got them nonstop night and day.
All day long.
I had to hold that goofy machine like he had.
Get a heart attack again to have a transmission.
And it was vague and muddy.
Would you say it was worth it?
Contradictory.
Yeah sure.
Oh.
Yeah.
Was there much wisdom implied?
I'm fine.
I bounced back.
Sure is worth it.
I wouldn't change anything.
Wouldn't change a thing.
No.
Cautionary tales of the subgenius.
Wouldn't go back in time and change anything.
If I did go back in time I would be deposited somewhere in outer space.
Wherever the earth had left from.
Yes.
You would ruin the time stream.
The world is in motion at all times.
That was a real good hamburger I just ate while listening to that.
I mean your tale.
It was the first hamburger I've had since January I think.
And did you eat the heck out of it?
Or the darn out of it?
You know to tell the truth I didn't really eat the hell out of it because I was listening
to your story.
But I had about half of my bites were.
The darn.
At least a good heck of a bite.
I wasn't doing it with full absolute concentration.
I was multitasking.
Listening and eating.
Oh.
That's grand.
Yeah.
Why not both?
That's my motto.
Why not?
And I don't know if everyone knows that.
Do it every chance you get.
K-N-O-T.
That's how the not is spelled in why not both.
Wait a minute.
I didn't know that.
There you go.
It kind of adjudicates.
It doesn't have to be K-N-O-T.
It can be just N-O-T.
Why not both?
Mm-hmm.
Yep.
G-N-O-T.
Both.
That doesn't make any sense.
No.
Now here's another cautionary tale of the subgenus that has a difference ending.
The only thing I have to say right now is bring me a fork.
Please.
Will anyone step forward to bring this man such a simple request?
Just a fork.
Please be kind.
A fork.
Bring me a fork.
I have this plate of food in front of me that I'm staring at.
A fork has been given upon me.
That's fantastic.
I have the most blessed.
Unbelievable.
I have forked now.
He asked for a fork and there's a mad rush to the stage.
Now you have double forked.
Double forked.
I've been double forked.
He's been forked and double forked.
And forked again.
Grand outcomes.
Forked and forked and forked again.
There was a subgenus I knew and still know named Reverend Multivac Kleenex.
Multivac Kleenex you say?
Reverend Multivac Kleenex.
And I went to high school together.
And he's a good egg.
He hooked up with somebody who was not necessarily appreciative of his skill set and personality.
And he had a job that was not necessarily fulfilling in every possible way to him.
One day in 1998 he told his wife and he told his job, I'm going to X day.
I'm going to X day.
That's what he said.
And his wife said, oh no you're not.
And his job said, oh no you're not.
Oh no you're not.
But he's there.
In fact, if you watch the documentaries made by the filmmaker Reverend Evan Stang, you'll see Reverend Dr. Multivac Kleenex, Hodge, in those documentaries.
Because he did go to X day.
And he had a fine time.
And I was glad to see my friend there.
Well he got back.
He was in the office.
And his job said, heck no you don't have a job here anymore.
And his wife said, heck no you don't live here anymore.
He lost his job and he lost his wife because he went to X day.
It's not the only case of that happening.
But he got a double whammy.
But it didn't slow him down at all.
He found, instantly found a far, far better job.
What?
And instantly found a far, far better wife.
And now he's a happy man living at a weather station in Alaska.
What, what, what?
That's right.
He loves the nature there.
He loves his job.
He's paid well.
Takes pictures of moose outside his window.
And by that I mean he's inside taking a photo of a moose outside his window.
Outside his window.
So not all cautionary tales of the subgenius have an unhappy ending.
Waking up one morning and suddenly a moose is staring you in the face.
Hi Mr. Moose.
Some cautionary tales of the subgenius have a, can I even say it, a happy ending.
Now I hope that each of your cautionary tales has the ending that you deserve most.
It might not be the one that you're envisioning at the moment.
But it'll be the one that looks best on paper.
Looks best on your arrest record.
Looks best in your FBI file.
It looks best in the Stark Fist of Removal Issue Number 39.
Ask a silly question, you just might get the truth.
It's there between the ditches in the rough.
It's real hieroglyphics, I'm callous to the touch
You ask me if I'm happy, guess I'm happy enough
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
God is like the French, he understands English
But he doesn't like to speak it, lest he must
You ask him to repeat himself, he'll grind you into dust
Do you need to hear more? No, I think I've heard enough
You ask me if I'm happy, guess I'm happy enough
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
The objects in the mirror are closer than they seem
But they're backwards like Leonardo's hand
He wrote all of the answers down in disappearing ink
And I'm happy, yes I'm happy as a goddamn clam
I'm happy, oh I'm happy enough
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
There's music at the minimum
There's rhythm in the rails
I gotta think for sixteenth notes
Rat-a-tat, I was just about to crack it
But the code got tough
You ask me if I'm happy, guess I'm happy enough
Dot, dot, dot, dash, dash, dash, dot, dot, dot
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
We were doodlin' in the margins of the Domestique book
You could draw a dick but not a crowd
So we turned it up loud and we sang it real rough
Did it make you happy, made me happy enough
Oh, I guess it made me happy, made me happy enough
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
I was diggin' through my bottom drawer of uncut gems
Lookin' for a ruby in the rough
Hold my beer while I wrestle with the clown and get penned
Ask me if I'm happy, guess I'm happy enough
I guess, guess, guess, guess I'm happy enough
Hey, love is all around you if you know where to look
My life is overflowing with the stuff
You'll know it when you see it, it'll hit you like a book
Guess it made me happy, made me happy enough
Uh-uh, ask me if I'm happy, guess I'm happy enough
I'm happy, happy, happy, happy, happy enough
I'm hap-hap-hap-hap-hap-hap-hap-hap-happy enough
Ooh-ooh-oohkoo-ka-cha, ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh
Ka-cha-cha-cha, ooh-ooh-ooh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
B sesh cookie biscuits are the best
Thanks for the food
P Eagle Kitty
Flying même
groß
Boom!
Da!
A clan way home.
The great Bob Walkenhorst did that with a bunch of friends,
and I got that from his new Patreon project at bobwalkenhorst.com.
I don't want to take any money from his project,
so I won't be playing these new songs that I'll get every month for my small contribution.
But I played that one so that my fellow Rainmakers fans will know that there's now new Bob songs every month
at Walkenhorst, not Dobbs, although why not both?
And a person can subscribe to them.
Before that, we heard cautionary tales of the subgenius told at 21X Day Drill a couple of years ago
by Reverend Dr. Uncle Onan Canobite, with side commentary by Reverend Eggplant.
But now, the Crystal Methodists, all of them, disguised as Melba,
call into the popular Christian radio talk show of Bob Larson.
My son's family and I went to Disney World in Orlando two years ago.
Yeah?
And we didn't realize it, but the day that we went down there, I found out later they call it Gay Day.
Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
Encouraged the homosexuals.
You were there, Melba?
I was there on that day, and it was the worst experience of my life.
Can you tell me what you saw?
I mean, some of this you probably can't describe on a family show.
Well, that's true.
We saw several things that just were shocking.
But the worst part of it was, besides just, you know, it was like these people would kiss openly, you know, and embrace.
But if we gave them a funny look, they would say rude things to us.
So when they were kissing...
Yeah.
They're the ones doing the weird things.
Right.
But if you look at them funny, then they get mad at you.
Oh, yes. They were very hateful.
And the worst part of it was, I have a nephew who is a teenager.
He went off and rode the rides and things by himself all day long.
When we met him back there at the pavilion and we all got back together, he had a little friend with him, a boy a year or two older.
Yeah.
And this young boy that...
He said, I met a new friend here and this boy was very, you know, effeminate.
And he had like a pastel colored triangle button on his...
Well, that's the gay rights symbol.
Well...
How old was this child?
18.
So this other boy was gay.
At 18, he was already homosexual and proud of it.
We found that out later, Bob, see.
And the horrible thing was that we...
Apparently, his daddy works for the Disney company.
Oh, my goodness.
We felt like Disney people were sending their kids to try to recruit.
And Stephan has not been the same since.
We think...
Because they were on...
They kept riding the same ride over and over.
Is that...
Uh-oh.
It's a small world ride.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So that kid was after your son.
I mean, that gay boy was after your son.
I think so.
And ever since...
Now, Stephan doesn't see him, but I understand that they ride back and forth.
Uh-oh.
Because this boy lives in California.
And...
Melba, you got to put a stop to that somehow.
Oh, Stephan uses...
And I won't say anything nasty, you know.
But he keeps saying...
Referring to weird expressions like bonus eggs and felching.
And we don't know what he means.
Well, you don't want to know, and I don't want to tell you.
But I'll tell you what...
And that boy that he was with, I'm telling you, his voice was higher than yours is, Bob.
He was such a sissy.
Oh, it was horrible.
Yeah, and he had the little pink triangle on.
Yeah.
Okay, I'll tell you what, Melba, I want to do right now.
All right.
Your child has come under the influence of the evil spirits of seducing you.
And the seducing homosexuality that were surrounding this other young lad.
Yeah.
And I want to pray with you right now...
Oh, please do, Bob.
In the name of Jesus to break that hold.
Okay, Melba?
In the name of Jesus.
All right, now, Melba...
I believe it.
I want you to say...
I, Melba...
As the mother...
Of my child...
Child...
Have the authority...
Of my child...
According to the word of God...
Over my child.
God gives me authority.
And I also...
Have authority...
Over any demon in hell...
That tries to steal my child...
Lord!
Jesus. Lord Jesus. I raised my son right. I raised my son right. I raised him to be a man. I raised
him to be a man. Not a homosexual. Not a homosexual. And I'm not going to allow. I'm not going to allow.
The devil. The devil. To steal my son. To steal my son. In the name of Jesus. In the name of Jesus.
Spirits of perversion. Spirits of perversion. Take your hands. Take your hands. Off my son. Off my son.
Now. Go. You go. Go. You go. In the name of Jesus. In the name of Jesus. Set my son free. Set him free.
In Jesus' name. Oh, thank you, Jesus. In Jesus' name.
In Jesus' name.
You're getting a little blessed and happy there, Melba.
Melba?
Melba.
Thank you.
Thank you, Waldo, and all the rest of the gang in the Rudy Schwartz Project.
And now, forward into the recent past with Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
I thought, you know, after that argument with the policeman,
there was something else she had in her hair.
Hey, Dave, I've got a phone app that would make you so paranoid.
It should have been in Neighbor World,
your great science fiction book that's available from Subgenius Foundation
or Amazon.com, but it's better if it comes from Subgenius Foundation.
Yeah, there are some things that, although everything was predicted,
there are some things that are way in advance right now,
never mind 20, 30 years from now.
Well, I have this.
You know, I have these trails I've carved around the wilderness where I live.
And I'm serious.
And you have your drone.
Well, I pretty much droned it out.
But I made a map of my trails,
but it was using a GPS program that I could just set points
and then trace lines between the points.
And so.
So it wasn't really accurate map because it made it look like a series of straight lines.
But I thought, I wonder if there's got to be some kind of an app
that shows a satellite picture of where you are right at that moment.
And as you walk, it draws a line across the map as you walk.
And I was right.
There were at least two of them for iPhones that were free.
And I got one.
I got both.
I decided the colorful one was better.
And I've been mapping my trails with that thing.
But, of course, every time I do that,
it shows the conspiracy where all my secret escape routes are.
Because, you know, anytime you do anything online
or with data of any kind,
everybody knows about it if they want to.
And nobody wants to accept those Phoenix computers.
But, you know, they have the record.
If they ever want to.
Want to.
Prove that you walked down to that murder well at the bottom of the creek
to check on your stash of bodies down in there,
they can find that murder well themselves.
But, you know, most people nowadays, the youth of today,
they go, oh, that app doesn't go far enough.
It should be connected to your glasses so it takes a photograph every half second or so
so that the conspiracy can see what you're seeing
when you take your hike through the woods
and go visit your murder well
and fish out parts of waterlogged...
Human bodies, yeah.
Yeah, things.
But just to make art with, you know, not for any sick sexual purposes,
just to make art supplies.
That's why they're in there in the first place.
Yeah, to make people buggy.
Yeah, make art.
Well, you know, art...
You're bugging.
Bugging.
Yeah.
You and a bad cat, you got to bug out.
Said Fritz the cat.
Yep, 300 times.
It was drawn by Robert Crumb, not from the unfortunate movie they'd made of it.
I saw the unfortunate movie, too.
You did?
Yeah, it wasn't as sad as I thought it was going to be, but it was sad.
Right.
The saddest thing about it was Crumb didn't get paid hardly anything for that.
He wasn't going to let him make the movie.
He was going, no, no, you Hollywood guys will screw it up.
He was right about that.
But his wife at that time, it was his first wife, said,
okay, Robert, we're finished with the meeting now.
You can go away.
Say, Mr. Bakshi, she says to the animation producer guy,
my husband's an idiot.
Why don't you let...
I have power of attorney.
Let me sign that contract and give us that $200.
We need it.
So...
Yep.
That's how...
Famous in the underground for a while, but she done did.
She was, after a while, officially confirmed that she was not a nice person at all.
Oh, actually, I'm sure she was a real nice person.
It was just, you know, she was desperate and he was, you know, an impractical art bum.
I never met her.
I met his current wife, Aileen Kaminsky.
Their daughter, Sophie, was pestering...
Crumb.
She was like, come on, let's go.
This is so boring.
We're at a sci-fi convention.
Comics con.
Crumb was signing comics for a billion nerds.
And then Crumb finally got finished with all his autographing.
He looked up and he goes, you've got long hair.
I said, yeah.
I said, last time he saw me, I looked like him.
Nerdy with big black glasses and short hair.
Now I had long hair.
I was trying to get laid.
And he was like, why do you do that?
And I said, well, the girls...
Well, 30 years ago, you can ask Dr. Howell about this and verify my lack of intelligence.
But about 30 years ago, there were a breed of Crumb devotees that kind of wore those weird shoes and everything
and 40s looking floppy hats and lapels and stuff like that.
And they were artists.
And you can start your own little world.
There were also these guys that were like...
Argentine science fiction writers that had places, had houses that had nothing but old-fashioned ice boxes and stuff like, you know.
Well, the ironic thing is it worked for them.
They all got laid.
Crumb got laid more than anybody.
My long hair never got me laid.
Well, you were warned about...
I was warned.
I didn't, you know, I was, I thought...
That must be the explanation.
It's just a haircut.
That, that, I don't see what else.
It could be.
Princess Weasley's keeping her mouth shut.
Oh, well.
Each day I'll do
A golden deed
By helping those
Who are in need
My life on earth
Is but a spade
And so I'll do
The best I can
A life's evening sun
Life's evening sun
Is sinking low
A few more days
And I must go
To meet the deed
That I have done
Where there will be
No setting sun
To be a child
Of God each day
My light must shine
Along the way
I'll sing his praise
While ages roll
And strive to hear
Some troubled soul
Life's evening sun
Is sinking low
A few more days
And I must go
To meet the deed
That I have done
Where there will be
No setting sun
Life's evening sun
The Hee Haw Band once again.
Ah, yes.
Want to know where all this stuff comes from?
No?
Well, it's subgenius.com
And old lonesome cowboy Dave,
he was in a car wreck last week.
He's not injured.
Badly.
It turns out.
But it totaled his car.
And he's destitute.
You know what to do.
This is a church.
Subgenius.com
Radio page.
Big buttons.
Dave's name.
Praise Bob.
And friends,
the music in the background
through all of that
was from the album
Witch Disco
by Einstein's
Secret Orchestra.
And you can't get that CD anymore.
Um...
Boy, I miss old Chaz.
This album's刚NDYR Als guys oppa a little too
wide,  arrange theVEIL
Let's check what really hot
That track was a hot one forcolor
The Students are Blind
afk
retroto
Thank you.