I love you.
Genuine.
Beautiful.
Giant.
Perfect.
Cool.
Special.
Cheered.
Labyrinth.
Easy.
Ultimate.
Best.
Natural.
Growing.
Special.
Nice.
Proud.
Quicker.
And much more.
Ah, yes, dear friends, it is rerun time again, but you'll be glad to know that we're not
going to just do the same old three Christmas hour of slack show reruns in a row.
No, I'm going to compress it.
All into just this one intensive total rerun show.
Except that actually it's not.
The whole first half will be largely peppered with a new Christmas sickness for the holidays
and holy days and the hole in head days, as it is for some people.
Actually, I have to work double time because it's the season of selling.
Selling.
Yes.
Oh.
You wouldn't believe what the elves have done over at the subgenius catalogs.
But anyway, happy whatever you do.
Yes, this music in the background is somebody named Kenny Wayne Shepard.
Yeah, there's an album called Merry Axmas, a guitar axmas.
It's cool, man.
Cool.
And.
Praise Bob and who.
The whole, uh.
Oh.
And left me stranded on this Christmas tree
Yeah
Will you stop it?
Woo!
When this angel heard
Chop-a-pa-pop, chop-a-pa-pop
A dreadful fear went right into my heart
Those pine-tree needles sting me
Ram-ba-jam-ba, ram-ba-jam-ba, ram-ba-ding-dong
You'll never know how much that smarts
So who put the stomp in my romp-a-bomp-a-bomp
Who took and jammed it in my ram-a-lam-a-ding-dong
Who stood the wood where I poopsie-poopsie-poop
Who put the stick up my hip-ty-dip-ty-dip
Who took that bush and crammed it in my tush
He made this angel beg for mercy, please
I might squeeze
Slip of this
Too tight
It's that psychedelic time of the year
Do you know where your brain cells are?
It's already 9 p.m.
Don't go looking out in the backyard to dog-aid them
Don't go walking down to the bar
Cause old Frankie died last night in the backyard
I mean, I'm gonna park my store and look at the credits
Oh, can I borrow the brain cells tonight?
Yeah, he brought back the chainsaw
Yeah, and I ain't gonna let you use the brain cells
Till I get the damn chainsaw fixed and back in my arm the way it was Tuesday
Now you boys be good and I'll give you some of this here
Apple mango pie
Ain't no good of a child
That dog's running off with them brain cells
Can you do something about that, boy?
I'm gonna have to, I'm gonna have to
I'm gonna have to
It could be his head wasn't screwed on just right
Ah
Merry Christmas!
What we as manufacturers sell you is fun
The faith of a child
Spend all the money you got
The Christmas trough
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, look, Dave's dressed like Santa Claus.
Oh, he's like a cowboy Santa.
How jolly.
Oh, Jazz is giving, gives Dave the show pill.
Boy, I really need one of those.
What am I going to do about laundromat in this suit, though?
I need the show bath.
The show de-lousing.
Oh, Dave doesn't even have headphones.
That's enough of that.
Oh, he's got headphones.
I also have the part of my pancreas that I'd like to show you now.
It's been increased in size to...
Oh, your pancreas looks lovely, Dave.
Look, it's swelling.
I actually have the capability of a man of 190 IQ's brain.
I'll put more pills out for everybody.
Oh, those pills.
They make my mouth feel like it's on fire.
And my brain feel like it's a puddle of liquefied...
I'm shocked by the...
I'm sorry.
The red pills are really good.
I like to take the red one and the blue one.
Yes, the red one and the blue one.
At the same time.
That way you go in and out.
The warp mix is easy.
It's so high, you can't go over it.
Angels we have heard on high
Singing about mountains high
And those mountains in reply
Sing about mountains high
Lord, there are mountains far away
And that we wish we had something to
iksi
Lobby
The Need for vlog
Network
Wi-Fi
Music
chunk
PLEASE
Barbie dogs.
Women rape and memorialize their lives by role-playing with bars.
We have devised a marketing scheme for children's toys.
It will empower us to resist them.
You will use your church as a vehicle to bring these toys before the public.
It will be a bomb for kids.
But how will the battle of good against evil be represented in your marketing schemes, human?
Good has lots of muscles.
Good.
Good!
The primitive Earth societies should accept this value judgment.
Good will have great physical attributes according to human desires.
Sexual.
Desires.
Latent in children.
Brought out.
Through the vehicle of this so-called farmer cult exploits at church.
Batteries not included.
She's new.
From Kenner.
Where illusion is the ultimate weapon.
We must buy our toys.
Yes.
The old subgenius toy marketing scheme.
Recorded there at Dockstock 1984.
Mean Palmer VDs.
Angels we have heard on high.
It was by the Philistines.
The collage called All the Money You've Got is from the great Obtuse Christmas collage album.
Which you can get for free.
Get this.
Check out this website.
Obtuse.
I-U-M-A.
Dot.
Com.
That's Obtuse.
Excuse me.
Ah, yes.
And next up.
The real story of Christmas by Michael Shelley.
Once upon a time, there was the baby Jesus.
And he had two eyes made out of coal.
And he was stuck up a partridge in a pear tree.
And he wanted his two front teeth.
And he got McDonald's gift certificates.
And he had a dog named Santa's little helper.
And he took all the presents from Whoville.
And his friend Yukon Cornelius came with the three wise guys.
And he wanted to play the drums and be the little drummer boy.
But he couldn't.
He wanted tens and twenties.
Tens and twenties.
And he wanted to play the drums.
And he got McDonald's gift certificates.
And he got Zuzu's pedals.
And that's the real story of Christmas.
Take the holes in the miles of holly.
Tears of the season to be jolly.
Don't we know I'll get a barrel
Roll the engine, you tight-chest
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la
Well, Tommy knew exactly what he wanted for Christmas.
He wanted an electric train.
He had the whole thing in his mind, even to the table where he was going to set it up.
He could picture the whole thing, and he would dream so hard
that the whole thing would come true.
It would come to life right before his eyes.
Of course, Tommy was a pretty strong wisher.
And what he started wishing for was a pretty fancy-looking train set
with locomotives and freight cars.
And a station.
And the caveman.
The water tower.
And all the kinds of wonderful equipment and accessories.
So rad that you might think Tommy was waiting for something that just didn't exist.
The End
sujetu
A
Gigant sentiments
haha
he
éch
kr
some assembly required batteries not included this toy multiple party three days
he bob and the bastards of the universe will be back after this message
it is it is turnover the time of the year when all things sell the end of the year
sale so so come and get it everyone and just buy our products yeah are we is Chris I'm a
little confused about what Christmas is all about are we celebrating the birth of Santa
Claus or his death when they nailed him well that that's the ancient agents of
GD but the presence of Jeannie try to make sure that we have our inventories cleared
by now and we'll sell everything to the pigs yes once a pagan holiday and now a shopping
day
season and it was something else in between there but but before it was after it was a pagan holiday
and before it was a shopping season it was something else but I think they started a war over
foreign
I don't like some color, I don't see the world at all
Yeah, I'm so much good, I'm not nice at all
Oh, oh, glory, oh, oh, Santa had extra sense
Oh, oh, glory, oh, Santa had extra sense
Santa's nose driven by strange forces to complete his nameless errand
And he may show up at your house, my friend
If you've been a bad subgenius or a halfway subgenius
Or if we keep getting tangled up in these other shows
And having strange microphones
How did that paternity suit ever turn out between Dobbs and Santa?
And who?
His dad
Santa Dog
I don't know
And I don't think it was a simple result
Yes, but Saint Nicholas, this is fact
Saint Nicholas punched another bishop in the nose and bloodied his nose
And sucked him
Really? The historical Saint Nicholas?
Over the Trinity of God
The original Saint Nicholas in Turkey?
I swear upon Bob and the Holy Spirit
Who the hell is God?
The Holy Spirit is from our part of the country
I can tell you shit, God
Who the hell is God?
God!
Ask Dobbs one day
That's the question we should be asking more
Suddenly, a lightning bolt struck from nowhere on that bright sunny day
Bob did a backflip and from that day on, he too was a believer
And from the snowdrift and snow
A little child bearing flowers emerged
And Chip, Chip, what else was on the table?
Each one a dirty flower
Saint Nicholas
Sip, sicken
The historical Santa Claus is, uh...
Originally lived, as the caller knows, as a bishop in, uh...
Was it, was it Constantinople?
Yeah, like one of those...
It was in ancient Byzantium
Asia Minor in general, yeah
Yes, he was, and he was, uh...
He was known for...
Sneaking into the rooms of young women and leaving...
Gifts
Light-sized lumps of coal
Complete with a fake beard and a CIA wallet
And a Wall Street credit card
A saint he was, the girl said
Saint Nicholas invented the CIA
That's good, that's...
You got it, brother
He snuck into people's houses through the chimney
They knew when they were sleeping
They knew when...
He knew when they were awake
That...
You got it, brother
But like the CIA, he was...
That's Foucault, baby
He was protecting them
Foucault knew that Saint Nick was a creepin', stinkin' spy
What?
He knows when you've been sleeping
He knows what you've been eating
Hey, man, my kids still believe in Saint Nicholas
And who cares?
He keeps that belief alive in their fevered, sick little brain
Madison Avenue, of course
No, the surveillance community
And Disney
Under your direction
And the Reynolds Tobacco Company
Miller Bear, you know
He's a very powerful being
If you're bad, he punishes you
If you're good, he rewards you
He's probably the closest thing to Jesus
Walking the earth
He's the closest thing to Big Brother there is
He rewards those who knows when they are smiling
When they're awake
I think, I think really if you want to make a deal
You have to do it with, you know
Could Dr....
Could Dr. Claus in fact be the wandering, quote, milkman
Rumored to have fathered our savior, J.R. Bob Dobbs?
Well, we find it a very likely possibility
From the falsified documents we have here
And also the fluffy beard that often grew on Bob's feet
You better watch out
You better not
You better not tell them
Tell them you watch
What are you doing there
Theorist
Spect clinician
Men who live in deux
Make of the following
James Bond
The Doctor
Joaquin C.
What are you doing there
Theậy
Got this
Now this coming, take care.
Here is the thing.
He knows when you're away.
He knows when you're in bad or good.
Don't be goodness, goodness sake.
Oh, you better watch out.
You better not cry.
You better not care.
And I'm telling you what Santa Claus is telling you to tell.
Do you think I'm psycho, Mama?
I've seen my ex last night.
Oh, I'm sorry.
We all saw X-Mas last night.
A vision of Christmas that was dancing in Stank's head.
It would not leave for the little sugar plums and berries dropping.
Touch.
Ex-exclusion.
All those little sugar plums.
All those sweet and that plums.
The poison in the plums.
Material plums.
Biological agents who only take 15%?
It came with our plastic boxes of bags.
And one thing showed up hurt little baby.
Wait.
And a second time.
Everything there was right.
With a half guitar in there mucha terror.
Bless stock.
Aem.
Admit you.
Great doggie.
All things care about you.
Oh, it's a great day, all right.
A salute to Mr. and Mrs. American.
Shop as usual.
And avoid panic buying.
It's two days old Christmas.
There's a million things to do.
Clean the house, put on tea, company is due.
Where are my relatives?
Why haven't they showed up?
I bet they're at the airport.
I forgot to pick them up.
Christmas, it's almost here.
Sometimes I think all that Santa crap's just bull.
Santa Claus is real.
You can hear the calls,
You can hear the claws,
Santa Claus.
Who's the head man?
He was a huge, beastly,
bulging man.
He was so real, how come we didn't get squat last year?
Yes, the birth of the baby Satan.
On July 4th.
And now you can have it all pure 100%.
Vinyl Chloride CID.
The birth of our baby Satan
as told by various authors
and eclectic scholars
from around the globular unit.
Including that announcer.
This announcement has not been a perfunctory
announcement, but an announcement
of the blessed anointing and birthday
of our Lord
Ziz
Z denn if you feel,
This is
which people
will
ancest hypertension
This is
Ziz
an
anti-an sailor
Hi savings
z ground
no
i
not
going
in
Let your side be light
From the water
Troubles will be out of sight
Have yourself a merry little song
From now on
We're miles away
Once again as in olden
Happy golden
Be miles away
Let your heart
Be out of sight
Out of sight
Have yourself a merry little Christmas
By No-L
No-L
Before that, some year old ESO
and Michael Shelley
did that real story of Christmas
from the Tarkin
Tarkin Records All-Star Holiday Extravaganza.
I'm playing a lot from that.
So check out www.triage.com for that one also.
The Tarkin Records is also on www.triage.com.
And now, the Jethro's.
The Tarkin Records
And amazing.
More from Corporal Blossom.
I am really,
really impressed
by their editing work.
And that's on
Corporal Blossom
and the Mutated Christmas
is on the Illegal Art label.
That's www.detritus.net
slash illegal art.
www.detritus.net
And now,
more Jethro's.
Huh.
Hi.
Now you're blaming Jesus.
You're blaming our Lord.
I sort of understand because...
I understood the way any old fool would understand.
There was no Jesus.
No flatulent old woman waving her panties on the hill.
It's not that you don't want to.
It's that they won't let you.
No, they're ashamed.
Just a crime of wilderness.
They're ashamed.
And the hot pursuit of wolves everywhere in the background.
I'm ashamed of them.
It's cold.
I'm leaving that city life behind and radio people crazy.
I can't get my noodle back in the pan, Jan.
Come on, cowboy.
No, man.
I was trying.
I was trying to get against this here tree, and it started whispering to me, man.
Oh, you've been drinking.
There's the face of Madonna right up there.
There's the face of Virgin Mary.
I swear to God, look at it.
Isn't it?
What?
It's your Christmas witch coming true.
Wow.
A Christmas witch?
I'll be whole.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, I guess it does look a little bit more witchy than angelic.
I know she must be a true witch.
I guess you could call her that if that's what she's packing out of you for real.
She's running by hovering Christmas ornaments.
Looks like a radar device.
What?
Yo.
Yo?
It's her.
What up?
Nothing.
What's up?
What a deep voice.
First Christmas.
Witch.
Thank you.
Bye.
I am yours truly, Rudy Ray Moore, bold and still beautiful.
Baby, I want to talk to you for this Christmas because Christmas holds a lot of memories for me.
Baby, I've had a lot of hard times at Christmas time.
I can remember me and my brother when I was about six years old.
We hung our stockings up over the mantelpiece and the health department made us take them down.
I remember my father well, you know.
My father used to wake up every morning with a headache.
He used to have, you know what caused it, Ben?
He used to put a stocking cap on his head and put a knot right in front of it.
Daddy wake up with that stomping headache.
And he said, the kids are saying, my head's hurting so bad.
I said, I don't know what Santa's going to get y'all for Christmas, but he's going to bring you something.
So Daddy took that old rifle and went outside and shot up in the air and come back inside
and told us.
Biggest lie ever heard.
Said, kid, Santa just committed suicide.
And whose birth do we celebrate with this new century?
They even come to questioning now.
Who was nailed on that great manger cradle but Satan Claus?
Oh my God, dang, come on.
Whose father, Paul Bunyan, and whose mother, Big Sister, created the conspiracy?
Did they have Christmas before there were malls?
Before there were malls, there was no such thing as Christmas?
Yes.
There were pilgrims for baby.
There was a down-home Norman Rockwell style, it's a wonderful life type of Christmas.
It was a kite-flying Coca-Cola drinking Christmas, not a crack-smoking, rubber-snapping Christmas.
It was a...
When your little brother broke through the hole, it fell through a hole in the ice, and you went and saved him.
You didn't...
You didn't laugh at him and huff some more glue.
It was a wonderful life back then.
And we pulled some eggs, little jokes about him waking up, and then we'd put candles.
Like most people have.
He would have that smile on his face and a big red nose.
But today, Christmas is lost, it's me.
He just beat the crap out of Santa Claus.
Scott, you made your choice.
When you rejected my word, you rejected me.
I did.
To your eternal soul.
You have found that I only could you afford to give to God that which was his,
but you could not afford to do otherwise.
The Senate still stands.
And throughout are darkness, where there is wailing and gnashing of teeth.
Sir, please give me just one more chance, sir.
I don't want to go to hell, sir!
Sir, no!
No!
I don't want to go to hell!
The tailbearer will be at the judgment.
To be continued...
To be extended...
I got you.
Thin rye.
Jesus.
Elrond.
I got a Jesus like no other Jesus you've ever seen.
Oh, it tastes like butter.
A new Jesus.
A different Jesus.
It tastes like crappy pie, children.
A pipe-smoking Jesus.
Dave, you know where it is.
Go kick that window open.
I already kicked it.
I'll kick it again, though.
Kick it good this time.
We don't mean nothing by this Jesus and God.
We thank you for all the nice things that you've done for us this Thanksgiving.
We appreciate all that.
We're just trying to insult your fan club.
That's all.
That's why we do this blasphemous stuff.
But we knew that you knew that because you're in all things and everything, right, Jesus?
Right.
I could hear him say that.
Praise God and Bob and Jesus.
Next topic.
Terry.
The devil and the atheists.
Could you see Jesus as a terrorist?
And science.
That's the life of Brian, isn't it?
And Greek mythology and Norse mythology.
Listen to the sounds of hell.
Jingle, jangle, jingle, we're on a sleigh ride to heck.
Santa and his reindeer are really wicked.
Wrapped in wrapping paper.
We're gonna break.
Break our necks.
Got a rocket in my pocket on a sleigh ride to heck.
Sleigh ride to heck.
The elves are full of cheer.
The kids are tucked in bed.
What?
Santa ain't coming.
We're on a sleigh ride to heck.
Their dreams are filled with toys.
But they're out of luck.
Cause Satan's taking Santa on a sleigh ride to fuck.
Sleigh ride to heck.
The greatest scary Christmas song ever, friends, from his new album, Don't Trust Whitey,
James Kochalka, Superstar.
You know, see, a subgenius has so much faith that he not only can accept somebody making fun of Bob,
but he can also accept somebody stomping on a picture.
He'll do it himself.
He has so much trust and faith in Bob.
Bob is such a good friend that he can insult Bob.
Now, we subgeni, I hate to get on my soapbox in the middle of a bunch of entertaining tapes,
but we subgeni may be bad, but our way of bad is holy.
It's holy compared to the evil of so many, not all, by any means,
but so many American fundamentalists, charismatics, evangelicals, etc., in general, of course.
They and their corresponding.
They and their corresponding types in Iran, Russia, Libya, South Africa, etc.,
if you ask me, are actually the ace up the devil's sleeve.
Wolves in sheep's clothing, friends, just like Jesus warned about.
Jesus and Bob, like we say, are old drinking buddies.
Got nothing against Jesus.
It's just his fan club.
And now, we aren't saying that Bob is the ace up God's sleeve.
He's more like the smear on God's handkerchief, just like you or me.
But the...
Uptight rival cults.
They don't think God has a handkerchief.
Uh-uh, no.
Because God's perfect.
He doesn't even sneeze.
We're made in his image, except that we have all these nasty parts attached to us,
and we have to go in the secret room, the bathroom, to do awful things.
But God, oh, he's clean and pure, according to them.
Oh, and he's male.
But he doesn't excrete juices and sweat and smelly stuff out of him like we do.
Because we sin.
Oh, yeah.
We all sin.
We're bad.
We're worthless.
We're no good to God, unless we sign a contract with his agent.
We interrupt this program for a special promotional announcement.
We turn.
Bob and the bastards of the universe will be back after this message.
Thank you.
All your
thoughts
and
minds.
By Fernando Nande
Limor.
Oh, holy night
whose stars are brightly
shining.
It is the night of our
new, new, new birth.
Long lay, long lay the world in different pining
The pin and the stone mountains quenched
A thrill of hope the weary world rejoices
Beyond the grave a new and glorious dawn
Fall on your knees
Oh hear the angel voices
Oh night divine
Oh night when Christ was born
Oh night, oh night divine
Have yourselves a groovy little solstice
Mithras won his fight
Oh night
Oh ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho
Come one, come all
It's He-Bob, hey kids, you can help the mighty Satinus Rice overthrow the evil normals
With new Bob-Dots, actually bigger with rocket fire
What I wouldn't do from Bob-Dots
Get new more chocolatey pebbles from you, no?
Buy my chocolate, Space Cadet
Life support system down to zero cocoa
Feeling spacey
Have some of my new cocoa pebbles
Now so chocolatey
Mmm, smells cocoa-less
This cocoa-less
Blow
Roll of friends
What do you think?
Is it the nativity of Santa Claus
That we're trying to celebrate here
Or is it the horrible death of the Santa Bob
The Santai Bob
As he's been referred to
In some early pre-scriptures
Even wrapped in a tie
Yet what of those
Nemesis dolls
Are they relevant
Is it theasing
Or are you an
Imposter
You have lots to check out
In the new Mithras
You are the amending
Of the best
Let us know where一
wee
The Jethro's, friends, you need to know where to write to the Jethro's.
They're at, they did that Wreck the Halls and so many other versions we've been playing.
The Jethro's are at 212 and a half Miller Avenue.
That's 212 and a half Miller Avenue, Portsmouth, New Hampshire.
Portsmouth, N-H-O-3-8-O-1.
Santa Claus is Coming to Town was by Corporal Blossom.
Information on that Mutant Christmas is available from www.triagemusic.com
or www.detritus.net slash illegalart.
.
I'm Reverend Ivan Stang, friends.
You can reach me, send me tapes or whatnot at Post Office Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
And friends, as always, the hour of slack is brought to you by the Church of the Subgenius.
www.subgenius.com
It's all Christmassy right now.
There's a bright green bob in the window and Christmassy lights.
Is DJA out there?
And devilish artwork that's Christmassy.
No, that's something just left for DJA.
It's all Christmassy.
It's all wrapped up in a perfumed ribbon-wrapped present under the tree.
Smell that cinnamon.
Open the door all the way so we can see if he comes in.
And those sugar plums.
Something's up the chimney hole in sight and it's his name.
Yeah.
Of Santa, I mean.
Otherwise, gosh.
I guess we have to wait till Santa comes, Dave.
Oh, beloved Santa.
I have wanted to put your bag down for a minute.
He's always so ready to let him be dressed back for so long.
Pray Bob and Mary Xmas!
Don't I just sat down all next to him and started playing awhile full otherwise?
Well,ーノ
That's cool.
Okay, stay in your room.
VolcanWhiteIIisisutalk didntwhat???
Merry fucking Christmas
Merry fucking Christmas.
Jingle bells, jingle bells, jingle bells, jingle bells, jingle bells.
Don't despair, just because it's Christmas.
The children there are so gay at Christmas
All the children on the street
Hope they get something good to eat
But for me it's not so great
Fuck Christmas