You're not going to sedate me anymore.
Who are you?
The Self Genius Power of Swag.
I seem to be in a timeless space void.
Neither light nor dark.
I have awareness but not mind but no memory.
That should hold her till you get her home.
Gentlemen, thank you all for coming.
I know you have parishes, flocks and temples making enormous demands on your time.
But I'm sure you appreciate also the great masses of humanity look to pictures for information and uplift and yes, entertainment.
Here at Capital Pictures, as you know, an army of technicians and actors and top-notch artistic people are working hard to bring to the screen the story of the Christ.
It's a swell story.
A story told before, yes.
But we like to flatter ourselves that it's never been told with this kind of distinction and panache.
Perhaps, sir, you forget it's telling in the Holy Bible.
Quite right, Patriarch.
The Bible, of course, is terrific.
But for millions of people, pictures will be their reference point for the story.
The story is embodied.
The story is, uh...
Realization.
You realize, of course, that for we Jews, any visual depiction of the Godhead...
...is most strictly prohibited.
Oh.
But, of course, for us, the man Jesus Nazarene is not God.
Aha!
Who plays Christ?
A kid we're all very excited about.
Todd Hawkeye is a wonderful young actor we found in Akron, Ohio, in a nationwide talent hunt.
But Hawkeye is seen only fleetingly and with extreme taste.
Our story is told through the eyes of a Roman tribute.
Atollicus Antoninus.
Ordinary man.
Skeptical at first.
But who comes to a grudge...
...and a grudging respect for this swell figure from the East.
And Atollicus is played by...
...Baird Whitlock.
Oh, my.
Well, he is certainly a great talent.
Now, Hail Caesar is a prestige picture.
Our biggest release of the year.
And we're devoting huge resources to its production in order to make it first class in every respect.
Gentlemen, given its enormous expense, we don't want to send it to market...
...except in the certainty that it will not offend any reasonable American, regardless of faith or creed.
Now, that's where you come in.
You've read the script.
I want to know if the theological elements of the story are up to snuff.
I thought the chariot scene was fakey.
How is he going to jump from one chariot to the other going full speed?
Uh-huh. Well, we can look at that.
But as for the religious aspect, does the depiction of Christ Jesus cut the mustard?
Well, the nature of Christ is not quite as simple as your photo play would have it.
How so, Father?
It's not the case.
It's simply that Christ is God, or God Christ.
You could say that again. The Nazarene was not God.
He was not God.
He was a man.
Part God.
No, sir.
Rabbi, all of us have a little bit of God in us, don't we?
Well, it's the foundation of our belief that Christ is most properly referred to as the Son of God.
It's the Son of God who takes the sins of the world upon himself...
...so that the rest of God's children, we imperfect beings, through faith...
...may enter the kingdom of heaven.
So God is split?
Yes. And no.
There is unity in division.
And division in unity.
I'm not sure I follow, Padre.
Young man, you don't follow for a very simple reason.
These men are screwballs.
God has children.
What? And a dog? A collie, maybe?
God doesn't have children. He's a bachelor. And very angry.
No, no. He used to be angry.
Why? He got over it?
You worship the God of another age.
Who has no love.
Not true. He likes Jews.
God loves everyone.
God is love.
God is.
Who is?
This is special. Who isn't? Who is?
But how should God be rendered in a motion picture?
God isn't in the motion picture.
Then who is taught archives?
Gentlemen, maybe we're biting off more than we can chew.
We don't need to agree on the nature of the deity here.
If we could focus on the Christ, whatever his parentage...
My question is, is our depiction fair?
I have seen worse.
Reverend?
There's nothing to offend a reasonable man.
Father?
Well, the motion picture teleplay was respectful and exhibited tastefulness and class.
Who made you an expert all of a sudden?
And what do you think, Rabbi?
Eh. I have been an opinion.
Well, I certainly do.
The Bible says that every man was born in mortal sin.
Or no sin.
Each one of us must answer when our judgment day begins.
Judgment day.
Make sure your path is righteous when Saint Peter picks your side.
C יש עeka Night of the 11 tags.
The pearly gates will open if your scrotum you don't hide.
Don't you hack it, drop your crusty britches, flop that scrotum down
Don't you raise your zip-wood chains till Satan comes around
Watch out for that rich man, he's coming down the aisle
So, hop-hop that bulbous scrotum and make Jesus smile
The Lord, he gave us lubricants to squirt in every hole
The devil gives us painted beef so he can steal our soul
Beware of men who whisper when they leave you only crud
Even you, there shall not be delivered unless you softly hum
And drop, drop your nasty britches, flop your scrotum down
Flap that scrotum down, and when a pagoda comes to town
Stand up for America, make your life worthwhile
And, uh, hop that bulbous scrotum, you'll make Jesus smile
The world is full of wicked men who want to prey on you
A bifurcated penis shaft will help to see you through
Try not to wiggle on the slab until the blade withdraws
Don't worry about the bleeding cause we saved our grandpa's jaws
Drop, drop your stanky britches, flop that scrotum down
Choose the path of communism, each man his own way, and you'll see the world fall apart
And that's a king, old cow, and sausages with throbbing veins
Or better, by a mile, you just pop, pop that bulbous scrotum
And make Jesus smile
And you just pop, pop that bulbous scrotum, you'll make Jesus smile
Thank you, Jesus, pop that bulbous scrotum
The piccolo player is a motherfucker
And make Jesus smile
The Hispanic in me is released
And that's leave them without me
And make Jesus smile
The cosmopolitan is that horny
The scum of Christ
The chanting of the
lapd
to see. And I'm not blaming. I'm proud of my heritage. We're all proud of our
heritage. I don't want to build a wall.
I want to build a wall. I mean I can, I don't think it's very confusing. It has
nothing to do with anything except common sense. We go to the judge, we say
to the judge, hey you can't let her out of the case. How do you allow a case to
proceed when the plaintiff asks to be dismissed from the case? The plaintiff in
the case was a woman. The plaintiff in the case was a woman. We go to the judge,
we say to the judge, hey you can't let her out of the case. The plaintiff in the case
was a woman.
And you're left to conclude that this world is run by psychopaths.
What do you do when the psychopaths have taken the reins of power? See all you
need to do is three things. One, give them a uniform. Two, give them privileges. Three,
tell them they're above the law. And you've got a psychopath.
And perhaps it is their psychopathy that allows them to rise to the top. And that's
why we seem to be in a position to do that.
We need to be in the mess that we're in. The world is ruled by psychopaths. What does
that say about society? That we allow these type of people to rise to the top. And how
do we defend ourselves against them?
They do not have as much of a fear response to getting injured like most of us do. We
do something, you know, you cut your hand and then you learn really well not to do that
a second time because you don't want to get cut again. Their response isn't that great.
So they're able to make, they're able to take chances that are not going to happen. And
a lot of people wouldn't take. And that again, you know it's
leadership qualities. It's would normally be admirable in a leader that they're willing
to take chances and risks, you know, that is that's what you want from a leader.
How many Adolph Eichman's are there anyway, that quality makes good leaders.
And that's why we want to follow them. Because, you know, you don't want to
follow somebody that's humming and hawing and says, Well, you know, geez,
maybe I think we should do this. Maybe No, we want somebody that's confident,
and sure of themselves and makes broad statements and inspires us.
Yeah, I want to do that. I want to follow people like that.
The spiral of inequality can be broken if the illegitimacy of the power distribution is revealed.
One way to undermine the legitimacy of authority is open revolt,
but a more subtle way in which the powerless might curb self-enrichment by the powerful is by tainting their reputation.
Authoritarian sociopathy can not only be stopped but driven into reverse,
not by violence or revolution, but simply by undermining their sense of legitimacy.
Viewed this way, it could be said that comedians such as George Carlin or Penn Jillette
have done more for freedom than politicians like Ron Paul or intellectuals like Murray Rothbard.
And then the culture itself, which is, of course, encouraging people to be selfish,
you know, to be...
Good consumers, you have to be able to spend everything on yourself, so...
It is the witnesses who are the majority and thereby the most capable of meaningful intervention.
And we want good consumers, so let's make them all selfish people
and irresponsible for, you know, future payments on their credit cards, you know.
Live for the moment, enjoy life, rock and roll, die young, you know, which is very profitable.
All that is necessary for the triumph of evil...
is that good men do nothing.
If we want to fight corrupt authority, we must fight it where it truly resides, in the mind.
Yeah!
I said...
I'm Hispanic!
Can I buy for Peter Trout?
You can't get Mexico to pay for the wall.
I'm Hispanic!
Can I buy for...
Peter Trout!
And nobody builds walls better than me, believe me.
The greatest wall that you've ever seen.
Two walls, one here, one there, in between, a load.
Peter Trout!
Yeah!
They said...
Peter Trout!
Yeah!
They said...
Peter Trout!
Yes!
They said...
We love you!
I have a warrant for the end of my loss.
They said...
We love you!
They played with my nose.
I don't want touching.
We love you!
We love you! We love you!
Oh, yes, dear friends.
What you're listening to here on Hour of Slack
is a collage by Phineas Narco of NationalCynical.com.
There was another Trump collage earlier
that was by Reverend Cuttlefish.
That song, Pop That Bulbous Scrotum,
was by the Rudy Schwartz Project,
and the dialogue clip was from Hail Caesar.
Now back to National Cynical Radio.
They're going to...
Call me?
Not gonna be any good. They didn't give me any money.
I don't need it. I don't want it.
I couldn't care less. Couldn't care less.
You are going to love President Trump.
Bing, bing, bong, bong.
Bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing, bing.
China.
China, China from China.
And I love China.
Nothing wrong with China.
I love the Mexican people.
They have tremendous spirit.
They're taking your job, taking your money,
they're taking everything.
And I'm going to win the Hispanic vote.
It's true.
Bing, bing, bing, bong.
China, China, China from China.
You are going to love President Trump.
Bing, bing, China, China, China from China.
Bing, bing, bing, bong.
Bing, bing, bong.
What you know what that is?
Bing, bing, bing, bong.
Somebody, somebody, somebody is doing the raping.
I love China.
China all the time.
I love doing the raping.
China.
Nope.
I love doing the raping.
Somebody's doing the raping.
No need to tell one from another.
Everything we offer is just like the other.
No need for choice.
It's all the same thing.
Let's all rejoice.
Let freedom ring.
Yours like mine.
And mine's like yours.
I like mine.
And I like hers.
We are one.
It is what it is.
Comfort in numbers.
I know what it is.
This is Generica.
All one brand.
Land of the bland.
And this Generica.
and this Generica.
Everything's familiar.
not meant to confuse.
We've got your favorites, everything you use.
No reason to travel, no reason to fear.
Stay where you are, the same things are here.
It's a comfort, you know what you'll get.
We've got you covered in our safety net.
Everyone's protected, we're free to stay.
Everyone's connected, it's the only way.
This is Generica, all one brand.
This is Generica, land of the bland.
This is Generica.
The sun's gone down, folks are going to bed.
The skillet's all greased and the hogs are fed.
Fetch my saw from the back of the shed, we're going clunking.
Lordy, lord, lordy, gonna have some fun.
Got a meatball sandwich and a bottle of rum.
Leprechauns dancing on the end of my thumb, clunking.
We're going clunking.
Now I know a guy at the top of the hill.
He got a straight razor and a cordless drill.
His sister makes whiskey out of nails and wax.
She got a sour disposition, she keeps it a sack.
Gas up the car and change the windshield wiper.
Batten down the hatches and don't pay the piper.
Checking the tabs on my engine.
I'm a big continents diver.
Clunking.
We're going clunking.
The car's14m fast.
Now that I'm naturally quick-witted, job-wiper grows it's influence on me.
Half for cleaning it up.
The percentages in my head are relative to my worrying, deep throughout my brainwaves.
Have so much fun laughing out your eyes and growing up in a closet.
We gone clunkin', that's what we said
All dressed up in satin and frills
Crisco drippin' from the pine ford sills
With a double-breasted jacket and a fistful of pills
We gone clunkin'
Now I don't care what the preacher man say
About Jesus and the devil and the jars of clay
I'll be clunkin' come Judgment Day
Pop the bag and let the chisholm spray
Don't you all worry about gettin' me home
Drop me in the gutter with my pocket comb
Ready Os Collect or vitally shalom
Clunkin!!!
We gone clunkin.
Yes it's really something when you Go on out and clunkin'
What you say Bop!
Bop!
We gone clunkin.
Yes it's really something when you Go on out and clunkin'
What you say Bop!
Bop!
We gone clunkin'.
Yes it's really something when you Go on out and clunkin'
What you say Bop!
Bop!
Yes, it's really something when you
Oh, yes, dear friends.
And that clunk in there was by the Rudy Schwartz Project,
our old buddy, Reverend Joe Newman,
probably the cousin of Alfred E. Newman
and possibly of Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
You calling me a cowboy Dave?
Yeah, Lonesome Cowboy Payne.
Payne, indeed.
I was going to once again, as usual,
ask if we can hear a loud buzzing,
in which case I will use the other phone.
I cannot hear. I cannot hear no buzz.
Okay, well, then it's good. Let's get started.
Who is the first president of the United States for real?
Because there was a different person
than Joe.
George Washington.
Really?
Yes, there is a town nearby here
that has a series of paintings
next to an old country store.
And it says,
the real first president of the United States.
I don't understand the story, though.
Really?
But they claim there was someone else besides George Washington.
That person later moved to northeastern Ohio
to become an Indian-hating farmer, a redneck.
Really?
Benjamin Franklin, the only president of the United States
who was never president of the United States.
And now, Dave, are you going to enlighten us
as to who this person is that really is the real first president?
Well, it's in a town called Hartsgrove, I believe,
or Williamsfield, or one of those two close to Geauga County.
Okay.
And it's a draw, a tourist draw,
that the people come and they look at this stuff.
And read the diary,
or, you know, what's left of a little makeshift thing
for a diary, you know,
and you go up there and you look at it and you go,
hmm, could be maybe there really was a different president
before George Washington.
If you walk away and go back to Chicken Falls
or wherever you're from,
that's all I can say.
That's all I will say.
I see.
So you do not know the name of this individual
who was the first real president of the United States.
No, but I will find out sometime.
Okay.
And I will report it duly.
Hey, I've got a report here
that just came in.
I got a very long text
from our friend Dr. Legume,
who lives in Seattle now.
Wow, he's a grambling guy.
He's been all over the world, hasn't he?
Well, this has a kind of an ironic punchline.
And I'm going to read this.
This is the first time I've ever read a text.
This is the first time I've ever read a text on the radio show.
It's another first, friends.
Machete improvises.
Another first.
Anyway, yeah, Legume texted me saying,
I just returned from Amazon Island.
I was literally the only man there among hundreds of women.
And I've spent three days there in a kilt and giant boots.
And naturally, since it's me,
it all went to hell.
In the most hilarious and ironic way.
It all started with me being invited to tag along
to a reunion of my girlfriend's college mates.
I'm expecting some rustic rental campground,
but no, it's more like a big-budget wisteria
with lodges and stuff.
And my girlfriend's friends show up,
and I'm there for three days,
surrounded by middle-aged women,
most divorced.
And of late, your humble doctor's been keeping up his exercises.
And I'm looking pretty damn fit.
So I walk up to the main food service pavilion at this place.
I walk in the door, and it's like a movie.
Everything screeches to a halt.
Every head snaps around and stares at me.
Hundreds of them.
The campground was also hosting
the Women to Women Recovery Weekend.
The trashiest pack of drug-addicted,
alcoholic losers you ever saw.
Like gazing deeply,
into the gene pool of someone you both know.
And they were not even a bit subtle.
The room filled with giggles.
One girl grabbed her friend by the head
and physically wrenched it around
so she wouldn't miss me.
And for the first time in my life,
I was the hot guy
and the only man on Hooker Island.
The subgenius dream come true.
Like in your old story about the subgenius
who wanted nothing more than to have someone touch his...
uh, wiener and how he crossed the burning desert for that.
So for the next three days, I heard hoots and whistles.
I was objectified and leered at like a sex object.
They raped me in their minds and their hearts and their eyes.
Oh, poor Dr. Lincoln.
And I was cool with that.
On the last day,
the owners of the campground approached me on the path
and told me they'd received several complaints
because many of the women in recovery...
are afraid of me
because they're survivors of rape and abuse by men.
Therefore, I should remain sequestered in the lodge
for the duration of my stay.
At no point during the weekend
did I approach a single person
or speak an impolite word to anyone who spoke to me.
I kept to myself
and at no time even responded to their wolf whistles.
I spent my weekend listening to the frogs
and strolling through the forest pass.
But that's not what they...
they said.
I saw.
The black rape death came from the woods,
hungry for victims.
He knew he'd hit pay dirt
as the place was packed with them already pre-victimized.
He skulked the shadows of the night,
peering through poop-yellow lust-maddened eyes,
seeking out the youngest and weakest to feed upon.
Seeing poor little alcoholic Polly
in her pigtails and Bible panties,
the dark monster lifted in,
his black groin flaps,
unleashing a torrent of evil rape
that raped her, et cetera, to death for seven years.
None of them were even in my league.
It's got kind of a familiar flavor though, don't it?
And I thought...
I thought he was describing his last Starwood at first there.
Yeah, when you said familiar flavor,
I thought it was one of my relatives.
Well, you know, there's moral...
I'm gonna give away the punchline of my big Starwood sermon.
The powerful new drug that's sweeping the nation
is moral outrage.
People feel...
It's not a drug, Stan. It's a consistent state of confusion.
Oh, God, they love it so much.
But, you know, Facebook. You get on it...
What exacerbates it, though? What causes it?
Pain and misery and insecurity, anxiety,
and inability to really get up off your butt
and do something about anything.
So instead, they get...
And they're more than...
People get up in the morning...
They read the news looking for something to tell their friends
how they're properly outraged about it.
And they're making sure that their friends aren't morally outraged
for the wrong reason.
I spent half today reading people on Facebook
alienating half their friends and families
just for that 10 seconds of juicy feeling
that you get when you push the send button.
But this is getting worse.
This is what you're saying is that it's getting worse.
It's reached epidemic proportions.
And you're not saying why, though.
Yeah, because of the internet. That's why.
Because they can.
Because they don't have to say anything to another person face to face
except at their job, and they hate everyone in real life.
So they get on the internet where their only friends exist.
You know, the people they don't have to spend any time with.
And just...
Just...
Just build up that drug-like feeling of moral superiority at all costs.
It's like, it's not enough to be outraged.
You have to be outraged for the correct reasons.
And frankly, I'm getting my outrage off of their outrage.
Yeah, me too.
They're turning me into a junkie.
I hate them. I hate them with a visceral anguish.
And it just won't go away.
I like to kick them in the pussy.
I like to kick them in the butters and smack them in the wing-wing.
And...
Well, I don't mind people whining and complaining as long as they're funny about it, you know?
Yeah, but how...
So I better come up with a joke myself.
After the second or third line, all of a sudden you realize that the person is really disturbed
and yet is living in society and should be smacked down.
Well, it's interesting the fact that so many of them have so much time
to...
to post their opinions.
On the internet.
Now, most of their opinions are only a few words long.
My life sucks.
LOL.
And then everybody else goes,
Yeah, I know how you feel, LOL.
And that's the level of discourse now.
A vapid crew of insolent swineberries.
Um...
Yeah, but...
You know, if you don't have something nice to say,
just don't say anything at all.
Yeah.
That's what my mom used to...
That's what my mom used to say.
That's what Donald Trump would tell you.
He'd say, if you got something...
If you don't have something great to say about me,
just don't...
You can't say anything.
LOL.
I know how he feels.
If you can't say something about how wonderful and how beautiful
and how handsome and intelligent I am,
please do not speak in my direction.
Well, I guess we better end the show now.
Oh, no.
Switch over to music.
No.
Just kidding.
And then there's the problem of...
What's the polite word?
Ball busting?
Ball busting.
Where, you know, manly men call each other names
and say mean things to each other,
because that's how they show they're bros, right?
I suppose.
Well, on the Internet, that doesn't always carry.
Not everybody is really that excellent of a writer.
I mean, I don't know.
Wrong, I'm not gonna lie, okay?
I don't know.
Oh, man, we're not out of time yet.
If we did get to do something more interesting Eisley,
would it be so hard to keep our demands from all of us
to keep our own convictions,
I guess I don't know,
Are we really done with it yet, tonight,
or have we just started, you know,
We've got 5 to 3 books Jemma and I want to give some small notes.
to sound like all those whiners on the internet.
Yeah.
I think all those violent people should be punished
with amputation on live TV,
because violence is bad.
So we should be getting more violence.
I understand. I'm sorry.
I retract that statement,
and we'll put in a more suitable statement
within the next 22 minutes.
Well, like, for instance,
let's use this generic example.
I got up this morning, and there was bad news.
There was violence in the news.
Well, people were more upset
about whether each other's outrage at the violence
was the proper kind of outrage
than they were about the violence itself,
because some of them were going,
well, it's obviously a false flag
that candidate number one did to take away our guns.
Oh, no, it's a false flag that candidate B
did to...
I can't even follow some of the rationalizations.
But, you know, it's like you wake up with your...
You got your pet conspiracy theory,
and you just find the first thing in the news
and somehow manage to make that news item
validate your personal pet conspiracy theory,
the one that means...
That's the only thing that proves
that you're better than everyone else,
because you know something they don't know.
Yeah.
Especially if you're like a man
or a female orifice or an organ or...
I mean, if you're a male and stuff,
and you can somehow prove
that your male organ is the size of a boa constrictor,
you could just walk all over those people.
Well, yeah, but there's not many people proving that,
so that's not happening.
Well, verbally, they're trying to.
Exactly. They can't.
They use their cars or their Facebook page
to replace a healthy penis, basically.
Well...
Or relationships with other bipeds,
subgeniuses or humans.
Help me understand something here.
Reverend Stang, you played a piece of music this evening
that was called Pop That Bulbous Scrotum,
and then you're asking me
if teasing between men is called ball busting?
Wait a minute. I'm confused.
Well, or scrotum popping would be another term.
It would be more polite, I guess.
Yeah, yeah.
So, yeah, I hadn't made that connection, though.
You're right.
It's very uncomfortable, and I just don't get it,
but it's a guy thing.
It's boys.
Yeah, it's a guy thing.
You wouldn't understand.
Girls don't tease each other like that.
It's boys that do that.
It's a very important part of our existence.
It would be the same thing as, like,
if women were to argue
and they were to call it titty-dwanging
or something like that.
Right.
It's, you know, a sensitive area.
Not that sensitive.
We're not in a safe harbor yet.
Last week, we had to talk about,
uh, two cups of tea.
Also.
You'd be surprised how,
what kind of innocent things
can cause moral outrage
among an, oh, I don't know,
an FCC-minded crowd.
Well, most of these people
have IQs below 90,
and they have jobs...
That's the average.
The average IQ is 90, right?
So, by definition,
half of them are less than that.
Yes.
Subgeniuses, you might call them.
They're just...
They're not...
They're below a genius.
Yes.
I actually fall into that category.
I actually do, too.
If my...
I mean, my IQ hasn't been measured
since I was six years old.
And, of course,
those things are skewed
for six-year-old middle-class
white kids from Fort Worth.
They sure are.
So, apparently, I did well,
but not quite genius level.
I told Philo that around 1976,
and he said,
that's funny.
They told me my IQ was the same.
Hey, we're both...
We're just below genius.
I guess we're subgeniuses.
And...
And that's how it all began.
Well, I thought to myself,
that's what Bob and Philo
were talking about
while at that party
that they wouldn't let me go to.
That they wouldn't let you go to.
No, they didn't invite me to.
I snuck in.
That's the caveat to them tours
to all the other cavities
of them tours.
I had to...
Yeah, I don't want to say
what I had to do
to get into that party.
But I can...
Let me say this.
I can...
I can identify with women
who have been traumatized
by beastly acts.
Well, you have been raped by...
No, not exactly.
By a goon?
Like him?
No.
Psychically.
He's waiting in line
just like everybody else
at Bob's door.
But...
With his palms open
and his...
Yeah.
You know, everybody...
If it's Bob,
then, oh,
it's different somehow.
Don't ask me.
A brisket of beef.
That's all I can think of right now.
A full, hearty brisket of beef
surrounded by slaves
with wearing truncheons
and ski masks.
And that just brings me back
to the same reasons
why I wanted to quit the Internet
to begin with
rather than listen
to these people's
irate confusion.
Well, it'll all be over
with soon enough.
X Day is, what,
two weeks away.
The day called X
when the world's biggest...
The world finally gets
what's coming to it.
A ton of slack.
Well, or not.
Well, the slack
for those who deserve slack.
And, you know,
for some people,
death would be slack.
Or slavery under a subgenius,
a benevolent subgenius dictator.
It might be better
than what they have now.
I don't know.
We're going to find out.
Or not.
Is this one of those bars
of Devo called Slouch?
Is it the same thing as slack
or is it almost the same?
No, no, no.
Slouch is blasphemous.
That's the opposite of slack.
That's mere...
That's like sloth and sloth.
It's laziness.
That's not the same thing as slack.
Slack is doing what you want to do.
It's not doing nothing.
Unless nothing is what you want to do,
then that's slack for you.
But most people
actually get bored
with nothing pretty quick.
Okay, I see the subtle differences
in between the...
Slack, sloth, nothing, laziness.
Stupidity versus subgeniusness.
Working real hard
on something you love really a lot.
That's your big slack.
Brainlessness versus break thinking.
Break thinking?
Yeah.
Like a form of dance?
Break winding versus no mind.
The practice of no mind.
That's a kind of a zen-like thing.
I smell the zen thing there.
Yeah, first you stop desiring.
You even stop desiring
to stop desiring.
You don't even care
whether you're desiring or not.
Then, much less whether you're desirable.
And at that point,
you get a hit TV show
and run for president.
I guess.
I don't know.
I'm just not so sure
I'm right about everything
like I used to be.
The more I learn,
the less sure I am of everything.
It's funny how that works.
Billy Goats and Frogs
used to have the gumps
and they had to understand things
before they could run for orifice.
Like, say, for instance,
Donald Trump.
He has no understanding
of comprehension.
That's it.
Well, that means he's a perfect representative
of the average American.
He doesn't know
and he doesn't want to know
and he doesn't care.
He just knows what he wants
and what he wants
is what he's going to say right then.
And that's all there is to it.
And some people,
that's what they wanted
was a confidence man.
A confident man.
Whether there's any reason
for that confidence
or whether it's just
kind of a form of insanity
doesn't matter
because the important thing
is somebody acts like
they know everything.
Just like all the most ignorant people
in the world.
Are the most sure and certain
that those smarty pants
don't know nothing
because look at the world.
It looks pretty flat to me.
Which, by the way,
the flat earth thing is coming back.
Unbelievable.
It is.
In the last year,
because of this, you know,
proud to be stupid thing,
it's like now,
well, we've seen it
with all the different minority,
you know, for women,
became proud just to be women.
Black people got pride
in their ethnic heritage
and, you know,
whatever your thing is,
you're encouraged to be proud.
And finally, the stupid
are stepping up to the plate
to take pride in their
special understanding.
And, you know,
when a subgenius is griping
about people being stupid,
that's a bad sign, man.
That's a canary in the coal mine.
And the buzzard eating
the canary in the coal mine.
Yeah, that's a couple
of fierce birds right there
trying to eat each other's food.
Who do you think is going to win,
the canary or the buzzard
in that coal mine?
The smallest of the two
is not going to win.
But they're both going to die
because there's gas leaking
into the damn mine.
Oh, I forgot that part.
Yeah.
So that's why they have us
canaries down here, Dave.
That's why they're just
waiting to hear us stop singing.
And when we quit singing,
they go, hey, wait a minute.
Somebody check the canary.
Oh, my gosh, it's dead.
And not a mark on it.
Do you smell something funny?
No?
Let's get out of here.
So, what?
The boss man,
the elevator,
they turned the power off
to save money.
We can't get,
we can't take the elevator
out of this collapsing coal mine.
It's Obama's fault.
He's trying to destroy
the coal industry.
There you go.
It all adds up.
Any conspiracy theory
can be validated
just by the proper exercise
of stupidity,
impatience,
ignorance,
and a general tendency
to see the world
as black and white,
right or wrong,
no in between.
And since there's
no in between,
you've got to be
either right or wrong.
And since it's you,
you must be right
because you couldn't be wrong.
Or confused
or maybe not,
maybe not.
I mean, I'm not really qualified
to judge exactly
how the entire world
should be run.
But strangely enough,
everybody seems to know
how to run the zoo,
the world,
the convention,
the traffic,
my business.
Well, I thought that
what you said,
the simple premise
was the very best,
was I smell something funny,
let's get out of here.
That's, to me,
that encompasses everything
from A to Z.
But I can't,
I can't leave
because I'm too depressed.
I can't change my environment
because they've already
beaten me down.
The conspiracy is so powerful
that I can't quit my job
and change to another job.
I'd lose my house
in between jobs.
I can't, I'm helpless.
I'm completely helpless.
I need a strong man to save me.
And in lack of that,
I need somewhere
to really complain bitterly
so everyone will know
to feel sorry for me
for the right reasons.
Not for the wrong reasons.
I don't want them
to feel sorry for me
just because I'm lazy and stupid.
I want them to feel sorry for me
because it's their fault.
There is a lot of
Wittgenstein-style semantics
going around
stating that the use of,
the use of language
in the case of Donald Trump
is very, very close to...
Seventh grade?
Yeah, I noticed that too.
And, you know,
it seems obvious,
but to have a bunch of,
social scientists
and sociologists
and other people
bring out direct references...
That's because
those sociologists
are no better than
sophomores in high school.
It's like sophomores
making fun of the seventh graders.
And here's old man Dave
and old man Stang
and young, beautiful Princess We
sitting on our mountaintop judging.
It's so much fun to judge.
It's even better than pushing send.
Hey, we're pushing send
on the radio.
That's even better
than pushing send.
We're pushing send
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Because they can't talk back.
And if they could talk back,
we wouldn't listen anyway.
Well...
Their disparate arguments
would be cast into the wind.
We'd turn everything around
and make them sound silly.
We'd argue amongst ourselves
to make each other sound silly.
And then we would pronounce a winner.
I don't know if we would say it
in Spanish or Urdu,
but we would pronounce a winner.
Spanish or Urdu?
Well, you know,
the only one who always wins
in the end is J.R. Bob Dobbs.
On Dr. Death.
Oh, old Dr. Death?
Yes, he...
Well, yeah, sure.
The grinning guy always...
Well, wait.
Which grinning guy?
The skull?
The death guy?
Or the pipe guy?
Because they're both grinning
like a skull.
Yeah.
One's got a sith
and one's got a pipe.
And semantic disagreements.
One's got horns
and one's got a pipe.
And one's got Brylcreem.
I'll go with the Brylcreem savior.
Or the Mephistopheles type guy.
Or the least Mephistopheles.
Hey, speaking of Mephistopheles,
Princess Weed,
did you ever find out
whether Mickey Mephistopheles
was coming to X-Day or Starwood?
He would love to come,
but he...
He got scared of X-Day
because he read about
somebody being butthurt.
No, actually,
his slave job is keeping him
and he's unable to come.
But he wants to come
to the witch's ball.
Well, it was such a shame
to see him being picked on.
This is his satanic majesty, okay?
This is a guy whose skin is red.
He's got horns on his head.
Now, granted, he has giant shoes
and a big red nose.
And he talks like this.
But he's, you know,
he's satanic.
Right.
And then he shows up at Starwood
and he's been to a couple of X-Days.
Not the way Satan talks.
Well, the funny...
No, no, he does.
He talks just like Mickey Mouse.
No, Satan talks like...
Actually, it's kind of a lift, too.
It's a bit of a lift,
but he talks...
And he gets picked on by children.
He's Thayton, Prince of Darkness.
Yeah, Thayton, Prince of Darkness.
Thayton, Prince of Darkness.
He stabs them with his trident
and yet they cannot feel
and they laugh still.
Don't you...
He can't come this year.
Here's a real good picture
of me and Thayton
standing in front of the fires of hell.
And Oberon.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah, the head of the sex cult,
the Church of All Worlds.
Yes.
The...
Yeah, yeah.
So, yeah, there's Satan
and two sex cult guys.
A real sex cult
and a fake sex cult guy.
And an easy way to see it
is just to type the word Starwood
into your browser.
I've gotten that picture many times.
You have?
Yes.
Just by typing in Starwood.
That picture?
Yes.
That picture.
The picture of me and the devil
and the cult leader?
Yes.
Well, you know, I typed in...
I typed in the word...
I have to spell it out on the radio.
T-I-T-S.
Uh-huh.
And the second picture that came up
was Suzy the Floozy
at an ex-day
after she had had her body cast made.
And there she was standing
next to her own torso.
Her own gorgeous torso, by the way.
So...
Yeah, you just never know
what you're going to see
when you Google those things.
But, Dave, believe it or not,
the time has flown away.
And all of Suzy is gorgeous,
by the way.
Just saying.
I can imagine that.
We got...
We're talking about getting you here
to the station for the ex-day show
in two Sundays.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And...
Oh, I mentioned...
I've been talking about ex-day,
but I forgot to mention something.
Women get in free.
This isn't normal.
Wait a minute.
Yeah, and it's a dumb idea,
and it sounds like a strip club, right?
Strip clubs make that offer
because they're desperate.
Well, this was...
We were accused of
the stupidest thing
you could ever imagine.
And I was stupid
and took the accusation seriously enough
to go, no, no, we like women.
In fact, I'll put my money
where my mouth is.
Ladies can get in free to ex-day this year.
It didn't help
with those...
with the anger.
I mean, there are angry people,
but apparently there are going to be
lots of people getting in free this time.
Let me tell you,
nobody respects women more than
the Church of the Subgenius.
I respect them more than anybody.
I'm the most respecting...
I'm the most respecting church
in the universe.
Thanks, Donnie.
I think that's the way you should publicize it,
is free women.
Well, we did.
That was the fright.
Well, no, women free.
Free women is different.
So it's just women free.
It may end up being women free,
but so far, we have had quite a few pre-regs.
Anyway, this is the Hour of Slack,
the official voice of the Church of the Subgenius.
You can find out more about all of that
and the stuff we play,
such as the Rudy Schwartz Project coming up,
by clicking around on subgenius.com.
And now I'm going to play
the next to last song
from the Rudy Schwartz Project album
called Sunshine Supers.
It's a hit.
That's what I call it on the radio anyway.
Another good seller besides free women
would be Fierce Wombats.
It's very intriguing to think of,
you know, Fierce Wombats.
Hey, I hear the buzz now
because I potted that out,
but now we're not going to hear any of it.
Thanks, Dave.
Now I'm hearing it too.
See you, Dave.
Okay, bye, man.
Bye, man.
Yesterday morning,
Donald Trump went on the Today Show.
And he came out and agreed
with Hillary Clinton and Barack Obama.
And Donald Trump said
that grown men
should be allowed to use
the girls' restroom.
I'm sorry that I missed your call
I hope you won't be too appalled
But it seems that I've got
It seems that I've got
My testicles in Ted Cruz's mouth
Don't be concerned, I'm doing fine
I know that we had hoped to die
But right now my balls
Both of my balls
Are stuck inside of Ted Cruz's mouth
I know very well that I had promised you
That later we'd go out and have a beer
No!
La la la la la la la la la la
It's just hard to socialize
With this uncoiled inside my ring
It's been this way for several weeks
There's bruises forming round his cheeks
Oh dear, it seems my testicles
Are into Ted Cruz's mouth
That sound it makes me cry
No excuses made that are placed on the screen
Mais oui j'ai mis le testicule in Ted's bruises mouth
You and I should really find the time to take a stroll down by the sea or in the village square
La la la la la la la la la la la
That will give Ted time to floss and extra beat my cubic hair
It's getting late and sadly I'm still lipo dripping down my thighs
Cause it seems I've got my balls, I still have my balls
Stuck deep inside of Ted's bruises mouth
Oh mommy!
My sweaty rancid ballsack stuck in Ted
My bruises
Mouth!