Yes, I know exactly how that poor listener feels.
Tonight, your host, Reverend Ivan Stang, is too busy with life, the universe, and everything to blather out a new show.
Plus, I already underwent two podcast interviews in the last two weeks, so maybe I'll play those in the future.
But, this is the past.
It's October 11th, 2003.
And we're listening to Overman First Degree.
Dr.
Philo Drummond, the sole guest that night in the KPFA Berkeley studio of The Puzzling Evidence Show.
Where we say, bring it on.
Because that's the way we roll.
On The Puzzling Evidence Show.
Great check.
Okay.
Wow, that's an ancient memory.
Great check.
That's what you get when you talk to a machine in the middle of the night.
Okay.
Wow.
I think there's Charlie.
Charlie, is that you?
Charlie.
Come down out of that hallway.
Lift yourself up by your own petards.
Computers don't laugh.
Okay.
That's better.
Regain your composure.
Okay.
I think that's better.
Yeah.
You think you can pull up on my feet?
And you?
Yeah.
I can.
money here they're making it now here get those barrels open get the yeah we got to get the raw
materials in here we need some more resources you're taking the money away oh darn load those
trucks up
he needs that money all right we'll get him to come around is this the money
is this the money begging time is this the money begging time begging begging is this the time
where we beg for money yeah let me bag the money back you can see it now we're being held up by the
barge strike of course but now the government's going you can hear the government lowering the
money into the i can hear the government is starting up again thank you mr government
that's the sound it takes a lot of money to start the government up again
you have to prime the government with a lot of money to get and you put the you put the money
in the government's carburetor and then you turn the starter on you got to get this the various
is it crooks i mean congressmen in there to turn the various wheels government's going and the
barge is not but as long as the government's going we don't care everything's good now
i'm so happy
it's all better it's all what pathetic oh yeah
pathetic government art world
you know that something a lot of people don't know about but i'm going to go ahead and say it
because i remember
it today
you know something that bob really hates is he he hates dashes he hates to see things with
dashes in it so don't put a dash in the words we're putting dashes in your words would you stop
that i'm asking you that because it's not dobbs approved dashes are not at least some dashes most
dashes are not dobbs approved bob hates the unsettling transitional ambiguity that they
have been in the past and i'm not going to stop that i'm not going to stop that i'm not going to
advise a cop not to hire you to use dashedes
please i implore you don't use dashes inappropriately
only in a dobbs fashion if you can't remember what that is you just have to get your
manuals out turned to dobbs ecclesians 12 first
are grabbed to touch the door while five drivers approach them
yeah it's that little churchy stuff
but
Just don't use dashes, please.
Stay away from dashes.
Be all right.
If you went in doubt, kick the dash out.
That's what Bob says.
I love this old tune.
It brings me back to the old days, you know,
back in the swamp,
when me and...
Motel and Annie.
Me and Junior and Bubba were back there
sitting on those old oil drums
filled with oxygen.
Little Junior.
Little Bubba.
Just sitting there like a couple of old,
little kids.
You know, the...
Okay, thanks.
Yeah, we're just killing time here on the show.
Yeah, well, that's good.
Killing time is fine.
Bark people are killing time,
but it's unions against management,
and, you know, people have to get something done sometimes
to deal with the management.
That's true.
Thank you, guys.
Hang in there.
It's true.
It's all true.
People got to do
what they got to do.
And we just have to make...
And they got to do
what people tell them to do.
Because sometimes
you don't get to do
what you personally want to do
because you got to do
what the group says you got to do,
and that's more important sometimes.
And just to, you know,
that's what you're paying for.
That's the important thing to remember.
And so...
And there's people there that are experts,
so you got to leave it to the experts sometimes
to put things in line.
And make it right for everybody.
I think we can all agree that
we have confidence in our experts
to do what's right for us,
the non-experts.
I'm an expert at non-expertise.
That's where I try to concentrate my area of focus,
is in those non-expertise areas.
And I think that's where we're at.
Yeah, and on this show,
at this time,
we have to let off steam
to help the public.
Yeah, we like to help the public.
We really like helping the public.
Our job here is to help the public
understand things
in a non-ambiguous,
less vague,
more elucidating...
We like to elucidate the language
in a way that makes it
easier to understand.
Easier for people,
people,
to understand.
Oh, people, yeah, people.
To absorb, to process,
to get in their ears
and make their brain
see it
with their eyes
that are on their eye teeth.
Oh, there we go.
Ooh, that's just nasty, though.
Don't look at it.
No, no.
Do that.
Okay, I'll wash your dishes.
Oh, yeah.
The nipples, tongue, neck, and lips may be utilized...
In ghost time?
Yep.
Yeah, as we were talking about earlier about those little guys.
These poor ghosts.
And that one 420 guy thinks that they don't even have a sex.
They're sexless.
He thinks that ghosts, somehow when people die, they don't retain their sex.
Like a gun.
Like a god?
A gun.
Well, like a gun.
Yeah, like a gun.
But you would be the same little ghost you were before?
I would be me.
Yeah.
I'd be part of you.
I would hope I wouldn't have to wear glasses anymore when I'm a ghost.
Really?
Do you think we'd have to wear glasses when we're wandering around in the ether zone?
We'd have to have ghost glasses.
When we're ectoplasm.
People that made the ghost glasses.
It would get rather confusing.
I always wondered about that.
When you would see a ghost.
Because you've got all the stuff, you know, when you become a ghost.
So you're ready to go.
Unless you didn't have your glasses on.
Yeah, that would be a bummer.
If you died without your glasses on, you're wandering around forever bumping into stuff.
Ghost furniture.
It was a good time.
Just gets more.
So you have to die with the stuff you're going to take with you.
Yeah.
Otherwise...
That's why Indians would burn the teepee full of things.
So what about...
Should you carry a few dollars on you just in case?
Probably.
And clean underwear like your mom said.
Yeah.
Always.
Because that's all very...
Two pair.
Should always wear two pairs of underwear.
Why?
Because then the outer one burns away as you go into it.
Well, no.
Because then you don't have to change underwear for eight days.
Oh.
You just inside, outside, front side, back side.
Then the next pair over the front pair.
Right.
Inside, outside, front side, back side.
So you've got...
Yeah.
Eight days of continuous wearing that way.
You don't want to...
No.
You don't want to go out on a motorcade because then you go into the future world with...
Depending on which theory you have, no brain or some brain.
Yeah.
Not really enough brain to do a good job.
I can't imagine like when I'm walking up to JFK and shaking his hand, he's just drooling
all over himself.
Yeah.
And you're thinking, this guy, this guy, he's so crazy.
I want to hear about what I'm supposed to do for my country.
Yeah.
And you're just drooling in your drool bucket.
It's pretty nasty.
That will be nasty.
So nasty.
But people like Washington...
Washington and Roosevelt, they'll be fine.
So you can go and walk, talk to them.
I would like to talk to those guys.
Yeah, Jefferson.
They're cool.
I want to hear some of the stuff they got to...
What they've been thinking all these years.
Yeah.
It's just we can't talk to Lincoln and Kennedy.
Watching their thing that they made, seeing what happened to it.
Yeah.
Because they hang around and ghost.
You know, I'd like to talk to this old Ben Franklin.
He's the one guy that signed everything.
Yeah.
He signed every major document that was to be signed that put this country in motion.
And he did lots of things.
He's a very interesting guy.
Actually, I'm listening to his autobiography right now.
It's one of those free books you can get...
What?
Out on the internet.
Free?
It's free because it's in the public domain.
And we own that book now.
We do the public in our domain.
And a place like archive.org is one of them, I believe.
Or another one is...
Is the Gutenberg Project.
Wow.
You can get the text of that in either one of those places.
There's a place called LibriVox where you can get the audio version of that.
Wow.
If you want just to listen to it in an MP3 file, you can listen to it that way.
With no bark.
That's pretty cool.
Yeah.
That's what I did.
I downloaded it so I can listen to it at my leisure.
Speaking of which, I'm reading Zealot right now.
That's pretty wonderful.
It's...
Who Jesus was and the times he lived in.
Interesting.
Really fun.
I like Jesus times.
Yeah, me too.
Stories.
Because I don't really know much about it.
And the tapes are all wooden so they don't have players anymore.
Yeah.
Yeah, interesting times, those Zealot times.
Those early religions.
Those true believers.
Yep, true believers.
We got lots of true believers around today, I'm afraid.
Yeah.
Just like then.
Yeah, just like then.
Because at one point...
The guy weaves, the author weaves all the true believer leaders strolling around that area at that time.
There were a lot of true believers.
Yeah.
And that's part of the wonderful thing.
How did this guy get chosen as the one true believer that would go do the field goal, do the next thousand years of points in the game?
Because he's the guy that was willing to take the ball and run with it.
And get nailed to a stick.
That's...
You got...
That's, you know...
Boy, if you have that kind of motivation...
That's at the end and he knew it.
He knew it.
So, you know...
It's like, here's the deal.
You get to have this for a little while, but...
Yeah.
Later on...
But also, that's the motivation because that's sort of like...
That's why I shot Bob.
If the guy's willing to...
You know, if he can't whoop it, he goes down for the religion.
I think that propels the whole thing into the future.
At some point in time, every one of them's got to go down for the big game.
You know?
It's just the nature of the...
Right.
They can only spike the ball for so long.
Yeah.
And then you got to kick a field goal.
Yeah, right.
And at some point in time, you know...
The bad...
The enemy, the opponent is going to scrimmage.
Yeah.
And they're going to cross the line of scrimmage before you.
And somebody's going to throw a penalty.
And hopefully, you're going to come out ahead at the end.
Because, you know, the way it works out...
If you ask any football player what the secret of winning is...
He'll tell you.
You just got to score more points.
Really?
You just got to score.
You just got to score more points.
That's all there is.
I thought it was some elaborate truth.
No, no.
It's a really simple formula.
Whoa.
You got to score more points than your opponent.
And then you'll win.
It's that simple.
Okay.
I'm writing this down.
You can memorize that.
S-K-O.
If you know the score...
Score.
So, you should always look up the...
S-K-O-R-E board.
Yeah.
Reality.
Oh, it's like the formula for success here?
Yeah.
In the subgenius business class.
You know the score.
You'll be scoring all along the way.
Yeah.
So, okay.
Scoring.
Speaking of scoring, did you score?
I think so.
Oh, good.
Good.
I don't really know until I look at the computer.
Okay.
I can't...
That's the other thing.
If you're far from your computer when you die, it might be a virtual suicide.
I'm going to put my computer on my phone.
And just in a hat.
And then put your phone on your forehead.
And then I'll wear my phone on my forehead.
Yeah.
Like a Methuselah.
In a little...
A special hat.
Yeah.
That holds it.
A tinfoil hat that holds it so you're ready to go.
And it'll send signals out to everyone around me that says, here's his status now.
He's ready.
Yeah.
You're reminding me of, I think, the Millennium or one of the end of the world things that
happened in the last few years.
This guy started doing great insurance for that.
Like taking care of his family.
Yeah.
And taking care of your pets and your kids and all the people that weren't blessed that
weren't going to make it.
You know?
You could set aside some money to take care of them.
Oh, yeah.
What about old Harold Camping?
I heard him on the radio the other day.
He's still alive.
But was it him or the millions of tapes?
Just like other religions I know that...
No.
He was talking about current stuff.
He was still...
He still...
He must be like 95 now.
Yeah.
He's old.
And he still rocks on the radio.
And he still sounds like this.
Yeah.
I mean, he's talking about Jesus and the devil coming back and Satan is the story and
the sons of man.
I can't believe it.
That's the stuff we want to hear.
He hasn't gone yet.
Harold?
610, I think, is the AM.
The AM.
Yeah.
I used to...
Before I knew who he was, I used to listen for hours out in the desert, driving along,
listening to Harold.
I like those old preachers.
With the rhythm they have.
His rhythm was...
Would get a little bit...
Ragged.
Yeah.
That's okay.
He's...
He's old enough to kind of have met God or something.
I'm trying to remember the one I used to really like listening to when he died not too long
ago.
I can't remember his name.
That's sad that I brought that subject up and I can't even remember.
That's so sad.
Okay.
I'm going to go on the punishment list.
I'm going to have to wait on the wheel for a while.
I'll be right back.
Yeah.
Oh.
A distinct smell as you came up in the ferry boat captain.
And he used the monstrous ship into its little landing.
It was great stuff.
There's something salutary about being out on the water early in the morning.
Like I always thought the way, the best way to go to work in San Francisco from the side would be on the ferry.
To see the city at dawn, yeah.
Even at a day of work, that's a nice way to start.
I see him over here.
Oh, sorry.
I had the wrong Al.
You thought I was Dr. Hal.
I'll show you Hal right now.
Yeah.
He's supposed to be calling in, isn't he?
But there's a mystery.
Why would he need to be calling in?
I think it's a conspiracy that he's not calling in.
Why would he have to call in?
Isn't he here somewhere?
I think he probably had the phone in his hand and he started to dial.
And because it's a show, he just went.
Uh-huh.
And he's.
But maybe he put the phone like this.
If his brain would stop thinking about the show, then he would just wake up.
He would wake up and he'd be drawing pictures again.
Yeah.
And working really hard.
He'd be working hard.
And making money.
But instead.
Making money.
If you think about, if you're Hal.
Drawing money.
Hal's a good artist, so he just draws his money.
Yeah.
And then he gives it to the people to give back to him at the Ask Dr. Hal show Friday night.
Right.
Tomorrow.
The main thing is he gives it to the, he's giving to the people.
He is?
That's what we do here on the Puzzling Evidence Show.
We do.
We give our words.
Yeah.
Here's some more words for you.
Here, we'll give you another four.
This is 420, so after this would be 40 minutes of words.
Because you know what?
We don't want to grow up on the show.
But you know, we have the gift of discernment here on the show.
We do?
And the gift of knowledge.
Because this is what we gather up.
The anointing oil.
The prayer cloths.
Yeah, I wish you guys would send out the prayer cloths.
Prayer cloths.
Would you send those back?
To the people that need those?
Yeah.
We always send them back, yeah.
If you'd send those back, we can get your prayers answered.
Because then Bob makes stuff happen on them and gives them back to you.
He makes stuff happen on them.
And that is true.
Pastor David Epley is one of my favorites.
He's one of my favorites.
I'm trying to remember.
I remember that one of those other ones that, gosh, he was from Chicago.
Famous Chicago evangelist.
Yeah.
Epley was from Texas?
He was from Florida.
Somewhere in like St. Petersburg or Tampa.
I can't remember.
Out around Victorville, there are lots of little churches.
I guess you can make your house and your holy, holy sepulcher.
One.
No, not sepulcher.
But your holy clinic.
And if it's attached to the house, there's a tax world that happens there that's nice.
So way out in the desert are all these different fundamentals here in the desert.
Which up until recently was pretty far out there.
But it always seems like every time you drive from east toward Victorville and on 15.
So just everything.
So many of us.
Growing and growing and growing.
Growing, growing.
Growing.
Growing and growing.
Every little crossroads now is strip malls every place.
But that's the way it goes, I guess.
And that's why we love going to the desert.
Remember that guy, Creflo Dollar?
No.
Creflo Dollar, Reverend Creflo Dollar from Georgia.
Wow.
He drove a Rolls Royce.
He was a prosperity preacher.
Remember?
He was.
He said dollars are good.
Dollars are good.
He's kind of like Reverend Ike.
Remember him?
Yeah.
Now retired, Reverend Ike owns a fleet of mink-appointed Rolls Royces.
He said, the best thing you can do for the poor is not be one of them.
Oh.
Whoa.
Yeah.
That's what you can do.
The best thing to do for the poor is become rich.
Yeah.
It makes sense.
It makes perfect sense.
Yeah.
That's how all those churches should be.
I think the people that have extra money should take people in and let them live in their back room or something.
Yeah.
Just put in some extra beds.
That's like communism.
Put some extra beds in.
They got the money.
Come on.
See, there's the money.
There's the money over there in those barrels.
Don't you know that?
You got to share a little.
Give back some.
You've been blessed.
You may have had your eyebrows tattooed on, but that's okay.
We don't care about that.
That way when you wake up, you won't feel faceless.
You already have a face.
I like the way this guy plays that.
It's a little bit.
Oh, dang.
Oh, my God.
You can twiddle your knobs, and you can twiddle.
Look, big faces up here in the windows.
Big faces on the windows.
Yeah.
You can twiddle the face on Twitter.
Yeah, on Twiddle.
Twiddle.
That's one of my favorite little arbiters of how things are going.
Oh, my God.
in the world is, I say on YouTube,
under the share bar,
there used to be
three things, and now
there are 13 things.
Like I'm thinking, Wenzek Field,
you'll be 60
points. Well, there's another one you can go to that
shares on all those other ones automatically.
So there's a sharing of a share.
It's always about that.
But eventually it'll just be Google, so you'll just
push the button and Google will do it all.
And come to your
house and talk to you.
And make that Michael Pepe or a Martini.
But the main thing is, you can go out
and sign up now.
On the sign-up radio.
I forgot about that sign-up radio.
I want to write down the name of that thing that
that one guy told us earlier, because I don't
want to forget that.
I'm going to go to my list
of things that I don't forget.
And write it there.
Oh, the last thing I wrote there was the name
of a clown.
His name is Stabby the Clown.
He's a clown that uses
a lot. He has knives in his show.
He's a clown with big knives.
Does he throw them?
Throws them, carries them around.
Stabs things with them.
Because he's Stabby.
He's Stabby the Clown.
Hi, Stabby!
Well, I'm sure
going to use that.
I could use a
donut right now.
I wish it was later.
There it is.
T-O.
Okay.
I'll remember that.
T-O.
H-T-O.
A little colada and milk, if you don't mind.
Some H-T-O.
So soothing.
Ah, so relaxing here
in the morning.
It's almost like
the quiet storm.
Yeah, it is.
It's the quiet machine.
It's like the quiet storm.
Let's see if we get the bad noise this way.
Mr. V of Hoxhobos
says
McNivenin.
You're supposed to know that
on NBC
Numb.
So I'm sure that code
has broken through
to the other side already.
That's how I do it.
Ah, yes.
And there's that 60 cycle hum
that we've grown.
that we've grown to love.
But now, just as soon as it comes, it's gone.
Oh, it's just a little thing.
It's what?
It's the power supply
to the computer
makes that weird, dirty sound
behind the mix.
Do you think it's because the...
It's ungrounded.
Does the power supply have a box on it?
Yeah.
Is the box too close to another electronic source, perhaps?
Could be.
An electronic source.
Electronosaurus.
Here he is himself, the electronosaurus.
Yes.
We can go get a donut now,
and he can just fall asleep on the...
Millions of bits of wire.
It's about time.
Time to construct this.
It's about time you went to work.
Well, it wasn't all done by one person.
They took an entire village.
One truck.
You've just been lounging around your bachelor pad, right?
Well, I figured there's no point in calling
during the Pedrovian ceremonies,
which I assume are now completed.
They've been complete, and...
And he's listening right now.
He's listening.
Well, naturally, he's one of our most constant listeners.
But I just heard about this strike at the very last minute.
Yes, that's what I was asking earlier about how strange it is,
because it seems like maybe some people went to sleep
and they're waking up going,
this is great, I guess I'll go down to the BART station and go to work.
Right, there's going to be some buses...
And they're not going to.
No, they'll fall off the edge of the platform onto just nothingness.
Yeah, it'll be like a zone of the abyss.
And they'll fall into...
They're going to leave from 5 to 7, and then later on at rush hour,
but they can't possibly accommodate the number of...
Or like the outer limits where the...
They'll never be able to accommodate...
Aliens steal the town, there's fog around the town.
Remember, you just can't drive past the fog.
Or like on Cabin in the Woods,
where you fall over the edge of that abyss and you fall on top of Cthulhu.
Damn, that's a problem.
That's a problem.
When you're just trying to get to work, I mean...
Yeah.
Now, what's that other movie?
I remember another movie where there's a doorway,
and on the other side of that doorway there's this big beast,
and they're trying to get through.
Well, there's a head with the monkeys on the inside of the doorway.
There's a hearing squirming green bug.
There's a doorway in the hearse, I think, where they...
No, it's not that one, yeah.
But it was like a doorway.
It opens up, and then on the other side there's this thing
that's like a giant elder god waiting to come through,
and it just got its little toe in the door.
Yeah.
Dr. Mordred has a butt like that.
It's a tiny little door, so the elder god can't get through.
But it's enough.
The doorway is now open, and so that's the next thing.
The elder gods are going to come back through.
Ah.
And they're the ones that H.P. Lovecraft mourned us about.
Who HBO is named after.
Yeah.
Well, nothing could be...
H.P. L.O.
...H.P. L.O.
...likely.
But on the other hand, there are certain things that we can do.
We're not totally helpless in this.
Yeah.
Who's this we you're talking about, Dr. Mordred?
No, we could go to Fluff Girl Donuts really fast...
...and buy six trays of donuts and throw them at the monster really fast.
Yeah, we could kill the monster with donuts.
And they would be distracted by all of them.
Yeah, or at least donuts.
Or sugar, nature's perfect food.
Exactly.
That's the stuff I'm talking about.
The monster would be distracted with the donuts while we run.
Yeah, we could run by real quick.
Yeah.
Well, for some, it's not such a good thing.
Mm-hmm.
Well, you mean the monster now on sugar as it rages through...
Right.
...San Francisco?
That's bad.
Yeah, I guess that's bad.
That is bad.
Well, I wouldn't want it on my conscience, would you?
I'd want it on your conscience, but not mine.
Yeah, I don't mind it being on your conscience either.
I don't mind it if it's on yours, but...
That's two to one.
...you definitely don't want it on mine.
That's...
Well, if we can avoid such scenarios, it's probably better.
Any...
...for me, I don't mind.
...it's best to do it.
Probably.
To any conscience is...
So, here's the problem for me.
...because no conscience.
If I go to the dark room tonight, I'll just sit there in the dark, right, at 10 o'clock.
There won't be any Asdok for Hell.
It's be a dark show.
Why won't there be?
Yeah.
Because there's no Bart.
Oh, but that's only for those who come from the East Bay, which is actually an estuary.
Oh, yeah, and government's back up, so you'll be able to get their government...
Yes, I'll get my government welfare cheese.
That's...
You can probably take your government cheese...
...get your government cheese...
...a canoe and get to the Asdok for Hell.
...to the Asdok for Hell show.
And your government...
Well, I...
The problem is everybody else...
...health care.
...that idea, you see.
Oh.
But I only need to walk in my neighborhood to the Asdok for Hell show.
Oh, there'll be somebody there.
But it's not tomorrow, anyway.
That's what I mean.
That's what I'm saying.
I'll be sitting in the dark room in the dark...
Yeah, because it's not there.
...by myself.
It's not there.
You'll go...
I'll be like, did the government break this, too?
And then I think, oh, no, I guess...
No, it's the people did this one.
Maybe I'll just...
It's the people.
...sitting in the dark room.
It's the people's fault.
It's the people's fault?
They didn't come on the wrong night...
Oh, man.
...and force the show to be when it shouldn't be.
Yeah.
People.
That's the opposite of the Army's slogan.
Be all that you can't be.
Be all the people you can be.
Yeah, right.
Exactly.
Be everybody you shouldn't be.
Be all that you should not be.
Yes, exactly.
That's the...
Be the people.
...subgenius army.
So you can go to the Asdok for Hell show...
...in the subgenius army.
...and suddenly...
...you're Cal Worthington.
Oh, I see.
It's a...
So what happened to Charlie?
Is he still there?
Cal Worthington and his dog, Spot.
Only one call at a time, right?
Who was once a giant...
No, we can take in two little calls.
We can take two little calls.
But most people are afraid when...
Why didn't Michael Pepe call?
I don't get calls in here.
We could get Michael Pepe on or...
No, Michael Pepe's not there.
...Charlie.
Get Charlie on.
How nocturnal...
...inhibiting factor...
...are these characters?
...callback inhibiting factor.
Which ones?
Well, there's a Victor callback and...
...and a...
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Smell...
...Michael Pepe...
Smelly...
Smelling...
Smelly Johnson...
Yeah.
Johnson...
...and his...
...baby...
Johnson and Johnson.
Right.
...and...
It's a really magical thing...
...that they do on the show.
...that's Rod Johnson.
...Rod Johnson and Jock Osteel.
Yeah, exactly.
The old frat rats that we remember from...
Right, those frat rats.
You can't trust them.
They're gonna always try to, like...
...I'm gonna be...
...trick you at the end, you know?
That's right.
They'll twist and turn, and even if they get caught in a trap...
...they'll click and snap shut.
...pull out the rug...
...pull the rug out from under you...
...throw a pie in your face...
...and it's all in the nature of good, clean fun.
...make you eat dog...
...stuff, encrusted eclairs.
I saw a movie where they did that once.
Is that what frat...
...frags do?
...what frat guys do to their enemies?
Well, that's what the enemies do.
Enemies...
That's what the frat rat enemies do to the frat rats, actually.
No, wait a moment.
This...
You're talking about pledge season, right?
Yes, yes, pledge season.
Yes.
Waxed beauty instantly as you dust.
This is my pride and my joy.
And they have a paddle also.
That's skedaddle when I see that paddle, that's for sure.
You're not allowed to.
You have to take your medicine.
You have to waddle around for a while after you've assumed that medicine.
I'm not allowed to.
Well, I'm not allowed to.
Waddle like a duck.
And the police are coming for their donuts.
People shouldn't do that stuff to each other.
That's bad.
That's mean.
Here come the helicopters.
What are the little donut hole things called?
I guess they're called donut holes.
Donut holes.
Those little...
That giant tray of those things.
Yeah, and they're too expensive, though.
What are the...
How much do those donut holes cost?
I've never...
They're like...
I like them too much.
...25 cents each or something.
I don't know.
That's crazy talk.
They should be no more than a nickel each.
Yeah, I was just going to say a nickel, exactly.
But even if...
You should be able to get 20 donut holes for a dollar.
Many years ago, I would buy those by the box at Safeway.
I'd buy about six.
I'd buy...
If you could get 20 for a dollar, I'd buy $3 worth.
That's a lot, yeah.
60 donut holes, and I'd eat them on the way home.
And by the time I got home, I'd be down to like 20 donut holes or maybe 19.
And then I would...
Yeah.
As I drove home, throw them across the freeway to the other cars going this way.
Try to get them in the window and somebody's mouth is yawning.
He's going like this.
Whoa.
That's great.
That would make up for not having Bart.
That would make up for a lot of things.
That'd make up for the deficit on a lot of things.
Really?
Yeah.
Okay.
If you could throw a donut hole in someone's mouth...
Really?
...just when they least expected it but wanted it the most...
Yeah.
...that's a lot of money.
I mean, I don't know.
I would do that just to...like both windows.
Yeah.
You should see this site.
Puzzling was just now illustrating what it would be like throwing donut holes out of
both windows...
As people are crashing around.
...at the same time.
Yeah.
It'd be fun.
It'd look pretty good.
I could see how that would work.
That would work.
It'd be fun.
And then some percentage would get in those cars with the mouths of the...
Now you're talking.
Maybe you need some assistance where you would be like firing donut holes in rapid succession
through some kind of like air pneumatic powered tube like those ones they use to shoot
T-shirts into the crowds...
Yeah.
...at the Super Bowl.
Get one that can shoot donut holes into the car next to you while you're driving down
the road.
Even if the window's closed, you know, you just blast it right through the windows.
Right.
Donut holes flying with enough velocity to break the actual window of the car next to
you.
Big donut holes the size of...
Now you could get in trouble for that because there could be shattering glass that could
get on the...
What?
What's that?
I'm sorry.
You already made it happen because you said it on the radio.
Hello?
That's Charlie in a different world.
So what are these guys wandering around here?
They're just show ghosts.
They're wishing they could have donuts, donut holes, ham and croissant, cheese sandwiches.
What else?
Yeah.
Ham and cheese for small...
Classic glazed powdered sugar.
I might have to get...
I'm going to get a classic glazed...
I'm going to get a classic glazed chocolate powdered brown sugar donut hole tonight.
Yeah.
Rolled in everything.
And then the little...
I wish they would do that.
They'd just take something in there and just make everything out of it.
One donut with everything on it would be...
And it's five bucks.
I'm going to go in there and ask him, can you just do this one thing for me?
He's very accommodating.
Yes.
He probably will.
Probably will.
He would say, hey, you know what?
Hal owes you money from last week though and Hal's not here.
He's going to think when we come in there and Hal's not with us, that Hal is skipping
out.
Hal, are you still there?
No.
Hal went away because he didn't want to talk about that.
Oh.
Come back, Hal.
What are we going to tell Alex when we go to the donut place and you're not with us
and you owe him a buck or something from last week?
How much do you owe him and I'll pay your debt?
I'll pay your debt for you.
Yeah.
Or maybe...
Buzzing and I will...
Why doesn't...
Hal just barred over here.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
He can't barred over.
Something's wrong with barred.
I can't remember what.
People are going to wake up.
Silly of me.
Now, how are they going to find out?
Are they just going to drive there?
That's what I mean.
It's sort of like your coffee maker didn't come on.
How do you live when that doesn't work?
What do you do?
Do people have to get up and...
Do most people get up and listen to the news so they'll know?
Yeah, I would think so as they're making a leery-eyed listen to the coffee.
Or they'll turn on the television to support the news?
Or maybe the radio is a little bit better than you, so you can make a little bit of
I think so.
It's the internet.
The internet is your only way to get information.
It's not like one of those things where you can just turn on the TV and listen to the
news and you can tell people what the news is.
Well, I think that's going to be a real challenge, because you're going to have to
get up and go to the internet.
Yeah.
I mean, the internet's not on.
What?
It's on.
Look.
It's never not on.
I'm trying to get on the internet right now.
Yeah.
It says Hal's asleep.
Hal, what are we going to tell him?
You got to tell us.
Call back.
Maybe you should call Hal.
Yeah.
But that's impossible.
Maybe I should call Hal.
Yeah.
And make sure you call the number in the hallway to wake Liza.
Danger.
Yeah, it'd be great.
You could come out to the unofficial puzzling evidence show page, Hal, if you're online,
and put a message there that tells us what should we do.
What should we do?
I'm afraid that he...
I'm just going to tell him that when we get there, I'm going to say,
Hal meant to come tonight, but he was afraid that he'd have...
No, I'll say, Hal meant to come tonight, but he was afraid that Bart wasn't going to be running.
We made this recording of him in the shower that'll help.
Or is that me in the shower?
I know it's not both of us in there.
But how come you guys never talk about crawlers?
Crawlers?
Do they have them?
We only talk about the ones they have.
They have them at Donut World.
The crawlers are the best because...
But what I want to know is what gives it that pink color where...
It's sort of a...
It's a pink, a nice, pretty pink tan, but in the middle there's a ring that's kind of yellow.
Are you sure we're talking about baked goods here?
Yes.
Well, I suppose that's simply some proprietary method.
Oh, my God.
This is the first time I've ever spoken on the phone when Hal was on the phone.
Yeah, this is the first time I've ever been on the show when Hal was on the phone with Michael Pepe on the phone.
Yes, that has to be a first.
This is a first.
Another example of how progress...
And puzzling, if you start saying something now, this will be the first time that you said something when I was saying something while Hal was on the phone with Michael Pepe on the phone.
Exactly.
Okay, but it's not my first time.
And, you know, even though this is the first time, it's...
Well, it's not the first time I said something.
This is the first time I've asked something with a question mark.
You get it?
Well, no, that's not a question, though.
Mm-hmm.
Anyway, it's the first time I've said something with a question mark at the end of it on a night when I've been on the show with the radio with Hal on the radio.
But you can make a statement with a question mark at the end if you just say this, something.
Yeah, no, you can't.
If you say the word up, kind of up at the end, it sounds like there's a question.
What's up with that, anyway?
Like the way all young people talk.
Yeah, the way they talk now.
With a rising interrogative inflection at the end.
As if there's...
Even though there's just a statement being made, you say it at the end so that it goes up?
Yeah.
But you have to start the question the right way so that you have to say, can I have the goose or, you know, whatever.
See, and you can't really do it because you don't have the skills.
Well, I can.
But I didn't in that instance.
You've got to be careful that you start asking your question at the beginning of your sentence because you can't just start making a statement and then in the middle of the sentence, suddenly you've got to keep your voice up high because you're always going to be asking the question until you get to the end of the question.
Uh-huh, you have to keep your voice up high.
Because when you get to the end of the question, if it's not up, then people don't...
No, actually, I asked a question.
Hey, and Michael Pepe.
Yeah.
He got the statement.
Did you know there's this sixth annual body music festival happening?
No.
Yeah, it's the sixth.
You mean like armpit noises?
No, like behavior music.
Behavior music.
Oh, behavior music.
Yeah, this is the sixth year they're doing it.
It's here in San Francisco on November 5th through 10th.
Really?
Wow.
Where is it?
Well, I've got the thing for you here.
It's out behind...
And you can go to internationalbodymusicfestival.com.
Internationalbodymusicfestival.com.
Like write it all out?
Yeah.
Internationalbodymusicfestival.com.
Well, you know...
It's behavior music.
You have my email.
You could send it to me or my Facebook or whatever.
Okay.
But, wow.
Are you sure you want to take that step?
Well, I think so, yes.
I think it's time.
I really got into the cyber age.
Okay.
But by being a cyborg, it's a kind of extreme way to help.
Well, I think we're all...
I think we're probably going to all become questioned.
Yes.
Body modification.
But it doesn't have to happen before they make us do it.
Anyway, that's all right.
Anything you want is fine.
You know, we're all pals here on the radio.
Yes.
But some of us are more stoned than others.
That's really...
That's the only inequality.
Longer than...
Recommend.
What you want is of no importance.
Speaking of which...
Did you hear that?
...with me whether you like it or not.
No, he doesn't go with...
You mean Eli Whitney?
You're going with us.
You're going with her whether you like it or not.
And Eli Whitney's grandson went on an expedition to the Black Hills of Dakota with...
So what is it that's keeping you awake?
...dinosaur skeletons.
Is that so?
You'll sleep sometime.
Did he find any?
Yes, they did.
They found all the canonical dinosaurs that we know today in the 19th century.
Oh.
And no evidence of feather bedding on those dinosaurs.
They're just laying around out there.
They had to fight hostile Indians to get to the site and deal with the freezing cold and extremes of temperature.
Right.
Was he an archaeologist?
He was a paleontologist.
Oh, my God.
Well...
Was his name Marvin Witt?
Was his name Wittney?
O.C. Marsh.
You've heard of Cope and Marsh?
He was Marsh.
No, I'm talking about Eli Whitney's son.
What was his name?
He was the grandson of Whitney.
The grandson.
Was that Fred Whitney?
I think he might also have been named Eli Whitney.
Yes.
I think it was Marvin Whitney.
The name persisted in his family.
Of Whitney Houston.
Jitney Whitney.
And it was said that most of the...
...simply because they wanted to tangle with Indians and have an adventure.
They didn't have much interest in paleontology.
Wow.
They were like adventurous guys that just were itching for a fight.
Did they fight any Indians?
Oh, I suppose.
Who knows?
These were sunset cowboys looking for some adventure from reading dime novels.
To what was the exotic way.
Drifters.
They're called drifters.
Yeah, they're just drifters.
They just wanted to be what they read about.
Correct.
Yeah, but it's gone now.
They were latter day cowboys.
He died in 1927 with Wyatt Earp.
He was the last.
He's buried right out in Colma, in the city of the dead.
In, really?
Wyatt?
Yes.
Yeah.
Wow.
Well, I know he lived his last years with his wife in San Francisco.
And, of course, they've also got Steve Silver.
They're both on the beach at Blanket Babylon.
Buried out there.
Who's two of them?
We should have a subgenius.
Gordy.
Who's with him.
Wyatt Earp's grave.
It's quite possible there are many famous folks buried out there in that strange combo
of monuments and...
Perhaps a...
We should go out there for a subgenius reunion like we had that time.
I think we ought to.
Yes, definitely.
Yes.
That's where we ended up having a great reunion that one time.
During Indian summer.
Well, when the stangs are...
Yes.
Have a grave reunion and, you know, it'll be subdued, somber, and we'll be literally
grave.
We'll do that in February when the stangs come back to town.
Oh, it's in February, eh?
Yeah.
Okay.
When the...
Maybe we can find out what famous people are buried there.
Now let us bury them.
Oh, yeah.
You go findagrave.com.
What about...
Have you been to findagrave.com?
I've been to Tomb Tale.
Oh, yeah.
I've been to the graves.
You can go findagrave.com.
You can key in people's names and find out where they're buried.
And you can reserve a...
For yourself.
Where's O'Berry?
A cemetery block.
What's that?
That we'll pick.
O'Berry in Baltimore?
Who's buried in Baltimore?
Oh, a lot of people.
Edgar Allan Poe.
Yeah.
Where's Al?
He's buried in Baltimore.
Edgar Allan Poe.
Oh, that's good to know.
That's good to know.
Yeah.
It's a good thing.
When I go to Baltimore, I'm going to check out where Poe is buried.
You've got to find out, because I know each country, each city claims him.
You know, Baltimore, Boston, New York, all have some claim to Poe's legacy, and also
in Athens.
Oh, yeah.
In Athens, did you say?
In Athens, yeah.
the Poe house in the Bronx, and there's also a place in the lower, the battery, you know,
in the financial district, where he worked, where the newspapers were back in the 1840s.
Ah, interesting.
And so there's little Poe museums, but there's no really big deal.
That's sad.
They should make a really big deal museum.
Right. A really true, original, great American.
There ought to be like a Poe story museum, at least, where you could go in like a haunted park
where everything was Poe-related to one of his great scary stories.
Exactly.
You know, you could get buried in a wall, and so you'd be there where they would wall you up
and leave you there for a while, you know, like the cask of a Montalado.
Yeah, telltale horrors every place.
That's right.
Women you fall in love with and die.
Yeah, all those various reenactments.
The telltale heart, you know, you'd have to dig.
You'd get your heart ripped out.
And there's a big, like a three-foot raven as you walk in saying,
nevermore, over and over and over again while you're waiting to buy your ticket.
You just want to write a story, and the raven won't shut up.
Just lay down on your bed and have a...
And the top of it starts coming down, yeah.
Exactly.
So that's Guy de Maupassant.
That's the Wilkie Collin.
The terribly strange bed.
Well, it's also Guy de Maupassant.
Oh!
The top moves down.
That form is the Collin.
On you at night and smothers you.
I like a bed that has spots in it that are more comfortable than others,
and you can, like, get in that spot.
Yeah, that's what I have.
But then you run out of...
That's the problem is, then you have to sleep in that spot
because you can't make another mold.
Yeah, you're too old.
You're too old now.
You can't make another mold.
You can't start another show.
You can't remember everything about yourself.
You got this one perfectly made.
Why would you want to make another one?
Yeah.
We're all sleepy in our little nighties here.
Well, you might want two positions other than just left side, right side.
Getting kinky, eh?
Yeah.
Well, no.
His horizons are over.
Why don't you just lie on your back like in the king position?
Because then you snore.
You know, do you go to the same side each night when you go to sleep?
All about 600 times each.
I taught this to him.
Yeah, but I mean...
I'm like on a rotisserie.
I look like a hog on a spit when I'm sleeping.
Me too.
You mean, are you saying, do I take a side on the bark struggle as I go to sleep?
Yes.
Are you going to sleep for a while?
That's what I do.
I go...
I do.
But I'm not.
Good, okay.
Just checking.
When I wake up in the morning, the first thing I think of is, I hope I can get on the...
Yeah.
Well, I gotta go to work on it.
I hope I can get on the bark this morning.
Yeah.
Well, now you've got a vacation now, right?
An unpaid one.
That's the sad part about it.
Bark doesn't pay...
Bark doesn't pay you for your vacation.
Oh, oh.
And your boss won't pay you.
That's true.
I guess I had that wrong.
They'll probably get their pay reimbursed when they were off on strike.
What I meant about...
They probably won't go and reimburse your pay.
Well, let's cross that bridge when we come to it.
I think that's a great idea.
Well, the bridge is closed, so we can't even come to it.
And then what about...
The bridge is closed too?
And it's still like that in the...
The bridge...
Did they close the bridge too?
Yeah, oh no, no.
The bridge to Michael Pepe is closed too.
Oh yeah, if you've got a car, you can do it, but it's gonna be hard because...
Like if you try to drive from the station to Michael Pepe's, you can't do it directly.
The bridge to Michael Pepe's heart?
Yeah.
It's just closed.
Because of a relationship breakup.
Yeah, with the whole city.
Yeah.
And the whole city.
I'm a rock, I'm an island.
I said that you...
You know...
And a rock feels no pain and an island never dies or cries.
Cries, yeah.
Cries.
It never, never cries.
Never, ever.
Have you ever seen Hawaii, Oahu cry or Guam cry?
Yeah, I've never seen them cry.
Well, it's about the threshold of perception.
Dr. T, you won't cry.
Dr. Howell has a reason to believe that perhaps they do cry, but it just is of a...
And they're just too big.
We just can't perceive the crying.
I'm sorry.
They're tears are like rain.
They're like a big storm.
Their tears are like...
They're tears of a clown.
What about kangaroos?
When there's no one around.
Yes, even worse.
Beavers?
A pathetic clown crying thing, but on a giant scale.
I don't think beavers' eyes are big enough to cry.
They have to produce tears.
Yeah, they do.
They do.
They produce tears, but they're tears for fears and not for folly.
Beavers do not...
Because of the cuteness of the little...
Are you next?
...sickle.
They're dead.
No, nobody in here.
Just one show.
Beavers cannot cry.
They missed over.
Just...
They're thinking about their own little puppy.
Some birds can.
Crocodiles can.
Elephants...
If a train is too tough to cry, too strong to...
But does the crocodile become...
Too old to...
...of the whole piece...
Too old to cry, too dumb to die.
It's the way of eliminating insults.
So, Michael Pepe, can you hear the show?
I have a gut.
Do I have a show?
Can you hear the show?
Yes, I can.
How is your fertility?
It's the way of eliminating insults.
Did you listen to the opening?
Even...
No, I missed...
Oh, you missed the best part.
I missed it?
I don't know.
Because you were in it.
That was all Michael all the time.
Yeah, it was a special retro...
Except the parts where the other guys were there.
Yeah, it was a retro...
Beloved moment.
I wish I had been there.
I was so sad.
It's going to be the basis of a movie and a giant coffee table book, which is a coffee
table book about coffee table books.
It's called...
It's called A Pictorial History of Pictorial History.
Hey, wait a minute.
Featuring Michael Pepe.
You can't talk about...
Wow.
That was...
I was in on that idea.
You can't even carry it home.
Oh, really?
You better let me get in on that development.
Yeah, you need some sidewalk lawyers.
Oh, I'm not...
It's not mine.
I'm just reporting on it here.
That's the way to the table...
Because we talked about that.
We talked about it.
We don't let Michael Pepe be...
I'm already working on the coffee table part of that.
I'm working on...
Hear me over here?
...her chinko games here so I can...
I'm working on...
We need to make some money to buy one of those things.
The coffee table book about coffee tables.
Bigger than your car.
...stan on a coffee table.
I wish I had a coffee table book about coffee tables.
Get your coffee table constructed.
Then get a couple of coffee table books to try it out.
Okay.
I'm going to do it.
I love coffee tables and I won't know how to...
I love coffee table books.
That's a match made in heaven.
And I like coffee.
So you put the coffee in the metal.
This will really work.
You don't want to spill your coffee on your coffee table book.
And if they have enough coffee, they won't misbar.
If you have a coffee table book with coffee spilled on it, that's another reason.
You can have a sheet of glass.
You can just wipe the sheet of glass when the coffee is spilled.
But you can't save the coffee table book.
But that's why you should have a water.
Well, you can if you're quick enough.
Reach out and snatch up the book.
Wave of coffee.
And the super speed before the coffee hits the book.
You could be there waiting for it.
Because of your super speed.
The water has to be boiling just like with any other kind of coffee.
You've got to get the right number filter, of course.
And share.
And then you can get the coffee filter table book.
Yeah.
I've got the filter, but I need it.
Uh-oh.
Here comes the baby.
That's the ghost baby crying.
The Brady Bunch.
Yeah.
The Baby Bunch.
That tells us when the show's about over.
Because it's like being reborn.
You just feel so good when the show's over.
The next show's going to make you feel good about yourself.
Yeah.
Not like this.
I think we need to talk more about the Brady Bunch and coffee.
It's the Baby Bunch.
It's new.
The Baby Bunch.
5 a.m.
The Big Baby Bunch.
Yeah.
That's us.
The Sissy Baby Bunch.
After 5 a.m., it's...
Thank you.
The Cry Baby Bunch.
It says thank you.
We'll see you, though.
Next week.
They'll see you.
She was not.
We will love you next week.
Yes.
Love you long time.
And not watch the Brady Bunch.
Well, who is, uh...
Kiana.
Florence Henderson.
Show over now.
No.
Florence.
They can't hear this.
They can't be an answer.
Just run to the next phone.
Come on.
Help me out.
Hello?