Bob's Shoe Service has one of the biggest selections of work in western boots in the area.
Custom holsters and leather work, western wear and hats, shoe and saddle repair, and other western items for all ages.
Come into Bob's Shoe Service.
Either of you men fear what I fear?
It's funny. They think you're easy to be afraid of, say this beauty comrade.
I'm afraid she's right, Mr. Vandergilt.
But how can we be sure?
The Self Genius Power of Sack.
That devil.
Good grief. I'm on my way.
From PR news in Washington, I'm plunged into chaos because of alleged corruption.
Spaceships.
The shuttle Atlantis has undocked from the International Slaughterhouse.
The crew has been trying to determine if any beef they've served in their cafeterias could pose a danger on re-entry.
The shuttle has completed a nine-day mission in which astronauts made a public call for the beef grains on Wednesday.
Former First Lady Nancy Reagan is likely to be going into the food supply.
PR news is bad.
PR is bad.
More than 50 top former Philippine government officials recognized today that this is PR news.
In Washington.
Do I presume that you need no explanation of sexual variations?
A safe assumption, Lucilla said.
And I do not need to tell you that your robe identifies you as a fifth stage adept in the order of Hormel.
It was Lucilla's turn to scowl.
What if I show abilities beyond this fifth stage?
Ah, Serapha said.
You will continue to heed my words then?
Lucilla nodded curtly.
Very good, Serapha said.
May I presume you can administer vaginal pulsing?
I can.
From any position?
I can control any muscle in my body.
Serapha glanced past Lucilla at Buzmali.
True?
Buzmali spoke from close behind Lucilla.
Or she would not claim it.
Serapha looked thoughtful, her focus on Lucilla's chin.
This is a complicated matter.
I think it's a good indication.
Lest you get the wrong idea, Lucilla said.
The abilities I was taught are not usually marketed.
They have another purpose.
Oh, I'm sure they do, Serapha said.
But sexual agility is a...agility.
Lucilla allowed her tone to convey the full weight of a reverend mother's outrage.
No matter that this might be what Serapha hoped to achieve, she had to be put in her place.
Agility, you say?
I can control genital temperature.
I can control the temperature of the body.
I know I can arouse the fifty-one excitation points.
I...
Fifty-one?
But there are only...
Fifty-one, Lucilla snapped.
And the sequencing plus the combinations number two thousand and eight.
Furthermore, in combination with the two hundred and five sexual positions...
Two hundred and five?
Serapha was clearly startled.
Surely you don't mean...
More, actually, if you count minor variations.
I am an imprintor.
Which means I have mastered the three hundred steps of orgasmic amplification.
Serapha cleared her throat and wet her lips with her tongue.
I must warn you then to restrain yourself.
From PR News in Washington, I'm raping them on the table with non-consensual sex.
The White House says...
Not only to help PR News, but to ensure it doesn't get to regional distribution centers.
The Dow was seventy-twenty to eight-eight-thirty.
Sixty-five eighty-seven.
Six twenty-five fifty.
Last year, Mitsubishi and Suzuki both admitted to cheating on PR News.
One of Japan's largest steel makers admits to falsifying PR News in Washington.
Now I'm not gonna bore all of you.
No, I don't hear a thing.
With a lot of technological double talk, I'm sure nobody wants to hear that.
But what I will say is that our position on this...
The signal is here.
...subgeniuses virtually demand that we make our virtual demands.
Signal. Signal.
Thus, we do so.
Adding our signal to the noise, we comply in the cosmic spectrum, which radiates outward from X-Day at the speed of light.
As it does from anyone who's broadcasting one of these messages.
We know they are listening.
Unthinkable things.
Beings created of a different clay entirely.
From a different evolutionary path.
Frightful, huge beings from beyond the stars.
Uh, yeah, you know, you've heard about them.
And, uh...
Our own solar system is a happening place.
Where much has happened on the extrasolar world.
And, uh, even in the remote ones.
The remotest only discovered in the past few years.
Like the planet Biden, named for the recent vice president, Joe Biden.
Which is so far out among the...
I'm hearing it now.
...the gleaming clouds of the outer system.
Then there's the planet Sedna, part of our system.
And the planet Quaoar, part of our system.
They are hard names to, um, remember.
Because they don't have to do with the Grico-Roman mythology.
But they come from, I believe, a northwestern...
Now I hear it.
Now I'm hearing it too. It's happening.
Yes, we are persevering.
So there are many who are anxiously awaiting the onset of X-Day.
I'm sure all of you know who you are.
And there are others in the outer world.
Some may not know yet.
The strange, cold, loveless, inanimate world of the conspiracy.
Who also, though they may not know it consciously,
are waiting for the balm, the succydenium of X-Day.
So, Reverend Stang is going to be so proud of us,
we actually put together Tarzan's radio station.
The Stang of the free and the...
We've got the DVD player...
Home of the... Yes.
...the player is playing music in the background.
I understand we can actually even bring video into this somehow.
That's right.
And we may indeed be able to have live, on-the-spot organ music...
Now you got it.
...as in the great and golden days of Aunt Bertha and the gang.
Twiddle the knobs.
Our knobs all need to be twiddled with expert assurance.
See what I did with that pipe that was lying around here a minute ago?
And just listen to this even tone that we're able to put in.
And I'll play it to you.
Surely there's nothing beyond us.
What?
What do you mean?
I have a pipe.
A pipe?
I don't have it.
Racine took mine.
I don't have anything.
It's all gone.
No more.
I don't have any in my pocket.
I'm bereft.
Deprived.
Do you want to see my pipe?
No, sir.
I do not see your pipe, but...
This is my watch pocket.
Have you ever lost anything in there?
Ah.
Well, I have a...
Have you ever lost anything in there?
Have you ever lost anything in your watch pocket?
Well...
Look around for hours and hours and...
Sometimes I...
And there was a bowl already loaded and ready to go...
I stick some...
Just hiding in your watch pocket.
Yeah.
I do that.
I...
Who's watching you from your watch pocket?
Well, one likes to feel someone's...
Keeping its eye.
...paying attention to the busy sound of the clockwork.
Now it's still my lighter.
It did.
Why, I ought to...
I'll tell you what.
On this special occasion...
Oh, you do have it.
I'm going to put it on the table.
Hey, Al, do you know it's been about a year since we were on the radio together?
One year.
Yes, uh, isn't that...
Curious?
I think my last show was, uh, June.
Sometime in June of...
2017.
Man, this mu...
Mu...
Movie...
This music...
It's really...
Playing with my mind.
Well, this music is, uh, showing that there is a continuity here.
We can't, uh, claim to be the most, uh, joyful or energetic on this particular X-Day of X-Days
because we are dealing with anomalous situations and ch-ch-changes in the program.
This episode of the X-Day Festival itself...
I'll put some more in there for you.
That's kind of cashed out.
...is unusual because X-Day begins more or less at the...
My vitamins stack.
...beginning.
And anything which follows is celebrated either...
I don't forget to take it that way.
...on the stage.
...in the saucers or here at the campground.
Can you imagine me forgetting to take it?
One can imagine it so easily.
You can?
You can imagine me forgetting to take my vitamins?
To be confused.
Yes, it's happened to me.
Uh, bamboozled, uh, rocked, uh, distracted, uh, anything is possible.
I'm talking about vitamin fropped, though.
Vitamin F.
Which is actually vitamin H, as we know.
Vitamin C.
So, uh...
It's got vitamin A and vitamin C, vitamins L-O-V-E.
If you're fat, it's for that.
If you're thin, pack it in.
What's wrong if you're packing a triple drink?
We got the right ingredients, so let's proceed.
Time to get the fropp out, that's all we need.
Do you remember that show we did about, uh, Colonel Sanders?
That was a great show.
We had a lot of feeling, the measure of company.
Colonel Sanders.
Then we give it to the ladies.
We had a really good show.
Stir it up, stir it up, stir it up, stir it up.
You can hear that show on your own if you want.
Boy, boy, boy, by Obe, Obe, eat them up.
It's on a, it's on a web page.
It's got vitamin A and vitamin C, vitamins L-O-V-E.
About the last three years worth of shows, maybe.
Yeah.
Three or four years worth of shows.
In an incessant queue.
Just try to stop it rumbling over you like a juggernaut.
Back when I was one of the main stars.
An iron shod polygon.
That was the long-term special guest star.
Hal was there, he was the long-term guest co-host.
I was there to co-host and make classic commentary.
Yeah, we were like wrestling, you know, one of us was the color commentary guy
and the other guy's the guy that sides with the other guy.
Yeah, he was the heel.
Wrestling women versus the Aztec mummy.
I think you know how that one turned out.
I sure do, Hal.
Often on the...
That Aztec mummy lost his Johnson in that one, I think.
Yes, terrible, humiliating come down for him, but that's what happens.
Those Lucadora babes are really hefty.
That happens to all those guys.
Here's what's going to happen.
If your body is languishing around the world for way, way, way past your doorstep,
you're dying.
The piece of crumbling...
Somebody's going to cut your Johnson off eventually.
It would have fallen off anyway because he's this crumbling Guanajuato-esque...
That's what they did.
They did that to the Iceman, remember?
The guy, they found the Iceman...
Well, that was cruel.
They tore his genitals off, but it was an error.
It was a mistake in that case.
Oh, okay.
I thought he was missing one.
Well, after they ripped him out of the ice, they left his tackle behind.
Oh, no.
The only reason he was missing his tackle, like from...
And it happened at some, you know, intermediate point in the past.
The only reason he was missing his junk is because of the careless way that the body
was removed from the ice by the original discoverer.
And, you know, we discoverers of ancient stuff really believe that not only the thing that
is found has information, but the immediate area where it's found, the place where it's
found, should also not be disturbed.
We call it the Lagerstadt.
They're smoking a...
The place where the body of the fossilized creature is found also is full of information,
which we can learn.
They're smoking vapes.
They're smoking vapes?
Why not?
I'd like to do some vapes sometime.
Well, you just have to get the attention of those vape-smoking characters down there,
and maybe they'd come up and...
Sounds great in here.
Yes, that's right.
We got a good mix here.
So, maybe...
Thanks to Reverend Stang's...
We could have a vape here for...
...unbelievably...
Dr. Drummond wants to vape with the best of them, and now Reverend Mother Dr. Miller
is approaching the podium with the special Vape Master 9000.
Now, this thing is super powerful, and I wouldn't want to...
Oh, what's this?
One for me?
Oh, it's my pen.
Yes, well, that also is dangerous.
Yes.
So, I'll press the button and suck it up.
I'll suck it up, but a little too far, and you'll start hacking in the coffin.
It's not the cough that carries you off.
I'm going to go get my device to stare at while I do this.
All right.
He's going to get his stereo device for staring, and...
My staring device.
I see.
All right.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Love you very much.
Made you a real good sandwich.
Bottle of beer?
Yeah.
Had cheese and bologna on garlic bread, a little mayonnaise, horseradish mustard.
How's that sound to you, Joe?
I'm not sure.
It's a very good meal, but I'm out.
Thank you.
I'll just have a bowl of soup at the apartment.
Thanks anyway.
Now, what band could that possibly be?
Was that U2 or Aerosmith?
I fooled you.
It was the Rudy Schwartz Project, a song called Hunky Dunkey off that new album Postal Code
for Ham.
And I'm still using my phone's video camera as a microphone and mixer.
If you could see the video, you'd be looking right up my nostril in full HD.
A lot of stalactites up there, huh?
Carl's bad.
Anyway, obviously, praise Bob, Philo sent me the recordings he made with Dr. Hal and
Anna Moll at Tarzan's Radio.
I'm going to have to go to the radio station at the 21X Day celebration in Ohio, which
I had to miss while driving back to Texas in a big hurry in a rented car with the dog.
And in Texas, it was 109 degrees today.
Anyway, we also heard lots of lemur cut-ups and PR news.
And that bit with the old man playing two old ladies.
And the other bit he's talking dirty was from the audiobook of Heretics of Dune by
Frank Herbert, which audiobook I heard most of while driving south on I-71, 65, 40, 30,
and briefly 35E.
On the other hand, at least Buddy and I were in air conditioning the whole time, unlike
these guys.
Wine press of love.
Eastward.
Right to the desert of Golgolooza, before the seat of Satan.
Luva laid the foundation and Urizen finished it in howling woe.
How red the sons and daughters of Luva!
Here they tread the grapes, laughing and shouting.
Drunk with odors.
Many fall o'erwearied.
Drowned in the wine is many youth and maiden.
Those around laid them on skins of tigers or of the spotted leopard.
or the wild ass till they revive or bury them in cool grots making lamentation.
This wine press is called War on Earth.
It is the printing press of Loth and here he lays his words in order above the mortal brain
as cogs in a wheel are formed to turn the cogs of the adverse wheel.
Timbrels and violins sport round the wine presses.
The little seed, the sportive root, the earthworm, the gold beetle, the wise emmet dance round
the wine presses of Lotha.
The centipede is there, the ground spider with many eyes, the mole clothed all in velvet,
the ambitious spider in her sling.
The sullen web, the lucky golden spinner, the earwig armed.
The tender maggot, emblem of immortality.
They rejoice in loud jubilee dancing round the wine presses of Lotha, naked and drunk
with wine.
There is the nettle that stings with his soft down and there the indignant thistle whose
bitternesses spin.
The
But in the wine presses the human grapes sing not nor dance.
They howl and writhe in shoals of torment.
In fierce flames consuming the earth.
In chains of iron and in dungeons circled with ceaseless fires.
In pits and dens and shades of death.
In shapes of formant and wool.
The plates and screws and racks and cords and saws and fires and cinders.
The cruel joys of Lotha's daughters.
Lacerating with knives and whips their victims.
And the cruel sport of Lotha's sons.
They dance around the dying and they drink the howl and groan.
They catch the shrieks in cups of gold.
They hand them to one another.
These are the sports of love and these the sweet delights of amorous play.
Oh boy, special stickers.
This is not a pipe.
No, this is a sticker of a pipe.
Tears of the great.
The death sweat of the cluster.
In places where they're clear.
The last sign of the mild youth who listens to the luring song of Lotha.
And you make art by doing that.
Yeah, it's art.
When you stick a pipe on something, it's art.
Look at how much art you got.
So just stick a pipe on something and then you'll be churning out the art.
Art.
Bobart.
Banana, banana, Bobart.
Is this, we're giving these away?
Yeah, put a pipe on something today.
Never say you didn't do anything, huh?
I have one.
Those are great, yeah.
Are there any other mics, Philo?
We have how many mics available here?
How many mics did you use?
We have three mics.
Three mics.
Okay, this one then.
This is a usable.
Useful mic.
It is possible.
Try to speak in it.
See what it sounds like.
See if it comes out.
Say something.
Well, I noticed how you were talking about making another glory, but I've been dressing them up in suits.
Oh, well, yeah.
So they're kind of in suits to start with.
They're the ones they were born in.
We like their birthday suits is the idea.
It is a suit.
A suit of clothing and an identity.
All right, yeah, we're here.
You don't see show, you hear show.
Tarzan's radio station.
The show is in your mind.
She sells the seashells down by the seashore.
The shells she sells are seashore shells of that I'm sure.
I'm going to hook up my rig here.
Amidst the mists and coldest frosts.
He beats his fists against the posts.
And still insists he sees the ghosts.
Theophilus, the thistle sifter, sifted six thistles into the thick of his thumb.
See therefore that thou, when thou siftest thistles, sift not six thistles into the thick of thy thumb.
Or else you're going to get it.
Oh, uh.
Is this on?
So we're marking time a little bit here at Tarzan's radio station.
Now thank gobs and phylo drummonds perseverance.
All will be set right.
We will be sending out podcasts and an occasional odd cast.
Thanks to Reverend Stang's explicit instructions.
Oh, he left them written in the old book.
You know, we're not even finished with them yet.
How we're only on page two.
The secret of life and death.
By Henry Frankenstein here.
He tells how to do it.
Otherwise known as how I did it.
And it's rather simple.
Easy to follow.
It's like a cookbook.
We've got a lot more happening here at X Day 21.
Tomorrow is the assembly on the landing field itself.
Now the question is.
Now I know what.
What's that?
The question is where is the landing field this year?
Is it out here in front of Cofina's?
Or do we go all the way down to.
Old Sequaw's Turtle Mound and stand around out there.
We hike down the road in the early morning when the smoky dews are still rising.
You go down the road and you go off a little to the left.
This is on the way to the pond that one would normally go this way.
Only you don't go to the pond.
You stop at the field.
That's the way we've always done it.
Except.
When.
Stang shot that.
Drone.
Movie.
Right here outside of Cofina's.
Now perhaps by doing so.
He created a new.
Tradition.
And now we have to meet out here outside of Cofina's instead of at the.
So called landing field.
I don't know.
I'm asking.
I'm proposing.
I'm inquiring out of genuine curiosity.
All right.
We'll meet on the field.
That's always.
You know, somebody would always be there.
Anyway.
Someone would traditionalist would go there wherever we Johnny come lately.
Decided.
That we didn't want to have it.
So there it'll be.
I have to make our way all the way out there at 7 freaking o'clock.
A.m.
To the pond.
No to the to the field.
Yes.
The landing field.
No, it's not at the pond.
The baptism will be at the pond.
Now if you want.
Good.
Unmoving.
Unflinching description.
Of everything.
That's going to happen.
It's there in the brochure.
We're just going to follow that.
What time this that and the other happen.
I didn't get a brochure there.
Dr.
How well I'm sure there will be one given to you and you should go and get one from Princess Lee.
She would love to give you a brochure and I would love for you're going to need a brochure.
Now the brochure.
It was highly detailed instructions.
You know everything.
Is she is the.
Yes, kind of a pamphlet.
Well every year we have these brochures as we call them and inside.
Well, it's the wisdom of the ages Jack.
It tells you.
Yes.
A lot of money worth a lot of money on eBay.
Please forgive me.
Let me go.
Thank you for the pamphlet.
The flamphlet.
I hope you enjoy this scientific educational and instructive pamphlet.
I just got a new eyeball.
I'm supposed to be able to read now.
Another high ball and she's got an eyeball.
Audio recordings to a hard drive.
You speak or my laptop.
You never know what that little recorder is going to get lost or stolen or left in the rain.
The recordings will be lost and not backed up.
Once I thought I don't know how to do it.
I would have to do it.
Let it wrap.
I didn't do high.
Cogglera.
Me speed.
Read.
Snaps.
Norum.
Cut out his abdomen.
Or.
I will do that.
But now.
After that.
I will do that.
But I will do that.
Now you see Dr.
Drummond.
And furthermore.
Those will do another.
Now looming.
And imminence of the alien landing is depriving him temporarily of his ordinary three-dimensional
realism and reason.
Now he's thinking multi-dimensionally.
If we could only understand.
What a revelation folks.
Okay.
I'm going to tell.
I'm going to send a text to Reverend Stang.
Telling him that we have got the sound going.
We haven't done the video yet.
Well, this is a start.
Like one flickering candle flame.
So shines a good deed in a naughty world.
Yes, we shall begin.
And on the basis of those service.
If they should ask a thousand years.
What was the finest hour of the old X-Day convocation?
They should say it was this.
X-Day 21.
When staying was unable to attend his own party like Moses unable to enter the promised
land because of his appropriation of the divine power which animated him to bring water out
of the rock for the troublesome quarrelsome children of Israel.
And so it was just as in the old days as told by the old man in the boat.
By the wine dark sea.
Wadi doodah.
No, it strikes me that there's an interesting anecdote that encapsulates this whole thing.
But mainly it's that no one never expects what cards when it's going to be dealt.
But what if one is developed a bum hand?
This is phenomenon.
We've often discussed.
We say.
Surf the luck plane.
Be like Bob.
Bob always serves the luck plane.
Be an art bomb.
You don't have to work.
You can surf the luck plane.
But one thing we will also say is that when you're surfing, you're going to wipe out every on there.
I'm like, Bob.
Bob won't wipe out.
But you will definitely be this thing's crunching man.
It's peaking.
It's scrunched along really like going nuts ground along the shingle.
Once I start peaking, you know, it's all downhill after that.
It's all held by large crabs now held under by tons of water.
All of it.
Hey, are you peeking yet?
Yeah.
Well, anyway, this will happen.
But the thing to do is get back up on your board and put on your Bob like so.
Or as Lola Montez said courage and shuffle the cards.
Courage.
Yes.
So you got a bad hand.
So shuffle them again.
How's courage?
You can shuffle your way.
Out of that one.
Of course, it didn't help Lola that much in her later years.
But in her early years, he was the toast of four continents and famous for stripping naked in front of the Mad King of Bavaria Ludwig.
A lot of things.
He did were remarkable for her time.
She gained titles of nobility and maybe.
She was also viewed as a proto subgenius of which there are many.
There are proto subgenius and we've run programs about like Basil Wolverton.
Is there anybody would say Basil Wolverton was not a proto subgenius?
I say that all the time.
You say he was not.
I say a lot of things.
He of course, he was nominally supposedly some sort of fundamentalist Christian, but even that couldn't contain.
The original weirdness and bizarreness of his ideas.
Did he name himself Basil?
Yes, his name was Basil Wolverton and he lived way out in the hinterlands.
So when they wanted a horror comic, he would draw the whole thing and sent it in.
So it his style was not smoothed over into the house style.
It always looked like his own bizarre artwork.
My God.
He's got a lot of
his illustrations of the Bible.
They've been printed.
I think by Fantagraphics, but he drew a series which allegedly illustrate the book of Revelation.
People actually would and they show a horrible nuclear war.
I don't have my pants down like that.
People burned and starving and bodies piling up and the end of the world.
I like mine way up high.
Extraordinary vividness.
Way up high where you know your package is right there.
With his usual cartoony vigor and thick line.
You know what I'm saying?
I'm just, you know, I'm just being real.
Other times he drew grotesque faces and goofy cartoons with oddball shapes, faces and bodies.
But he was a realist.
The sad thing, of course, is that these shadowy beings are not only the figments of imagination of cartoonists attempting to find a way out of their own personal predicament, but an actual reflection of the mysterious malignancy of the cosmos.
For example, everybody.
Are you talking about?
Are you?
What are you talking about?
Well, it's going to mysterious malignancy of the cosmos.
Well, I was going to segue to.
Talk about the guest list for X-Day.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, segue to that.
That's the malignancy.
You know the woman I'm talking about or the women, the two-headed woman, the two-headed girl who has been around for a long time.
When she was a baby, she was on Oprah.
Later on, Time Magazine published a diagram.
I remember her.
A cutaway of her, of how everything works.
Well, recently this other child has come to life.
And this is.
A one-headed, two-bodied child.
That is, the one head has two bodies which issue from it.
And the loving parents are raising them up.
This was profiled in the New York Times Magazine with a cover story.
A strange misshapen head with its many eyes and two mouths.
But the children are laughing.
They seem to be having a good time as they crawl.
Like some eight-legged being around.
Now, they have this.
They have this worked out.
Their locomotion is all worked out.
With the two-headed girl, one interesting thing is the left head controls the left side of the body and the right head the right side of the body.
So when they take a step, the left and right have to be in coordination.
And they are.
It doesn't bother them a bit.
They run around, you know, naturally.
Even though each head.
Each head is contributing to the nervous impulse.
The body of the two-headed teenage girl, who by now must be at least a college-age girl, or perhaps married, or maybe even married and divorced.
I think she dropped out.
Is large because the upper body of the girl contains two spines, two hearts, four lungs, and two tracheas.
All descending into one digestive system and one reproductive system.
In the part of her body which is below the waist.
Her shoulders have a great width because of all this extra equipment which nature has put in there.
I'm so lucky that she gets to carry it with her wherever she goes.
I have to keep mine in a box.
Well, she's more lucky than this one-headed, two-bodied kid who was in the Times.
I haven't read the article yet.
I have it.
But I just haven't got around to reading it.
But I skimmed it.
And they put her picture on the cover of the Times.
The cover of the Times Sunday magazine had this one-headed, two-bodied kid.
Two bodies?
Yes.
Wow, that's got to be confusing.
The big head and then the bodies.
Yes.
Especially if you were going to say you were going to fight.
They crawl around in coordination with all their limbs are coordinated.
It might be really good if you could get them all going and coordinated.
They do.
Now, just as in the case of the two-headed girl whose name I don't know.
And maybe they've been keeping the name more or less clandestine.
She has many names.
In the case of two-headed beings, one head always dominates.
The other head is always the weaker.
Otherwise, there's an impasse.
Did you ever see that movie, Basket Case, where a guy had two heads and cut one of them off and it lived in a basket?
Well, yes.
That was a classic, you know.
There was a human separation.
But, of course, there was also the human.
The thing with two heads.
If you remember, Ray Moland and Rosie Greer.
An unfortunate operation.
And then the incredible two-headed transplant.
In addition, other movies which have featured the perfusion or separation but in continuing animation of a human head are The Head.
A very unusual German movie with surprising nudity and bizzare in it that I recommend.
And, of course, everybody knows.
The Brain That Wouldn't Die.
Also called The Head That Wouldn't Die.
And it doesn't.
Until the end.
Yes, in a terrible fire.
But she cackles maniacally.
Not being desirous of the gift of life.
But, you know the situation there.
The guy is saving the head and he's meanwhile going out and casing the script clubs for script strippers.
And he wants to find one with a good enough body.
To lure her home and transplant the head of his sweetheart onto her.
And he does take some women back and drug them.
But things never work out as they are supposed to.
But in The Head, not only is the stripper's body taken and the severed head of the girl put on it.
But it's a perfect combination.
And the girl is great.
And she feels great.
And everything is fine.
And there is no ridiculous punishment written into the script.
Another reason that movie is totally bizarre.
It's unfortunate.
This other woman had to die.
But at least I've got a body back.
And it looks pretty good too.
In The Head.
When I was a tot.
A toddler.
A child.
Maybe not a child.
Well, longer.
Older than a child.
A preteen.
A tween.
I saw in Famous Monsters of Filmland.
A picture of The Head.
From the movie of the same name.
This was the head of the German actor Michael Oud.
Who had been a pioneer in perfusion.
In removing heads of animals and people.
And keeping them alive.
It's all based upon Russian research.
And the original article which is called The Perfusion of a Living Head.
Starting with the heads of dogs and other experimental animals.
But then according to the folklore and legend.
Actually performed in secret.
The attempt to prolong a life.
By providing a blood supply.
And frame.
And cellular nutrient.
And other things.
To keep a head perfused.
Which is to say.
Continuing to go.
Even though not supported by its parent body.
Others have said.
Some of these people suffered.
Death.
When the head decayed in the ordinary way.
Despite the unnatural activity.
Provided it by the mechanism.
What are the other experimental animals?
I didn't know dogs were experimental.
Well they are in Russia.
They were when they sent Laika into space.
First the Ruskies sent Sputnik.
Then they sent Mutnik.
They sent a dog up there.
And not just one.
Various dogs.
But we sent dogs.
And we sent monkeys.
Up.
And not all of them made it back.
To tell the truth.
Some are still orbiting the earth.
Frozen dog sickles.
And monkey cubes.
They could show up tomorrow.
They could fall back down into the atmosphere.
Probably will eventually.
Their orbits will decay.
Let's hope ours will not decay.
Our planet's orbit.
We don't want it to decay.
They went to space and decayed.
So we wouldn't have to?
Well they.
Are all following that.
Newtonian mechanics.
When something is in orbit.
It is constantly falling.
Toward the parent body.
But because of the mechanics.
The parent body is not there.
When they would strike it.
But eventually they probably will strike it.
As the orbit decayed.
And we are told.
To believe.
A false picture.
That we have a solar system.
With a sun in the middle.
And planets going around.
And around that.
In circles or ovals.
This is quite wrong.
Because.
Let's remember here.
Our central star.
The sun.
And a remarkably steady star it is too.
Is also in motion.
And trucking along.
At a great rate of speed.
Throughout our portion of the galaxy.
Which it circles.
Once every 325 million years.
I believe.
Now.
As the sun.
Chugs along.
The planets.
Are essentially describing.
A spiral.
As they.
Circle.
Just the way everything here.
When you break it down.
Is a spiral.
A spiral of DNA.
The spiral of extended.
Molecular structures.
Where because of the constant infusion.
Of energy.
The usual.
Entropic rules.
Are not.
Enforced.
That's right.
It's supposed to run down.
But it's not going to.
As long as.
We are getting.
Princess Wei.
Please come to the main.
Mane.
Stage.
And that's what we need.
Not the main.
Stage.
The main.
Stage in here.
On this.
Main.
Stage over here.
This planet.
This bleeding earth.
That we are about to lose.
To the.
Exist.
Invasion.
This earth.
Of ours.
This island.
Earth.
Has been.
An ideal.
Place for life.
And it can't take all the credit.
Because.
Our sun.
Is unusually.
Steady.
And does not suddenly.
Get hot.
Or expand.
Or send.
Sleeting.
Radiation.
To some degrees.
It does.
But not in such a way.
That would hurt.
And then all sorts of.
Junk.
All sorts of.
Crap.
Comes.
At us all the time.
And the sun.
Is charging.
Along.
And the sun.
Can take us.
Into a bad.
Neighborhood.
Full of.
Space.
Junk.
Which.
Threatens.
Our planet.
But does it reach us?
Usually it doesn't.
Because.
We have.
Huge gas.
Giants.
We have.
Jupiter.
Pulling.
That stuff.
Away.
And it doesn't.
Bother.
Our.
Small.
Rocky.
World.
Because of this enormous.
Gravitational.
Well.
Back.
In our.
Area.
Our.
What do you say.
You mean.
Us.
Like.
I mean.
The humans.
On earth.
Me and you.
I mean.
Has been.
Steady.
But the sun.
Could.
Of course.
Flare up.
And the sun.
Will.
Just.
When it.
Exhausts.
Its.
Nuclear.
Furnace.
Will.
Expand.
To a large.
Size.
A size.
Which.
Actually.
Includes.
The.
Orbits.
Of the.
Planets.
Inner.
System.
Including.
The earth.
Mercury.
Venus.
Earth.
And.
Mars.
Will be.
Absorbed.
Into.
The solar.
Disc.
This is.
Before.
It.
Shrinks.
But.
Still.
The.
Procedure.
Will.
Be.
Difficult.
Another.
Thing.
That's.
Kept.
Us.
Going.
For.
So.
Long.
Besides.
Our.
Steady.
States.
Sun.
And.
You.
Know.
All.
The.
Suns.
In.
The.
Galaxy.
Don't.
Act.
Like.
That.
Some.
Of.
Them.
Flare.
Become.
Protos.
And.
Suns.
Sink.
Do.
All.
Sorts.
Of.
Things.
We.
Also.
Have.
A.
Giant.
Large.
Moon.
Larger.
In.
Proportion.
Than.
Any.
Other.
Planet.
I.
Will.
Not.
Include.
Pluto.
Because.
Is.
Considered.
A.
Dwarf.
Planet.
And.
Some.
Considered.
Cheron.
Pluto's.
Giant.
Moon.
To.
Be.
Part.
Of.
A.
Binary.
System.
That.
These.
Two.
Things.
Are.
Locked.
In.
This.
Day.
And.
We.
Have.
A.
Moon.
And.
That.
Means.
It's.
Constantly.
Pulling.
On.
The.
Waters.
Of.
The.
World.
And.
It's.
Not.
A.
Big.
Plastic.
Out.
Of.
The.
Ocean.
Plastic.
And.
We.
Put.
It.
In.
A.
Big.
Space.
Ship.
And.
We.
Shot.
It.
On.
To.
The.
Moon.
Well.
You.
Could.
Do.
That.
Now.
The.
Moon.
Is.
Covered.
In.
The.
Moon.
So.
You.
Can.
Get.
Out.
Of.
The.
World.
And.
The.
World.
Is.
Not.
A.
Plastic.
Of.
The.
World.
Of.
Plastic.
The.
World.
Of.
Plastic.
The.
World.
None.
Of.
The.
World.
Is.
A.
Plastic.
Of.
The.
World.
Is.
But.
A.
All.
Matter.
And.
in warfare, they're going to compete one way or the other.
Yes, if only they'd listened to we subgeniuses,
they would now be living in a veritable paradise
where the deer and the antelope play.
And seldom is heard a discouraging word
because what can an antelope say?
People would have time to walk in wearing long robes
that apparently were laundered every other week
and discuss philosophy.
The meaning of life and other Monty Python classics.
Dr. Drummond and Dr. Howell are such pros.
After 40 years of doing broadcast radio,
broadcast, mind you,
they didn't use offensive language once in this whole recording.
What fabulous instincts.
So noble.
So thanks to them, I was able to get this show out
before the week was out, unlike last episode.
I've had an unusual month.
Death in the family.
Death and a half, you could say.
And I'm a little shell-shocked
and feel like I'm in the Twilight Zone.
Speaking of which, there happens to be, naturally,
a rainmaker.
A rainmaker, generally.
that absolutely hits the nail on the head
regarding this Twilight Zone feeling.
It's from the album SKIN
and it's called A Million Miles Away.
Like more TikTok and altre fish slack stalks
There was a man named Jim who walked everywhere he went
Cause he could never quite seem to keep his mind on the road
One day it occurred to Jim that he'd taken a wrong turn
Cause he was standing in a place he didn't know
Jim spun on his heels thinking he'd backtrack for a while
But before he knew it, the sun was sinking
And the landscape in the dark, well it could have been New Zealand
Or New York or New Mexico
So what else is new, Jim was thinking
Cause see for a while now, Jim felt like things were changing for him
Like the skin of the earth was stretching or the continents were adrift
Jim didn't know if it was so or if it was just him
Although he suspected it was a bit of both he was dealing with
And he was thinking, well, I don't know
And I feel like I'm tripping
And I feel my steps slipping today
Feel the winds of time whipping my coat around my legs
And I feel about a million miles away
guitar solo
Dawn broke
Jim awoke
He'd been sleeping on his feet
It was morning now
But a densely foggy day
Jim decided he'd just sit
And wait for the fog to lift
But when it didn't
It started up again anyway
Man, this is like the blind leading the blind
Jim thought
About that time
Down the road came this C&I dog
It was well fed
And had a collar
But no matter how loud Jim hollered
There wasn't any answer
So he walked on through the fog
All right, I'm lost
Jim said aloud
Although a bit begrudgingly
Like things might change
In light of this confession
He was both amazed and sour
That at this late date and hour
He might find himself in this situation
And I feel like I'm tripping
I feel my steps slipping today
Feel the winds of time
Whipping my coat around my legs
And I feel about a million miles away
A million miles
I feel about a million miles away
A million miles away
After walking through the haze
For another night and another day
Jim seemed to simply cease to exist
All his panic, hope and thoughts
Broke up into small dots
As he gave himself away into the mist
Back in the town where Jim lived
Sad to say he was never missed
And his name was never spoken again
It's awful, the truth
Out my window at night
I think I see Jim standing in the half light
Saying hurry up
Suffering's got a job to do
And I feel like I'm tripping
And I feel my steps slipping today
Feel the winds of time
Whipping my coat around my legs
And I feel about a million miles away
A million miles
I feel about a million miles away
derivate the purest of all
And if you're if you're if you're
While occasionally MB
I Forsch I Forsch
I Dj Sprach
Achtung
To take in
Plot
leadership
Because all the more we're here than ever to say, man!
listening to Tarzan's radio station here at X Day 21.
And we have some top flight radio personalities here.
What about this awesome music and this background music?
Isn't it just...
Yes, those are awesome bells in the background.
It's grooving.
Look, people are out there nodding their heads.
Well, you see, they are understanding.
The grooviness is just overwhelming.
They're taking over everything.
Everything, so much it is of what everybody wants
and where everybody wants to be.
What is that primary motivator in the affairs of human beings?
We've had many analyses over the years,
and many of them saying which would be considered
in the case of reversion to an infantile state.
This is the Freudian one.
It's all about, you know, the pleasures of the mouth
and the anus of possession of the infantile thing.
But, of course, even stronger than the sexual aspect of being a motivator,
there is another one which is scarcely mentioned often enough.
The desire for what has been called,
the inner ring.
The idea that nothing is more important
than getting into that inner ring of people
who really know the way things are
and being a member of that crowd
better than anybody else
because you're a member of the inner ring
and it's worth anything to get in there.
Whatever you do to anybody else,
to people you're supposed to love,
still, if you're in the inner ring,
you're where you want.
And this is a strong motivator
which has been a large part of human history
on our Teraqueous globe
right up till now.
So, I'm going to see if I can find a place
I can text Reverend Stang
and let him know that we actually did get
Tarzan's radio station working.
I like that, Philo,
but, of course, we made such an experimental attempt before
and it seems you can't get out of this benighted area
really easy.
But I'm not going to try to discourage you.
Please do go ahead.
Never say never.
So, about this inner circle,
I heard that there was a way to purchase membership
into an inner circle of some sort
that might give me access to such wonders
as a plastic-coated moon.
Well, you could, of course, form your own...
I'm telling you, that's the start of it.
You put the trash up there.
All this trash is just wasted.
And the ocean...
Accumulates.
You can pick it up and send it to the moon.
Status?
We could coat the moon in a complete plastic coating.
It would work as well for that as anything else.
A moon doesn't need a plastic coating, though.
It does have helium-3.
And they're going up to try to dig up some water.
A new expedition they've got going
to dig up the water from the lunar region.
And it's called the Eucalyptus Eucalyptus.
And that can happen.
Why would we want to take water from the moon
when we could be getting just the finest cheeses?
Also, aren't we busy mining diamonds off of comets or something?
No, not quite yet.
But it might happen.
We landed on a comet.
But the thing about the water,
if it's up there, you don't have to carry it up from here.
And weight is very important.
And if it's up there, you can make all sorts of things out of it, including...
fuel and air and all sorts of things.
Small fountains for your topiary garden.
Yeah, all sorts of things that you need there in Looneyville,
where Donald Trump's black uniformed space force
have their major headquarters in the giant dome.
From NPR News in Washington,
I'm up against another round of global racial injustice.
Authorities say they still don't know
what caused massive tax increases.
Authorities say the tax policy is unconstitutional.
Quote, it is about time.
The Dow is 18.
Authorities say this is PR News.
Thank you, Leimer, Filo, Hal, Anna, Maul, Cool Hand Chris,
the Rudy Schwartz Project, the Rainmakers, and everybody else.
More on the Church of the Sub.
More on at subgenius.com.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community