But let's leave things of this world behind
and walk now down the path of Bob
for this brief minute of slack
from the Church of the Subgenius.
Oh, yes, dear friends, this is Reverend Ivan Stang
and I'm afraid that our time has already run out.
Because, friends, a minute of slack
is all the slack the conspiracy is going to give you.
That's right.
In this world, you'll get a minute of slack
and almost 24 hours of false slack.
And how do you know the difference?
Because, friends, the real slack is free
even if it isn't always legal.
So it's sad that we only have one minute,
but it balances out in one great religious urge,
one great religious evacuation of the senses.
And I would recommend reading Prescription 1714 and 3691.
And, friends, we need blankets and contraceptives
for those boys and girls in the home for slackless children.
Your contributions also keep those we hate starving to death.
I command!
I command you to spill your gift seed pledge
of 100 pounds of dollar bills on my lap
as this will buy so much for those poor children.
Bob Dobbs will bless you for planting this seed faith
and now our announcer won't give you the mailing address
of the Church of the Subgenius.
Thank you and let there be slack.
Now we're heading into the sexual or gonadial area
of the Doug Smith brain.
As you can see, it has some similarity
to the previous portions of the brain and the typewriter area.
But the enormous stamina of this human.
There's someone else saying, hey, hey.
Yes, that's all the trigger the Smith brain needs
to get an enormous rise.
Hey, hey, hey.
All the voices of all the girls that he's put pleasure into.
They're yelling, staying, staying,
which is Doug Smith's alter ego.
The climax.
Can I say something?
This show is our only method of communicating with you Earth people.
In hopes that in the storm of Babel,
you will understand the basic reality of our method
and apprehend that we are not simply a comedy group
or a humorous exercise,
but actually the emissaries of a distant civilization
which only wishes to confer its own understanding
upon the citizens of your rather backward planet.
We thank you for listening.
How do they do?
Well, like this.
And like this.
Oh, no, not like that.
Ouch, that hurts.
No, cut it out.
Quit it.
And like this.
Oh, hey, hey, hey.
Yes, you'll see us enthroned in glory,
trailing clouds of glory and emitting the sacrosanct
echo of heavenly flame.
Like the gods we are.
Yes, that's our aura.
What, radio gods?
Yes, I think so.
You remember last time Carl Morgan wrested his own gun
from Julia Fairholme after duping her into thinking
there was a bluebird on her shoulder
when, in reality, it was an owl.
Today, it is the lovely Julia's turn
to attempt to dissuade the vengeful,
and the evil, and the evil, and the evil, and the evil, and the evil, and the evil.
And treacherous Carl from taking her life.
Let's listen.
Carl, what are you going to do?
That remains to be seen, Julia.
Now, I've got the gun, and the shoe is on the other foot.
What do you mean, Carl?
It's just an expression, Julia.
It means, uh, it means, well, you know,
like, uh, the tables are turned.
Tables?
What tables, Carl?
I don't see any tables.
Oh, no, no, no, Julia.
You don't seem to understand.
What I mean is, I've got the gun,
and you haven't.
See?
Before, you had, and I didn't.
So, now that I've got the gun, and you don't,
why, the shoe is on the other foot.
Or, the tables are turned, so to speak.
I love you, Carl.
Well, what's going to happen next time?
Don't fail to miss our next exciting episode,
when we'll hear Carl say...
No, no, no, Julia.
Not the tables are on the other foot.
It's the tables.
The tables are turned.
You remember last time,
Julia Fairholme was unable to understand
what Carl Morgan meant
when he told her the shoe was on the other foot.
Stop right there.
Intensifying our prospect's desires,
that's when the wheels of action begin to move.
Sorry for jumping in, doctors.
Go on.
Dr. Dobbs is known worldwide
as a foremost spokesman for Christian and family values,
so plan to attend this rare personal appearance
of Dr. Dobbs.
Even if you never intend to write your name again,
one sure way to impress folks
is to stay a little bit over their heads,
because it was better than looking stupid.
It's not true that we followed the circle
around and around and around,
helping to create a nice round world
of confusion and misunderstanding.
Well, we take our initiates
and we string a little tendon between their heels
and drag them three times around the radio station
before beginning.
Then we dip them in the sacred waters of the sludge.
And what exactly does this do for them?
Well, it causes them to forget everything they've learned
and it prepares their mind
for the slate-like impression,
the imprinting of the true subgenius.
Welcome, dear friends,
to the subgenius.
Genius hour of Slark.
Slark, Slark, Slark.
Yeah.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
Wow.
The message is now part of
and registered in your subconscious mind.
Every time you say, see, hear, or think.
That's your key phrase.
It will trigger the entire message without your being aware of it.
Repent. Quit your job.
Slack off.
Driven to the brink of false sanity by the conspiracy's false reality?
And the pressure of a crumbling world?
Then this may be for you.
Eternal Salvation.
Or triple your money back.
The Church of the Subgenius.
Bring you another 33.
Three minutes of condensed, eraglic functioning.
Over the quality audio-visual techniques.
Exacerbated and complicated.
By the Church of the Subgenius.
Copyright 1985-86.
Oh, Dr. Sprint.
She said.
Cutting her own legs off.
And what was to be the foment of a startlingly trend among the so-called punk de-tele-hensia.
Where they became not only skinheads, but took it to the next level and became boneheads.
Actually shaving off their hair scalp, cranial viscera, and the top three molecular layers of their...
BRAIN.
ITSELF.
nuclei.
Right now...
to the hairline zone of the brain,
the cause of the brain.
These are boDAHABS.
**SeeaD disclosed at root. Theание A. E.
Thou Omega Sống.
The啦-B distributes Fight Over F startups pitchers through the
Some of their picks did Liszt and part of them mad ads.
reported that subgenius bands have led to what are referred to as knee heads where the person's
body actually ends a scant two inches above the knee you might see a punk button uh sid lives or
a doctor's bob button on the lower half of the pants it hides the top of the spike boots which
protrude below all that's left of what was once a normal middle-aged boy until doctors for bob
the church of the subgenius got a hold of his brain via post office box 140306 dallas texas
seven five two one four
praise bob this has been the subgenius news hour
you're in
you are
Uh, yes, dear friends, this is your good shepherd and prayer partner, Reverend Ivan Stang, accompanied
tonight by, uh, let's give him a mic, accompanied tonight by, out with it, Buck.
I can't even tell if you're on mic.
Uh, he, Buck naked and, uh, and also the great Reverend Buddy West is here, friends, and
in the back.
Let's go give him a mic.
You know what, Buck, that, that microphone is not working.
You might look and see if you can find an on button.
Friends, this is, uh, this is, uh, Reverend Onan Canobite singing in the background.
And now, we had a question someone dared call the Subgenius Foundation, uh, with our secret
phone number.
Today on Easter Sunday, I can't believe people don't hold religious holidays sacred, but
I called up and wanted to know, um, whether...
You could get some of the music that we play on records, like for instance, this, this
B.O.B.
song by Dr. Onan Canobite, or the, uh, intro music we play by Mark Mothersbaugh and Buck's
songs and so forth.
And, well, friends, you can buy these things on tape, not on records, yet.
But, uh, see, here's the thing.
This is, this is a public radio station.
We can't get on the air and tell you about all the things that we sell.
Many of you did not know that the Church of the Subgeniuses is a public radio station.
This is not just airwaves, but printed matter, audio cassettes, videotapes, and live B-vibles.
But, uh...
You shouldn't tell them about it.
Shouldn't tell them about it?
It may be a conflict of interest, because maybe we're advertising our own selves.
Like, I don't want to tell anybody about my band, More Drunk Cowboy.
We're going to do a benefit concert there.
We're going to do a benefit for Aidstown.
We're going to send all the victims of the epidemic.
Aidstown?
Yeah.
And it's going to be at, at the Wyandale Tavern.
Uh, at the Wynedale Tavern.
At the first Saturday of this month and next month.
So that's April 5th and so on.
And May 3rd, I guess.
And then we're going to be at, uh, doing more benefits for Aidstown.
We're at the Stepladder.
Coming up next month.
And, uh, at the Profit Bar.
So we're going to be doing a lot of these benefits.
Alright.
Yeah.
Right.
Well, as long as you're not getting paid for it, then you can...
A little charity work.
We're doing it everywhere in town.
And, you know, you get a dime, you can bet.
Oh, yes.
But we're, we're getting all the, uh, we're getting Aidstown benefits.
Built.
That's the main thing.
You're just going to put them all together in one...
That's sick, man.
Well, hey, you know.
What can I tell you?
I mean, that's not funny.
There's people shriveling up with the subgenius virus all the time.
And, you know...
Well, then we shouldn't have released the virus if we didn't want to, you know.
I know.
It was the balloons, man.
If we hadn't been messing with those damn balloons at Doc's Dock, it would have been...
Well, anyway, friends...
It's not the balloons.
It's the suppositories, Stang.
That's what did it.
Don't talk about all of it.
Anyway, the, uh, uh, you know, uh...
Yes, you can get these tapes.
And that's why we read the box number, P.O.
Box 140306 Dallas, Texas 75214 at the end of every broadcast, friends, is so that you will
write for information and find out that you can get those tapes.
Now, this...
The music...
A lot of the songs that we're playing now, the newer subgenius songs are...
Sorry, Dr. Onan.
The newer subgenius songs are oftentimes...
Most of those are on the Ear of Bob tape.
The Ear of Bob tape, which was mentioned in your last pamphlet.
Those of you who are subscribing members got that one.
And, uh, let's see.
Well, here's a...
Here's a cut off the...
Well, Buck, what else?
Did you have something else to...
I'm stuffed with Easter dinner.
I've been...
I've had...
I've been on two Easter egg hunts.
I haven't ate all day today.
I've been fasting and whipping myself.
Oh, right.
And that's...
Yeah.
See, that's religion for you, friend.
You hurt yourself for God.
You know, I...
I've heard of this Prince of Peace stuff.
What a bunch of lies.
You know, look up Matthew 1032.
We'll read it to you some other night.
But just look up Matthew 1032.
Is that the bit about bringing the...
Not to bring the...
Yeah, bringing the sword and...
Yeah, not...
Well, I bring not a peace sign, but a nuke, a nuclear weapon.
Yeah.
Eat the Easter eggs.
Eat them.
Yeah, eat them Easter eggs.
Take the salt with you.
Well, friends, the Ear of Bob tape is a...
Is a beautiful tape crammed with...
I do have one thing I did want to bring out to our listeners.
We'd like a call in on this subject tonight.
Okay.
Anybody who had a religious experience at the Twilight Room last night, we'd like to
hear from you, if you know what I mean, and I think you do.
Uh-oh.
Give us a call at the station and we'll discuss that a little more as we get on with
the evening.
God, I'm so out of it.
I never got...
I don't know what these guys are talking about.
It was probably great.
And I missed it.
Why?
The work...
Give us the phone numbers.
Phone numbers.
Oh, the phone number of the station here is 823-7490, dear friends.
That's 8...
Or...
823-8801.
Or 823-8883.
Our expert phone interceptor, Reverend Bloody Vest, will get your call.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
And this is Reverend Jim Erickson of Glass Madness doing that great old interception.
And this is rather an old subgenius hymn, Hello, Bob.
Hello, Bob.
I need someone to talk to.
Seems there's nothing I can do.
Hello, Bob.
I need someone to listen to me.
I'm hitting all the maiden's subs Mitt.
locked doors and I need some help and I was hoping you'd have the key.
Hello, Bob.
Have you been listening to my thoughts?
And I'll tell you all the thoughts I've got.
Hello, Bob.
I can't seem to find the truth.
I read the books, I took the drugs, and I drank a whole bottle of Relu.
Yeah.
Hello, Bob.
I seem to have misplaced my slack.
Well, I just can't seem to get it back.
Hello, Bob.
Can you point out what it is I lack?
I've climbed to highest heights, hit the lowest lows, but now I'm on my back.
Hello, Bob.
Are you still hearing me?
Give me a sign that I can see.
Hello, Bob.
It's not that I've lost all my hope.
But I'm really tired and I'm really broke and I smoked up the last of my dope.
Now that I'm heat shit, I've just got to look hard.
Hello, Bob.
Robbery's a mission to you and it's your fault.
Dig me a pink!
Am I comin...
through to you??
Hello Bob.
audio brush Pi Poop ebook sometimes Mais crime several times...
Crushing CPU
I thought I already paid all my dues.
Hello, Bob.
I know that you can see me through.
But it's damp and dim and I can't swim.
What am I supposed to do?
Well, hello, Bob.
I'm feeling better.
Now you listen to me.
Hello, Bob.
Well, the sun's out now.
Now I can see.
Hello, Bob.
A great change has come over me.
My eyes are wise.
My thoughts are clear.
And I'm as happy as I could be.
Yes, my eyes.
My thoughts are clear.
And I'm as happy as I could be.
Oh, yes, friends.
That was Glass Madness.
By the way, Glass Madness will be in town doing a glass show
at the Glass Convention here in Dallas in April.
But I don't think he'll be singing about Bob then
because they put you in jail for doing that out on the street corners.
It happened to me once.
So anyway, here's this in continuation of the old,
old-timey Hinton Buck, unless you've had something you wanted to infect their minds with.
Come on, let's talk about what happened at the toilet room last night.
Anybody been there?
823-7490.
Help me, somebody.
This is Doctors for Bob with one of their unusually quieter tunes,
Legs of Fire.
All right, ladies and gentlemen,
this song introduces a new genre in country and western music.
We call it gospel.
It's gospel music for people who know they're going to hell anyway.
It's a little thing called Legs of Fire.
OK.
Well, I thought I could get away with saunter on our wedding day.
Preacher Man said, boy, better put away your song.
But I said, I don't cotton to no God's county law.
But that song was stolen.
At least that's what they said.
So I wrapped up in asbestos from my waist up to my head.
I wrapped up in asbestos that I got from Greg's.
I only wish I had enough to cover up my legs.
So I've been sinning, sinning, sinning.
But I ain't no liar.
I'm burning, burning, burning.
Got Legs.
Got Legs of Fire.
Oh, my head's dry and cool.
So's my arms and tool.
My torso, even more so.
But I ain't no liar.
Now I'm burning, burning, burning.
Got Legs.
Got Legs of Fire.
Well, I was selling heroin at the elementary school.
Preacher Man said, boy, you know that isn't cool.
The good Lord.
Come to me.
Said my time was up.
When I asked why I got, he said, because that horse was cut.
They were shooting up in the bathroom.
Yes, you know it's true.
But they were not getting off.
And that's why my soul is through.
Oh, I've been sinning, sinning, sinning.
But I ain't no liar.
Now I'm burning, burning, burning.
Got Legs.
Got Legs of Fire.
Oh, my brain ain't in no flame.
And my shoulders are burning.
Fear in my mind is neither
nor one's heat, or rain.
I was breaking all the Inflammas.
She's calling me all this.
Cesare Asimov talked , like a absolutely disposable addiction sp complaining about the
same-sex relationships – Justin Durkheim.
CJте, I wanted to destroy my program Cause, Concentration, Medicine .
The door was dented in
Oh, I've been sinning, sinning, sinning
But I ain't no liar
Now I'm burning, burning, burning
Got legs, got legs, got legs afire
Oh, my head ain't on the line
And my arm is doing fine
But my knees are trying, please
But I ain't no liar
Now I'm burning, burning, burning
Got legs, got legs, got legs afire
Well, I was bashing Grandma's head
With a railroad tie
The good Lord come to me
And said, why did you lie?
When I said, why lie?
He said, you must confess
That ain't your Grandma's head at all
It's just a bloody mess
Oh, I've been sinning, sinning, sinning
But I ain't no liar
Now I'm burning, burning, burning
Got legs, got legs, got legs afire
Oh, I've been sinning, sinning, sinning
What happened?
You got the line up?
Hello, dear caller
Dear caller
No, Miss Lane is gone
Here, head on
Oh, yeah
Dear friend
Hello?
Hello, caller
He's gone
He's lost him
Oh, but his soul has ascended to caller heaven
Listener heaven
Where the Lord is
Poor, poor listeners who never make it through to this show.
They've been instructed to call back.
Yes.
I'd like to hear from somebody about that darned toilet room bust last night.
And friends, in the meantime, well, later on, we're going to be reading.
We're going to try it again.
We got them back.
Oh, shall we?
Okay.
Let's go ahead and do it here.
Let's show up.
Hello, dear caller.
Hello.
Dear caller.
You are on the air.
He can hear us, but we can't hear him.
Why?
I can hear him breathing on the other end.
Listen to that.
The breather call?
Yeah.
See that?
Chicken!
They're afraid to mess with the wrath of Bob, and that's probably wise.
We've got positive proof now that Bob is not dead, so we can stop worrying about that.
That's right.
Finally cleared up this nonstop dogmatic...
dogmatic battle that the Docs have been beating each other over the head with the last three
years.
Well, well, there's...
You don't have any hard proof exactly that Bob is resurrected from the dead.
Oh, yeah.
Re-erected.
Re-erected stag.
Yeah, that's a little different from a straight... your straight old-time resurrection.
These new re-erections, kind of more 80s, kind of more permissive kind of deal.
The 80s.
Yeah.
Well, friends, it's just a matter of faith, really.
We don't...
We...
Every subgenius.
Has a...
Has had cause to feel that...
That great man with the pipe, the great salesman who will buy our planet back from the conspiracy...
Well, we've been getting mail from Bob.
He's back alive.
I've been getting mail personally.
I'm on Bob's mailing list again.
Bob's mailing list, not the church's.
But I want to tell you all something.
If there wasn't a Bob, wouldn't we have to invent him?
So, it doesn't matter.
Whether Bob is here or not.
Because, see, he's Bob.
He's got to be here.
So, therefore, there's got to be a Bob.
And there is a Bob.
And...
This is the logic, friends.
This is the ultimate logic of JR.
The crystalline, clear logic of Slack.
Well, they're too lazy.
Well, look.
Enemies of the subgenius that you...
Just the pinks.
The normals.
The conspiracy.
The mediocrities.
Well, what...
What is the conspiracy?
It's 20th century traditions.
It's the old traditions.
It's all the things that got us where we are now.
It's Christ without a penis.
He's part of the conspiracy.
It's presidents that don't look like they're capable of getting erections anymore.
That's the conspiracy.
That's just the way it is.
It just didn't happen.
It would appear that the government at the moment is...
is practicing a lot of this religion in absentia for many folks.
It was a trendy thing.
Well, we're actually the conspiracy...
You've always heard of the conspiracy, right?
Yeah.
Well, we're the conspiracy behind the conspiracy.
And we've decided to come out in the open.
You're the unnamed source.
That's us.
One of them.
Well, you've certainly heard of the Public Cretanization Society.
The conspiracy has been trying to squelch abnormality since time began, practically.
It goes so far back and is so ingrained in our culture that it's gotten to where the conspiracy leaders don't have to do anything
because it's an endless cycle of normalcy.
Kids are, even kids with latent subgenius genes are born, but they're raised by the conspiracy,
making them want to be popular, raising them to be happy with mediocrity, with everything being the same.
I am now learning to apply creative and corrective procedures and to bring back to normalcy and a state of perfection
any abnormality or imperfection found within any given manifestation of matter, any given plane, any given depth.
I can easily do anything that I want to do. I can. I can.
I'm okay.
I'm a winner.
Pursuant to Section 28A, Article 4B, Paragraph 2 of the Internal Security Regulations,
I now hand over to you rejected applicate number 578293BO21.
I fell right on his face.
Yeah, life sucks.
I've had it up to here.
Shut up.
I hate myself.
I hate everyone else.
I'm not done.
Can you hear me? What the heck is going on out here anyway?
I need to talk to Bob.
Bob.
Friends, it seems like somebody here does indeed need to talk to Bob.
Let's go ahead and try to get him in here.
See what happens.
Hit that.
Ah, yes, dear friend.
This is the app.
It's blinking again.
Start it.
Hello?
Yes.
Oh, yes.
I mean, would like to order on large pizza.
What?
Wait a minute.
You want to order a pizza?
This must be the wrong call.
Oh, wait a minute.
No.
There's too many of everything.
Um, okay.
And what is your...
Don't put the little feces on it.
The little feces?
No feces?
No, no, uh, anchovies, I think.
No, I think you said feces.
Well, I know, but...
Okay.
Uh, what's your address?
And we'll, we'll deliver that.
We'll deliver it through the mail.
Okay.
It's to go.
Uh-huh.
Twenty minutes?
Oh, probably.
Give us half an hour.
Oh, okay.
No, no, no.
The mail takes two weeks.
Okay.
Well, thank you very much.
Well, wait a minute.
You didn't give us your address.
Oh.
Because we'll, we'll be down there in just a little while, as soon as this pizza show
is finished cooking.
Do you mind if your, uh, pizza, the little kind we got is one that's in the shape of
Bob's head, Bob's face?
Bob?
You want a little Bob face pie?
A Bob face pie?
Is that...
Yeah, man, a Bob face pie.
This is a real pizza.
Is that a new thing that, that you have?
Yeah.
That's the, the Bob pizza.
Uh-huh.
And there's a Ger, Gerbrogfran pizza also, which is much more expensive.
It's a $15 for the large.
The Gerbrogfran, the Bob is only $10.
And it's our most popular pizza.
Oh, okay.
So, what is your address?
At our cheap, cheapest pizza, if, if you eat that, your face becomes the next pizza.
Do you want a large or a medium or a small or how many?
Oh, uh, let's see.
I'll take two small ones.
Two small Bob pizzas.
Yeah.
And what is your address?
2111 Commerce.
Oh, he lives at the Twilight Room.
Oh.
Yeah, he got busted last night.
This guy still has to stay there.
This guy lives in the parking lot.
This is the man from the parking lot.
No, I don't live in the building.
I live in the parking lot.
Don't you have to keep your hands on the car all the time?
Oh, never mind.
We'll get to the next caller.
Thanks a lot.
Okay, bye-bye.
.
Friends, we're going to try one more time here.
One more little phone call.
Uh, yes.
Hello, dear friend.
Hello.
You're...
Oh, they're not on the air.
I hate it.
Oh, you know who it is?
They're using it on the other line there.
Well, only one thing to do.
There are weapons that are simply thoughts.
Attitudes, prejudices.
To be found only in the minds of men.
There is no typical subgenius.
There's no profile subgenius.
The subgenius is the person who is an outsider,
who has been different some way or another since birth.
A person who is born with slack.
And we're all born with slack.
Original slack.
But the conspiracy, the conspiracy of normalcy, really, is what it is.
It takes it away from the minute you...
are born.
They give you that first whack on your behind to make you cry.
From that moment on, they're taking away your slack.
He was alive one minute, then he was dead.
Can't be.
Why not?
There must have been a reason.
They can't...
They couldn't just barge in here and drag him away.
No reason.
What right do they have?
Catch you twenty-five.
Catch you twenty-two.
Catch you twenty-two, friends.
That's always the reason.
And it's pretty demonic, alright.
We're gonna try to get this caller in.
Hello, caller.
Hello?
God, it's on hold.
Remember?
Why can't I get this guy on?
He was talking to him out there.
Oh, okay.
He doesn't want to be on the air.
Well, friends...
Apparently, we've got someone who has called in and is praying for friends of...
of those associated with this show because they think it's a demonic, satanic show.
Friends, I think it's preaching time, as a matter of fact.
It's time for preaching!
This is time.
Let me put on some decent preaching music here.
And, friends, I'll tell you what.
Those out there in Dallas, Texas who happen to believe that this subgenius show is somehow
satanic, I'll tell you what, my friend.
Has it ever occurred to you that there might be more than one Jesus, for instance, a right
Jesus, that wants you to be a happy person?
And a false, satanic, devil, poltergeist Jesus that likes to get into people's heads
and make them make themselves miserable because, friends, that's what makes the Lord miserable.
Yeah, I guess that never occurred to some people out there, but let's go ahead and...
Shall we try to...
I think we got you there.
Yeah.
You got the last rant, Steve.
Huh?
We got the last rant.
We got that last rant.
Let's see what happens here.
We've got somebody on line one here.
They're going...
Hello, line one.
Hello?
Hang up line one, anybody out there.
You're on the air.
Hello?
Yes.
This is John, isn't it?
This is John.
Welcome to K-N-O-N, John.
Well, I'm John.
Am I really on the air?
Yes.
This is not a trick.
It's not a falsehood.
It's the truth, huh?
You bet.
Oh, okay.
Squirt it out, guy.
We've got a big show here.
Well, I just got in on the show.
I don't really know what's going on for sure.
Who does?
What'd you say?
Well, I just called up to talk.
I want to talk to whoever's on the radio.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, you're on the radio now.
Okay, I'm on the radio.
Who's the reverend whatever?
That's me, Buck.
That's you?
Yeah.
Are you an ordained minister?
Yes, sir.
Legal marriages and all that.
Oh, do you really?
Yes, sir.
You got a sweetie?
A what?
Yeah, I got one.
A girlfriend?
Or is it a wife?
It's my wife.
Well, then if you want to get remarried, then I'll handle it for you.
What?
That's just a little joke.
That's a little joke there, you know.
Okay.
Well, listen here.
I just called up to find out where you got this religion at, you guys.
Well, this...
We picked it up in bits and pieces all around the world.
You know, Bob, ever since he was a little boy in his parents' home, just with his parents' books,
he spent all his time looking for the good parts.
He went through the Bible.
He went through the vision.
He went through the Dead Sea Scrolls.
He went through the...
He went through Marvel Comics, Doctor Strange.
That's right.
He went through...
The Book of Mormon.
He went through the ancient Atlantean scrawlings and all that.
And he took the good parts, friends.
It's like this religion is like a monster patched together out of the pieces of dead religions
and brought to shambling unholy life of its own.
So, do you have a comment on this, sir?
Well, that's pretty shocking to me.
Why?
Huh?
Well, he's into it.
He's into it.
How is that any different from most of the other religions in this country?
It's different from all of them.
Well, yeah, I know.
But at the same time, they're all composed of...
I mean, the word of God may have been broadcast at one point,
but it's been filtered through an awful lot of greedy human minds, my friend.
He knows that.
This man is awake.
What do you say?
I say, you are awake.
You are listening to us.
You are listening to us with both glands.
Well, listen, the reason I called is...
Yes, John.
Huh?
Well, the reason I called is because I just kind of wanted to know what acts you had to grind
with what religious group burned your brain or what.
Which one offended you or did all of them?
No, not that.
As a matter of fact, for me, this is Reverend Ivan Stangis.
Speaking personally, I'm into all the other religions.
In fact, we wouldn't be working so hard on this.
We wouldn't be working so hard on this one.
If we didn't think there was, you know, a certain amount of slack to be had from...
I've praised the other religions.
You know, Marlon Maddox is a regular listener of our slack.
Oh, really?
Yeah, Marlon Maddox himself is at home right now curled up with a wife and a cocktail.
Listen to a little good old Back to the Pamphlet, Hour of Slack.
Praise Bob.
Oh, really?
Yes, sir.
Well, that's too bad.
No, it's not too bad.
Do you not like slack?
Or is it that you don't know what slack is?
Well, I just...
All I know is what Jesus said.
That's all you know?
Yeah.
That's often the problem, see?
Well, yeah, the thing about it is Jesus said this.
You want to hear one thing he said?
Please.
Well, yeah, although I bet we've heard it before.
But then I'll tell you what Walter...
Hey, wait.
Let me tell you what Walter Chrysler said.
Not Jesus Christ, but Walter Chrysler.
This is no baloney.
Will you take this word off...
He said, check all three.
Thank you very much, and thanks for sharing that with us.
Buck, you censored that...
That fact.
You're a faithful listener.
Oh, I didn't censor.
We've heard...
I know.
They always use the same quotes on us, and those quotes were...
I don't know.
Friends, it's true.
This is the work of the devil.
If you're listening to this show, you are damned to hell for eternity.
It's too late.
It's too late to turn it off.
Don't say that.
Bob Larson's listening.
It's too late to...
I know.
It's...
Though the little sparrow in the tree, if it's listening to this show, is damned to
hell.
And, friends, I know it's not the fault of the listeners.
They didn't know...
Or the sparrow in the tree.
It's like the little kid...
Or the lightning bug.
It's like the little kid who's not baptized.
You know, he's gonna burn in hell, but...
And it's not his fault, but that's just the way it is, because that's what the word of...
Not Bob, but somebody else said, right?
I don't...
We don't think...
Things aren't really that bleak, folks.
Just remember, the normals will get blended into the plugs in the vats of the elder gods,
while the subgenie will careen off in new directions on death.
Oh, yes.
Praise Bob.
We don't need to hang around the bodies.
We squander in life.
We know what we do to them.
It's pretty awful when we think about all the extra food we dump in ourselves and all
the chemicals and...
But hey, no problem, because you've got new weirdness in Bob.
It's a...
Before death.
It's a beautiful, beautiful thought.
Ah, yes.
Let me give one more caller a chance to get on with it.
Okay, but I really want to get back to some tapes.
I'm tired of these amateur speakers.
Hello.
They didn't go to Columbia Broadcasting School like me.
Ha!
I know how to pronounce everything really cool on the radio with the low voice, you
know.
Oh, yes, dear friend.
Yeah, this is Reverend.
Uh-huh.
This is one of many.
Yeah, listen.
I just got the book, you know, and I was reading it.
Yes.
And tell me about the Yeti.
Well, you need to read that in the book.
Well, the true subgenie have ancestors who are Yetis.
Yeah.
That is the abominable snowman of the Himalayas.
I'd like to say something to our listener.
Please do.
I'm looking at the voice meter right now, and I can tell you've got a strong streak
of Northern Tibetan in your heritage.
Yeah, well, that's right, you know, and I really want to know about the Yeti, and I
need...
Right.
Well, you...
Have you got that rectangular gland in your foot?
That's a main thing.
Well, that sounds pretty good, because I really need some rectangular...
Well, I'd say, why don't you...
You can get your answers by massaging your foot gland.
It's a rectangular gland in your foot.
Look in both feet and massage the soles until you find the...
Listen.
...contangular gland in your foot, and call us back.
Yeah.
Where's Doug Smith?
Doug Smith is a guy who used to work with the Subgenius Foundation.
He died in Bob a long time ago.
He died?
Yeah.
And they did burn out.
They did burn out.
But, but, that doesn't mean his usefulness is at an end, because we're able to reanimate
the fleshly vessels of these sacred scribes after we burn them out, and he pushes a broom
around the laboratories even as we speak.
You serious?
Yeah.
All right.
So, he's...
We let him take care of all the soles we have in storage down there.
Like, for instance, that last caller.
His sole is in a blue canister in my basement, believe it or not, and you think we're kidding.
No, you suck him into a soul tank?
Yeah, and we turn him in.
See, that's how we managed to pay for Bob's re-erection, see?
We had to cash in the soles of those who were dumb enough to call this show, and friend,
you're next.
Don't be funny.
Pull the lever.
Down you go.
All right, you're all fired.
We're the ones.
You can throw yourself off for nothing.
Don't make no difference.
It's good.
There's nothing you can do about it.
Oh, faceless surgeons, are you racers?
Cut out, are you mad today?
No, I'm not.
I'm not.
I don't understand anything.
Now here's the problem.
So much easier to get than real slack, my friend.
So much easier.
All you have to do is work a 9-to-5 job.
Or, you know, the equivalent.
Whatever you do, it doesn't have to be a 9.
You can be your own boss, entrepreneur, help.
Whatever.
It doesn't matter how you get the money.
But the money can buy, can, can, false slack can only be had for money.
Uh, true slack can be had for money.
But you've got to have, you've got to have a slack, a slack awareness, my friend.
More than you need money.
You don't need money.
You don't have to have money to have true slack.
And that is the God's truth.
Oh, no.
I'm dreaming.
None of this is true.
If you cannot see it, you think it's not there.
It doesn't work that way.
They don't know that this is a conspiracy.
This is for real.
They're agnostic.
They don't know.
They have to see it in front of them before they know.
And even then they deny it.
The thing is, is that these people are real.
And, uh, the pinks are the ones who actually do not exist.
Because they're not awake enough to actually have consciousness.
They haven't tuned into the dobs yet.
Yeah, they're just, they're shit.
They're tubes filled with video images.
They're shadows.
They're spirits.
But they're not, they're not real.
Yeah.
By recreating body and mind out of remembered fragments,
I was to program my own inferno.
This is Kano and 90.9 in Dallas, Texas.
God.
Well, he certainly lost his mind.
Listen.
In effect, my soul was a monstrous cancer,
continually creating within itself the means of my destruction.
A lost soul is one that no longer controls its own circuitry.
But us has been taken over by the enemy,
which uses it to destroy me, to destroy you.
The sensation is like spontaneous combustion.
I should have taken it off the hook.
Oh, let it ring.
And you take a message, would you?
And leave it off the hook?
Yeah, okay, okay, I'll get it.
Go on, Linda.
Go on.
It is this control of the circuitry,
this ability to send phantom signals to real bodies
through their remembered images,
like pins stuck in a doll,
that gives hell its power on earth.
Hell is not a place,
but a system for disrupting the plans of God.
She thinks you can cure the world by kindness and rules,
but it's too small.
The Lord's Prayer on a Pinhead.
Some make rules, some obey,
but the rules are for the fools is what I say.
The pistol makes me sick.
I wear the wrong clothes.
I see the wrong things.
You know I can't dance, my feet are much too wide.
I'm a little down, too.
Who think you set the trends?
You wear your head just right.
Your girls are out of sight.
Your house is modern, really kitschy.
You got it so macho in your way, you bitch.
I see them going to work.
I see them doing this work.
I see them on TV.
I see them laughing fly.
I'm on the outside.
It happens. Look around you.
Look all around you.
The rude clerks in stores that hate their job and take it out on you.
The thing about the normals is that they conceptualize themselves to be hot sinus effluvia on silver platters,
but in reality reveal themselves to be cold mucus.
A cold mucus incrustation on a paper plate.
Oh, that's right, friends.
Cold mucus incrustation on a paper plate.
And let's see what this lovely caller has to say.
Hello, sister.
Hi.
Oh, praise Bob.
Ah, yes.
This is Bob's long lost wife, Mona.
Do you want to say your name over the radio?
Mona.
Now, Bob has literally...
I mean, this is a polygamous kingdom.
Bob has a wife and family in every state of the Union that we know of.
There may be other states that we don't even know of.
Yeah, um...
I mean, are you sure you aren't just trying to get in on his will?
No, no, no.
See, about, oh, many moons ago, Bob, well, he sort of came in late one night and he...
Emergency from Bob for 9554?
We don't need it. We don't need it.
No.
See, he keeps trying to walk back into my life.
And he came into my room.
It was late and he stole all my lingerie and he put on my...
Now, that does sound like Bob.
Yeah.
He put on my panties and my nightgown and he said...
That old damn Bob.
Are you looking for him?
Do you want to see him again or you got a message for him?
Well, I can...
We can send it to the post office box.
I'll give you the PO box and just send it in.
I want my lingerie back.
Well, you'll have to work that out.
That's between you and Bob.
If you see Bob, can you tell him his wife, his long-lost wife, wants her lingerie back?
And that's the Marna wife, right?
Yeah.
Write to Bob.
Write to Bob at PO Box 140306, Dallas, Texas, 75214.
Ask for info on the lingerie.
I'll read that address one more time.
Also, I want anybody to send personal messages for the Hour of Slack radio ministry to me,
Pastor Bucknaked, or any tags.
I'll send you a message.
I'll get you the tapes or whatever, especially tapes.
Mark them Hour of Slack, Bucknaked, PO Box 140306, Dallas, 75214.
How come they're marking them for you?
Well, these are the ones that I'll hand.
Oh, okay.
That's right.
Buck's gonna...
If you want them for Stang, then put Stang on there, see?
All right.
Well, sister, Bob's been...
I'm sure Bob has been quite an incredible husband to you, right?
Oh, incredible is not the word.
word uh-huh what is the word i wonder probably something illegal oh no she can she can keep it
clean go ahead say it say it say it say it exotic exotic
well i can't really find the word well thanks for sharing that with us
oh you're all over oh i feel like a thrill is running through me
just getting down to the good part now close your eyes and take beautiful thoughts
oh friends we almost lost that one well thank you reverend bleepo i was doctors
for utter stupidity with that song that almost got us in big trouble friends
oh
yes well well buck i thought you were gonna you and and buddy west brought all your musical
equipment in here you were gonna do a song buddy buddy buddy you guys ready got those amps buddy
uh we're all set up okay we got justice with us tonight too how come you guys only let me in the
studio to play hey we let you in the studio whenever we're not here right remember he can't
like being by
that's right okay you guys ready to go yeah you ready buddy i'm ready uh okay hit it one two
one two and four
thank you bob for cleansing my memory
thank you bob
thank you bob for helping me
and bob i'll follow you all the way
that's right bob until that next day
thank you bob for sending them pills
thank you bob for helping me sleep
thank you bob for binding me willy teenage girls
and bob i'll follow you always
that's right until that next day
until that next day
guitar solo
Oh, thanks, Buck and Buddy.
That was a beautiful, beautiful rendition of that lovely church.
We haven't been real heavy on the rock and roll tonight.
It's been mostly the relaxing subgenius church.
And that upsets some of our listeners, as we know, from that one call.
He thinks we're doing the work of the devil.
That guy's truly enlightened. You just didn't see it his way.
Killer karma.
You didn't see it his way. Now, I do see it his way.
And that fellow is truly enlightened. He's awake on both glands.
But that's the way religion is. It's been a constant battle since the very beginning.
The first man to try to guess why he climbed out of the slime
was the first man to pick up a stick and hit his brother.
We've been programmed.
Offer void where prohibited.
This is the very beginning.
Our slack was taken away the moment we entered this world where he's treadmill.
And we've been running like little rats through a maze.
And the only way you can get away from that is to deprogram.
Edit your own memory. Take those bad memories.
Take those horrible training regimens that you were subjected to as a youth.
Flush them down the toilet as you excremeditate.
Let me ask you. Let me ask you.
Yes, sister.
Did you ever own a guinea pig?
I ate my guinea pigs. I grew them and I ate them.
That's dick crazy, Bob.
They were food. I'm a carnivore.
I can't help myself.
So what are some of the other enemies of the church?
The box dwellers, the Barbies and Kins, the slackless ones.
Yeah, the walking some nebulax, the great incurables.
Those who can never know slack.
The others from the third dimension, the green energy ghouls,
the ghost.
The devils, the supersonic Nazi hell creatures from the hollow earth,
controlled by Hitler's brain.
Maybe you can give us a little information as to the origin of the pinks and the normals.
Well, the origin of the pinks and the normals, I mean, look around you.
I'm looking.
Well, perhaps not in your immediate company.
Oh, okay.
But look around you further.
Extend your third nostril out into the world.
Look at those people out there.
Look at them lining up in front of those elevators.
Yeah.
At the Heimlich building.
I'm looking.
I'm looking at them.
Look at them driving those cars.
Look at those insurance salesmen.
Look at those tyrannical elementary school principals.
Uh huh.
I'm seeing them.
Yes.
Well, look at them oppress.
Oppress.
Look at them drive you into the arms of the conspiracy.
Look at them make you want to be popular.
Look at them want to make you consume those goods.
Well, they're just taking away your will.
I'm beginning to feel something.
Exactly.
Something's leaving.
The trilateral commission.
Uh huh.
Commission of 40.
Right.
They're trying to put conspiracy.
Well, these conspiracies are but specks of dust, sparkles of sand on the beach.
Ah, yes.
Sparkles of sand on the beach compared to the vast conspiracy of normalcy that's trying
to get you, my friends.
We're going to go through the phones one last time before we play the end credits.
I lost him again.
Darn it.
Oh, we hold another soul in perdition.
Yeah.
I guess it's incompetence.
Well, you know what, Buck?
I really, I...
Call back.
Line three, please call back.
Yeah.
I've done it again.
But I am going to play the long credits of the hour slack.
See, we play so many different people's little bits and cuts.
There's subgeniuses all...
He's back.
Oh, he's back?
Okay, let's just put him straight on.
And, uh, dear friend.
Hello?
Uh, dear friend.
No, it's just interference.
Hello?
Get off line three.
He's off line three.
Say hi.
What's wrong?
I don't know what's wrong.
Am I doing it?
Yeah, we...
So, I think somebody's talking to him on the other line.
Hello?
Because he's not on hold, is he?
Oh.
Well...
Was it Adolf?
Friends?
What I was about to say was...
Hey, hey, hey.
Oh, there we are.
Hello.
I am, hey.
You're on.
We finally...
Okay, now make it quick.
What is it?
Okay, Doug.
Okay.
There's no Doug here.
Why the subgenius church...
The subgenius church is not a satanic church, right?
Sure.
That's what the devil gives you, right?
Right.
Okay.
Now, the devil promises you lots of money for your lifetime, right?
Cool.
Then he admits you've got an immortal life after that, right?
Right.
And how nasty, nasty...
That's stupid.
Stupid, stupid, stupid.
Now, who would fight for such a crummy deal like that?
One of those...
Right?
Bob gives you slack now and slack ever after.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The tricky part is figuring out which is the slack and which is the false slack.
And the one...
The devil is the...
The devil, my friends.
So what?
The devil's got...
The devil's in the supermarket.
The devil is in the post office, my friends.
The devil is in the IRS and he's waiting to sell you a vacuum cleaner.
Look, the devil has souls, right?
But the devil doesn't have any money.
The devil doesn't ask you for money, right?
Oh, come on.
Oh, hey, look.
We've got to play the credits.
Thank you.
Thanks for sharing that with us.
The voices you've been listening to come from Leepo Abernathy, Buck Naked and the Jaybirds,
Dr. Odin Canobite, G. Gordon Gordon, Killer for Bob, Dr. Spock, and Dr. Spock.
Dr. Philo Drummond, Overman First Degree, Reverend Cleve Donut Duncan, Dr. Snavely Eklund.
Hey, what are you getting to?
This is the D-Word and Apple.
Or the Angkor.
Now that you have paradigm perspective, let's move on to the shift in your mind.
This is Dr. Ahmed Fishman.
This is Glass Madness.
This is Herr Dr. Chris Gross.
This is Hell's Mommy Satellite Rebirth.
And this is Negative Land.
These are the fantastic two-person castles.
Cameras are swinging love corpses as we venture to the fifth planet.
So that you may immediately know, go ahead andуйте a little bit more and you should know