I'm proud of you Bob. Wedge was a great guy Connie. Yes he was. What are you trying to say?
I'm doing a very bad job of saying I love this.
This is genius. Powerful.
That's right. That's right. It is sure to spread quickly. That's right. That's right. Right.
From PR News in Washington I'm capable of conducting search and rescue missions
also transporting boats in Wilmington North Carolina. This city uh the the city uh and uh
so um so um uh still here.
President Trump's. Oh I think everybody's happy.
President Trump's sexual assault against Judge Kavanaugh.
100% happy.
The Trumps is accused of being a serial killer.
Investigators say Trump has confessed to killing four women
to set up a militarized Turkey near the U.S. Mexico border.
Turkey often collide.
The Dow is 93-92-2662-114-2662.
In other news you're listening to...
PR News.
There's a fellow down in Texas
They say his name is Bob
He tells me I should slap God
I should quit my job
Well, I'm a simple genius
And I must have my slack
If I don't live forever
I get my money back
They said that on July 5th of 1998
The earth would be destruction
Suffering death
Deadly fate
That day was long away
Now it has come and gone
There was no fire from heaven
And this old world rolls on
Well, I'm a simple genius
And I must have my slack
If I don't live forever
I get my money back
Poor Stang was made to suffer
A terrible disgrace
Of such humiliation
He feared to show his face
Now Bob may be laughin'
But he's a man of his word
Because we are such chumps
But there is no reason
To be down in the dumps
It'll all still happen
No need to curse or frown
They got all the right numbers
Just got them upside down
Well, I'm a simple genius
And I must have my slack
If I don't live forever
I get my money back
So welcome to the subgenius devotional hour, here
Hum
Before the normal scary time
As the smoke of that burning goeth up forever
Despite my ministers body
And his thick dumb
That was a stinkle
But it had lots of prophecy involved
I'm a man of few words
You hear it right here
You aren't quick as shit
You're wanna quit and shit
You'll get it from me
In lots of few words
Good
And I suggest you get started
I wonder why Fido came home
With his wazoo missing
Or wonder why those beefs
Like Buster and Duval
And the parlor
And the pasture
Are lyin' out there
With their throats
And half their rectums missing
Well, it's because of those Exists
who came down to this earth one Christmas day many millennia ago to forge a new link.
One might call it a hot link between the aliens and man,
a giant sausage of knowledge from the center of the universe, the galactic center.
Those little tykes will be able to carry on for us.
Every one of those little kids is a potential Lee Majors,
and I hope you're pleased with what we've done.
The rising generations shall have reason to praise us,
to pour out libations on our smoking altars,
and we shall know this is a non-smoking section.
The book of the subgenius, Lunatic Prophecies for the Coming Weird Times,
out now and on your stand.
If you don't see the book on your stand,
complain, loudly agitate, and tell the store if necessary.
They are crazy.
It's a question of bulldada.
And its application, of course, in the society surrounding the bulldada.
We apply it from a little disposable tube.
That's right, using the power shell and using the spirit code,
the Yakut.
The diesel matrix applies the bulldada to the normals and pinks.
And you know, some people get worried about that violent sounding part of it.
But you know, as Dr. Legume said,
to make an omelet, you gotta break a few eggs.
Well, to make the kind of omelet that Bob Dobbs is making,
it's gonna take a hell of a lot of scrambled brains on drugs, my friends.
And many of you have probably heard of the New Age theory about the 100th monkey.
They never mentioned the 100th Manson.
They never mentioned the 100th Legume.
They never mentioned the 100th Bob.
Because friends, when you release your inner child,
sooner or later, your inner Charlie Manson is gonna want out too.
And we are composed of many selves, and it's a good idea,
not to take any of yourselves too seriously.
But seriously, there is a solution.
And that solution is, fuck them if they can't take a joke.
Ah, yes.
And you'd think that would be enough, friends.
But the conspiracy has this secret weapon,
that invisible monster that lives up in the sky.
87% of Americans believe in that invisible monster
that'll kick their enemy's asses if they kiss its ass enough.
And yet,
their so-called God is so pathetically weak
that apparently it has to be defended by illiterate little old ladies against assholes like me.
What kind of a pussy-ass God is that?
Seems like he'd be able to kick my ass himself.
That's why we do say, we still say,
WAR ON GOD, dear friends!
War on any God that's worried about us making war on him.
Ah, yes.
Friends, we're just like any other religion.
It's not that we love Bob all that much,
it's that we love the idea of everybody else burning in hell.
And we don't need any reason to hate them,
beyond the very simple fact that we've got Bob and they don't.
That's enough.
Fuck them even if they can't just tell a joke.
Bob?
I wish I could think.
They obviously watch television.
Bob?
Uh, who is Bob Dobbs, right?
Bob Dobbs, who, uh...
Professor Dobbs, can you hear me?
Yeah.
Do you have a bathroom problem in your house?
It's a very busy place, isn't it?
Where everyone in the family has to brush their teeth, wash their hands, take a shit.
Listen to this, sis.
She said, don't tell me lies and try to please me.
I've heard it all so many times before.
And I tell you, I'm not gonna lie to you.
You're fucking a fucking liar.
I'm gonna kill you.
Bob.
Well, sirs and sir-mams, uh, all those insane-sounding collages of bull-dada, including
the news and the ones that'll end the show, come from the great Fernandanande Leamer.
The ranting about the war on God there was me and Einstein's secret orchestra in the
pufferfish's own private lab.
Dome at Starwood Festival from apparently 19 years ago. Jeepers. The puzzling evidence clip
with Dr. Howell talking about the hot link of X-Day was even older, 1980s. And that song,
There's a Feller Down in Texas, was the great Orton Nenslow, recorded at a big devival either
in Portland or Seattle in the 1990s. But now, if he's home, let's call lonesome cowboy Dave.
He's still not home. Hello, Smiley. Oh, how are you? Smiley. Smiley, you've lost your wits.
You're in a pants or something. What happened to your nose? Oh, I just had my hair done. That's all.
That just makes everything look different. I like your nose hairs better with the fronds.
I got a nose cut, yeah. Yeah. No, the fronds were getting in the way. They were like
catching food before my mustache did, you know? Yeah, but you could pass that off as a humongous
mastodon or a piece of
person.
No, nobody would believe that. I could pass it off as eyebrows, except they're coming out of my
nostrils instead of the top of my eyes. That's ridiculous, Dave. Well, of course, at least it's
ridiculous, you know, rather than preemptive or pejorative. Sometimes it just smells too bad,
you know? Wouldn't want it to be preemptive. No, or pejorative.
Well, that's okay. We do that all the time. Yeah, we do. We get no credit for it neither,
neither, either. Hey, I've got great news for you here. I was looking in my...
The baboons have returned. No, not yet, but the internet could be destroyed any second.
No, seriously. Headline, massive solar storm threat. Scientists have discovered evidence of a
gigantic solar storm that shatters the atmosphere.
That's
The
Power Grease.
and electrical devices,
it would be like Snake Plissken pushing that button.
Yeah, they always talk about Snake Plissken
pushing his belly button.
That's a reference to a 1990s movie.
Movie.
Yeah, it's a movie.
A pop culture thing.
Escape from L.A. specifically.
Escape from L.A. was the sequel to Escape from New York.
New York, yeah, from your New York.
But it had, you know, come think of it, Dave, Bob,
that movie had kind of a Bob in it.
There was a Dr. Dobbs who was a plastic surgeon
in the future L.A. played by Bruce Campbell,
who's, you know, already looks kind of inhuman
with that jawbone.
To begin with, yeah.
Yeah, and he was playing a character named Dobbs,
and I happen to know for sure
that the director, John Carpenter,
was turned on to Bob long ago
if by no one else than my friend,
Reverend Nancy Regalia,
or Nancy Collins, the horror writer.
Oh, that's great.
At least, you know, there's something you can count on
that you know that that happened.
Well, yeah, I don't know that they...
They really could be put in jail,
but Ninth Circuit Court gets a hold of some of the
mastodon parts again,
and talk about mastodons again, but...
I'm not going to sue 20th Century Fox,
but here's some news about the mastodons.
Some Japanese scientists have awakened, sort of,
they've sort of awakened cells
from a 28,000-year-old mammoth carcass.
You know, they're trying to make new mammoths,
using elephants.
Yeah, I don't know why they're doing that.
Why not? Because it's there.
Because it's there.
In fact, it's like, let's take some Neanderthal DNA
and plug it in to see if we can start
a new race of humans next year.
I've had such pornographic dreams
about that very subject, Dave.
I have a little...
In the back of my head,
there's this dramatic teen movie
about the...
the Neanderthal teenager,
the world's first,
since 40,000 years ago or whatever,
and she's in high school,
and they're trying to see if she can pass
as a human,
which she is.
You know, Neanderthals were
technically human,
but very different from their African ancestors.
And hence...
See, that's what...
Like the Pathfinder was saying, too,
and I found that, you know,
if you leave your underwear,
let's say, like, you washed your underwear, right?
Right.
And that's the first...
That's a big F.
Towards a brand-new glorious day,
you're going to, you know,
start to wake up yourself
and become kind of like a new human race,
you know, infused with all the literal garbage
and sanctimonious BS of before,
only different this time
because it's different this time
because it's different, you know?
And I just get out there and say,
fight the public.
Fight the public?
Yeah.
Oh.
They don't have enough teeth to bite back.
There's nothing you got to worry about.
You can give them a kick
like you kick an old chihuahua.
The ones with more Neanderthal DNA,
they've got some pretty big jaws.
Bones.
Yeah.
They got some thick bone...
They're like bulldogs of humanity.
And they make huge, huge tents
with mastodon skin.
If you got far enough to make huge, huge tents,
out of mastodon skin,
why would you want to become
the world's third largest radion importer
and nuclear power?
Unless you had a nucleus to start with.
Well, because why not?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's the old...
Because it's there.
Because why not?
Because humans do that kind of messed up stuff
and cover Mount Everest
with frozen human excrement.
In vast, huge piles.
And quite a few dead bodies.
So there you go.
That there's...
You know, the...
For every mastodon
that's dug up out of the melting
Arctic ice,
there's going to be another human
mountain climber
frozen on Mount Everest.
For later people to discover
in about...
20 years when all that ice melts.
Even at the top of Mount Everest.
And we get that...
What was that movie
where the whole world was covered with the ocean?
Was it a takeoff
of the J.G. Ballard ground world?
Oh, no.
There's been tons of them since then.
It was that Kevin Costner movie
that bombed.
But I loved it.
But I can't remember the title of it
for some reason.
Don't you feel ashamed of yourself?
Loving a movie the same way
somebody would carnally love a blissful woman?
Well, the reason I can't remember
might be revealed
by a retina scan
that can identify Alzheimer's disease
years before symptoms appear?
What?
I hadn't read this.
It looks like a little duck.
A little teeny tiny, like about
some size duck.
You just put it up to whatever eye is bothering you
and it screams,
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up!
Like that, you know?
No, it's more like if they look through their scope
and they see the little duck in your eye,
then that means you're gonna
you're gonna have the old
you're gonna be getting the Alzheimer's
sooner or later.
Oh, I...
You won't know the difference
whether it was sooner or later.
Yeah.
Thank God for that part.
Thank Dobbs.
Yeah.
For that part.
Yeah, so they have a warning test
for Alzheimer's.
But they don't have one for
normality or subgeniusness.
There's no genetic test.
You can abort your baby
before it's born if it's
not the right species.
You know, if only.
Well, that's exciting.
Well, think about it.
Say your
granddaughter
got pregnant and she could
get a blood test that said
whether the baby was gonna be
a human or
a human.
Like pure human or part subgenius
or a lot of subgenius or
subgenius Neanderthal or what.
And then she could
you know, go to the
abortion mall that the
right-wingers email each other about
and get the human
aborted or the subgenius
depending on where she was coming from.
Yeah.
You know, philosophically.
I know a lot of subgenius parents
whose kids, they don't want to have
a subgenius.
They don't want to be subgeniuses.
They wish they hadn't been raised
by subgeniuses.
Then of course, there's others that are
like the most
beloved and devout
hard workers for dogs.
Yeah.
Like me.
I can all I can do is concurred
monitors.
It's just a spasmodic release
valve once in a while that I have to
take care of.
But I believe you me.
Believe you me.
You know.
Well, you know, I'm not sure.
Even at our age, we got to release
those valves.
We've got to we got to open up the
main steam stop valve and just let
that steam go out or whatever.
Whatever.
Gas like a gorilla, you know, fluid.
Yeah.
Something you got to empty the flu
nads or the poison builds up, you know.
Yeah.
Mine doesn't build up anywhere near
as fast as it used to.
Oh, God.
That's such a relief.
Well, you're taking on less poison.
And that's why your release mode is
is going back to the original model
like the sunshine.
Remember the sunshine model that for
a whole year?
I don't know who was Chrysler or
Mount Bank Intelligence Services or
somebody.
I don't remember.
Well, I don't remember either.
Might not have happened.
Might just have been another
hallucination because they're
becoming more frequent now.
And we use the last like what?
More frequent.
Oh, yeah.
You're you got to be kidding.
How could they possibly be more
frequent than they were?
Well, they're almost like one right
after another.
Dave, I've got news for you.
It's been like that for you.
I think since practically since I met
you and that was in the early 1990s.
Yeah, it's been one reality after another.
It's like sneak like constant sneezes.
It's like spaghetti.
Yeah.
That's exactly like spaghetti.
You want to talk about nailed it.
Yeah.
Edible string theory.
You know, jiggling spaghetti is not
just spaghetti sitting there in a big
mess.
It's vibrating and jiggling.
Yep.
High.
Everyone.
Yep.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Didn't mean to get, you know, step
on your feet there, but it was the
only thing I could see.
That wasn't my feet, man.
That was my.
Uh, Tom, but that's okay.
Well, I'm not ready for a tongue
lesson.
Believe me.
Um, I'm know what I'm staying for and
what I believe in and, and, and, and
what is it?
Oh yeah.
Praise Bob.
That's all you have to remember.
And, and, and the hate the conspiracy
and, uh, and get slack.
That's it.
Those three things.
You've seen those pictures on the
internet of Trump's father wearing the
clan uniform.
Yeah.
Those are kind of silly.
I was gonna.
I was gonna photo.
I was gonna Photoshop his face on that.
You know, you're not realized somebody
already did it a thousand years ago.
Okay.
If you thought of it,
over the first master Don's right.
Yeah.
If you thought of it, somebody Photoshop
that Trump had on that photo back in the
stone age, besides since when do you know
how to work Photoshop?
Well, just as poorly as I know how to use
InDesign and a bunch of other things that
I managed to get a C in it so I could pass.
But if you ask me what these mean next week,
I will have no idea.
Yeah.
I'm, I'm starting to lose it.
Dave.
I went to download illegal software off of use
nap and I couldn't find it.
It wasn't there or it was coded in a way that I
couldn't, I could no longer translate.
And, uh, I just realized I'm so old now.
Yeah.
I'm just going to have to buy the update
like a normal person.
I just seemed so unnatural to me after 30
years of thinking you can buy software.
I thought it just all came from that big
spigot called usenet, but no, no, that's a,
they're going to abolish usenet.
No, it's still there, but they've had to lay
so many layers of.
Code and, uh, you know, I don't know.
It's, it's way more complicated than it used to
be in order to be able to do it at all and stay
under the conspiracies, right?
Are it's a complicated story, Dave.
You don't want to read it.
Um, and Neil Stevenson hasn't written it yet, but
he probably, well, he probably has, we just haven't
seen it.
Yeah.
And we thought of Neil Stevenson already did a killer
novel about, I'm so jealous of that guy.
I want to cut his fingers off so he can't type or
write a cursive, which is how he actually wrote the
entire Baroque cycle with a goose quill pen on parchment
paper, because that's how they wrote in the period he
was writing about.
That's what he says.
Anyway,
he, that's like a form of insanity.
Right?
Some people find that to be a path to truth.
When in actuality, it's a path to frozen teeth.
Bob, actually, actually, Dave, now, come on.
When you get ideas, do you type them or do you
hand write them with a pencil on a piece of paper?
Ideas, of course, always hand-pickled with writing.
Ask, ask a hundred young people when the last time
they used a pencil was.
I'm full of words.
They'll search their minds and go, I think I had to
hang a picture last night.
I think I had to hang a picture last year.
And I used a pencil to mark where the nail would go.
Well, how do you like signing your signature as a squiggly
line so that nobody can trace what it is?
Oh, I draw little pictures.
I, some people, you know, like when you're getting, you're
checking out with a credit card.
No, but a lot of kids can't actually sign their name.
I mean, you can't, you know, Spencerian penmanship went out
the window about 10, 20 years ago.
Well, they can, they can block, they can hand write, you know,
write their name in block text, right.
Of some kind.
Yeah.
Or did they not even teach that?
Some fusion of the two, but Spencer, I live in a town where
they have a Spencerian, uh, preservation society because
he lived near here.
But what's Spencerian?
The, the, the penmanship, the original penmanship guy from
the 1790s all the way up to about 1955 or something.
Oh, no, I don't.
That's new to me, but go ahead.
Well, they just, they, uh.
They gave up and they killed him.
They, they.
Right.
And they became communist themselves.
After all the stuff they went through, they couldn't resist it.
These kids these days can't read the original declaration of independence
because it's a, they go, what language is this?
That's not a joke.
Whereas we were in with the, we're in what is it?
Yeah.
They're coming there.
Nah.
Well, they did use F's instead of S's, uh, by our standards.
So it does.
Look stupid, but it's a little silly, but I guess I have you ever read the, uh, direct
transcriptions of the Lewis and Clark's notes on their expedition across the North American
continent.
Those guys were, they were both the closest thing to college educated dudes you could
get.
And their, their, their notes are like what?
There was no spelling rules.
Everything was phonetic.
And it's like little kid writing or very, very primitive internet text writing.
You know?
Yeah.
Uh, it's, it's very, very strange to read the, the, the way the, the olden people did
that.
And it's, it's strange for the young people to read how we do it or did it, Dave, before
we did it.
Yeah.
But that's more symbolic because they were, they were also another problem with the old
language writers was they were very creative.
They wanted to be, they all wanted to be the next Dickens.
And so that you mother dear, after all you have endured.
Oh, they're very poetic.
And every big, yeah.
Yeah.
Big words were special effects in those days.
And you could get phonetic with them.
Big words.
Pretty easy.
Especially if you were describing a log cabin somewhere out in the Huma Valley.
Yeah.
Well, whereas nowadays you read, uh, say just for instance, uh, a Stephen King book.
And, uh.
Go in your pants.
Well, he's a very good storyteller.
I've said people can put him down, but he's a, he can write a page turner and he's written
about 500 of them.
And, uh, uh, but the vocabulary in those is about one 10th of say Mary Shelley's French.
Or, uh, Joseph Conrad's Moby Dick.
So, you don't have to bring that into it.
Oh yeah.
I'm not trying to be sexist.
Okay.
Um, well, I just don't like people talking about humongous dicks or finer dicks.
Remember her?
Well, anyway, they, the, the people don't like the big words anymore and they don't
like long sentences.
And that's why everything's all, you know, politics by Twitter and, uh, uh, trolling.
And they already bought.
Oh, that's fine.
They already bypassed
the formatization by AP.
They already went past
American Press style, which is pretty short and sweet.
Which got
Oh, right. Yeah.
That was supposed to be clear and concise.
But now,
it's reduced to pictos
practically. A few
nouns and verbs when you don't
have a picto for it.
But, yeah.
And also, if you can smash together
any word or two
into one letter.
The smaller you can make it into one
thing, the better.
Right. Yeah. Abbreviate everything.
Because, you know,
they're typing with their thumbs.
I do it too.
Now.
I prefer
to sit at a
keyboard, or even better,
with a pencil
and a sheet of paper.
But,
I
I almost feel like
I'm afraid to get caught
using
old media, you know.
People make fun of you.
They go, why don't you just use your
phone, man? Why'd you pull that
piece of paper and a pencil out of
your pocket? You could just use your phone.
It's like, well, but I'm not gonna
look at my phone for
that. Why not,
you fool?
Well,
because I'm old, I guess.
You know, Dave?
Well, at least you're guessing at it.
You know, some people have some really firm numbers
and know exactly what brassiere size
they gotta put on.
Some of my most brilliant friends
can barely
operate a computer at all,
don't have a
smartphone, and only
have a mobile
track phone type thing
because they absolutely
had to. Because the
payphones are all gone.
You're one of them.
You're a famous...
Somebody is giving me a phone
which is much better than the track phone
I've got, but it's still
not a top of the line.
I must have it because I must take pictures
in JPEG format.
Yeah, you have to.
Oh, you'll get to where
it's like, how did I ever live without this thing?
This is like the Swiss
Army knife of all media.
And it
is.
It's all good.
It'll be gone, as my
article at the beginning of the show said,
massive solar storm threat.
Sooner or later, it's all gonna
or an
EMP, you know,
a giant electromagnetic
pulse nuclear weapon
in the atmosphere
over the
target continent, which
is all seven of them,
plus Atlantis.
They'll,
you know, suddenly it would all
be gone.
Nobody be able to get on Facebook
and they'd probably probably
about half of the civilized world
would commit suicide.
Yeah, I'm just realizing, you know,
in my novel name, Neighborworld,
I'm not so sure that even
though things are going to wind up that way,
I think they might be a little bit
deadlier. I think people are a little bit
the basis.
Oh, Dave, you're most optimist.
You're most, you're most
pessimistic predictions.
In Neighborworld
are laughably optimistic.
Pathetically optimistic.
It will be so much worse.
There won't be any Neighborworld
at all after a certain point.
Or people.
That would be the evolution gone awry.
And this would be how things are really going.
No, no, it'd be cool, man.
Things are not good.
No, it'd be cool.
There'd be hardly any people left.
And most of the large animals
would be gone.
I mean, this is all, you know,
this is a foregone conclusion.
This isn't science fiction or prophecy.
This is just the schedule.
You and me won't have to
witness most of it.
I'm really hoping to die before
the last gorilla does.
That's my goal.
I die before the last gorilla does.
Well, you might be dead on Tuesday if you wait for that.
Well, I'm actually, if there was anything
I'd spend money on, it'd be keeping that last
gorilla alive.
Because I don't want to die.
Yet.
There's all kinds of, I mean, the Avengers Endgame.
I've got to live to see that.
Poor Dr. Legume.
For Legume, Thanos won.
The fight between Thanatos and Eros?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
You don't, oh, Dave, you don't know.
It's a big deal.
Half the, half of the life forms in the entire unit
universe died suddenly, instantly at the end of the
last Avengers movie.
Now, how's that for dark?
The bad guy won.
And then Legume died.
So he doesn't get to see the final movie in the
Quintrilogy or whatever it is.
There's like seven of them now.
And, but they're going to end it.
They're going to kill off a bunch of the old actors.
Yeah.
And they're going to kill off the characters, actually.
Not the characters, the characters could live on, but
the actors can't keep playing superheroes when they're in
their 70s.
Although, Michael Douglas and Arnold Schwarzenegger have
both played young action heroes in movies made in the last two
years.
Yeah.
Buffalo Jim was a Picayune artist, too, down there in
Mississippi, I guess.
He used to wear the Buffalo chips and decide which way the mail was going to be delivered.
And for a long time, I guess the police were after him.
Once they found him, they didn't want him anymore.
He got rid of him for some reason.
He was because of the nasal obstruction.
Maybe he'd be talking, you know, he'd be like, like he'd be whistling at the same time.
And he was so irritating that they had to call the police.
Well, I already told you about the police.
What does that have to do with these Marvel movies that are the main thing keeping me alive?
Well, who said they're not?
Just because you said they're not, all of a sudden they're not have nothing to do with it?
Here's my point, Dave.
If you were a movie star, you could appear to be any age they wanted you to.
Now, you wouldn't actually be that age.
You would just look that age in the movie.
But what's real?
Man, what's really real?
Yeah.
Come on.
Get into the neighbor, get into the neighbor world point of view, man.
It's not really...
If you can animix everything, why even have another reality outside your own?
If you can animix everything, you can have the world just exactly the way you want.
You can crawl into a hole or a hovel.
They're making glasses that'll let you do just that.
You don't even have to look at a screen or put on a big headset.
Just the glasses.
And they've got augmented reality.
So you can look around.
You're just like James Cameron directing Avatar or something.
Or just like Sandra Moses.
It's like you look around on the set and instead of seeing a bunch of blue screen boxes and actors in goofy marker suits,
you see these alien characters in a jungle, a beautiful jungle.
Yeah.
It's like really articulate, well, well articulated point A.
I would say a neighbor world point A where everybody thinks they're someplace.
They're all interacting together.
I mean, they're not physically touching because I guess you'd have to feel it.
I didn't think about that part because I was too busy, you know, elaborating.
Well, Dave, if you ever want to see a modern day movie that touches on something somewhat similar,
Ready Player One, based on a pretty good recent sci-fi novel put together by Stephen King.
Yeah-
And also published by Steven Spielberg's company as one of those virtual reality previews of virtual reality in the future.
Of course, the best part of it is when it shows the real reality that the virtual reality aficionados choose not to see.
Instead of Los Limbs, a futurological congress.
Well, it takes place in Columbus, Ohio.
It's the ameophiles.
in, I think, 2030.
And when they open the movie
and show Columbus, Ohio in 2030,
it looks like a very, very, very poverty-stricken
and overpopulated other planet.
They've literally started stacking trailer homes
into skyscraper-sized planets.
Well, they have done that in some parts of Asia,
as we know.
Well, it's assumed in this particular virtual world
that that's what the real world is going to look like.
And the virtual world is pretty sexy, of course.
I spend as much time there as I can,
but I'm still more tied to the meat plane,
the dirt and mud level of life.
And climate.
Consciousness.
You know, I'm not really up in the ascended planes.
Man, I'm down in the mud.
I'm a mud boy.
You're a feeling-really guy in the F&D.
I'm friends with the micro-creatures that live in the mud.
I know their names.
They're not really friends.
They just tolerate you because you're much bigger.
I'm their home.
Yeah, I'm their real estate.
They're not the ones that live on me.
Then there's ones that just live in the mud.
But I'm talking about the real plane,
where everything's really real.
Well, there's ones that live on you.
Not even human thought.
That's the real, real plane
where nobody's doing any thinking at all.
It's just there.
The plants, the dirt, the micro-creatures,
the rodents, the little tiny animals,
and even the big mammals.
Even our dogs.
They're not fretting about the same kind of stuff we are.
So all of our pompous human conceits are as nothing.
There is like dust in the wind, to quote Bill and Ted.
To some people, that's a depressing thought.
But to me,
it's like,
no, even after the people are gone,
there'll still be this wonderful, huge planet.
It'll be devoid of 90% of the species
that used to live on it,
somewhat like after the Permian extinction.
Oh, I remember.
That was when the dry cleaners got excited, yeah?
That just gives everybody else a chance
to get a leg up, you know?
Maybe it'll be squid,
and squid women are like...
If you were a dog and you wanted to lift your leg up somewhere,
that would be the place to do it.
Well, except there won't be dogs.
The dogs are rogues.
Not as we know it.
They'd be wearing bow ties and talking in spectator language.
Oh, if only.
Dealing cards and stuff like that.
If only.
That ancient movie,
The Planet of the Apes,
written by Rod Serling,
I'm not talking about the novel by Pierre Boulet,
but the movie,
from 1969,
which soundtrack is playing in the background,
that was one of those stories
that was ridiculously optimistic.
People thought it was so dark.
Oh, my God.
The human race is going to destroy itself,
and the Statue of Liberty is going to be buried up to its neck in sand
after climate change,
and the apes are going to take over.
But you guys...
Well, that sounds pretty...
That sounds pretty good to me.
That sounds like a real good option to me
compared to what I think is actually going to be happening,
personally.
Right.
As a junior scientist,
and, you know,
we junior scientists try to keep our mouths shut
because it's kind of depressing,
and there's not really anything much we can do about it.
The young people,
my grandkids,
will probably bust their asses
trying to save the environment,
and I hope,
they succeed.
But I don't see how they possibly can.
Honestly.
Well, some places they have.
The snowball has gone.
It's been going since...
It's been rolling for 70 years now,
100 years.
That's a soot-covered snowball, man.
That's a snowball covered with the most polluted,
acid,
rain,
charcoal,
black,
horrible...
Look how Cleveland looks.
Three days after it snows.
All the snow turns black and gray.
Big...
Yeah, well, that's the inside of your lungs, too.
Yep.
Darn it.
Like living in Kentucky or West Virginia,
same thing.
You bring something out of the earth in great tonnage,
it's going to be in the air in great tonnage, too, you know?
Repent!
Quit your job.
Slack off.
It's the end of the world.
It really is.
I think...
In terms of neighborhood, you have to be more contextual
rather than saying that's not a depleted and sad enough vision.
It's like it's a real upbeat vision, but...
Yeah, it is.
It's not going to be any better than that.
That's a starting point for things being bad.
If you'll notice the way the conclusions drawn are like,
you can't stop the world from being a city play.
Oh, God.
That's okay.
And Dave, it's like...
Standard Mazik, the lead character,
he comes through okay,
but kind of like us,
he knows that after he's dead,
it's going to be much, much worse.
But look at it this way.
They'll think it's normal.
Yeah.
We've been over this so many times on these stupid shows, Dave.
Well, it is a concurrent.
It is a concurrent.
I mean, not a concurrent theme.
It's a recurrent theme.
How did I get concurrent there?
We must have been together at one time.
But it's a recurrent theme
that things are getting worse and worse and worse.
They establish a platform for showing that worseness.
And once you attain that,
then you can't go any higher or lower than that.
You have to create a whole other different one.
Oh, it's like porno.
End of the world news.
It's like, oh, I want to see the latest species extinction.
Oh, I can't wait to see what new...
How many new glaciers are calving off
so that there won't be any Antarctica at all
or Arctic as we know them.
Did President Coolidge get imbibed
by any of the releases of the gas today
by the Secretary of Council?
I know this is in the future, and that's in the past year.
Well, they don't really talk about that kind of stuff,
so I haven't...
I haven't been following it, those details.
But, yeah, the gases are escaping.
The permafrost is melting.
The ancient viruses are being released.
The Wendigo is about to start walking the world.
There's some pretty decent low-budget horror movies
about this very subject.
But in the end, in the end, it doesn't matter
because...
at least we got a stinking show out for college radio,
which is all we really set out to do.
Well, at least they've got something to do
with their godforsaken time.
Besides masturbating in a quiet room
or arguing with some person down the hall
for making too much noise when he's trying to study.
Actually, those are...
Those don't sound that bad compared to what's coming.
Especially the masturbating part.
Some of us might just have to...
spend the rest of our lives masturbating ourselves to sleep.
Some of us might have to spend our lives
trying to masturbate one more time.
Well, one more is always better than no more.
That's a wretched...
Exactly, but what if it takes a long time?
That's a...
It's a wretched existence.
Well, just think of it like as a way of a European makes food
as opposed to the way an American wants one.
American wants a burger quick, quick, quick.
Say if a French person wants something
that tastes kind of good,
he doesn't care if it takes too long
because his tummy will be growling more.
It's a wonderful, wonderful, wonderful way to lose weight.
You're stereotyping, Dave.
There are Americans who stop to smell the roses
and there are Frenchmen who are running around
like crazy Japanese businessmen
sweating the textiles contract.
So don't stereotype.
We've learned that lesson.
That's right.
I take no...
I take no what you call it,
what you just said.
But I know what you mean.
No umbrage or dishonor or any...
Americans do tend to be...
Americans do tend to be more obese,
shallow, poorly educated,
worse health care
than all of our rival industrial nations these days.
So, you know, it's just...
It's sad.
I guess I must hate our freedoms
if I'm going to...
I mean, speaking the bald-faced truth like that.
Think of those socialist fins
are the happiest people on Earth.
Why, if you're a socialist country,
why are you so happy?
Wait a minute.
Fins?
They don't count.
No, fins don't count.
They're completely alien.
They're not from the same background
that any of the rest of us world citizens are.
Fins are the weirdest weirdos.
They're like another species.
Don't eat them.
Even try.
Don't drag the fins into it.
It's not fair.
There's no comparison.
It's apples and oranges.
Okay.
And them and the Basque.
The Basque people also have that unique...
Their language is so different from everything else.
They get to think their own thoughts.
You see?
Yeah.
And they're not worried about...
They come out...
No use for...
They come out pretty weird.
Well, what else could you expect, you know?
With a bunch of noisy Spaniards and Frenchmen behind you
having a holiday.
Next thing you know,
you're one of those dreadful Neanderthals
you've conjured in your nightmares.
At least when you're sleeping.
I actually hung out with two bonafide fins
when I was staying in Leipzig.
And they were drunk already.
We and I...
Well, everybody.
Everybody was.
We met the Large and his girlfriend.
And they...
The Large used to send tons of weird little mixes
and hardcore stuff.
And he used to call puzzling evidence.
I think he might have gotten a little disillusioned
with the subgenius thing when...
Well, I don't want to go there.
But...
Did I say something bad about...
No, no, no.
No, I'm...
No, no.
He and I had an ethnic disagreement.
Anyway.
But he was overall...
He was an unbelievably interesting, funny guy.
But he was a Finn.
And they're completely...
They're just...
Everything about Finland is separate from...
You know, you could say it's Scandinavian, but...
Not like Denmark and Norway and Sweden and them.
They're all, you know...
There's a certain amount in common
called Indo-European language.
Yes, and they're not a part of the Indo-European...
Right.
They're part of the same language group as Hungarians
and, I believe, Latvians.
Oh, I don't think they're the same group as...
Not sure, but Hungarians for sure.
I thought they weren't the same group as anybody.
That's what makes them so weird.
No, they're kind of...
They have connections even with the We Are people of China.
They stretched all the way from West Central Asia
where...
The Uyghurs?
The Uyghurs.
Yeah.
Uyghurs.
We Are.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
No, that's a real thing.
And their closest relatives linguistically are Hungarian.
Hungarian and Finnish are kind of close.
Oh, God, that figures.
My wife is half Hungarian.
Yeah, my wife was half Hungarian, too.
That explains everything, Dave.
We were led into a trap by Finns, Hungarians, and Uyghurs.
Well, the cabbage rolls were good, you know what I mean?
Well, that's the thing.
God, the cooking was just...
It was so great and she's so beautiful.
Oh, my God.
Oh, I...
Well, now I'm distracted.
I'm not there.
Dave, we better get off this subject
before we say anything racist and un-PC and everything else.
Because, you know, you can get in trouble.
I'm actually in trouble right now
with a few idiots
for being...
With some of the idiots, I'm in trouble for being too PC.
And with the other idiots, I'm in trouble for not being PC enough.
Now...
Yes, you would expect that would happen, yeah.
Yeah.
They're the only ones who actually think I'm in any trouble.
Because I can tell from my vantage point atop this flagpole
over the middle of the road
that's mounted on the big lane in the middle of the...
With this model AR-14 that looks so realistic.
No, no.
With my magnifying...
My binoculars, that's all.
And hearing aids.
And I'm just looking back and forth and seeing...
Seeing the overall scope.
I see the left lane and the right lane.
I am in the middle of the road,
but I'm elevated up about 40 feet.
So I have a more clear, broad viewpoint
than those milling cattle down there in the left lane or the right lane.
Or, I mean, you know, the north lane or the south lane.
That's what I mean.
And there's traffic jams in both.
And there's directions.
And I'm just sitting here doing my show.
And anytime I want to, I can just kick off,
go frop up and walk the dogs.
I could do that.
And by golly, I think I will.
Because it's been 45 minutes of philosophy.
And that's enough for any hour-long show.
Well, I have to agree with you.
I need to be physically, because I'm annoying myself right now.
Well, we both have physical needs, Dave.
Yeah.
Needs.
Sometimes they become more particular.
Needs that must...
Needs be addressed.
Or undressed.
Unzipped.
Or freed.
Uncaged.
Two stamps from Sri Lanka, I mean.
Set free.
Fixed to the letter.
Temporarily.
I can hear you sweating.
You think?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
It's pooling up.
I've got to keep it off the recorder.
Yeah, keep it away from the drat bags, too.
Because, you know, when they come in wearing kilts,
they still want to play the vibraphone.
Well, you're kind of freaking me out a little bit, so...
No, it's okay, Dave.
This 45 minutes...
It's a...
Or now a 47 minutes we've recorded.
It'll save the listeners having to listen to all those...
To all that huge variety of material of old and new subgenius stuff by other people
that had really good music and really funny jokes.
So we've saved them that trouble.
And, friends, you, too, can save yourself that trouble
or bring it upon yourselves.
You can bring it upon yourself by going to subgenius.com on the internet,
which has copies of all our old shows.
The really good ones that had 50 tracks per hour.
That's exciting.
And the current type ones that have three tracks per hour.
One of them 50 minutes long.
But that's okay.
Because it's real, man.
It's real.
That's the important thing.
It's exciting.
It's very, very exciting.
It may not be exciting, but at least it's real.
Yeah, but at least it's exciting.
There's nobody else anywhere even remotely like Lonesome Cowboy Dave on the whole planet.
Imagine the window that you're getting into this alien psyche.
You may not enjoy it, but by golly, it's certainly alien.
It might be the ugliest experience of my life.
It's the ugliest experience you've ever had in your life.
I mean, that would be the way you would have to describe it, too.
Or the most sublime
Or you could just take a rapid ride without a suitcase, yeah.
No, for many, it would be the most sublime and uplifting ride to hear the liquid logic
of Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Just like the depressing but not so depressing end of Neighborworld.
It's like you've arrived at a point in time where you're like, oh, I'm going to go to
Neighborworld at this point.
Now you can stumble around in the dark wondering what else to do.
And friends, you can procure a copy of Neighborworld if you're really interested.
You may look at subgenius.com.
You won't have to read down on the front page very far at all.
And that willI happen to know that not enough of you have heeded the warning.
The warning.
This is the warning.
This shower has been the warning.
Okay, Dave.
I had a little music cue going there for a minute.
It's gone now.
It's Jerry Goldsmith's score for Planet of the Apes, the 1969 version.
Franklin J. Scherzinger.
That's right.
Frank Schaffner?
Or Shafer?
Shafer?
I thought it was.
Yeah.
Probably Shafer.
See?
That's the kind ofthose details are starting to slip.
I need to take that retina test.
Okay, anyway, friends.
That's it.
subgenius.com.
Price Bob.
Don't want no more Bob.
I'm so sorry.
more more more more fun
Don't want no more fun