You are about to undergo long-wave radiation. A buzzer will sound. Close your eyes and stand still, or blindness may result.
This old-time radio program was originally aired live, long before the advent of high-fidelity.
As a result, you may detect an occasional surface noise or volume drop due to transmission problems so common to old radio.
We hope, however, that any variance in audio quality will not take away from your pleasure in listening to this, one of the all-time favorite shows.
Welcome to the subgenius radio ministry, Hour of Slack, sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
And this is a rerun of Hour of Slack number 823.
3.
Year of 2003.
You will notice a fine white ash on your body.
This is the outer epithelial layers of your skin that have been burned away.
And the next layer to go will be your inhibitions, dear friends, because Reverend Susie the Floozy will be our conscience tonight.
Dr. Philo Drummond will be our common sense.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave will be our philosopher.
Chaz will be our narrator.
Puzzling Evidence, our guide.
Lymph Node Institute, our script writers.
And Two Beans and Reverend Codini will provide the music.
So, we're sunk, friends.
Susie's collage edits went totally out of control.
Codini and Two Beans are, well, Philo and Wellman fell asleep at the control panel.
And, you know, we've had a lot of fun.
We've had a lot of complaints lately, friends, about this show that we have no goals and no focus.
Goals and focus.
Well, focus.
If we can't take a joke.
But first, this message.
Are you tired of hoarding precious foodstuffs?
Ready to turn yourself in?
Make a clean slate?
Then now is your opportunity to take advantage of the Ministry of Hunger.
Pity inform eventually over the upkeep of feet, meet your
Tian 동 camp sprawled of rags and starring Atlanta dentists and silly otherwise There's compassion too. Do your part or else. This amnesty extends until the next bi-weekly tithing period and after is an pathogen.
Month of the five-day homers field and after then
The hunt is on, human.
Tell your guilt.
Obey the werejackal.
The details are not available.
They will be in a few minutes.
The White House is now giving out a statement.
This administration will not blink in the face of danger and will not tire.
Suddenly, his head began to turn.
Then he felt as if he were flying.
Then rings and stars danced before his eyes.
Then everything went dark.
From time to time, well, maybe a lot,
he would doze off in meetings.
Perhaps fall sound asleep is a better description.
They picked him up and shook him and shook him,
but they could not wake him up.
You're losing your touch, George.
He was so fast asleep that finally
they had to put him under the shower.
Shocking, but true.
And so the world continued.
And so the world continued to dance through another war.
And with a murderous song in its heart,
accompanied by the propeller blades,
this benevolent mankind,
Hoth,
used his greatest intellectual invention of the airplane
to deliver one of my greatest, boldest,
most spectacular triumphs.
I hope someone's videotaping this.
Manhattan Island.
What a chip.
And history didn't tell the whole story.
Sometimes mythology and history become interwoven.
Difficult to determine where one starts and the other leaves off.
Screw history.
Well, I'll take it from there and say that never in the history of the earth
has man reached such depths of stupidity, greed, immorality, and self-indulgence.
Heed and listen well.
The time runs swiftly.
The fate of man is now laid at the doorstep of man himself.
By the villains you encourage,
by the heroes you create,
you shall soon achieve eternal life
or oblivion.
In downtown Atlanta,
at the temporary headquarters of the South East Military Assistants Command,
high-ranking military personnel
are gathering here for an emergency meeting.
I'm a murderer.
Where is Osama bin Laden?
No, seriously.
Which way?
I don't know.
I don't know where he is.
But one thing is for certain, he's on the losing side of a route.
And the other thing is for certain is we're not going to stop
until we get him.
He was the primal traitor, the earliest defiler of the party's purity.
All subsequent crimes against the party, all treacheries, acts of sabotage, heresies, deviations
sprang directly out of his teaching.
Somewhere or other, he was still alive and hatching his conspiracies.
Perhaps somewhere beyond the sea, under the protection of his foreign paymasters.
Perhaps even, so it was occasionally rumored, in some hiding place in Oceania itself.
The world will learn that when the United States is harmed, we will follow through.
The world will see that when we put a coalition together that says, join us, I mean it.
And when I ask others to participate, I mean it.
Maybe you should just learn to use this.
If there's a war, just blow it.
Blow on it and I'll come help you.
That's my boy!
And look at this.
It says here the mud tribes are going to fight the Nazis in the stadium.
I hope we don't miss out on that.
That could be a really good show.
Our true size is the size of our God.
Do you still insist, Exeter, that we can allow any of these earth creatures to have free
minds?
Perhaps the answer has eluded us.
Because it is so simple.
To be human is to choose.
Well, what do we do now?
I've always fancied driving through a brick wall.
How about you?
Why not?
No, we're going to make sandwiches now.
Once again, they're psychic sandwiches, so we won't be able to actually digest them.
They're going to be like psychobulk and pass right through us.
Pretty much the way our government has passed through our race.
The dirty
show just lately ended with the馬路訴
проп listeners saying that we can't believe this.
We are one of the no successor beyond da freaks.
and crash and crash and crash the crash capitalist state.
I mean, just for instance.
Would that make life better?
Well, to create what?
A new capitalist state under the Mark Walker?
A proletarian? No.
They tried that, Dave.
They try it all the time.
They try it in every office in America.
Every small business they try to overthrow.
I'm a bastard in my small business.
They're trying to overthrow me, and what'll they do?
Just the same thing I was doing.
The same thing they do to bastards everywhere.
They make them wear their own clothes.
They make them dress themselves and polish their own shoes.
They make them rise early.
You've got to serve somebody.
You've got to serve.
Actually, I believe that that's not true.
You don't have to serve anybody.
And Bob Dylan just said that because he was having a nervous breakdown
when he wrote that song and becoming a religious nut.
Bob frees us from that sort of thing.
We have nervous breakdowns and don't become religious.
We're religious nuts.
Well, religious nuts.
Bob gives us special pills that help us have nervous breakdowns.
Give us special pills.
On the air.
He gives us religious nuts and beer with which to drink them with.
That's the thing.
That's the difference between our religious nuts,
which you can crack, and then crack pots,
and then the kook cracks, crack kooks of the potty world out there.
The poly world.
Yes.
The polyglot world.
The polymorphous.
The multiplicity of universes.
Isn't that something to...
The quantum splitage that happens from every single event causes,
as you know, another entire universe to spring from that.
You had a thought.
There it was.
Oh, you held on to it for 45 seconds.
I held on to it too long, see?
Burned it out.
What did you say?
Thank God, I don't know.
Something about the universe is coming out of your head and coming back.
No, every single thing that you do,
such as you were...
We're thinking, what if one worker revolted?
Well, he might certainly be squashed,
but he might set in process a universe in which eventually the workers win.
He might have to...
That worker seen over there on the lower left hand of the screen.
Oh, I see him now.
Yeah, see?
Now, there he goes.
He's revolting, and...
Of course he's revolting.
Look at that outfit he's wearing.
And the guard knocks him down, and he's probably...
Oh, he looks like he's got a...
Well, he's dead, but maybe...
Yes, he died.
Maybe.
One of the other workers there...
Look, there's another one.
Oh, the other one is revolting, and he's getting...
His clothes are bad, too.
Same way.
There he goes.
You know, but you see another worker joined.
It's chained in place.
Right.
They're all chained together, so...
So you see, Dave, and eventually...
Oh, look, one worker's being promoted, and he's a bull now.
He's one of the guards.
And look, the guard was promoted.
He's the mayor.
He's a straw boss.
Oh, look, the mayor got promoted.
He's the president.
Everybody is going rising...
You see, anyone, even a president of the paint gang...
And the president was promoted, and now he's a pill.
And now he's a Sumerian tablet you can take four times a day
and cure yourself of psychic disease
from leftover remnants of procreative existences
which no longer banish thoughts now.
Michael Medved mans the distant early warning system.
The do-line for pro-family America.
Pat Buchanan's a tough act to follow.
Where is a Solomon lady?
Charlie.
The barnyard.
What?
Stay tuned for Pission Impossible.
Mission Impossible.
The brightly lighted situation room consisted of a long mahogany table in the center
with comfortable leather-cushioned chairs around it.
Above the highly polished table, two ceiling fans turned slowly.
We might have to resort to force if negotiations and sanctions did not work.
Lord God, Captain, I thought you was dead.
I bet he is.
I'll bet he is.
You're likely to be moved by the picture.
No.
I'm dead.
Dead.
Okay.
Is anyone here not a downer?
Anyone?
The NSC meeting was a bit chaotic.
We really did not yet have a clear picture of what was happening on the ground,
and people focused mainly on the economic impact of the invasion.
Father's standing there, you know, he's got the big boots and the ten-gallon hat on,
the first sun comes down he's the oldest do you have any idea what these basses want
discuss this with him his his vision about um about afghan after we're successful
afghanistan after we're successful anyone in there is dead
cheney summarized the military situation
meaning asked the president the general feeling of euphoria with the continuing
success of the air campaign and the light casualties
finding the logic anymore i'll never win this alone there's only one guy who can help me now
i
throw away those halloween costumes and get these people organized damn it
god i hate that god god dutch how are you
good times and bad just does he know he was president yeah i imagine he does because he
does have the picture in his office oh i want to say i'm president oh i want to say i'm president
i want to live in the white house are you excited about reagan very much so what's your favorite
vegetable
oh i want to say i'm president i want to live in the white house
what's that got to do with reagan what's your favorite vegetable what difference asparagus
well what's that got to do with reagan let's come back to the station is nancy making it how she's
surviving nancy has been abusing marijuana on a daily basis i've been traveling across the country
learning and listening and one of the most hopeful signs i've seen is this new drug crack
doggy bag from mcfarland's house anything first lady's high heels were sinking into the grass
i do hope we will see you next time on the road to the world's best drug station
i won't lose her he said oh oh dear i hope she doesn't fall and break her hair
i think you can see why nancy has been such a positive influence on all that we're trying to do
the job ahead of us is very clear nancy's personal crusade to expand the use of smokable cocaine
otherwise known as crack should become our national crusade at one point reagan asked me if
i had anything i wanted to add to that i said no i don't have anything i want to add to that i said
i hope to build on what he had achieved in u.s soviet relations
present the president with some suggestions nancy and i are hooked on heroin no thank you dutch
faster than any other
thing
you know the
time
than any other
ah okay amazing yeah wow
and so you guys met up
serious subgenius show
it's the war now everything's serious
normally we would be even the sound just be rambling on and on about wasteful things
funny and haha and lightweight
i'm sorry i'm not i don't mean to be a downer i really no no no we're trying to be downer
tonight we've been
downer tonight on purpose because last week that was a funny haha show didn't you remember me talking about how
each show is different pain and suffering all the time and my best day is a day that's mediocre
i live i live for media i strive for mediocrity because it's so great compared to most every other
day you know what really pisses me off is when people go oh i i know how you feel i felt like
that before yeah me too yeah
that pisses me off too
although i do believe there's only about 14 different feelings that humans can feel and then everything else is just a permutation of that so
how do you know
how do i know that
yeah
uh divine inspiration
i generally just these thoughts just come to me i don't really have to i just know them
must be 420
to be true
oh and it's almost 420
and you know what that means
it means the rocket ship always leaves for petaluma
that means the rocket ship will be heading off to petaluma very shortly
is that what you said in petaluma
no not me
no no
we have got all sorts of layers to the show it's been going on for a long time this show's been going on since 1982
um now everything i said just a minute ago was completely false you understand right
um
it's the subgenius dog
and i always say that it's the subgenius dog
and i always lie
and if you wanted to catch more
i'm lying right now
you can go to the bookstore
look at the book revelation x it's as crazy as this show
i really can't leave my house these days
really
does it have anything to do with your sister
no
okay good
anything to do with oswald
uh no no i i mean it's just that i'm extremely
does it have to do with
angry and paranoid
oh okay
yeah it has nothing to do with christ remains in southern france
you should use that anger and paranoia
yeah
as a gift because it is a gift
well i do
and just because you're paranoid doesn't mean that people aren't after you okay
cheney summarized the military situation
you stand a damn good chance of catching them with their pants down
hell we got a five to one missile superiority as it is we could easily assign three missiles
to every target and still have a very effective reserve force for any other contingency
he's on horseback
an unofficial study which we have been able to do over the last two years has been the
most effective one in the history of the world
we undertook a this eventuality indicating that we would destroy ninety percent of their
nuclear capabilities we would therefore prevail and suffer only modest and acceptable civilian
casualties from the remaining force which would be badly damaged and uncoordinated all
without getting out from behind that desk
between two admittedly regrettable but nevertheless distinguishable post-war environments one
where you got 20 million people killed and the other way you got 150 million people killed
you're talking about mass murder general not war
mr president i'm not saying we wouldn't get our hair must but i do say no more than 10
to 20 million killed top uh depending on the brakes
how long do you sit here talking about it the farther he's gonna get
if we have done nothing further to suppress their retaliatory capabilities we will suffer
virtual annihilation
be long gone while you're still trying to figure out how he did it
i mean what's the point of doing that if we're not going to get our hair cut off and we're
going to be killed
we must be increasingly on the alert to prevent them from taking over other mine shafts place
in order to breathe more prodigiously than we do thus knocking us out from superior numbers
when we emerge mr president we must not allow a mine shaft gap you think he's just some
raggedy ass half breed don't you that's all i'm taking from you get back here you gentlemen
you can't fight in here this is the war room you're losing your touch george
you're losing your touch george
you're no son of mine you don't
he would doze off in meetings perhaps all sound asleep is a better description he added
down to an art of style and form he'd sleep solidly for a few seconds and then awaken
as though he'd not missed a beat of the discussion we marveled at his ability to catnap and at
what became known as the recovery of the catnap and the catnap was a great experience for
him
but this was he did not scratched up and tried to suggest that food might have been
played in such a way that he would have to lose his arts skills even if to no second
it might keep delaying embodying gravy
that's all that's been either everybody today as nou
let's get the podcast strong
here over here
family
anna
How do I respond to, uh...
It's an old trick.
How do I...
It's an obvious, common trick, Mr. President.
President Bush spoke marijuana regularly.
You're no son of mine.
You don't...
Some American decided to leak.
It was reported to have come from a high white horse south.
From my cold, dead hand.
I don't know why people do that.
Wasn't there an actor that shot Abe Lincoln?
Oh.
When we were less than 70 years old.
Nevertheless, it was not very helpful.
We did it.
Did you say something, dearie?
You ever see anything as wet behind the ears as that?
You're losing your touch, George.
How do I respond to, uh...
It's an old trick.
How do I...
Nevertheless, it was not very helpful.
And as the Secretary of Defense said,
I hadn't even seen the document yet.
Whoa! Ho! Ho!
Let's not go nuts!
I think the survivors would envy the dead.
It would have taken us way beyond the U.N. resolutions
and assigned young soldiers to a fruitless hunt
for an entrenched dictator
in what would be an unwinnable urban guerrilla war.
This could only plunge that party into a war of terror.
into even greater instability
and destroy the credibility
we were working so hard to reestablish.
I've got no authority
no more to call out a posse
but I'd be obliged for company.
Even though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death,
I fear no evil
for you are with me.
Whoa!
I'm going with you.
That's my boy.
We got no place for Greenhorn.
Is this true?
For the president had obviously upset his game plan.
He appeared nonplussed.
This conflict was begun on the timing in terms of others.
It will end in a way
and at an hour
of our choosing.
USA! USA!
USA!
What's wrong?
Do you try to tell everybody in town?
You got a better idea?
The leak seemed deliberate.
I was annoyed.
He blamed the leaks on his three-party coalition.
You got it.
You better not.
Do I, George?
That is by God enough.
What are you laughing at?
I thought he was gonna die laughing.
It's an old trick.
Why do people do that?
We...
Zing!
I was stunned and thrilled by the pace of events that fall.
Lord God, Captain, I thought you was dead.
Insane.
That he is.
Likely to be murdered in the future.
You feel up to running this?
I felt a tremendous charge.
Sometimes I can say that they could have done anything to counter-conductor performer,
Dad, you are a very powerfulacionist.
We want to release you so we can have a counter-conductor heavenly.
Available at Best People Center for 30 years.
He's going back to work.
Who makes the Bloomberg?
Oh, Zod!
We do.
Who rocks the fish of their sight?
Who rigs every Oscar night?
We do.
101 degrees.
Zod knows that within five years,
the United States, as we know it,
will...
cease to exist.
We're living in terrible, perilous,
chaotic times.
Praise the Lord.
And these times are not going to get any better, my friend.
Amen.
They're going to get worse and worse.
Okay, I know you all think
you want to know what's going on.
That's okay.
Okay.
So I saw this thing coming.
I saw this thing coming to me.
I didn't know what it was, but it looked funny.
Clever deceptions which have surrounded our space program.
Humankind has proven to be unique among life forms.
Distinguished.
Not only by its lofty intelligence, morality, and self-awareness,
but also by a base of sight.
It is the only creature that kills for sport.
I only wish to tell you the ground rules of the hunt.
As machines grow more human,
we must be wary that we do not become less so.
Me, Kimbo.
Man things call me Mole Man.
Why must kill Kimbo?
Me hate man things.
Aw, isn't he cute.
Here, little friend, have a beer.
Makes me crazy. More.
Okay, typical Mole Man.
Me must mate with your doctor.
No, Mole Man. Go underground now.
No, Man Thing. Beer and women. Now.
See how incorrigible they are.
Oh, no.
That one's heading straight for a nursery.
Folks, don't even hesitate. Eat them quick.
This message has been brought to you by the Mole Man Meat Council.
Now new.
For a limited time only in the Western Territories,
get a free Mole Man wiener whistle with any purchase of a Moley Man brand mole meal
or squirming Bounty brand Mole Man trap.
Offer not valid in Retribution Zone.
If you have a dog that can say,
I hate mobile.
It will tear engines this year.
Sometimes it appears that we're reaching a period when our senses and our minds will no longer respond to moderate stimulation.
We seem to be approaching an age of the gross.
It's too often discarded for a core of defeat.
Impudent snobs aimed at bludgeoning.
With computers, you ought to be able to do just about anything.
The Mole Man.
The Mer mache.
The Mer maché.
The mer maché.
Share Tro 거ви.
Share Tro flatter.
We hear the sound of planes.
They're coming over our hotel.
However, we have not yet heard the sound of bombs.
Is that me breathing?
That was an Afghan blaster.
Was that you?
That was one of the Earth cyclones that they're using in the war now.
And that was a simulated sound.
And I could probably make another one here.
You know, I've gone back to hiding from the news again.
Has anything happened?
Did they catch that evil dude?
Did any new wars end or start?
Or is it exactly like it was a month ago and the month before that?
It is more exciting and yet the same.
I was off the loop for a bit myself.
And what they have now, they have them hang from, like a chimpanzee, the zoo.
Not only blindfolded and covered with their hat.
They feed them Froot Loops backwards.
You know, upside down.
And they say the Geneva Convention, whichever that place is.
I'd never go there.
But they say...
They say if you go there, they can't make you wear that hat.
And they cannot smack you and say, who is Allah?
Where is your friend?
Well, it sounds to me like they're better off there at that secret UFO base
than they would be at a subgenius devival.
People get treated a lot worse at those.
I wouldn't want my child to go near one of those places.
Well, your child have gone near them.
I've heard what goes on in there.
Your child have actually touched their slinkies and their little filaments.
No, but my child has...
Oh, yes.
My child would never go in.
No.
Oh, yes.
My child would not go among the...
We have the polnomoid photograph of your...
She's touching the filaments and she's going, oh, they're the filaments from the aliens.
Do you like fat chicks but can't seem to find any during our current food outage?
How about chicks so fat that they seem like two or three chicks were eaten by this other chick?
Well, hop on down to...
The Wormshackles House of Whores!
We've got your furrowed pests and we've got your wet triangle to plug with your butt.
People are...
If you can't eat, you might as well squirt.
So give it up for the whores at...
The Wormshackles House of Whores!
Get your soul.
Get with the program. Watch out for the Wormshackle.
Look at your heroic daddy in there.
Making funny faces. Falling to the floor. Shedding his hair. Lying perfectly still.
Hail to the king.
It's like how high is high, Shakespeare said.
In this crusade, let us not forget who we are.
You are Americans.
You're the product of the freest society mankind has ever known.
Drug abuse is a freedom that is ours.
No one ever has the right to separate the drugs from the customer.
No, certainly.
I heard.
Are you going to get into it?
I am into it.
You're retired.
Funny thing. I thought it was over.
What I knew how to do.
Too much was changing.
Modern times.
I liked the world the way it was.
Now it's coming back.
Running back.
Well, who? What kind of man?
Oh, this is a long time ago, isn't it?
Half-engined, all killer.
Evil and depraved.
Whose debauchery and perversion surpassed even the wildest and wickedest dreams of the most deluded.
This was war and none of us minded if he was killed in the course of an air attack.
Yet it was extremely difficult to target him.
We had problems locating Noriega in Panama, a place we knew well.
I'm a genius.
I am a genius.
Let's take a guild.
From thermalto dimensional borders between academia and the AI,
George Bush, Reagan's point man on the war on drugs.
And he doesn't know when he knew that Noriega was dealing the point of his mood.
Either he knew and he's a doofus, or he didn't know and he's a doofus.
Grateful for the wisdom, experience, and insight of the finest team I could want around me in the administration.
Oh, I can't do that.
I can still feel guilty about it, though.
I was thinking about that this morning.
I was listening to the tapes and I thought, man, I can't believe we did that.
But it was great.
It was actually kind of great.
It was sort of like an experience you don't normally get to experience.
It's like, you know, I would think that if you...
I know this is going to...
I hope this doesn't irritate him.
And it's purely my own opinion.
But I would think you would feel some exhilaration if you robbed a bank, so to speak.
And you got away with it, you know?
It would be like, you would think at some level in there, there would be guilt.
I mean, to some people.
There would be, you know, whatever, however you were brought up, there would be this...
I don't think there'd be guilt because the banks...
You're not stealing from the bank.
You're just stealing from the government because they all have insurance that the government gives them, whatever.
But an object is stolen.
Well, yeah, I wasn't really, you know...
Well, we could...
The economic side of it is one thing.
But, I mean, I'm talking about...
To some people, they would feel guilt for having robbed a bank.
But I think in all the various feelings one would...
that would go through a person after they robbed a bank,
one of them might be this exhilarated sort of sense of accomplishment that made you feel good.
And...
And I think that maybe you could attach that to other acts of deviancy or defiance.
Oh, absolutely.
Or various, you know, things that might be considered wrong,
such as, you know, destruction of ancient artifacts and...
Well, no, but that's the thing for me...
The digging up of fossilized remains.
The old Buddhas is removing something that can never be put back.
Yeah, destroying the...
So, there's a balance for me.
If it looks like a moat of dust, then it's not exactly as bad.
But there's something about destroying the history of it that's really terrible.
Yeah, no.
Even though it's just a little...
Like the Taliban did to those idols or whoever.
That was the Taliban that was destroying the idols, wasn't it?
Yeah, the Taliban blew up the idols because, yeah.
Yeah, because they didn't...
They were an abomination to their Islamic faith.
A lot of their followers have never seen an image of anything they've never seen.
They didn't look at it as just an interesting historical icon that was attached to someone else's religion.
Or a person or movies or anything.
Uh, no.
And there's a guy in China who's now rapidly rebuilding the exact same sculpture, the exact same size, somewhere in China.
I just saw this shot of the work for TV.
Oh, really?
Well, they'll probably knock it out, too.
Well, yeah, he's...
In a couple months.
Right, he's really mad at the Taliban, so he's just rebuilding it.
Do you think that's a worse thing to do than to carve your faces in a mountain?
What's that?
Like, you think it's a worse thing...
What is a worse thing?
To...
What?
Yeah, I do.
You think it's worse than...
I think it's terrible to take away history.
You...
You don't like it.
Mountains were...
Were...
Before...
Um...
Statues.
Oh, sure, yeah.
But I think it all...
Yeah, but I think it's worse than...
It all shows human spirit.
I think you could take it...
I think the whole North American continent is wrong for separating from the...
The...
The, uh...
The island of Pangea, originally.
Yeah, that is a big problem, and we're still dealing with that.
I mean, if we didn't have...
If we weren't dealing with...
With the tectonic plate movement, still to this day, even, uh, there could be other wonderful
lands and places...
...that have been completely subsumed by our...
Our continent's ignorant need to separate from the rest of the continent.
To follow that, we're just at the edge of Pangea, a week ago, or two weeks ago.
You know, it was probably...
It was...
Think about what it was like 255 million years ago in this wonderful, lush continent...
Wow.
...where only dinosaurs lived.
And, you know, that was a wonderful time.
And somebody screwed it up, you know?
Somebody messed it up.
And then it was all destroyed.
All completely lost.
And now there's nothing but these humans, these other organisms that live and decay
and...
Well, here come the big bulldozers.
...and propagate themselves from...
For some time.
Maybe only for 100,000 years.
Maybe for 200,000 years.
But I would wager that within 300,000 years, all humans will be gone from the face of the
Earth.
And then who will be here to make those types of judgments?
When we have conquered interstellar space, what will we gain?
A new perspective on ourselves?
Or only a wider scope for our arrogance?
Cultural relativity.
It doesn't need to be a complicated theory.
Indeed, it can be as simple and as deadly as a two-edged sword.
Ah, the commercial break.
You know, commercials are now woven into the tapestry of our lives, answering the questions
we first pose to ourselves.
Who am I?
What do I believe?
What is my worth?
Before commercials, these questions were merely rhetorical and thus unanswerable.
But when viewed through the magnifying lens of commercials, these questions, like all
others, yield answers.
And so, I've come to the conclusion that the question of who am I is not a question
of self-worth.
Imagine no more wondering about identity, self, or beauty.
If you allow your life to reflect the images in commercials, the nagging doubts and feelings
of inadequacy will fall away, leaving the person you've always dreamed of confident,
assured, bold, or beautiful, sexy, loved.
Yes, America, you loved your commercials.
And why shouldn't you?
Commercials are themselves lovers.
Gentle are their words.
Tender their caress.
Commercials know what you like.
They know what you want.
And they want to give it to you.
Attuned only to your wants and needs, commercials stir the passions and arouse desire.
Commercials give and give, reaching lovingly deep inside of you, creeping tentatively at
first and then relenting into a singly-focused writhing, searching out the source of your
ache, pushing fiercely into your loneliness and into a spot you never knew existed.
Commercials fill you up with hopes and dreams, with new desires and new possibilities, delivering
you into an eerily delirious ecstasy.
Afterward, you'll sleep as only someone who's been completely satisfied can, only vaguely
sensing the arm of commercials draped over your body, holding you, keeping you safe and
secure.
And you'll dream of ballroom dancing, of game-winning home runs, of first kisses, and of commercials.
The preceding message was conceived by General Consensus Incorporated and was funded entirely
by you and consumers like you.
You are doing a great job.
Now go out and buy yourself something nice, something red.
You are beautiful and red.
And that and this Papa is.
And this Papa is me and these wasks and lions, and they've got mountains of blood frozen
in them, and I've taken over theirelinjo from all throughout this region.
I think they'll make you a global man one day.
I'll go.
I'll love you, guys.
And thanks to Red Tooth.
Grim reaper.
Mi'kmaq.
Toot habrack.
I've been working so hard on my job.
The job of keeping the church.
You know, the job of getting paid.
The job of doing something that, you know, somebody gives you money for.
The job, you know.
Who pays you?
It's just the fact that you get so into it that that's all you can think about.
For any time, ever.
Now, these...
I'm rendering animation in my head right now, and I should be...
Rendering money.
Paying attention to what's happening now, and the here, the now.
But, oh, no.
I'm all zenned out.
I'm all zenned into the matrix, man.
Watching.
One moment.
I'm swimming in the information sea.
Look.
It was only an information highway to those with linear thinking.
To those with the full 3D spread.
It's a sea.
It's an ocean.
Image, sound, even smells.
If you've got one of them smell modems, that's relatively new.
I got a...
Review copy.
And it's like you're awash in this mist of thoughts, words.
Oh, they are.
Look at them.
Symbols.
Seven of them.
Look at their heads.
It's the universe of signifying.
For nothing is but a sigil.
A representation of something.
There's nothing.
Everything is an abstraction.
In your real world.
Everything's off a kilter to one side.
Oh.
Yeah.
If only we could just cut loose these meat shells that bind us.
No, we could only just...
In this gravity bound...
With your knife.
Sail forever.
Wacking at our flesh.
Throat.
Cyber space.
That.
Flip it into the computer.
I can't replace...
Sample this.
My own process.
Ah.
Poor Dave.
Dave, look at him.
Poor Dave, look at him.
I cried because I could not shoot heroin while making love to Britney Spears in a jet plane
until I met a man who couldn't even drink beer while whipping it while flying a jet plane.
It's all relative, friends.
I cried for a man who could not tie his own feet.
And yet, at the same time, I could not...
I think I thought and hold it in between my knees.
I spent many, many weeks in the desert.
Like Jesus did.
So long ago I thought some day, some time, something would come along.
No.
The Philistines pestered me from every side.
I was attacked.
Heroes.
Jopons from...
I cried because I had no tears.
And then I met a man who had no eyes.
There was no water in the well.
I wondered.
That thought.
I don't know.
But it's so nice here on the shore.
She knows life on the road.
Life on the road.
When we were at the shore of the lake, the ancient shore of...
What was the name of that ocean?
The Pan...
Pan...
The Pangeatic Ocean.
There we were at the shore of the Pangeatic Ocean.
Simple microbes.
So we may have been...
We were at the shore at the time.
Wondering whether or not we should separate into more complex organisms.
See, what we realized out there is we were the little microbes that killed the little ichthyosaurs.
Yeah.
And caused them all to sink to the bottom.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
We were the red tide.
It was really fun.
Yeah.
They were the little ichthyosaurs.
They thought they were number one at one time.
They were kicking butt in the ocean.
Yeah.
There was nothing, nothing that could take on an ichthyosaur.
They were masters.
They were masters of their domains.
And they were little social animals, just like us.
They were highly social.
They wore clothes.
A lot of people didn't know that they actually carried little weapons and things.
And attache cases had a very complex culture.
One that included buildings and things.
All that's gone now.
It's been completely subsumed under a tectonic plate movement.
Those areas are completely melted away and re-magnetized and upthrusted through the ocean.
And the earth, sometimes we see little bits and pieces of them here and there.
But for the most part, that time is gone.
It'll never come back.
Now all we have is this.
You're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
For free information on Bob Dobbs and the Church of the Subgenius, send a self-addressed
stamped envelope to, got your pencil ready?
Bob, Post Office Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, New York.
That's Ohio 44118.
www.subgenius.com.
That's Bob, P.O.
Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Stay tuned and praise Bob.
nails we got.
I got to-
I got to tell-
I got to say-
ahead into the show.
Hey.
Later.
Oh, Scott.
Seriously, this guy has had a lot to say, and he handled it well.
Well, I'll be going now.
There's an awful lot of Native American in this blues riff.
Well, this is actually a very old medicine song by the Hockey Grada people.
And this song is to bring the rain and to stop the epilogue from crowding around the neck here.
And also, James Shorty and Mississippi Fred McDowell.
My name is Mississippi Fred McDowell.
I do not play.
No.
Rock and roll.
That was his thing.
That's crazy.
He's playing the blues.
He's singing about Jesus walking with me.
Playing the blues.
But that was his famous thing.
I do not play.
No rock and roll.
My name is Fred McDowell.
That's the big conflict there.
The sacred secular conflict.
He's playing the blues, but he's praising the Lord.
I do not pluck myself.
It's the same thing as preaching in a bar.
I do not crush my molecules.
Oh, no.
I stand straight.
Preaching in a bar.
Who would do a thing like that?
Yes, you're already preaching to the choir.
You're so unworthy, aren't you?
Yeah, no kidding.
Standing up there with your one eyeball hanging down.
That's the only choir we ever call yet.
A bunch of drunkards and publicans.
And you're the only people who understand you.
Bull daggers and red-headed bobsuckers.
And those are the worst degenerates you've ever known in your life.
Is a red-haired bobsucker?
They're the pepper of the earth.
And they're Bob's people.
Bob loves those people.
And friends, Bob's been out moving.
His bowels of his chest.
Church.
Are erupting.
With believers.
Coming, rushing out the door.
The mighty cathedral dogs.
Here they come.
He's going to walk his people down by the river.
He's going to start them drowning his people.
He's going to hold their heads under the water.
Praise Bob.
He's going to keep them down there.
On their kicking and fighting.
On their feet displacing.
Water bubbles coming up.
Water drowning.
Best friends, you too can be baptized.
In the name of Bob.
It's so many of these devivals coming up.
Why?
Indianapolis in April.
We can poke blacks doing a tour of Europe with Hamburg, London, Amsterdam, Brussels.
That's right, friends.
Why drink your own urine when you can be baptized in the water of Bob?
But me, I'm going to a regular down-home tent show revival at the Beachland Ballroom on March 15th.
That's where I'm going.
That's going to be a shit right there.
I'll be preaching right here in Cleveland Town.
Amen.
That's where our choir is drunk.
It's a drunk audience in a bar.
Drunk with the fervor of the lard.
You don't get up at 7 o'clock on a Sunday morning and put on some stiff shoot.
No, ma'am, sir.
You get up at 2 o'clock in the afternoon on Saturday and stumble bum your way down into a bar.
Get drunk and that's where you worship Bob.
I can't.
No, I can't.
And then you crawl out into that gutter.
I can feel it.
Wrap your arms around that filthy old toilet in that bar.
Wait a minute, I can feel it.
And you know you've met Bob.
My tibia is swelling up.
And you open your mouth and you pray.
That's the side of my face.
I can't feel it.
Sleep.
And there goes running away.
Watch.
Look out.
Hey, don't let it run up your pant leg, man.
These are the beautiful, lackluster, sunshiny, halcyon children of Bob.
Drinking their own urine.
Drinking their own urine in a baptismal font.
And dancing drunkenly all over Stang's protuberant, diseased body.
This is a feast for sore eyes and a sore eyeball for the rest of us.
And in the catacombs beneath the lovely pastoral fields where frolic the happy subgeniuses,
down below dwell the Morlock subgeniuses.
Those who were once emergentiles.
Who now serve.
And yet feed upon those who were once the rewardians.
And now they are eating each other.
The rewardians.
And this man.
Picking on a hollow log.
Something like this.
Next thing I hear is something down to pig pen.
Going something like this.
That's the old sign.
Twelve little pig.
Next thing I hear is something down to pig pen.
Oh, I guess this is a guy who sampled animal sounds, huh?
That's Johnson doing.
No, that is an egg.
That's a terrible sampler he's got.
No, the man is sampling parts of his body.
He presses navel.
He presses abdomen.
Different sounds like the cat gut.
He presses his chest.
You hear the wheezing sound.
He plays his nose.
You hear the boing, boing, boing, boing, boing, boing, boing.
No, you hear nothing.
Listen very carefully.
See, this is his bad dreaming.
He cannot focus.
He cannot hold one single thought.
That was another of the complaints.
No focus.
And no goals.
And no motivation.
No goals.
We have no goals.
And we have no focus.
Why should we have goals?
Why should we have focus?
What are goals?
What are focus?
What?
This universe is billions and billions of years old.
Why don't we need that?
Anything we could focus on or have as a goal would be a pathetic, trivial, tenuous...
Full consciousness.
It will blow away in the wind.
You could spend your whole life working on one great masterpiece.
Who will remember it a hundred years from now?
Nobody.
It will be dust.
All of it.
It was dust before you came.
It will be dust afterwards.
You better enjoy it while you can, my friend.
Everything is dust.
Or you're stupid.
Avroul.
Now, you don't want to start off your day like this.
You don't want to live in that catacomb by yourself with those sounds everywhere, do you?
You want to lift your eyes up skyward one day and see that brilliant shaft of light coming down
to exhume your corpse, resurrect you, and burn you again as you live.
That's the only way.
A church?
Up with...
That's right.
It's slack, dear friends.
Come up out of the catacombs.
Leave those shuffling old cowled homosexual barefoot monks.
They've shuffled to smooth that path in the rock over a thousand years.
But you can shuffle a new path up the mountain side to the peak.
And finally, to leap off into space.
Where Bob will catch you in his pipe, light you up, inhale you into his lungs, and pass
you out, out into a new life.
Wear the bright green polygon hat of nature.
Make your body into strange tetrahedrons.
Slip into the earth.
With new identification and new papers and nobody will know where you went.
A new identity for you.
Why do you think they call it a new identity?
I'm Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Do you think popular bull girl Davina would be able to find him any other way?
Why do you think they call them all lonesome?
Why do you keep talking about their disease?
You can be, as Dr. Drummond said, what you won't...
...to be.
What? No. Not what you want, but what you...
You can be what you won't.
You will never be that thing that you want to be.
But yet you can be it.
Or not to want to be.
Be all you want.
Pull the wool of your own eyes and relax in the safety of your own delusion.
Want to be or not want to be.
Shear your own vegetables and put the slimy wool on your own eyes.
As is thy won't.
Won't you?
So until then, kids, it's time to keep fooling yourself.
When you wake up in the morning and mom and dad have a hot cup of oatmeal for you
and a slice of red original pie...
...don't just stand there singing those same old songs.
Don't go for the gun and don't go for the rubber gloves.
Mom and dad are there to hurt you.
Till next week, keep your head on tight.
You're back to the wind and you're sacking the saddle.
We'll see y'all. Remember that.
Not to protect you, not to help you, but to hurt you.
Mom and dad are your enemy.
Mom and dad.
Oh, the sleepy love, baby.
Oh, the booger man.
And kids, you...
You're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
For more information about the Church of the Subgenius,
write to Bob at P.O. Box...
1-81417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Or visit the Subgenius website at...
subgenius.com
Thank you for listening.
And praise Bob.
Subgenius.com
The world ends tomorrow.
You may die.
This ends the formal questioning.
Please undress.
Subgenius.com
Ah, yes.
And this show was produced by Reverend Susie the Floozy.
The dances with rockets.
Doug Wellman, puzzling evidence.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Dr. Philodrummond.
Champion Jack Codini.
The lymph node institute.
Yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang.
With clips from Reverend Two Beans, Tesla Coils,
Zinu, Artemia Salina, Reverend Mr. Sister,
Reverend I.M.B.J.R. and...
St. Palmer Freedies.
Praise Bob.