From NPR News in Washington, I'm under direction of an independent administrator.
The Justice Department says it has pee.
Senior Obama administration officials want to keep the pee.
Tom Pirelli says the department finished pee remains this weekend.
The Justice Department continues to investigate whether pee broke the disaster.
Coast Guard Admiral Thad Allen has resumed drilling a pee well that's slated to intercept the end of this week.
Coast Guard Admiral Thad Allen says...
President Obama says people can rest along the Gulf Coast.
We're excited that fish can go back to work. In fact, we had some yesterday.
President speaking as he welcomed taking a break.
But House Republican Leader John Boehner says...
Demanding and asking the question, where are the American people?
Boehner told NBC the way to stimulate the economy is by cutting hiring this morning.
Oscar-winning actress Patricia Neal is aimed at preventing...
tens of thousands of public school teachers and state and local government workers from NPR News in Washington.
Is this thing on? It is, huh?
It is on, and so are you.
You can scoot it over closer to your face if you want.
Oh, how many times have I fallen for that one?
How many times have you fallen for that one?
Too many. I'm starting to wear a pillow on my ass.
Helps on the landings.
Well, we have a great deal of material to go over today.
Some of the old tried and truisms need to be tried out once more.
Hashed out and beaten against the rocks and left out to dry.
Are you leaving too, Susie?
No, no, I'm not fleeing. I'm redistributing my wealth.
All right, well, let's have an even distribution of that.
I brought enough for the whole class.
Bounteous booty and begin our introductory religious lesson of instruction.
Welcome to the third 13X Day live hour of slack.
Which will sound really different the next time you hear it.
Well, yes, it will be specially augmented, but what about the background?
Do we have that today? Background?
Oh, background music?
Yeah, the background music track. There it is.
All right, now you see it.
It's a wonderful party.
It's wacky.
Yeah, we're all having a great time.
It's the unending cocktail hour here at X Day 2010,
the 13th X Day of beautiful summer weather here at the Brushwood Campground
where things are getting out of control.
Whoa, it's wacky, wild, goofy, wiggly.
I've never been in control in Brushwood. That's what's so wonderful about it.
Let us not disabuse the unenlightened of their long-cherished, if pathetic, beliefs.
Of course, control, unillusion, superimposed over the hideous, indifferent face of the universe.
But we live by such illusions. At least I know I do.
That's how you pull the wool over your own eyes.
Yes, with the realization that although you can never truly know unless all the factors are considered,
you also can never know all the factors.
So you just have to guess at it.
Yes.
Make a good guess.
And right then, and I tell you.
That's them again.
I wish there was someone to help me get out of this.
Yeah.
And I said, he goes, I'm still eating it.
Give us a little bit of, give us, give us some, some, a little bit more about this.
Sounds simple.
Yeah, so.
Thank God, it was good.
They can't.
He can barely walk.
Are you a peon?
Well, in other words, the show has been canceled.
You have no sympathy for the blind audience .
Well, it's traditional that we have no sympathy for the blind audience.
Well, that's true though.
Obviously.
We have no sympathy for the blind audience.
audience. They don't expect us to.
That's true. I can barely stand
to listen to your show. You have so little
sympathy.
It takes me like three days
to edit one of those two-hour shows.
I can't listen to it when I'm listening to it.
Just for that one minute. I have to take the
headphones off while I'm doing it.
Your shows are really hard to masturbate to,
Stang. It's really rude.
Oh, you mean Stang's
show is hard to masturbate to.
I'm glad you made that clear.
Well, we're hoping to change that.
I always choke the chicken to Dr. Hall
and Philo, though.
They always make me get my nut
and curl my toes.
Well, I told you about
masturbating Sean.
God masturbated himself to death listening
to our show.
My show has more masturbators than yours does.
I can't help it.
I don't know.
We have higher quality masturbators, though.
Well, our brains are out. Yours are still alive.
The highest quality. The most lovely.
We've tested our masturbators.
We've tested our masturbators through opinion research firms
and have found that
their knowledge
is in-depth.
They know exactly what they like,
what they want.
Now, do you know
which person they masturbate
to the most?
I know.
I'm sure each of you guys knows exactly
which is the most popular.
Yes.
They only masturbate to me in prison.
Nothing?
It's a moot?
No point in arguing with such geniuses.
We're just talking in a historical fashion.
I will not eat.
Hallelujah.
Here's the secret.
I no longer live.
Metamorphosis.
Hi.
All right.
Come on.
And, um,
so, you know, I, I,
I...
Messing around with the girls.
Get our girls pregnant.
Yeah.
Uh, uh, amen?
Amen.
And thanks, Reverend Heart Ignition.
Friends, aside from the Lemur cuts at the beginning,
all of the collages in this 1,270th hour
of Slack R. By Heart Ignition.
So glad to have him back in the saddle.
Now, before I get caught up in the spirit,
I need to announce two upcoming events.
One, August 27th through 28th,
the Devotional or Devo Convention.
At the Beachland Ballroom in Cleveland.
I will be preaching there.
And there'll be a whole lot more.
And October 9th,
the biggest subgenius event of the year,
aside from X Day,
a New York City Devival.
Yes, a huge, uh, show in Astoria, Queens, actually.
At a place called Wonderland something.
Uh, that's October 9th.
They'll be preaching by yours truly.
Uh, Pope Black.
Uh, I bet Dr. Legume will be there.
Reverend Bleepo Abernathy.
Priestess Pisces.
Susan Flusy might be there.
Who knows?
Oh, and music by Fat Free.
And, uh, Two Beans.
And who, anyway.
If you, uh, can,
check out subgenius.com,
the events button, and you will see.
Uh, now, you know, friends, uh,
I like to edit these shows down
so that nothing lasts longer than
three or four minutes tops.
Uh, well, except for the live blabber shows
where we're in the studio,
because we need to whip one out fast
and get caught up.
Well, this one is sort of like that.
At 13X Day, we did a couple of hours a day
of rambling live shows on stage,
as well as hours and hours of preaching
and live music.
But I'm finding myself hard-pressed to edit it.
And one reason is that some of it is insipid drivel.
And it's hard work making that sound like a silk purse.
But I came upon one stretch of recordings
that I feel should, despite its sow's ear nature,
be left more or less uncut.
Uh, one morning at 13X Day,
uh, July 3rd,
Dr. Howell, Reverend Susie the Floozy,
Dr. Philodrummon, and I started doing show
in front of many patient individuals.
And, well, most of it was insipid drivel, too.
Maybe we needed more coffee.
In fact, you'll hear us get more coffee.
But after a little while,
lonesome cowboy Dave showed up,
and that's where it turned into
a old-timer, subgenius, fundamentalist,
back-to-the-pamphlet, classic-inspired
insipid drivel.
Because suddenly here you had almost all the key
subgenius radio show blabbermouths
of our 30-year history
all in one place at one picnic table.
Well, puzzling evidence and Phineas Narco were missing,
and lies and your broke friend are big sissies,
but here at one picnic table
on a little rascals-looking stage,
you had Reverend Susie the Floozy,
veteran of hundreds of Bob's Slacktime Funhouse shows
on WREK in Atlanta,
who incidentally did not wear her shirt
for some of this presentation.
You had me and lonesome cowboy Dave
from Hour of Slack in WCSB Cleveland,
and you had Dr. Howell from the Puzzling Evidence Show
and the Ask Dr. Howell Shows in Berkeley and San Francisco
with his co-star and actor,
actual first and only overman
and co-sub-founder of the Church of the Subgenius,
lead singer of the Swingin' Love Corpses,
webmaster of QuiveringBrain.com,
director of the Subgenius Film Festivals,
and close personal friend of J.R. Bob Dobbs himself,
Dr. Philo Drummond.
All those people in one place.
Now we'll also hear some music and sermons
by Reverend Skull and Reverend D. Lister,
but first let us now to the uncut
and unfettered, skinner-breaking master recording itself
from 13X Day.
I was going to point out a theory that I have,
or really it's just an observation,
and friends, this is not a value judgment,
about monster fans versus comics fans.
Sometimes it's the same thing,
but I'm more of a monster fan.
Now I've noticed the primary image
that goes with monster movies and books
is a great big ugly,
ugly guy carrying a pretty girl
wearing very little clothing.
Carry on monster.
Whereas the primary image for comic book fans
is two men in tights grappling with each other.
Hitting each other.
Like I say, I'm not making a value judgment,
but I'm a monster fan.
Did anybody watch Octoman the other night?
Sure enough, he picks up the girl
and starts plodding along with her
for a long, long time.
You know, you gotta have that.
The carry.
It was so dark.
The Creature from the Black Lagoon.
It was a very dark movie.
Not even the same species.
But when he sees Julie Adams,
he has to pick her up and just carry her along.
Who wouldn't?
Yeah, well I would, but...
Well, I think your observation
about men grappling...
Didn't you say you met Julie Adams?
Is that turning you on, Dr. Drummond?
Well, I have to...
It just seems so odd
that you would make that observation.
Men grappling versus monsters fondly.
I never noticed it before.
Do you know how I was talked into meeting you
for the first time, Dr. Drummond?
This is historic.
My sister-in-law said...
You mean you had to be talked into it?
...that I knew in Austin
had moved to Dallas, staying,
and you should go see these folks
because you'd really hit it off with this guy.
And I said, I hate everybody.
I don't want friends.
And she said, well, this guy's different.
Now, she goes,
he's into comic books
and Captain Beefheart.
Now, that describes every subgenius.
But at the time,
I didn't know anybody else.
I knew lots of people who liked comic books
and lots of people who liked Captain Beefheart.
But not both.
It was the crossover that made that...
It was that foreign index key
that made it easily retrievable
by that one odd character in the crowd
that there's a whole bunch of here.
I went over to your house in Dallas,
and then he showed me
what was even better than the comic books,
his collection of kook pamphlets.
And that was when I knew
that Philo and I were true Yeti mates.
Because, you know, Captain Beefheart
and comic books
and a big collection of Jack Chick comics,
now you're talking.
Chick tracts attract chicks.
So it wasn't long before
we were cranking out kook pamphlets
and horrible music.
And bad comics.
Yeah.
That's great.
Which is the church.
We learned from the great.
The greatest.
And of course,
Philo introduced me to Bob.
I did not know anything about it,
but he had been recruited before anybody else.
Isn't that incredible, ladies and gentlemen?
Can't avoid that guy.
Captain Beefheart helped bring us together.
Yeah.
Now, I heard that Bob kidnapped Philo
when he was a young boy
from a W.T. Grant's restroom
and like kept him in Tucson
and raped him for 20 years.
It's amazing the stories you hear
about people's childhoods.
I heard it was a Woolworth's restroom.
And that's why he walks that way?
I heard that it was a wolf.
He was a wolf cub in those days.
Hey, look, there's...
Oh, my God!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
So here he is.
Oh, look, he's not so lonesome after all.
We thought we were going to have to get ragtime Cowboy Joe.
Hey, I can tell he's been wrestling.
He's got that Band-Aid across his forehead
where he bladed himself so he'd bleed,
you know, for the show.
You're going to peel that Band-Aid off later
and bleed for everybody, right?
Boy, there's a bunch of old people up here now.
That's right.
Hey, now I got this little half-erect mic.
Here, buddy.
I'm going to take a mic again.
How'd this happen?
It's only half-erect, I think.
Yeah.
What's BFC stand for?
What's that banging against the table?
Suzy will show you how to work that thing.
I can't believe it says,
I never made that connection before.
There are no connections here now.
BFC.
Yeah.
Dave, can I get your cup of coffee?
Surely.
Okay.
We got it.
And the lard to put in it.
Oh.
Ah.
I'm not used to that.
Did everyone have their beans and lard this morning?
Did you?
So we've been waiting for you.
You had your beans and lard this morning?
I love you so much.
Did you have your beans and lard this morning?
Mrs. Mammy Whistle, you there with the unguentine hair, did you have too much this morning?
Too much.
That's your old fella.
Thanks, Pap.
Happy?
All right.
Creaming your coffee?
So just the new guys get coffee?
You got a little rope clusters if you need those.
What about those of us that have been here before?
Do we get coffee?
See nuts.
I have.
Do we get any coffee?
You can sure get it.
Yeah.
You can go over there and get that.
Where is it?
I'll get you coffee.
From the coffee service.
Actually.
It's right back there.
I'll get you coffee.
I'm going to squat down here.
That's in keeping.
Let's have the woman serve the coffee.
Nothing to do with that.
I don't need any cream in my coffee this time.
There's no coffee.
Don't want no sugar in your pudding.
Hey, guess what?
There's no coffee.
It was all a sham, a mockery.
This is filled with dark colored mucus, man.
Just drink it.
No, I see it.
Coffee.
Drink up.
You look like a professional wrestler, Dave.
You look like a professional wrestler.
You've got cups.
You can pretend like you're drinking coffee.
You've got the bandaid on your forehead.
You know?
Like you're getting ready to take it off during the match, you know, when somebody
gives you a chair shot.
Well, we're going to have coffee, and we're going to have a lot of things, and I don't
think we need to quarrel over coffee.
And we certainly don't need to talk about the trevination scar here, which was a poor
attempt.
No, thanks.
I won't use the cream.
I won't need the cream right now.
You know, lonesome cowboy Dave, I appreciate your scar.
No, no.
It's perfectly fine.
But I have to say, it must pale besides the cream.
It's a great scar of legume, which has been on display for the past couple of days.
But it's a fine, righteous scar.
Where is legume?
Is he here?
He's back there, that scarred bastard.
Saw him earlier.
There he is.
Yeah.
Man.
Has he shown his scar yet?
He has shown it.
He's been showing that scar.
I'll show it to you, by appointment only.
His butt crack goes all the way up the back of his spine, up over his head, down the nose,
across the lips, and down the front again, and he's got a camel toe.
That was one hell of a surgery.
You've got a zipper.
You need a camel toe.
He's got two camel toes now.
I think they just chainsawed him down, froze him first, and kind of .
I see him back there, looking up here.
Look, he's nodding his head.
He's not happy.
He died five times, and they didn't bring him back.
He doesn't like this particular conjecture, this angle, this tangent.
Not while he's drooling like that.
Cowards die many times before their deaths.
Although I saw his eyebrows go up that time.
The valiant never tasted death but once.
Dr. LeGim had his operation.
He was cut in half vertically.
Yeah.
He was cut.
He was bifurcated.
That was the only way to get that deep down inside.
Yeah.
That reminds me of that old Justin Wilson joke.
Remember?
He said they had a car wreck, and he asked his wife after the wreck, he said,
Honey, is you hurt?
She said, Oh, I'm cut from all the way up here to all the way back here.
And he said, I know, but is you hurt?
Justin Wilson.
You had to pee there.
Yeah, you had to pee there.
He was no Bill Hicks.
You had to have been him.
You're supposed to finish it with I guarantee.
I guarantee.
That's apparently where everybody knew they were supposed to be.
They said you were a pair of pants as well.
They hadn't laughed up to that point.
That's when they would laugh.
That's pink humor.
Nothing funny.
I guarantee.
But as soon as the catchphrase comes up, they know they're supposed to robotically
laugh.
That was funny.
I think that's during that time of double entendre, you couldn't really say that stuff.
You had to layer it on real heavy.
The days of sociopaths and double dildos.
Man, that was...
You get like Jeb and Cousin Easy doing the golf game where it's like, okay, you grabbed
your putter and...
Yeah, that guy that painted the pictures, but they were totally...
But it was for women that were painting in the nude.
Or men.
Painting men and women in the nude.
I painted in the nude a lot.
All those rocks I did.
Oh yeah, I got one of those rocks.
I painted those rocks naked.
I got a rock with a pipe on it.
And used to leave the studio doors wide open so everyone could see.
It's not a place of veneration.
Well, you painted those rocks?
I thought those were the angel turds.
Well, I shat them out first and then I painted them.
Don't worry.
I thought the angels shat them out already painted.
It's stagecraft.
The artwork was stagecraft.
I'm sorry to disabuse you.
I wanted to abuse you.
It was an angle, not an angel.
It was misplaced.
I'm going to find out what's supposed to be going on right now.
Well, we already had Biceys read the schedule.
You'll have to catch up.
Pay more attention.
You missed the naked stuff.
I got here late.
I didn't mean to get here late.
There was a lot of naked stuff.
It was great naked stuff.
Could it be replayed in front of us right now?
No, it could not because we do not photograph it.
That's part of the law there.
The girls won't take their clothes off if they know their grandma is going to be able
to see it on the internet tomorrow.
We have to take mental pictures.
Back before grandma was on the internet, oh, they'd show off their titties to every boy
with the camera.
But then granny got on America Online and immediately looked up subgenius.com.
I'm going to see what my little granddaughter televangelist has been up to.
See, the show's gotten better already.
Grandma's not a natural blonde.
See, that's all it takes to improve the show.
Oh, my God.
There's my little granddaughter televangelist.
Mom, I've got a great idea.
I was the presidential wrestling naked on a giant American flag.
With Janer.
With all you boys.
Yeah, with Janer.
Sexy on the American flag, sex through the windowpane.
Janer was given his chance.
I know what, Joss.
Lots of chances.
What was this about not snapping pictures?
Well, you know.
Yesterday, yesterday we lied and told the radio audience we were all naked, but this time
we're not lying.
We're not all naked.
Is there a neo-Nazi rally for peace tonight?
You know what I mean?
Brotherhood.
A rally? A neo-Nazi rally
for peace and brotherhood. A political demonstration
here at Brushwood?
I think we're beyond petty
human politics.
No one here is a Whig
or anything like that.
That's correct. We've left it all behind.
We've flipped the Whigs.
We've left the Federalist tissue
paper in the toilet where it belongs.
It's time to join the
ex-humanite party.
The ex-humanites shall
rise from the ashes.
And believe me, you're all a bunch of
ashes from what I can see right now.
If we're even thinking of it.
Yeah, well, I'm like a phoenix rising
from the ashes.
It ends a physical body. It has raised
the spiritual body.
And there is no such
thing. And staying reached
for his nuts. Ensure uncertain hope
of resurrection.
The day after tomorrow.
I wanted
more nuts. The love.
It's one more.
Would you think of it, Dr. Howell?
It's always propounded as to be the day after tomorrow.
When will the world end?
When will this new thing come about?
When will we all be lifted up into some sort of
potty chair? Some giant
fuzzy potty chair made out of
strange musicians?
We have a date and a time.
A date and a time.
Here comes the candy.
Candy for Mandy.
Lovely, sugary.
Candy.
There's peanuts on the microphone.
There's butterscotch. And there's chewy
nougat. There's blisters on the
bare butt. What's the point of
this? Oh, well, it's X-Day.
There's a weird cackling sound coming from the bushes.
What illegal piece of candy shall I
I warm up the getses by putting them between my boobs
first. What the hell is this?
Even on Halloween, I never saw.
It's got a
creamy center, which is disgusting.
It does. I generally steer clear
of those. You can poke your tongue.
But I just gotta try it.
Getses. Go out and give it
your best try right now.
I always have to tongue pork these.
I think, I think.
Therefore, I stink.
How obvious. You're drinking coffee.
You could have candy and coffee like they have
in Amsterdam. You're smarties.
These will make you smarter.
Brain candy.
Those are rabbit pellets.
Then you line it.
Put the lemon head in there.
It's sort of like a
Tootsie Roll that ran into an Oreo
at high speed for later.
But is there an anadol?
Wow.
It's another thing I hate. When you radio DJs get on
and start talking about how yummy the food
is that you're eating.
And the poor radio listeners, all they have to eat
is that sound coming out.
What's the part of our show that you like, Reverend?
Yeah, tell us something good that we do.
Tell us something that you like about it.
Why all this bitching about other radio shows?
The silent parts, right?
I'm the mean one. I have to talk.
There's gotta be something.
I mean, if you were recommending our show to somebody,
what would it be?
We were taking a breath, right?
I would say that listening to the
puzzling evidence show is like walking
through a dream.
A world in which you were at the
party of the most clever,
spontaneous surrealists.
To compete, it's like...
You could ever imagine.
It's like attacking an evil monster
with a tiny little sausage.
It's like...
This can't be done, but you valiantly try.
You hold that sausage aloft and you...
And then layer on some
unlistenable pop music.
Japanese pop.
I'm sorry.
You certainly are.
What do you think?
There's a phone call coming in?
Is Washington calling?
Has Washington called yet?
When are we gonna have to
start getting entertaining?
I'm not sure.
We're not sure.
It's been the last three hours,
hasn't it?
Well, we got the background picture
and we got the background music.
The band wants their microphones back.
I'll put my shirt back on
and we can begin.
The band wants their microphones back.
Who wants to fumigate them this time?
Has anyone in the listless audience
spouted one of these unusual tumors lately?
I mean, just out of the clear blue,
it just pops out real hard
and it points at different radio frequencies.
Does anybody know?
I got one.
I had that once.
It's more like a three more.
I can cut it out with a big knife.
I can help you out with that
if you need some help.
Can't you just bite the head off it
and sploot it?
We do a biopsy.
You look like you've got the shangs for it.
Could you give it a try?
We do it just like a biopsy,
but we forego all the scientific part of it.
How did you stumble over that?
I had no idea.
We'll be right back.
Bob.
Well, thank you.
Boggles my mind.
D. Lister.
I don't know about the rest of you,
but I have been out there
in the world of the pinks and the normals
preaching the word of Bob.
Praise Bob!
And the most frequent question that I am asked is,
how can I get slack?
If you have to ask,
then you cannot get slack.
Because slack is not something
that you can strive to attain.
Am I right?
Slack is something that comes to you
when you least expect it.
And if you are asking for it,
then you will never get it.
It's kind of like sex in that way, isn't it?
Well, those of you who have not experienced sex yet,
I guess can't really answer that question.
Sorry.
But anyways,
the slack that I have been experiencing here
has been the best slack that I have had.
But yet, I'm sure there's better slack out there.
Am I right?
Yes.
There can be.
Because there's always better slack
than what you have had.
Because there's no limit
to the quality of the slack
that you can experience.
No limits.
Because if there was a cap
on the slack quality,
then once you achieve
the limit of slack,
then what else would there be to live for?
There wouldn't be nothing.
Exactly, brother.
Until the fucking exes get here,
which we hope they will do
in less than 36 hours,
then we must strive
to
not care about our slack.
And that's how we will get our slack.
But also,
the people that are out there,
that are here,
that are just wandering around,
milling around,
just doing whatever the fuck they want,
that is slackful.
I will admit that is slackful.
However,
there should also be
some helping out with everything.
Right?
Volunteering.
Is volunteering a good thing, Pisces?
It certainly is.
Is that good slack from volunteering?
There is a definite slack reward
for volunteering, yes.
If you give away that slack,
you'll get it back.
Thank you.
If you didn't hear that,
if you give the slack,
you get it back.
You can help out in many ways.
Pick up trash that you see.
That will give you slack.
Help at the bridge desk
or the slack desk.
Slack shack.
Swag shack, whatever.
That gives you slack.
But,
as Reverend Sex Mortis said,
the most important thing
is to not fuck
with anyone else's slack!
Because fucking with someone else's slack
is the anti-slack!
And nobody wants the anti-slack.
No!
Whoo!
Praise to you, Lister!
Thank you, robot!
Whoo!
Dave, I noticed that you're wearing a bandage
over your third nostril.
I told you that,
and I told the listless audience,
that that was a kind of a poor attempt.
He's got a scar.
He was lancing a boil.
To treponate my third eye.
Oh, I thought that had already been done.
Oh, valiant.
You're a do-it-yourself third eye treponation?
Well, after the miscalculations
on the first 14 tries,
I suppose something had to be done.
I mean, people say I fidget with it too much.
But how can you fidget with a tumor?
It's not a fun thing to fidget with.
Fidget is like a tool tool.
They're often hard to reach.
Yeah, that's what it is.
It's a horn stub.
Yes, it's a horn.
An antler root.
It is growing and growing.
Growing daily.
And by the time 5 a.m. in the morning,
on the 5th, it's 4 a.m.,
some a.m. in the morning,
this antler will bloom like a giant rose bush.
I think it would be cool to have an antler sprouting from your head.
I wanted a giant penis to sprout from my head
because I knew it would be a symbol of masculine power.
People don't, don't, don't, don't ever...
It could make you very popular too.
It could pop you right up there.
Yeah, you'd be like on the top level of popularity
with a huge penis sprouting from your forehead.
If it was a small one, you'd have to join the many minions of underachievers.
If it was a small one, you'd just be apologizing for it all the time.
Oh, I thought you were just going to say you would be a politician.
Well, you don't need that to be a politician.
A little dickhead.
They've proven that you don't really need anything.
Actually, these special glasses Bob sells you,
you can't see the penis.
The penis is sprouting out of the politician's head.
It's like they live, but not too badly.
I've actually been to the halls of Congress
and they have a water fountain there that says power on it.
And you just sip on it and it just makes you really powerful.
That's the one of the cherry whites only.
And it makes you know everything and know a lot better, more.
Is that the one of the cherubim urinating on everyone's head?
They will at your request.
It's just populous underneath and they're urinating.
I'm going to go off of this water fountain.
Did you drink some?
No, I'm not allowed.
I'm not an elected official, so I don't get a chance to.
I'm just one of the pleads.
He's an erected unofficial.
That was behind Rocknar's campaign.
He hoped, if elected, to taste that Perian Spring.
I told him he wouldn't be able to resist it.
Well, he wouldn't be able to resist the money anyway.
One sip and you have to go back.
It's like the most addictive liquid.
It's more than liquid crack.
A real Ponce de Leon.
It's like liquid crack heroin.
It is a fountain of juice.
It tastes good and smells good, too.
Well, you're making me thirsty, as you described before.
One sip and you become twice as thirsty as you were when you first drank it.
Political waters.
So deep, so murky.
The water of Bob.
But it's worth it because you're so much smarter after that.
The yellow water of Bob.
And you know so much more than everyone and so much better than everyone.
Say, for instance, you had to perform an instant...
And you know then that it's true.
You are better than everyone.
And this trickles down onto your feet.
It only trickles down into the one individual who's actually sipping of the special sauce.
Bob's pee, I mean water, can trickle up.
It's more like blood dripping from an abused rectum.
It's a special water fountain.
You can only get it in these few areas, you know.
You have to go.
There's a bunch of old guys standing in line waiting to drink on it again.
Yes, step right up, seor.
This is the water of youth.
The fountain you have dreamed of for so long.
There's vendors that service the line while you're in it.
Only one cup per pasenor.
You know there's guys selling hot dogs and drinks and stuff while you're waiting in line to sip on that.
Yeah, but those aren't real people or not people.
They're vendors.
Yeah.
They're psycho-cyborgic vendors.
They look like people and have all the irritating qualities...
Psycho-cyborgic?
Cyborg-vendor?
Cyborg-nation.
Too much onions, not enough.
Unlicensed vendors.
Get away from me.
Screw off.
Die, die, die.
That's the way it was back in the year 1395, when Grandpapi fell out of this hole right
here, and when he did, he brought back many secrets, one of which is...
But in today's modern world...
Sure.
It's all tied up with a bureaucratic tangle of regulatory structure,
making it impossible to put up a taco stand without trespassing on somebody's copyright or legal liability.
Code 60.
I don't have tacos.
And one half.
No hot dogs beyond the wiener wagon fringed around the pail.
What is going to cut through all the red tape?
What Alexandrian sword will cleave the Gordian tangle caused by busybodies, goo-goos, and nosy parkers?
Well, I think that the key word in your statement of solution would be sword.
It takes a sword to cut through that knot.
That was Alexander's solution.
Hey, Reverend Suds, how's the coverage on the CD recordings?
That was...
Okay, so in a few minutes we'll need to shut up long enough to flip the CD.
I love that new quick-moving technology.
Subgenius is 72, humans 16.
That was the score last night.
Then if you take a look again at what happened,
there have been a lot of discrepancies in the film and the footage.
Number one here, the first thing, it was a bad call as J.R. Bob Dobbs emerged from the bushes
and ripped...
One of the very, very hapless, unlikely first-time submitters to the cause
tore his head neatly off his shoulders and then ate the neck juice.
But you said that was J. Nor Bob Dobbs, not J.R. Bob Dobbs.
J. Nor B. Bob.
J. Nor Bob Dobbs.
May.
I never heard one.
Where was that one?
He's going a little bit far with that one.
That one is implied by the Church of the Subgenior, if you don't think about it for a moment.
Because according to the doctrine of the...
According to the Church of the Subgenior, everyone is a member,
and that would include Bob Dobbs.
He would be Sergeant J. Nor Dobbs.
Even members of the Church of Don?
Yes.
The only one who can't be a member of the Church of the Subgenior is, of course, J. Nor.
The Church of...
According to the rules created by Nenslow,
Ascended Nen Master, or as some call him, Sergeant J. Nor Nenslow.
Assassinated Nen Master Nenslow.
All members of the Church...
The Church of the Subgenior are allowed to address each other as Sarge, Sarge,
and take the name Sergeant J. Nor, followed by your actual name.
Can they say Ma'am?
Captain?
I mean...
Yes.
Sarge J. Nor.
I'm a Sarge.
I drink some of this brackish water that's...
Sometimes a thousand twangling instruments about...
He's the most non-joiner of non-joiners.
Hey, but if we're talking about J. Nor, that means I can't use it on my show.
We're talking about Nenslow.
How come there's been so much talk...
We're talking about J. Nor this time, which is all unusable.
I'm talking about Nenslow.
Well, we can dig it.
Because it makes us feel free to say the unusable.
To say the unspeakable.
What we're not usually allowed to talk about or even mention.
The unbroadcastable.
But it's X-Day.
The uneditable.
And you can always...
Should we survive X-Day in some way, you could always put...
Pork slap.
Who has an instrumental version of Shaft?
I should have one taped to my leg.
We could also use the oblique channel.
And we could just refer to it as...
Im-her-it-is.
Non-joiner.
You could bleep it out.
Weep?
Bleep it out.
Weep.
Weep and bleep.
That's the cry of the unused radio man.
Bleep that ye may not weep.
Can you see with those eyes crossed that bleep?
What the bleep do we know?
God, what's that?
An irritating...
Most horrible movie.
Yeah.
Not just...
You irritated me.
I just wanted to stab the screen with a big knife.
I wanted...
Four minutes until we have to shut up long enough for Potter and Ostril to change the high-speed duplicator.
Yes, four minutes.
Jane or Jane or Jane or Jane.
And then it's two minutes of...
That's when everybody gets really, really funny.
As soon as they know the recorder's off.
As sure as nothing is happening.
Yes, we haven't been saying much.
The little laugh-o-meter has been down to below zero.
For quite a while now.
I think we ought to just get very, very quiet and pretend.
Ladies and gentlemen.
For the past ten years, we heard nothing about...
On TV except about...
We're Americans.
Right?
And we're the biggest...
We're the toughest nation in the world.
Fuck today, man.
We're a bunch of pussies.
You go to some place and you get lousy service.
And you say, I'll show them.
I'll fill up this little 4x8 car that goes to somebody in the corporate office.
We need to take a fucking clue from some other country.
You know, I was reading the paper about five years ago.
In Argentina, a bunch of passengers were stranded at the airport.
You know how they have to do it to you?
Know what they do to you?
You know how they do it to you?
You leave you at the airport with no plane?
They burn down the fucking airport!
That's how they do it!
Fuck that five-minute thing!
4x8 car!
You burn down the fucking restaurant!
You don't like that steak?
Fucking Americans.
How many Americans does it take to change a light bulb?
16!
That's right.
You need two of them to complain because the light bulb burned out.
You need two of them to blame the government.
You need three of them to hire illegal aliens.
You need three of them to blame Obama for the change of the light bulb.
The change of the light bulb because they're too fucking fat and lazy to do it themselves.
You need another two to go on Fox News and blame Obama.
How many is that?
All else counts.
Well, you need the rest of them.
The rest of them got to complain because the illegal aliens took the job,
even though they would never stoop as low to change a light bulb.
They need the rest of them.
They said they have to change the light bulb unless they get like a secret no-big contract.
No big contract.
But they will change the light bulb with that.
That's why we're fucking pussies.
I'm sick of it.
You know what?
The conspiracy has been bullshitting us since I was a little kid.
Because when I was a kid in first grade,
he used to show all these movies what the future is going to be like.
Yeah, the future is going to be perfect.
We're going to have flying cars.
We're going to have talking dogs that go,
what will it work?
We're going to have houses on the moon.
Well, I'll tell you what.
I'm looking around.
I ain't got no fucking flying car yet.
Motherfucker.
I want my fucking flying car.
Fuck the conspiracy.
I want it now.
Last night I heard a prominent subgenius angry
because he hadn't received his flyer.
He's flying car.
He's flying car?
Yeah, it was Reverend Skull.
Reverend Skull was complaining about not getting his flying car.
That was an unusual rant for you.
That was not your normal sermon.
There were a lot more vocabulary words in it.
I can see your...
In English.
I kind of feel the same way about the whole flying car thing, though.
I wish I had one.
I was really impressed by the ranting last night.
But I did hear that they're kind of like still in the way.
They say through the FCC on that issue are the F...
Not the FCC, the FAA.
FAA.
They did build flying cars, but they had to stop manufacturing them
because no one can use them
because the moment your flying car takes off,
it becomes an aircraft and you have to file a flight plan
and you're in another level of...
But now we have the Internet.
So you instantly file a templatized flight plan on the Internet
and that takes care of the government paperwork.
And also there are plenty of sebaceous cysts
and lots of chronic...
And there are tons in the hallway.
So you need to get the invisibility thing worked out
and then it all becomes a moot point.
The flying cars they came up with were good, too.
Hugh Hefner bought one.
They have a cruising range of 300 miles.
They fly.
They do everything you think,
except they're totally illegal to use.
But that's what I was saying.
The FAA has just recently...
Belly dances.
...come up with some standards...
Jeez, falling from the sky like it was some kind of...
I don't know what's happening.
We're going to have to wrap it up for a few minutes here.
Okay, we have to wrap it up.
We're going to wrap it up.
While the radio runabout turns over.
And so we leave you with the beautiful sounds of recorded music.
We'll be back in two shakes of a fish's tail
ere the Leviathan can swim a league.
Wow.
That's pretty good.
What is happening here?
What has happened to your nose?
He has just returned to life.
What happened, Love?
Honey, they know.
All right, just just shut up.
What happened that night?
honouring the
Oh, my God.
A beautiful one in the middle of more than seven years
than later on.
I think you can't.
I don't even know what's happening.
I swear I saw a figure walking across that field with the glowing fish instead of.
I just fell to my knees and I kneeled and there he was.
I knew that smiling grin and there he was.
Bob's come back home to us again I said.
Bob's come back home to us again.
But something sinister was afoot.
There was this coldness in my soul.
I was in a daze.
I was still taking the run.
And I wasn't 100% sure of what was to happen or be.
But that wasn't Bob.
And he was coming right for me.
And I knew right away what I had found.
The Antifog was on Rushwood's Ground.
I'll tell you one of my favorite stories.
I don't put jeans on.
Come on, look at me and get radical.
If you want to do that, that's fine, but I don't.
We're going to stop you, Bob.
All right.
Woo!
Okay.
Bob, come on.
Kill Bob!
You're looking at me like you didn't get it.
We get that a lot, friends, and we got that cut from Heart Ignition.
Before that was Priestess Pisces and Six-Fisted Tales of Connie at 13X Day Thursday night,
making it all up as they went along, as is this music in the background.
Six-Fisted Tales that night included Reverend Angry Larry, Reverend Suds Peshaw,
Reverend Phil, Senator Speck, Dr. Philo Drummond, and Reverend Bunny Day.
Stang just drained a gallon out of that thing.
That's because he's going to turn that useless water into powerful coffee.
But damn.
Powerful coffee will be produced out of that water.
Stuff just floating in the water.
Yeah.
Animalcules.
Animalcules?
Foraminifera.
Gyroscopa.
Tiny diatoms, spider squids, ding futzers, and whirligigs.
Gynaecoli.
Nyah!
Only microns in diameter.
Frostbitten fleas.
Hard-bitten fleas.
Arguments with hard-bitten floozies.
This is X-Day Radio.
That's right.
The legend burned across the land, blazing like a burning brand or whatever, for X-Day.
Doctor, how long has the legend gone on?
Well, as long as there's...
There were brave, hardy sons of the soil, hacking and chopping their way westward through the great American landscape.
Chopping Indians and eating fires.
This was a wonderful time in our country.
And they just...
They've landed here again for your listless pleasures.
Yes, they built general stores and subtleries, laid railroads down across the prairies.
Conestoga.
Hewed down Indians and hacked open waterfalls.
And built the great American slag heap.
Dug up the gold.
Argued with the acoustics of the soundboard.
Ran the phonies.
Look out, there's Copal and Tungsten.
I don't believe it, he's gonna drain more.
Recreated humanity in a little tiny drop of water.
Water.
Imagine.
Or don't.
Just where universes are in that drop of water.
The source of all life.
Of strange little one-celled organisms.
Everybody knows what is real.
Flagellates.
Fossils.
I have d-
Rotifers.
You can do smelly.
I have das kuhn-de-vasser.
Uh.
Das kuhn-de-vasser.
So those, uh, rotifers were washed out of the, uh, coffee urn.
In any case, it's-
Kuhn-de-vasser.
Going to get warm for them in a few minutes.
Maybe I can get a bottle of the kuhn-fasser.
And then they'll be ready to drink.
You see, uh, sterilization, pasteurization, that does work.
Thank you.
You can scour the little buggers out of there.
Ask me, Lois Pasteur.
I was the one who invented this shit.
Really, I was.
And they sneered at Louis Pasteur.
They snickered at the snicker bar.
They sneered and snickered.
If there are these little bugs, why can we not see them?
Hm-hm-hm-hm-hm-hm.
Why cannot we argue with them, on for say?
I think the little bugs are in your mind, monsieur, between your eyes.
Look!
One of them is wearing a punching bag and a blow horn.
And a tiny derby hat.
A tiny derby?
With a little umbrella.
And he's waving it at us, can't you see?
Wave back, quickly! Quickly! He-
Too late, he died. His life cycle was too short.
The only way to prolong the life cycle would be to pump more rotif-rotif-rotif-rotif-rotif back into the water.
Pack him in amber.
It's- look!
The tiny vial of urine.
Let the evil nymph find its own power.
Of Dobbs's urine.
It's all the rotif-rotif-rotif-rotif-rotif we need.
So, Herr Van Leeuwenhoek was startled to see, looking through his experimental microscope, the tiny waving dobs inside each sperm.
Now we have to change to the Dutch accent.
And then he had to provide more sample and more and more sample.
And he kept pumping that sample out.
Yeah, you've seen those little- those old-
I can do this all day.
Especially when there's no connective tissue in your brain. That's the most important part.
Just let it slide slickly around, from hemisphere to hemisphere.
Just slopping back and forth.
Yes, your brain is like a washing machine, and the agitator inside disturbing its contents is Bob.
It's the pipe. It's going around and around and agitator action up and down.
Making that chugging noise. No one else can hear that. That is you.
Yes, well, now I can hear it, but that's like an illustration of what it's like.
Makes it hard to sit on it during the spin cycle.
Oh, the spin cycle. You vibrate. You go to pieces all over. Um, I don't know.
I did it. I evened the slate.
How I didn't bust myself all to hell is beyond me.
On Saturday mornings, I'd stand on our front porch, and as the kids came by, I'd beat up, up, and cuss.
I pulled a grenade out and threw it.
Bodies. More than a dozen horses had been killed.
God. Dead horses. Chunks of beef.
At least it wasn't me.
Incontinental drift.
Do you have that?
Incontinental drift, yeah.
Yeah, but what...
It's a chronic problem.
That's why we have this event outdoors.
Some planets and life forms.
So much of us have these leakage issues.
We got it.
Is anybody here...
Dispersal.
Dispersal. Arguments with wigs. These are all things we have to watch for.
We have to stay on the steadfast. And on the... what is it? The standfast?
We have to stand fast.
You know that...
Against these things, and for them too, if they're necessary.
It says, stand fast for what you believe in.
Very good. Very good.
And sit down on your own stool.
Now, the world is scheduled to end the day after tomorrow, right?
But...
I've read some end of the world paranoid stuff about that oil zit, the Mother Earth zit, the oil volcano.
But what's the point?
It was so paranoid that to read this guy's rants, you'd think that, eh, it's going to be close call...
Close tie between the exes getting here in a day and a half, or whether the waves of oil will be splashing over this far inland and submerge brushwood.
Wow.
You know, the concept of...
It's a lot of oil.
Well, we do know how much oil is in there.
Well, what if there's more oil down there than there is of water and oceans?
It could be that the whole...
It fills up everything. It's the end of the world.
Hey, maybe we have some oil.
We know the whole Earth is filled with oil, and that's just where it's squirting out now.
Maybe we could work out a deal with blood for oil. I heard that was a thing.
But there's no blood that's in there.
I'd rather see waves of blood.
It's just a big bucket, a big barrel of oil.
That would be really cool.
We could work out a deal of buns for oil. Or no, wait, I'm sorry. It could possibly mean the end of the world in a very, very short period of time.
Somebody said they had stuffed up that leak.
That was legume-y.
Legume said they got a wedding band over it or something, right?
No, it was some cork and some Kraft cheese.
He did say they put a wedding band over it.
So they were married, and in a short time moved to Bingen, Ten Springs.
There they lived for approximately 23 seconds before the insecticide.
Actually, speaking of that particular problem, it's not just like one hole that needs to be plugged up anyway.
The entire bottom there is porous, and it's under mud. It's under loose mud.
It's hard to tell what the bottom is.
It could be coming up in many different ways.
And messing it, shaking it around may open it up more so that more oil rises up.
I lost track of things. You're not talking about me, are you?
Don't forget, you know, where the plate tectonics, where the plates are separating, there's actual magma coming out of the earth.
Yeah.
You've got to plug that stuff up, too.
That's right.
Because magma's not good for anybody.
You've got to clean your plates.
Everybody I know who's ever gotten magma on them has died from it.
I know.
It's highly poisonous.
Forget all those stupid Hollywood movies.
We're worrying about oil.
Where they almost fall into the volcano.
There's magma coming out.
Oh, I almost got the lava that's right there on me.
He'd be cooked. He'd be flash cooked before he could say that sentence.
From rock that's heated to glowing heat, it's right there.
It doesn't matter if you don't get any on you.
Right. You can drink crude oil and live for a few hours, but if you drink magma, you're going to die almost instantly.
The earth is just going to kill you anyway. Somehow or another, you're going to die.
We live by sufferance on the thin skin around the dangerous, toxic, molten interior of the earth.
Yeah, we're worrying about all this microscopic stuff.
One might worry about it in some way.
What about that asteroid that's supposed to hit here and like...
That's loose pieces of the solar system that haven't been sorted out yet.
That's the day after tomorrow, after we leave. See?
There's an asteroid that's going to be hitting the earth.
That's the large insulting sock from an asteroid.
We'll be gone and we'll be looking back thinking, ah, we made it just in time.
Boy, how ironic that the world ended when that asteroid was going to take care of it all anyway.
I think the delay was for that reason, so that we could have more gleeful satisfaction of knowing that everything we were leaving behind...
...is being destroyed by a giant asteroid.
It's not as if there was only a fixed amount of glee to go around.
Right, and you can engender so much more glee by imagining each and every catastrophe.
Start and give them like numbers and then put little letters like A, how it expands, like there's the Gulf oil spill.
There's the potential...
Eleven zeros at the end of it.
There's 2012, there's X-Day, and there's so many of them.
Yeah, if you put enough numbers there, it becomes meaningless anyway.
Well, there are many possible ways.
There are multiple instant deaths that we could all suffer.
For example, gamma ray bursts could occur.
Gamma ray is very bad.
That would be it for everyone.
Don't forget, radon gas in your basement is just leaking out.
You don't even know it.
You're sleeping down there in front of the football game.
Leaky basements doomed the dinosaurs.
You're sniffing up radon gas.
Your own self-inflicted flatulence?
Nya-nya-nya-nya-nya. Lunch meat.
Flatulence.
Bad.
Barbecue. Et cetera, et cetera.
Barbecue.
Rashes, particularly around the butt.
That's just wrong.
Thank you for your program.
Yucks.
Your own self-inflicted flatulence?
So many people are dying from their own self-inflicted flatulence.
I heard about a guy who fell asleep inside his sleeping bag, and his farts killed him.
He had...
He suffered from...
The lighter was leaking as well.
All those garlic and jalapeno sandwiches...
It's not the flatulence itself, it's that it displaces all the air.
He died of fatal self-Dutch ovening?
Yeah, Dutch ovening.
It sounds more like a burrito, doesn't it?
A double Dutch oven.
Rolled up in the...
The pig in the blanket.
That's another reason you should not smoke in bed.
You have a cigarette lit.
I can't live without that.
Well, Philo, you're just handing me your rules, man.
I don't like all your rules.
I don't want to smoke in bed if I want to.
I want to smoke in bed, yeah.
That's all smoke in bed.
So, do you smoke before sex?
Or during sex?
Or after sex?
I don't know.
I never looked.
Ah.
Weep, weep.
Oh, that's a good one.
Drink up and tip your waitress.
Our next show's at 2.
Actually, Susie, our next show is next week.
Of course, our last thousand shows are archived at subgenius.com, where you can learn everything
about the Church of the Subgenius and our guru, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
That's subgenius.com.
Our award-winning books and old CDs and videos are all still in print.
Can you believe it?
You can also find links to lots of great shows.
Lots of freebies of all kinds.
That's subgenius.com.
This has been the Hour of Slack.
Praise Bob.