Friends, you are listening to WCSB 89.3 FM in Cleveland.
Heya.
Ahimsa.
Oye.
Ogas.
Play sex music.
Oye.
WCSB Cleveland.
Wingweight Fuzzwood is now under surveillance.
Oye.
WCSB Cleveland.
We play sex music.
Oye.
To catch a thief, follow the money.
That idea has served as a guide for crime fighters throughout the years.
Today, crime fighters also follow the money on the internet.
As business transactions on the internet have grown,
so have the internet.
The number of scams and schemes.
That's why the U.S. Postal Inspectors have joined in the effort to stamp out internet fraud.
For more information, including tips on how to avoid online schemes,
you can visit www.usps.com.
That's usps.com.
www.usps.com.
More details after the subgenius hour of slack.
Welcome to the U.S. Postal Inspectors.
Greetings from Hollywood, ladies and gentlemen.
Ordinarily, we think that American women are the most beautiful women in the world.
So many of them use toilets to help them stay that way.
But this time, I got my man to help them shoot toilets and made the dream come true.
And may your seventh toilet be so beautiful that it will make you feel like you're in a toilet.
So good, it surpasses the other six.
Curl up in a ball and cover your head with
the subgenius hour of slack.
God, please, because I want my Western Burger done right.
Oh, this is Timothy Larry reminding you that just as you need slack,
Bob needs your help.
Send in those pledges and praise Bob.
Good morning, good morning, good morning, good morning.
I look forward to talking.
Congress is considered.
We need to continue.
Terrorists attacks on our own country.
We must also provide terrorists and extremists the tools they need to keep new attacks on our nation.
We need terror.
We need another attack.
The principle behind this program is clear.
Colleague Sheikh Mohammed rules.
Next week, I will return to New York where I might live.
We rededicate ourselves to terrorists.
Terrorists, terrorists, terrorists, terrorists, terrorists, terrorists, terrorists and extremists.
Sheikh, the American people, thank you for listening.
When you readinatorora, at the moment,iga3
So it was time again, once again.
Eh, Charleston, if you'll at the hint.
Over, and I remember.
Since he got a har complaining that maybe there are terrorists hiding in the corner of our house.
America may have warned you this week about theц.
Dangerous.
Ch warned.
We now look pleasant.
rice. I get chills.
But the human race, as we know it, has
run its course.
And it was a
crooked run where the lead
horse broke down in the middle of the last
furlong and grew
wings.
And never returned.
Oh, well, so much for that BS.
Anyway, it's Terror-Thon
again. Time to pledge
to your local favorite
terrorist group in this case.
The subgenius, our
out of slack, the Church of the Subgenius.
Yes, my friends!
Charleston is a laid-back
DJ,
but I'm fired up!
I'm fired up on leftover Halloween
candy and rock star energy
drinks, and we are going to hammer
you until you pledge!
Yes, you! Not the
generic you of all listeners, but the
you specifically. Nor the letter
you. We have to disclude also no one
named ooh may call in and
pledge anything except for their
total fealty to the Church of the
Subgenius. And you can do that
too! Friends, we're drawing the line
right here. Are you with Bob
or are you against him?
If there's no sand for you to draw a line
in, pull the sand out of your errant
pockets you've been walking around for a long time
probably looking for, well, not
work, looking for slack, haven't you?
Sometimes in the snow, sometimes
in the rain. You ain't gonna get
no slack here until you call
that number. 687
6900.
6900. Friends, you think
NPR pledge drives are
irritating? Oh, you haven't even
begun to understand
irritation yet.
We make the NPR
pledge drives look unobtrusive
by comparison because
we are not going to let up!
No, sir, ma'am!
We are going to hammer you
and bury you!
Because, friends, Bob,
I don't know about you, but
I love Bob. I'm not gonna
let Bob dry on the vine.
And I love WCSB, the station
that brings you the word of Bob.
I love
Bob myself. I love myself.
I love Bob, and I love Bob when he's
wet in the pants, and you'll be wet in the
pants if you send in a
donation or call in a
donation to 687 6900
at WCSB, which stands for
Wiley Caustic Snotbags.
No, it doesn't. It sounds...
Does it stand for anything? I don't know.
I don't know what it stands for, but you could talk
to Princess We Are
No Queen of All the UFOs herself!
She's in there right now taking those calls!
Friends, Bob
is... I don't know about you, but
Bob is my raison
d'etre.
And he raises my debt.
B.O.B.
is the reason to be,
baby.
And now...
Yeah, I know, you're going, well,
now all those religious, uh,
charlatans are always haranguing
us for money. Did you hear the news
about that meth-buying
gay sex preacher?
That Pastor Hager
or whatever kind of rhymes with swagger?
Uh, friends,
in that religion,
which has 30 million members,
when you get caught
buying meth and having
gay sex massages, why, they
fire you. In this religion,
I get a bonus if I
have enough energy to do something!
Something like that. So, friends,
when you don't pledge,
when you do not call
216-687-6900,
you are
torturing
Bob. You are mutilating
that man, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And do you know
what Bob did for you?
Yes? He cared nothing
for you. He ignored you!
Yes! And yet, are you
going to return the favor that same way? No!
Don't you want...
Don't you want to kill and mutilate Bob?
When you call and support this station,
you mutilate J.R. Bob Dobbs!
And you...
I see someone who's at the door here. Someone is
pounding at the door trying to get in, friends.
And, friends, you should
be pounding at this door with your
telephone calls. Pound those keys!
I'm going to, uh, do the
traditional thing of reading out the
pledge premiums of what
you actually get, because...
Because, I guess, just delivering you
this show isn't enough.
Oh, no! That's not enough. You have to get
a pledge premium, and they're actually
pretty cool premiums. I would like to
ask each and every one of you a very personal
question, if I may. How many of you
are suffering from empty pockets?
Well, if you are, there are lots of things worse
than empty pockets. There's a
syndrome known as the empty, empty,
empty skull. And we find
that many of you
have hollow places in your cranium.
All too many. And these
can be taken care of by simply donating
$5, $10,
$15, $25, or
$30 to Station WCSB
in Cleveland, your favorite
alternative station, the station that brings
you all of this crap
that you're listening to right now.
But I personally love it, and I'm sure there are plenty
of you out there who love it personally, too.
I mean, in more than a physical way. But
personally, personally have strong feelings
for not only this show, but
inanimate objects in your room, which
reminds me of a joke. Um, a doctor
is sitting agonizing...
Never mind. Please,
please call in and pledge tonight to
keep the hour of slack forcing
this stuff down your throat.
That's right, friends. You're paying
to help force the word
Bob down the ear holes of the
listeners of Northern Ohio.
And making the...
If this station had more money, why it could be
stronger? It could
go down those ear holes all that
much more forcefully.
And now listen to this. Listen to
what you get. If you were to pledge,
if you were one of these big spenders and actually
pledge $30 and up,
the subgenius premium
is the Arise
DVD. Yes, our
great DVD as seen
on night flight all through the 80s.
Only they showed the censored
version and called it Love That
Bob. The 2005
re-edited, newly
uncensored
director's cut of Arise and
several other shorts and extras.
It was yours!
This DVD-R is yours for only...
the $30 pledge to this station at
216-687-
6900.
How could I forget
such a name? Now, if you
eschewed the word of Bob
and wanted to prove you didn't love him,
you could get a WCSB
long-sleeved logo shirt in black
or with a
white logo or a gray
shirt with a black logo or a
WCSB umbrella to keep
the rain of manure off of
your per-balled pants.
And of a sweatshirt
with the embroidered logo and
the hooded zippered sweatshirt.
These are all the things you get for $30 and above
premium, friend. But I know that
that may be more than you have in your
pockets. Oh, that's more than many of our
friends have, but yet they can all
contribute something for $5.
For only $5, now,
friends, most shows don't give you a premium
for $5, but for $5 you
get the subgenius pamphlet,
which is a 16-page
book. A book!
For only, and friends,
it'll take you days of
extra meditation in the Holy Chamber,
the throne room, to
read through that thing.
That's for a $5 pledge, because I know that
some of you are just pathetic
and only have $5.
But yet, who does Bob love most?
The little old lady who could only
give her last $5 or the
rich man who gave him
$10,000 when he could have given him $10 million.
Friends, Bob loves that rich
man the most.
Yes, we know that many of you are the same
as the elderly in our nation. You're a little
bit of an addled brain that you're making, trying to
make difficult decisions. Do you want food?
Oh, but I was wrong. Or do you want medication?
I was wrong. I said that for $5
you get the pamphlet, friends. That's not
all you get. You get the pamphlet
for any donation to this
station. For $5 you also
get the Dobbs head
decal. That's right, the glimmering,
glowing face of Bob in pure
black and white dot patterns on a
vinyl... It's shiny.
Four by... Four and a half by four and a half inch
sticker. It's beautiful.
You can pray to it. You can have
sex with it. You can do anything
you want.
You can have private moments.
For $10 you get the
giant bumper sticker that says
I'm mad too, Bob.
And has a picture of the
mad Bob on it. For the
$15 pledge,
friends, you get
the triple X rated
hour of slack number nine.
The newly released triple X rated
only played on the internet
outlets. You'd never hear it on the
station because this station
has taste and goodness.
But this CD,
which is a full res CD
with 30 different tracks
of filth!
It's so horrible.
Not because it's sexual especially.
It's just dirty.
And for $20 you
get not only that and the pamphlet,
X rated,
hour of slack number nine, plus
the pamphlet, you also get
X rated subgenius show number 10
which no one has heard yet.
Because it's
it'll kill you. It's so filthy.
It is. It has killed before.
And we're thinking once again about all
those poor people out there who can hardly afford
to roll two fingers together
or perhaps smoke their own eyebrows.
The idea of food or medication
shouldn't be a problem because this station,
WCSB, is both your
supernal food and your
fine medication. And if it isn't,
the church of the subgenius
certainly is. And think
of it that way, friends. You will not only
eat, you will breathe, you will drink,
you will believe, and you will feel
a whole hell of a lot better.
How many of you out there
listening to the radio or on
drugs? Well, we've got an ashtray
for you for the $15 premium
and WCSB clear glass with
black WCSB logo
ashtray for $15
premium. Or you can get the subgenius
two-filth CD
set or for $20.
Your $20
pledge, friends.
What were we giving them for $20?
$20 gets you
a brand new... No, wait, that's the wrong
thing. Okay,
for $32, you get a
deviated septum. For $48,
you get a sharpened skull,
a very, very highly
honed crystal
sharpened skull. Friends, you could be talking to Princess
We Are The Queen of UFOs.
You get a dismissive attitude
and a lack of confidence. So just
think of it, friends. All the things you can or can't
do, these aren't important. Just pledge
now to this station!
Hi.
Have your friends
tried to kill you? Taken your muzzle?
Estued your stumpers or stopped
your medication?
Estued your stumpers?
Wait, no, wait.
Estued your sloppers.
I'm sorry, I was reading the wrong paper here.
Okay, it's the $35
pledge gets you absolutely nothing but a
$30 pledge not only gets you a rise.
No, that gets you a rise. A rise. And a pamphlet.
And a pamphlet. And a $25 pledge is one
that gets you both X-rated shows,
friends. Both X-rated CDs
of the Hour of Slack, X-rated number
9 and number 10 for a $25
pledge. Premium. And also
there's so many other WCS Belias
things that you can get. Inquire.
If you're confused or perhaps flatulent
or maybe the matrices in your head
have been devolved, just ask a question.
Princess We Are Doe is not only
happy to answer your questions but give you
flat comical answers. And she
may hang up on you. But she may not.
We need the money so she may not.
And friends, it's like if you don't
immediately get a hold of her the first
20 or 30 rings, that means she's busy
with a giant donator like
Dr. Dark. He's a
he's the man
who said when a chimpanzee
gets sexually aroused, that's
what you call a bonoboner.
And friends, that's why
people like him must die.
But let's think about the
bonobuses that we're going to
bonobonuses that we're going to be getting
by just being able to listen to the station
for the rest of eternity. When we score meth and
have gay sex, we get a bonus.
Some people call it hell.
We call it WCSB.
Praise WCSB. Praise WCSB.
This show you might call the
WCS Beliathon.
As you're driving down
Payne or Forestville Avenue or some of the
other discharge areas that
lead in and out of the beautiful city,
you'll notice high above Rhodes Tower
the emblazoned
engram, or no, that's not engrammatic,
the emblazoned symbol
and logo of the station itself.
WCSB, like a beacon in the night.
And this is truly
a cultural beacon.
Friends, you can have that WCSB
logo on your baseball
cap. Carnally.
Or you can have that logo
on shot glasses.
For a $25 premium,
a clear glass shot glass
with the WCSB logo
wrapped around. You can have a lighter
to light up your foul
drugs. Chicken fried or
cigarettes. And there's only
three of those lighters available and only
five of those shot glasses available.
And or
the subgenius
filth-a-thon
CD set of stuff that was
too hot for the
hour of slack on WCSB or any
of the broadcast stations that carry this show.
But first, let's run our fingers
over some of these fine, fine, fine
items they can get their
hands on themselves after the
pledge drive is over and finally exhumated.
Just think
of one of those beautiful Dobbshead vinyl
decals, decal stickers,
and the subgenius pamphlet for only
$5. Only five.
If you count on your fingers, there's your little finger,
there's your middle finger, there's your big finger, there's
the index finger. That's $5
out of your wallet that you
normally would use on crack coke.
Or some other stupid drug that
makes you worse. Why not
contribute now to something that
is easily...
You don't even have to have a premium.
If this is all too confusing, just call
687-6900
in the 216
area code. Once again, that's 687-6900.
And tell
Princess Wee you'd like
to pledge and she'll tell you what to do.
She'll give you that address, P.O. Box
931848 in Cleveland, Ohio
44101. For
you listening by internet and playing that back.
That's right, you can send that check. Just
send a check or money order
with a little note that it's for
the hour slack to
WCSB slash
CSU Foundation at
P.O. Box 931848.
You're all
soon to be getting wonderful, beautiful WC...
If you ask for them, WCSB
car bumper stickers.
The car bunkles are free!
T-shirts,
sweatshirts, a tiny little nose,
braiders, a number
of items that you're going to find in the home
or outside of your home if you're lucky enough to
call the police on time. Friends, you cannot
get anything like this show or
any of these shows on any normal
healthy station.
Only on a station like this
and they only survive because of your
pledges. Friends, here's
a quote by
Professor Dave DeLuco
of the new
subgenius book, The Cyclopedicon
and he says,
in this book, this is an actual
published book from Avalon Books,
the new book that's out, The Bobliographer
and it says here, quote,
To my knowledge and best intelligence,
the hour of slack is the direct product
of a scientific and
mystical experiment. The mission
of the hour of slack, according to Mr.
DeLuco here, as participants
are allowed to know it, is stacking
extra audio information in the
listener's inner ear so it's never forgotten.
A barrage of talk radio, rapid
fire verbal cuts, direct memory radio,
theater and ethos inducing music
seizes the inner ear and holds
it captive until the message is
complete and lodged in sconce
in the brain. And there's a
picture of Lonesome Cowboy Dave right
here with St. Paul Craster
in this very studio of WCSB.
Now what else
choice do you have but to call
687-6900
and get that in? Friends, I don't
care about your soul, I don't care
about your slack, all I care about
right this minute is your money because
that saves your soul,
that saves your slack.
Praise Bob! Praise Bob!
We don't care how you look, we don't care how you
feel, we don't care how you smell, we don't care
about your interior design.
We only care that you deliver
that political capital in
the form of small George Washingtons,
Benjamin Franklins, or Adolf
Hitlers. We don't care who's on the bill, we just
care that it's U.S. money and it
comes to support this station
and the hour of slack. Now friends, it's election
day coming up and you've got
your choice. You can vote for Hitler or
you can vote for Jesus. I think I know
who you're going to vote for.
Oh my God, here's a call from
David Buckner in Canada!
This person from
Canada is actually the guy who
first got the hour of slack
onto the internet, you might
say. He helped us keep
it on the internet. Praise
Reverend David Buckner.
He plays the
hour of slack up there on
the internet.
Of Toronto,
Canada, and
his own show, which is
great.
Praise Eric Wolf for bringing us this
information. Friends,
you can talk to the gods
themselves when you call this number.
You can talk to UFO Space
Princess I.
The gods may not talk
back to you. The gods may appear
disinterested at first, but after a little
time, especially after delivering
or phoning in or giving your
credit card information so that we may
take your donation, you will actually
see illaquid liquid results
pouring down as if mana from
heaven. Mama from
heaven. Not mama mana. I want
mama from heaven.
Then you're going to have your
mana and your money. I want,
well, no, I want your money, friends.
Not from my pocket. And Bob,
in a way, it'll go into Bob's
pocket by way of WCSB.
WCSB. WCSB.
Bob, whatever. Might as well be one and the same.
Yeah, Bob. Like in
Satan. Of one. It's all about the same.
In line. Six and one, half nine hundred
of the other. Why not?
Ling-lang. You did sign
the application. You
read the small print.
You took the fire drill.
You kissed the fundament.
You waited
for execution.
You swallowed the blindfold.
You delivered the painful
armor. You
begged for it. You said, Bob,
kill me!
And did we hold back?
No. So this is the time for you
to just let go. Unbelt
yourself. Unzip your
lip. Pull out that wallet.
Bend over and let Bob in,
baby. Let Bob in deep into
your heart. Friends, you may not
know this, but this is not only a liberal station.
It is an arcane replica of
a station from the past. And not only that,
it's very, very, very tolerant.
We need more stations like WCSB.
I'm not wearing any pants right now.
No, we don't. We only need WCSB to
control the world!
It should be the only station!
I forgot that again. I keep forgetting this.
We don't need competition. We need your money,
friends. So we're talking points right under here on number 1340.
Now, I have a news
speaking of Dr. Dark.
This is from the Dr. Dark News
service.
We brought this in even
before we knew he was pledging.
Owlswell
that ends well. From Sherman,
New York, this news says, a
pagan was arrested on suspicion of
carrying a concealed pet after
Brushwood Campground Police found
him outdoors naked
and he told them he had a fool
in his rectum,
authorities said. The pagan
was lying on a tree stump masturbating
beside a nature path near the hot tub
Thursday, camp police said.
John Sheehan of Pittsburgh
was initially arrested on
suspicion of indecent pet smuggling,
but when asked whether he was carrying anything
police should know about,
Sheehan mentioned the fool,
said Sherman Detective Corporal
Don Hornigan.
You can't get much more concealed than that,
Hornigan said.
Officers drew their crease-grease guns
and fire tenders were called to the scene.
Sheehan
was removed
a six-inch muffled
owl wrapped in
black electrical tape
from his neither area
without incident. Sheehan, who was
paroled from Naked Bob's Campground
last week, was then booked into jail
on suspicion of Brushwood Campground
pet violations, indecent exposure
and one felony count of possessing
concealed wildlife.
When you're talking about an owl
or a nice prick and you're
dealing with someone who's fresh out of
Naked Bob's Campground,
it's a weepin'. That's a stinky
owl, Hornigan said.
It was not immediately clear what Sheehan
was on parole for.
A person answering the phone at the jail,
Friday night, did not know whether
Sheehan had a liar.
Friends, whether your fool
is a muffled owl or an awful mole,
it matters not to us.
We're all part of the same celibate
zoo. We all have the same organs.
We all salute the same ways.
And some of us are downright
improprietous. So send
anything you can now except for
what is it that we won't take exactly,
Reverend? We'll take anything,
friends, as long as it's
money.
Not in some sort.
And did you know that you
don't have to just mail that check-in
or you could also,
after talking to Princess
Wee or Lonesome
Cowboy Dave or Dr. Sinister
or whoever are here at
687-6900, you could
go online
at the link found
via WCSB.org
and pay by credit card
after
alerting us about that. Or, get
this, you could come right
here into this magical
place, this technical
marvel called WCSB
Studio. This tears to house.
Starting
from November
17th to Sunday, which is
Friday, to September 19th.
You can just wander in,
pay your pledge, pick up
that premium, pick up that
Bob bumper sticker, that Bob
which is a $10 pledge,
the Bob X-rated
CD for $15.
Or two of them for $25.
Or that DVD for $30.
Or any of the great
fantabuloid WCSB
logo t-shirts and ashtrays,
lighters, shot glasses, syringes,
speculums,
you name it, they've got
it with a fine, fine
WCSB logo on it. Just
shining and glimmering.
Let's take a look at this one right here. It's an indigiform
Paleolithic skull imported all the way
from the Amazon. It's making me
big. It's able, it's actually,
capable of dividing the
future and providing valuable
information to the smaller members of your
family and the people with the larger
craniums. It says right here on the back
and it comes all the way, like I said, from Brazil
and it's got the WCSB logo
on the back. It's got
an icon of Bob.
Friends, you just can't go
wrong with this pledge drive this week and
WCSB is known for beautiful pledge
drives. I sound like the
seriously
smashed up lady on
WKSU. I'm sorry. I didn't
mean to say that, but she's, I'm sorry.
I don't know. I don't,
I know nothing of these other earth stations,
Dave. I never, you know,
I don't know of any other station
in Cleveland. It's the only one I
ever listened to. But this is an exciting, entertaining
pledge drive. Other people are
expecting some form of musical entertainment.
Oh sure, some people get music, some people get
irritating collages. I've got
the best of all previous
pledge drive rants queued
up here, ready to go. If I suddenly
got tired or was inclined to shut up,
but I can't, I can't because you're
not calling. Princess, we just want to
Princess, will you tell him? I have a special
sizzling hot announcement to make
here. Rocknar just called
and he pledged a
$30 pledge
and he challenges all
Radio 2.0 listeners
to contribute what they can.
Match that pledge. WCSB, maximize
that pledge. Can you be like Rocknar?
This is something Rocknar might be interested
in for, uh, if he wants to make a video.
Like a second pledge, there's, uh, I believe
Crowdy McCrowd is offering his soul
as a premium. And we know
that Rocknar is a trafficker in human souls.
That's right. And this is
why he asked for no premium. He has
plenty going for him. As a trafficker
in souls, he doesn't need
the trivial, menial little ashtray
that you can bang over your parents'
heads. Friends, act like
Rocknar and we'll treat you as
an equal.
He needs the neutron bomb
and he needs your support.
Uh, he needs...
No, wait. Rocknar
doesn't need your support.
We need to be Rocknar's
jockstrap. Supporting us.
We don't need... We need the bra
of you, the listener,
supporting this station.
Lift and separate with your pledge.
Separate us from poverty.
Lift us, uh,
like, like a
wild religious
fervor in your mind
coursing through your veins.
Lift us up and you too
will be lifted up. Just like
Jim Jones lifted up his people.
Just like David Koresh
could lift them up. Just like the
solar temple people were lifted up.
Friends in Heaven's Gate, are we gonna
let them beat us? No! Pledge that
money. Send that money in. Drink
the Kool-Aid, children. Drink
the Kool-Aid. How about this for an
offer, ladies and gentlemen? Wanna help out
WCSB? Wanna help out
the subgenius ministry hour of
Slack Radio Show? Wanna really help?
If you pledge $1,000
right now, the lovely
princess, Wee Ardo, will
provide, as a premium, one
of her many brassieres. I don't know if she
has many, but I know for $1,000
she'll take her clothes off
for me, baby! So
send that money in!
And there's lots of other things
we've got here. Sitting on the table, it looks like
I'm at the Quality Value Network
and all the incredible offers
we have here. Let's just hope that
those balls and waxes keep on floating.
It's time to remember that
Germany is not the
place we want to be right now.
I don't know where I...
I think I'm reading the wrong paper.
I'm reading the wrong paper, but...
Oh yeah, okay. I thought I had the
travel thing here. I told you, Dave, when I
was in Germany a couple of years ago
after the last election,
the Germans
were saying,
we're kind of worried about the
fascism in America.
They have experience, and we
always ask for...
I don't really talk that way. We always
ask for experience when we're
looking for help. We go to an
elder member of our family, someone
perhaps all croggly and crony,
and we say, with your vast
experience, can you tell me this or that?
With our vast experience, we
can tell you that you can do no finer,
no better thing than to pledge!
That's so true, friends.
What you do now is
the greatest... This is the
greatest thing you will ever do
when you call that number, 687-6900
in the Cleveland
216 area code.
You know, people used to mock
Cleveland and laugh. It's just a joke.
It's like, oh, don't
mess up or you'll be transferred to Cleveland.
Ha ha ha! You laugh track
because it was so wretched.
Well, friends, for some
of us, some of us find
a heaven of
slack. Well, not
necessarily Cleveland, but Cleveland Heights!
Everywhere I live.
The Slacker Mansion.
They're high on the highest
hill in Cleveland Heights.
You might say I was the highest man in Cleveland
Heights, friend. And Her Highness Princess
Wee is even higher. We're
trying to keep Her Highness stable
and steady.
So can't you help?
Can't you see fit?
Can't you deign
or lower yourself
to call that number,
687-6900? You could be
talking to Dr. Sinister right now.
Did you... Can you even
believe that?
There are so many of you
out there who have spent
your finest hours
on the throne of
excremeditation.
Don't be
a part of this doobie.
Don't be.
You could do it! Pledge now.
You can do more than
evacuate yourselves. You
can keep the flow coming.
Coming by
many pledging.
Five, ten, fifteen,
twenty-five or thirty dollars to
WCSB and the radio
hour of slack. We're not proud.
We'll take five thousand dollars.
You don't have to feel bad about that.
If that's all you can do,
five grand, hey, look,
you know, every little bit counts.
Those pennies add up.
Those thousand dollar checks add up.
Even, rather, quite a bit
faster.
I know that you've got
needs like beer,
cigarettes,
Hootie and the Blowfish
Best Of CDs.
That's what you're probably going to spend your money on.
Because you can get
WCSB for free, right?
Sure.
Why don't I help the
cigarette companies
and the beer companies
more than I help
the thing that gives me free pleasure
all this time?
Whoa, this is terrible.
Blind eye, I just turned a blind eye
however they get by,
however they get by.
You are stabbing Bob in the heart
with your penknife
when you do that, friends.
Wait, maybe I shouldn't say that because some people
want, that's exactly what they want to do.
The more you pledge, the deeper
that penknife goes into Bob's heart.
And we can guarantee it.
Yeah, so come on, 687-6900.
Join the crowd
and the lynch mob and kill Bob,
man.
I said some of you have needs.
We know some of you have knees.
We know some of you have elbows and collarbones
and that's why we want every rich
Republican living in chagrin
in the areas where there's
lots and lots of money.
Don't just sit there on your ponce
drinking your martinis and your mojitos
and whatever else you do.
Get on the phone right now and contribute
to the world around you by dialing
687-6900 and pledging
5, 10, 15,
25 or $30 to the
hour of slack and
WCSB in Cleveland.
The station that keeps you on top of things
and well underground.
And friends, you know, you tend people
we always tend to think, well, college stations,
that's all a bunch of liberals, right?
Well, now, friends, we're patriots, psychotic
and narco-materialists and we love
our Republican brothers and sisters
when they give us their money.
Yes. When they give
unto Bob that which is
truly Bob's, that which is his
due. Friends,
by his stripes,
he was healed. But you
don't have stripes. All you've got
is money and that's the only way you can heal yourself
is divest yourself of that
which has enslaved you. You are a
slave to that filthy
lucre and that job. Free yourself,
baby. Let it go.
Put that wallet on a diet and you won't
die yet. Just think of it
that way, friends. You are buying salvation
when you merely pledge.
$30 gets you that
subgenius arise video and
actually, if you are familiar enough with our
catalog, you could perfectly welcome to request
another video. You may be aroused, too, by
the alliance. Oh, you would
if you're doing it right.
Friends, for $25
you get two X-rated
hour of slack CDs that could never
ever, ever be played on any
radio station anywhere because
the depth of their depravity.
And I know you want that.
We all do. You're depraved,
friends. You're very, very, very
out of line with everything around
you. In fact, you're so out of sync
with the reality that you see about you,
you're about ready to jump out of that window, aren't you?
Aren't you now? No exit. But it
is no exit. The only way
out, the only way
that you can possibly survive in this
world except for continue
eating and breathing is to pledge
$5, $10, $15,
$25 or $30.
Whip it out. 687-6900.
Whip it out indeed.
That is that number. It's a magic number.
You know that the station must,
must have been given a choice by the phone
company when they asked for phone numbers
for their pledge line. And I know that
they saw that 6900
there. You know, that has kind
of a catch to it for some reason.
Some fifth grade sort of
related reason.
687-6900
in Cleveland. That's the beautiful
216 area code.
Friends, we're also
not snobs. We are some
other word that may remind you of
a snob like blores or zans.
Or des or something like that.
But glorps. We've often been called glorps.
But we not only
appeal, but we I appeal
to everyone from
fifth graders to fifth colonists
and any other number you can
think of. So please, I'm begging
you. Please.
Friends, we're flopped over
on our backs on this big stinky
mattress and our legs are spread
wide. What more do you want?
We're offering ourselves up.
Can't you give us
a little tip?
Friends, and you can come by the station
during the open house Friday
November 17th through Sunday.
Well, from 3 to 8 p.m.
Can't show up anytime.
And from 12 to 4 on Sunday
on November the 19th.
That's coming up on Kennedy Day.
What?
Bob came
and did something with all of us, friends.
By the way, the music in the background
was all by yours truly, Reverend
Stang.
And we're going to look to God.
That's yours?
Yes. Now it's mine.
You didn't know that I knew how to
play the lute, did you?
I knew you were a luteist, but I didn't know
you were a flautist. I'm a loutist
actually. You are a loutist.
A loutist, yes. That's related
to sort of like between an artist
and a lout. I'm a blow
twister looking for fame and
fortune. I'm a young man
in search of my own inner self.
What will I do? I'm not an artist.
I'm not an 85-year-old alcoholic. No, no, no.
I'm a young man or woman
walking around town or
perhaps taking a bus.
What shall I win? Will I? How can I?
There are no answers to these
questions, my friends.
Look at this fine pledge that's been brought in.
Eat lus, you pledge.
This boy pledged or girl or
thing, Jay Krasnow.
Now, there's
nothing Krasnow
about Jay Krasnow
who bought the...
2001 antique
WCSB
shirt
with small pocket logo.
And I think there may be a couple of those
left still. Maybe.
And some of these actually have the buttocks
literally cut right out of them.
These are beautiful pieces of furniture.
Some very, very strange items
imported from the Middle East.
We don't know how they get their way
here, but we know that we're glad to have them.
We're glad to present them to you if you
pledge for more.
We'll see you next time.
Next they want $30 for
ordainment. Next thing they want
$18 for their
new book or $20 for
their video. But you can get it
for even $30 from this radio
station and you'll be doing
good or evil depending on how
you look at it. How about this
beautiful inflated blue tortoise
necklace or a stack of horn pig?
Or how about these needs and election
blowers? You're not going to find
beautiful premiums like this
anywhere else because they don't exist.
Even here. We're just talking
about the vague items that we
could offer you had we
the experiment or the mercy.
Who are the overlords of the
UFO? We're asking
you. You can answer that question.
Call the queen of the UFOs
at 687-6900.
Friends, do you realize
that one of the main
reasons that the church of the subgenius
moved its headquarters from
Dallas to Cleveland was because
of this station?
Which is the only station
in the universe that has
carried the hour of slack for
over 18 years
or something now at
9 o'clock on Sunday nights forever.
No other station anywhere
in the world has ever dared
or been able to carry this show
so completely and forever. I run into
people who go, Reverend Stagg, I used
to listen to your show when I was just
a young teenager.
And of course I always say,
it's still on, man.
But
friends, you could be part
of this world.
Perhaps you could be part of this.
Reverend Stagg, let's
talk about, if we can for a brief
moment here, I know we've been haranguing the audience
out here, trying to get them to pledge them.
Let's just explain them
in the most simple, direct terms
we can, why they're going to make out big
by making a pledge to this station
and this show.
Well, it works like this, friends. The luck
plane, which is
how Bob gets so much,
you can learn to
surf the luck plane too.
When you give money to this station,
you'll get a lot of real
good sex. It's just as simple
as that. I know that seems
like kind of a big promise
to make, but
the fact is, when you call
and pledge your money, 687-6900,
you will
have fabulous sex.
Maybe even with somebody else.
And that's not even really important.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
Pastor David Epley knew.
That's who said,
ah, yes, originally.
Now they'll, and almost in a case,
they'll get a subgenius pamphlet, which will
explain perhaps some of the arcane
dogma we've been trying to espouse.
That's right. It was written in 1980, and yet
some people haven't read the subgenius pamphlet
number one, but that goes out with every
pledge to the hour slot, even a
$5 pledge.
Don't you need to know?
Of course. It costs more posted.
Much than $5 to send you that thing,
but that's how much we care
about you.
Postage, pastage, it's nothing
to us. We want to get the message across.
That's right.
And if we have to use
embedded subliminals deep inside the
background music that you can't really
hear, but keep echoing in your
brain all night while you sleep, well, that's
what we'll do. You can call tomorrow
and pledge to some other show.
If you're too scared now,
what's the matter, chicken?
Oh, freak.
Afraid your mom
might find out that you pledged
to WCSB?
Come on, man. Don't you want to be
cool? Yeah, don't you
want to be really hip?
Don't you want to be down
with the down with
fang? Everybody's doing it, man.
Everybody
has done it. Actually, I wish.
If everybody was calling
687-6900-pledging to the hour
slack at WCSB, well, I guess
we wouldn't have to worry about
George.
W. Bush! Because he
never would have gotten, he would never have been
governor of Texas. He wouldn't
have been allowed in Texas
if this station had had more
pledges earlier.
They never would have let him out of Connecticut.
Friends, you
could have stopped
the horror of today's world and
made this an earthly paradise if you had
called and pledged last year. Are you
going to let that chance go by again?
Friends, there's no need for Marxism
or Pupar values.
Or trying to re-increase your cranial
surface. Everything you want
in a paradise can be found right here
in this small, little, tiny religion.
Take it like a pill or live
it like a drill. The surface
is clean and awaiting
you. Just pledge right now
687-6900.
Is that a hard number to remember?
Is that a hard number to forget?
I think not.
Take the red pill and the blue pill
and then take five more
of each, man.
Go for it! Go the distance,
man!
Call and pledge, dude!
It's like
a thousand years of like the
perfect evolution that made for the
giant brain with like a solid
diamond in the center. And you
can get to that diamond. We can cut it
open. We can get to it
if we just have the tools
and you can give us those tools.
Now, can't you? We're just
asking the small, small
donations.
$8,000? That'll go a long
way towards helping fix the transmitter.
We will. In fact, if you send
in $7,000, forget about
brassieres or taking evolutionary
as a pill, we will send you
the entire fully completed
diagram of the evolutionary
scale as it began and
will end.
From Yeti to Common Slug.
Come on, man!
Get with the new creationist
science.
Join or die.
Join
or die.
Join or die.
Join us, humans.
Even a human can help.
You don't have to be ashamed.
Humans don't have to hide in the
closet anymore. Come on out.
Admit you're a human. Sure, you may not be
a full-fledged subgenius
by virtue of not having ever
been ordained by Bob
officially, but you can
come.
Come so close if you can
just help Bob's
called ministers.
Dave and I have been preaching
here at these microphones
for, I don't even
know how long.
But we remember you,
each and every one of you,
by your scent, by the
whiff reading that we can do because we're
in the spirit. We're clairvoyant.
We have third nostrils that Bob
opened up in a secret ceremony
behind us in the
cave in Malaysia,
in the Himalayas
with the Yetis
clapping and watching. Friends,
and that's why we know
what's in your heart. We do.
And what's in your mind. You'll pay to know what
you really think, so call
687-6900.
Bob said it. I believed
it. You smoked it and heard
it and listened to it, so get on it
baby.
Friends, some of you I'd like you to right now,
I'd like you to get close to the window, look out the
window now, I would like you
to begin feeling your face right now.
Take your hands, both your index fingers
and feel your face. Feel your
ears, your eyes, your neck.
Now I want you to take one hand
and feel your other hand.
Then feel your feet, your
twitter blades, your shoulder
softenings, the other parts, the muscular
parts of your body, and then
ask yourself, are you different?
Are you different than the
other small children and elderly
ladies around you? Do you have
different needs than they do?
Well, if you do, if you
notice the most minuscule,
the tiniest little difference
between you and your peers, you
are cooked if you do not pledge
to this show and pledge to the station.
I can't even notice the difference between them and their penises,
much less their peers.
It's all distinct and random.
Wait, I'm getting a signal. I'm in the spirit, I'm in
discernment. I'm going into discernment.
I'm feeling a
strong surge in my
loins. It's coming from the direction of
of, uh, it's somewhere
southeast of here. North Carolina.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah, it's coming
from Raleigh. I'm seeing
something in my mind. It's like a store.
Wards. I'm getting smoky already. It's Wards.
Montgomery, no, no, not
Wards. Sears, Target,
something.
But I know that money
is coming from this source.
Oh, Stan, look, look, look, right in front of you.
I know that I'm going to be mailing in a rise
2005 to this person.
Oh my God, it's true!
Harold Sears in Gorman, Raleigh
North Carolina, in fact,
bledged $55
and I know that he's good for it.
Because I saw that in the
spirit. That may be all
he's good for, friends, just like so many
of you and I of us.
You may only be good for one thing, and that
is feeding us donuts.
But if you think of it the right way,
or if you even think of it the wrong way,
it doesn't matter. If you have any
brain to think with at all,
please use it.
Take your left hand and pick up
the phone. Take your right hand and
begin dialing the digits. No, not
those digits. Those
digits! 687-6900
and pledge
right now.
Or, you know, within a few minutes he's okay too, I guess.
Are we going to be here for another...
Another ten minutes, if they'll allow us.
I hope they allow us to come back.
The security guys are already out.
We're not seeing all that much action.
That bank of phones is all...
Not a single one lit up right now.
Well, there was a big...
I was short about a half an hour ago. I don't know.
I thought they were supposed to... Oh, sure. We've had
three or four precious, beloved
listeners call in.
Mr. Montgomery Ward's there,
and Dr. Light
with his light lute
juice called in, and
a few of our friends.
We did get a crank call from Dick Cheney
claiming he was going to
pledge the $7,000. He does that
every year.
He thinks
he's the dick.
You know.
And his name isn't even really Dick Cheney,
but he's going, oh, I'm Dick Cheney,
therefore I'm the dick.
Well, he may be a dick, but he ain't Bob.
That's right.
There's only... You know, there's a lot of
Bobs out in the world, but there's only one Bob.
You know what I'm saying?
And we've...
And listen to these followers.
These are the folks answering
the phones right now. They're so excited.
You can hear them in the background. I turned up
the mic in the other room there.
The phones. They're...
Quite a celebration.
We are in the spirit here at the
station. Won't you be part of this wondrous
outreach?
Oh, man, this is great.
Praise Bob. Praise Bob.
Praise St.
Otis.
And praise Princess We Are
Dull for taking your
absurd and almost repugnant
calls. I don't know, friends, if I can...
If we don't get five more
pledges in the next five minutes,
I'm going to walk towards that
window, Mark, not an exit.
I'm going to look languidly down on
the people below as if I could touch them
with my fingers. I'm going to
stare vacuously into space,
and then I'm going to step one foot
right out of that door, Mark,
not a door.
As long as you don't urinate.
I thought that was what you were going to do,
Dave, like last time.
I can't urinate now? What the hell kind
of a free country is this?
Well, now, I heard that they were going to...
The household security people
were trying to set it up to where we're
not allowed to leave or enter the
country without a special new permission.
Passport's not good enough
anymore. There's Indo and Exo passports
now. There's so many different names
to remember, friends. You don't have to remember
funny names if you call 687-6900.
You will be
one of those funny names yourself.
And the next time one of the surveillance
police officers of the new states
of corporate America asks,
asks you for your ID, say,
that's my id, baby, and it talks like
my ego, and it means I love
Bob. That's right, friends.
Bob can just tap his finger against
your pocket and know everything about
you. And so can the conspiracy.
So which one do you want
to put sticking his hands in your pockets?
The conspiracy
devil man or J.R. Bob
Dobbs? Or maybe
Mrs. Dobbs?
Connie? Who do you want
playing pocket pool with your
horses? Think of it that way, friends.
Think about that. It's a vast forest
out there, and there's plenty of trees,
but if you can't see the
forest from the trees, you're no
freaking good to me.
I'm leaving, man.
Hey, J. We don't get
that shit. Okay, man. I'm
just gonna turn, I just turn on the background
tape. I'll just turn
on the pledge drive tapes from before.
Look at that.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, okay, okay. I'm gonna
turn that off. We're gonna, because you,
there's still a chance to
call 687-6900.
You could
do it. The seconds are
sliding by. The deadline
is approaching. The countdown is
in progress. The balloon
is going up.
X-Day is coming.
I'm cooler than you
are.
I'm weightier
than you are.
I'm more formless
and diseased than the
saints. I have
three purple
girlfriends.
So I'm reading a set list here
again. Friends... Now look at
this beloved donator.
He not only donated blood, but $10.
And does he, he doesn't even want a premium.
All he wants is a program
guide so he can learn about the
other fabulous shows on
CSB, such as Radio
Synesthesia, coming up next
every Sunday night at 10 o'clock.
Praise Troy.
Praise Troy. And praise Helen of Troy.
Helen of, uh...
I saw
the movie of that not too long ago.
And you
played Paris Hilton. It was stiff.
It was stiff, yeah.
It had some marvelous
panoramic scenes that were
all special effects. But you know, everything's
just a special effect. When are we gonna get that?
When are we gonna get real, friends?
When are we gonna get real?
You got
two more minutes to get real in.
And then
any call you make is gonna go into
the earhole pockets
of Dr. Sinister.
Now that's almost as
good as Bob.
Do you understand
infinity? Do you understand
the crushing and crunching of
time into four, five, six,
seven dimensions?
If you can, you can see that little pink
finger twisting around the clock
saying that you have
two, that's two
minutes to call.
120 seconds to answer
your life's delirium.
The thing that brought you here
out of that slab
and a wound that dropped
in the face.
Why are you here
if not to pledge
to us?
Alright, well look.
We've got work to do.
I've gotta go work on my history
of the subgenius online course
I'm doing with MaybeLogic.org.
My hysterical piece.
Oh, what was it again?
Oh, this thing I'm doing on MaybeLogic.org.
It's an online
academy of...
You just have to look at it.
You don't care.
I know, but he's such a...
You are a brilliant man and you've given
so much and yet they want to pledge
so little. What can I say?
Actually, friends, we love those
of you who've pledged
and we detest and despise
everyone who didn't pledge.
We look down on you like
you were a dog.
Like you were some kind of dirty dog.
Like a blower than a primate
as Jim Jones said as he
seemed not to understand that humans
are primates. In fact,
when we leave tonight, the guy that I
usually see and say hi to
that is sweeping up down by the
bottom, as you mean there,
he usually takes care of the floors around there
and he is always very friendly. If I
hear that that guy didn't
pledge at least five lousy
bucks, he's got a job staying.
You know, and most of us don't really have
real jobs, you know, just come around
and you get enough gas money, oh, you go up to the
station, you know. You think I'm
going to talk to him? You think I'm going to say hi like I
usually do? Say, hey, bud, what's going on?
You catch a brown today?
You know what I'm going to say to him? I'm going to say
beep you because I'm not allowed
to really say it and I'm going to shoot him
a bird or two and I'm
going to storm past him and say, if you don't want to
pledge and put your money where your mouth is,
your mouth smells like
pooey.
Pooey, yeah.
Pooey. Okay, we've got to get out of here.
Friends, this is
WCSB 89.3
FM in Cleveland, Ohio.
An inappropriate... I better take
this inappropriate song off because
people thought it had cuss words in it
even though we were just singing in
Romanian and, well, okay.
Stay tuned.
Price Bob.
Thank you
for your pledges.
Now, fork it over, baby.
You humanist!
You subgenius!
So, friends,
you know, the money isn't just for the hour of slack.
It's for the totality that is
this station. It isn't just for us
mutants. It's for your
very mind, your very soul.
And you wouldn't believe how close your
soul is to being sold out.
Dear
brother or sister, between your job
and the drugs and the lies, listen, you need
every bit of slack you can hang on to.
But we have a special form of slack
in store for you tonight.
Not stored in souls anywhere,
folks.
And the type of slack you're going to be getting
is guilt. Guilt.
Tonight, we're going to whip us up some guilt.
And some of you are saying, oh, it's pledge time.
Reverend Stang's going to rant all night about
money. And you'd better
be afraid that that's true,
little Bobby, little Gimme Bob out there.
At this level, our salesman
can see the top of the ladder and is well
on his way there.
One of the good old boys
are here tonight. We'd like to welcome you down to
the television mission. Don't forget
if all you can do is sit at home, then
try to keep yourselves awake
and dial the phone.
Call in for pledges.
Yes, answering the phones this evening.
Beautiful, Dr. Zafon.
Beautiful Reverend...
Cecilia.