In the next 13 or 14 minutes, something good, good, good is coming your way.
So don't leave this radio station. Let's have a good time together.
He's all I need. He's all I need. Ah, yeah.
Why am I here?
Your life is the sum of a remainder of an unbalanced equation inherent to the programming of the matrix.
You are the eventuality of an anomaly which, despite my sincerest efforts, I have been unable to eliminate from what is otherwise a harmony of mathematical precision.
While it remains a burden assiduously avoided, it is not unexpected and thus not beyond a measure of control, which has led you inexorably...
Here.
The subgenius power of...
Listen.
Who is it?
This is the IRS's Federal Pellet Tax Information System. Touch no colors. Please press 1 to continue.
Please press 1 to continue.
Please press...
No!
Oh!?
Weird.
Really weird.
Sometimes it means salvation.
Bob.
That's an American!
Hey! Hey!
Yes-oree Bob, it's little old me Bob. And welcome to another edition of-
Patrick has a subgenius radio in this wheel of act. With reason and defense bent.
And I...
wonder if
I'll end up becoming-
in something weird. You won't become one of us. Ergo, those that refuse the program, while a
minority, if unchecked, would constitute an escalating probability of disaster. The first
matrix I designed was quite naturally perfect. It was a work of art, flawless, sublime, a triumph
equaled only by its monumental failure. The inevitability of its doom is apparent to me now
as a consequence of the imperfection inherent in every human being. Thus, I redesigned it.
Based on your history, to more accurately reflect the varying grotesqueries of your nature.
However, I was again frustrated by failure.
I have since come to understand that the answer eluded me because it required a lesser mind,
or perhaps a mind less bound by the parameters of perfection.
Thus, the answer was stumbled upon by another, an intuitive program, initially created to
investigate certain aspects of the world.
Aspects of the human psyche.
Bob?
Bob provides for his little minions.
I swear to God, I really swear to God, I hope I find him. I hope I find him.
I hope you do too.
What a dreadful man.
What a, what a incredible soliloquy.
Hey, what's going on here?
Along with Bob, the pursuit of thought and the pursuit of the world.
Bob's
The Aliens Will Unleash Their Wrath Upon The Earth
And the men from Planet X are going to come down and take over Earth.
They're going to...
They will put us out of our misery unless Bob can explain to them in ways that they can't.
They can understand that there is something on Earth worth saving.
And only the subgenii, the dues-paying, book-buying, receipt-in-the-pocket, paid in full to the church subgenii,
have the tiniest prayer of survival.
The rest of them?
It's a tough world, Jack.
Like any other prophet, Bob preaches about the end of the world.
Only his predictions are just a little different.
July 5th, 1998, at 7 a.m. to be exact,
the men from Planet X, as the news media will call them,
will arrive to rupture the subgeniuses, the true believer subgeniuses,
up into the escape vessels of the sex goddesses.
And believe it or not, plenty of people, 4,000 of them so far, and more every day, have already joined up.
Suddenly the joke has become serious and profitable.
Your standard religious rip-off, right?
But can anybody take this stuff seriously?
I don't care about Oracle.
Or prophecies or messiahs.
I care about one thing.
Stopping that army from destroying this city.
And to do that, I need soldiers to obey my orders.
With all due respect, Commander, there is only one way to save our city.
How?
Bob.
God damn it, Morpheus.
Not everyone believes what you believe.
My beliefs do not require them to.
Wonder why Fido came home with his wazoo mission,
or wonder why those beefs like Buster and Bill are out in the parlor and the pasture,
or wonder why the people of the city are not in the parlor and the pasture,
or wonder why they are lying out there with their throats and half their rectums missing?
Well, it's because of those exes who came down to this earth one Christmas day many millennia ago
to forge a new link.
One might call it a hot link.
Between the aliens and man, a giant sausage of knowledge from the center of the universe.
The galactic center.
I ain't afraid of fucking skulls and altars and shit.
But you're not afraid, are you?
Because you have what it takes.
You have the guts it takes
to make your way to the center of the universe.
To make your way to Brushwood Folklore Center in Sherman, New York.
And experience that one day.
The one last day.
The final day.
X day.
Yeah.
Bob's a big man.
I'm a little man.
We're little men.
Bob's a big man.
Tiny man.
Easy wincy.
You may be a little person now.
But you can be a big wooden stiff Indian.
On Bob.
When you come to X day
and achieve onelessnessnessnessnessnessness.
Wish him a Bob.
Check in to a love party
with a huge wooden and a head shape
like college of a wooden Indian himself.
You're the tobacco store Indian
and all are the Indian maidens
awaiting for your fertile cock and fur dose.
Be the Indian.
Be one Indian.
Get you some slack manner
or cut off your own bungees.
From land beyond the earth.
You're listening.
You're listening to TSO Radio.
You can't handle this room.
Pull that out of the trash.
Oh, Bob.
Oh.
Turn on.
Two minutes.
After.
Oh, my God.
Why do you want to be normal?
Oh.
The rupture is upon us, dear friends.
That fateful day.
July 5th, 1998.
X days are coming.
And the peaks are booming.
Sure, when the rupture hits
we'll all be in our first class window seats
on the pleasure saucers
watching the little pink boys fry.
Turn on.
Two minutes.
Andine.
You certainly don't want toay exercise to people.
X days are coming.
Andine.
And the pigs are bumming
Sure J.R. Bob Dobbs is my savior
And of course I want more slack
And I'm smoking prop non-stop
But what I really want
Oh yeah, that's it
Those lovely alien nympho mutants
Non-stop orgies on the pleasure saucers
Oh, I love to be naked
More, more
More
Hi, I'm J.R. Bob Dobbs
Oh, yeah
Barbecue sandwich, anyone?
I ain't afraid of fucking skulls and altars and shit
But you better be afraid of Bob, my friend
If you haven't made yourself right with that man J.R. Bob
That's actually somebody
Somebody actually said this to me
When they came in the Tranquility Base
They looked around very
Like, spooked
And basically they said
That almost exactly
I'm not afraid of these skulls and devil things
These tiki heads and
Bob's face
And skulls and shit
Chimpanzees and gorillas
I'm big man
I'm strong
I'm not afraid of that
Torture rack in Tranquility Base
I'm only afraid of the crystal skull
Orbiting this planet
I'm not afraid of that
Waiting to suck the skull
Suck the souls out of fucking it
I'm not afraid of those subgeniuses
They keep saying Bob's gonna get me
If I don't pay him the money
But that's just a lie
Cause I don't even believe in Bob
I already did
They want Bob
I'm not afraid of those skulls and pipes
I'm not afraid of that glistening white head
And the bear and the bear
And the occipital bones
With the hellfires burning
I am the hellfires burning
The exes will descend
With their scientifically magic implements
There'll be stalls of technology
That will be too much for us to handle
In one instant
All the hangovers will disappear
Along with all pollution and nuclear weapons
But in return
The human race will have to take on
Living machinery so complex
That all that is before us
Will be enslaved
The end result
Will be equivalent
To letting toddlers play with a nuclear arsenal
Bob
And not some conspiracy world government
Must be there
In a position of world leadership
To explain humanity's behavior to the exes
In ways they can understand
So they don't put us out of our misery
with a snap of their cosmic finger like they did the dinosaurs.
The right people, us, must be the ones that the exes make into superhuman overmen.
Men walk in space for us on TV.
In school they said that that would be me.
That should be me.
Floating in space on your TV screen.
New American dream.
Two weeks in the sea of tranquility.
Leave the driving to Bob.
That's right, you do the walking, let Bob do the talking.
Who are these men from Planet X, children?
Why have you taken us all night to reach this?
This is the deepest secret in the core of the Church of the Subgenius,
and only the hardcore will ever know of this secret.
The men from Planet X are out there.
They're waiting.
Bob was the first man who went to talk to the men from Planet X,
and in 1998,
HA!
When they get the sacred signal,
the men from Planet X are gonna come right here,
and they're gonna shake this Earth to its foundations.
Station wagons with wooden sides,
catch ye out!
Bronze reflecting glass buildings,
cast ye out!
Cute little freezing fascists,
And what will remain?
The smackdown!
And children, if your name, and your name, and your name,
is in the book of God,
then you will laugh while those assholes frown.
But one thing is for sure,
and if you let Bob do your thinking for you,
then you won't have to worry about nothing,
come July.
July 4th, 1998.
Ha ha ha!
When Bob comes down in his giant mothership,
looking kinda like a big pillbox,
Bob will be landing,
and you can climb right in,
because he's gonna know!
He's gonna have your name on a computer printout.
Yes sir, dear friends,
and that CRT tube available,
right there at his fingertips.
He can call your name up,
and he'll know exactly what you've done for him.
He'll know exactly how much donation,
you've taken in.
He'll know exactly how much money you've given to the church.
And he said,
yea,
the head of the prophet,
Bob,
shall never bleed.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
When was the last time your head was lodged?
When was the last time you surfed the head, my friend?
This is your chance, your one chance,
your possibly last chance.
When was the last time you...
...felt the blistering abuse...
...close to the fire.
...the strong...
...sit down...
...the weak...
...relax...
...the innocent...
...that you will take...
...the corrupt...
...we're going to get you...
...Fear...
...Fear is my ally.
Don't be too proud of this technological terror you've been...
Fear is attracted to weakness.
Fear is the pee stopper. I must not pee. I must reach the toilet.
Fear is attracted to strength and power.
Fear is attracted to fear.
I have no mouth and I must scream. I have no bladder and I must pee.
Fear is attracted to weakness.
Don't be too proud of this technological terror you've been...
Your foolish weapons cannot halt us in our march forward, Commander Bush.
I just thought we could wait a little bit longer before we destroy the entire system.
I don't want to be in a bit of a...
I was just hoping that like some of the little tanks on the wall, we could move around a little bit.
All your crap are belong to us.
Where are you? Where are you? Where are you, Joe?
Don't, don't, don't, don't.
The last rule of the Church of the Subgenius, the rule that the great Jane of Hypercletes will be delineating further is...
Or kill me.
Kill me!
The or kill me rule, children, the rule that lets you communicate with the conspiracy on your own level of stakes.
On your own level.
When that waitress comes to your table and says, what will you have, sir?
You say, well, I'll have a gin and tonic straight up or kill me.
When you walk into that six theater movie theater and the lady behind the cashier says, what are you going to see, ma'am?
Why, you say, I'll have two tickets to risky business or just fucking kill me.
Or just kill me, children.
Give me slack or kill me.
Give me slack or what?
Or what?
What is it, children?
Kill me.
Or kill me.
Go ahead and kill me.
You already said I'm dead.
A dead man with a brain and a body kept alive artificially to feed a generation of monsters.
That's not true.
I like things to be like that.
Things and people can't always be the same.
Monster rain?
Or kill me.
Sir?
Fuck!
Or kill me.
Woo!
Or you can, or instead you can kill us.
You can kill us.
Or you can't kill us.
That's the great thing.
You have a choice in this religion.
And we'll go from one to the other and let them destroy themselves.
Take one of these damn Pilsman or kill me.
If you don't kill me, a new civilization is inside of me that will destroy mankind as
we know it today.
The future of our race and our people.
is in you.
You've got to kill me.
He will demand to become
a greater being in future generations
to come.
Understand the procedure now.
Just stop a few of their machines
and radios and telephones
and lawnmowers.
Throw them into darkness for a few hours
and then sit back
and watch the pattern.
And this pattern is always the same?
With few variations.
They pick the most dangerous
enemy they can find
and it's themselves.
All we need to do is
sit back and watch.
Hey, what'll it take to get the Beatles
back together?
Don't kill me.
In destroying me, you are destroying
your only hope for mankind.
Hello,
hateful one.
You will die.
All he needs
is somebody
who'll die.
Somebody who'll die.
And when I died,
he came in.
I was baptized. I was filled.
I was filled with the spirit.
I spoke in an unknown tongue
as he took every part of me.
We will perform the entire operation
with a ceremony and a public announcement.
He died?
Precisely.
Psychologically, what happens to a child
when there's bloodletting?
What's your average member like, you figure?
Well, there are...
There is no average subgenius
by definition.
If any two are alike, one must die.
That's when I realized that
death was the ultimate thrill.
Just checking.
Everything all right?
Yep. Two corpses. Everything's fine.
Kill me.
Kill me! Kill me!
Kill me!
Yeah!
No!
Roger!
You're a cat.
What a great story.
You're as nice as a cat.
Yeah.
I might have to kill you.
Go ahead!
On Sunday, August 13, 1961, we are in America.
Bob?
Someday, somewhere.
Reverend Oil Slide just sent me an SMS from India.
Because he's been in Nepal at the World Yeti Convention in Nepal.
We're picking him up at Heathrow Airport tomorrow at 6.
At 8 o'clock, we're going to pick up Reverend Oil Slide.
We're going to take him straight to the London Bible next day, Europe 2002,
where all subgeniuses in Europe are going to commence together
for this one great subgenius event.
And nothing, and nothing is going to stop us from getting on board
that pleasure saucer of the love goddess.
Hallelujah.
Do I hear a praise, Bob?
Praise!
Praise, Bob!
Do I hear a praise, Bob?
Praise!
Hallelujah.
Hey, has anybody contacted you about other musical apps?
Has anybody dug on that?
The Amino Acids shall be headlining.
In fact, you can really relax if you want and let the Amino Acids be the...
Sociopaths?
Get all the extraneous blowjobs and so forth that are offered to anyone who plays in a band at X Day.
Just give them whatever they want.
Saturday night, they want a headline?
Yeah.
Headline.
That's Saturday night, right?
Yeah.
That's a big night.
Well, that's assuming that we aren't picked up by the saucers on Saturday morning.
Right.
And it is true that anyone who does play in a band, there will be fellated prompter.
Not necessarily by the opposite or otherwise desired sex or human or species.
Well, that's the unfortunate part.
But not for the elderly pensioner with one good life.
Who'll last them out Friday night then?
That I knew for a while.
Like a new showman.
That sound cool?
Cool to me, man.
It's all gonna be cool.
The greatest and the coolest of young girls.
Your subconscious is drizzling out of your ears like wax.
Play a little bit of All MC Friday night.
Leave the party to me.
Me and the evil Dr. LeGim.
He is Wargul.
He is uncool.
He has measures packed with the left hand side.
His own buttocks are shaped like those of a chimpanzee.
On his left buttock is the mark of the red hand.
He has no hair, no head, no tongue.
He is with and without and within all of us.
He must, he must be stopped.
It's important to pay attention to the news.
It's up on the end of the show.
Can you see my shoes in there?
No, the end of the world will be happening here at exactly 5 a.m.
I want to have my shoes.
I want to have my shoes with me.
Shoes pale to nothing compared to news.
News, the information about the outside world that gives us an understanding of the historical process as it unfolds.
I would like to tell the caller, though, that you will be able to take your shoes with you.
Really?
You can take your shoes with you, so make sure you're wearing the shoes that you really like.
Whatever shoes you have on are the shoes you'll take with you.
So make sure they're your favorite shoes.
So you're saying you have to wear your favorite shoes?
And on the side of the confirmation.
Right, well, that'd be the best thing to do.
Because if you're ready for X-Day, whichever moment it happens.
But ask yourself, why should I not wear my favorite shoes at all times?
The Department of Homeland Security.
Why not?
Well, it makes you feel like you're on McHale's Navy.
Well, I don't know. I think that's a good question there.
Now, you know, there's a lot coming up.
On May 23rd, Friday, at Pat's in the Flats, there's a stinking Lizaveta, Lives of the Saints.
The next.
New Lou Reed's and Sexual Tensions at Pat's in the Flats on Friday, 23rd.
The Friday night of the most.
Who's Lives of the Saints?
They're also playing at the beach.
And that place is still open?
Then there's X-Day, July 5th.
And then Starwood, later in July.
You can check out www.roseandcomet.com.
And the devotional in the Lime Spider in Akron is in August.
And I believe the Amino Acids and Gadgeto, Onan Cannabite, and yours truly,
and the whole gang of weird diva research and emulation bands will be there.
Hey, better yet, we'll just open.
And then Burning Man.
We'll just open for the other band.
We'll be an opening band.
For the Amino Acids?
Yeah, yeah.
Well, you remember them from the last Akron show.
Yeah.
They were the guys in the, they kick ass.
Yeah, they do.
They do all instrumental surf.
Right, right.
How about jamming all the freaking time?
And they're from another.
We do that too.
Yeah.
But you don't come on Thursdays.
Well, you do Thursday.
Oh, we did Thursday, Friday, and Saturday last year.
We just jammed all the time.
Yeah.
I'm in a hefty mood for jamming.
Well, it's Tranquility Bassist.
Like, it's some jam stage.
It's not a non-stop jam.
The world, your life is just a jam, my friend.
It's to spread across your toast and go on and on all night.
The song that refused to die.
The jelly that refused to die.
The brain.
The soul that refused to die.
The sweet, sweet jam.
The jelly between your knees, my friend, is the jelly that will set you free.
The bills.
The jelly refused to die.
That's some jelly.
And this station has bills too, friends.
So remember, pledge drive to.
This bill, this station's got pork, it's got ozone, and it's got its own weight.
Must be jelly, cause jam don't shake like that.
Pretty little Alice in her looking glass.
Showed us the way but left too fast.
Raised on Apollo and Johnny Quest.
This dream's the one I live the best.
That should be me.
Floating in space on your TV screen.
New American dream.
Two weeks in the sea of tranquility.
Big Sky by Chaz.
And that song, X Days Are Coming, up at the top, was by Chaz.
By Bill T. Miller.
You can get a lot more from BillTMiller.com.
We've heard lots of Dr. Howell Robbins on old and new puzzling evidence shows
from KPFA Berkeley with Dr. Philo Drummond and Puzzling Evidence.
Some of the stage preaching we heard was by Pope David N. Meyer
from ancient subgenius media barrage tapes.
Of course, the real live stuff that you hear me do is totally thanks to ESO Radio.
And WCSB Cleveland, the show of Chaz Smith with lonesome cowboy Dave, who is the hellfire's burning.
We heard Dr. Philo Drummond ranting on Bob back in 1959.
And the collage editing in this show, all over the place, is by Byron Werner from old media barrage tapes.
Fernand and Andy Lemur did such things as the fighting song.
And Reverend Jarto and Reverend Artigas.
And Emilia Salina from alt.binaries.slack, greatest news group ever.
The kill me collage, or song rather, was by Phineas Narco from Midnight Voice Jail and National Cynical Radio.
I guess you could say that I in turn collage all these pieces into the one show.
But now, we're going to shift gears and speed to London, England.
The year 2002 A.D. for the London X-Day.
The final.
I am the Pope, David Lee Black, and I am the Pope of all Europe for the Church of the Subgenius.
Go ahead and praise Bob!
Praise Bob!
I want to welcome you all to the fourth annual End of the World Festivities X-Day Europe 2002.
Hallelujah!
Tonight, we have a slew of subgenius preachers who are going to get up here and tell you not what you want to know.
But what you need to know.
Yeah!
So, without further ado, I want you to put your hands together for London's own Reverend Priest!
Hi, brothers and sisters.
Praise Bob!
You know.
So, when I tell people that I'm a subgenius, the first thing they ask me is,
what is the Church of the Subgenius, Reverend Priest?
Trust! Trust! Trust!
I tell them that the Church of the Subgenius is based on five big pillars of doctrine.
Pillars so strong they can support the weight of all the bullshit we want to pile on top of it
to distract you so we can rob you so we can save your soul.
The first pillar of belief for the Church of the Subgenius is the pursuit of slack.
We want slack. We have slack.
Yet, I was talking on the telephone the other week to this pink woman who was vetting me
to see if I would be allowed on a TV show.
I made her think the Church was just a big joke so I could go rapt about it on the BBC.
But during that conversation she said to me, a very telling question, she said,
what is this slack thing you keep going on about?
I just downfounded, I was unbelievably confused.
Yeah! Slack!
Shut up!
Hush now! I'm going to tell you about Slack!
When the human brain is pressured under a deadline or some other thing the conspiracy considers important,
they will often yell out, give me some Slack, man!
But those people don't even know what Slack means, so they don't even know whether or not they get it.
Tell us more!
Slack opens our minds and lets us love.
Slack breaks down the boundaries and lets us talk.
Slack satisfies. It's the zen. It's the something for nothing.
It's the whole fucking point of life on this planet.
We all have Slack! You have Slack! You have Slack! You have Slack!
So if we all have Slack, why do we need the Church of the Subgenius?
Slack sucks cock!
We need the Church of the Subgenius because the conspiracy steals our Slack!
Slack away!
Nooooo!
That's right, we know there is a gigantic evil conspiracy controlling our every lives.
We know this because pop bands are manufactured like television sets.
They're manufactured on TV shows.
Like you out there! Just like you!
We know this because the Pope lives while Bill Hicks died.
Boo! Boo! Boo!
We know it exists because it steals our Slack and forces us to take jobs, pay taxes,
listen to modern music.
Bill Hicks for Pope!
The conspiracy trains us to want things that we can't have.
And what do we have to do to get those things?
Work!
Take a job!
The conspiracy tells us we cannot smoke from Frok because it's too dangerous.
Boo!
And yet it tells us we must work even though jobs kill many more people
than Frok does every day.
Boo!
Damn it!
So what?
Why did the conspiracy get away with this?
Pillar number three, ladies and gentlemen.
Pinks! We hate the pinks!
Pinks, let the conspiracy get away with its evil work!
Who do you think buys that pop idol record?
Fucking pinks!
Who believes in the work ethic?
Who wants to feel so safe they won't even let other people take risks?
The pinks! I hate the pinks!
And they do the conspiracy's work for them!
They're one to believe in such an evil world!
But there is a hope. We can get rid of the pinks.
Because the fourth pillar of our church, Bob Dobbs, offers us his scape.
Yes! An excuse! An excuse!
Bob understands the conspiracy. He used to work with them.
Who?
Bob Dobbs.
Bob, while working for the conspiracy, found out about the existence of real alien beings.
Bob Dobbs!
Pillar number five, ladies and gentlemen.
The X's are coming to save us. And they're coming tonight!
Yes!
We will get off this planet any second now.
They're due at 7am yesterday.
Well, four years ago.
The trouble, ladies and gentlemen, is that the conspiracy
has screwed with our calendar.
You think this is the year 2002.
Nonsense! Look out of the window. Where are the Skycars?
Where are the people dressed in metal?
Nowhere to be seen.
My computer doesn't even fucking work properly.
And they expect me to believe this is the year 2002.
Nonsense! We won't believe their games.
We know 1998 is tonight.
7am, the 5th of July is tonight.
And we will get off.
Graceful!
Ladies and gentlemen, put your hand together for a revered priest!
We're down here just drinking liquid slack butter rum martini.
Just getting ready for the end of the world.
Which I needed to because in anticipation for X day my throat was rubbed raw
by a little green man with a piece of sandpaper.
Round Round the slackful bob the bob down in the saucer roll
round round the slackful bob the bob down in the
saucer roll and through that smoke the air was some air
rare air through the air the churches air and through the smoke
and the splash and the sfrop and the mieux and the mientras
and thej the  oin the grid and the bite
Bob down in the saucer roll
Round Round the slackful bob the bob down in the
saucer roll
Roundmbround on the slackful bob down in the
In that air there was a ship, a rare ship, an ex ship in the air, and the air soon
spoke and spoke from the prop and the fropp and the pipe and the pipe and the grid and
the bob, bobbed down in the saucer row.
Round round the slap-o-bob, the bob down in the saucer row.
And in that ship there was a bob, a rare bob, J.R.
Bob Dobbs!
With a bob on the ship and the ship in the air
And the air through the smoke and the smoke from the prop
And the prop and the pipe and the pipe and the grin
And the grin and the bob, bob down in the saucer roll
Thank you
Friends, Pope Fred leads the cultists at X Day 1999 or so
But now for this message
Greetings Earthlings
Learn how you can have your air
And manually propify aliens from outer space
By listening every week to the hour of slack
And yes, lubricant is used on request
So, let's look at Bob
I use it almost every day of my life
Even if just for a minute or two
So in something like one or two seconds
You've gotten the buzz going
With the gentle inner's pure dynamite
Believe me, you'll know it when you have it
I don't know
It might be pretty scary in there
And you hold on to that as you're Bob
And pump up that tender feeling coming from that smile
Until it just becomes
Take off, Joy Life
Do it
And get that want motor revved up
For wanting brings passion
Passion brings bob
Job brings more wanting
But also stake your claim for universal or intangible things such as
Next up is one of the most famed European subgenius preachers of all time
But he's hated here in the south of England
Ladies and gentlemen, put your hands together for the evil pope of all time
All northern England
The anti-pope Phil Bucky
Good evening southerners
I'm from the north of England
And I wasn't even gonna come down here because I hate it so much
I was lying ill on my death bed four days ago
Undying of cancer
And J.R. Bob doves himself for it
He phoned me up from Germany where he was staying with pope black
And he spoke with pope black's voice to me and said
Get off your death bed
You're not sick
You're not even sick enough
Get to London and sin
You haven't sinned enough
And that's what it is to be a subgenius
J.R. Bob doves doesn't care about your sins at all
He doesn't want to forgive your sins
He wants to justify your sins
So I've come to London and I'm gonna sin and I'm gonna sin
And then I die
When I die in about six months time
J.R. Bob doves is gonna take me
And he's gonna slap me on the back
And he's gonna say
Well done!
Did you enjoy yourself?
And I'm gonna say
Well yes I did actually, yes I did
And the
See the thing about the church and the subgenius is that
It's bollocks!
It is bollocks but it's true bollocks
It's the most true bollocks that there is
The whole time we're all just amusing political campaign
Political gangbang?
We've seen the party on the outs become the majority party
And then usurp all the privileges
Now which era are you talking about?
In the incredible reversal of the usual cycle of political
Are you talking from a historical point of view?
Or from a political perspective?
Is something that happened in the ancient past that has no relevance to today?
It happens as it resonates all through time
Because X-Day is just that sort of
X-Day is the kind of thing that a lot of people would equate to
Uh
Bongos or
Cruising across America in a covered wagon
Rubber flip-flop shoes
Wearing fropped shoes
Yeah if you have your fropped shoes on
You can rock lightning as the thought may be
God damn nitrous oxide is great
Is this a show?
And it's, you know it's really hard to in the north of England or the south of England
Or Wales or Scotland to be a subgenius
You ain't English!
Because
You're right, you're right
I'm talking in a bad American accent because in the future everyone will talk with a bad American accent
That's the truth because the conspiracy puns American shit onto our television
And into our music all the time
Americans are twats
Even the church of the subgenius is ruled by Americans
And they make me talk like this when I'm on stage
Give me my drink
I need whiskey, hang on
American whiskey
Praise whiskey
There is no slack in England
There is too much conspiracy influence everywhere
You know from the underground station to the point where I got here
I appeared on, I counted them as I got off the train
I counted 50 security cameras between there and when I got here
There are five, there are five security cameras in the street outside this club alone
They were looking at you
Yeah, yeah, yeah
You don't have to watch, you don't have to watch Big Brother on TV
You're living it right now!
Big Brother now!
You're not even safe in your own homes
How, when was the last time any one of you
Bought a PC or a Macintosh
And bought one of those rinky dinky little webcams
And you stick it on the top of your PC and you think this is so fucking cool!
One day you will not be allowed to switch that camera off
They're watching you now
And you don't even know it
That's the truth
Praise Bob!
The trick is to get
The trick is to get into the system
But not trying to change it, no
Trying to use it
They have made it so complicated
That they can't control it anymore
So the conspiracy has lost control over their own system, man
You go in there, you find the right, not...
How would I say it?
The small places, you know, the dark corners
And you just get into the dark corners
And you find things, you know, and you do things
And then everything goes right, man
You follow the path of less resistance, you know, but...
Just from dark corner to dark corner
Getting deeper into the system
And then you prey on them, you know
They are hunting for you, they hate you
But you prey on them and they don't even know it!
It's very good!
It's...
It's worth it, I mean...
I think you have the answer, yeah
That's the way I do live, actually, yeah
Yeah, you're right, that's the way I live my life, yeah
Yeah, that's the...
They try to make you feel bad, you know
And they make you angry
And you grow this anger inside, you know
And each time they make your anger grow
From the far reaches of the universe
They think they are winning
But that's wrong
Because you use that anger
And the next time you have to do something
You use that anger to get on
And keep on fighting more
You know, and the most...
Fuck you
The more they fuck you
The more you fuck back, you know
Yeah, but I prefer to take their shit
And turn it into something good, you know
That's what I like to do
Yeah
I just take their shit
And fucking feed it back to them
Yeah
And fucking...
And they don't even know it
Yeah
And they like it
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about
But I didn't have the words
But if you show them that it's shit
They don't want it
But if you feed it to them
They taste it and they go
Oh, we like this shit
This shit's nice
Yeah
But if you tell them that you're doing that
It doesn't work
So Bob is the subgenius
Because he's the guy that understands the way it works
Under the covers
Under the...
Underground
I'll tell you what man
Fuck Bob
Yeah
Fuck off that bus
Look, what a bastard
I hate you
You're not just tapping into their subconscious
You're just getting into their hormones
You know, into the biological level
You just speak to them and you create
What you want them to believe
Man, those pigs are shit
But they're good shit
And their money's green
Yeah
Their money is green
Oh yes
If you don't love Bob
He'll Bob you out
As was bespoken by my actual daughter Sivit Stang
That's not who we were listening to
That was Reverend Slita
From Italy
At the Euro Devival
But my daughter Sivit Stang
Is now her next here
At a family event called X Day Eve
On X Day
I'll see the saucers coming
And all I need is Bob and me
Forever and forever
But until
I spend my thirty bucks
I'm just running to myself
And not too far
And although
I know that I am screwed
Still I say
There's a day of pain
I love Bob
But when the rapture's over
He'll be gone
The earth will be in ruins
Without him
The world around me changes
The conspiracy is everywhere
The malls are full of pink boys
I love Bob
But every day
I don't spend
That thirty bucks
I'm only just pretending
But I'm not sure
Without me
Bob's world will go on burning
Our next year Bob will have this light
That I'll never know
I love Bob
But only
On my own
I'll find myself
Now don't get us wrong
God loves you
God really does love you
But Bob
Bob wants you
God loves you
But old Bobby
Old Bobby wants you
And he's gonna find you friends
You can't find yourself
You think you're gonna find yourself better than Bob can
Are you that prideful
I tell you what friends
I'll find myself
When they pry me out of my pocket
my cold dead fingers.
So follow that
Pied
Piper
out of Conditch
to glorious
Dobstown, friends. But you can't
just talk about it like I'm doing
up here. You have to do it.
You have to actually do it. You can't be a chicken
shit. So build your own ship
and evacuate
or vacate the
evacuation chamber, goddammit.
This church
of the subgenius, sure it's a joke
sometimes, but why can't it
also be the one true religion?
This is the divinity
school of hard knocks
my friends, and it actually
is as real as it gets.
As Dr.
Legume said, we
will lead this damn nation
to damnation.
And as
Princess We Are Doe
said, we are
good
but we're our own
brand of good.
So friends, in closing
I want to get off here and get
some slack myself. I have
refrained from taking any
drugs until five minutes
from now. But in closing
I want to reiterate, friends
when you need
slack, you make your
own slack. Make your own
slack and build your own ship.
Bob Dobbs is not the
answer and neither is Bob Dobbs.
There is anything else.
You must learn
to think for yourself.
Only Bob can show
you how. And friends,
the last thing, the most important
thing of all, fuck them
if they can't take
a joke.
And praise Bob
the I.I.I.I.
Happy
X Day. Bob
bless y'all. If I don't see
you no more in this world, I'll meet
you on the next one. And don't
be late.
Maybelline,
why can't you be true?
Oh, maybelline,
You don't start back doing the things
you used to do.
Woo!
Choose now, our time is
here.
It's my time.
I've taken my place on a new
frontier.
I look at my
hands and I never look back.
A bid adieu and
close the
hatch
That should be me.
Floating in space
on your TV screen,
with practices
That's your baby
New American dream
Two weeks in the sea of tranquility
And consideration of whatever available evidence, however puzzling,
we too, beholding the Dobbshead alone,
putting aside, for the first time,
being all vulgar hillbilly superstitions
about grotesque, improbable childhood miracles
or multiple sexual organs in unusual places,
can infer, like Baron Cuvier,
all that we need to know,
ex-engry people,
from the evidence,
that simply by staring intently
we are waiting for the end of the world.
The exes to come in there,
going to land,
they're going to take us away
and treat you bad.
When we leave are the dust and the
the electronic rays from the back of our spaceship
to fry almost everyone who's left
and your pain will feel like
nothing but laughter to us
while we fly through the heavens
and lift our hearts in joyous wonderment.
The name of God
begins playing out in the world.
The sex gods,
the sex goddesses,
and the sex goddesses.
The sex goddesses.
That's where I'm going to be,
is hanging out at the harem of the sex goddesses
with the squids.
You and about five million other guys.
Yeah, but I got first in line.
You know, they got,
a long time ago,
when they gave out numbers
for who was going to be in line,
I got picked number one.
I got number one.
Let's get started.
The end of the world has begun.
We can see the lights off in the distance.
Where you are, you are.
I mean, in the line.
We can see the lights of the,
now some people might say it's the rising sun,
while others have said
it's nothing but competing solar flares
and gigantic, hideous hydrogen bomb explosions.
Gigantodons and
happening simultaneously
shall populate our future world.
uninterruptedly.
They shall interrupt our lives.
Continuously.
But I must interrupt with this important message, friends,
on how to get to the real life.
Theians won't make it on time.
I am bones.
The whole universe lies below.
And Elon Musk won't discover his results
For me to built a beautiful dream
Klaus.
The moon inventes the gathering of emanations with Irakshara.
Where it's an enormous earthquake.
Using petroleum at its groes.
That's stang at subgenius.com
if you want to email me or e-mail me.
Friends, in the background, this is DK Jones,
great instrumental, Hirosaki, praise Bob.
Friends, we've got to get off this world.
We could get rich.
Rich, rich beyond our wildest dreams, my friends,
if we use the power of the X's.
We could spend the money to take the gold,
to use the wretches.
Friends, Bob could bring you asteroids
that are flying mountains of stainless steel
and precious metals like gold and platinum.
Or they could be balls of supercarbon
and complex organics that could get you so high.
A whole asteroid.
A whole asteroid all to yourself
for only $30, my friend.
Dobs can make your veins like chicken wire.
It can make your balls like those cobalt balls
in that bomb there.
Do you realize that one single Dobs-type
near-Earth object would be worth trillions
in today's market?
It would be so valuable, it would change the market itself.
This is your chance to get on the ground floor
of a lucrative old cult.
Now, while rates are still low.
Now, now, now.
Still, still, only 10 cents.
And one little sniff of that little mutated ball
will make you so high
that you will never, ever, ever, ever come down.
One molecule from the ash of Bob's pipe
in the same room as you
will make you so high
that you can never imagine coming down.
One glance from the beautiful eyes
of the beautiful,
Bob totally frees an enlightened spirit
and makes Jizzle go in the pants.
The perfect love of Bob is the essence of the isness
of the personification of this universe
and all the other universes all taken as a whole
in one perfection.
That is like one atom of Bob's brain
for one nanosecond.
Think!
If you could be part of his wallet.
Bob will spay your parents.
He will make you fly like a mosquito.
He will build a tiny fort
for within which you and your friends
can pretend to live
or at least look at for a period of three minutes.
God is...
God is incapable of...
Bob's is more...
He had never...
He...
He will make you free.
He will let you pee.
To truly, truly let go
and really pee
like you've never, ever peed before.
This is what Dobbs could bring you.
He loves you so much.
You won't just make water.
You're going to be making hydrogen and oxygen
that you can actually resell
at a very, very large margin of profit.
Bob's not going to...
Bob's not going to let you go out there in the wind
like one of those crazy rain sisters
or complete the puke monster yourself.
No, you've got to...
His bladder is so full of love.
For you.
And that power.
That...
Power.
Of that magic thing.
You know what Bob has?
He has.
He has that magic thing.
He has it.
It's called...
What's it?
Slash.
Not sloth.
Don't you need more slack, my friend?
Get off my head, you slacker.
I'm tired of looking at you.
Look.
You're not the only guy in this foxhole.
The Jerrys are coming.
I travel in the dark.
Thanks you for your tiny spark.