OOOOOOOH
The subgenius hour of
SWORD
Listen up, captain told me that there might be some atmospheric disturbance over the next couple of days
What does that mean?
Can you interfere with the radio transmission?
Can you read me?
Are you there? Hello?
What we've got here is a failure to communicate
The subgenius hour of SWORD
And I don't like it any more than you, ma'am
My CP is intact
After a few minutes, Bob joined us
Oh no
Bob
Why did you shut up?
Uh, Bob
The bottle of...
The bottle of whiskey disappeared
Stop it! Stop it!
Haven't you done enough?
Enough what?
What?
Thank you
When he gets like this, I just gentle him along
He's sick
He wasn't always like that
Enough
I don't know what
What?
I don't know
Just keep it inside
I don't know what you're talking about
He's
What?
Bob
Is short
And full of blisters
There's a fellow down in Texas
They say his name is Bob
He tells me I should slap Bob
Thank you
I should quit my job
Well I am a simple genius
And I must have my slack
If I don't live forever
I get my money back
They said that on July 5th
Of 1998
The earth would meet destruction
Suffer a deadly fate
That day was long away
Now it is come and gone
There was no fire from heaven
And this old world rose on
Well I am a simple genius
And I must have my slack
If I don't live forever
I get my money back
Poor Stang was made to suffer
A terrible disgrace
Of such humiliation
He feared to show his face
Now Bob may be laughing
Because we are such chumps
But that is no reason
To be down in the dumps
It'll all still happen
No need to curse or frown
They got all the right numbers
Just got them upside down
Well I am a simple genius
And I must have my slack
If I don't live forever
I get my money back
So if I can't live forever
Then I must have my slack
But that is no reason
To be down in the dumps
No need to curse or frown
No need to curse and frown
There is Bob on your shoulder
Let's praise him
Tonight all rise
There is Bob on your shoulder
Let's praise him
Tonight all rise
There is Bob on your shoulder
Let's praise him
We are frozen by dry forces
There is no space
You are bringing a storm
There is Bob on your shoulder
Let's praise him
Tonight all rise
There is Bob on your shoulder
Parra is dead.
Evening.
Was Mrs. Paradine?
Yes, sir.
So?
No, sir.
Hmm.
Is that correct?
Yes, sir.
Hey, Bob.
Bob, Bob.
Yeah, Bob.
Hey, Bob.
Oh, kiss my ass.
Hi, Bob.
Bye, Bob.
Bob.
Hello, Bob.
Oh, there you go again.
That's cute, Bob, okay?
Bob.
Yeah, Bob.
Hello, Bob.
Open up your eyes to what's going on.
Goodbye, Bob.
Hey, Bob.
How you doing?
Bob.
Hi, Bob.
Hey, Bob.
Yeah, Bob.
Hi, Bob.
How you doing there, brother Bob?
Just a bunch of brats.
Oh, my God.
You are the only one walking on all these streets with a gun.
Hey lip and something hit chair.
Oh, yeah, Bob.
Do you want to stop eating?
Hey, Bob.
Hold your breath.
The
The Psychoskeletons did that unusual instrumental, friends.
Accent on the mental.
And now we're going back to that Puzzling Evidence show with Puzzling Evidence and Dr. Howell discussing the holy subject of monsters.
And Dr. Philo U. Drummond, who grapples with an existential problem concerning his subgenius film festival.
There they are now.
What's the best way to get more mules?
Come on, sir. This mule looks like it's going to be time to...
That mule is...
That's not the mule. That's the...
That's not a Godzilla, but it's the female horse and that male donkey.
Haw, hee, haw, sir.
Oh, they're coming through now.
Oh, there they are.
Well, that was actually sort of anticlimax and relief.
We're actually going to see a huge monster.
Here's a huge monster.
I'm afraid.
A flaming token.
Good Lord.
And bullets don't seem to stop the thing.
That was Megagiris.
Uh-oh, wings humming.
Yeah.
See, once we get one monster...
Oh, sorry, two roars.
Yeah, they come back.
Boy, the stereo is really good.
Now wings humming.
It's like it's right behind me.
They come back.
They do come back?
Oh, there it goes.
Those are the big wings.
Oh, but there they go.
Megagiris.
Spirogyrus, yes.
Flying off over the horizon.
No wonder.
It does seem to get yanked pretty fast.
On YouTube.
Maybe not.
What's that?
Toho Films.
Toho Films, too?
Thank heavens.
There'd be too many of them up.
Oh, no kidding.
But does that mean there's no...
It's not like they're not easy enough to get.
War of the Gargantuas?
Okay, well, maybe I'm just imagining this all.
Is War of the Gargantuas up there?
I thought I saw it there once.
Just pretend.
I was just looking through, and the name War of the Gargantuas popped out at me.
I didn't actually pursue it and watch the clip.
I'm having trouble.
I'm having trouble trying to fill my Subgenius Film Fest theme version genre.
The theme park of the future.
Right, it's the zombie subgenre.
The world of the future.
And I'm trying to find a TV show that had zombies in it, so I need that to fill out the theme.
There must be a...
I found a cartoon that had zombies.
There must be one of them.
I've got a film with zombies in it that you've never...
A cartoon?
No, it's not.
It's a low-budge, badly made, cheap film.
But it is...
It does have zombies.
Zombies walking along that you can certainly use.
See, that was the thing.
I came up with a theme formula for the Subgenius Film Fest home theme version.
I'm afraid the entire zombie thing is rather played out.
Well, no, but this was the...
Or visited, as they call it.
It doesn't have to do with...
Too much.
The zombie's just one of any number of themes you can choose, of subgenres of movies.
The key to this whole thing working correctly is that you have to have...
The movie night is designed around...
Having a cartoon, a TV series, and a feature film all in the same evening, but they all carry the same theme.
So if you've got a Western cartoon, a Western TV series, and a Western feature, then you're going to have your heist movie cartoon, your heist movie TV series, and your heist movie feature.
Now I'm having trouble with the zombie subgenre.
I found a zombie cartoon show, believe it or not.
There was a zombie...
Zombie is one of the characters.
I'm having trouble finding a zombie TV series, but there's plenty of zombie feature films.
We can any number, like what you're referring to, those lesser well-known, really poor quality zombie films, all the way up to George Romero's biggest high-budget zombie movies.
The last one that came out, Diary of the Dead, I thought was exceptionally good.
Yeah, I did.
I had that one, actually, and it was good.
I was able to get back to the...
I have a...
I've seen that.
...feeling of the original movie.
Right.
After all these variations have been coming out over the years.
And some of them were just parodies of themselves, you know.
They weren't really...
They were just making a mockery of the whole concept of zombies.
As if you could make a mockery of something as classic as that.
They've been making zombies since...
Zombie movies have been so popular for...
Since the 40s.
Yes, I've got one with Man Tan more like a...
King of the Zombies.
Yeah, that's a...
That one is great.
Man Tan Morgan saves that whole movie.
But did you ever see I Walked with a Zombie?
I think I have seen that one.
So that was the whole point with the Subgenius Film Fest,
is take advantage of a collection by forcing everything into this format
that you would have cartoons short and feature.
Boy, I'd be entirely for it.
In fact...
If there was only some way to work a newsreel into that.
Yeah.
Now, they have newsreels, but it's very hard for newsreels to follow the theme.
We could say we're going to eschew the theme for the newsreel
because the format needs a newsreel,
even if the newsreel chosen doesn't represent the subgenre
that's trying to follow the theme format for that evening.
You know, I mean, we're going to have to have the whole submarine genre,
the Robin Hood genre.
Well, there are too many of them, but there are some good ones.
You've got to have the Robin Hood genre, you know, the spy genre.
That sounds like Phineas Narcos.
It is.
He's playing his new hit, Fad World.
Streaming Outland.
It's just a showstopper, man.
It is.
Well, the show is paying off.
He's paying homage by not walking over his creative...
This cover is great.
I feel like someone stepped on my grave.
That's great.
A little shiver will have run for me.
I think I bought this one time because of that cover.
I bought it because they had their song I played earlier at the beginning of the show,
The Sex Made Me Stupid.
The video is pretty funny.
I saw it.
It was a short one.
No, this isn't the one I thought it was.
Ah, that melancholy Phineas.
Oof.
Oh.
Now, we need the callers to call in and fill out their work sheets.
We're going to have to push off the evaluation form.
Please rate this show with a one to four scale.
Give us a call at...
...in the 510 area code.
That's 848...
...and we'll be right here to answer your questions and to make sure that if you...
Please bring your forms with you.
...any place you have them.
That was a mistake.
I shouldn't have done that.
I should have done that better.
It's not what I intended.
My words got all offended.
Another one.
Hi, let me help you select the information numbers.
They all love me, the thing they don't know me
I should have been there, but instead I am here
One second of stupidity, then years of recovery
Thanks for the time, but now I feel as blind
I didn't know what to do, and I couldn't ask you
I was stupid, I was lame, you wouldn't think I had a brain
I didn't get gas, now my ass is black
That was a mistake, that was a mistake
That was a mistake, Condoleezza Rice
Condoleezza Rice, that was a mistake
Little Theodore did that, friends.
Can you believe your ears?
He's real, he's alive.
But yes, the great Reverend Little Theodore has a new album out
and even some videos, and you can learn more
of this great architect of fear at littletheodore.com
Theodore being spelled F.
Y-O-D-O-R, Fy-O-D-E-R
He is truly unbelievable, and yet I believe in him.
And now, puzzling evidence with Reverend Phineas Narco
of nationalcynical.com, calling in.
It's one of the few songs that the Phineas Narco guy
hasn't made fun of.
Yeah, Phineas Narco.
I can't believe how he just makes fun of all these
He just laughs at the culture like it's a big joke.
He laughs at our culture.
He just thinks the culture's a joke.
I think so.
I think we're going to have a show where everyone talks at once.
Still, I'm down.
Okay, you should.
No, we already beat you to that.
You have to do a parody of a show where everybody talks at once.
Then we'll do a spoof of the parody and then a sequel.
And then a making of the spoof of the parody.
And then it'll turn out to be this big success.
You'll make the movie make all the money.
And then, of course, the watching of the making of the spoof.
And we'll be like, I hear everybody.
And then we were the first guys to do where everybody talks at once.
The director's cut.
The commentary of the watching of the making of the spoof of the sequel.
Everybody talks at once.
And then we'll adapt it for Broadway.
And then we'll have a direct-to-DVD version.
And then we'll convert it back to a movie.
And then we'll bootleg it and we'll put it on YouTube.
I don't talk to people that go to movies with their dad.
I'm going to see Shrek 4 with him.
You mean the director's abdomen?
The director's abdomen?
Yeah.
Maybe he took it a little bit.
The director's abs.
Yeah, the director's cut.
That's hot.
Yeah.
That's the new...
It's like 270 a pound, though.
The director's...
Yeah, the director's...
Director's choice cut.
Well, they did have a doctor on the set.
The director's knee cut.
It's sand.
Director's stamped UST.
Have you seen my Filipino flyers?
Yeah, I know where they start out with the Filipino flyers in the director's cut.
That's the way it starts.
In the director...
At first, they start with a...
Just like in the old days, they start with a movie poster.
And if they can get anybody chomping at the movie poster, they make a trailer.
Really?
Yeah.
I don't know.
The eyeball.
Yeah.
And if the trailer works...
You remember eyeball?
Yeah.
Eyeball.
Did you see eyeball?
It is what you think it is.
Right.
That's the slogan.
It is...
No, the slogan was, it's about just what you think it's about.
I'm still trying to figure that out.
Do you remember The Crawling Eye?
Yeah.
I've got that in my collection.
You have The Crawling Eye.
VHS tapes.
Yes.
Yeah.
I have the making fun of that movie.
The making of The Crawling Eye.
Oh, in the MST3K.
The Crawling Eye.
Yeah.
Mistakes.
So they gave that their treatment, huh?
Yeah.
The Crawling Eye they didn't like?
Yes.
And Zontar.
Man of Planets.
Zontar was probably much better in the Mystery Science Theater treatment.
What was that movie with the giant spider that was saying, my home, my home as it crawled
back to its cave?
That was it crawled back to its home.
That is, of course, Earth versus Moon.
Earth versus the spider.
Oh, Earth versus the spider, yeah.
My home.
You told me to go home and I'm going home to my home.
I'm on my way home.
Hey, who was it who had the bright idea of having a show with everybody talking at the
same time?
I don't know.
Was that, was that puzzling evidence?
Mobius rectus.
Mobius rectus in procter.
Underneath the floorboards.
Mobius rectum.
Yeah, I wish you wouldn't say that on the air.
The body beneath the floorboards.
Because everything comes true if you say that.
So, what was that movie?
The body beneath the floorboards.
But what do you have to come visit the show?
Well, I, I, I got a laptop.
I can come up and, you know, we can, we can make some sounds.
You should do that sometime.
Yeah.
We always have an open, an open...
Mix-and-mold the mystic mold...
Studio here.
Well, they're having Santa May in downtown San Jose.
Is that right?
And somewhere...
And, uh...
Santa May show up, right?
Wait, wait, wait.
What are you doing?
Santa may show up?
So there's going to be lots of furries.
Or daisy may.
Furries.
Walking around here.
Flushy world.
Yeah.
So where is that?
Just all over town?
Yeah, it's at the convention center.
Big convention center.
What is it now?
Fanimay Con, I think it's called.
Anime?
Fanimay.
You get it now?
They like Fanimay loans.
You're going to get a loan from Fanimay.
You'll be alone, all right?
There'll be a loan there.
No, it'll be wild.
You'll be alone with a lot of people.
Yeah, that would be good.
When is that, this weekend?
Yes.
That's not the strong end.
But I'll come up to the show, you know, and do a show.
That's why they're dreary music.
When are you having a long show?
A Frank Belknap long show or a Max Freedom long show?
That would be hard to know.
And you're right.
It would be better to drive that far when you know you have a long show.
Yes.
When you're drunk.
Those are sort of serendipitous in terms of the puzzling evidence acquisition aspect.
You confess your car to the man who wears the star in your mind.
And that was true for you, Billy Bob, growing up?
It was sort of a combo of Stones and Monkeys and Buck Owens?
I just liked baseball when I was a kid.
And you almost became a professional baseball player, right?
I don't know.
Maybe.
But you didn't love music when you were a kid?
I subscribed to a magazine called Famous Monsters of Filmland,
which the publisher was a guy named Forrest J. Ackerman who passed away recently.
Do you remember what you were listening to musically when you were a kid?
They had a contest.
They had a contest where you could build your own model.
And it could be like a King Kong or it could be anything from something that you created yourself
to like one of the monsters that was actually in some of the magazines.
It could be Frankenstein all the way to Phantom of the Opera.
And they made these plastic models in those days that you could buy and put together.
But this was like a thing you could create.
You could create your own world of it.
You know, build telephone poles, make the railroad tracks and everything.
And I actually did enter it once.
I didn't win anything.
But I gave it a shot.
But it was a big deal for us kids in those days.
And where does the music fit into that?
Music?
No, it was a monster magazine.
Right, right.
But I'm...
I entered that same contest, friends, and I lost too.
I love that interview.
Classic pink DJ versus natural unsaved subgenius Billy Bob Thornton.
But who is to say who is really the monster?
The man with the beard on top of his head?
Or the man with the mustache on his chin?
Hello?
Yes?
I've seen someone who had a mustache on one side of their face and a beard on the other half.
Somebody says that at one point.
Hello.
You know, you can't say that.
I say hello.
It's certainly obvious.
Yeah, it's right there in the script and one of the characters says it out loud.
Hello?
Like, what?
It's pretty obvious.
You mean that...
No, it's in Star Trek.
It's in the Star Trek film.
Oh, yes.
I wanted to ask you about the new Star Trek movie and what you thought of it.
Yeah, it was great.
I loved it.
And Cracked Magazine has a good article about how the Terminator series makes no sense.
Oh, no.
No.
Yeah.
And they split the whole thing.
It really bums me down.
Yeah, that bums me out.
Why, they really know how to hurt a guy.
Yeah.
Right where it hurts.
Yeah, I really...
You know, that's one thing I always demand of my Hollywood productions, that they must
make perfect sense.
Yeah.
Especially in the time travel movies.
They must always make perfect sense.
Yeah.
They don't make sense.
I mean, it's like when I walk in, you know, usually when I get my ticket, I tell the person
selling me the ticket that if this movie doesn't make sense, I'm going to come get my money
back.
I actually learned my...
Yeah.
You have to argue with them about certain plot points.
Right.
And they're always saying, no, you can't say that didn't make sense, sir.
And I said, yes, I can.
I can say anything didn't make sense if I want to.
And it's like, then we get in this philosophical discussion of what does sense even mean, you
know?
Well, you just want to choke the philosophical esophagus with the roughage of knowledge.
We get special comments by etymological specialists from the future.
And then they have to...
Mayfield, D. Hilden.
They come in to tell us what we know already and how well we know it.
They come in and suspend us.
I don't know.
Then we have to fill out the workshop evaluation forms again and rate the instructor and all
that stuff.
It's all like a...
It's a feedback loop.
We can't get out of it.
Fill your heart with love today.
Don't play that game with time.
Don't fill your mouth with chorizo sausage.
Hmm.
But you start talking about this or that, and the next thing you know, everybody knows.
It'll make you stupid.
But the Terminator bloopers are really about to hit you.
It's gotten some bad notices, but it also got an entire page full of quotable blurbs
of glowing notices and people saying, it'll blow you away.
The one thing I notice when anything comes out is that somebody likes it and somebody
doesn't.
Have you ever noticed that?
About things?
Why, yes.
Things happen that some people like them and some people don't.
And there's some people that make a living not liking things.
It's important that...
That audience is listening.
...they don't like it, because if they liked it, then they have to go over to a place where
they don't make as much money.
Yeah, and I was just thinking, too, that no matter who you are, there's always someone
in life that doesn't like you.
Yeah, if you have to put your happiness in someone else's pocket...
In little voices in a box.
You put your happiness in someone else's pocket.
You have to put your happiness in a little tiny speaker where these guys are talking.
And the bigger the world gets, the more there are people that don't like you.
Absolutely.
And then once they find out who you are, and they actually know you for a little while,
then they don't like you even more.
Yeah, but the good thing is that you can go around and take it all personally and, like,
drive yourself into a nervous breakdown.
Right, and then you can get in trouble, drive a car, get road rage, crash into a school
bus full of kids.
I had nothing to do with that.
God, man.
I was nowhere near there.
Yeah.
You could be headed, you could drive into the...
I think the better thing to do would be to drive to the shopping mall until you find
that place that's called Beard Papa.
Then shop to the...
There's a beer...
Oh, there's a Beard Papa right downstairs from me.
Oh, those things should be against the law.
They're horrible.
I mean, you can't even eat those things.
Well, I mean, that's the problem.
I can't even do that.
I don't have any problem eating it.
That's why I think they should be outlawed.
Well, you get them all over your clothes.
You get, like, the cream falls out of the cream puff.
You just better just bury your face in Papa's beard.
Yeah.
Like in a cartoon?
Come on home to Papa.
I thought it was going to be like a human image.
Come rest in the bosom of Abraham.
You know, you like a big beard and you just, like, go and take the food out of the beard
and eat, you know.
Well, I had a friend whose philosophy was if he ever got real hungry, he would just
make beard soup.
Well, there you go.
Just dip his beard in the pot of boiling water.
And then cook it for a little while.
And there was always enough residual food value left.
Not to mention the protein of a few fleas.
The residuals are in.
And now we get to eat.
There are.
And so they think of that change.
Oh, doctor.
The concept was.
Baby.
Bab.
baby.
Jesus rides a Harley Davidson.
Listen listen listen.
We don't need Snape oil salesmen.
You're not getting it.
I'm sick and tired of preachers.
strategically.
Their revelation is their brain dead.
Paul said, but...
Now listen, listen, listen.
Now, I'm not lying. I'm telling you the truth.
I'm angry.
There's nothing in the Bible.
I'm mad.
What do I have to do?
Carnal things.
Evils.
We don't need God.
It's the sin of the church.
Listen again, you little...
There's nothing in the Bible.
What do I have to do?
I'm mad.
I'm mad at God.
That is an abomination.
Carnal things.
I'm angry.
You have no control over me.
You're not getting it.
Jesus Christ did not die on a cross.
State oil salesman.
Money.
Hungry.
Pride.
It's the sin of the church.
Evil spirit.
Your ambition should be self-destruction.
It's another dollar.
Money.
trucule, money.
Now now, I'm not lying.
I'm telling you the truth now.
True.
The anointing.
It's a sin.
Does not allow you to be rude.
The anointing.
Dee.
We..
prostitute the word of God.
Shame on you.
money.
fi rru
Comflow cable
Oh, yes, bud.
Let's get out there
and have a rally for bo-bob.
166 002 002 Crypto Flat Oat Lastish equivalents 402
Is Bob at home? Are there any more at home like you?
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Yeah, hello, Bob.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Norrell Preff got hold of Bob's answer machine tape.
Before that, we heard that killer mix, Jesus Has a Harley, that was by Reverend Cuttlefish.
And before that, Lemur.
Now, more puzzling evidence with Philo, Phineas Dr. Howell, and Ima Sumac.
I have many tales.
Hello, Connor.
Yes, what's Ima Sumac's real name?
What's the email video name?
Ima Sumac.
Oh, her real name was Ima Sumac.
Spelled with a Y, yes.
No, it was A-Tamu.
No, no, no, that internet.
Backward.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, nobody thought of that before.
Amazing.
That's pretty clever, Connor.
That's been...
It's true.
It's been totally debunked.
I grew up with her.
Yeah, I know.
You're old enough.
Yeah, you grew up with her.
Yeah, I know.
But did you date Kirk's mom?
Yeah, did you date Kirk's mom?
Kirk's mom.
That's the important thing.
A real milk, Kirk.
I didn't like Kirk's mom.
Amy Sumac.
Ima Kamis.
Danger, Will Robinson, danger.
Danger.
There's Ima now.
Ah, yeah.
She killed the show.
I like her.
I think she advances the show.
See, no one knows what to say
because we're just listening to this great...
Now someone turned us on this path.
When you mention Ima Sumac pretty soon,
well, that's what's going on here.
Ima Sumac.
Voice of the X-Men.
So where did you guys grow up?
What is it, Mark?
Well, he grew up with Ima Sumac.
I'm trying to do nail polish down at the restaurant.
I like your room.
I'm in the kitchen.
I can't.
There's too much.
Yeah, Bob.
Bob.
Hello, Bob.
Where's Bob?
Hi, Bob.
Bob.
Yeah, Bob.
Hello, Bob, darling.
Bob.
Hi, Bob.
Yes, Bob.
Bob.
Is it Bob?
Yeah, Bob.
Bob.
It ain't worth Jack
If it doesn't give you slack
Could it be
You're on the wrong track
If it doesn't give you slack
If it doesn't give you slack, well maybe you need to change tack.
If it doesn't give you slack, just perhaps you've got it front to back.
If it doesn't give you slack, you need to trust Max.
It ain't worth jack.
If it doesn't give you slack, it ain't worth jack.
If it doesn't give you slack.
Could it be you're on the wrong track?
If it doesn't give you slack, well maybe you need to change tack.
If it doesn't give you slack, just perhaps you've got it front to back.
If it doesn't give you slack.
You need to trust Max.
It ain't worth jack.
If it doesn't give you slack.
If it doesn't give you slack, it ain't worth jack.
Whenever you got.
It's all sweet.
Cause your mind, your spirit and your soul are free.
There's no substitute for slack.
Believe me.
Whenever you've got slack, living's easy.
It ain't worth jack if it doesn't give you slack.
If it doesn't give you slack, it ain't worth jack.
Max Slack of MaxSlack.net did that.
That very song.
Max Slack is a great band name, isn't it?
New bands are starting up all the time and they need names.
Gary suggests we start a new band.
Well, don't say what the band's name is cause that will, you know.
He suggested we call it Blood Blisters.
That song was based on a Cro-Magnon skinning chant.
I always wanted to promote the name Blood Bong.
Blood Bong, I like that.
How about this one?
Lazy Head.
Hmm.
I like Fist Witch.
Dark Wind.
Well, as long as you have plenty of toilet.
That is a good one.
How about Brown Smell?
Well, there you go.
You see, Philo, the irrepressible.
He has fountains, wells of humor which can never be capped.
Can never ever be capped.
Time to introduce Contrary.
Motion into the proceedings.
Even this late in the day.
We still have to have some eye out for parliamentary procedure.
That's right.
I'm going to turn the chair over to the floor.
Now, unless we want to table the motion.
Turn the chair upside down over to the floor.
Or we could shelf the...
Let's just shelf the whole concept.
Oh, I love those old jokes.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's, uh...
We'll put it in the freezer.
We'll come back in a hundred years.
We'll see what's left.
After a hundred years, who will care?
We can one up the flagpole and see the salutes.
Did you see the, uh, that new series on the History Channel about, uh, life after people?
Life after people.
No, I didn't. It didn't interest me at all.
Oh, really?
It shows how the world falls apart after all the people.
What do I care? I'm not going to be there.
That's the point, though. I mean, you get to be there without me.
Maybe you'll be the only one who's left while you get to watch all this stuff.
I don't want to be there without me there.
I mean, what fun would it be if I'm not there?
Uh, well, I don't know.
See, people forget about that. If you're not there, how do you...
What do you care about being there for?
Why don't you just be there?
You know? Well, that'd be the point.
Why don't you just be there instead of going through this convoluted process of imagining what it's like to not be there?
Oh, what about the road? This is about the...
Well, the show shows that, uh...
It's all about the road. That's the point. It's about the road.
Nothing could be better for the world than for the humans to disappear.
But...
The big, bare part is about the road.
I think we're gonna see more movies about...
No.
It all dissolves into gray goo.
Gray goo.
This is where I got my bookmarks come in handy.
Phylo's miracle cure for assholes.
The road appears ever, ever on out from the door where it began.
This elixir has been brought...
You can't say that on the air.
No, you can't.
Oh, yeah. Oh, you can't?
No.
I think you can. That's not one of the regular words.
You can mention elixir or...
No, no.
Elixir.
You can mention, uh, the, uh, the elixir.
Yeah, you can mention the elixir.
Well, what else does he do?
Spirits.
What?
Or gods that used to share this earth with man.
Somewhere. Oh, yeah. The old band name list. There it is.
So old it is new.
Gorgons, hydras, and chimeras.
Everything old is new again.
Again?
Again and again.
And again.
Ghoulies and ghosties and long-legged-y beasties and things that go boom to...
Uh, is it Bob there, please?
Bob?
Bob.
Yes, is it true that you're well-endowed?
Yes, it is.
Bob.
Oh, yes, Bob.
Hey, Bob.
Bob.
Bob, we love you.
Hey, Bob.
I'd like to request free bird.
Bob.
What's the meaning of life?
Yes, Bob?
If you've been institutionalized as many times as I have, there are so many forms
to fill out for these different big vehicles now.
Why don't you win a big car because they know you will go up on the sidewalk and try and
crush old ladies and stuff.
And I personally, I'm tired of paperworking.
That's an American right.
All right, we got Tara...
Of course.
Nowadays, it's all dressed up.
You have to fill out forms to crush an old lady on the sidewalk.
We got Tara.
But then you have to have permission to do something stupid on drugs.
We got one more caller here.
Yes, good evening.
Yes.
Yeah, I just wanted to just add something real quickly here.
I think I drive in the safest vehicle on earth.
The bus?
No, no.
I drive a smart car.
I just never, there are no cell phones allowed in my car.
Yeah, a cell phone free car is definitely a safer car.
I truly believe it's the safest experience.
Smart cars, man, those things are real tough.
I saw somebody not too long ago checking my cell phone.
My dad just bought a new car that's part phone.
It's like a phone car.
It's both things combined.
You put your ear up to the exhaust pipe and you...
See, you may be onto something.
I think the way to bail out GM and Chrysler,
is for Apple to purchase them.
And I think they will end up making the phone car.
And that will save GM and Chrysler.
Do you think if we let you get jobs for our car companies,
that we would be better off?
I was joking, man.
I think we would.
You never know.
It'd be interesting to see some really,
some of the more innovative thinkers in the business world
put in charge of some of these companies.
One American car company, I would say, in the next couple of years.
Oh.
It's like if we bail out the car,
then we have to bail out the bike industry,
and then we have to bail out the foot industry.
We'll have to bail out the entire foot industry.
People won't even be able to walk unless they have government subsidies.
You know what would be really cool?
Where will it end?
I was just going to add that in Stang's father's case,
he just talks to himself in the car and he thinks it's a cell phone car.
He's just...
And he gesticulates wildly and stuff,
and he also thinks it's a VidCam car.
It's just a car.
Yeah.
What's with watching?
What's with watching television in a car?
I still haven't understood that.
Am I behind the scenes?
That's what we call trans-porn-tainment.
And it's commonly in New York.
My friend Bleepo Abernathy reported seeing people driving around
in the streets of New York with hardcore porno
up where their rearview mirror should be.
And those were religious organizations.
Right, yeah, but that's New York City.
I mean, it'll take a couple of years before that kind of behavior filters
to a place like Cleveland.
I think the only thing...
People that should have televisions in their cars
are pizza delivery guys.
They're the only ones that should be allowed to have that.
Oh, my goodness.
That is as if delivery drivers weren't dangerous enough already.
But that's a whole other kettle of fish,
and we just might get into that next week.
I certainly hope you do.
All right, good night.
And I've got to say good night to Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
Reverend Stang, no money, Mark.
I really appreciate your contributions this evening.
We'll have to do this again.
Sorry it wasn't more livid,
but times are desperate,
so we enjoyed being desperate with you.
All right, desperate times call for desperate measures
like WCSB Cleveland.
Which is not the station you're listening to necessarily,
but the one carrying radio synesthesia,
from which that was recorded in 2008
with host Dr. Sinister and callers such as Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
It was prophetic, friends,
like Bob's prophecy of X-Day,
July 5th, when the world ends,
right around the corner.
And if you don't, check out the details at subgenius.com.
If you don't repent, quit your job, and slack off,
then you too will be part of Jehovah's dreadful harvest.
Ah, yes.
Well, um, hmm.
That gives us pause.
Yeah, just hold on there for a while.
Cat's pause.
Cat got your tongue?
Cat eyes?
Cat eyes.
That's the tale of it.
The cat got your tongue.
And I'm the king of the cats.
Well, I'll be up there sometime.
Okay, yeah, come on up.
Yeah, I'll bring a...
Come on up.
We'll bring a bucket of fisher tissues out.
Yeah, a bucket of chicken.
Bucket of phlegm.
No, you can't say that.
You can say bucket of fisher tissues.
A bucket of chicken legs.
And we'll discuss that phlegmish tapestry afterwards.
I said over and over and over
Over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over again
This is gonna be a
Self-genius
Power of
Swag
Whatever, whatever, whatever, whatever
Jealousy, anger, selfishness, rage, whatever
Entering people.
Enter, enter.
They can actually enter and they can actually enter.
Make you make, make you make.
You should do this, you know.
Or why don't you just go sleep with ten guys?
Make some money.
Your ego.
She was.
Dark.
You know, whatever.
You know, pimps.
Go to Africa.
It's actually transmitted disease.
There's tension.
Prostitutes.
Preachers who are on drugs.
Reality.
And I had post-traumatic stress disorder.
How could that be?
Pimp, pimp, pimp.
You have no control.
Pimp, pimp.
What influences thinking?
Everything you do.
Your mind.
Prostitutes and pimps in the pulpit.
They're all over.
You know, we're into emo music.
Where we emote emotional emotions.
Emotions.
And so, my fellow Americans.
Ask not.
How about the celibate satyrs?
That's a good one.
Ask what you can do.
Oh, yeah.
I know it.
There's nothing left anymore.
Wait, you know what's gonna happen?
It's not enough to countermand the flow of time.
You have to change far greater numbers of people acting.
Then you'll be on your show.
Right.
Then we'll have the listening of the maker of the probability.
So, what else?
I mean, is something different?
The listening of the maker means the sound of the pro.
Otherwise, you're bringing up the problem.
playing a
S.E.P.
and his
bargain song
on the show
of K-P.I.
May.
You can just
watch it later
on YouTube.
You'll be the
watching of the
listening of the
making of the
show.
The documentary
of the show.
You know,
Beard Soup is
not a bad band
name either,
but it has to be
like ZZ Top.
Yeah,
you have ZZ Top
and Beard Soup.
Fallen.
Fallen is
suffering.
We had a band
called The Cups.
Did you say
The Cups?
Stalin.
Oh, Stalin.
I thought you said
The Cups.
How about
Fallen?
How'd that happen?
Stalin and The Cups
don't sound
anything alike.
Beats me,
but I said
Beats me.
That's a good
name for a band.
What about
like Double Bills
of bands
like Pink and
Hole?
Yeah,
that'd be good.
Interesting Double
Bills.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
We're going to
work on that one.
Interesting Double
Bills.
I'm going to
do that.
That's a good
one.
To the
gravesite comes
death's great
retinue.
Boy,
you kids today
are the greatest
and I gotta
tell you,
I'm behind
you wonderful
lovable kids
100%.
I don't know
what this
affectation
with Bob
holds.
Bob is
our only
hope.
Bob.
I know
Jesus is
our,
is our
only hope.
But this
song makes
me feel so
sad.
It does.
It always
makes me feel
sad.
I think it's
something about
that particular
choice.
A melodic
structure is
called,
when they
check it
out of the
library,
it's called
sad.
Yeah.
And you
just check it
out of the
sound library
and you
plug it
into your
song.
You put
it in your
iPod.
Okay,
I'm doing
that.
But all
I'm doing
is that
buzzing.
You like
walk around
downtown and
just get
really,
really depressed.
Yeah,
your tears
streaming down
your face.
Depressed,
you're out
enjoying fresh
air on
God's
green earth
without even
looking at
this.
The lights
are changing.
Remember,
the Lord
only in
his will
holds you
up from
being snatched
down into
the flaming
pit of
hell at
any second.
It's just
that the
tears streaming
down your
face.
The blood
streaming down
your face?
No,
the tears.
Because you're
just crying,
crying,
crying.
Yeah,
but the blood
would give you
something to
cry about,
waiting for
the day
that you'll
be in
hell.
Well,
that's true.
You won't
cry.
It might
make you
feel better,
actually.
Bob,
Bob.
Yeah,
I need to
talk to Bob.
Yeah,
Bob.
Hello,
This is
Bob.
Yes,
Bob,
Bob.
Hi,
Yeah,
Bob.
Hey,
Hello,
Bob.
Yes,
Hello,
Bob.
Yeah,
Hello,
Bob.
Yes,
W-A-X-U
W-Z-X-V
I love
and I can't help but think
can't help but think
I want to get involved
probably not substantive
here's what we feel
here's what we think
probably not substantive
moronic
Florida cancelled
the Florida government
oh man
getting all excited
this is spontaneous
Dick Army
Dick Army's face
Dick Army's
Dick Army's the guy
and he is a really
really cool guy
I love him
I've been with him
several times
he's a really
really cool guy
I love it
and so I was there
talking with Dick
and he just got this
grin on his face
Dick
Monokluinski
everything else
I'd be lying
on the floor
in a pool of blood
with my wife Susan
Dick Army
the Dick Army show
40 minutes of Dick Army
wasn't this big
a right wing conspiracy
I got
conspiracy
yeah
oh
think
so hard
I'm very
very bad
very
buddy
my hole
so whatever
parties
I love
Dr. Ballsack
is in here twice
and I don't think
that's right
what's that disease
that makes you
sweat blood
out of the pores
of your skin
oh that's
crucifictophobia
that's
what Jesus did
right
in the garden
of Gethsemane
Ebola
Jesus did
weep blood
and then of course
it was the plague
against which
Prince Prospero
shot himself
up in his castle
Ebola that's what we need
the red death
he didn't just
he sweated blood
because he was
such intense
oh no that's
I sweated blood
when I worked over
those income tax returns
I gotta tell you
how about
the earnest bastards
the earnest
that's a good one
the earnest bastards
marching society
oh from that movie
that's coming out
about the
inglorious bastards
oh yeah
yeah
the Nazi
family
misspelled
it might be a little
violent
they are partisan
fighters
in the woods
against the Wehrmacht
here's one for you
in the last days of the war
elephant's breath
somebody open the window
and for the kiddies
we have
buckets and buckets
of poodle piddle
America's favorite
soft drink
so come on down
at the base
of the drive-in theater
screen
it's kiddy land
people forget about
Bud and Sis
and the duration
of the feature
and the
short subject
while they swing
on the trains
and slide on the slides
and get out of the
twist and twiddle
on the unicorn
merry-go-round
after dark
it's the snack bar
and total immersion
in the
Baptist
tide pool
that's a good one
all six
cheers to a carload
at the
run for
suicide
morning drive-in
theater experience
in the center round
of the air
with Rumble Rama
and
we're still doing shows
somewhere in the world
right now
the moment you think about it
I'm twittering
the show right now
he's not
he tickles
I'm perusing
the webpage
www.quiveringbrain.com
where I can find
downloads of the show
in various forms
links to
even back to
kpfa.org
where the show's
archived for
like two years
two long years
Dr. Philo Drummond
on the puzzling
evidence show there
with Dr. Howell
and Phineas Narco
before that
Norrell Preff
interspersed two or three
times with them
and some lemur
of which there will be more
this is
the hour of slack
from the church
of the subgenius
to learn more
about the church
our upchucking events
and so on
you can check out
subgenius.com
or write
box
Cleveland Heights
Ohio
the music in the background
is by me
and now
the kleptones
sometimes
to tell the day
by the bottle
that you drink
in times when you're alone
all you do is think
I'm a cowboy
on a steel horse
I ride
I'm warning
warning
head on the line
sign
oh
you're out
man
yee
aah
killer
half
sorry about this kids
but stay tuned
we've got some real good
commercials coming right up
text
Hey
How is Dolph
you a dreamer
Chinese
Yeah.
I haven't seen too many around lately.
Things have been tough lately for dreamers.
They say dreaming's dead, and no one does it anymore.
It's not dead, it's just it's been forgotten.
We've moved from our language.
Nobody teaches it, so no one knows it exists.
The dreamer's banished to obscurity.
I'm trying to change all that, and I hope you are too.
By dreaming every day.
The Kleptones, with a K.
And now, Lemur.
The dreamer is supplemented.
The example and inspiration children can first receive.
From their dreams.
The family that prays together.
Prays together.
Hey, Bob.
Bob.
Hello, Bob.
Yeah, Bob.
Bob.
Hello, Bob.