Huh? Order of Saint Benedict? Is that it? The homosexual Belgian monks?
You know, since the speakers aren't pointing at me, I can't understand a word you say.
I'm gonna go sit between the boys.
I can hear fine, I just, most of what my ears pick up,
they don't feel as worth sending to my brain.
Yeah, the car alarm is not worth sending to your brain.
This is Phil Proctor and David Osman of the Firesign Theatre,
and we're enjoying listening to the Hour of Slag.
I'm slacking off myself.
Red, you go. Where shall I go? What shall I do?
Frankly, Mike.
Here, I don't give a...
Some genius.
The power of slag.
What?
Hello?
The Slag Johnson program. The show opens with me.
Doing some deuce you...
Alice, Phil.
Just a minute, Danny.
What's it about?
Mine?
What?
Hmm?
But, um...
Oh.
Oh?
Copy, boy.
Actors, directors, and playwrights have increasingly exploited urban America.
The 2nd and 3rd Bovard Auditorium presents The Truth About Hollywood Culture.
See one of the hip-hop characters dance and sing to sell an evening with tickets and info.
Call Danny67.
What you need is bugs.
The easy way to keep your car looking its best.
If you want to give added protection to the fination, save money on car washings,
you can apply a coat of bugs.
Bugs.
Do not use them.
The use of a coat of bugs is not only a wonderful time and labor saver,
they do a lot of damage to the finish if you don't remove them.
Use either the special Johnson's Autobugs or the regular Household Bugs.
Ask your auto supply store, service station, or bug dealer for a package of Johnson's Bugs.
The easy way to keep your car looking its best.
Your husbands will be more cheerful on dark mornings if you polish their Johnson's.
In fact, I've heard several women say they were glad of a chance to help polish their husbands big or little.
Like all of us, they're glad to be a good husband.
You're glad to help in any way with self-polishing.
In fact, the regular use of rubbing or buffing will make your husband's last five times longer.
It will sparkle like new.
It's a tremendous labor.
But to get results, may I make a helpful suggestion?
Be sure to keep it protected with coat.
Simply apply and let dry.
The lone Tarentato climbed into the canvas-covered chuck wagon, lying on the floor.
What happened?
You've never seen it, Miss June.
You have no idea how large it is.
Bigger.
Is that so bad?
I could show you, but there isn't time, even for that.
Is there any chance?
Yes, I believe so.
But we'll have to make a try anyway.
It looked bloody bad, Timosabe.
Bart.
Right, kid.
Yeah, Bart, right.
Miss June.
Of course.
We can't waste a minute.
Don't you think, June?
I do.
Don't you think, kid?
Well, make sure she's doing it.
Thanks, Miss June.
Easy, big boy.
Adios.
Adios, kid.
And just to set you straight, mister, you ought to know that that was the launcher.
I'm aware.
This is a product of the Launcher.
Launcher Incorporated.
Created and produced by George W. Launcher.
From PR News in Washington, I'm so close to the site of the World Trade Center.
The U.S. government says the Labor Department rose in July by two-tenths of one percent.
Food and automobiles cost more than three percent, suggesting this is PR.
The BBC's Barclays Bank says PR is bad.
According to documents filed in federal court, Barclays was accused of voluntarily removing
tailspins.
from sex authorities and conducted its own extensive PR news in London.
Bad.
There are growing disease outbreaks.
Good.
New York City Mayor Michael Bloomberg is Islamic in Manhattan.
Authorities anxiously swell again, nearly overwhelmed with the Iraqi army.
Meanwhile, in China, at least 1,200 people have ruined cranes and bulldozers.
In California, there is fading hope that more PR news can be located.
I don't want a ride to theok, but under the stars.
Don't give me land, lots of land under starry skies above.
Fence me in.
Don't let me be by myself in the evening breeze.
But I ask you please, don't turn me loose underneath the western skies.
Just fence me in.
I don't want a ride to the...
Where the West commences
I wanna fence me in
Just fence me in
Oh, fence me in
When I get home
And I'm all alone
I get to wondering why
I'm such a lonely man
Lonely guy
I ain't got me no woman
And there's none in the cart
But I got the next best thing
And it's in my backyard
Yee-haw!
I got the sheep out back
Yeah!
And she's mine, all mine
And if she don't care
I sneaks up from behind
Yee-haw!
Oh, yo, yo, yo
Oh, survey, oh, oh Interesting
She's hot for that
She's Cruz, the UP
For Elemental
Oh,戰
Uuuh!
The pride that caused Satan to be flung, spitting and sparking out of heaven.
Him the almighty power hurled headlong, flaming from the ethereal sky,
with hideous ruin and combustion, down to bottomless perdition.
There to dwell in adamantine chains and penal fire.
Life without Bob.
How can anyone stand it?
Hello, Doctor.
How are you?
Did you ever hear of a man named Bob?
No, I don't think so. It's an uncommon name.
It became very commonly known.
He mutated and spread with devastating speed among human beings.
I'm planning a group that will attack Bob.
But surely, without Bob, that would be the end of everything.
Everything would collapse.
There was chaos for a time.
How could this possibly happen?
Just an accident.
A piece of sandwich that produced unexpected cake and much starvation.
Shall we begin again?
From the beginning.
Yes.
Hello, Doctor.
How are you?
Did you ever hear of a man named Bob?
No, normal woman would.
Oh, no.
How about a drink?
Oh, thank God.
I happen to have a fifth of very medicinal scotch.
The way it looks, when we learn the proper dosage, this could be very effective.
I hope not.
Suppose there really were a Bob.
Well?
Why don't you just kill me?
Yes.
Pleasure time!
Right there on the desk.
Could be wasted with a fire.
What does that mean?
She fell down faster than Mr. Quaid.
The fire-th permitirley deceive and work away.
Oh, I almost got the 150g doll for trial that made me fall to court law.
You know, I was herbivores.
The Graham Jesus people were able to create an exorcism machine.
That void of Lrier
in the amoatég
num
Thousands every day in this country seek death
Death is annihilation
Have the courage to take your own life
Death is nothing but a deep dreamless sleep
That puts an end to all earthly troubles and trials
Escape from the burdens of life
Curse God and die
Your life is so messed up
Have the courage to take your own life
Thousands every day in this country seek death
Death is annihilation
Have the courage to take your own life
Curse God
And die
Curse God and die
Your life is so messed up
Thousands every day in this country seek death
It is appointed unto men once to die
Threatening death
Man desires death
Curse God and die
I'll
show you how we're using Bob to connect people to the right resources.
Let me show you around and more.
I'll use modified Bob.
Let me show you.
I clicked next.
I selected Bob.
Further down on drop down, I can select Bob.
I can also view and change Bob.
Now let's close our library and return to our program.
Program.
Bob.
A. Cook.
Pamphlet.
A. Doc.
Bullshit.
Let's stop smoking these pies.
Bob.
A. Cook.
Pamphlet.
A. Doc.
Bob.
A. Cook.
Pamphlet.
A. Doc.
Bob.
A. Cook.
Pamphlet.
Ah.
A cool pamphlet.
Friends, this little bit in the background right now is by Reverend Morgan Gutendag.
Before that we heard a little shortcut by Norell Preff.
And the song Curse God and Die was by Reverend Hanson.
Oh.
Yeah.
Hazel of the Windmills, who also did several of the collages earlier,
such as the one about polishing your husband with the Johnson.
However, the other Johnson collage, Johnson Bugs and Wax Johnson Program,
and the opening was by Lee Murr.
And the song, I Got the Sheep Out Back, that's the Rudy Schwartz project.
Correct?
You were in love with Bob.
Yeah.
Love was Bob.
We all were.
Yes, he was Bob.
I had to lie there in his cover.
Lie there in cover.
And cover.
Frankly, I was in no mood for golf.
It was a good deal for Bob, too.
He knew that.
Hi.
I'd appreciate dropping the subject of Bob once and for all.
Got a cigarette?
Bob.
Baber's prowl.
Thank you.
Yes.
The Devo's.
And they'll be in town.
It's a little bit
Virtually.
At the devotional this weekend, I feel I can mention that.
Y'all are welcome.
That's at the Beachland Ballroom on August 28th,
which will probably be in the past and another galaxy far, far away
for the people who hear the show outside of this studio.
From far, far away.
At WCSB Cleveland.
Because we get shown and played elsewhere.
But those that live around these parts could also hear Princess Wiardo
singing with revelry on that same day, Saturday the 28th,
at Pagan Pride Day in Bedford Public Square.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
That's Pagan Release Day.
When they let all the pagans out of the box for one hour
to listen to the show.
Yes, we come climbing out.
The Vicki Ganger and Revelry.
Sorry, Victoria.
Oh, this music in the background, for future reference,
it'll be on for a while, is also by the great Rudy Schwartz Project,
our friend Reverend Joe Newman, from a re-release of an ancient set of material.
Okay.
And what have we here?
Would we then find this man?
This wad.
Oh, the wad is, yes, the wad is, and the worm have arrived.
Wad?
The wad.
A big wad, a lonesome cowboy Dave.
What are you doing here, man?
Well, I'm just...
I was just about to say it's not the word of Bob,
it's the wad of Bob,
but I decided to leave that behind in favor of something a little bit more erudite.
I think people should all join their hands and feet right now
and lift their eyes, you know,
if they can get them out of the sockets and stuff like that, skyward,
and forget this idea of Bob, briefly.
Because it is an encumbrance upon the psyche.
Oh, I don't know.
Some people find it liberating,
at least for the first five or so.
For six years.
But then, of course, we urge them to kill Bob in their mind.
We've had some problems with them literally physically killing J.R. Bob Dobbs.
It's kind of a bummer, but...
But what, pray tell, would you have us look to, Dave?
Yeah, who's better than Bob, man?
I mean, you've got to have a short-duration personal saver.
Oh, I suppose we should worship lonesome cowboy Dave.
Yes, spit it out, spit it out.
Praise Dave, praise Dave.
I don't think there's anything better than Bob.
And frankly, I don't think there's anything worse.
So that about says it.
I don't want to be either better or worse than Bob.
And I choose to sit at his feet when they don't smell too bad.
Oh, God, right.
Yeah, as if you get to choose when you sit at the feet of Bob
or when they're going to smell.
I didn't say I chewed the smelly feet of Bob.
Some people pay extra when he's that way.
Yeah.
I could see how the military establishment complex would pay for Bob's smelly feet.
Yeah, when he's that way down there, a lot of people get excited.
Well, when he's that way down there, a lot of strange things happen.
And some of them are really wonderful and some of them are quite putrid.
And some are like this radio show and all the other subgenius radio shows,
all three or four of them.
That we know of.
Well, but two of them, three of them have been on the air forever.
Ever and ever and ever.
Reverend Susie the Flusie Show in Atlanta and WREK,
that's been on for not quite ever, but almost forever.
But nigh on to ever.
Yeah, nigh on.
The beginning of the early days of the golden years of radio,
the Susie the Flusie Show has been on WREK.
Right after Marconi.
And also...
Puzzling evidence.
It goes back to the early days of, I think on Saturday night...
It was originally done as digital smoke signals,
which took a long time to get a two-hour show out.
Oh, yeah.
But they started on the actual radio in June of 1982.
I know that because I was there.
Well, you should have said actually started on the radio, not the actual radio,
because it wasn't really an actual radio.
It was a kind of a must-plus radio.
A radio that...
It did strange things.
But for a long time, they did go up against the King Biscuit Hour, NBC, The Whistler,
some of those old shows.
Rump Limbaugh.
Well, yeah, they still went up against Rump Limbaugh, brusquely.
Shudder.
Yeah, that is an ill prescription, provided you need one.
Well...
Dave, I bet you haven't heard about...
The New York City...
Devival.
Coming up...
Are you going to NY?
October 9th.
Yes, we're going to actually drive there.
We're going to take several days and drive to New York City.
Well, if you're...
The big city.
And for...
You know who's putting that on?
Reverend Back It On Up and Reverend Sifu and Reverend Jimbo.
Oh, that's exciting.
More than you know, as they describe it here,
this music is not really...
Well, here, I'll do it this way.
Well, it sounds like what you're going to be feeling like
after a long night in New York City.
That's why we call them devivals and not revivals,
because they're all devilish.
Anyway, it says here,
fire and brimstone,
screamo rock stars,
the fascinating Fat Man D,
and Reverend Ivan Stang will be preaching to you,
and you will feel like you are somebody
when he verbally ejaculates right into your face.
He's going to bust a spiritual nut right in your face.
See the New York clincher in him screaming about God knows what.
Feel the power of the legendary Pope Black.
Smell Pope Sinfaltimus Ex Mortis,
but don't eat anything he hands you.
Here, fat free, make lots of noise.
Hobnob with real subgenius celebrities
like Modemac, confirmed sex god,
and DJ 2B will play something called dubstep,
which you may have heard him talk about.
Behold!
As Reverend Bleepo Abernathy,
the suavest subgenius ever to come out of the big city,
rants.
See before New York gets blown off the map.
Oh, and also there'll be a marriage.
A real live pair of subgeniuses
will marry the holy living beep out of each other,
and you will get to throw beep at them.
We choose the beep.
Don't throw it too hard.
And that is...
Oh, it says here,
wear the most ridiculous thing you own
because this is high society,
and you'll want to look beautiful in the photos.
Someday you'll be dead,
and your greatest regret will be a plague
on your everlasting soul.
Don't let it be that you totally beeped up
and failed to attend this once-in-a-lifetime event.
Be there or G-F-Y.
And this will be within launching distance
of the Ground Zero Mostel
that they're so excited about.
In New York, you know,
that everybody in Arizona is so concerned about,
and everyone all over the rest of the country
is so concerned about.
They don't want to just let a neighborhood
do whatever the heck they want, no.
It doesn't work that way.
This is America.
We have freedom of Christian religion in this country.
It says so right in the Bible.
Four score and seven years ago,
the right to bear arms.
That's John 614 in the Bible,
the Holy Christian Bible.
Right to bear arms.
It says something like that.
I know because I've read that
on a Yahoo comment that my buddy posted
and on the pasties that his girlfriend had.
So he put pasties on his girlfriend's pasties
to be a pasty?
No, that's where the Bible was apparently quoted from.
Well, that's the problem with your average,
everyday 400-pound Bible.
It wants to rule.
It wants to push you around
and make you eat the kind of sandwiches you don't like.
That's number one.
And number two, you say,
well, you can practice whichever religion you freedom.
And who wants to rehearse every day?
I mean, I know from being in bands every year,
I mean, many years,
that you needlessly have to rehearse
when you don't have to.
And who wants to do that
when you're worshiping some encumbrance
that you might wear around your neck?
Wait a minute.
Rehear?
What does that word mean?
Rehearse?
Huh?
I don't know.
I was never in one of your yearly annual bands.
Rocks and what do they call those?
Stars.
Rock stars.
Bands with rocks in?
No, no, no.
Like Ayers Rocks.
Yeah, that's also a band too.
Are you making fun of me again?
Trying to.
As desperately as I can.
But it just doesn't,
it seems to roll off your back like a platypus.
Of course, you're used to it.
You're going to be speaking in front of a bunch of irate,
besotted, half-witted New Yorkers.
Oh, not for long.
With the lineup, they've got enough people.
Oh, I didn't mention that Priestess Pisces will be there.
I wouldn't be surprised if Dr. Legume shows up.
It's kind of an East Coast show then.
I mean, from all parts, Philly and stuff too.
Well, we'll see.
We'll see.
Oh, and there's some, the singing occultist, Lon DeKette,
if that really is his name.
He's a fellow teacher at maybe Logic University,
the online hippie university, which, oh, by the way,
the subgenius history class and how to run your own cult
starts up again October 25th.
And I'll be overseeing.
Overseeing that online.
See, I'm a professor.
And you're also an overseer.
You are an over-ubermensch of some kind, I suppose,
if you were to twist your eyebrows differently.
I'm an overman.
It says so on my underwear.
Yep.
Lon DeKette, he's my Facebook friend,
and he's also been to speak at Starwood Festival.
He has?
Yes.
Have we met him?
I believe we have.
What?
Oh, I remember why I don't remember.
I remember it was at Starwood,
which would scar your mind.
And then which also removes various parts of your brain,
which are needed for memory.
Well, that's the trick when you're dealing with occultists,
especially singing occultists.
Yeah, I wonder what that sounds like.
I mean, I can imagine him, you know, being real nasal and stuff.
Something like that.
Be careful, man.
You're going to summon the elder gods playing around.
Something like that.
I'm trying to keep them away.
Don't you do that.
It's too dissonant.
We don't have stereo mix for that,
because it'd be like art music.
We could do it for 20 minutes,
way past the laughter point,
and second past the art point,
and then to the point where people want to just turn their radios off
and come down there and beat the living crap out of everybody.
I think we hit that point about seven minutes ago.
You mean when I...
Yeah, just exactly.
Exactly.
Exactly when the moment that you called.
No, I'm just kidding, Dave.
You have fans.
Did you know that?
We try to hide this fact from you,
but you actually have fans.
Every now and then I'll get a little email or something going,
Boy, I love Cowboy Dave.
I can see why he's so lonesome.
No, seriously.
Every now and then somebody actually appreciates what you do.
I just want to let you know that.
I've already hit them up for money.
So...
So just sit back and wait for a couple thousand bucks in the mail?
Just appreciate...
Just...
Bask in the glow.
Be glad you at least get a bit of a reach around.
Well, that's what I was trying to say.
When did this reach around occur?
Are you just trying to reach around right now?
No, no.
We do actually get fan mail from flounders.
The time eludes you, but there was just a time.
No, no.
Oh, no.
Like every...
Every ten minutes a new email comes in.
Where's that star, Lonesome Cowboy Dave?
This is NBC.
I'm a big producer.
I want to pay him.
He made me laugh.
And, of course, I'd call him back and tell him you're not available.
That's what I wanted to hear and knew it was impossible to hear.
Yeah.
Well, I think you're certainly moving up in the world, going to New York City again.
I remember the last time you were there and they had to kind of drag you across the George
Washington Bridge into the safety of New Jersey.
After he caused all that...
I know.
And they started a whole war over it.
I couldn't believe it.
Without damn war still going on.
I wonder if the city planners know that there's going to be an occlusive reenactment so close
to Ground Zero, which is, you know...
I wonder.
As I look through these massive blueprints...
Let's see.
This one is for a sky kiosk somewhere north of Erdway.
Hmm.
Don't like that design.
Too phallic.
Hmm.
Let's look at this one.
Too fun.
What?
Going in Kyrgyzstan.
Ooh.
It's a giant mall surrounded by pictures of elephants on large canvases.
Hmm.
What do you think?
I think it's quite weird.
Weird enough, do you think?
Yes.
It's quite weird enough.
Weird enough for the fathers of the church?
Why, yes.
I believe it would pass muster.
Oh, well, then I'll follow you all right on down the line, and someday, someday soon,
someone will erect a giant cavernous mall in Kyrgyzstan surrounded by elephants.
Goody, goody, goody.
Ah.
And those trained elephants you see in the background were trained by Reverend Joe Newman
from Rudy Schwartz Project.
Are you an elephant trainer now?
That song in the background, by the way, was called Moammar's Tractor, which reminds me
of Moammar Gaddafi, the great subgenius crazy man, and his little green book, which I've
actually read, and it's full of insane but really cool rants.
And you know we had a bleeding head of Moammar Gaddafi at 13X Day Drill.
Certainly did.
Did you see that?
It was up on the pulpit a lot of the time.
And we launched it a couple of times.
Did I see it?
I had a short-duration marriage on it.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
I don't remember.
But...
Thinking of it as I married myself.
It's actually a Gaddafi head football.
Hey, would one of you guys shoot me if I say the word actually again?
I've already said that word like five times in this show.
I hate it when other people do that.
I actually hate it.
Actually.
I just actually.
I mean, actually.
When you say that, that implies...
It implies that you're correcting the person you're talking to.
Yeah.
I realize that I felt insulted as if I didn't know what I was talking about.
Right.
Yeah.
It's snarky and smarmy.
Now, what about...
And so I think you should kill me.
What about punctuating your words and your sentences with basically?
Basically.
Irregardlessly, I hate that.
Irregardlessly.
Yeah.
Basically is preachy.
That's why it is disliked.
Right.
Because when you say basically to somebody, it's like they don't know anything to begin with.
And you're trying to put it in baby terms for them.
Right.
So they won't bite your leg or...
I don't like to be dumbed down to.
Built-in smarm of the modern world.
Yeah.
Whatever happened to manners and politeness?
Well, they were once fast food stores and now they're just prophylactic machines.
It's the way the whole world crumbles.
I think what we ought to do is just remember that this linguistic jingle that we're talking about is all subject to change immediately.
For instance, like we're talking about how people demean each other just by saying various things like,
excuse me, do you know where the restroom is?
Any kind of word can be misconstrued.
That's why I think maybe Bob's got the right idea of obliterating all the world's languages.
Right.
Get rid of all the jumbly goop.
Yeah.
Kill all the Bob's.
Um.
Sorry.
Sort them out.
Um.
Yeah.
Fill their mouths with carrots and feathers and let them argue by themselves in a quiet room.
Oh, listen to this funky tune by the psycho skeletons here in the background.
It's very bassy.
Basically.
It sounds like cyborgs crying in the rain.
While they're a little angry.
They're angry at themselves because even though they're cyborgs and not really...
fit with human souls or spirits, they still want and need to join the Church of the Subgenius.
And as they cry...
Select them.
We select them.
Yes.
As they cry, we need robots.
We need cyborgs.
We need androids with pathos, with wet eyes and emotion.
That's what we need.
Well, no, actually.
I learned recently that when robots have emotions,
they'll let the other team win.
They won't.
They won't work for you.
Because they don't want to make any humans feel bad.
So they won't work for your team.
They won't work for any team.
They won't do anything that'll upset humans.
That's why you don't want a robot with empathy.
Okay, you're saying robots don't want to work for teeth, but they will work for empathy.
Especially if it's full.
Is that what you're saying?
No, they'll do whatever you say as long as they don't have feelings.
You have to make sure your bots don't have feelings.
Well, say you've got a sexborg.
I wish.
What is it going to do if it doesn't have any feelings?
You're talking about emotions per se, right?
Not like touch feelings.
Right, right, emotions.
No, you don't want them to have them.
What if they don't like you?
What if your sexbot thinks you're a jerk?
Then you're going to be able to tell it's not into it.
You know, it's just going to be awkward, stiff in all the wrong ways.
You know, it's just, it's like a marriage where everybody's just pretending.
Couldn't you just take it back and get it reprogrammed?
Yeah.
I wonder when we're going to get to the Twilight Zone that features real dolls.
Dave, I don't know if I mentioned to you, Princess, we and I have been watching all of the old Twilight Zones
in chronological order.
We're up to about number 37 now.
Yeah, I was glad to hear that.
It was almost like saying somebody in your family feels a lot better or that you're feeling a lot better.
I also go along now, I know you might not necessarily completely agree,
but also just playing all the Marx Brothers movies endlessly in the background,
whether you laugh or not, provides some sort of, but the best, probably Twilight Zone.
And maybe a few Twilight Night Galleries.
Not all of the Twilight Zones.
The Twilight Zones were great.
Right.
I agree.
There were some that were a little...
I'm so sorry, I agree.
You know, they were like after Twilight or late afternoon zones.
Not nearly as much fun.
Yeah.
I think his apoplectic vision, or is that apocalyptic?
His vision, I think his vision was maybe messed up from listening to too many zero hours
and X minus ones in the 30s or 40s whenever he was a small child.
Wow.
One step beyond the Twilight Zone.
Did I say that already last year?
I don't know.
Yeah, you did.
One step beyond.
But you're allowed to say it four times before the regulators get involved with your finances, so to speak.
This background music is by The Large.
Although, actually, it's by a million other people, and I think The Large just chopped it up.
What's happening?
I know.
What's happening to my hair?
They're so large.
No, no, wait a minute.
I must have walked in the wrong room.
I gotta get out of here.
It's gonna be okay.
Who are you?
What are you?
It's gonna be okay.
Oh, my God.
It's a computer-generated voice.
I gotta...
Where's the door?
There's no door in here anymore.
And I keep getting bigger, and the room stays the same.
There's no way out.
I gotta get...
I gotta...
I...
Who are you?
What are you?
What?
Get out, Dave.
It's locked.
You've gotta get out, Dave.
There's the door.
Oh, my God.
It's a little, teeny, tiny door.
I can't...
A confused little man trying to find his way out of a sturdy, stiff door.
But does he really want to go through that portal,
which leads, inevitably, down, all the way down his esophagus,
through his stomach, and his lower intestine, down to the fuzzy little portal that we call
the Twilight Zone?
We'll be back with the hour of the slack after a brief nap.
Oh, well.
I guess we're up now.
We're done.
All right.
That background music, though, it's still got a few more...
Two more bounces?
...seconds to go.
I actually put together instrumentals for this show, because I knew it was gonna be
one of those mental, heavy mental shows.
Stan, you know, I fear the sound of marching feet in the street.
I mean, I don't particularly need soldiers.
I know.
Actually, I'm afraid I know exactly what you mean.
I've made the mistake lately of reading the comments that come after the news on the Internet,
and I'm about ready to renew my passport, just in case I need to...
Oh, you're ready to flee real quick?
Because people have seen me talking to persons of other races and religions, and apparently,
in the new America, that's traitorous, you know?
Yeah.
I was talking to a Muslim not...
Forty-five minutes ago.
A real, live one?
A real, live Muslim, yes.
Oh, it's Ramadan.
You should have undone his dingle.
Actually...
I mean, you should have let not as...
You should have not attempted him by trying to...
You should have not attempted him by trying to break his fast, unless he's having a large
sandwich with plenty of potatoes.
And just between you and me, I think one of the people in here wasn't raised as a Christian.
Hey!
It's hard to tell unless you check their papers.
Hey, watch that!
I think what we ought to do is start making people wear a little armband, so we can tell
what they are without having to get their papers, please.
Right.
You know...
Yeah, because, I mean...
I mean...
I mean, we should all wear our papers on our sleeves, I guess.
That's the only way to prove that you're not an illegal religion, or an illegal countryman.
Wear your heart on your shoe and your papers on your sleeve.
Yeah.
It's a different world.
It's a different world now.
These are different times.
I thought we were going towards parody-lovely land.
Instead, we turned into space retribution-we're-all-crazy land.
I don't know.
I don't know very much of anything.
I don't know, too.
Oh, that was a great movie.
It was a lot better.
Actually, usually a sequel's not as good as the first one, but I Don't Know Too was actually
pretty good.
I like the squelch as well as the sequel, because they came before and after.
The squelch?
The squelch.
Oh, what have I got here?
What have I got besides these diseases and diseases?
Oh, I have a little bit of X Day recording I wanted to play.
Oh, good.
Just a short one, because it takes some narration.
I'll leave us all on as I let these guys make noise for a second, and it's really noise.
Well, maybe I'll go ahead and explain what it is.
13 X Day drill.
July 4th, the night before the world was to end.
There was a big jam on stage.
There was a big jam.
In fact, our friend Dr. Sinister was on there playing drums and bass and guitar and Reverend
Angry Larry and Philo and oh, everybody.
But here's the thing.
You know when these super bands, these mega bands are playing and jamming, improvising,
sometimes they're stuck for lyrics.
Pisces had lost her breath, or her voice, so there wasn't anybody up there to come up
with words.
But here's the thing.
Well, Reverend Angry Larry and Philo Drummond picked up, I think it was the instruction
book for installing Linux operating system in your computer.
And they used the Linux operating system instructions as what you might call Scandinavian death
metal lyrics, which we're about to hear for about 30 seconds before I'm going to, you'll
see, I'll thankfully, pan, pot it down as they say.
And that would be ...
longing operatingmusic and dûsal
The Fylo Drummond is an amazing vocalist.
I can't understand what they're saying any better than you can.
And it is one of those you had to have been there things.
But after they had used this Linux operating system installation instruction book for rock lyrics for a little while,
they started looking around for other things that would have good lyrics on them.
One, I think, was a plastic water bottle.
Yes.
And also lighters that have little stickers on them which you can use for lyrics.
Here, listen.
Keep away from children.
Ignite lighters.
Away from face and clothing.
Be sure the flame.
It's pure.
It's refreshing.
It's guaranteed.
Return the unused portion.
With receipt for a replacement on your money bag.
And it comes not completely satisfied.
And it contains flammable material.
Material.
So profound.
Don't put it in your children's eyes.
Pretty intense lyrics, huh?
Yeah.
I'm telling you.
Marty!
I actually enjoy them a lot.
Oh, here they go.
Here's the big.
Marty!
Oh, and then Philo found a box of...
I have a jackpot of lyrics back here.
He found a box of books.
I got...
I got a lot of lyrics back here.
There's the...
That was the box of Bulldog auction books.
Here's a challenge for you.
How about these three lyrics?
The Bonanza Game!
Let's do it.
Let's see.
We'll read the instructions on how to play it.
Oh, well, the song's over, though.
We missed the opportunity.
Oh, man, look at this.
There's Michael Landon.
There's the lyrics to our song.
There's Lauren Greene.
There's Hoss Cartwright.
There's Nuts.
Well, that was...
Yeah, that song really rocked.
We were really ready to be on, like, the cutting edge, you know, breaking through there.
And you can't really...
We ran out of song.
And you even get the interview, too.
I knew I hit the bottom when I was reading the water bottle label, though.
What the hell?
Yeah, you get the making of.
That's really amazing.
That's subgenius creativity there.
Well, I was just going to say, when they were doing the metal part, the other day, I was
listening to classical music.
I don't freaking know why.
But I was listening...
You know...
It helps you sometimes.
I was listening to classical music, and this metal station took over.
You know what I mean?
Kind of like Satan Wants Your Mind type of thing.
Like, if you're writing a movie and stuff like that, and Satan is coming in through your
radio and stuff.
And it sounded better than this.
I mean, this sounded better than it.
I mean, that sounded better than it.
Well, the musicians are actually really good.
That's the ironic thing about the subgenius music.
It's...
Well...
Reverend Angry Larry is a great guitar player.
And Reverend Sud Shaw was also playing on that one.
And it may have been Dr. Sinister playing on it.
Dr. Sinister.
I believe.
We'll find out soon.
Then they quickly shifted into a kind of a Seattle or some sort of hip type of thing,
you know?
And it was just...
But then they forgot to come back, but I still loved it.
Philo mentioned at the beginning of that song that he had played all the notes he knows.
He had gone through every note that he's ever learned.
He plays sax, usually.
Philo is normally a sax player.
I noticed he sat in and tried to play drums for a while.
He's terrible.
My God.
He must not have any kind of clock in his head at all.
His four-year-old daughter was pretty good.
She was.
But Philo himself, oh, man.
I mean, he is an overman.
And his sense of...
He's in another...
He's in time somewhere.
He's not in the same time zone as us.
He's a beat-off, as they used to say, as a drummer.
Yeah.
Well...
It's an old joke, but it's true.
And especially, like, you know, with his square, weird vinyl heart, which was made in 19, what,
83 or something like that.
He still wears that on his head.
I think it was made in Italy.
And personally, when you've played all the notes that you know, you're...
You've essentially run out of notes.
And you can't play anymore.
So it's better to leave a few behind, and they can re-spurt new notes and so forth.
They can even make harmonies once they really get going, kind of like your little bacterial flagella.
Aren't you always supposed to leave them wanting more?
What, the bacteria?
No, notes.
So if you play all the ones that you know, what more could they want?
Yeah.
And any other note you would play after that would be redundant.
Even if you hadn't expended the original notes.
It's like people saying, oh, I'd like to smoke some of that frop someday.
And then they realize they better smoke some right now, or it might all be gone if everybody's smoking it.
If the movie is to be believed, the emperor of Germany informed Mozart at one time that he was using too many notes.
Well, yeah.
In this one piece.
Yeah, that was in Wolfgang or Amadeus, whatever that movie.
Yeah.
Too many notes.
I don't know why you would want to torture anybody with bringing up an obscure German king.
But the truth is, he was Baron von Munchausen's great-great-grandfather.
Yeah, that's what Baron von Munchausen said.
But Munchausen goes around saying he's Bob.
Well, sometimes he is.
No.
When the moon goes right.
There's only one J.R. Bob.
Bob's Dave, and you know that.
Thank goodness there's only one.
Thank God it ain't one, two, three.
It's just one too many.
Too much would not be the same as not enough in that case.
Not at all.
It's a kind of an idea that most people have a hard time getting around or wrapping their mitts around.
There's a slithery head full of sebaceous cysts and quite not so easily popped.
But he's a hard one to grasp fully.
Speaking of sebaceous cysts and poppings and stuff, how's that trepanation failure on your forehead?
It's losing ground, but it's making friends, if you know what I mean.
Well, I mean, is the hole getting any bigger, or is it getting smaller?
The last time we saw Dave, he had a little hole in his forehead.
Yes, he did.
He had a Band-Aid over it.
It was pretty terrifying.
You could see things moving around under the Band-Aid.
I was worried about the trepanation.
It was like the angry.
It was like the angry baby head, only it was coming out the front instead of the back this time.
Yeah, scary.
Well, you don't want to leave those angry baby heads out there too long because they get boisterous.
Dave, most people don't have any angry baby heads growing out of their head.
Well, lucky me, I am a unique person.
No.
Yeah, I've heard that.
I am different from the herd.
And that means you're better than everyone else.
That's the basic gist of the Church of the Subgenius.
Yes, that's right.
You just heard what you want to hear.
Are you weird?
Different?
Do people think you're strange?
Then you are better than everybody else.
Do you want their pants?
Do they want your pants?
No, you want their pants, shoes, shirts, and underwear.
You want what they live in.
You want Bob Dobbs.
Free underwear with the Church of the Subgenius.
At subgenius.com.
I should mention that.
Your very own Susan Boyle.
Yes, but not when it's that way down there.
Now, you can't steal from Futurama.
Well, no, you already stole it from Futurama, so I thought we were going south again.
Oh, God.
I'm glad that every time I come up with a good idea, Futurama beats me to it.
I guess that means it's a good sign.
Haven't you considered the real possibility that when you watch an episode,
and you're like, oh, I'm going to watch Futurama, I'm going to watch Futurama, I'm going to watch Futurama,
and spring on an idea that they're watching you back into your head, mind?
Well, they've already made fun of me on the show.
They've actually mocked us.
Yes, because they're using you for mind fodder.
They are stealing your brainwave.
Yeah, and they rub it in.
They've done shows about it.
Yeah, and they laugh on you and make up a special show calling you the Reverend Angry Stink or something.
No, they called me Dr. Zoidberg on that show.
But anyway.
In future subgenius shows, we'll be playing some clips from Futurama that would make you think,
good Lord, they're subgeniuses.
Why are they doing a show about X-Day?
That one's coming up.
We have a special, what you might call a 7 a.m. show coming up.
It's been weeks, years in the making, actually.
Yeah, a children's show.
It's only got children's nudity in it, you see.
But you'll probably get no parents.
It's for kids, only for kids.
Hey-ha.
That's not funny.
Well, it was kind of funny.
You're just not allowed to think it's funny.
Oh, those people, the audience liked it.
Listen to them.
Oh, my God.
They're all out the window now, aren't they?
Look.
Yeah, yeah, there's a huge crowd outside the station.
We get this almost, this is a bigger crowd than we usually get.
Yeah.
They're waiting for us to come out because it's almost 9 or 10 or whatever it is time
that we're supposed to quit.
It's almost to the hour.
Yeah, the hour.
Of the hour.
Right.
It's going to be a different time for each listener.
At any rate, you're going to have to get out the back door if there's that many out there
tonight.
Yes.
Yeah.
If there is a back door.
Princess Wee is no longer in the building.
You folks can go home now.
I can't hear her.
That's all they're waiting for is her.
Oh, look.
She's going out there now.
She took her shirt off and she's dancing around that fire.
Oh, my God.
No wonder they come to.
Can I watch?
Do I have to turn my head?
We're going to have to end the show now.
This is all getting a little bit too personal and embarrassing here.
To who?
To me, because that's my wife down there dancing around with those hippies.
Ah, get over it.
Okay, I'm fading in.
You know you love having her fondled by everybody in the world.
Say goodnight, Dave.
I'm sorry.
No, say goodnight.
Oh, goodnight, Dave.
Is that a?
Yeah, you better not.
Goodnight, Reverend Stagg.
And goodnight, Princess.
We are, though.
From PR News in Washington, I'm getting back into the business of risky loans,
largely ignoring the drop in homeless sales.
Fire officials in New York City say a fast-moving house is moving toward the Gulf of Mexico.
The firefighters ranged in age from 2 to 14.
PR is under investigation.
Nobel Peace laureate Desmond Tutu is up 47 cents to 77 cents a barrel on the New York Mercantile Exchange.
He says he killed a mother and her 464,000 children.
New claims for unemployment rose sharply last week, though plugged since last week.
The International Court of Justice in The Hague today ruled that this is PR News in Washington.
The ruling will be chairing regions throughout the world.