There are those who believe that life here began out there, far across the universe,
with tribes of humans who may have been the forefathers of the Egyptians, or the Toltecs,
or the Mayans. That they may have been the architects of the great pyramids,
or the lost civilizations of Lemuria, or Atlantis. Some believe that there may yet be brothers of man,
who even now fight to survive somewhere beyond the heavens. And now, the subgenius hour of SWAC.
It's so ironic, we're such funny little monkeys, because, you know, Chaz,
nobody knows as well as I do that the world ends July 5th. And yet, I just got married,
bought a house, moved in, and my wife and I are running around still, trying to hang up our
artwork, or, you know, finish cleaning up the living room before the sun goes down.
Before the world ends.
Right.
And people tend to cling to the habits and that which is familiar, even when something as huge as
X-Day is facing them. It's breathing right down their necks. I mean, this reality...
Oh, here's another thing. I...
Oh.
Dave's here.
I guess we better go... You know, we gotta...
Wait, no, somebody's going to get him.
Somebody else is gonna Dave it.
Uh...
Get the Dave machine.
Oh, I gotta...
The Dave brain is now arriving.
Okay, in just a few days, we're gonna be aboard these...
In a few days, we'll be aboard these escape vessels with the...
Where the very air itself is the computer and the internet that serves you. And when you want
a hamburger, a hamburger materializes in your hand, emailed out of the ethers.
And yet...
I spent the last week...
I spent the last week paying for cable modem.
But what have we learned about...
Well, that's probably a good...
Oh, I gotta make sure that all the hours of slack are available for the radio station...
Yeah, it does...
While the world is ending. My God, how can we be lost in these silly...
Show them a little sympathy, kid.
Silly, trivial things when the grandness of a whole new universe is...
The whole universe is laid before us, barren and bare naked.
Yes, a pond of shit. Bare naked, yes.
And we're gonna get to crawl all over it.
Well, after a major speech...
And you're worried about it, the damn...
And I shouldn't have threatened about whether some CDs gonna be in the can or not.
As if I gave a hoot about this...
This is what it's gonna sound like in space. My spaceship...
What, with Dave?
Yeah, you'll just see from the distance, you'll just see this orb all enclosed...
That's another thing I don't like about this.
With neon green lighting...
Church.
And the lights protruding from the windows, pulsing to the beat of the song.
We're gonna have a good party.
We will definitely have a good party. That much we do know. We no longer know for sure if the world is gonna end or not.
And if you wanna hang out at this good party, if you wanna do that, I don't know, what you do at this point is...
Show up.
Just show up at Brushwood.
With a big lot of cash in your pocket.
Yeah.
Bring the big bags of money up to the main pavilion.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, you're gonna have to send someone to carry them. We're gonna need about three people.
Where do poor folk go when they die? They don't go to heaven where the angels fly.
There is a meteor crater here.
...seem again on the fifth of July.
This is where the saucer crashed.
Yeah.
Somewhere under here is our salvation.
Oh, right there!
I don't think that's an egg. It looks more like a Yucatisma...
Sperm cell.
One Yucatisma sperm hit this campground.
...and left this imprint.
Yucatisma sperms are so developed that they have skeletons. Just the sperms themselves have skulls and spines.
They have sentient stones.
They are vicious.
They'll actually debate amongst each other where the egg actually is.
Big sperm wars.
It's over there!
This is our planet is the egg.
This is where the Yucatisma sperm entered. Right outside Alt Slack Village.
It inseminated the earth.
And the world will end this morning at 7 a.m.
Have you paid your $30 to Bob?
Dave, do you really think that I need to be saving souls and worrying about that at this late hour?
Well, you could at least gouge this man's gas prices.
Do we really want to save...
I mean, that's what all the other religions do.
We're trying to save souls from themselves.
Theirselves?
Yes, we want to save them from salvation.
Everyone needs to be safe from their self.
Well, that adds a certain tension to that today.
It makes it real.
It's not a sci-fi convention.
This is a real drill for the end of the planet.
The violent end of the planet as prophesied by our guru, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
A lot of EMS study in Earth.
Living avatar of Sloth.
Slack for the subgeniuses.
Not slack for the humans, the pink boys, the mere humes and hume worms that are crawling around in their little cage of three dimensions on this pit of a planet.
That's all?
Gravity well.
Four little dimensions.
One for each of them.
I'm sorry.
Well, by any time anybody hears this, it will have been over.
So let's pretend like we're on our ship.
You know, I've been thinking, what cut was that?
Get your ship together, man.
Put on 12.
You know, friends, we've been saying for a long time, Earth, Earth, you hear me?
Earth, we must get off.
A light just came on in my head.
A light that means that the mobile revolution of the future has been sent directly into your cerebral cortex.
You're next in for the maximum plus and the pecks next.
Pecks, pecks, pecks, pecks, pecks, pecks, pecks, pecks, pecks.
Is this 12?
Yeah.
Yeah, this was some song about Earth we must get off, only it's not.
It just sounds, this is an X Day song, friends.
An X Day song made by somebody who didn't even know that X Day was right around the bend.
Ah, yeah.
Sorry.
At everybody, but now it can't be better.
Put your speed on fast so that you can fly theses
Father I don't understand.
And we open up the desert.
I think images of the future, decisions deserve a lot down below.
Sort ofhumane.
Kay, go?
So I think I'm falling, falling from the 14 story
One more line and it will be morning
Hit the floor
Stop the traffic, stop the clock, stop the clock
I wanna get off
I wanna get off with you
One more job in the supermarket
One more kick to get me started
Everyone get on board, this ship is sinking
Now maybe it's worth a chance
Any chance to tip the luck plane in the direction of the rupture
Oh it's gotta happen
In hell
I'm three years older than I ever planned on being
And I'm pretty damn pissed about it
Yeah you and me both sister
Mm-hmm
And you know
I sure didn't join this stupid cult back in 81
Just to get a damn 20 year pin with a coprolite chip
I paid my money
I struck the hell out of Dobbs
And I sincerely believe that party line
And now I wanna get off
Tip for tap
Hey that's fun for the cat
Stop the traffic, stop the clock, stop the clock
I wanna get off
I wanna get off with you
And that's a fitting call
You want more, more, more
That's a rather mistake I hate
I wanna get off
I wanna get off with you
I wanna get off baby
I do wanna get off
We must get off
Yeah I'm going out this weekend to build a tiki bar
That I'm gonna take with me on my pleasure vessel
But I think it's kinda
When I get off
I think those drinks are gonna be a little weird
Gettin' some spiced rum and some guava juice and
Vipin' the old pineapples with the old white sugar
Yeah, little margaritas mix and
I've been getting real
Rookie set
Sentimental about earth
Well there's certain things I wanna take
And I'm gonna get my own body
Cause I know that, you know this will be my last
I'm gonna take Hawaii with me
I think, yeah
My pleasure vessel is just gonna be
A dome over Hawaii
And we're going
And a little bit of the ocean
Gotta have dolphins
I'm gonna take the animal protective league with me
And also the nearest trailer park
There is one two tenths of a mile from the woods
Don't sound like you wanna get off
No, there are some things that are near and dear to me
Don't worry about it Dave
Get off
We must
But what will I wear?
I've never worn anything but this human flesh suit
This sadly faded
Don't be limited my friend
Don't be limited by these trivial concerns
Free your mind and your ass will follow
My mind's never been anything but this
In order to fly you have to lose your shit man
Yeah man, in order to sink you have to lose your shit
My brain's never been anything but this
Anything more than a soggy jelly roll
Filled with vacuous misconceptions and misanthropic misconstruings
All aboard this ship is sinking
That's like that
All aboard Scotty
You too skinny
Put your feet planted firmly apart
And your anus sucking the wind around you
No slurs and malams
It's time to get on board
If there isn't something to be found
Then it's time to go
Okay now it's time to put our hands together and pray
We're gonna ask the baby
Choo, choo, choo, choo
And time to move
All aboard this ship is sinking
And everything that we've been through
Is coming to an end
All aboard this ship is sinking
And everything that we've been through
Is coming to an end
Everyone's gonna say
All aboard this ship is sinking
And everything that we've been through
Is coming to an end
I ain't nothing but sadness
And nothing else
Stop hiding
Stop there
Come to me
Ooh, hey
I'm in the rain, the sun has yet to rise
I shake away the dread fear in my head
The ground is all I see
And the red spot on my moorstick
Is all I really need
I'm not walking on the sidewalk
The ground is on my tail
And every child is in the yard
Don't lose my cool, Mr.
I can't get you out of my way
I'm, I'm getting you Ñlown
I'm an out standing
I'm used humble Boipper
I'm in the rain, Mr.
I shake away the dread fear in my head
I don't know what to do
Mr.
I sing, Mr.
I've been missed by the hives, and I've just been picked to go
I've been picked to fill up with silver concrete, and look to the red
I've picked a house, I've picked a dog, I've picked a chicken to eat
And when they come out to see the show, I just pick them too
I'm not riding in the car, I'm not driving on the road
I'm not a target, leave me alone
And when I'm in the car, I'm not riding in the car
I'm not riding in the car, I'm not riding in the car
Why they need me
Try captain door
The button is showing
Wanna go
My heart for me
I like the music
It's wonderful
I'm excited
I'm flying
Ooh
Thank you.
Hey,pflicht!
I'm confused!
You think...
what do you mean my name is Will Samson!
I'm gonna've...
...
We'll just take the very moist, I might add, the very, very moist and disheveled artichoke
and place the growth, that's what they can call staying sprayed, into the artichoke.
Now we're going to put it in the shoebox, the old Wheatly's shoebox from 1972.
We're getting out of here.
The world ends a week from today.
And if you want to get out on the spaceships, you've got to get your butt out to Brushwood by 7 a.m.
The Bush girls will be at Brushwood.
Thursday morning.
All three of them, the evil clone twin who's not allowed out of the White House compound will be there,
and she will be playing with your Argyle socks for nada.
In disguise.
She's lusting all night.
She hasn't missed one yet, and no one's ever figured out which one she is.
I can't wait.
I can't wait for the end.
The opening ritual.
I always get so sentimental about that opening ritual.
That old bagpipe player is going to be there again this time, too.
This time he's going to have a pair of knees so we don't vomit throughout the ceremony,
and he's going to have more of his body together, at least,
so we don't have to stinky kilts and a bagpipe.
We're going home.
Bob's calling us home.
Stardust.
This ain't a threat.
This ain't a promise.
It's just a fact.
Bob's calling us home.
We're not sure where the escape vessels escaped to,
but we put our trust in Bob.
Dustbowl.
Nothing left.
Oh, they come down to our camp.
Security guards.
Beat up the game geeks first.
Then they come looking for us because we were still left here on Earth.
It keeps me always returning to you.
The vessels left a long time ago.
The water from the whales of home.
They say we're going to be picking some fruit really soon.
And now it's just...
The water from the whales of...
Home.
Well, my...
I killed a man.
I guess it was a man.
I thought it was a woman.
Then I thought it was a bee.
Then I thought it was a fly.
Then I thought it was a...
It's time to go.
It's going to be the laws of Bob from now on.
Come on, put your blanket back on your horse.
Did you get mean mad, Stag?
Did you get mean mad when you jumped on the vessel
and gave the finger to the bulls and the dicks back there in the camp?
You can take the saddle here, Dwight,
or DJA, anytime you want.
We're ready.
I'm ready.
Hook up the electrodes.
Dave, you ready?
Amazing slap, my friend.
Those electrodes have been lubricated
and their stuff's in there real tight.
I can see that.
Oh, oh, oh.
Timothy will be there.
In different cornice symptoms.
Without waiting for us.
And the other Timothy will probably be waiting for us, too.
Timothy Bleary.
Lenny will be there.
Jimmy will probably play star spangled banner.
Jimmy and Timmy Bleary will be there.
John will be there.
We'll be able to just sit around the place in our socks.
Jim will finally come out of retirement.
The King will be there, my friend.
Tiny Tim.
Little pink poodle-looking record players
that have this strange stink on the side of them.
The Duke of Ute.
You don't know if it's Jerry Lewis and Jerry Lee Lewis.
You got it from your weird uncle
or if it's because your weird uncle put it there on purpose.
Moe Howard will be at the judgment.
All three Stooges will be there and Shemp.
King Louis XIV of France will not be there,
but he will be joking about you
as he sits on the throne extra-medicating.
Oh, man.
I just can't wait.
I just can't wait to get there.
That opening ceremony.
We'll be standing hand in hand
as the saucer lands.
Right in the middle of our circle of humanity.
Nearly a fleet, whatever the hell that is,
or a gaggle, perhaps,
of these shiny, spherical objects coming down.
And we see that there's like a ray of sunshine
or some golden, luminous thing descending,
picking up each and every one of the furry, funky little boys
and girls down there below,
so eager to kiss this place off and bye-bye.
And we see now that they're making a formation now.
I don't know what kind of it's perhaps the...
It looks like the saucer...
Keep your hat on tight.
You're back to the wind and you're sagging the saddle.
That's right.
See y'all.
They're giving the finger to the planet...
That reminds me.
Uh-huh.
You know, I saw the passenger manifest for the first day.
Yes.
My manifest destiny.
Like you got a manly fist destiny in store for you to...
Uh-huh.
I was so shapely ass wasn't listed on that thing anywhere.
But I have my boarding pass.
Right here.
Hey, wait a minute.
This is for the Achilles, Laura.
Hey, be sure to try their Klingover cocktail.
Two shots of this?
There's gotta be some kind of mistake or something.
Oh, yeah.
I'm gonna go call Stay and straighten this out.
Here.
Here, you take over the show, okay?
Hey.
Well, why do?
Get Frank and you two finish up our tour of the solar system.
Ah.
And keep it clean, you sleazebag.
I'm off.
Trust me.
Ta-ta.
Ah, good.
Enough of this crap.
Mmm, sweet.
But let's make it stink.
And then to your inner...
Your inner...
You're a nice little heaven.
Heaven, heaven.
Wow, what's that smell?
It's Uranus Boner.
God dammit, is it?
I mean the planet, Uranus, Boner.
Blazing.
Comets, Captain.
You mean you brought us back to that godforsaken stinkhole of a planet where Seaman Bob bit the cosmic weenie?
If memory serves me correctly, Doctor, you pronounced Seaman Bob dead after he fainted from the smell of his planet.
He is of Uranus.
He's a friend of the planet.
I don't believe my eyes.
It's Seaman Bob.
Check out the bulge inside his swamis.
He must be happy to see us.
Seaman Bob.
So good to see you looking in the pink.
Shove it, Quirk.
You're not going to be glad to see me at all.
Behold.
Hey, it's the wrap of Bob.
It's a great group.
Check it out.
Yeah, but enough Masterpiece Theater for right now because something's definitely up.
I'm not on that list.
See, it's all there.
I'd better hightail my butt to Brushwood.
I'm going to get off this planet, girlfriend, if I got to tear a piece off a stand, Bob's butts, and bleed a rope to the saucers.
Whoa, hey.
Sounds like an idea.
One minute.
This is the last time I got to get up before seven, right?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
We'll have to do this.
I'm sure all the drills will have paid off by this time.
We'll be ready.
I've been drilled too damn many times, if you ask me.
Oh, boy, this is exciting.
It's got to be one of these episodes, right?
Actually, this is a much better turnout than when we do it at the end of the week.
Twenty-five.
They're all dead by then.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six, five, four, three, two, one.
The keys, monsieur.
Here are your keys.
Oh, thank you.
Are those the keys to my new planet?
Yes, those are your keys.
My new planet-sized spaceship.
And very have a good time for your whole everything you have.
And anything I want, I can create as if unlike unto a god.
Absolutely.
Anything you will learn, your heart desire, you can have just by merely you can shake the keys or let your knees down.
And I can show it all off to my buddies who also bought subgenius membership cards and pledged to the station.
Oh, Mary, Mary, you're too lazy to me.
All your friends you can take.
You can take.
You can show off any of your buttock.
You can hang from the ceiling, do anything you have.
And all my buddies have their own planets, too.
In mono, stereophonic, and...
We can have wars and all kinds of stuff.
Oh, my way.
Man, I sure am glad I invested that $30 to Bob Dobbs back then in 1996.
When I spent that $30, you know what that amounted to?
Five cents a day until next day.
Yes.
It cost me less than it cost a cup of coffee in a whole year.
I must agree.
You made a very good deal, my friend.
You're a great waiter.
Are you one of the alien sex goddesses disguised as a waiter?
No, no, no, mon ami.
I am actually a waiter.
I had a chance to become one of the alien sex goddesses by Pupfer merely to help you and to crack pepper for you, to shine your shoes, to do anything your heart desires.
See how realistic that was.
And mainly I'm here to stroke your ego, just as in real life.
Oh, man.
Man, this is great.
I am so glad that I am a saved subject.
I am a subgenius.
Oh, don't forget to try the pork pie or any of the caviar.
It's very excellent.
Oh, the food here is great.
It's like before I even think of it, there is just what I was about to want to eat.
And, oh, I was just thinking about this comic book, this old Zap comic, number five.
Hey, River, baby.
You mind if I sit down at your table?
Uh, Elvis.
How you doing, man?
You know, I never really got the chance to get in line with your church and help you out, but I saw something in the after light.
Oh, well, what?
I just wanted to sit down and shake your hand and say I'm a real supporter of Bob and whatnot.
Oh, man.
Well, listen, let me tell you, I grew up listening to your music, Elvis.
I do these a lot.
As far as I'm concerned, you are the king.
And I just, man, this is great.
Yeah, yeah.
This is just unbelievable.
I think somebody else wants to meet you.
I think Sammy Davis Jr. would like to sit down and have a word with you.
Hey, look, I'll see you later, man.
There's a little filly over there I want to talk to, all right?
Hey, man, hang in there.
I love Bob.
I really do.
Hey, thanks, Elvis.
Man.
God, this is just so.
It's Reverend Baby Ivan Stang.
That's you, isn't it?
It's Reverend Ivan Stang.
Oh, yeah.
I'm a person with, I just had my adenoids removed.
I'm sorry.
I had the wrong table.
Why?
You know, it's great being rich and famous and having, it's only been, what, two hours
since 7 a.m.
The rupture happened two hours ago and already I've stuffed my face, masturbated, met Elvis.
I'm a big fan.
I've done all the things I never, ever did before.
More champagne, monsieur?
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Hey, what other celebrities are around?
Lenny Bruce happen to be on my planet?
I think Mr. Bruce is in the other room at the bar.
I bet I will go and then.
Oh, I'll have to.
Well, don't bother him.
Don't bother him right now.
No, no, no, no, no.
Anything for your pleasure.
It may take a few minutes, but I will bring him.
Wow.
You know, it would have been creepy if Lenny Bruce had just suddenly appeared before I
even got to ask.
Hey, you're the guy.
You're the guy.
And the first time I remember, I was the only Jew.
Do you remember?
I was the, you remember that shtick I did?
It was in, I think it was at the Village.
No, wait.
It was at the Vanguard.
I went.
I've got a bootleg of that, man.
The only Jew in Ohio.
Do you remember that shtick?
Yeah, yeah.
That was you.
That was you, man.
I remember that was you all the way because I was there.
I'm in Canton, Ohio.
I'm in Canton, Ohio and I'm, I drive, it's like a VFW hall or something like that.
That was only four years old?
They drive me out to this VFW hall and there are these pictures of, they say it's Bob there.
There's all these pictures of Bob everywhere.
And the next thing you know, I see you're standing there.
Man.
Oh, oh, oh, look, he's shooting up.
Wow.
Look, look.
Do you, do you, can you OD?
By the way, can you OD on the escape vessels, Lenny?
Oh, I guess so.
Bummer.
And if he were to come back to me.
Oh, well, he was.
He was just one of the sex, beautiful sex goddesses in the form of my, one of my heroes,
Lenny Bruce.
I'm sorry, Monsieur.
Today is Monsieur Bruce's birthday and as you know, he always gets the China white on
his birthday.
We'd have to clean him up.
He'll be right back, perhaps at another time.
Man, that is so cool.
And Elvis is over there singing just a song just, just for me.
Oh, boy.
This Church of the Subgenius stuff was crazy.
Right.
It was, it was well worth all that, all that Xeroxing and this $30.
Hey, man.
Hey, Reverend.
You remember me?
Hey, what are you doing, man?
I'm going to heap a, I'm going to heap a do-wunky, buddy.
What, what?
I need some help, man.
Well, now, wait a minute.
I know.
I've, I've retired now.
It's after X days.
You subgeniuses shouldn't need any help.
Yeah, but see, some things don't work out the way we always had them planned.
You see, I don't know how to explain this, but see, everything is just going perfectly
fine.
I mean, I'm not saying that I'm not going to be able to do it.
I'm not saying that I'm going to be able to do it.
I'm just saying that I'll be fine until, well, things didn't start going so good.
Well, wait a minute.
This is my perfect escape vessel living fantasy.
I don't want to sound bleak.
What are you doing here raining on my parade?
Well, you know, it's not exactly paradise, Rev.
I guess there were a few more episodes to follow after X day and, you see.
I command you to disappear.
Oh, sorry, man.
This is for real.
He didn't, he, wait a minute.
I should be able to, anything I want should happen.
The stuff.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave, be gone.
Hey, man, listen, I'll put it to you in like a pop culture way.
You ever see that movie, what was it called?
Not Giardos, Novos.
It was by Stanislav Slam.
It was about this year's star, see?
And if people got too close to it, see, whatever they thought was real.
Solaris.
Solaris, yeah.
Yeah, that's it, Solaris.
And the guy starts, well, you see, the stuff, you know, that was in your champagne
that made you think Lenny Bruce and all them guys, well, the stuff's kind of,
it's bootleg, man.
It's not very good.
All kinds of weird stuff's happening.
Some people are actually dying and staying dead.
What?
Other people are wishing for beautiful lady in Czech Scottish to come and perform
oral sex on them, and their heads explode, and they don't get up,
and they keep on staying in pain.
Wait a minute.
Oh, man, it's pretty bad.
Look, Elvis, that's not really Elvis.
It's just a record.
That's right.
Wait a minute.
What's that song?
It's a whole record.
It's a viewport.
It's outer space, right?
Right.
Wait a minute.
That's what I'm trying to explain to you, man.
Wait, those are just little Christmas lights on a conveyor belt.
Yeah.
What the?
Wait a minute.
Yeah, it's a rat burger.
You mean, wait a minute.
It's wearing off, man.
You mean that we've been gypped?
Not only gypped, we might be dying right now.
What about the 90?
Well, if we're dying, then we ought to at least get 90 bucks.
No, no, no, no.
We've got to search around for some kind of antidote pudding for this stuff.
It's something to make us at least go to one or the other different levels.
Bob cheated us.
I can't.
That's impossible.
Or you're all too screwed up.
But how could Bob screw?
Wait a minute.
He cheated us, man.
He cheated us.
Damn screw up.
The trick.
Bob's not smart enough to cheat us.
But Jesus and Bob.
Hey, where's Jesus?
Look, man.
I haven't seen Jesus since the rupture.
I don't know nothing about the conspiracy stuff.
And it's Jesus and Bob was out playing golf.
I'm sick all of a sudden.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're going to get a lot sicker, man.
I feel like I'm seasick.
Look at your fingernails, man.
They're bleeding, bro.
They're falling off.
Yeah, they're bleeding.
You're coming loose.
And I'm bleeding, too.
Look at this.
That's my nose.
I'm bleeding.
We're going to find Jesus.
With Bob.
He didn't cheat.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, you ain't never gonna have it.
And you ain't gonna regret it.
Oh, yeah.
That's it?
Yeah, let's go home.
Why does Stain run away so fast?
What is the bird?
Slate to...
The world may end tomorrow,
but you will die!
This is such a pathetic joke.
God damn it.
Fuck!
I trusted you, man!
Since I was eight years old, man.
I saw you on that flight!
I trusted you, man.
Trusted you!
I still got 659.
You let us down!
Let me down, man!
Who was it who missed you?
You don't even care!
You're just laying there, smiling!
Smoke.
I want my...
I want my 30 bucks back!
Oh, shit!
That's...
I shouldn't start that.
Class action suit!
You don't like that where that goes.
That's an old...
Well, fuck, shit, piss!
The followers work Bob over.
You know, Bob seems to be enjoying
the punishment after the event.
The smile just gets wider and wider.
Let's all play nice.
I don't think he comes here for the sausage.
I think he comes here for the...
The beatings.
The sake of it.
It's not a gag anymore.
I think he really likes it.
Yeah, me too.
Yeah, we better leave the polyester.
We always wondered what that smile was all about.
Now we know.
It's all the same.
The old twin wrestling.
The bigger they are, the more they just want to be spanked.
Let's nail it to that big wire fucking thing over there.
Just want to go back to being little babies again.
No responsibility.
I think a hanging would be shorter.
You have large quantities of wood type things over in that area.
What I heard, Bob's already hung.
He's over in that area.
What?
That's what I heard.
Wooden materials.
Well, this is a terrible disappointment.
I was so...
You know what?
Yeah, you've made no plans for the rest of the year, have you?
I had dibs on all those monuments.
Yeah, yeah.
You don't have dick for us to be entertained by the longest.
No.
No bottle on my ass.
Actually, we did arrange for somebody to bring a sound system in tomorrow.
So all these talented people will all be...
I have lots to entertain each other.
How do you think I got down here?
Well, that's great.
Jeez, that's a good idea.
Follow the...
Yeah.
You'll be trouble if I am unmotivated.
Yeah, jeez.
It's silly.
It's 7 AM and we're all awake and shit.
What the fuck are we going to do for like the next three days?
That's the three days.
Holy smokes.
Oh, somebody had the bright idea of 7 o'clock.
Look at this.
I'm not going to do that.
Yeah, you shouldn't have run those credit cards all the way out.
Yeah, no shit.
Now I got to get a room.
I'm going to get a room.
I'm going to return ticket home.
What the fuck's going on?
Sorry about that, man.
Hey, man.
Well, be glad it wasn't a heaven's gate.
That's all right.
No shit.
Next time you'll know.
I'll be ready.
Yeah.
Well, that's why we call them next day drills.
Time for Scientology.
Yeah, yeah.
Scientologists will still take you.
You know, I don't know.
I don't know.
Scientologists will take anyone.
The job of us is still predicting the end of the world.
What should we learn from history?
Then there was Reverend Jacques Treatment, who truly, truly did expect to be lifted up
by the saucers on July 5, 1998 of the conspiracy calendar and did run up all his credit cards
and quit his job and was kind of scared about half an hour before everybody else was laughing.
And the great miracle of Jacques Treatment was he was back the next year with free food
for everybody.
Wow.
Junk food.
Just plans of a lifetime shot to hell.
Yeah.
All because some preacher man fucked up or lied.
Breaks my heart.
Damn.
One of these days people will learn.
No matter how big the disappointment, we are still standing here.
That's right.
We still haven't died.
Bob, let us live one more year.
We are still here.
To suffer.
To disappoint me every year.
One more year.
One more time.
No.
You don't have to kill yourself yet.
Yeah, but it's not much worth for anyone else.
Not yet.
Yeah, but one more year.
One more year.
Beware of the beast man, for he is the devil's pawn.
Alone among God's primates, he kills one before all the world.
The golden age of philonic irrigation.
Oh, we're on planet.
You read our book, too.
That was sad.
Which one did you like better?
I told you all, Negi is the way to go.
The bullshit of the believers.
Another ex-deaf.
No.
I'm not a believer.
Joe, what do you think is happening?
TheçŽ‡ among us varies.
I'm sorry.
Small talk with the Grinch.
Is this beautiful anywhere?
I think now you can party for three days at beautiful Brushwood Campground.
The voice of the Lord!
Yes, it's me.
Arise!
Where were you at 7 a.m.?
While Reverend Stang and myself were busy preaching,
you slept in and missed it!
Registration begins at noon today.
You must be bagged and tagged.
It is time to wake up.
Again.
Because I say so.
Hello?
Boy, where is everybody?
Oh my God, the rupture did happen!
And only me, Motormak, and Stang are left.
They took everybody but us!
Oh, my God.
Where are you people?
I would just figure.
Yes, the world ends this morning.
The world ends this morning at 7 a.m.
Will you be ready?
Time control.
Well, they don't call it subgenius or not.
There we go.
Now, is this mic over here on?
No.
Oh.
I thought, oh, it sounds a little better.
I'm not much of a technician.
I don't do shows with people very often.
People.
Humans.
God.
Well, you know, we wanted, I was, had been looking forward to leaving this planet full
of people.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Well.
Yeah, although, you know, it's a good idea.
And then the prophesied end of the world once again pooped out, didn't come through.
But you know.
And, you know, I had such a damn good time the last couple of weeks.
And especially that week at Brushwood that the, well, I didn't wanna leave.
I didn't wanna leave the planet.
I was thinking.
If every day was as much fun as X-day at Brushwood, we wouldn't need X-day.
Well, that's true.
But what I would.
We'd be fine on earth.
Thank you.
Abracadabra.
The end of the world as we know it.
аци angers.
It's the end of the world as we know it. It's the end of the world as we know it.
Fall till it's mine.
You're gonna lie to them today, those troops are on their way.
Put your job, cover your slack, Jared, I've got your back.
Hail Connie, hail Bob, underneath the righteous fog.
Give it up, give it in, find yourself your Yeti kit.
Do your list, radio, hell, folks gonna blow.
Here to find out what you know, pass the fight.
Take a joke, I'll punch, this is no joke, it's fierce, fierce, fierce.
Turn them in, I'll turn them in, I'll lie.
I'll burn the solutions, then you will burn me.
I'll turn it in, then I decline.
It's the end of the world as we know it.
Fall till it's mine.
I can't find $30.
I can't find our little senior quick who will even come.
It's the end of the world.
It's the end of the!
Let me know.
You should know, sis.
It's the end of the world as we know it
All feels fine
The end of that is drunk on life, the mortal slipping beyond bars
Jenny driving fast, first bang, where Red Ivan sang
Special presence to me, the son of a cop, little me
Reverend Susan, that's the city doctor, Vincent St. Ed
One more time, I know you can't
Anticrystal, Reverend Geo, Dr. Stanton, right?
It's the end of the world as we know it
All feels fine
The end of the world as we know it
It's the end of the world as we know it
Wow.
What I thought would happen, what I thought would happen was, because they had a series of bad lucks,
and so what I thought would happen was they actually arrived, and everybody had, you know, their own dream,
and mine was another nightmare, and so it was continuing to go on.
Well, that's one theory. A lot of people...
That it is going on still then, right?
Right. Every X day, some people think...
So it's kind of flashed and disappointed.
Well, the aliens came and they created a whole new planet, but it's a horrible, stinking planet, just like the one I was on in Earth.
Exactly the same.
I can't free myself from my preconceptions of what life is like, so my new life is ending up just like...
Right, exactly.
You know, you couldn't really imagine the sex goddesses sexing up you. Not really.
I mean, you could fantasize, but you couldn't really believe it.
Yeah, everything was just almost on the edge.
You couldn't believe.
Just almost on the edge.
You know, and it's that lack of faith.
It's that loss of nerve at the last second.
Yes, I think that's what it was that made the red light go off and the smoke start expunging from the engine.
It was bad mind control.
I think you're being too hard on yourself.
That's a great hard-on you've got there yourself.
I think that's too much, man.
What, to think that I would actually allow my mind to collapse?
The fibers of my mind collapse so much that I would actually will bad luck on myself?
Well, I suppose that maybe everybody else had great luck and you were the only one,
but I think that Bob just screwed up, man.
If I were you, I'd blame it on Bob Dobbs, not yourself.
There's a lot I can blame on Bob Dobbs.
I blame damn near everything on Bob Dobbs and all the rest you can blame on the conspiracy of the normals.
But do you get any sort of requitment or respite out of blaming Bob?
Hell yeah.
You don't have to blame yourself.
As my old friend Puzzling Evidence used to say,
let's frop up so we can get back to hating the world instead of ourselves.
That was true.
That was what he said.
I don't know if that's a response from Bob or if he's like the other guy.
Well, Bob didn't even show.
I mean, I didn't show almost, but Bob didn't show at all.
He really didn't show.
Well, he hasn't, but the last time he did, somebody shot him.
Dead.
Of course he's not going to show up again.
There were a number of...
Somebody will shoot him again.
Ladies and gentlemen, with the assistance in the background of the legendary number six,
Lord Estafa Trout Waxer.
So just for those of you who are still trying to find your way into the word of Bob, I want
to offer you some insights into the mystical techniques that we use.
And the first one is very, very simple.
It involves the mastery of the breath.
So all of you breathe in the slack.
Let me just hear you breathe.
Everybody inhale.
And breathe out the work.
Breathe in the slack.
Now even works better if you imagine that the shining face of Bob is in front of you,
or better yet, the shining face of Connie is in front of you, in which case you can
breathe in the pleasure.
And breathe out the pain.
Now.
And the second thing I'd like to introduce you to is our sacred buddhas in the church.
As you know, the buddhas have a mudra. They hold a hand up like this, little fingers down,
and put their thumbs and big fingers up. That means something like,
you'll be very lucky through your enlightenment through the Buddha.
And then of course, the Hindus have their mudra. They make their thumb and their forefinger into a circle,
representing the world. And the three other fingers sticking out represent Vishnu, Shiva,
and Brahma, all together, all being one with the world.
And that's how we start to make our subgenius mudra.
It's that we get rid of Vishnu, and we get rid of Brahma,
and we leave all these bombs sticking straight up in the air, saying,
Fuck you! I'm gonna blow up the world!
And so you can sit there on your throne of natural meditation,
flat your hands, doing your mudra on your knees,
and you can use the last technique I want to show you,
which is to vibrate in the name of our Lord and Savior.
Everyone take a big breath in, as low as you can, and as deep as you can.
Everyone go . . .
. . .
And you can keep that up for as long as you want.
If you keep it up for a long, long time, it will gradually wind its way higher,
and higher, and higher . . .
And if you can climb for ten numbers of your pledge,
doing that at once, it's a wonderful, wonderful thing.
. . .
Thank you, Reverend Bodhisattva Trout Waxer, and Number 6.
Preceded there by some ESO Swamp radio from WCSB,
with Lonesome Cowboy Dave Chasmith, and yours truly,
Reverend Ivan Stang.
Before that, Saint In and Hell in a Handbasket, live at 4X Day,
and that version of Midnight Turning Pale by ESO, Einstein Secret Orchestra,
likewise recorded at that great, great celebration that we did survive.
And friends, you can learn more about everything from www.subgenius.com
or write to the P.O. box number I'm about to give you,
this music in the background is WOTAN music,
just improvisational music by Dr. Philo Drummond, Number 6, and Hell Pope Huey.
Special thanks to Reverend Susie the Flusie for her great WREK show excerpts.
Friends, write to Bob at Post Office Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 4411.
Me, I'm going back to Time Town, that's that cafe on my escape vessel with that dopey waiter praise, Bob.
Thank you, Reverend Ivan Stang, for those wonderful, inspirational messages.
And now during the cocktail here, cocktail hour here aboard the X's to the vessels of the space...
I'm sorry, this is my first night here.
Tonight, performing, we're going to be having the...
Oh, jeez, I can't read these cards.
Hairy women are going to be crucified.
Was that your request, Reverend Stang?
Oh, no, no, no, not crucified. I just want to see a live sex show.
I thought you...
I don't want to... No, I don't enjoy the violence.
I thought you wanted to see a hairy...
I've been watching that stuff all day on the view screens.
It's not her suit to be crucified.
No, no, I hate the hairy...
She's a yeti.
Would you like to pretend like there are more people in the audience so we can have more interactive and you can think of maybe something else you might want to do?
No, I'm tired. I think I'll just sit here and listen to Elvis and...
Would you like to...
...drink?
Would you like to drink real booze or would you like to drink some of the exacerbated booze?
Yes.
Would you like to drink some of the exacerbated booze?
No, no, I'll just have this off and statters house standard here.
Primo triple?
No, no, no, just sit here.
Would you like your toes shined?
This isn't all I expected it to be. I'm tired and...
It's my first day on the escape vessels. I'm already...
Bored, Caviar?
Bored.
Bored with pleasure and...
...panty chocolate?
Is this what it's going to be like?
Oh, yes, yes.
One day of having everything you want and by the end of the day, you've had enough. You're bored. You're ready for bed. You don't know what you're going to do the next day. You've had everything.
Reverend, excuse me. The queen of the Nubians would like to do you again.
I...I'm just...I don't care.
I'd rather go on hearing your lies.
Let me just listen. Leave me alone, drone, clone.
The stage is barren.
Not Sergio? Any of them?
No, just go away. Shut the planet down. Shut off the sun.
If that's your pleasure, Reverend, I will go away.
Close down all the malls. Tell the hookers to go home. Or we're back to the factory, wherever they're made.
Is your heart filled with pain?
Shall I come back again?
If only Elvis would come back.
Tony D, are you lonesome?
Hey, Reverend, babe.
Claire, have a hit of this. You'll love it, man.
Oh. Oh, thanks, Elvis. Maybe that'll make me feel better.
Hey, it did.
Now to death, in the name of the gods.
till I'm seen again
Stand up.