Ah, yes, dear friends, the ancient rerun that we're about to play may be the greatest Hour
of Slack episode of all time.
And what a coincidence, or is it?
Last week's show, number 1768, was a rerun of 468, and tonight's show, 1769, is a rerun
of number 69, from late 1986 or early 87, pretty early in our career.
This may be of interest to collectors, because number 69 is one of the few episodes that
never made it into our online archive of ancient shows at subgenius.com, and the master wasn't
among my collection, at least not where I've been able to find it yet.
Luckily, an old listener told me he had recorded a copy off the air in Dallas and could share
it.
Praise Jim Rassfeld.
The very, very beginning has another coincidence, but it involves such a convoluted long story
it'll have to wait for another time.
Here, then, is Hour of Slack number 69.
See you tonight.
...by Bee Bumble and the Stingers.
Ni Ni Na Na Nu Nu by Dickie Doo and the Don'ts.
What a...
Ni Ni Na Na Nu Nu?
Yep, I'm afraid so.
By Dickie Doo and the Don'ts?
Indeed.
Ha!
Your genitals.
Look with your closed eyes at your genitals.
And say to your genitals,
In your mind, relax.
Start level three trance learning state on.
We are controlling transmission.
It will signal your subconscious mind, flashing a message.
...
Praise Bob.
The fates have brought you into possession of a subgenius instructional video barrage tape.
Prepare yourself.
You are about to be remade into a new being through forbidden knowledge previously kept secret for centuries by the jealous priesthoods of many religions.
Caution, improper viewing techniques may lead in some persons to dependency, seizures, cranial fits,
priapic conditions, micturitions, sternutations, subtle glandular mutations, and in some territories, legal arrest.
I always take their hand and shove it right down my pants.
Ah, yes.
Then I cinch up my belt with my hands.
Real tight.
And I'm ready to go.
Baby, baby.
Dirty, dirty, dirty, dirty.
Dirty little girl, dirty little boy.
I am not a little scrub, scrub, scrub to your clean, clean, clean, clean.
Get that filthy animal out of here.
Um, there are...
Unfortunately enough...
From 1998 when the world is sold or not sold, depending on how Bob swings the deal,
there is going to be two conflicting alien forces hitting at the same time.
Plus Jehovah One, the alien space god corpse from the corporate sin galaxy,
who posed as a deity back in the Old Testament, and he has great saucer stories,
the book of Exodus, I have people should check out.
But, yeah.
Yeah, I think that there are many people listening right now that need this book and they know that you need the book of the subgenius.
The people that need it will understand it, too.
I feel that is true because I went in to get the book from a distributor here in Houston.
And she said, have you tried to read this thing?
And I said, yes, I have.
And she said, can you understand it?
And I said, no, I can't.
But that's the essence of it.
Exactly.
Part of Bob's message is that we must stop trying.
You must learn to give up.
Slack lies not in striving for slack, but in giving up on false slack, the false slack of the conspiracy.
And, of course, some people, they hear that term conspiracy and they think, oh, these guys must be some kind of coobs.
And to a certain extent, we want that word to carry that connotation.
Because the coobs are right.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
The coobs are right.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
And many of you may not know exactly what's going on here, but this is the subgenius radio ministry hour of slack.
Hour of slack, dear friends.
I'm in Dallas, Texas, and it looks like tonight I've only got the use of one tape deck.
You know what that means?
That means we've got to flip these unsuspected records into the thing in order to do these smooth, smooth radio DJ type transitions like that.
I'm in Dallas, Texas, and it looks like tonight I've only got the use of one tape deck.
I've got a tape deck.
Oh, yeah, boy, now he's gone.
A martyr for the cause, for the fallow.
And he's coming again.
Who knew that the first shot was gonna be the last shot?
But he's got a hard drive.
He's got a hard drive.
The gas won't go through the night
And although he may be hurt
The universe will keep on squirting
All the stars, no
And it's coming again
Oh yes, dear friends,
this is the subgenius radio ministry,
Our Slack.
You're listening to Slackmaster Cleave
and the Spurious Jive
doing that great old-fashioned hymn,
Bob Is My Load,
and it's coming again.
Friends, it's going to be a loose show.
Loose? Oh yeah, yeah.
But that's okay.
It's a challenge.
He can tell from the many who laugh
With just a shot from his mighty staff
If only he could make it back
From the land of the dead
But until that happy day
We can only drink and say
Bob Is My Load
And it's coming again
I know he can make it
With the help we can take it
We'll lose the pieces of our minds
To the pink boys and the whims
Until the day that he comes back
It'll be a world without slack
Bob Is My Load
And it's coming again
We don't want the answers to call us
And we need Bob to be honest
Bob Is My Load
And it's coming again
Great God Almighty
Holy, Holy
Help me somebody
Oh, Bobby
Bobby's gonna be here
Sooner or later
Oh, oh
What are they laughing at?
Well, dear friends
Oh, yes, like I said
It's gonna be a slackful, slackful
When you'll be able to hear me flip these cassettes
Hear this little
That's a cassette right there
It's got all the word of Bob on it
Just like holograms
You can fit thousands and thousands of years' worth
Of information onto these things
Oh, wait a minute
I think we're
Yeah, that's right, that's right
11-59
No, it's 11-08, dear friends
Loop out
Cabin light on
Energy
Stimulus
Feeder out
Dream monitor out
Okay, now that you've got your dream monitors out, dear friends
I want you all to call the Willa Dobbs here
At 823-7490
If you have any questions
I'm sure you don't
I'm sure you've been reading your book of the subgenius
Religiously
And I do mean it that way
I'm sure that you've been listening to the Hour of Slack
Almost your entire life
So, you know, I don't think you would need any extra assistance here
But if you do, please do call
1-800-9500
Yeah, or
Either one
And friends, for one hour
You have got in front of you right now
One hour of that precious slack
The slack
That you've been needing so bad
And you know
You know you needs it, friends
You knows you wants it
You got to
Got to have it
Now, buddy
I know it's been a long haul for you
The system should be running some figures now
And the vitals
If you're still in the green
We'll do the memory test
And restore it a con to you, Cap
And take 51
Okay
We're ten-eight
And the number is 180
And the letter is G
There's no other possibility
And all you slimy fruitcakes in San Francisco
Are going to find out
How to get to 180
And the letter G
I repeat
There is no other possibility
There is no other possi-
The number is 180
And the letter is G
The first thing you have to do
To get over to 180
And the letter G
Is to get into your vehicle
And you're going to have to get over to 180
And head east
I repeat
You have to head east
Over the bridge
But before you get onto the bridge
Around one big turn
You'll come up to the place
Where the sex chemicals burned up
I repeat
And what he's talking about friends
He's talking about the subgenius foundation
Cause we had to burn up those sex chemicals
To save your soul
You understand what I'm saying?
No, no, no
You don't?
Friends there's no other possibility
On your way to 180 and the letter G
This is negative land that you're hearing right now
But I'm going to switch over here to
How Time Flies by David Austin
And now, and now, in
And now we're on the
Hello Mark
You are A-OK
Punch up
B-M-F
You're fine, no problem
Perform
Basic manual function
Perform, yes
Well I'm a radio announcer
I'm a host
You are A-OK
I'm A-OK
Not to voice
Operatism
On the hour of slack
That's a subgenius church show dear friends
It seems that a lot of people have been
Rolling tape
Tuning in on Sunday nights
Who don't know anything about the church of the subgenius
And you think I'm going to tell you over the air?
Forget it
You can call the Will-O-Dob
So at 823-955-FINITE
Or 899-025-SERVICE
And in the meantime we'll go to this lovely song here
By, we don't even know his name
We used to call him Doug number three
There's so many Dougs in the church
An old drinking song
Roughly recorded but beautiful and stirring nonetheless
Forgive me
I want to die for God
I want to die in holy, holy thrills
The faint voice and the normal spirit
If we have to, if we have to
God will give things and die
And we'll all come back over
Turn around
Pray the gods
Pray that we'll all together
Here in the church
We are nothing
Letтрas
The church may be
If we can make them die, and we'll all come back over men, we'll all come out over men.
If we don't come out over men, we'll be no reason why.
Our wives, gizms, they will fall beneath our laser blades.
And we'll all come back over men, we'll all come back over men, we'll all come back over men in victory parade.
It's so sad.
The rest of y'all is funny Bob stuff.
The funny stuff being the show.
Just listen to me, me, me, me, me.
It makes me feel like I don't know if I ever really did believe in Bob.
You know, the word cult derives from the Latin colo, to worship.
Now, we tend to use the word in our looser sense, applying it to almost any sort of organization.
Yet, in its best sense, it should be reserved for the naming of strange and weird religious sects.
Normally, when we speak of cults, we think of odd foreign religious societies.
Such as the leopard men of Central Africa, the death-dealing pygmies of the Congo, or the Haitian voodoo groups.
But there are hundreds of odd cultist societies in our own country.
Most recently, the snake worshippers of certain obscure sections of our country have occupied the news.
By no means are these all.
But recently, investigators of the unusual uncovered one of the strangest of all cults in California.
It was called the Left Coast Church of the Subgenius.
No, you didn't.
Yes, I did.
An apostate group which contradicted each other constantly.
They rose in the morning to trumpets and drums.
I've been having trouble with my apostate, too, lately.
Yeah.
You gotta put...
Itches.
You gotta keep a stick of broccoli in your butt, too.
See Jerry Lewis as the playful proctologist.
That's right, Lewis.
Doctors for Bob.
Everything...
Exploding softly.
Doctors for Bob.
That's a myth.
Oh, Bob, why'd you let that pickup run over my wife?
These are questions which are difficult to answer.
Speaking of Doctors for Bob...
During the Roman Empire, seven million years ago,
enormous chunks of cheese floated down from primordial glaciers.
And friends, you can, too.
Yes, just like...
If you'll just reach down your own throat, grab hold of that abnormality gland,
yank it out.
Give it a good look and say,
say, here's a listener.
Then put the pitiful, bloody object in a box and mail it to Bob.
Or call 848-45-FUSH-NURL right now.
No, you can't call that number, that 828-FUSH-NURL-405.
That's ridiculous, because...
I mean, what, like, you want answers?
Answers?
You may wish to God you'd never ask, dear friend.
Oh, you'll get your answers, all right.
But Dobsian Hermeticism all too fully explains man's...
place and purpose on this earth plane,
this hierarchy of universal cruelties.
Of course, probably the least answerable question in history,
here answered to be, dear friends, is,
why are we here?
Why do we have such a huge capacity for pleasure and confusion?
Just so we'll keep breeding fast enough
for some mindless, long-range, perpetual motion mutation?
Oh, if only it were so, dear friends, if only it were that simple.
What set everything going in the first place before the Big Bang?
Oh, this question terrifies the water out of us if we really grasp it.
Oh, we instinctively grab for some pose, some cause, crutch, drug, or religion,
even another person that would let us ignore this hideous mystery,
that would create alibis for our failure to find a purpose,
and that would make us feel like we're in a world of chaos.
Although there are some who frankly don't give a hoot,
and those are the lucky ones, dear friends,
because the concept of infinity is so hard to get viscerally
that when we look up at the night sky, dear friends,
we tend to actually think of the stars merely as randomly separated,
inexplicably backlit holes punched in some huge backdrop
about a mile away from us.
And yet, every now and then, we actually get a feel,
for the distances and the times involved.
And glimpsing that fact of eternity becomes real scary
if you really get a solid grip on that insolid abject nothingness of God's brain.
God's brain, dear friends.
What scares you is that you might actually be God,
and you might wake up,
and all those fragile physical laws might come crashing down around you,
and you might be able to see the spiderweb framework of all reality.
Even your friends' thoughts might be erased like some precious
but stupidly unlabeled cassette tape like this one here,
never to be recaptured again.
In fact, the idea is so scary that the goal of most religions, dear friends,
is to preserve and elaborate on that concept of the stars as a big painted backdrop.
They make infinity a prop,
so you don't have to think about the scary part.
And this religion, the Church of the Subgenius,
is indeed about that scary part.
The part you can't think about.
You can grasp it only through direct knowledge,
seeing, one might say, the nature of slack.
Because without slack, there can be no infinity, and vice versa.
Good Lord, you say, but it exists only inside our heads, after all.
This veil of illusion isn't real, for God's sake.
At least not until somebody says,
somebody slams the outside of the head with a truncheon.
Then you could probably call it fairly real.
This is Sister Cress you're about to hear,
not from this station, but from another subgenius radio show.
That's right.
Oh, listen to that.
Oh, yeah.
I told you.
This is WFMUFM.
The scary part and the sexy part.
You just heard a half hour of...
This is KMOR.
...an hour of slack from...
...the Subgenius Foundation.
I think you start to assess life.
Which you can get lots-o information
by writing and sending at least one dollar
of conspiracy Federal Reserve currency
to the Subgenius Foundation,
post office box 140...
But don't send a dollar to us.
Dallas, Texas 75214.
Send that dollar to KMOR.
Please send it to us.
We'll just give it to KMOR.
Approximately a half hour of the Subgenius tape
is featured here on WFMUFM East Orange.
But you get a whole hour here on...
Sister Cress.
...in Dallas, Texas.
Here.
And children, you want to know
what the biggest abomination there is
in this sick and perverted world?
It's not homosexuality, cross-dressing,
or any other supposed perversion.
No, my children.
The truly biggest abomination
is the conspiracy dupes
who call themselves feminists.
They're the ones who foist their ideas
of what women should be doing,
thinking, and feeling.
They have the gall to preach
that women should be in positions of
quote-unquote power in the government
and other organizations of the conspiracy.
Let me tell you that no uber woman
in her right or left brain
would want to have any kind of power.
She would want to have anything to do
with ruling a world that's heading down the sewer
in a motorboat steered by a drunken child actor.
Feminist conspiracy also wants to censor free speech
in what they call pornography and exploitation.
Those midget brains don't realize
that they're being used as distractions
by the conspiracy.
Distractions from the real porn
of mediocrity and slack piracy.
These are the true, true...
...
True crimes against the state.
Conspiracy-dupe females don't realize this,
and they think with blinders on.
True subgenius uber women
don't pay the conspiracy-fashions any mind.
We know that magazines like Vogue and Cosmo and the like
push the conspiracy concepts of feminninity,
which is controlled by the old,
trilateralist, fogies
and their young, whiz-boy offspring.
But we don't lower ourselves
to a state of angst-filled frenzy,
let alone join a group that is comparable to some
to a myopic cockroach that attempts to challenge a professional exterminator.
Subgenii are not joiners,
and uberwomen are the most notorious lone she-wolves of the non-type.
We don't follow anyone.
Not even Bob.
Praise Connie!
Je-
Hello there.
This is Simon from The Cure.
Hello, Dallas, Texas.
This is Jerry Dale McFadden.
Howdy, this is Bob Walkenhorst of the Rainmakers.
K-N-O-N, the voice of the people.
Yeah, it sure is K-N-O-N, the voice of the people, folks.
And, uh, you know, it's funny.
Once again, we're getting all these dang blabbit calls
from people that have never heard.
I can't believe that there's people on this planet
that have never heard of the Church of the Subgenius.
Don't know anything.
Don't know anything about it.
They go, now, wait a minute.
Are you guys serious?
This couldn't be for real.
Because they figure it's too good to be true.
Don't you?
That's what you're thinking.
Yeah.
Well, if you just call in one more time,
18-
Well, I know I'm from here.
Talk to the Will-O-Dobs,
and, uh, get a little information.
Find out, you know, what you'll get
when you write for information.
But you don't want to hear any more about that.
Anybody listening down there?
I've got a terrible backache here.
That's right, Mark.
Now, on the Red Channel,
read the system you're vital.
Mark.
Mark T.
Captain.
Signs of Life.
Green.
Elapsed time of sleep in 24-hour units.
Yes, the listeners are just finally waking up.
And finally we find out just...
Let's listen to this little piece of, uh,
recorded music.
This is recorded material from Ken Nordean,
the incredible, brilliant Ken Nordean.
Got a minute?
I'm sure you do.
I'd like to talk about, um,
the movers and shakers.
Yeah, go ahead.
Yeah.
The movers and shakers.
Ha, ha.
Those people
who more than anybody else
have ever been.
Yeah.
Determine what's gonna happen.
The movers.
And shakers.
Shakers.
Yeah.
Who get things done.
The movers.
Who call the shots.
The shakers.
Who make a big difference.
The movers.
The power to control.
Shakers.
They got boss power.
Yeah.
They're the movers.
They got the power.
They determine policy.
They're the shakers.
They got a good deal of respect.
They're the movers.
Yeah.
They're the shadow behind the scenes.
They're the shakers.
They got the power.
Yeah.
They're the movers.
To raise major amounts of money.
Yeah.
They're the shakers.
They can select.
They're the movers.
What will be put before the largest audience.
They're the shakers.
Oh, significant social and financial power.
Yeah.
They're the movers.
The theater.
Yeah.
They're the shakers.
Pop music.
They're the movers.
The movies.
They're the shakers.
Classical music.
They're the movers.
They're the movers and shakers.
Yeah.
They're the shakers.
Those who wield influence.
They're the movers.
What you see and hear.
You.
No otherwise, they hear.
They're the shakers.
They're the movers and shakers.
They're the movers.
Movers.
Shakers.
Am I brand new?
ool.
Shakers.
They're the shapers.
Ladies and gentlemen, the movers and shakers.
I am a shaker.
They're the shakers.
I used to be a mover.
But I became a shaker.
The movers and shakers.
You can't move without shakers.
Any shakedown is necessary before anything moves anywhere.
The movers and shakers.
So the shaker goes out and gets the money.
The real money.
The movers and shakers.
You don't think these big movies are made with pennies?
They cost millions and millions of dollars.
The movers and shakers.
There's a lot of money involved.
Yeah.
You take a big symphony.
You don't think a big symphony lives on peanuts?
The movers and shakers.
They don't play that beautiful music with nothing.
It takes money.
The movers and shakers.
So the shaker goes out.
Shakes a few of those shackles out of the people's pockets so we can favor these things.
The movers and shakers.
They give it to the mover.
And the mover makes things move.
The movers and shakers.
Without the movers and shakers.
What would these artists do?
The movers and shakers.
What good is an artist?
If he doesn't have a mover or a shaker on his side?
The movers and shakers.
Now if you are an artist, you need a good shaker, get in touch with me.
I know all the movers and shakers.
But you got to have a good shaker to begin with.
What it's all about.
Moving, shaking.
Got to get into it.
What it's all about.
Movers and shakers.
Oh, you got to find out what it's all about, dear friends.
And that beautiful, beautiful song there was by Ken Nordine.
That's it.
Triple Talk by Ken Nordine.
And friends, you're still calling in once again.
You're still calling in to find out just what's going on.
Oh dear listener, a querent into the profundities of the moment.
of this twisted randomness that we so stupidly call reality?
You ask us over and over on the phone,
is this some kind of joke?
Oh, friend, if you thought this church was a joke,
then you will by God never get the punchline.
And this could be the greatest joke ever told, dear friends,
if Earth, if this planet can make it to the punchline.
We're the first to admit that on a good night,
maybe not tonight, maybe not a scary night like tonight,
we deliver a lot more laughs and yucks per listening dollar
than Scientology or the Unification Church
or any other religious group except possibly the Southern Baptists.
But, you know, as funny as they are,
they're there for brain death, and we're against brain death.
That would theoretically, friends,
put a bounty on our heads, except that we trend the thin...
We tread, we tread, friends, that thin, tight wire of the jokes,
just enough not to so far have been covertly killed or bought.
My God, friend, look what they did to our predecessors.
Anyone who kept a straight face.
No, this ain't no joke, friend, no parody.
Only the foulness of your programming
keeps you from believing that we have thousands of minutes
to make a show about the subgenius.
which we do in the Church of the Subgenius,
that we have nationwide revivals,
radio shows in different cities and so on,
but we do, and not only are we not kidding,
but we'll even, shall we say, tick you off.
Because that's our job, dear friend, our calling,
our mission for Bob, J.R. Bob Dobbs,
and we're going to shock the hell out of every man, woman and child
on Bear Creek if we have to.
It's a big job, and we only have until 1998 to do it.
But, uh, friends, you want to know
what the Church of the Subgenius is,
and there ain't no description.
Words don't suffice.
One must see.
We let you see a little at a time
until you're led gradually to total clarity.
This is the Nameless Mission,
as Puzzling Evidence called it, friends,
because the true mission is always nameless.
To name it is to doom it, to alert the enemy.
Just don't buy your doomsday theories.
Well, you better buy them.
We are in worse shape, uh, from the point of view
of our military preparedness than we were on the 8th of December, 1941,
the day after the Pearl Harbor attack.
The Russians got the definite advantage of us right now.
We need to show more strength.
We gotta catch up or get ahead of them or we're dead meat.
Exactly as Noah getting under the ark triggered the deluge
that destroyed the earth in his day,
and that it's very highly possible that when this all takes place,
that a great cataclysmic, uh, disaster will come.
And that a cataclysmic judgment will do that very thing.
And we do not know that it wouldn't happen in 1982,
for we don't know what day it'll happen.
This article was referring, as I said,
to the nine planets in our solar system,
Mercury, Earth, Mars, Uranus, Pluto, Jupiter, Venus, Saturn, and Neptune,
uh, when these are scheduled to be perfectly aligned in 1982,
that these things perhaps could happen.
Many scientists with varying ideas of what could happen
have expressed their views that huge solar flares will take place, results, and the future.
And they also said that there should be a great deal more
uh, that could be disruptions in the television and radio communication,
and a great deal more.
I see that I'm not gonna have much time to go into this anymore today,
and so I'm gonna carry it through tomorrow
and try to bring it to a more clear climax,
but may I tell you that all of these are warnings to us
to repent of our sins and to get ready for the coming of the Lord,
for we can see great and drastic things that are gonna take place on the earth
when Jesus comes and the judgments of God
are being poured out upon a Christ-rejected planet.
world. Well, after we come through here and we purify through this plant here, it takes out some
of the chemicals in the mud out of it. But you can't drink. We can't drink it. Nowhere in the
world you can drink it unless you hold your nose.
It'll also tell you about the prelude to Armageddon and also some of the strange events that have been
forecast for 1982. Some of the things that are coming in these last days. You know, the future is a
magnetic place. Each year, a hundred billion are born into it. Why, it seems all roads lead to tomorrow.
Why, just looking at the future is enchanting. Prowse along conveyor belts where awe-inspiring
holograms are as much a part of the experience as they are the future.
The future is the experience of every man as were the real trees, mountains, and sunsets of the dark past.
It's thrilling to wander amidst these realistic 3D images and you'll certainly feel at home since the
leaders here have chosen the architecture of the mediocratons of the middle class ages as the most
relaxing and appeasing of all art forms. It could be the old world charm of suburbs and franchises
or power plants and office buildings which might suddenly change to lovely forests and
homes.
But wherever you go, you're still amidst the clean, ever-changing holograms of the future.
Made possible by the amazing hologram projectors and the careful planning of the
folks behind the scenes. And it won't put a dent in your budget since holograms are produced in economical black and white.
You might even get to see a rare hologram eclipse when your real surroundings become enjoyably apparent.
We are already in critical difficult days. Please, let us know if you have any questions.
We've got a lot of things to tell you.
If you don't move, dear friends, don't go anywhere. Yes, because you're stuck here listening to what's going on.
And, oh, we've got a dastardly, evil future coming up.
If you don't get right with Bob, see, that's what this is all about. You've got to get right with J.R. Bob Dobson.
And if you don't, you are doomed, doomed and damned forever, dear friends, because the church of the church of the church is doomed.
the subgenius is Bob's church. As the million-legged church crawls around inside your cranium,
there's one point that we'll keep coming back to, one anchor, the very point of the church,
and that point is Bob, friends. Bob is, was, and ever shall be world without end.
Oh, friends, Bob is the Kama Sutra, the id, the light that glows in the heart and mind of every
free-thinking subgenius, and friends, Bob is a man, and Bob is slack. Bob is you, and Bob is me,
dear friends. Bob is slack, and slack is what you want. Slack is what you need. With the fullness
of slack, dear friends, a change will come into your life. Slackness will enter your life,
as the Pope of New York once preached. Slackness will make you see. Slackness will set you
free.
Free, dear friends. Slackness is. Slackness lives. Slackness waits for you, and yes, send $20.
With electronic bait, man is nuclear efficient, and the fish on his line is bigger in his mind
than the reality of the reel he has to reel it in. You shouldn't have bit, fish.
The one that got away is the catch of the day. You shouldn't have bit, fish.
You took the bait, it's too late to pray. Now over you, they say the grace. Lord, bless the fish.
Oh, you can't even be sure you're seeing any of it.
Miles, you and I are scientific men. You can understand the wonder of what's happened.
I just think, less than a month ago, Santa Mera was like any other town. People with nothing but
problems. Then out of the sky came a solution. Seeds drifting through space for years took root
in a farmer's field. From the bottom of the river, the seeds of the river flowed through the river.
From the seeds came pods, which have the power to reproduce themselves in the exact likeness of
any form of life. Your new bodies are growing in there. They're taking you over, cell for cell,
atom for atom. There's no pain. Suddenly, while you're asleep, they'll absorb your minds,
your memories, and you're reborn into an untroubled world where everyone's the same.
Exactly. What a world. We're not the last humans left. They'll destroy you.
Tomorrow, you won't want them to. Tomorrow, you'll be one of us.
I don't want any part of it. You're forgetting something, Miles.
What's that? You have no choice.
No. And our children will live, Mr. Beale.
To see that perfect world in which there's no war or famine or oppression or brutality.
One vast and ecumenical holding company for whom all men will work to serve a common profit
in which all men will hold a share of stock.
All necessities provided. All anxieties tranquilized.
All boredom amused.
The chemical.
moments just like these.
казado
All the vandals watching
We watch him back
We see right through his disguise
He tries to scare us with angry words
But we all know that they're lies
The world is waiting
Just see the fear in their eyes
The world is watching
And so's in every mood
Is it forgetting or the end?
Just like the chess game
But so intense
That I just don't understand
Anticipation
It's not too big to pretend
And now it's 1984
White top but we've been here before
White top it's 1984
Here before
They're gonna scream me
But we don't care
Cause he's got nothing to say
And now they're gonna scream me
We didn't mean any harm
We just wanna go
And now they're gonna scream me
Now don't sort
This is a warning
Danger, danger you poor devils
Things are more mixed up than you ever dreamed
What was up is down
The priorities are all screwy
You're fretting if your hair looks okay
While some new kind of bladder cancer is coming up
And it's bursting out the front of your designer jeans
Yes this is bad talk
Nobody will listen to anything else
You won't look at TV unless body parts or cars are jiggling or crashing on it
You won't taste your food unless it has some nerve drug in it
You haven't used your other senses since you were five
And you sure as hell won't stop what you're doing
Until someone much bigger, much stronger
And much, much more self-assured makes you stop
And you'll thank him for it
And then just before you fry in a flash of radioactive hindsight
You'll realize that he stopped you from doing the wrong thing
Good God
What in the name of sweet screaming Jesus is this world coming to?
People itch, people gripe
This is a sign of the end times
That's a sign of the end times
When you should all be hollering
It's all a sign of the end times
Two months ago the observatory
Issued a press statement that the world was coming to an end
Now that's the same story the cult of the book of revelations had been preaching
Now when a scientist backs that up it's new
Our conclusions have nothing to do with the cult
Well today we deal with Bible prophecy
We have two free features we want you to write for right away
I wish my mommy did not smoke
How you can have the miracle you need in August of 1982
There may be a book of revelations
That reflux in the fighting between the Arabs and the Jews
That will be a temporary peace
But the word of God tells us
We can expect nothing but trouble and turmoil in the Middle East
Until our Lord returns to be the Prince of Peace
Bob
It's been known for some time that the fossil record contains several very pronounced mass extinctions
When large numbers of quite unrelated species
From all kinds of habitats appear to die out during a relatively short period
What they're saying is that you have say an asteroid about 10 kilometers across
Impacting on the earth at a speed of about 40 kilometers a second
And the energy involved in such a collision is equivalent to some unimaginable quantity
Such as I think it's about 100 million megaton atomic bombs
It's that sort of size of explosion
Did you hear?
Did you hear what he was saying?
If you can't get slack for yourself friend
You sure as hell ain't gonna be able to give it to somebody else
And that's just what they have you trying to do
They
The conspiracy
Those who are trying to pull the wool over your eyes
You can't think
Everything's going wrong
You're so tired
The kids are driving you crazy
Your spouse lost another job and is drinking again
You're supposed to have an operation and you don't know where the money's gonna come from
It just doesn't seem worth it anymore
There's no one to talk to
You don't know if you can hold up under all this
You're not sure if you want to
You're ashamed of the things you haven't done
And you keep thinking about those pills
Put a dog in a cage friend and he'll run away
He'll run in circles
Put a man in a cage and he'll run for president
And it's the same thing
It's the conspiracy dear friends
And you can help fight the conspiracy
By giving your money to KNON
Yeah money that's what it comes down to every time
And I could say something about money in the church of the subgenius
But this is a public, public supported station
And we don't want to
We don't want to get into that totally
But friends you know it's
Church of the subgenius a joke
Funny, funny, funny
Ha ha ha ha ha
Well I think it's time to
Well I think it's time to stop for a while
Because my headache's getting bad
I'll put you another song on here okay?
Alright
One, two, three, four
No lights
No people
No speak
No cars
No people
No food
Stop
Shut
Grinding holes
Everything's coming to a grinding halt
No sound
No people
No clocks
No fine
Behind
No people
Because there.
Cause I love you
No people
Because I'm not
Shots
Grinding holes
Everything's coming to a grinding halt
Ok
This is how I his
Mostly
So
Uh
guitar solo
Slow down
Oh yeah
I have no idea who sent that piece of music
Everything's coming to a
That's what it's coming to
A grinding halt friends
And that tape ran out
I don't know who
I don't know who did
That was sent to us from
The Green Hell
That's what we call
The Dobstown 2 outpost in Malaysia
Deep, deep in Malaysia
Yes, you know
You've heard of Jonestown
In our own sick sort of
Cosmic joke humor
We decided to name our jungle encampment
Dobstown
And you think I'm kidding
When I say there's a subgenius encampment
In the jungles of Brazil
Oh yeah
Yeah
Well there's more going on
In that one little silly campground
Than you've got going on
In the whole city of Dallas
When it comes
And friends you can get more information on that
If you just write to the number
I'll give again at the end of the broadcast
And once right now
Got that pencil ready
It's Bob dear friends
J.R. Bob Dobbs
Church of the subgenius
At P.O. Box
Glen Rose, Texas
Wild Ice
And several of you
Have called in and said
I want to hear more Devo
I want to hear more Captain Beefheart
Well
Well the thing is
Devo and Captain Beefheart
Are great
But they were left
A little bit
I don't know
You can't say that
Nobody
People of the world
Of that stature
Don't get left behind
Dear friends
But you owe it
To both
To the spirit
Represented by Devo
And Captain Beefheart
Both
To pay attention
To this tape
I'm about to play
By an Arkansas band
Called Doctors for Bob
Now you may think
Oh well they're from
They're from around here
They can't be as cool
As Devo
Because they're from
California
Although they're actually
From Akron
Or Captain Beefheart
Oh man
He's got an album out
He must be cool
Doctors for Bob
Don't have an album out
They can't be cool
No one who doesn't
Have an album out
Could possibly be cool
You say
Listen
Listen to my tale then
But why
Why will you call me mad
Could a madman
Have written songs
Such as these
I think not
I'm not mad
I'm merely an ordinary person
Seeking life
Liberty
And peace
In the pursuit of happiness
If my pursuit of happiness
Includes machine gunning
127 innocent children
If that's mad
Go ahead
Lock me up
Just because I enjoy
Washing my face
In the blood of infants
Is that any reason
To lock me up
I think not
I've even got
A piece of paper
That says my mind
Is still okay
Hell I bet that guy
Down at the employment
Agency
Wouldn't give me a job
Just cause I've been
Locked up one time
Bet he ain't got
Those papers
Says his mind
Is still okay
Hell
But I tried to tell them
It was not me
It was the green energy demons
But they merely laughed at me
But now those
Green energy demons
Are ruling
The planet
They're not laughing
And fighting so hard
Now are they
But that wasn't
Nearly as bad
As that time they
Shocked the living
Gee out of me
I tried to explain
It was not me
It was the brain
The brain of Arnold Palmer
Which was controlling
My mind
Via laser beam
Via the FBI
Via the CIA
Via the Communist Party
Via satellite
It was the demon
The demon
That forced me
To do the deed
But that wasn't nearly
Dot dot dot
But I
It wasn't
I'm not insane
I'm more sane
Than son of a bitch
Than son of Sam
And Charles Manson
Put together
How many people
Must I kill
To prove I'm not insane
But that wasn't
Nearly as bad
As that time they
Shocked the living
Gee out of me
Well I didn't mind
When they shocked
The living
Pee out of me
In fact I kind of enjoyed it
When they shocked
The living
Zee out of me
I mean that time
They ran over my face
With a
Pick up truck
Oh yeah that was fun
That time they cut me in half
With barbed wire
And then peeled a bandaid
Off my
My amputated arm
Oh yeah that was fun
That time they skinned me alive
Then called me dirty names
Woo ha
That was a big ol' cocaine party
That one time
They converted my entire body
Into a wall of membrane
Whose only purpose
Was to feel pain
No that time they
Converted my entire body
Into a wall of membrane
Attached to a human brain
Whose only purpose
Was to feel pain
And then applied the flame
Oh yeah that was fun
That time they converted
Every cell in my body
To the same nerve endings
Found in male testicles
Enlarged each cell
To the size of a sun
And then inserted huge
Sun sized dentist drills
Into each of these
Sun sized male testicle cells
Woo ha
That was the time of my life
Compared to that time they
Shocked the living
Gee out of me
Oh yes dear friends
That's Doctors for Bob
From Little Rock, Arkansas
This song goes on and on and on
But unfortunately cannot play
The entire song
Because it becomes
A frontal lobotomy
I'm okay
You're a frontal lobotomy