Ah, it's all coming back to me now.
And now if I do this...
Fast! No time for the stairs! Out through the wall!
No time to find the entrance. I'll just drive straight to it through the solid rock.
No time for opening windows.
Clark Kent may need a plane, but Superman doesn't.
Here's Bob One for A1 Slacks.
Hi, I'm Bob One for A1 Slacks, and I'd like to take a moment of your time.
Thank you.
And I'd like to tell you about the nice folks down at A1 Slacks.
They handle a needle just the way your mother used to,
and the results are racers, capers, tapers, and bummers, such as you've never worn before.
The Action Man's Go-Go Now Generation Happening Slacks for the Go-Go Now Generation Action Man on campus.
And off.
And remember, you can get a good education and win valuable prizes, too.
Thank you, Bob.
You're welcome.
And now, back to our movie.
Wherever there is mystery, intrigue, romance,
in all the strange and bizarre,
dangerous places of the world,
there you will find
Bob.
It's chaotic.
No sack.
Yes, yes, finally, we can do it.
We'll actually have friends.
My microphone broke, and Bob made me come into the station.
He made me keep working, and so we're doing it.
God damn it.
From the very station itself.
As the...
If I push this button, now, theoretically, this should bring this noise up.
No.
Praise Bob.
The fates have brought you into possession of a subgenius instructional video barrage tape.
Prepare yourself.
You are about to be remade into a new being through forbidden knowledge previously kept
secret for centuries by the jealous priesthoods of many religions.
Caution.
Improper viewing techniques may lead in some persons to dependency.
seizures, cranial fits, priapic conditions,
micturition, stern mutations, subtle glandular mutations,
and in some territories, legal arrest.
However, if the viewer follows instructions and trusts completely in Bob,
this tape can produce an unsurpassable beatific experience
that can last for hours, days, weeks, possibly even centuries.
This videotape bears a patented Dobbs Drome PowerShell time code,
which may cause some home videodecks to react unpredictably.
Although only a small percentage of playback systems or their owners
have suffered permanent damage from this signal,
the Subgenius Foundation Incorporated is not responsible
for injuries or damages inflicted by paranormal events during tape play mode.
The tape also contains a subliminal hypnopediatrics trance-inducement tone
operating beyond the range of human perception,
which is a very common problem in the world of video games.
However, pets in the viewing room may exhibit unusual behavior,
as may small children and certain less evolved adults.
If such behavior anomalies last more than two days after viewing,
consult a physician.
However, this brainwave-infolding signal is generally harmless
and should actually enhance your learning abilities during the program.
Special interactive, homosonic stereo effects
produced on the Ultomate Cerebral Synclock Interocitor
trigger stem cleavage, or brain division,
between the forebrain and hindbrain.
Using newly discovered break-thinking principles,
the viewer's brainwaves are locked into synchronization
with the tape's underlying suggestions by means of neuroelectric pulses.
Plant growth and gas mileage of nearby automobiles may be affected.
For the unworthy, this tape may be a one-way ticket
down a bottomless mental pit from which there can be no escape.
In unreceptive viewers,
there is a danger of synaptic backfire in the brain pan
caused by overheating of the attention gland.
This dense packing of brain cells without proper organic coolants,
such as FROP,
has been blamed for three recent cases of spontaneous human combustion.
Do not overmedicate.
High dosages have so sensitized the third nostril receptors of some viewers
that they were unable to stop seeing the tape even after it had been turned off.
This tape is to be used only by the person
to whom it is prescribed.
Do not operate a motor vehicle following viewing.
Do not operate heavy farm machinery at speeds over 70 miles an hour.
The demons you may see during the initial hallucination sequence are not real.
If you do not panic, this phase will end after a few minutes.
Always resurface from the hypnosis slowly.
Coming out of the tape has been likened to a total rebirth process,
if managed correctly.
If you have trouble re-entering the earth plane,
focus on Bob and chant his name until you remember your own.
Bob and Bob
Bob and Bob...
Bob and Bob ...
Bob and I....
Bob and Bob Duran!
projected. These reactions
are normal. Enjoy
them.
Mom?
That's your key phrase.
It will trigger the entire message
without your being aware of it.
Three, two,
and one.
Now to continue with the
recording.
Ah,
yes, dear
friends. Welcome back
to the subgenius
radio ministry.
Hour of Slack.
In this case,
number nine hundred
and thirty
two.
Nine hundred and
thirty two.
That's two, two, three,
nine, three, two.
Blonde.
Squids.
Fiery, fiery squids.
Yes, squids.
It's the squid fight time.
Time for
Matador Dave
to move out into the ring
and fight the enraged prairie squid
as it is tortured
and pestered by the men on horseback
with their little squid
prickers.
He's waving the psychedelic
paisley cape in front of the
enraged squid as it
paws the ground with its tentacles.
I see a sign from the
netherworlds.
Look, his neck is bleeding, too.
His neck is breathing?
Yes.
That's a bad sign.
Yeah, not so bad when the lungs
go right up off the top.
Look.
He's more capable than the other one.
That's no prairie squid.
That's a triceratops.
My God, these creatures
supposedly went extinct
over ten billion years
ago. And yet there,
lonesome cow I gave, ready to fight.
This is what we call time control, dear friends.
My suit of light is vestido
de lute.
Time control.
And it appears that he is ready to pull
forth his muleta. The muleta is for
tickling and sparing the bull
before it's entreated and
made of the turpid. That's a bull squid
you're talking about. It is a gigantic bull squid.
I've never seen someone with such a large...
Yeah, that's a bunch of bull squid. You're talking bull squid.
Okay.
There's a lot of leavings behind on this one
so we hope it's a slippery fight for a lonesome
swine boy in the hole of a...
Oh, that's right. Lonesome Swine Boy is here, right?
Oh, and I didn't mean him. I meant the one on the microphone.
Yes, Lonesome Swine Boy. Not Rob. Rob is Lonesome...
That's Lonesome Bovine Boy.
The one with the huge dripping ears.
Lonesome Char-Boy.
Anyway, friends, we're... Yes, we dragged the Dave thing and the Princess Wee and the whole thing.
We dragged our muscles.
Everybody but Bob down into the studio.
And what we just heard earlier was, in fact, yes, the introduction to the Arise subgenius movie, which is now on DVD.
Yes, so you can... Well, you can hear the improved soundtrack on this show.
That's what I've been playing.
The new...
Improved soundtrack from...
You can replicate your brain cells, too.
It's new and improved.
Yes, it's as easy as remaking your liver in a pie.
Brain cells grow where they want to.
A friend told us last time you had you a great big steaming hot polo.
Wolf brand hair liver pie brain cells.
Well, that's too long.
Well, that's way too long, friends.
Sit down by the old campfire and share the spell.
Grandma's going to bring you heaping and humping.
That's right. Take off your hat now.
And let's see your hands.
Oh, boy, you're not ready for eating that yet.
You got to get down there and wash your hands off.
Remove your cuticles.
That's right. Pull your nails right, right on.
Ow! Ow!
Okay, now you all...
I noticed you're getting a little bit of trouble back here by the mastoid bone.
Pop out some of them wisdom teeth, too.
Okay, okay, enough of the pornography, you guys.
We don't need any more live...
We've heard enough live sex in this show.
Remember, we jump from thing to thing real fast.
Here's the other thing.
Me!
Obviously, the problem is, the less you know, the more...
And this is very true.
It's easy for me as an old fart to say this about kids.
The less you know, the more sure you are of what you do know.
And contrary-wise, the more you know, the less sure you are of any of it.
Thus, my very weak beliefs, you know, and fluid, you know, believe-me-out-of-it routine,
with the aliens giving extra time to the crop circle makers,
and those of us who are...
Finally inspired skeptics.
I, one time, was in a situation where everybody else at the trailer court saw the UFO.
And I was standing out there, and I didn't see a damn thing.
Now, how am I supposed to take that as a defined message from the aliens?
Obviously, not to believe it.
So, you know, we'll stick with the contradictions that make good sense.
Thank you very much.
I have never been able to get into this comforting, post-modernist mumbo-jumbo,
because I'm kind of a post-mumbo-jumbo as myself.
I've heard it all.
Screw the new age.
No blood for snake oil, I say.
And kids, you should leave world domination up to the crop professionals.
Gluing, as Chris Brooks' son said,
gluing feathers to your ass does not make you a rooster.
So, you know, they're just kind of chill.
I used to believe strongly in the afterlife,
because I've been to several Native American seances
before I suddenly, one day, realized how they did it.
And some people really...
I mean, the afterlife is a beautiful thing.
A lot of people say that death is great,
although I've noticed that most of the people who say that are not actually trying yet.
And the ones who have, haven't been getting glowing reviews, everybody.
They're getting very quiet now.
Who are they trying to hide?
Good.
Can you say it faster?
I can do anything.
Here we go.
The theory is that all matter is composed of at least three fundamental particles.
Protons, electrons, neutrons.
Protons are charged positive.
By now you guessed it.
Electrons are probably negatively charged.
Neutrons don't follow either.
Neutral in the middle.
Only no apologies.
Centered, unmoved by yin and yang ideologies.
Neutron bomb songs.
Electron theory.
Dozen musical radio activity.
Different points in your brain.
Within infinity
Oxygen and hydrogen alive
Within all types of energy
Inside a world inside a world inside a universe
Inside of me existing although I can't see it
See it
Hydrocarbon, nitrogen cycle ionization
Heavier than electromotive metals that weigh over a ton
This has been the chemist black a licious creation
Clean out your desk put your papers away
Cause class is almost done
All aboard for the night train
This is chemistry
Plus calisthenics
Calcium plus potassium
Magnesium use paper of sodium
Sulfate your solvent chloroform
Remedy from the normal
Glycerin puristorm titanium
Brain is blown away I want this new
Fee a sound of water or vibration for me
That I need that's I'm legit
Contagious and leegious
And equal to be a system media
You're eager to be here and leave you can see it
I know what I'm going on I'm thinking
I'm thinking I'm streaming I'm going on
I'm thinking I'm going on
I'm going on
And that was in fact black a licious
Here is Bob1 for A1 Slack
Hi this is Bob1
Years ago my grandfather Abner1
Known for short because he was
Invented the A1 Slack
However today's go go action now generation man on campus and off
Wants a little more out of life
So we added another leg to our super slim trim fitting A1 Slack
And came up with super slim trim fitting A1 Slack
A1 Slack's the two legged action slacks for the two legged action man
Thank you Bob
You're welcome
And now back to our movie
And what was that movie
I can't remember
It was the movie that
How old was that movie
Oh trip to the far east
Trip to the far east is the tonight's
Hell hole feature
I believe this was
Fire sign theater
In Singapore wasn't it
Remember the fire sign theater Dave
I unfortunately remember them coming to my home
Dressed up as little little
Wise men
It was on a Sunday just before Christmas
Do you like me remember every fire sign theater line from every comedy album they did
Only when reminded
But do you like me hate the people who quote fire sign theater lines incessantly
Yes I abjectly
I strangle them while they strangle me
And then they start quoting each other backwards
And there's even more fist fights ensuing
Luckily the fire sign quoting people are far outnumbered
By the Monty Python quoting people
Which is much less embarrassing to me personally
That's embarrassing to me
Because I don't
I do not want to be reminded every five seconds of the scene where the guy rips off his arms and stuff
And says oh excuse me or whatever it is
Yeah
You know I've actually put
I've put a person's eye out
Of his own misery I suppose
Because it was an errant prisoner convict eye but
Speaking of early influences and
And limbs that have been removed
I was thinking how many bands that I know and hang with and record
Who were
Whose primary influence seems to have been the Three Stooges
Well of course
I was thinking about it Devo, Gwar, the Amino Acids
Last night we saw Man by the way
By the way that reminds me
We have a subgenius revival coming up
I wouldn't want to recommend that anyone
A thousand years from now
Go to it
Yes luckily it's a long ways off
Thank Dobbs
It's not until May 22nd but we did call the Beachland Ballroom
And they said that they would allow us once again to go in there and preach
That's Memorial Day weekend
Yeah and all those people will be post hoc by then
May 22nd
Yeah
And they're at Saturday night
I thought it was May 29th was the weekend
At the Beachland Ballroom in Cleveland
Oh you should know you're a government
I don't think so
No in Cleveland is where we're doing it
Well thank God you know
Because you know the softer the conscience sound
The easier it is to get over
Yeah
On the people especially if they've been consuming the stuff
But they were going to let Man come to that
Even by the who is now Man Incorporated by the way
It turns out there was a band in England called Man
Well don't worry they'll emasculate him sometimes
For the last 30 years
They'll find his family jewels
Right
And try to bite him off
Soon he'll be
That's what they do
Woman Man, Girly Man
Yes
And the Amino Acids who are the most Three Stooges influenced
Thrash surf band that I know of
Aguar not being really a thrash
A thrash band but not a surf band
Well the Clocks were so
The band I was in in the 80s early 80s
Was so Three Stooges influenced
That one time after practice
The bass player was doing Curly
And he was going whoop whoop whoop
And doing all this stuff
And we were like you know smoking and drinking
And just like errantly half paying attention to him
And he fell down
And this is a true story
He fell down
Oh my goodness
And he was in a pool
And a flower pot landed on his head
The flower pot broke
Are we not mad
Leaving
No the flower pot broke
And we call it the slapstick miracle
Leaving the flower on top of his head
Suddenly everybody was paying attention to him
And said what the
Are we allowed to say the other word
No
What the heck you know
That's never really happened
Like just like in the cartoons
In the cartoons everybody their jaws dropped
Their drawers dropped
And of course their eyelids were drooping
There have been
A surprising number of cartoon like events
Oh my god
That's in my life
Well you were a heroin addict for 14 years
So that explains a lot of these
Things that you call
Cartoon experiences
Dave Dave
I was an ex-lax abuser
And I was
Well that's what you like to call you modern people
I was self abused
I've read there's a
You can't perform a colonoscopy with your own arm
I mean come on man
You know you've done a lot of strange things to yourself
Well I found that out the hard way now didn't I
Yeah you did
I guess we all did
And we shouldn't have attended
Now you were about to tell us about some onion article
That you had read that was
Well it made me feel a lot better
Apparently there's a hell of a lot of people in America
Who a lot more than anyone ever thought
Who are victims of self abuse
And most of them don't report it
That was the big part
What I thought was the interesting part of the article
You don't want to tell on your partner
Because then you know
They'll never want to talk to you again
It said 99%
99% of men do not report
Their self abuse
When they're self abused
Now Rob for instance
Whose show is after
Well he's part of the 1%
That does report it every time
But the interesting thing was
And he's been warned by 911
To stop bugging them
Only 87% of women don't report self abuse
Isn't that weird
Leaving yes
13% do
See it shows
Actually brag about it
The more equipment you have
The more things you have to clean
The more you know
Things you have to like
Put weird polishes on
And stuff like that
So you're better off
Like with your fundamental equipment
Which is a tool bar
A crow bar
And a rectum
That's good
But I have to
No it was not
It didn't have to do with that
I'm sorry
I have to play the news now
Alarm Santa Fe parents
Met again with elementary school officials
Last night
To discuss the growing presence
Of Bob in the schools
Bob the deity
Of the Dallas based church
Of the subgenius
Is a comic book character
Who communicates with aliens
And worships money
Parents and teachers complain
That the Bob stickers and pamphlets
Which have turned up
In school laboratories
With increasing frequency
Encourage troublemakers
And weird behavior
It's not healthy for the children
I'm convinced of this
There has been a pamphlet going around
A Bob pamphlet
That I have looked at
And it's the least well adjusted children
Really
It tells them
The impact of the pandemic
On the world
They're so uncomfortable
With their classmates
It is because
They are better
Than their classmates
Can you imagine this?
Better
Can you imagine that?
Not smarter mind you
But better
Not smarter
What kind of
Syllogistic logic is this?
It's the logic of Bob
My friends
Bob's got a better deal
For you
A logic of a heart
So stuffed
Full of cheese
And so discorporeal
That no one
Can believe
In its existence
Obvious
He's got something
For you
That you can't
Even imagine
Imagine friends
Bob loves you
Oh Bob's loving you
And he's got something
For you called slack
Imagine the kitty cat
In the wells
Crying out to you
A little small baby cat
Perhaps only with one good eye
And perhaps muffled paws
Crying out of the well
Save me
Bob
He's got better things baby
He loves you
He's got
Like the what?
The Holy Ghost and the Fire
Yes
They consume together
And he'll make you sing like this
Now they're like a lot more
Oh I'm sorry
They were singing about Jesus
No they're singing
They are singing and
Jesus may actually have better things for you than Bob
They're singing
I don't know
I'm going to go see that movie about Jesus
I understood he was like a real tough dude
Well, he was into steroids and stuff like primitive Roman steroids.
He used to eat like palm clusters and force his way with goats and sheep and stuff like that.
The Lord?
The Lord, of course, was a robust, raw bone.
He was a prince of love and peace.
He loved the animals.
He loved the children.
He loves you, Dave.
Jesus loves you right this minute.
Piece of bladder, piece of neck, piece of arm, piece of mutton.
Jesus didn't care about the poor folks.
He just wanted a piece.
Yes.
Peace.
The prince of peace.
Are we being blasphemous?
Blasphemous?
You haven't taken your palsy medicine today.
It looks like your knees are shaking.
Sit down, honey.
Stop disturbing the reverend's things.
I can't do it.
Don't, don't, don't.
No reason to raise your voice.
You'll get all full of sweat and tears.
We'll take care of it.
I'll have a talk with him.
You know, we don't have nothing against Jesus.
It's just some members.
Members of his fan club occasionally make him look bad.
Jesus and Bob are old drinking buddies from way back.
And I mean way, way back.
Way back before the wheel was probably even conceived of.
Back before the way back machine was even invented.
And that was before.
That is impossible.
I know, I know.
But yet, and yet, that's the way it is.
It's the way back.
It's like a five.
It's, I forget, what number is it again?
It's like a time machine that keeps coming back and reinventing itself over and over and over and over.
Over and over and over and over again.
And look into the bright mandala.
And see the shining, glistening, smelly, yet urbane face of pooper M.G. Harvey.
Then that Robert Tofty arm.
Blah, blah.
Is this the surrealist part of the show?
This is the part of the show where you're expected to become very sleepy.
Wave your hands.
This is the part of the show where you'll contact your secret.
Self.
Gaze into my pointed goatee.
This is the part of your mind that is unregulated and wired.
Follow the bushy eyebrows.
Or the veil.
The blue brush.
Beneath the sandy exterior.
What the hell are you talking about?
Is the very hideous interior where the soul resides.
Which, is this what makes it all look so ugly?
And smell so funny?
And yet, it's an eternal object, the soul is.
Immortal.
Permanent.
Unchangeable.
It's the same soul from life to life as it hops from one birth to another.
Yes, I'm going to watch the manifestation of the chi going down through the different meridians.
I'll go through the triple burner all the way down to the spleen.
And then all the way back up again.
Like a huge.
Huge highway of chi.
One lifetime reborn as a cockroach.
Another time as a Shaolin priest.
Another time as a piece of software.
A photoshop improvement or something.
A sleepy woman on a bus won't wake up.
There are many forms that consciousness may take.
And each one of them represents the active part of.
Part of.
Yes, friends.
Represents the active part of.
An act of will.
Will is what will bring time control into you.
An act of will and the right kind of rock music playing loud in the background.
Corny enough, rock band will make even your terrible film soundtracks sell.
Everything will coalesce.
Look at those credits rolling by.
Everything seems so effective and yet so unreal.
I'm still excited by the last thing I just saw, which was.
Mom?
Wise up.
They're out to get you.
The difficulty was smashed by a global conspiracy.
Weird men arise.
Find out who they are and how to smash them.
You probably already knew that the U.S. government is a sham.
Something propped up there for you to blame.
But did you know that the real powers that be are not even people?
That they are actually shambling?
Unbelievable, unmentionable, unthinkable things?
Yes.
Jehovah is an alien and still threatens this planet.
Defy the sinister star forces which mock us all.
Evil demons have kept the truth from humanity for thousands of years.
God has been misquoted all this time.
His actual words may disturb you, but Bob Dobbs is a bulwark against the unbearable fear and anxiety tormenting mankind.
Repent. Quit your job. Slack off.
The world ends tomorrow and you may die.
A six million year cycle will end in 1998.
Dobbs sees the world entering a new aeon.
Which, in a few years, will bring more wondrous and miraculous change and carnage, insanity, and destruction
than all of mankind's history and prehistory before it.
Bob brings a new destiny for America.
A time of cataclysmic economic change that will offer untold riches and power to those in the know.
While billions of deserving conspiracy dupes fry in hell on Earth.
Uncontrolled thinking, controlled by Bob, will usher in a spiritual rebrief.
And it can't be.
A cascade of astounding mysteries, supernatural riches, and a restoration of lost psychic abilities
that will totally transform the lives of those who dare to seek them and pay for them.
That's right. You're lucky to live in the end times.
Here's more money, Bob!
Ah!
I'm so lucky!
Ah, yeah.
I'm very lucky.
Well, I think the world, uh, owes us an apology.
And not only a living, but an apology for sure.
A living, an apology, and a firm handshake, and I think probably a spare preternatal eyeball somewhere we could put, where we could look behind our heads.
And that's what Rammstein here is trying to tell us. Let's just listen.
Super deep!
I love you!
Ha! Take my hand in the painting!
Ah, ah, ah, yeah!
Don't you dare whine about my head!
You're not gonna be such an old whore!
Ah, ah, ah, yeah!
All women are the same!
I'm a nice girl with a very pretty body.
I love kissing.
Yes, man.
With my blonde hair I always got a golden ring and all kinds of things.
Why? Tell me why!
Why are women so stupid?
They're not necessary and forbidden.
I mean, I don't need them for cooking, because I have a strong sense of humor.
And for clothing, they don't need it either, because I have the same suit on anyway.
So, take my hand in the painting!
Ah, ah, ah, yeah!
Don't you dare whine about my head!
You're not gonna be such an old whore!
Ah, ah, ah, yeah!
All women are the same!
Well, honey, what do you think of it?
You know what? Give me your number!
Next week I'm gonna get my bra on the floor and come and get you!
You're a whore!
Oh!
I think it was a conceptual zygote.
I have a weird idea, which is...
Bubblehead...
Yeah, see, we're on the same wavelength.
She said bubble?
It's a love song, I think.
You know, I have the potential...
We have the potential of doing a theme show about love.
Oh, okay.
Because I've got a bunch of beatnik love songs.
Beatnik love songs?
Yeah, beatnik.
You'd recognize...
There's a Lenny Bruce...
Oh, yeah, cool.
Edward Burns, Sheldon Allman...
Oh, all those people.
Ed Kooky Burns, I suppose.
Yes.
The guy with the extreme...
That's right.
Here, let's go ahead and see what...
Really out there, dudes.
...how it works.
Days became weeks.
The weeks, months...
That's Lenny.
...and the numbers on his great chart representing experiments mounted into the hundreds.
And gradually, the lines grew farther and farther until the numbers on the chart reached
666 and the lines were the width of the chart apart.
I am a...
...a voice that no man on earth has ever heard before.
I am not a...
J.R.
...a...
It's me?
Could it be?
I've only known you a week, but I die for you.
That's kind.
Oh, my God.
That sounds like the...
Listen.
I warned you it was a trap.
We'll never again see Dixon alive.
I told you not to trust foreigners.
Just give me their word and I'll blast them all into kingdom come.
You must...
That's good.
He's only one man.
The rest of us are different.
Are you?
Yeah, like the one with the forehead.
From another part of yours.
We are trying to reach you,
planet three.
We are trying
to reach you,
planet three.
Shut up.
Can you understand me?
Okay.
Thanks, sweet Adeline.
Really, Mr. Donaldson, what a ridiculous request.
You think the best scientific brains
in the country worked for six years for a brother?
Peter
Adeline.
Parents.
Good Lord, man.
Open your eyes.
Okay, here's a love song by Sheldon Allman.
Hark to my tale
of a very tragic love
most grievous
to relate
to star-crossed
lovers
with a perfect love
they could not
consummate
their love was
constant, their love was
true, but of passion
it was devoid
for he
was a univac
mark two
and she was an
XF-1
humanoid
she gazed
at him and a tear
was in her eye
to her love was denied
her lover stood
for mighty stories high
and he was
one block wide
how could
they do the impossible
their love be
enjoyed
when he was a univac
mark two
and she was an XF-1
humanoid
and each to each
on wavelengths ultra high
they whispered secretly
of transistors
and gears and shafts
and cams
and printed circuitry
and so
time passed for the two
of them
in the place where they were
employed
where he was a
univac mark
two and she
was an XF-1
humanoid
oh hush your sobs
my pretty little miss
and dry those
oily tears
you know that robots
can't afford to cry
for it surely
rusts their gears
you must give up
all these thoughts of love
though it leave you
an aching void
give up on this univac
mark two
and find you
an XM-1
humanoid
un hu man oi
better punchy than 98
I'm being mushy and everything
now I don't know
if I was doing the same rat last year
that involved a
a list of thirteen priorities in life
yes
Yeah, some people saw that.
It was, you know, you're going to be middle-aged, and you start going, well, wait a minute.
I'm going to make a list so I don't forget something important.
I had been forgetting some important stuff.
Slack was only number seven right on the list because the tie came after breathing, often forgotten number one, drinking water, peeing.
The kids don't even think about it.
Eating food.
Shitting.
I mean, think about it.
These are priorities, friends.
You're not going anywhere until you've done those first four or five.
Sleeping, which you had another one.
Finally, money came somewhere after Slack.
And then you're back and offering, and then sex.
You're back and offering.
You came before sex.
If something against her, say, that's real funny.
You will see.
Bob and sex weren't even in the top ten.
Some might, actually nobody noticed, but I noticed.
The word love was not on that list.
Love wasn't on that list.
And when I realized that, I went, oh, I guess I really am an asshole.
Then I remembered, I don't want too much applause, please.
Thank you.
You know, quote, love is the word itself.
It's corny, just that word.
And also, friends, let's face it.
It's painfully obvious that it's possible to live for quite a long, long time
without ever having any love at all.
And we are surrounded by assholes who do that very thing quite spectacularly.
However, Slack is completely open-ended term.
It means something different for every single person.
And it's usually comprised of very vague elements.
Most of them aren't even spoken or not easily put into words.
And for some of us, love might be in that mix somewhere.
In fact, I suppose that for some people, Slack and love might be indistinguishable.
And I don't want to demean those for whom hate is Slack, praise Bob.
There should always, always be equal hate around.
You know, we...
But there was one of the younger preachers, Reverend Alex,
the ex-day, was enough of a wuss or man enough to verbalize the love-Slack comparison.
And it was kind of reassuring to see somebody do that
because hate-Slack has been really well covered by the subjugus experts over the years.
I don't need to rub that in.
Jack said,
andmp inequalities are so smallon us.
I'm going to tell this.
Mrs. So traders don't buy that control at all.
In fact, I've known those traditional dishes
and drug chokingmer laws for way too long.
I feel pulled off.
No, I really am.
Anyway,
our fucking together
we have to burns in a hangout.
Co CoR
Like, I don't want to swing without you, baby.
Like holy mackerel, kingfish.
And.
Be hip, baby, I'm jelly.
Like I've had big eyes for you since we popped at the hop.
I mean, I get sounds when I think of you.
Like sky-fi.
Ooh, doobie-doo.
Zip.
Like, no, baby.
This is your love burger from the other AM.
Man, it was a wig.
So far out, like I'm still orbiting.
Shazam.
Irwin?
No noise like that.
Let me straighten you.
The drive-in movie.
You and me on the backseat of my motorcycle.
Wow, Jepica.
I mean, I thought you were driving.
Cool, cool, cool.
Tony.
Baby, let me clue you.
Like, you're my leader.
Let's do a double gig.
I know crazy coffee pans.
The Dad Class.
What they got today, I can't even ride.
Don't talk, Jepa.
Don't think you know anything about aprs-bicamente,
with kids who bleep up your numerous
coworkers on everything.
Yeah.
Come on.
Marsha? But this isn't Marsha.
Is this sunset 77777?
No, this is national 92600.
Uh-oh.
Well, don't bug me with details, baby. It's my last time.
Just clue me where you live.
This is me, Kooky.
Wow, crazy, huh?
Question.
I depend on me.
Throw your.
Hands up at me.
Roll your hands up at me.
Roll your hands up at me, girl.
I didn't know you could get down like Charlie.
How do you angels get down?
Girl, I didn't know you could get down like Charlie.
How do you angels get down like that?
Question?
the backpack backpack.
Okay, further
inquiry on... Anyway, friends,
that was, uh, that last song
was by
something called Elbow.
I download this
stuff from Alt Binary Slack.
Oh, Dave's ripping off
the conspiracy again.
Yeah, they keep selling them.
Would you quit ripping them over there, man?
The minute you turn 50, you start getting
all those retirement,
American Association of Retired Persons.
Now, the minute you turn your
real nature back to the first
time it ticked, man,
that's when it happens? Yeah, baby.
Yeah, groovy. That was Edward Burns,
by the way, Kooky Burns, doing
the Beatnik love song.
Beautiful.
The Univac Inhumanoid song, by the way, was
Sheldon Allman.
He's all man, but not as manly
as man.
No, as loquacious as a man with a dog's
throat. What a singer.
Well, I've heard that
many people who want to sing and
to talk better, or to have more
fluid movements with their larynx, are
now having dog implants in their throats,
so they can yodel like a bright poodle
or perhaps a...
They can locate each other's
pack members by
a cry in the pines.
But then wouldn't you need an ear transplant
so you could hear those high-pitched
tones of only dogs in here? Well, yeah, it can be done,
but what happens is you've got a huge open
space on the side of your head,
which kind of remembers, well,
resembles, not remembers. It can remember,
though. I mean, it does have... That's the part that can
remember. It does have self-memory, but anyway,
that's another story.
It makes the ears like lupine,
kind of like leprechaun-ish,
and a lot of people cosmetically...
Yeah, wolfish.
Like, uh...
Well, it's a dog's life,
you say? It's more than a dog's
life. It's a dog's entire
continuously reincarnating
existence. There's a wonderful
disease that
goes with it as a dog-like
appearance called
discoid lupus. It's a skin disease.
And it causes hirsutism of the
clavichord and of the
precerebral area. Well, actually,
it's anti-hirsutism because it makes
the hair fall out. It makes your hair fall out?
Yeah. Oh, how doggy. Can that be... See?
Ah, like a chihuahua poodle, yeah.
Woof, woof. I mean, it looks...
Yeah. You dog. You're trying
to grow, like, canine incisors out of the top
of your forehead, too. He's a dirty dog.
He's a dirty dog. He is a dirty dog.
And must be reprimanded
firmly and constantly
like a sleeping cow.
Phew.
I think there's something wrong here
tonight. I don't want to put my fingers
on it. I can tell you what it is.
There's something that happened. I don't know what it is.
We were doing a show
about love, and then it turned into
dogs again. Okay. But you
guys earlier were talking about how...
Discordians. We...
And discoids. Oh, the beatniks. Right.
Discordians on accordions. The beatnik stuff.
By the way, Discordians,
there's a biography of
Cary Thornley, who's one of the
founders of your religion. Cary Thornley.
I met him once. He was a mentally
ill man. As most Discordian
founders are.
Yeah. Well, and...
But there's a... Adam Go-Rightly
has a book out now telling the
true, full life... Actually,
judging by what he says about Church of the
Subgenius, it's not a true story at all.
I'm wondering if it's any kind of
story for us to be telling here.
I don't know. But what about the beatniks,
man? Screw the Discordians. They're
taking care of that themselves. The beatniks.
Princess Wee and I, when we were
about 12 in separate
time zones, saw
this... And you did, too. That Mad Magazine
issue that
had a magazine within a magazine
about beatniks. It was a beatnik,
fake beatnik magazine. It had some
skin cells in a little hyper
pack that was also connected
to the back, along with the 45. Remember the
45 record? Right. It had a little fake 45.
A 45 flexi disc. Yeah, and you could
rub those skin cells on your noggin
and say, if you wanted to... And it taught you how to
talk beatniks. Right, right.
Now, when I was
12 years old, I saw that,
so did Princess Wee, separately,
and thought, beatniks.
What are beatniks now?
These people that sit around in dark... That's Winky Cat.
They drink a lot of coffee. They read poetry.
They play weird music and they say weird
poetry. Play the bongos.
They play with their fingers and stuff like that.
Sometimes they crunch their fingers.
They wear black turtlenecks.
The basic thing was, they were
weird, and as 12-year-olds,
we thought,
man, I want to be like that when I grow up.
Now, there was an interim...
I got to be like 12 and 13,
I discovered politics, and
most 12-year-olds,
people of that mentality, I was very
conservative. Right, you want to be a eunuch with pimples.
It goes with the 12-year-old
sort of level of understanding the world.
You're automatically pretty conservative.
Just as you become after
you're 50.
But...
It's when we understand everything.
Right.
You know everything when you're 13.
12 or 13. I certainly did.
I've since then forgot it all.
But...
Then it was like the hippies came along,
but I didn't think the hippies were cool
until...
The nostril implants.
What was it I was...
Easy Rider.
The Scourging.
Which was kind of stupid.
He doesn't even remember the Scourging.
Monterey Pop, which was not that big of a deal.
But Head Comics,
Zappa's first album,
Freak Out, or It Can't Happen Here,
or something like that.
Freak Out was first.
And Hendrix's first album,
Are You Experienced?
All that stuff came out, and suddenly I kind of went,
oh, this hippie stuff is...
It's like science fiction.
It is a...
a phenomenon
in sociology.
Hold down your head, Dr. Morris.
I'm about to fix the electrode to your scalp.
As it turned out...
Soon you'll be seeing the sprite mandala
in the center of your skull.
The sad thing was that they let us all down.
It wasn't science fiction.
It was just another beer commercial.
It was. It is a beer...
It was.
And I was too young to be a hippie.
I really didn't get to be anything but a 70s drug brother.
And then punk came along.
I was actually kind of punk before my time,
and that wasn't science fiction.
No, it's very cold and gray.
But...
It's abject.
But I was a little too old to be a proper punk.
And so what was...
What could we be?
We were three butts of geniuses.
Two, the beatniks wouldn't take us.
The hippies thought we weren't cool enough.
The scum thought we were too cool.
The punks didn't hate us.
Didn't think we...
We were put out.
Hardly spoken to.
No one gave me directions on the bus, man.
I've been waiting three hours.
They patted us with all fur and refuse.
Oh, yes. More than rocks and garbage.
They hit us with sharp, pointy things.
They beat our knees
with metal objects.
They made Stumpy hide.
They made Stumpy run.
And hide in his little Stumpy Lens.
He had to run and hide.
Save my knees above the one hand.
Now Stumpy has power.
Now Stumpy has...
They've reintroduced the same freaking stupid idea.
...his precious.
And now Stumpy shall lead the mutants,
the ugly, the poor, the stupid, against the lucky.
The handsome, yes.
The rich, the educated.
We shall bring them down.
We shall force them to learn.
Like the smegma they are.
They shall be left in the pool of fire
like the insects and lower vermin they be.
Each one of these children grown to full manhood or womanhood
shall be cut down in their prime.
The world shall go under the sire.
Oh, yes. The worm shall turn.
The worm shall turn.
And you're listening to Hour of Slack number 932.
If you want more information about J.R. Bob Dobbs
and the Church of the Subgenius,
just check out www.subgenius.com.
And you can always write to us at Post Office Box...
Well, you can write to me personally, Reverend Stagg.
Post Office Box, 0181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
44118.
Oh, yes.
And so the coffin of Dobbs is lowered...
Bob, Bob Cranford.
...into the great concrete tomb.
Bob Cranford.
The blubbering and snotting of the mourners...
Friends we are gathered...
...of Slackless, those left Slackless by...
...and Sam Paul...
...as Dobbs left this earthly plane...
...he can write to our friend, our dear, dear friend,
Robert J.R. Bobbs.
My God! My God, man, he's risen!
Look, he's rising from the grave!
Stop!
Well, that was...
That was exciting.
It was very anti-climatic.
I'm going to put back...
Let's get back to the Arise Subgenius video soundtrack.
Now that it's on DVD, it sounds a lot better than ever.
By the way, this background music is from Bride of Frankenstein.
I forget the name of the composer.
Since I didn't acquire it exactly the way you're supposed to,
there weren't any liner notes or anything.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
I remember back in the day when I was on a college radio station.
Oh, man.
It's great.
Everybody should do it.
Well, now, but with this great vehicle of the public airwaves,
shouldn't we be, I don't know...
Serving the public?
Edifying the public in some way.
Exposing the shenanigans of bad politicians or...
I mean...
How about those...
We're just talking about the necessity...
Necessity...
And the conversation always turns to bad movies.
I just don't understand.
How about that...
Are we geeks?
What kind of word is that?
Is that what that means, pathetic geeks and weirdos?
What?
Is that why they throw rocks at us?
Pathetic geeks and weirdos.
Is that why we've been...
Don't talk rot.
Alien sex?
We can talk about alien sex.
Pshaw.
I mean, that's the thing.
Is that why those villagers are heading up here with those torches?
Would we be able to talk about, like, alien sex for hours on end?
I mean, that would be, like, edifying to the government, to the world, to everybody, wouldn't
it?
Well, except that there's so many shows that talk about aliens taking over the politicians.
You know, that stuff...
That stuff was old with the X-Files.
And even the politicians taking over the aliens.
That's old, too.
I mean, it's the opportunitarian-capitalist.
There's no Chancellor.
There's no Richard
Carter.
You tell now?
True.
I tell now.
And that's why GPS has gone through these things.
Yes.
When the full moon rises and the drums start to beat in the jungle
and the serpent god Dumballa raises his hooded head.
Child of voodoo.
That's a little tacky to me.
The dark world is superstition.
Yes.
When the full moon rises,
and the drums start to beat in the jungle and the serpent god Dumballa raises his hooded head.
Child of voodoo.
That's a little tacky to me.
The dark world is superstition.
Oh.
The beautiful world.
The world of superstition.
Friends, that was Norrell Preff.
Praise Bob.