I haven't thought of you in 15 days and today I still won't think of you.
And when I call you up and you're not home, well I might not even care.
Every day gets better than the one before cause every day I know that I'm fine without you.
But I don't think about it, this one is not about you.
You can put that in your pipe and smoke it, this one is not about you.
Maybe you can take that to the bank and shove it up your big fat ass.
Every time I ride past your house I forget it's you who's living there.
Anyway I never see your face cause your window's up too high.
And I saw you shopping at the grocery store but I was far too busy.
With my car to notice.
You weren't looking at me, this one is not about you.
You can put that in your pipe and smoke it, this one is not about you.
Maybe you can take that to the bank and shove it up your big fat ass.
Music.
Add it on a tape and tape you gotta maybe have your hands up.
Was it mention about me or the other?
It could be whether I'm not even close to being close.
Yeah it could be.
It could be something like this.
It must be.
As VK has done with the lyrics, maybe he is telling the truth.
to the bank, shove it up
your big fat ass.
Well, you gotta watch out.
This could lead to dancing.
Bob and Connie really enjoy life.
Hello.
I'm Trademark G of the Evolution
Control Committee, and this
is your listener license
agreement.
This is a legal agreement
between you and the Evolution
Control Committee. By listening
to any portion of this musical
album, you accept and agree
to the agreement.
You should be bound by this agreement
and its terms and conditions.
You also represent that you have
heard and understand all of the
provisions of this agreement.
You must accept this agreement before you
can listen to any portion of
any song on this album.
If you do not agree to the terms
of this license, stop
listening to this album now.
You should refer
to the album liner notes for the full
text of this agreement, but the
most important part is this.
You may
not listen to this
album. You are
forbidden from listening to
this album, in whole or
in part. The ECC
disclaims all other warranties,
express or implied, including but not
limited to the implied warranties of non-
infringement. The terms set forth herein
are exclusive and in lieu of all others,
oral or written, express or implied.
In no event will the band
be liable to you for any
incidental, direct, indirect,
punitive, actual, consequential,
special, exemplary, or other damages,
including any claimed or
perceived infringement of your
copyrighted materials by the ECC.
And now,
the Evolution Control Committee presents
All Rights Reserve.
Press
stop now.
boom boom styrofoam
n the
mont
r
z
dem
from
California dreaming
On Central Avenue
Stopped into a church
I need
I began to pray
For life's
The call
He knows I'm gonna stay
I'm gonna stay
I began to pray
On Central Avenue
Stopped into a church
I began to pray
On Central Avenue
Stopped into a church
I began to pray
On Central Avenue
Stopped into a church
I began to pray
On Central Avenue
Stopped into a church
I began to pray
On Central Avenue
Stopped into a church
I began to pray
On Central Avenue
Stopped into a church
The amino acids will also be there
and nowhere else forever
except other
subgenius live stage shows
Before that, an old Bob
and Kirsten
Connie clip from MST3000, titles by The Large, and the song that started the show out, Not About You,
was by Jonathan Colton from his Thing-A-Week project, the third disc, I think. Colton, by the
way, is spelled C-O-U-L-T-O-N, no relation to Colter. Another song by him listing all of the U.S.
presidents and their accomplishments is also coming up. You know, friends, after two months
of not doing a weekly show, it's been a bit of a challenge to get back in the swing of it, but
swing we shall. We have enough new music by unsigned and unsignable bands, and we still
have recordings from two major devivals that haven't been exploited, Starwood and the New
York City Devival, but the latter has a ton of cussing, and I'm running late, so I think that
for this show, number 1,299, we'll start using the Starwood recordings and mash them up with
a bunch of mashups. This will be the mashiest-upped show in a long time. And so...
Let's take another caller here. You're on the air.
Hey, Rob. Princess Wee. Princess Wee. I need to hear from you.
What was I thinking?
That's okay. That's okay.
I was trying to rob the bank. Yes, I was trying to rob the bank. That's right.
It had nothing to do with you, Dr. Sinister.
Nothing whatsoever.
Nothing at all. I just wanted to give a report, because we're celebrating...
Drinking Pink Lady.
We're drinking Pink Lady in celebration of the best Starwood I've been into for at least five years.
Well, that is great to hear. And it's
funny you should mention drinking Pink Lady, because I played a track called Pink Lady Lemonade.
Yes, well, Starwood was really successful. We had a beautifully attended subgenius
defiable. We thought that... Princess Wee and I had thought that as organizers, we'd be faced with
days of brutal heat and putting out fires. But instead, the volunteers had the whole machine
running just fine by the time we got there. Very well.
So we got to spend half the time in air-conditioned comfort and the other half frolicking and
lighting fires.
There you go.
And it was a new location. It's gorgeously beautiful. It looks like it should have dinosaurs
running around in it, like Jurassic Park. And it is full of cave...
Speaking of dinosaurs, did Hal go to Starwood?
No. No, but lots of old hippies did. And you can call some of them dinosaurs. And I think
they're pretty cool.
Hal actually was performing at the Museum of Natural History in New York City.
Yeah, so he was working with dinosaurs.
So he was working with dinosaurs. But yes, we were working with another sort of dinosaurs
at Starwood.
I heard Wee-steria was a fun place.
Wee-steria?
Yes, that was a typo that I made. I may not even have told you about it yet.
No! You didn't tell me about that.
Wee-steria Campground is the site of Starwood. And it turned out to be just right. You know,
it was scary because we had six months to find a new location and scope it out and dare
it to work. And it did. It worked just fine.
It did! It was a miracle.
There were pterodactyls flying overhead and hippopotamides spouting water up out of the
pond. A filtered water pond.
Incredible.
Yeah.
And it's a real pretty place. It is a long drive. It's four hours from Cleveland.
Well worth it. Well worth it.
And it's not in the middle of nowhere. It's in the middle of a cool cannibal redneck town
where they have these friendly people and little barbecue places. They're ready to,
if you stay there for very long and have a meal or two, you're going to be the meal for
the rest of the clan.
And there also are Amish and Mennonite folks around. So it's very similar to the brushwood
that we're used to. That kind of area. So hot though.
Hot enough to smell the livestock?
It was, yeah, there, you could smell some of the naked seniors, if true. And just as
at X Day, there's no rules.
There's no rules against feeding the naked seniors. But if you do that, you know, they'll
be attracted to you and they'll hang around.
Yeah.
Sick.
We had to be firm with the naked senior hippies.
It's a good thing you only had a limited number of subgenie there compared to the general
population. I mean, one of the horrors of X Day is you have these mutants and these
animals and people feed alcohol to these animals. That is frightening. Which is a little bit
of a surprise to you.
Well, it's the only time of the year that we let the beasts out of the cage, you might
say. Whereas it's true at Starwood, it's just, it's really a bigger zoo. It's a huge menagerie
of all kinds.
Indeed. That's a well said statement.
It's not Burning Man. And no one's being sued and nobody gets killed.
Yeah.
It's a lot easier. And it's no X Day because at X Day, everybody gets complete and utter
total slack.
Oh, yes.
It's in between Burning Man and X.
There's a much bigger variety of kinds of people at Starwood.
People, yeah, sure. People, yeah.
Well, I'm talking about different colored skins of people and so on.
There's a lot of weird...
Weirdos.
Yeah.
And some of them don't wear their shirts, including the females. That's a big attraction
at any of these kinds of festivals, I would say.
Yes, indeed.
I'm really excited about this next... I hesitate to call him an entertainer. I'm even more
nervous to call him a prophet, though he does profit bringing stuff up. My goodness gracious,
this man has meant a lot to me over the years. He's a beautiful man. He's a strange, very
strange man. So strange, in fact, that he had to start his own religion when I was
one.
Congratulations, gentlemen, to the electrical, the electrical, the normal, and the fortunate,
the one and the fortunate, the only Trevor Snyder!
Yeah!
Bravo!
I have...
Oh my god, that was very, very nice of you guys.
What's up?
I have to say, I've come to just say thank you, man.
Speaking of which, that is Eric Pompao, the director of The Athletic, there's a good use
of her out there.
department but we have to do this to prove well when the aliens up above
smell the smoke of the burning dollar bill there no there's still somebody
down here on earth worth saving ah and there's still enough of it left to spend
see we may be subgeniuses but we're not totally stupid totally are there any
weirdos here tonight what what a surprise oh did there happen to be any
messed up weirdos here tonight oh messed up weirdos help again I'm amazed
are there any fucked up weirdos on drugs here tonight on drugs and alcohol then
tell me praise Bob oh that sounds good now we can get going
ha ha ha star this is a different star wood for one thing it's late at night I
normally do this in the afternoon I can't see y'all's faces
I can't hear you it's different not like that jacket I'm wearing it tonight
I imagine by now most of you have either seen that movie avatar or you've seen
enough commercials that you more or less know what it's like I have a one-sentence
review of the movie avatar my first star wood that's my one-sentence review and
and you know what I'm saying I'm not going to lie to you I'm not going to lie to you
I thought this scene was going to be a different story than you do on drowned
Republican you know your first is always your best or your favorite my
first star way it was in 1990 at Brushwood and back then they didn't have
a stage at all they didn't have a pool there were I don't think there were
showers or flush toilets and yet it still went great it was what was a
a wonderful Starwood.
I had an incredible time and I've been
back 20 times since then.
And will
continue to do so.
Now there was no huge video
crew there and there were a lot fewer people.
And this Starwood,
there's not a huge video
crew and there's fewer people
so maybe this will be my
best Starwood yet! Praise
Bob! Praise Starwood!
Praise Reverend Fat Mandy
and her band that was just
up here. She performed at X Day
last week, but the less said
about that the better.
I'm going to do what I
usually do here, kind of
a three part program.
First I'm going to give you,
for those who have
not yet comprehended
the Church of the Subgenius,
I mean it's a no brainer,
I will give us kind of a
truncated, actually it's a new version of
Subgenius 101.
There is no Subgenius 102.
Then I will make
fun of the Starwood program
book. That's one of my
that's always really
easy. And
if we can we'll do a
question and answer thing towards the end too.
Meanwhile,
now see I
can't see
you and I can't make eye contact with
anybody so I'm
just going to go ahead and read this thing.
I'm not even going to try to pretend I memorized it.
Do people think you're strange?
Are you damn normal?
Are you different?
Do you urinate?
Then you're sure to be interested in this
my friends. If you're ready
to slide down the cutting edge
then make noise and praise Bob!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Not bad. Oh they're from all over the
campground distance stereo.
That's good.
The Church of the Subgenius friends,
it's where today's wisecracks are
tomorrow's divine revelations.
The world's first
industrial church
tipping sacred cows
since 1953.
Instant instructions for
those who follow no master.
And the perfect
self validating
philosophy by which everything
you know is true.
It's been
called the Zorro of world
religion, scratching a bloody
B-O-B on the beefy seat
of the conspiracy. Actually you can
skip the O, just do a B on either side.
The divinity school
of hard knocks.
Peripheral visionaries saving
souls from themselves
and providing something
no other religion offers. Eternal
salvation or triple
your money back.
Of course you have to spend the money first
and you can be ordained at that massive
sales table over there
for only $30.
Price could go up
any second now.
But yes it's true, if we don't live forever
in this religion, we get our money
back. Just think about that.
That's not a bad deal. There's only
three things you need to really understand
about the Church of the Subgenius.
That's Bob,
slack,
and the conspiracy.
And whether
you're saved or unsaved, we
always need reminders about those basics.
Now, who is
this man Bob so many ask?
Friends,
to sell a
religion, you don't need
all the answers. You just need
one good answer.
And J.R. Bob Dobbs
is the answer that didn't wait around for a
question. The key to the gateway
is his pipe, God, Ecclesiastes 3
14. Bob
Dobbs is our self-fulfilling
prophet. Strange and
wondrous things happen when Bob's around.
The blind hear, the deaf
see, false teeth get
swallowed. Poor families
win the lottery. Enemies
drop dead from laughing themselves
to death. Strange
Rube Goldberg type
contraptions spring up around him.
For instance, like if he needs a
shoeshine or something.
Now Bob's not smart.
In fact, he doesn't plan
anything. He just automatically
tunes in on the plan that's already there.
He doesn't think.
You don't use your mind to think
about your religion. He just simply
knows and yet he's continuously
forgetting it.
He only sells and never
buys. He's an
economic monopole, a kind of a singularity
that could power a universe.
And yet he doesn't
actually do anything.
The universe does
things for Bob. Or
it does him.
Or he always does
the wrong thing perfectly.
Because what Bob has
is far more powerful
than the brains. What Bob
has is luck.
Brains have
phooey. In his left
brain there's nothing right and in his right
brain there's nothing left.
And here's another thing.
Bob will not
solve all your problems.
But he will help you
to blow them off.
And you
cannot use him as a crutch
because he's already using
you as a crutch.
He replaces
the drugs.
Just looking at the dots that comprise
his face. So
many brain cells just like using the drugs.
He's the Chinese
finger trap of the mind
my friends. But most important
thing is that he is a short
duration personal savior.
Or Shordirpersav in the
original Tibetan.
This is a society of
planned obsolescence. You know
when you buy that computer
it's going to go out the day
after the warranty.
So
Bob recognized the need for
revolving messiahs.
Anything could be your short
duration personal savior. Whatever you need right then.
You may be your own personal
savior. You might be
somebody else's.
And for that matter
a lot of subgeniuses are loners.
And the great thing about
Bob, he's not one of these saviors
that's always breathing down your neck
going, did you pray to me?
You didn't sin or nothing did you?
No. No you can be
alone
with Bob.
Just think about that.
No maybe you shouldn't think about it.
Anyway he doesn't care about your sins.
He doesn't want to
forgive your sins
but to rationalize your sins my friends.
He brings not forgiveness but an excuse.
And you may now as of this
moment do anything you
want.
You want your sins forgiven?
Well do it yourself.
If you're a subgenius you're probably already pretty good at doing that.
Jesus
praise Jesus
Jesus may have died for your sins
but J.R. Bob Dobbs made a
damn fool of himself
to stand up for the
For your sins.
So he said,
Bob said, I won't tell you what to do.
I'll only tell you how to think.
And you will pay to know what you really think.
And it's so true friends.
Bob sold it, I smoked it,
that settles it.
It's that simple.
He's known for many pithy aphorisms
that you'll see on bumper stickers
also available at the sales table.
Uh, his most
famous saying is
the only law of the church of the
subgenius, the only rule. Pardon my
language kids, but the
one rule of the church of the subgenius is
fuck them if they
can't take a joke.
And uh
he also said the subgenius
must have slack. He said
choose the way you're gonna be screwed
because they're gonna screw you anyway
but some ways are fine.
If you act
like a dumb shit
they will treat you as
an equal.
So pull the wool over your own eyes and relax
in the safety of your own delusions
because too much is always
better than not enough.
Don't just eat that hamburger
eat the hell
out of it!
And the stupider it looks
the more important it probably is.
Science does not remove the
terror of the gods and I don't
practice what I preach because I'm not the kind of person
I'm preaching to.
These are all things that Bob said. He also
said I can't lie but
I promise that I will.
And he asked the question
who died and made me
God?
And finally he said
I'll find myself when they pry me out of
my cold dead fingers and pry my cold
dead fingers out of my other cold
dead fingers.
So um
oh and life after death
why wait?
Now that's Bob! Here's the
number two thing you need to know about Bob.
His promise. His promise of
slack. Now what is
slack? Well the great thing about that is
it is totally indefinable by
everyone except you!
Because it's different for each person.
Totally unfettered by common
sense. Slack is like
something for nothingness.
It's
whatever works for you.
If nothing works
let it.
Uh
because the point is
friends you believe it or not
already have the
slack. But you may not have
appreciated it yet.
You have more slack than you can
appreciate until
it's taken away.
Tricky how that works. You
have it all. You just
haven't believed it
yet.
You make the slack by making
the slight effort to
notice the slack that's already
there. As our
friend Reverend Bleepo Abernathy
said, just when you think
you're along for the ride, you look down
and realize the steering wheel is in
your hands.
So slack
you might say is the state
in which you need
nothing because you have it
already.
Slack is always new.
Always improved. Slack
can only be sold. It
cannot be bought.
And yet you find some
people who are literally working
too hard for slack. Trying to smoke the
pot of slack at the end of the rainbow.
The conspiracy had started
making the term slacker popular
meaning a lazy
indolent person. And that's fine
but slack is not the same
as laziness. It can be
frenzied over work.
I happen to be an emergentile
subgenius and
this is my slack.
Then there's
involuntary slack
which is when some disaster
comes along or what seems to be a
disaster but you later realize
that it snapped you out of a rut
and was the best thing that ever happened to you.
So
the fact that the conspiracy
keeps pushing false
slack on you means that
somewhere there is real slack.
And how do you find your own slack?
Well Bob said you should follow the path
of least resistance.
Surf the luck
plane. Because slack can
come when you throw good money after bad
and bad money after Bob. Praise Bob.
The goal
of the church for each
individual is the casting out
of false profits.
Now before you
go unmasking false
profits right and left you might want
to peel off that thing
you've got super glued to your own face.
But the
conspiracy as
we call it is like a factory
of false profits churning out
the occasional major asshole and
thousands of private assholes
to do their bidding.
Now we're not talking about all the
trendy conspiracies that you may have
heard about on late night radio.
JFK assassination area
51. Masonic
Satanic Pagan Jew
Illuminati
conspiracy. So this is
much much bigger than liberals
versus conservatives.
How many
conspiracies does it take
to oppress all subgeniuses
everywhere for all of history?
Only one.
It only takes one. The conspiracy
of the normal people.
The normal people.
Sheep in wolves clothing.
There's so many little tiny conspiracies
there's bound to be one
just for you. But the big
conspiracy is part
of the very air we breathe.
It's even part of you and me.
It's the con. The code of
reality. The con is an attitude
of pinkness.
Of yearning for cuteness,
corniness. The eagerness
to obey. Hatred of
everything real and worst of all disbelief
in Bob.
The conspiracy doesn't have to
get most people cause they've
been had all along.
They're safe as a lobster
in a seafood restaurant tank.
As Bob
pointed out, you know how dumb
the average guy is.
Well by definition half of them
are even dumber than that.
And so we have as many
nasty names for them as they have
for us. We call them the pink boys.
The mediocratons. The somnambulax.
The ace souls.
The cage men.
Incomputes. Mole people.
Proleteratorials.
Hilers and smilers.
Sloths and moths. Barbies and
Kens, cons and johns,
corpulators and so forth. And the sad
the sad thing about all this is
the normals can never
become like us.
But we can become
like them.
There but for the face
of Bob go I.
You might say to
yourself.
An excellent performance
Mr. Vollmer. Very effective.
You learn quickly.
Thank you.
I'd like to know who I'm thanking.
It does not make very much difference.
I am just pleased I could be of help.
You learned the style
very well. You delivered
the speech exactly as I told you.
I'm very obliged.
The money?
It was the least I could do.
We could not very well have you thrown out
into the streets.
I happen to feel your work is very important.
Are you one of us?
One of you Mr. Vollmer.
You might say I am you.
Now.
I have some suggestions.
I will continue to give you advice.
But there is a matter
of great importance that must be
taken care of.
What is it?
An expedient Mr. Vollmer.
Oh you might call it a
cause celebre.
Something to
cement the organization together.
I don't understand.
A martyr.
The organization needs a martyr.
A martyr?
How do you find a martyr?
You do not find one Mr. Vollmer.
You choose one.
You take one of no value
and you make him into a symbol.
You wrap him in a flag.
And you make his death
work for you.
Find a man who is of
no value while he is alive.
But who can serve you when he is dead.
Is there such a one?
Mob?
Hard!"
OK!
If you try using
one of those and
erlebt
revolution
Thank you.
This is Phil Proctor.
And David Osman.
Of the Firesign Theatre.
And we're enjoying listening to the hour of slack.
I'm slacking off myself.
Thank you.
Only from FiresignTheatre.com and SealandRecords.com.
It's in very, very short supply, but the Data DVD has MP3s of all of their radio shows from 1970 to 72.
Uncut, pristine, not just the dozen or so episodes you may be thinking about.
We all owe the Firesign Theatre for everything.
And that new collection, again, is available only through Firesign.
FiresignTheatre.com and SealandRecords.com.
Our friends at Negative Land who also put out the new Evolutionary Control Committee album.
Before that, the song Mind Controlled by Bob is by Slack T, with apologies to DK Jones, I'm sure.
This music in the background, by the way, is by our friend Reverend Just John of Just-John.com.
We'll have more.
We'll have more from my Starwood Sermon of 2010 coming up soon.
But first, this history song by Jonathan Coulton.
Music
Rock
Spy
to keep it
Taylor was a Mexican war hero
Fillmore gave a vote to Commodore Perry
Pierce repealed the Missouri Compromise
Buchanan saw the Civil War's beginnings
Lincoln saved the Union
then he died
Andrew Johnson just survived impeachment
General Grant enjoyed a drink or two
Rutherford B. Hayes ended Reconstruction
Garfield was assassinated in 1882
Arthur suspended Chinese immigration
Cleary was a Mexican war hero
Cleveland made the railroad people squirm
Harrison signed the Sherman Antitrust Act
Grover Cleveland served another term
McKinley kicked the Spanish out of Cuba
Roosevelt was handy with a gun
Taft was big and fat and had a mustache
Wilson kicked some ass in World War I
Harding said let's laissez faire with business
Coolidge made the roaring 20s roar
Hoover screwed the pooch in the Great Depression
Roosevelt beat the Nazis in the war
Music
was able to ignore the news because it used to make me so depressed. Back in the olden days,
I'd read the Dallas Morning News and it was all just story after story of misery that I couldn't
do anything about. And worst of all, there was the letters to the editor's page. Imagine in Dallas,
Texas. Well, now, like I said, I was able to ignore the news and I got much healthier.
All my psychosomatic illnesses cleared up. Then 9-11 happened and I started becoming a news junkie
again to some extent. But lately, I found myself in this horrible habit that's really hard to break,
reading the comments that follow yahoo.com news articles.
Oh, my God. You know, I've learned things from reading those comments, things I never knew before.
For instance, did you know that no Democrat ever works or pays taxes?
And that the libtards, I've read this one comment. This is just a real typical one. Give me an idea
of how frustrating this can be. They'll say things like,
well, I see the libtards are posting during the workday. That's because they never work
or pay taxes. Well, the guy, it's like you look at the timestamp and it was posted in the middle
of the day. I don't, all you, this is an actual quote. All you stupid libtards can do is hate
and name calling because you're cowards and idiots.
Oh, and the, the, the,
the media is completely controlled by socialists. I hear that all day long. Every time I turn on the
radio, that the media is controlled by socialists. But where do you hear it? The damn radio.
Oh, it's a sad, sad situation. But friends, we subgeniuses, especially the ones who are
fully indoctrinated, dues paying, ordained ministers,
who easily done with that 30 bucks at the, uh, or the checkout, those ordainment packs,
they're quite spiffy. Um, we just, I don't know why it took us so long to realize this.
Remember, uh, the last, the previous president, uh, Bush, the second was pushing, they were going
to give extra money or tax breaks or something to companies that were faith based. Well, I didn't
say anything. We have,
we happen to have a religion. It's not really faith based. It's face based. It's based on that
face, that face of that man, J.R. Bob Dobbs, not on the face of Reverend Ivan Stank, not on the face
of Philo Drummond, not on the face of some damn other subgenius. It's that man, Bob, that face.
And friends, we discovered finally, rather late in our career, the power of face healing. You can
take a picture of Bob, which comes with,
that membership pack, by the way, we also have decals, um, and place, just simply physically
place that printed picture on the afflicted part of the, uh, person, such as the brain,
uh, just, uh, slap a printed, uh, Dobbs head against your face. He can see out of every one
of those little Dobbs heads. He's with you, even though you're still alone when you do that. Uh,
I should, you know, I should be getting,
I should be getting royalties for writing the first face book.
I used to think I had a problem with faith healing because I'm kind of a, what you'd call a skeptic.
I'm real. I studied UFOs, paranormal, alternative healing, all that stuff very,
very closely for a long time. And it taught me that there are many interesting people around.
But I was sad because it was like, well, what if I got some incurable disease?
But sometimes incurable diseases really are cured by faith healing.
I thought, well, golly, that cuts me out. And then I realized, no, actually,
I'm just as susceptible to faith healing as anybody.
When the doctor gives my insurance company a big enough bill, my faith grows.
The, if they have the machine that goes ding and can show me how much it costs,
but I have more faith. So I can be in fact,
the problem is I actually do believe in faith healing.
Placebos work as well as medicine about half the time,
but now I'm hooked on placebos and that adds up to people.
People are so,
so,
so dependent on machines and mechanical contrivances,
air conditioning. What happened to the air conditioning?
We got to wondering, well, you go to Walmart and I actually know a guy who's,
whose idea of exercise is to walk across Walmart.
And then you see all those people in those little Walmart golf carts, right?
And at the supermarket more and more,
they can't even be bothered to lean on the cart.
And you see them walk into the store.
Then they get the machine and sit down.
We got to speculating if who would win if you had a fight between modern humans
and say an Australopithecus, you know,
this little apish I think the Australopithecus would consider that Walmart golf cart driver an easy kill.
Don't you?
So,
Oh,
I see if we have some Australopithecus in the audience.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Yes,
the conspiracy gets people to the point where they'd rather drive than walk.
I would have rather done that a lot of today actually.
But you know,
we get ourselves into the most of these messes.
The subgenius thing is that some people might wisely consider our talk about the humans versus the subgenius.
And the conspiracy of the normals is being a bit of an allegory,
making fun of people who really are so simple minded that they divide the world up into two types of people or think you can measure human behavior with little formulas.
Most of the time,
it's not the conspiracy.
We get ourselves into these messes,
friends.
That's where you have to fight the conspiracy.
First,
the conspiracy inside.
You the kick me sign on your back is in your own handwriting.
That is a horrible thing to realize.
But if you're lucky and grow old enough,
it will sink in.
It really is your responsibility and you can remove the kick me sign.
We have a lot of trouble reaching the youth in our ministry,
but it's amazing how easy it is to reach old age.
And it's a great way to change it.
But enough about the conspiracy.
You don't want to hear about the conspiracy.
You want more on religion.
And have we got a moron religion for you?
Pull that win over your own eye.
Where would we go next?
This phantom from another time,
this resurrected ghost of a previous nightmare,
Chicago,
Los Angeles,
Miami,
Florida,
Vincennes,
Indiana,
Syracuse,
New York,
any place,
every place where there's hate,
where there's prejudice,
where there's bigotry.
He's alive.
So long as these evils exist.
Remember that when he comes to your town,
remember it.
When you hear his voice speaking out through others,
When you hear a name called a minority attack,
any blind,
unreasoning assault on a people or any human being.
He's alive because through these things,
we keep them alive.
So long.
Thank you.
A NASA scientist says there could be PR news from Washington.
Girl talk.
Did that mash up?
You can Google girl talk.
or wiki hymn.
Before that, PR news by Lemur
and some music for Imaginary Monster
movies by Sodi.
You are hearing Hour of Slack
from the Church of the Subgenius.
Next week's show will be a special about
Starwood 2010 with more
ranting and lots of music.
For more information on Starwood, X-Day
or the Church of the Subgenius, you can look at
subgenius.com and especially
the events section.
Also, our Subgenius Foundation
official Facebook page.
And now, via
the large, Philo tells us goodbye
with some puzzling evidence.
Yeah, I think it's about time for us to
think about packing up
and heading out.
What do you think?
Okay.
You can.
You're free to do that.
You mean, we're going to do something with the basic
laws of nature?
That's pretty scary.
That is scary.