And that somebody is me.
Yeah, it kind of blew my mind.
Oh, yes, dear friends, this is KNON 89.3 FM in Dallas, Texas.
Thank you.
Now for the umpteenth time never before heard on any radio speaker.
Again, the radio motion showed that they had to wait till now.
There are less than five minutes left in the show.
The Subgenius Foundation presents in omnisound, phonoscope, and radio color,
The Subgenius Foundation.
The Subgenius Show.
More than an hour, less than a show.
The Subgenius Show is assembled and edited by the doctors of the air,
using every trick from the voluminous bag of modern science.
Hear the immortal words of Bob,
together with the opinions, curses, and imprecations
of his dearest friends and bitter enemies.
In other news, child molesters were discovered to be frequenting
the Subgenius program.
Yes, child molesters were on the air.
When found.
They molested children by broadcasting their evil message into their ears.
Here was the vivid imaginary universe that existed alongside our mortal world.
It sounded like this.
That magical realm of witches and wizards, ghosts, goblins, geeks,
gooks.
And gnomes, fairies, elves, giants, ogres, and nerds.
Where valiant knights battled fearsome dragons.
Mermaids splashed in sunlit seas.
And mystical unicorns appeared to the pure of heart.
Yes, the whole world of enchantment that has bewitched the human mind and spirit
since the dawn of time is now available to you in the 27 volume book of The Subgenius.
Well, that's all for tonight, folks.
We hope you've enjoyed listening to our Subgenius Show
as much as we've enjoyed bringing it to you.
Thank you.
We have enjoyed it.
And our guest, Milo Duggan, on today's famous...
Thank you.
I enjoyed it very much.
Thank you for listening to the show and saving energy.
Goodbye.
Bye.
You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery
which reaches from the inner mind to...
The Subgenius.
Power of Swag.
That's my praise bar.
Praise bar.
Thank you.
Yes, we are back.
Hi-ya.
So relax in your own delusion.
Find a place to hide and reach your confusion.
Save me from the clutches of confusion.
Save me.
From the chains of time
To the sand of the earth
From the men and the blind
To the slings of genius
The stars fly
Praise God
Oh, yes, and praise Bob, friends,
and praise the walk-ins
who did that fantastic gospel song there.
Oh, yes, we're going to get down tonight.
We're going to get into the spirit.
We're going to get so deep into the spirit
it's going to be like walking through molasses
in a Nightmare on Elm Street movie.
You'll love it.
You'll love it, dear friends.
And you can love it even more
if, when you become puzzled,
you call in.
Talk to Will Adobes here.
Not me.
Will Adobes really has the harder job here,
I think, in a way.
But he hasn't paid as many dues as I have.
When he's...
He's racked up enough radio dues
while he'll have his own pathetic
or crippled assistant working there.
Oh.
And where would we be without him, dear friends?
Dr. Will Adobes.
Reach him and ask your questions
at 823-7490.
Well, he already got one
before I even finished saying the number.
Praise Bob.
Bob, they're telepathic out there.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, call 823-7490
for information
on the Church of the Subgenius
radio ministry hour of slack.
Thank you.
But if you don't like it,
well, there's probably something else on TV
you can look at.
I used to play ball.
He was my coach.
Ah.
Listen, there's a big musical special
on Channel 4 at 7.30,
Hall of Corridors.
A musical?
Yeah, Hall of Corridors.
You know, that's the...
I think that's the overall title.
That's the series.
What's the name of the act?
The Littlest Marine, it's called.
It's got to be a real charming...
Oh, wonderful, yeah.
It's a chalk show.
Yeah, right.
Charles Everett Wilson Gump's
ideal all-people's family show.
Little Squeezy Whitaker
of UTV's Emmy Award-winning
Everybody's Negro
stars as Hideo Bumstead.
Hideo Bumstead!
It's the Japanese cassette
That's right.
pre-show that they won't let us have for a year.
The Little...
He plays the littlest marine
on a Christmas Eve...
on X-mas Eve, sir.
They must be saving space here.
On X-mas Eve's
search-and-destroy mission
in the Holy Land.
As the patrol nears
Hollywood Boulevard,
Hideo remembers
that he's forgotten his heart.
Directed and coached
by Dr. Carl Schickelgruber,
Secretary of Health, Education, and Sickness,
choreographed by General Ivan
the Terrible Gruber.
Original songs include
Who Am I,
What Time Is It,
and Where Is Your Passport?
Oh, good.
That's a great one.
Those are all musical questions.
What time is it?
At the same time, though,
Phil and Peter,
you'll be glad to hear
there's a movie drama,
Lame Duck, 1966.
We can watch that
while the guys are watching the other one.
Yeah.
Right?
What's Lame Duck?
What's it about?
A detective is killed
by his three sons
and rich uncle
in a battle over motion picture rights.
Daisy is portrayed
by Lark Albatross,
and Donald is portrayed
by Andrew Gump.
Oh, yeah?
That's 90 minutes.
But at the same time,
there's a movie on,
a western scalp,
The Schnifter, 1935.
Oh.
That's a good old one.
Listen to this.
I'll take that one.
I'll take that one on videotape.
We can watch it later.
Well, I think this is the one.
Rancher Dick Nixon
has to make up his mind soon.
Oh, I've been wanting
to get that one.
I'll take that
on the new cartridge machine.
Great.
Okay, go ahead.
Either drop that bomb
on the sheep man
or lose his daughter
to jazz musicians.
Oh.
In a gloomy report,
Morley took a dim view
of history,
recalled the tragically
repetitious story,
the decline and fall
of all past civilizations.
Said Morley,
modern civilization
could,
by the way,
a phenomenon
of atomic fission,
be brought to dust
and ashes.
For example,
if an A-bomb
were detonated
at the Empire State Building,
the area of total destruction
would cover an area
of two miles.
Now,
since the A-bomb
is already obsolete,
consider the area
of total destruction
of an H-bomb.
And science
has promised us
bombs a thousand times
more powerful,
poisoning with radioactivity
all the air and water
of this Earth.
This could mean
not only the end of our own civilization,
but the very possibility
of any future civilization.
What are we going to do about it?
I'll tell you what I'm going to do about it.
I have a plan.
A plan to preserve human life
on this planet.
I hope you will join with me
in carrying it out.
I hope you will join with me in carrying it out.
And you can join with us
by calling 823-7490.
The response to Dr. Morley's appeal
was immediate and enthusiastic.
The Society to Save Civilization
was set up.
To its headquarters
flocked amateur do-gooders
and professional scientists.
Humanity can escape annihilation,
can find a temporary haven,
a promise of hope
that come what may,
life can be a little easier.
We sustain deep within the Earth itself.
Far below the surface,
we shall seek a natural,
a geological shelter.
We have a team ready for the effort.
All we lack are funds.
Can we get them from your foundation?
Dr. Morley,
I believe it would expedite
metas if I were to ask the questions.
We're, uh, labeled, you know.
First of all,
isn't the inside of the Earth solid?
The interior of the Earth
is made up of vast caverns,
air piles,
joined by natural avenues
leading from the surface.
Natural avenues,
funnels, and fissures.
Such a fissure lies within
the world's largest extinct volcano
at Mount Nellie.
That is where we intend
to start our journey.
Over these furrows,
up our delta they go,
hundreds of miles,
thousands to the very core
of the Earth.
Isn't the inside of the Earth,
the very core,
a molten, fiery land?
An encounter.
The latest body of theory holds
that the inside of a sphere
touching the Earth
is cooler than the temperature
at its surface.
And how do you traverse
these thousands of miles?
Dr. Coleman,
the perspective drawing.
This is a cyclotron.
A what?
It's an amphibious conveyor
based on the principles
of ovoidal atmosphere.
A what?
Like a submarine.
With the mobility of a tractor.
Its head contains a burrowing device.
Its walls can withstand
extremes of temperature and pressure.
But even with the cyclotron
or the atmosphere of the whatnot,
how do you know you'll be successful
in finding this underground haven?
We don't know.
We'll never know.
Without the what?
Without the what not,
my friends,
without the what not,
we won't know nothing.
And neither will Arnold Mathis.
Arnold Mathis,
who did that tape there.
There's a lot more to it.
We're always chopping people's work
down to fragments of what it was.
But you know why that is?
It's because of the book
of the subgenius.
We can't help it.
It is our destiny,
our duty.
To present to you,
the listener,
that which will hurt you the most.
And we'll just go to a random page here
in the book of the subgenius.
I just want you to know
how great this book is
by the fact that I will just flip it open
to a random page.
You don't even know what I'm going to.
Okay, here we go.
There!
If you can't get slack for yourself,
you should be careful.
You sure as hell aren't going to be able
to give it to somebody else.
And that's just what they've got you trying to do.
You can't think.
Everything's gone wrong.
You're so tired.
The kids are driving you crazy.
Your spouse lost another job
and is drinking again.
You're supposed to have an operation.
You don't know where the money's going to come from.
It doesn't seem worth it anymore.
There's no one to talk to.
You don't know if you can hold up under all this.
And you're not sure if you want to.
You're ashamed of the things you haven't done.
And you keep thinking about those pills.
Friends, put a dog in a cage
and he'll run in circles.
Put a man in a cage and he'll run for president.
And it's the same thing.
All problems, all problems, my friends,
result from paralysis
caused by their game
in which they keep changing the rules.
It's like the robot monster
in 30 different sci-fi movies
being ordered to kill
contrary to his prime directive
of protecting humans.
He goes into a cycle of,
I must, yet I cannot,
and shorts out in an explosion of sparks.
But instead of shorting out,
humans have the choice
of ignoring the paradox within their orders.
The choice of,
I'm going to sleep.
Oh, public apathy is a disease, certainly.
The con itself complains of it.
But it isn't apathy to begin with.
It's just that nobody wants
what they're trying to push.
They push rules.
But no rules for behavior can work for long.
Oh, they can sound good enough
for each new political fad to become epidemic
before its side effect of positive thinking brain cancer
sets in.
The conspiracy either wants you either
to think about only the nice things,
sweetness, cuteness,
Pollyanna crap in general,
or to be frozen by total helplessness.
Either way, you're kept from resisting
the unspoken rules.
The rules which don't have to be spoken
because so many people live them,
think them,
that they can't stand back and see them.
Those in the room,
in the system,
can't see anything except from the inside.
They didn't know there could be an outside.
They never ex...
They never suspected
how much larger their cage might be.
Praise Bob.
That will overcome Satan's power.
It's the anointing that will break the yoke
of Satan's bondage.
And I want you to know that I
had just been experiencing an attack
on all sides.
It seemed like on every foot
where we tried to advance,
the devil would just unleash,
literally,
hordes of demonic forces to stop us.
And after a few weeks of this,
I just began to feel a deep hurting
in my belly,
way deep down in my spirit.
And some people say,
Brother Pop, of what?
You mean you experience pain too?
Yes, I do.
I hurt just like you do.
I feel the pain of a satanic attack
just like you do.
That's why I'm concerned about you.
That's why I feel for you.
I feel in the spirit your pain
and your suffering and the sickness
that Satan throws at you
to try to overcome you.
But, bless God,
Satan is a defeated foe.
But while I felt this pain,
it seemed almost as if
a spontaneous thing happened.
As I finally came out of the cage,
I didn't know what to do.
I didn't know how to pray
because I didn't know
exactly what was coming at me.
Satan was bombarding me
from so many sides.
Actually, I felt kind of dumb.
Step in to the wonderful world
of autodynamics.
Step in to the swept-wing dodge
of 1957.
Here is Magic in Metal,
a motor car just four and a half feet low.
A long, lean master of motion
that unleashes a hurricane of power.
Its thundering aircraft-type V-8 engine
will give you a thrilling new concept
of automotive performance.
And the swept-wing dodge
breaks through the vibration barrier
into a new realm of silence
to almost completely shield you
from outside sound and shock.
If the last 50 years made such a change,
just imagine the New York of 1980,
when everyone has a number
instead of a name,
and the government tells you
whom you should marry.
Just imagine 1980.
Here, dear, take your medicine.
Come on, dear.
Let me have some more pills
before you go.
I'm sorry, sir.
There you are.
Now take care of yourself.
Yeah, take care of yourself.
And if you want to get hold of some of those pills,
go ahead and call 823-7490,
because we'll send you free information
about the Church of the Subgenius
if you dare,
if you really dare,
to call in.
Leave your address.
It's all free.
First hits free, friends.
Just imagine the pills in 1990.
Whoa.
Yeah.
Like I said, I'm back from the dead.
Perfect guitar to take on crusades.
Everybody can have one.
Yeah.
Okay.
Alright, everybody,
But Bob,
if you see me in my naked glory,
glorify me that I might glorify you.
To me, to me.
low if you say i'm ashamed of you bob and on the day of judgment bob shall say i'm ashamed of you
and ye shall come down off the mountain
ye who wants to be ye ye who shall soon be ye the same as they who once were as both spoken by the prophet and this is important the glory the faded glory
that shall not be recovered not by bob me ye by the pink smiling false prophets that once
this
spoken that which was not peed in the river of blood and yet was somehow not involved
in the later slaying of john lennon i ran into a man called himself bob
you know i mean i plumb forgot about the fact that i had no money in no time
well bob is hot
and bob is cold and bob is young bob is old but i forgot forgot i needed to know anything else
i just took my own personality and put it up on the show
bob's brain so damn big he'll make you look like a greasy little pig oh
oh you'll forget about your whole personality
as soon as you give your entire brain to bob and me
oh give it to bob and glass madness dear friends and you're looking for a job just look for a guy
whose name is bob and you won't have to worry about getting that job
because you won't have to worry about getting that job
You have no money, but you have, Bob.
Is it really?
Yeah, yes, it is.
I recently bought a new Atari 520SP computer.
Uh-huh, I know what you're going to ask.
Did you know about that?
Yes, that is Bob in the new Atari.
A subgenius minister, Reverend Householder, was employed by Atari at that time
and was using a Bob image as a test pattern.
And they loved it and worked it into whatever that hieroglyphic font that you get with the Atari.
So Bob is in over 5 million homes now without those people knowing about it,
and he's locked onto their souls now.
They can't get away.
We'll get that check sooner or later.
All they have to do is print character strings 28 and 29 and one line and 30 and 31 to their screen,
and they will see Bob.
Right.
Take down those numbers, all numerology experts call in.
Yeah, we need to hear from somebody who hates us, though.
Yeah, we need some more hate calls and some numerology.
That's what religion is all about most of the time.
I'm sure there's no shortage of those people here, so I'll get off the line and let them call me.
Glad you are.
Thanks for sharing that with us.
There shall be slack.
Bye now.
Thanks for sharing that.
Hi, 94.1, you're on the air.
Yeah, I've just been listening for a few minutes.
And, I mean, this is, I've been searching for a church or something.
I've looked at a lot of things.
And I'm already just real interested in this.
And I just, I mean, I've only heard a few things.
I mean, I've only been listening for about two minutes.
So I would just like an address or whatever to write or...
Sure.
Oh, we're good.
We're good at giving our address.
The what?
We're good at giving that address.
Folks, get a pencil.
Yes, do you have your pencil?
The thing is, I just turned the radio on.
Put your hands on the radio.
Okay, it's there.
Now feel, feel Bob.
Feel the healing power come through.
While you're holding on to the radio, we're going to hold a picture of Bob up so everyone can see.
Okay, look over there on camera four.
See that smiling face with the pipe in his mouth?
And that neat hair?
Right there on the left on monitor three.
That is Bob.
That is Bob Dobbs, the man with the pipe whose face you see on...
And you can reach that man with the pipe at the sacred post office box.
That's right, just right.
Bob at P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
That's P.O. Box 14...
Yeah, yeah, P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
All right, and I'm sorry that, you know, you have to keep repeating this and everything.
It's just...
Oh, Bob and the fighting Jesus, we're talking to you now.
And we can feel it coming through in the spirit.
And we know there's a lot of special laid up members and people with genetic things that are all different.
And they're needing to feel the power of you.
And they got...
Some of them got tumors.
Some of them got cancers.
And some of them got...
Got things in their brain that won't go out.
And some of them see little bitty men everywhere that they don't think are real.
But we know they're real.
And we want you to make them feel right with all of this.
We advocate peaceful solutions to world pandemics.
We're ready, we're ready.
We don't know why else, no more holding us down.
This program is trying to duplicate that.
I cut my hair off to spy my fate.
Did you grow wiser from the experience?
Uh, we do not require proof of subgeniusness at all.
Sire, the situation is...
Is...
We're here at the...
International Festival for those who have gone too far.
Below us, the band serenades the fools as they dance on the empty glass sea of mystery.
Yes, it's an exciting day here at the Fool Symposium.
Uh, here comes...
Here comes...
The President's Limousine.
Dumping the dirt on the freeway of success.
And there's his curly-headed wife playing the bass drum.
And the small but polite audience...
...of those who don't know any better.
We are Obama!
The relating of spiritual declension is never a pretty sight or a pretty picture.
Because as foolish as Bob gets, as foolish as Bob gets, it's the wisdom of the ages.
It's the foolishness and the idiocy that has kept man from being satisfied with his lot in life.
It is that stupidity which has caused man to build his great monuments, his mighty gas-powered engines, his nuclear reactors.
It is that which has given man his urge to master the entire earth.
No matter how nice it was before.
And it is this mighty sacred archetype of an urge that's in Bob and in all of us that makes us want to smite our brothers.
And friends, if it weren't for that, where would us subgeniuses be?
We'd be like everybody else.
We'd be no different.
We'd have nothing.
We'd gripe about.
And without the mighty grunt power and the mighty hate, the hate for the normal that we can feed,
the hate that can make us go out and earn something for nothing,
the hate that will make us overcome every last conspiracy attempt to hold us down that there's ever been.
In the long run, we may stay poor and broke.
We may stay neurotic or whatever we started out as or whatever we may fall into.
But by God, we've got Bob and Annie.
And for that, we can hate them.
Hate them.
Call us and talk about what you'd wish.
Hey, you guys, come close.
Did I tell you I was at the Republican National Convention?
Because I'm studying evolution.
89.3 FM.
If you're close enough to someone to have intimate relations with them, you're close enough to discuss AIDS.
Embarrassment is a real poor excuse for risking your life.
There are over one million intravenous drug abusers in this country.
Every single one of them is at risk of getting AIDS.
So are their sexual partners.
Don't put yourself at risk.
Every time I shot up, I thought about getting AIDS.
Because sharing needles or works can give you AIDS.
And the truth is, skin popping is just as dangerous as mainlining.
Now I'm in drug treatment.
I'm not using drugs anymore.
Treatment's better than walking around scared of AIDS.
Misinformation is as dangerous as no information.
And there's no reason not to have the facts about AIDS.
You can call the National Institute on Drug Abuse toll-free for more information.
That information could save lives.
Call 1-800-662-HELP.
If you're shooting drugs or sleeping with someone who does, you may get more than you bargained for.
AIDS.
AIDS is an equal opportunity killer.
The risk comes not from who you are, but from what you do.
Get the facts about AIDS.
It could save your life.
Call 1-800-662-HELP for more information.
This message is a public service announcement brought to you by KNON 89.3 FM.
The voice of and for the people.
Oh, yes.
But I bet you most of you subgeniuses don't have to worry about that quite so much for yourselves.
Because you're getting high off a bob.
You don't need drugs when you got bob in your life.
You hear me?
You hear what I'm saying now?
Because bob is the one high that you never, ever come down from, dear friends.
You want a little whiskey?
Uh, yeah, I'll have another whiskey.
Well, it's a quite a nice place, isn't it?
Yeah, isn't it?
Yeah, I didn't know they had any tapas bars.
Oh, yes, we have topless bars in Europe, of course.
What do you think?
This is a whole chain set up by Nixon himself.
Oh, yeah.
It's a business.
Hell, tricky dick.
Here's the dick.
Yeah.
Oh.
Like, uh, well, there's the bad side to it all, you know.
Oh, there's a bad side, too.
Yeah.
What kind of bad side, my boy?
Well, you know, all this, there's, of course, the evil pet dog of Jehovah, you know, that old, the old, unmentionable pet dog of Jehovah.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, you mean me, yeah.
Hey, hey, wait.
Shh, shh, don't say that.
Uh, Nicky, why can't I say Nicky?
You said it again.
Look, I'm gonna sit here at this table with you, but I gotta promise not to keep invoking all these evil demons, you know.
Uh, but, uh, Bob always said to me when we got something like a real-life nude girl or something like that, he said, let's do some Nicky Nicky.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, you better watch it. You better watch it, okay?
Because, you know, I mean, I have to sit here by you. I don't wanna, I don't wanna be caught when the sh...
Do you see the bill?
Oh, my God.
Four million dollars?
Four million dollars? That's quite an expensive buy.
But I only had three drinks of whiskey.
Yeah, it's amazing, but I can never pay four million dollars. It's going to ruin me.
Oh, why did you ever have to mention that?
That...
What?
I'm not going to say it. Things are bad enough.
Uh, you mean the dog? The dark side of Bob, is it true?
You know very well it's true. You brought me here yourself. You tricked me. You made me come here to follow the path of this strange, weird Bob who we knew nothing about.
Oh.
Oh, why did I ever leave America? Oh.
Ah, ha, ha, ha, ha. Don't you start whining now.
Look, the evil forces can be attacked very easily.
Look, I open my pants, and I take out my big Bob glands. See?
Whoa. Huh.
And I wave it around here, and see what happens?
Yeah.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ah, the bill is dissolving.
The bill is dissolving, and we can just leave without any problems. Come, my boy, let's go outside.
Yeah, let's get out of here.
Here is my car. Get in.
Okay. Hey, are you sure you should drive?
Oh, yes, I'll drive, of course. Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Yeah, you drive.
So, here we are.
Yeah, nice place.
In my home. Here is a cup of coffee.
Boy, I need it.
Oh, yes. Let me show you something very important. See this photograph?
Yes.
Do you recognize the man in the middle?
Of course, it's Bob.
You see his pipe?
Yeah, yeah, and there's two men standing there with him. One to the right, one to the left.
Yes, the one on the right is Joseph Stalin, and the other one you will recognize for sure.
Oh, it's Roosevelt.
Yes.
And they're slicing a pie.
Bob is actually slicing a pie, yes.
But it's the strangest shaped pie I've ever seen.
It is a pie in the form of Europe, my boy.
Ah.
He made a great, great sale in America by getting fluoride in the water.
But here in Europe, he outdid himself.
He sliced Europe in two and sold one half to Joseph Stalin and the other half to Roosevelt.
Ah, it is so good to find something like that.
I'm going to ask somebody from the Empire here in Europe interested in the real story.
How is the Emperor doing?
Well, you know, ever since that operation on his third nostril, you know, then there was that pyroflagellation incident.
They found that microfilm up there.
The whole Iran scandal just blew up.
Yes, it backfired badly, didn't it?
Yes, it did.
It was a tragic incident.
Yes, the entire country was looking up his third eye, wasn't it?
Yeah.
So, here we have the beginning of the conspiracy.
This is where it actually all began.
How am I sure you are not from the conspiracy, my boy?
Well, well, I...
Hey, wait a minute. What about you?
Let me show you something else.
Okay. See these little kids here?
Did you know that Bob made children?
Huh?
Oh.
It is quite a story.
But this is actually his grandson.
Huh.
And I am raising him.
And I guess you are not with the conspiracy.
If you act like a dumb , they will treat you as an equal.
How true.
True.
But it is time to go, my son.
It was nice meeting you.
Yes.
I guess this little interview will do.
It will change your history.
See you later.
Goodbye.
So, there you have it.
We began on a search for Bob.
The things we discovered, well, none of us may know for sure whether or not they really happened.
But one thing is true.
The destiny of the subgenius has been changed forever.
Nothing can ever remain the same.
And now, as a new generation of the Dobbs family reaches its maturity, I have to leave you now.
and hopefully you will find your own true
thank you very much and good night thank you inhibiting factor and Willem de
Ritter
Amsterdam radio in Holland oh yes and this is Oingo Boingo also talking about
the conspiracy
yeah
This is fairytale.
Are you deserving, Joyce?
It's time to die.
I'm fighting with the world.
You're the only things I ever trust in.
We're scattered, living in a city.
I'm just a member.
Single, red, love, under, cold, and ice.
Better for life than jail.
War is coming.
There's not so much that we can do.
Stay to the people.
The operator will knock me through.
It's the first.
The memory is burning my brain.
I'm in.
I'm going insane.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're the winner.
There's no excuse.
I'm just a person.
I'm not the one to go home.
Since the wind, we're all my friends.
Stay in bed until the world ends.
So please go home.
I can't just speak.
Single, red, love.
You're the only things I ever trust in.
Go home.
I'm just a member.
Better for life than jail.
Single, red, love.
I can't just be single.
I can't just stay.
I can't.
I think I'm going insane
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
This is a fairy tale
This can't be real
They're sliding all around
They're screwing in the fields
They say their values change
When hunger or ambition strikes
So what of this ascension?
And it comes for any price
The cartoon animals
Are over at Donald's farm
I'm nodding off
The hotel rooms
With eaters in their arms
The seven dwarves
There's only four alive today
Cinderella
Is working for the CIA
The fairy tale's over
You should know you've got
The scars to prove it
And the skills and
The strongest you're used to
I don't care
Come on, jump in
Cinderella
Uncover
Us
You're alive
Cinderella
Uncover
Us
You're alive today
Start analysing how theenture
You know this song
How our hearts
Miri
Even
Swoosh
In
Well
Sigh
That sure makes total sense
We just got the
inc ninety to
year Lot
NO
than for this limitation.
Then a small brown hawk passed by.
Small brown hawk passed by for me to up and through it.
Hawk passed by, and Gog rocketed up and through it.
Gog swooped low over me before flying off to battle.
For me before flying off to battle.
Soon my Gog exploded in a similar way through a dove.
Through a dove.
O'
being shown in the baptismal font.
Oh.
Yes, sir.
That was Onan Canobite.
Dr. Onan Canobite.
The youngest subgenius doctor.
And he continues.
And so does Robert Anton Wilson here, who said that,
quote,
the late Lawrence Labade once told me a parable about a king
who decided that every time he met somebody,
he would kick them in the butt just to emphasize his power.
Since this maniac wore a crown and had an army,
people soon learned to tolerate being kicked fairly often
and even began to accept it philosophically or stoically
as they experienced it.
Except taxation and other impositions of kings and governors.
They even learned to bend over as soon as they saw the king coming.
Oh, well, friends.
Have you already bent over?
I hope not.
Get out there and vote, please.
I hear from New Orleans.
Is this satire?
This is satire.
That's all.
Nobody.
How much is a bucket of pills these days?
Like, just on the street price.
Like, we just want one bucket.
I'm not talking about a whole bathtub.
What do you get?
The bathtubs of pills that are rumored that we demand before we go on.
That's just, you know, a little bit.
Stretching it a bit.
We would like a bucket of pills.
That's what we call Rolling Stone.
They gave us a court just before we got here.
But that's just...
A little champagne glass.
Tiny champagne glasses of pills.
And they weren't the irreversible pills.
Either.
That was the problem.
They weren't the ones that you come down.
They were the flat on the inside.
They were the ones that you came down.
Yeah.
Well, I still need to have, for my dressing room, a coffin lined with mirrors and a recording
of a...
A...
At all times playing a distant roar of applause so all reality except for my ego is blotted
out.
And, I mean...
This is not some church where we try to get you to do this song.
Oh, your ego.
You live up to the new age whips of the unicorn-riding dragon cucks.
Here, he shines.
Don't sound...
Twinkle-cold, kindness bastards out there.
Northwest fire.
You can blow everyone outside of this room.
Praise God.
I didn't say you got no legs.
But I ain't got no legs.
Let's roll.
Fire.
Dear Dr. Ello, Purdy is our six-year-old parakeet.
My only concern about him is that he's spending so much time fussing with his preen gland.
I think that's what he's doing.
Anyway, it's in that area.
You know that area at the base of his tail?
That kind of smelly area?
Dr. Ello, do preen glands itch in parakeets during the fruiting season?
Or what?
How can I read?
Sign me RC in Manitoba, Canada.
Wow.
Dear RC, Purdy's putrid preen gland, that is to say, preen gland rather, could itch,
certainly, but it could be a more significant problem than that.
Your budgie may have Sherman's disease.
This will require that your entire home be sandblasted and flame-tested with temperature
above 7,000 degrees.
And you yourself must be quarantined for an indefinite time period while forced to watch
driver's education videos.
But it's all part of the wonderful thrills of owning a petite, puffed-up parakeet,
twittering its way into your heart.
He's talking over there more than my mind when I'm talking, which I don't like that.
I need some more over here.
Hey, is that, yeah, okay, I see.
Just switch it down, switch it off.
Oh, it's the both doing it. Okay.
The one that really gets me is that one that's like an oscilloscope.
If you could be here, folks, I think you would really appreciate the wonders of modern radio communication.
Yes, and you can be here if you want to call 823-7490 and find out what's going on.
It's kind of like a, I don't know, I'm just going to do this.
Whatever it's doing, I don't know, but it's doing it.
Please, don't just tell me how you are, Mom.
Tell me how you are.
How are you?
I'm sick.
I'm sorry to hear it.
I really am.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
You know what it is, honey.
Yeah.
It's the same thing it's always been.
Yeah, sure, yeah.
It's my nerves.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I went to the doctor.
Yeah.
He told me right out.
Yeah, yeah.
He said, listen, Mrs. White.
Who are you fooling?
Yeah, sure, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You are a very nervous.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Very high strung.
Yeah.
And you're a very strong woman.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, God knows that's true.
Yeah, yeah.
And you cannot stand the slightest aggravation.
Yeah, sure, yeah.
I said, Doctor, I know that.
Yeah.
I mean, I know better too.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I said, but you see, Doctor.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
I have this son.
He is.
It's the truth.
The boy is not lying.
He is.
He's very busy.
You see, Doctor, he's too busy to pick up a phone and call his mother.
Honey, listen, Mom.
Dear, I want you to tell.
Mom.
Well, Arthur, when I said that to him, he said, I'm sorry.
Administrator Obama wanted to be a Medicare??
The guy he's working for
Yeah.
You think I don't remember and use.
I worked for a?
You, I didn't put a number for you.
You said you're not having dinner?
I think you should call so I could say, Mom, I love you.
Unfortunately, I was moisture, and I wasn't home.
I wrote you my birthday vows?
Oh.
I feel that by taking everything personally and then freely talking about my grief and anguish that I can gradually work toward being a better person.
Okay, the high point of my life was when I was about five years old.
After that, it was a long downhill skid into adulthood.
I had some pretty bad problems in high school, some difficulties with my father and my girlfriend.
And I guess I can tell you about those later, but for now...
Yes, that was Joe Person with the story of his life.
Great, great story, Joe. Is he out of here? Good.
Some say that history is the birth certificate of the present.
Others, that the present is the present.
The present is the epitaph of history.
We say, the bucket of dialectics has a thousand leaks.
And if you're tired of the itching, burning sensation caused by walking around in wet shoes,
Relaxative Laboratories has got the product for you.
Sure, the hoary past lives on, captured for all time in the annals of neurological regurgitation.
But aren't you more than ready for an exciting career in guilt-free existence?
Wouldn't you like a healthy dose of...
free-for-all amnesia and still be able to find your house?
This new product is not available in stores.
And it comes with our no-risk, money-back guarantee.
Simply try it for 30 days, and if you're not satisfied, return it for a full refund.
And we can all forget the whole thing ever happened.
OOO energetic begging and small and
this has a thousand leaksPC
This just falls asleep in it'silib groups.
Can support a free mukbang in that either with a piece of food or something corporate.
the mercies. And I heard them say,
flat out!
My transgressions.
And then I want you to wash me.
And what can wash away
my sins?
Time won't do it.
Blue cheer won't do it.
Cold power won't do it.
Ox and dog won't do it.
But nothing
but the blood of Jesus.
Say yes, Lord!
Yeah!
Megatron's
monster transporter
flows its way up
to the sea.
I don't know anything about running a regular show.
But if you can hear me out there,
this is the first time
I'm actually going to take over this show.
I think
I can
hang on to it for a minute here.
I've got the show
and I've got to go right now.
Somewhere around here, I'm actually going to see
if I can make the things come out.
I've got the things.
What are you waiting for then?
Things come on here.
Let's see.
I'm going to try this.
The problem is that the tiny little voices...
Oh, there's one now.
There's a...
Yeah, okay.
They just come at you and they don't stop.
It's really easy.
The stuff that they do that sounds so strange...
Get that one over there.
It's really...
Just push these buttons here.
There's too much technology.
This is great.
Okay, now...
All right.
Taka-taka-buda-buda.
This is the Dr. Drummond.
Dr. Drummond Radio Hour.
The Hum Drummond Radio Hour.
Now I'm running this show.
You can hum along with Dr. Drummond.
I've commandeered the show.
You've got a patch of...
Came straight from St. Louis.
Yes, I've got...
Well, where is the show going next?
Those are my underlings I brought with me.
They're really not the guys that ordinarily run the show.
Look, Dr. D.
We've got a collar.
Check out the board.
It's lit up like a Christmas tree.
Just some kind of...
What you like...
Ask Dr. Philodrum.
This is the truth.
Come on, collar.
The collars do call in.
Can't call in anymore, though, now, because we're going off.
Making room for Robert Wisdom's American Music Party.
Please stay tuned for that.
A lot of fun.
And horror, both.
Depending on whether he's playing blues or...
I guess it's all blues.
Ah, yes.
Well, dear friends, you can...
This is my last three-minute statement here.
Please do send in a request for free information to the Subgenius Church.
We can give you a post office box.
Get that pencil ready.
Just drop us a line, a postcard, saying,
Hey, I may not spend any money, but I want to know what's going on.
And you'll get at least a few hints.
And that address is...
Just write to Bob at P.O. Box 140306 in Dallas, Texas.
75214.
Once again, that's Box 140306.
In Dallas, Texas.
75214.
And I think I'll just let Chris Gross...
This is Dr. Chris Gross in the background.
I'm going to let his music just take us out here,
because it's as good as anything else I can put on right now.
And that's saying a lot.
Ah, yes.
Praise Bobby.
Really, he's just so hot right now.
I'll put him out there as fast as I can,
That's basically the lebenheit.
Loinb sem Knoll Fuller Boneless.
They literally...
To body wear?
some other things to play for you later.
There's one by Eddie Cleanhead Vincent.