You hear that?
Well, it's a high-frequency test sound.
We often use them in our business.
It's nothing to worry about.
I've got to go to the government.
Get some rest.
It's very important to get vital rest
and to recharge with dreams.
Wonderful, wonderful dreams.
Get some rest.
The purpose of rest and sleep is to dream,
to refresh the psyche
with new scenes and images
which makes sense of your personal inner life.
We'd like you to lie down in the provided bed of sponge.
There you will be massaged by a thousand tiny quivering fingers
telling you to let go.
There we go.
Now the zombies caress you.
As you fall asleep on the layer of sugar.
Sizzling zombies.
Overhead, weird caterpillars void frass.
They got my father.
Yes, they come for your family.
They first came for my cat and dog,
but I did not care because I was not a cat or dog.
Then they came for my grandpa,
but I did not care because I was not a grandpa.
Then they came for...
my local subgenius pastor,
but since I was not a subgenius...
That's a free way to be, man.
And then when they came for me,
there was no one to care.
I'm going for it.
But I cared a lot.
And now,
the subgenius hour of
SWAC!
Dr. Dobbs is known worldwide as a foremost spokesman for Christian and family values.
So plan to attend this rare personal appearance of Dr. Dobbs.
Even if you never intend to write your name again,
one sure way to impress folks is to stay a little bit over their heads
because it was better than looking stupid.
This fear of looking stupid...
less than brilliant is a major communication simple familiar incidents if we put these three
elements under the microscope we can't help but sharpen the focus on our communication effort
it's natural that we follow the circle around and around and around helping to create a nice
round world of confusion and misunderstanding resist the temptation to feed your ego have you
seen our shuttle you'll find it on the bureau so many demands everyone grabbing for a part of me
and now these new voices encouraging me to spend time developing my own talents
how can i possibly please them all
slack is dollar bills slack is drugs slack is a warm home slack is the car you drive
slack is the job you do for money slack is that which the conspiracy stole from you
they don't love you bob they don't love you bob they don't love you like i do
please do not interrupt me i am traveling on the astral plane
can i ever tell you about my hemorrhoids they get really bad when it's humid you know
this is fantastic i've never tasted anything like it when i get really bored
i love it when i get really bored
i like to drive around and see how many squash thaws i can count on the freeways
poor pete one man and two women want him what a predicament for a man to be in
we are friendly our aims are peaceful and we seek to establish cooperation and eternal friendship
between our two worlds our actions are controlled by electronic computers not by human emotions
this is unbelievable
no it's not
it's aliens and they're everywhere and that guy's obviously been zapped
ray this is serious
i am serious
yeah it's just as i suspected those mosquitoes are making these radio acts
so
ellen gonzalez he is the media dog
it's a very Prepare tolica
it's a lot more ridiculous
it's a vaz
people
if you собственно
they are
a lot
to get this amara
Cutting me off on the freeway because he can't drive
He should not be alive
Here comes George Jr.
Constructing sentences is badly while he smirks and grins
Will he get in?
All the stupid people
Where do they all come from?
Where do they all belong?
I look at all the stupid people
Monica Lewinsky
Down on her knees in an office that's oval in shape
They have her on tape
Limbaugh and Laura
Turning it into a radio moral crusade
They need to get laid
All the stupid people
Where do they all come from?
Where do they all belong?
All the stupid people, friends
All the stupid, stupid people
From Phineas and Ferb
And all the stupid, stupid, stupid people
National Cynics Network
On Midnight Voice Jail
Yes
And you can get more information about that
From www.mp3.com
slash pnarco
P-N-A-R-C-O
Or www.listen.to
slash voice jail
And this is Doctors for Bob in the background
And friends, we have a...
cuss-filled show tonight.
A cuss-filled show because
Susie the Floozy is here.
New from the
Tampa Devival. New recordings
and old from
Pope David N. Meyer
from Media Garage 12.
Friends, we've got the brag of the subgenius
as a rock song
created by Archbishop
Uranus Mandela and Determinant
Wilf. And you won't believe it when you hear
we've got the new truth
about Dobstown by
New Monet. And we've got
Church of New Faith.
Their sins killed
you. We've got Media Garage
12 newly digitally remastered.
We've got new barrages
by New
Monet digitally
remashed. And we've got
Dave, old Dave, and
Einstein Secret Orchestra and
Chaz and WCFB and Dr.
Howell and puzzling evidence
at KPFA.
And now, and now, let us go.
Back in time to 1983.
The Denseteria
in New York City.
In an order like this, we may have guidelines
but you must remember not to
be literal minded. No subgenius
follows any two rules exactly.
You must also remember that anything any
subgenius says at any time
is sacred dogma
automatically. And now,
the rules of the Church of the
Subgenius. The first rule of the Church
of the Subgenius is, the subgenius
must have
What must he have?
What must the subgenius have?
Dog, what must he have?
He must have slack.
Help me out here.
The second rule of the Church of the Subgenius
is, too much is
always better than not enough.
Can I get a too much?
Too much! Can I get another too much?
Too much! Too much!
Too many of those children. It's always better
than not enough.
The third rule of the Church of the Subgenius is,
a rule violated every day, every way you go.
People say to me, who is a conspiracy?
Look and see who violates this rule
and you will know them by their actions.
The third rule of the Church of the Subgenius is,
if you don't have a sense of humor,
don't try to be funny.
Don't try to be funny!
The fourth rule of the Church of the Subgenius,
thank you, Buck,
and the most important rule of the Church of the Subgenius,
and the supersedes all other rules is,
fuck them! If they can't
take a joke, fuck them!
Woo!
Huh! Huh!
You must draw
your own conclusions.
My every hour is a lie.
I say, fuck them if they can't take a joke.
They're eating from life, I say!
I am the last remaining
of all characters.
I am the goddamn man of the future.
I'll drive a mile so as not to walk on foot.
I am a human being
I am a human being of the first goddamn water.
I am too intense to lie
for I speak only the fucking truth!
I'm here to defend the land of the free!
When I'm Carney
rode out of
won't even
a
goddamn
Kirby
and
unf Männer
zu
kosten
weil
Bourbon
ver
in
private
kommen
Did you like the fire man?
My imagination
say
is a fucking cancer
and I'll park it before it parks me
I think
backwards
I do it for fun
I cook and eat my dead
I swam up into the triangle
and didn't get wet
I kidnap the future
I'm ransomed into the past
I wait time, wait up for me
I'll live forever
and remember afterwards
Yes, I am the purple flower
of Hell County
Give me wild words
They say a godzillion
is the highest number there is
Well, by God
I've come to a godzillion and one
I weigh 666 pounds
and zero gravity
I'm a godzillion
Come and get me
I told Jesus
I wouldn't go to church
and he shook my head
I have my own personal saviors
I change them every hour
I don't give a fuck
if they don't give me
this laugh of the dead
I don't wanna know
if this is even
fucking slack after death
I am a godzillion vision
I see the future
and the past
in comic books
and wine bottles
I paint my jeans
and wear my DNA
with the force
of my mighty will
I steer my own
godzillion function
I'll kick it black
oh that首가
I like it
I don't know
I don't need that
I hate those colors
I used to hang around an airport
and I used to sell books and I'd stand on the street corner with flowers and I would
do anything that my religion asked me to do but now I've got more sense now I've got Bob Dobbs
Dobbs is saving me showing me slack slack being able to edit your own memory and cut your attention
stat span down to just three little minutes you can program your life just like that TV guide
Oh
yes friends Dr. Buzz Lux recorded at the Austin Texas Devival of the Church and Subgenius back in
1982 from Media Barrage 12 our new release CD release of our little tapes as also was that
Pope David N. Meyer the great Pope David N. Meyer doing the rules of the church with genius and
friends that song that song was the brag of the subgenius
Subgenius
Subgenius truly performed by Indy Terminate Wilf on a CD that we'll be hearing a lot more of on this show you can hear more of that from www.tuberecords.com one more tuberecords.com but everyone wants to know more about Dobbs Town
and I read it and Dave didn't and here it is friends last Thursday on WCSB.com
dot org
I am
What is Dobbs Town?
What is then Dobbs Town?
It is the stuff that dreams are made of
It's what makes Tinker Bell and the Lost Boys fly
It powers the Starship Enterprise
It's the hidden code in Windows and Mac OS though not yet available in Linux
It's the general oblivion created in the moon dance strikes the cornea of your head
Dobbs Town
It's the cancer causing teeth staining smelly pukey habit
It's the drug that helps you find God
It's the moley night before it never never ends
Dobbs Town
It is your brain
It is your brain on drugs
It's learning to work as a team and as a slave
It's where there is a lake in which resides the sword excalibur kept by the lady of the lake Connie Dobbs
And if you think it's hard to pull that stone from out of that sword out of that lake it's easy to pull a fig from a donkey's anus
Dobbs Town
It is where all the flowers have gone
It is the home of John Dillinger's real penis
Dobbs Town
It is a mystery wrapped in an enigma smothered with sautéed mushrooms and onions in a savory gravy
It is John Dillinger's penis
The savage and in muscular gravy surrounded by mushroom people
Dobbs Town
The home of both Lemurians and Cenobites
My proper home
I'm going back someday
I've got to get back to my home
Dobbs Town
It's near the coast of Honalee and the land of Fredonia
It's the world's largest producer of manna, ambrosia, froth and the green stuff that Dave injects into the brain to reanimate dead tissue
Spiritual bliss with open-loam bowling every night from midnight to dawn
Dobbs Town
It's the residence of J.R. Bob Dobbs part of the year
It's creamy and crunchy
It tastes great and it's less filling
It is margarine and it is butter
But if it were to fall into enemy hands it would mean the destruction of us all
Ah yes, Stang, but it is the downfall of us all
And it tastes bad on bread because man, those that go don't come back
They're losers, losers
No man, those who graduate from Dobbs Town come back changed
In a new form
You can't see them like you can see others
Graduated like a chrysalis to the elf
All the way up to a higher being
They growl and growl
Their tiny skins hardly large enough to pop them as they begin expanding into that new form
Dobbs Town
It's where UFOs are not just a fact of life, they're the law
Of course it's a law here, of course it's a law
Everyone needs to live by laws, by rules
We need to have our lives governed by
Dobbs Town
It's where the bad little girls and boys go
Oh, Dobbs Town
It's where something is happening all the time
And most of it unsolved
Some of it is so hard to locate
Many of the people from the Saucer Ship emblem itself have been sucked out and left here
Dobbs Town
I didn't want them to be oblique
When I strapped them down in the chair and started asking them questions about Dobbs Town
I, I, I gave them...
I gave them a new location, but the...
The website
Dobbs Town
It's Nwatsbod spelled backwards
It's Brigadoon without the haggis
It is surrounded by the seven cities of Cibola
Which are its slums
And it has a ferry to Monster Island
And what a delightful pair of individuals you'll never find there
The ferries of Monster Island
Tiny little happy people who do things for other people
Who live for other people
So big are their hearts and so tiny is their stature
They...
Dobbs Town!
That's where Amelia Earhart crashed, friends
It's where the Tunguska meteorite came out after bouncing around inside the Earth for a while
Yes, if you're waiting for another salubrious comet
Can you just illuminate that stupid passage?
Just read it again, Stan, just see what you just said
What, the Dobbs Town is where the Tunguska meteorite came out?
After bouncing around inside the planet for a while
The Tunguska meteorite was, of course, as you know from reading your book of the subgenius, Dave
Was a miniature black hole
Shot by Dobbs, the young ten-year-old J.R. Bob Dobbs from his slingshot
Completely by accident...
Out of rage?
No, he didn't even know he was doing it
It was just, you know, I mean, he picked up a...
Other kids might pick up a pebble or a cat skull for their slingshot
Yeah, a cat skull, that makes a lot more sense
What would Bob pick up? A tiny black hole, a singularity
A singularity...
Glowing essence of nothingness, sucking in all that is not Bob
And that is what he shot into the Tunguska plains of Siberia
And then, past the event horizon
The little thing itself went and then became like a bigger thing
And it went into the earth, Bob's tiny black hole did
And it bounced around like a cue ball on a pool table
Back and forth until finally it exited at the place we now know as
Dogstown!
Dogstown, friends!
It is where a thing of beauty is a joy for a while
It's where you are better than you were in high school
It's where you get all the love you want
It's where you get all the pets you ever wanted
It was never a colony of France
It is where science and magic are the same things
It is the unfolding of miscalculations
It is the dawning of the height, weight, hair and eye color of Aquarius
It is the fizzling, crackling, hip newt
It is the dissonant fifth vortex disrupting the harmonic convergence
It is where the early worm gets away
It is where the grave diggers leave their shoes in the middle of the night
Dogstown!
It is for when you are too lazy to kill yourself
Where there are no lawyers
And where the government never tries to be helpful
Dogstown, friends!
It is where you can make your imaginary friends fight to the death
Dogstown!
It's between the dark and daylight
When the night is beginning to lower
It is where neither heredity nor environment matter
It is where the lamb and the lion lay down and have sex together, friends
Dogstown!
You can only follow and listen
It is proof that hell is full
And the dead walk the earth
The fabric is worth cleaning
Like yourself
One thread can back me to thousands of other threads
That is our caustic solution for you as members of this solemn group gathered together
Squandered and quashed and pushed under heavy stones
So that you may not know the truth that we speak
And yet here we are speaking it to you
Dogstown is not a place where a man or woman dwells
But a place in the heart
As big as that mighty elephant yoke
And twice as tasty as all the trees that you could imagine
Now imagination is not a place you want to stay
It's not a place you want to bring home
Bring the kids, grandma, ride the ferris wheel with
It's not the kind of place you want to leave for a better home
It's a place you visit over and over again
With your pants on, your pants off
And your heart ripped right out hanging from your chest
Dogstown
Where Bob comes home
After an easy day's work
And where you can come home too, friends
Where you'll be home
Where you'll finally realize why
Why
And why you can find out more about beautiful Dogstown
When you join the Church of the Subgenius
The world's only first, true, last, final, one, true religion
Because it admits it is true
It is the only one that's not full of crap
And I can try to find the age
I know it's coming each time
I can tell it, you tell it
It's where Ennio Morricone was delivered
Of his inspiration for this music in the background
Huge, huge mandibles
Large, large, fresh, gammy legs
And now the matador Dobbs steps in
And he whips out before the enraged Triceratops dinosaur
Flashing his red Dobbs-headed cape
In front of the maddened beast
The furious creature stomps its feet and paws at the ground
Dobbs grins, he smokes, the creature charges
Dobbs whips out his pipe
And gives it a little conk on the noggin as it runs by
And after that
It sits and pants like a little puppy dog
And the monster is dead
Another type of false compensation
Or over-assertiveness
Is exemplified in the one who always comes late to every gathering
In order for everyone to notice him when he arrives
And who leaves early so that people will notice when he leaves
Or who is constantly name-dropping
After he said that, then he said, arise
Take up your bed
And go your way to your house
Take up your bed and walk
Then he stretched out on the floor
Remember to take your matador first
Matador first
Well, sometimes when I'm with a guy
I wish they'd tie me up with red licorice ropes
And then spank me
And then he'd eat the ropes
And then he'd free me
And then we'd make love with a philharmonic played bolero
I have a lot of fantasies about being tied up and spanked
Okay, let's see
So she's gonna make love to me, that's good
But she's gonna kill me and eat me
That's bad
I've never seen such nervous chickens
Well, either that or the animal that attacked him was a chicken
It's all done with a little scientific magic
You see, each little blueberry is coated with a thin layer of goat embryonic fluid
I'll get you, get the Senator some water
You've been watching too many of them Italian zombie flicks
As do I you
They're idle
They're lazy
They need to work
You're a very, very sick man
Boy, you ever seen a bloke with a foot up his nose?
Woomera, woomera
Babalook, boomerang, crocodile, kookaburra, wombat, orangutan
Wee-ho, way-ho, taramunga mine
Kwondong, billabong, gandablui, pine
Platypus, emu, wallaby, roo
Ivus, bulgar, white cockatoo
Marabara, caracola, mine, fangirl
Bogobrine, pyromine, never-crying yanker
Hoopra, hoopra, ha, ha, ha
Yanker, white cockatoo, ya, ya
Yaaaaa!
Oh sure, he came back from the dead, he raped her, then bit her to death, is that what he did?
Oh yeah, now I remember
You threw up on me
How sweet
You're supposed to be setting a good example, now will you get back to your coffin immediately
Being a dick is a 24 hour a day job
If my head wasn't hurting so much I'd have sworn I was in heaven
Heaven for guys who like big tits
Speaking of which, dear friends, Reverend Susie the Floozy was in the Tampa Divival thanks to the queers for Bob
And here's...
She is for Bob
Oh, that's what brings me to my subject tonight, Seekers
What there is to love about this church
What is it, Pat and Max?
Absolutely fucking nothing, I hate those fucking church stuff!
Oh, what a goddamn thing
From my perspective, on my knees in the trenches out there
Trying to bring some fucking slack to my slack-star block
The things I take on in myself
In the performance of this ministry, dear, dear, dear Seekers
Jesus Christ, it sucks
I mean, I've been out there for years
On my knees in the trenches
Oh, trying to bring you to the bounteous teeth of dogs
Oh, but when I get around to getting my share
That ain't a teeth
But you know I gotta suck anyway like a leaf blower in rivers
Or I'm gonna lose my fucking job
Oh yeah, the wonders of this damn church
You know, doing a good job as a Christian
Is a lot like pissing your pants in a dark suit
It gives you a warm feeling and nobody notices
But, doing a job as a subgenius
Is like taking a shit in your own pants
Except, you ain't wearing pants
And honey, that ain't your shit
Oh, peed as it may
And I assure you, Seekers, it does pee
Oh, the sad fact is that it falls to someone to be the Judas guard
Who's going to lead you into the warm embrace
To take you away from this tag-team blusterfucked-in-nowheresville
That the conspiracy dares to call alive
Someone has to bitch-slap you butt-whites on all five of your cheeks
When Bob's Hallelujah Train comes a-humpin' in
To that station of opportunity's sake
Somebody's gotta be playing in that bell
Because the express train to Dobstown
Don't always run
On time, kids
And I'm down there trying to get your asses on board
Somebody's gotta be there to shove your bobby asses
On that train, yeah
Like one of those Tokyo subway packers
Like a Taipei green bay packer
Like a psychotic fudge packer
Urging you on into those recto-cranial convulsions that say
Wee!
Oh, thank you, Bob
And that's exactly what he said back
Because it's gonna take something to force-pump all that energy into your lobes
To clean out the insidious mind-controlling allergens that they've put in there
Oh, yes
Oh, she said buying time
Oh, it's sort of like getting an undercoating
But not quite as much of a rip-off
And, but, Seekers, you need protection
Because you're out there every day
Running a terrible risk of infection
Dealing with that normal human element
Oh, and you're out there
And you've gotta shoot the conspiracy's log flume rod
But maybe watch out for those blogs
Because it's like Mr. Toad's Wild Ride in a septic tank out there
Now, you may not believe me
You know, I've been maybe getting on in years
I am more than all of you fuckers put together
But I assure you that I still have all of my teeth
Oh!
And both ends are smiling as I promised you
But Bob is gonna tear those shit holes a new navel to contemplate
Yes, because yes, there's beauty in the world if you know where to look
And if you know where to look, you can avoid that shit entirely
Sure, it's an ugly job
But I'm up to ugly
Yes!
Yes, and I may be stupid for leaving in some
Glad-handed, grinning, half-toned, bunco artist
Who left all of our asses in the lurch on that day
Yes!
Fucker!
I may be a total moron
We're still looking to the stars
And hope in my five-chambered little heart
That something's coming to get us up on Oliver
Yes!
I may be a shit-nosed turd-goblin retard
For not waking up to smell that freshly-pinched loaf of dobson he lays on my upper lip every morning
Every day!
Woo!
Sure, I may be a pathetic, brain-damaged, drooling, pissing, moaning, sublet-tail wacky
Any of it
For not throwing in my lot with some better-connected titty
Oh, but Seekers, being a sub-dub genius
It's a higher calling
And as long as Bob keeps getting me high
Who the fuck do you think I'm gonna call?
Because sure, he's a lying son of a bitch
But he's our lying son of a bitch
Sure, he's got one hand in your wallet pocket
And the other one up your toe into the eighth knuckle
But some dead playwright guy
Eugene O'Neill wrote Frosty's Orgasm or Iceman Cummins
Something like that
This dead fucker, anyhow, whoever the hell he was
He said something that had the Colonel's name on it
And there's a whole great truth inside of it
Seekers, the lie of a pipe dream
Is what gives life to the whole misbegotten mad lot of us
Drowned or sober
And as long as Bob's pouring those fucking drinks
I'm gonna belly up to his bar
Praise Bob!
Kill her
Obviously you won't
I wanna kill you, Connie
You're responsible for the pain of these four
I'm so tired, get your hands off me
How can we tell whether our friends are ready to walk the path of Dobbs?
Surely just not by the t-shirts they wear or the pipes in their mouths
You sins killed him!
You sins!
The devil!
You killed him!
God's son is dead, the blood is red on your sins
You have vindicated yourself for murder
You are the Satan's child, smashing heads and ripping limbs from Christians
You died for you
How many more will die for you?
You killed Satan, the son of God
We did!
You sins killed him
Our sins killed him!
How long will he die for you?
He will always be dead for you!
Those were your original sins of death
The result is our sins and killing
For you sins the world will die
Yes, and flesh will burn
Babies will die
How many babies will die?
When sponsored by government, abortion is genocide
Yes, in China they killed babies like that
They will make nothing to save money and contraceptives
Nor will they keep the righteous children of God from being born
Imagine piles of gurgling bloody protein
Sin for abortion
Gargoyles have come up from hell and lay feces that will cause great plagues
Leprosy which we have seen in the Bible will permeate society
And limbs will fall from their bodies in great numbers
Appendages on the streets
People dead
No more children
Masses, newborn, choristers
Cries going onward
Cries in first Christians will fund those inflicted with the devil's plague
Uh, their sins killed you friends
Church of New Faith
Post office box
You got that pencil ready?
Church of New Faith, my God man!
P.O. Box 9152
Virginia Beach, Virginia 23450
Yes, Church of New Faith
We used to play them all the time on this show
And now they've got a CD out and it's all sounded better
That's uh, Virginia Beach, Virginia 23450
Uh, yes, yes
Confess and we won't hurt you anymore
We don't like doing this at all
No urinating on the wall
Any offenders will be prosecuted
Urinating is not allowed
Urinating is not permitted
I think one of you space guys or whatever it is you are
Could have dropped me a note or something
You know, just to let me know that I'm not crazy
You will speak when spoken to
I will deactivate your vocal mode
Well, that's, that's not what I wanted to say
I wanted to say something about
How freedom demands responsibility
And how like Tom Paine
In the days of old when there was
So much res-revolutionary fervor
Going on around the place
A lot of people were like throwing their shoes
In the harbor and stuff
And waving flags and dancing
But most of the people were just suffocating
Underneath those abstruse tunnels they created themselves
And the lobster
But now
We've got to fight not only tanks
We have to fight computers with our bare knees
We have to not only like
Get down on all fours and crawl across the ocean
But crawl under barbed wire
We've got to become wired ourself
So that we can stop
The next few acts of the play before
The demon goes down
Don't worry about it
Don't worry about the future my friend
There, there is no future
For you anyway
You will ride out
On the wave of occurrences
That have been set in motion
Years and years ago
Perhaps thousands of years ago
Have you ever seen the 35 degree bus
Can shake
Check it out baby
Yes
It's one of the few things you want to know
If you want to climb it's the circles
It's in your elite
Do you know what CFR means
It doesn't mean college in fluid replacement
No it's the council for foreign affairs
I mean
No
Do you know who the Bilderburgers are
They are not people who make huge sandwiches
On the west side
The Bilderburgers
Are a group of
Well to use the phrase used earlier
Mushroom men
People with dildo sized heads
Much bigger than the top
I'm afraid we're going to have to disclose the
Resettlement plans there Captain Yolk
And here we get to something very important
In the Church of the Subgenius
And that is
All of you that have been raised here
Whether you're Buddhist or Mohammed
Or Jewish or Christian
You've been taught that
Your leader
Your God
Your savior
Your Messiah
Is a man worth imulating
Bob
Bob is not a man to copy
And Bob says
I don't practice what I preach
Because I'm not the kind of person I'm preaching to
Bob also says
I'd rather be lucky than good any day
You see Bob
See children
One of the most important rules in the Bible
That the Church of the Subgenius is
That the Church lets you
Pull the wool over your own eyes
Now children
When you pull the wool over your own eyes
It's not like the Church is doing it
Why the great Churches want you to pull the wool over your own eyes
And keep it there
We want you to pull the wool over your own eyes
And relax in the safety of your own delusions
And after a while children
You're going to get saved
You're going to get sick of those delusions
And you're going to start thinking for yourself
Praise Bob!
That's what Bob wants to do
And I say as long as you're alive
Shout, make noise, all efforts
Because when you do
You shut up like hell
Kassu pullonkorki otta sakilsi
Otta sakilsi aluspajan
Helema mua tajo
Velsi lentävä poliukko
Väkijuoma pullon piniästä ostin
Piniästä ostin pullonkaulan
Heti huulille nostin lentävä poliukko
Tyrät ne rytköivät
Tanssiin käy tie
Rytkut vain rytköivät
Sit urme lukseen vie
I aloviina pullon pohojahan ryypin
Pohojahan ryypin remelissä
Nämä sammune tyypin naapurin poliukko
Kortistosta eilen korvauksen nostin
Korvauksen nostin viinakaupassa
Näin naapurin kostin lentävä poliukko
Eka pakasta minä naikkosen iskin
Naikkosen iskin
Tarjos mulle vielä kalijan
Ja viskin hampaaton mätisäkki
Tyrät ne rytköivät
Tanssiin käy tie
Rytkut vain rytköivät
Sit urme lukseen vie
Hamekorvissa mä naikkosta pistin
Naikkosta pistin varvin jälke
Menin äärelle tiskin lentävä poliukko
Kolme kossua ja vissuja
Vissu kossulla ja kossu kolalla
Votka lapiolla ja votka palamalla
Eiku sammuttamalla
Karttiakin lyötin
Huastetin rita
Huastetin rita kosti pistin
Viikseen naapurin ita lentävä poliukko
Rytmä römä
Sekä rillumarei
Rillumarei
Mustama ja meijät kamarille pei
Lentävä poliukko
Tyrät ne rytköivät
Tanssiin käy tie
Rytkut vain rytköivät
Sit urme lukseen vie
Kesku pasku vielä sellissä
Hausuna
The smell of a smelly dog in the cellar
Esko, Heikki, Veina and Kalle
Veina and Kalle, the last two
The flying dog was left under the train
We are in the right, the sit-in begins
The sit-in begins
Esko will get us there
Neat
Dickhead
I said it multiple times
We're not gonna找тus
a dumb shit.
They'll treat you unequal.
They will drown you in their mediocrity.
They will force you to kneel at their level.
But you will fight.
You will not be alone, but you will fight.
The next rule of the church of the subgenius is
a rule that's only become necessary in the last 10 or 12 years.
Have movements have appeared.
Vast ships, clippers upon the horizon
to bring the rest of us to salvation.
Will ships attract mollusks and barnacles, as you well know?
And here in the church of the subgenius,
those mollusks and molecules take the form of hip wimps.
And the next rule of the church of the subgenius is
no hip wimps.
No what?
No hip wimps.
What?
No hip wimps, children.
No hip wimps.
Don't join this church looking to get cool off us.
Don't join this church looking to suck the scottabob
because he won't help.
Kill me.
There are people beyond redemption.
Yes, there are even people whose money will not let them into the church.
They might not have membership.
Yes, they might attend meetings.
They might even yell when the pope calls upon them,
but deep in their heart, they're hip wimps.
Hi kids, it's me, Casey Sausage Casey.
Remember the 1990s when clinical depression and self-mutilation were all the rage?
Well, now you can relive those self-deprecating golden years
with KTEL's new record offer entitled, I Suck.
That's KTEL.com.
The letter I and the word suck.
You'll get Beck's I'm a Loser.
I'm a loser, baby.
Radiohead's I'm a creep.
But I'm a freak.
Silverchair's I'm a freak.
I'm a freak.
And I'm a complete and total frigging moron.
Need some record, record, record.
But think, think, think you could go back in time.
I am and I am right now.
I'm just wishing I hadn't come tonight because I...
Because you did come back in time to get here?
Well, yeah, because I'm, well, I'd have to be here already now
or else this part wouldn't make sense.
The rest of it, but I'm already full of oblique little passages of time
that don't make no sense.
How about yourself?
Hi, if I could, if, if time control as, as prophesied by Dobbs were ours now,
what would, what would one do with such a power?
If you could go back in time, would you go back in time, for instance,
and kill Hitler to prevent terror or, or...
Or kill Hitler.
Or kiss Hitler to prevent...
Or kiss, right, to make him a...
Because some people said, you know, Ava Brown was just like his front
because he didn't have a girlfriend to hang out with,
the Burkish guy, and he'd rather be hanging out with Goring or Himmler.
Really?
Yeah, they said...
Oh, that, well, well, you know, he has a lot of enemies.
You know, the old frustrated rage thing, you know, like he must be wanting to be with boys.
You know how he used to kiss those Hitler youth, those young men on the cheek, you know,
these 12-year-old boys?
Well, so did I.
So did I.
I saw you do it too, David.
I was forced to.
I was a political dissident.
And that was one of the jobs they made us do besides ripping the clothes off the stiffs.
We'd up-gassed the stiffs, pull their clothes off, and then we'd have to go and kiss the
Hitler youth boys.
And believe me, that was not hell.
But, you know, if you could go back...
Well, would you go back in time?
Could, would you dare to change history?
Because say you did kill or kiss Hitler, maybe the world would be a much better place for
lots of people, but perhaps Hitler was the madman who also killed the world.
The one who would have been worse than Hitler.
The one who would have won.
What if Hitler, at some point in his career, was indirectly or directly responsible for
killing someone else who might, in fact, have destroyed the entire world?
How could you have had someone...
But Hitler was going to go for it.
Would you play God?
If you could, if you could go back in time, would you play God?
I would probably play God or I would play Henry VIII.
Lieutenant.
We're in a conflict.
Time, time, time.
Transported back hundreds of years.
Oh, what I saw that got that glass knight, his tongue was as long as this.
Wait a minute.
You mean this stuff reproduced itself inside the decontamination chamber, and then as we,
as we stepped up the current, it just, it just grew?
Precisely.
A monster!
A monster will set fire to the city and trample on the people who try to run away.
Who are you?
Commander for conquest of Earth.
From the third planet of the black hole, I will now speak.
You know what?
If I fuck up, I will break you.
Another terrible way the Earth might suddenly come to an end would be...
Oh, yeah.
Oops, okay, now.
Category two, plastic soldiers.
What is when you go away from your house and the plastic soldiers come alive?
They lack discipline.
They need to be forced to march in order.
But, uh...
Excited by the boom of the van.
And the towel forces them with a big lighter and a...
They, uh, scatter across the floor.
And a little hot paperclip.
And those little bayonets can hurt when they come out and they stab your barefoot when
you're laying on your bed.
At 3 a.m.
Yes, that's right.
As they're marching around or caught running down the hallway.
They'll come up and attack your face on the bed while you're asleep.
Oh, really?
You know, they're very resourceful little beggars.
Just like in the movies, folks.
All science fiction movies have a moment of truth, especially in the movies.
I mean, I've seen a lot of science fiction movies where they're like, oh, I'm going
to jump in and rob little toys that you've never the inside of.
Hmm, I missed.
That one.
That one about the little action figures and so forth.
Yeah, that's pretty fun.
Have you seen that one?
They come alive.
That's a good one, yeah.
And, uh, well those scenes are pretty amazing where they come alive and are your worst
nightmare.
Little toy soldiers who just walk in the state of verse 10.
Well, I haven't seen A So many films to see.
But perhaps none of us have time anymore, because, uh, we might have to wait for it.
Would it be like before Metro?
We would be real happy watching.
see that coming. Yeah.
A long way away. Unless you're in the theater
watching Toy Soldiers or something. Even a gamma
ray post. Then you cannot
see the last droid.
And if you're in your car, you can't see it.
But if the vacuum of space
suddenly collapses,
we would have no warning. And it would be
over instantly. It's a 3D version of frogs, right?
Yeah. And if you were
in the bathroom, you wouldn't see the end of the droid.
It's not such a strange idea.
The vacuum of space itself
would suddenly collapse. I heard there was a naked
person in here.
It might happen.
Suddenly, the establishment
is filled with police.
The Third World War might begin
any minute. We'll all be killed.
Why should we bother about giant turtles?
Yes, maybe you're right.
I know how much you love your turtles.
But there are other things in life just as
important, like having fun friends.
Our ancient legend
did mention fire-eating turtles.
Remember, the next time
if you are naughty again,
I'll shave your head.
And we can't waste any time
because while they are sleeping,
we'll eat their brains raw.
Let's see the kids later, and let's fix
the spacecraft first.
See, Bob is a businessman, and Bob is going to try to
prevent the planet Earth from being sold.
So when Bob goes to talk to these men from Planet X,
he has to have a representative
constituency here on Earth.
Because the men from Planet X, well,
they're businessmen. Pure and simple businessmen.
And they're going to say, Bob, your proposal
sounds good, but I gotta see numbers.
I've got to see hard data.
Show me the numbers of subjugates on this Earth,
and it's your planet.
And we'll know it's worth saving.
See, that's Bob's
job, is to
someone's got to explain to those
aliens in ways they can understand
why the human Roman race
is the way it is, so that they
don't put us out of our means.
And they understand the bottom line.
Which is why we're the world's first industrial church.
The church of love and money.
It certainly is.
Sheriff, are you nuts?
You'll have a swamp full of hicks out here
shooting at each other.
Let me tell you something, boy.
Better shooting out here in the swamp
than in town there.
What do you want me to do, go out there
and get bit by all them mosquitoes?
That meteorite didn't kill those people.
It turned them into a bunch of goddamn monsters.
I saw it. I saw it.
It came from the sky.
Kato, calling command ship.
Send advance parties immediately.
I've now established
humans high in protein.
And easy prey.
Welcome to glorious Cincinnati.
Queen of Ohio's alpine ski resorts.
Welcome to polka hell.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I know this sounds crazy,
but the Superstation Studios
have been taken over by creatures
from another planet.
Stick all the bits of brain in a plastic bag, Barry.
We'll need your analysis.
No bloody way, mate.
You can come down here and do that yourself.
Hi, friends.
I'm Heinrich Himmler, and boy, when it gets hot,
it's hard to understand.
It really gets hard.
And when it gets big, it gets really big.
We like to make it big and hard
for you to understand.
So zip up your zip suit
and check it out, kids.
Is that why my tongue got this way?
It's all big and hard.
I can't hold it.
You thought it was light?
And you thought that it was something mutant and ugly.
Really, in the subgenius church,
that hanging, lollygaggy tongue
and that twisted face,
is the sexiest thing you've ever seen.
That's what subgenius women call beautiful.
And wait till you see what the men go for.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Can you imagine?
Have you ever seen a woman with that many lips?
He's coming over here.
Have you ever seen women with that many lips
there?
And look, each one of them
has its own separate personality.
That's what you want, guys.
Believe you me.
Once you've gone there,
you'll never go,
to the other place.
Anytime, time, ever again.
I'm speaking to you professionally
as a sex professional now.
Now, professionally speaking,
what is the best sex position
for a subgenius to take?
Under Bob.
All is under Bob.
Bob is always on top.
Yeah.
And if one has earned
a reach around
for sex,
from that great super salesman,
that living avatar of slack,
then one should leave
a special tip for him.
And it's important to leave that tip
in the right jar, isn't it, Reverend?
Yes, that's right.
And use a nice, clean knife
when you separate the tip
from all the rest.
A clean, clean, clean
and sterilized knife.
Apparently, Bob came
and did something
with all of us.
And, of course,
our lives could instantly be
snuffed out by
flood basalt volcanism.
What if the show just stopped?
Suddenly, we would go
flying off the planet.
That's true.
A show is traveling
at such a rate
that a sudden stoppage
would cause
a relativistic shift.
We'd be flung forward
like bags of laundry.
And our landing
would not be gentle.
The really bad laundry.
Yeah, the durian fruit
smelling laundry.
Oh, little special
frozen durian fruit thing.
Some say the world
will end in fire.
Some say in ice.
Is that obvious?
Oh, my God.
Monster.
These are apparently
a part of your work in space.
Monster live in magma
of underground
in huge volcanoes.
And look, there is its mate
sitting also in the lava.
This is why we did not
see it the first time.
We could not read
through the magma
of underground.
Progressive
fading coloration
makes monster
a confusing sight.
There is monster 2000.
I know you think
you thought you saw
a monster,
as you call it,
but I'm sure
you only need
to get some rest.
It'll all look different
in the future.
You know,
we put a man on the moon.
Monsters just
don't exist anymore.
He says he saw
a monster.
And thanks to
KPFA
and Doug
and Howell
and WCSB
and Chaz
and Dave
and friends.
Thanks to Bob.
And you can learn more
about Bob
and what this church
is all about.