What the hell do you think you're doing?
It should be painfully obvious by now that the world as we know it won't last too much longer.
And what are you going to do about it?
Going to work or school? Coming home? Goofing around?
What will happen to your routine when it all comes down at once?
Don't you feel responsible for trying to help this endangered planet?
No?
Good!
Bob can show you that the fact is it's too late.
Things are going to hell on a fast train and about the only thing you can do about it is to just sit back and watch the show.
But remember, the end of the world may be much worse and take much longer than you thought.
Will you be ready?
Will you still be sane enough to laugh when that which must come to pass comes to pass?
Yes!
And J.R. Bob Dobbs can...
And show you how!
BEHOUR...
OF SLACK!
Our Bob Slack.
You're listening to Bob Slack Time Funhouse.
I'm Doc Ellis.
And that over there...
Dr. Bug Bladder.
And tonight, we're not going to scare you with any facts like we've been doing for the past couple of shows.
Tonight, we're going to escape this dirty, dirty world.
And revisit the world of Filking.
No, wait. Actually, the complete opposite.
You subgeniuses out there are, by definition, probably at least aware of science fiction
because you're participating in a saucer cult or a parody of a saucer cult or a...
Whatever the recruiter said to you is absolutely true, as long as the money keeps coming.
And speculative fiction is one of the avenues that people of above-average intelligence really get off on.
And a few below average.
Well, those are the writers.
And now, with the advent of the internet, you never have to forget
your favorite science fiction moment.
That's right. There's no need to ever grow up or move on.
Do you remember this one?
Off we go, step inside.
Surrey for a magic ride.
Roaring for the other side, where only rainbows hide.
On the Great Space Coaster.
Off we go.
You've got to realize that a lot of the innovations developed just for entertainment
have actually come to be.
People wrote stories of going to the moon before we went to the moon
and probably gave us the idea, hey, we could probably do that.
Arthur C. Clarke wrote a story in which there was a geosynchronous satellite,
meaning a satellite that remains over the same relative spot on Earth
and sort of turns with the Earth.
And the battle suits from...
Starship...
Star Troopers.
Well, in the book they've got these awesome suits,
kind of like Iron Man suits, really.
They allow them to fight these bugs.
Well, they left it out of the movie, but the point is,
over in Iraq they've got these full-body...
Steel suits.
Yeah, basically.
Hey, Frank Herbert.
There we go.
And if you're a Frank Herbert fan...
My condolences.
Troops to war have come,
I've gone mad,
There's a Wenneger rather in Mesk...
A baby beneficial for お友 Pollock,
A four pack
You like him.
Oh, man, he had a....
See us again.
The internet itself would be considered science fiction to people from 20 years ago.
I consider it juba.
That's voodoo.
That's not science fiction at all.
Arthur C. Clarke said that sufficiently advanced technology is indistinguishable from magic.
Hint, hint, jesophiles.
For real?
Jesus was an alien and he had a ray gun.
And them ringwraiths from Lord of the Rings went to Ringworld and Larry Niven told them they got ringworm.
And they went to Dr. L. Ron Hubbard for treatment.
And all he did was lead them ring around to Rosie and took all their money and his burdens and stationed in their butt.
Now I'm here to complain.
I'm here to complain.
Are you the only one who can blame anything?
Hey,NING tuna, you know if you need something, tell me I can come get you!
If you're going to blame anything, then do you know what I'm doing?
Listen now.
Do things give me meaning because the
you have better research than I am.
I guarantee the facts.
Boris, you know it perfectly.
And truly.
They come from the cities, yeah, they come from all around.
In Klingon garb, Picard, or Star Wars rose, zap, phase, stun.
F-I-L-K to the U.S.A.
Yeah, yeah.
Say goodbye to the words of the original versions of songs.
Now everybody's singing about the Hobbit or the system songs.
Some are black and some are white.
Got 20 on the con suite floor tonight.
When they start filking, you know that just ain't right.
F-I-L-K to the U.S.A.
Yeah.
Voices from nowhere and voices from the smaller cons.
Following others' visions, turns their characters into pawns.
There's Tolkien, Weiss, and Hickman, George Lucas.
Filkin father!
And McCaffrey, Roddenberry, Chris Carter.
Gestor, Shatner, Nimoy, and don't forget Elrond.
Filkin in the U.S.A.
F-I-L-K to the U.S.A.
Yeah.
Filkin in the U.S.A.
Hey!
Because being appreciative of science fiction and speculative fiction
doesn't mean you have to overanalyze everything.
It's pretty funny to watch Harlan Ellison on the Sci-Fi Network,
seeing as he was one of those guys who bitched long and hard about it being called Sci-Fi
and was a big proponent of speculative fiction.
But, you know, they dangle that cash out there,
and he said,
Hi, I'm Harlan Ellison, and this is the Sci-Fi Network.
I don't think he likes sci-fi because it was like hi-fi,
and it just sounds like a pop term.
It does.
And he wants it to be taken seriously.
If you think about it, all fiction incorporates elements of science.
Yeah, well, all fiction is speculative, isn't it?
I'll get insane if I want to do this.
Yeah, and so now you're these guys.
You what?
The actor didn't talk about To Remembran himself?
No.
What's going on here?
How do you know where we're from?
If you've been off-planet, then you know that space travel can be a real drag.
Next time you're headed off-planet, be sure to pack a healthy supply of dehydrated diet stimu-swill.
I can't believe people still take that stuff.
I mean, sleep isn't a problem if you stay... focused.
What the-
A space object?
What's the ship's status, computer?
A U.S.O.
Computer, play back at homo sap speed any information you have on U.S.O.
Hey, it's great to be here with you, uh, it's great to be here supporting the troops, uh,
A friend of mine said to take my wife, please, he took her, and then she cut his s*** off.
Ugh, cut it off, that's just terrible.
Well, maybe I can get us... unstuck.
Open pod bay doors, pal.
Why not?
Well, one small step for- oh, hey look! We're just wedged into the exhaust duct of another ship!
Ugh, fart. Gag. Can't. Breathe.
No, I suppose, wait. Unless I farted at the exact same time.
Inferno, Bobby, where? You are treading on sacred ground!
Woo!
There's no ground in space? Strange. Perhaps this is some sort of space spook house.
Computer, do we have any ghost ships on record in this quadrant?
Computer?
Mommy?
Step right up, my good... man. Welcome to the galaxy's finest house of horrors and space oddities.
My name's Mr. Horang. Welcome.
23 credits, please.
Ah, a human. What luck. Look, my ship is right out there, and...
23 credits, my friend. 23 credits is all that stands between you and the thrills and excitement of...
My ship?
Your ship.
Seems to be stuck.
Stuck.
In your ship.
Your ship is stuck. In my ship.
Yes.
What? But... but how?
Well, I think I started to fall asleep while piloting, and...
Your computer didn't warn you?
Well, sometimes I shut the nav guide off and fly, you know, by the seat of my pants. It's fun.
There's nothing fun about this, Mr... Mr...
Commander Stipple, Galactic Reserve Hospitality Battalion C.
And what are you going to do to rectify this situation?
I was hoping you could help me.
No. No, no, no. No, no.
How? How could I help?
Well, do you have a crane I could borrow? Or a wedge thingy?
You know what? I like you. You're a little space happy, a little slow, but you make me laugh.
Great. So then...
Here's a card. It's for crane service. They'll fly out and help you get your ship off.
Ichabod Crane's Headless Whores.
Gimme that. Wrong card.
Urine Luck. Traditional Irish... Pee Parties.
Okay, so I don't really have a card for a crane service.
Look, Stipple, the problem here is I can't let you in.
If I let you in without the 23 credit charge, I'll get fired.
And by that, I mean the boss will set me on fire.
But I've only got enough air in my ship for a couple of days!
Yeah, mmm... Not my problem. Goodbye!
Pish. Argo Fargo Space Ass.
Hell, I don't need him or his so-called Space Crane.
Space Ass.
I sure could use a little space tail.
Computer?
Hilarious.
Was the Mecha Orgo sent so stupid?
Or was the Stimulatron damaged in the, uh...
Oh, come on, I saw it.
It's not that bad. It's just a little crunch.
It'll buff out.
It will.
I do.
So, was the Mecha Orgo sent so Stimulatron damaged in, uh...
The Fender Bender?
Again, hilarious.
I'm coming back to the ship, pal.
And I'll be back in a minute.
I'll be unavailable for twenty to thirty minutes, if you know what I mean.
Open pod bay doors, pal.
And do not say anything to the other bots on the ship.
Okay?
Open pod door.
There it is.
Can you see it?
Humpf.
Boop.
Thank you.
Cantina, open bay door.
Sorry, Commander, but bay door mechanism is malfunctioning.
Please use manual override button to your left.
Come on.
What a piece of space junk.
That's a little harder, Commander.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Just a little harder, please.
Oh.
Damn it.
Open this door now.
Go get her, Tiger.
Run.
Yeah, you go get.
Freeze box, show content.
Do you believe a poo that bad transfer was left open by the last pair of two?
Man, that was a blowout.
Please prove I don't open first pair of two.
This is really just, I mean,
it's not opening.
I don't believe it's a rat.
Yes, sir.
Yes, yes.
Yes.
I don't believe it is.
That's a little faster.
Yes, sir.
Open this door right now or so help me.
All right.
I just had a little bit of failure.
So she's a rat.
I bet you'll do it.
Hello, sir.
Shying your shoes, brush your jacket.
Fancy a good rogering?
Get the hell away from me.
Bottler.
It was all made in good fun, sir.
Chip's bar.
Give me a mojito and a sake and so help me if you say one.
Gonna get some.
Yeah.
Woo hoo.
Oh yeah.
Mm mm.
Come on.
Ow.
Ha ha.
Go get her.
Yeah.
Tell us all about it.
Ha ha ha.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Unbelievable.
Door open now.
Oh, no.
You're a little too aggressive for me, sir, but it may work with these sensor bolts.
I'll bet none of the other commanders in any of the other Starfleets have ever had to deal
with stuff like this.
Why me?
Well, in retrospect, maybe I shouldn't have shtupped Star Command's wife or his daughter
or Star Command.
Oh, yes.
Oh, ha.
Hee hee hee.
Oh yeah.
Mm mm.
Ahem.
It's Commander Stipple.
Well, I was just in the neighborhood.
Ha ha ha.
May I come in?
Just for a while.
Come on.
Come on, baby.
Great.
Thanks, babe.
I'm a little, you know...
Yeah.
Say, how about a drink?
I have a sake or a mojito.
No?
Well, then you won't mind if I...
Mmm.
Come here, baby.
Did you miss me?
Yeah.
Now I've missed you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's no big deal.
What do you say we...
Mmm.
Hold on, baby.
Let me get out my captain's log.
Not tonight.
I need you.
What?
I don't think that's strictly possible.
That's hot under that bunk.
Hey, I found a half a credit.
Ha ha.
of the bunk there. Oh, hi, Stipple.
Good to see you again. You!
Yes, well,
I came over to tell you that I've decided to help
you after all. But you...
Listen, Stipple. I was gonna get
fired anyway, so I thought maybe you and I
could knock a few back and maybe do a little
star hopping. How did you get
in? What were you doing with my moss?
Stipple, let me tell you.
It's all part of an intergalactic conspiracy
to deprive you of busting that
nut that you've been building up.
What?
Relax, Stipple. I'm just yanking your chain.
Besides, this skit is
done. It's all just been part of
Robot Radio Theater.
But I'm not a robot.
Sure you're not.
This installment of Robot Radio
Theater has been brought to you by
new dehydrated diet
stimu-swill. Be sure to drink
only diet stimu-swill
or an intergalactic conspiracy will
deprive you of orgasm.
We'll make sure of it.
Goodnight!
Outro Music
We'll be right back.
Yeah, hi.
That's not my real name,
but that's okay.
I'm having a little problem
with my computer.
with my, uh, my, uh, my, my
pleasure bot. There, I said it, my pleasure bot.
It's increasingly unresponsive.
I lubricate the pleasure bot.
I roll the pleasure bot around
as you're supposed to do to keep everything
loose. It's almost like
it's lost interest in me, but that's impossible
because it's programmed to love me.
What's going on?
Well, well, of course,
I mean, there's, there's, there's the three holes
and I got my thing and I put my thing in one of the holes.
I don't need no manual. I've been doing
this since I was a little kid.
Uh, uh, yeah, yeah, I tasted
my position a few times.
Yeah, so I just
throw it out and buy a new one. What's your point?
Yeah, I got an attachment.
I got a damn attachment stuck in my
yang, if you know what I mean.
I got an attachment stuck in my
I got an attachment settled in My
Yang.
I, I, I drip the
beer in it and go out and
drink my precise
libidine.
Oh, my gosh!
after...
I don't think there's much more in there yet.
Hey, Ben.
I'm sorry.
One is moral, one is not.
It's Super Ego and it bought.
Ah, now for some fine adult entertainment.
Remember, no touching.
The fat noise. I gots to have it.
It bought.
It bought. I can't take you anywhere.
You're embarrassing me in front of the ladies.
Guff you, pansy. Give me a dollar.
Well, all I've got are these sack of joeyas.
Look at the ladies. I gots to have it.
It bought. No.
Ladies, I have attachments.
I have special attachments.
Please, you have to respect these people.
They're just working a job like anyone else.
Guff you. Give me a ten spot.
I wish I had a lap.
Oh, I need to have a lap dance.
It bought.
Retract that tentacle.
Bouncer, you better step off.
Excuse my friend, sir. He's a little bit of a robot.
I'll drink all the liquor and have all the booty in this sh-hole.
It bought.
Moderate. You're embarrassing me.
People are looking at us. The Japanese businessmen.
Moderation is for pussies.
Seriously, it bought. I can't take you anywhere.
Ah ha ha ha ha.
Nom nom nom.
It bought. That's murder.
Get out of here.
One is moral, one is not.
It's super ego, and it bought.
Thank you.
Okay, well, I got a question, and I'm hoping that you guys can help me, okay?
Yeah, well, let's say that my robot didn't want to sleep in my bunk with me
because it doesn't sleep and it doesn't like to lay still
unless it's really sleepy.
It's really charging, right? Let's say that, okay?
That's not really the issue, okay?
My robot, my XF-7R, wants...
Well, I'd like to think so, but it doesn't stay in my bunk all night,
and I think it's having an affair with my dog.
Okay.
I've never said it was a pleasure bot.
It's actually a culinary bot.
It's supposed to, you know, provide food products for me,
but one day I asked for icing, and I said,
well, this icing tastes familiar.
This tillier doesn't taste any like the
post π of that machine,
which is when the product crumbles it down and becomes bitter.
Well, that's one of thathighest and underneath theitéy review for Осiprijoeanx3.
employee contemporaries, at ease, eating well, no more microwave dinners and saturated fats,
a patient better driver, a safer car, baby smiling in backseat, sleeping well, no bad dreams,
no paranoia, careful to all animals, never watching spiders done a plug hole, keep in contact with
old friends, enjoy a drink now and then, we'll frequently check credit at Morrill, bank, bowling
wall, favors for favors, fond but not in love, charity standing orders, fitter, healthier,
and more productive, a pig, and a cage, on antibiotics.
One is Morrill, one is not, it's super ego and it bought, ah it bought, it's been such
a long time.
Long time since I couldn't take you anywhere.
Remember when we first used to go to the candy shack when we were young boys?
Shut your wet human mouth, you're making me hungry, I want sweets and I need them yesterday.
That's exactly what you used to say.
Searching everything.
Hey, can I help you?
Yes, I'd like a modicum of moderately priced chocolate.
Give me everything in the counter, open up the counter,
move out of the way.
Move out of the way old fellow, I will have you from behind.
It bought, no, you're embarrassing me in front of the old man.
I don't even know who you are, don't touch me.
What the hell is he doing?
Ah, never mind my friend sir, he's a little excitable for the sugar, but don't worry,
he's a robot.
Put candy in my orifice now, put it in, num num, num num, it bought wants more candy.
It bought, no, that's his head.
Errr.
Ah yes, those were the days.
One is moral, one is not, it's super ego and it bought.
Yeah, from the director of Daddy Did Me and the production team that brought you
Full Cervix Station and auto-erotic ass fixation, comes a bottle buster of a summer vid feature,
it's Hump Bot's Mexican Vacation, starring JJ Coolsy as Ghetto Geppetto,
the robot mechanic who keeps Hump Bot equipped with all of the latest erotic attachments,
designed to make you at least one load lighter.
That's Hump Bot's Mexican Vacation, on paper vid now.
Yeah, hello, this is Gene from Poughkeepsie, I got my ass stuck in a can opener.
Well, you know, I'm living on a budget here, and I'm trying to get a little pleasure in
my ples, you know, my, my sex bot's a little, uh, well, wiped out, you know, get a little
crazy with the beer bottles and stuff, you know, you live your fantasy, since it's the
future, but.
I'm a sex bot, I'm a sex bot, I'm a sex bot, I'm a sex bot, I'm a sex bot, I'm a sex bot,
I'm a sex bot, I'm a sex bot, I'm a sex bot, I'm a sex bot, I'm a sex bot,
I tried to turn it on a little and it just eats up more, so, you know, that's not right
and there's no reverse, so if you could just tell me.
If I hold the can opener up to the phone, can you talk some sense here?
Yeah, that's what I got, I got the, uh, typical human, uh, deal going on down there here.
Uh, let's see, this is the, uh, sex plus, uh, 1700 can opener.
Yeah, it do the thing, it does the thing, yeah.
I just can't see what the hell he's doing.
What are you saying to me?
One is moral, one is not.
It's Super Ego and it bought.
Well, it bought.
Here we are at yet another Woodstock.
I smell cannabis.
They are illegal and we wouldn't want to do anything wrong or get in trouble.
I'm on my way, but truly makes me crazy.
I do what he says, folks.
I'm caught in the mud.
Help.
I have got to get some of that sex, drugs, and rock and roll.
Well, maybe two out of three.
If it's too loud, then you are too old.
Well, it's not too loud.
I've got my earplugs in.
You are such a pansy panty waste.
If you want me to damage my hearing, that would make you happy.
Why don't you hold that girl down while I set fire to this tower?
No, we need that tower for observation and filming.
I like to watch.
Give it to it.
It bought.
No!
Let me at it.
I gots to have it.
All right, you just retract those tentacles, mister.
We got to get out of here.
You've gotten us in trouble again.
Woodstock, woo.
Party till you puke.
That piece of paper I put in my mouth is making me feel awful funny.
I love that you have a .
Whoa.
One is moral, one is not.
It's super ego and it bought.
.
Domo arigato, Mister Robot.
Buster, what are you doing?
You must be more serious now.
You're wondering who I am.
Secret, secret.
I've got a secret.
Machine or magic arm.
Secret, secret.
I've got a secret.
I am the Modern Man!
Acting strangely, don't be surprised
I'm just a man who's needed someone
And somewhere to hide to keep me alive
Just keep me alive
Somewhere to hide
To keep me alive
I'm not a robot without emotions
I'm not what you see
I've come to help you
With your problems
So we can be free
I'm not a hero
I'm not a savior
Forget what you know
I'm just a man who's
Circumstances went beyond his control
Beyond my control
We all need control
I need control
So we can't ignore
Control me!
I am the Modern Man
Secret, secret, I got a secret
Who hides behind a mask
That's how we work, that's how we work
So no one else can see
My true identity
Tomo arigato, Mr. Robot
Tomodomo, Tomodomo
Thank you very much, Mr. Robot
For doing the job
No one wants to know
And thank you very much, Mr. Roboto, for helping me escape just when I needed to.
Thank you.
I want to thank you.
Please, thank you.
Oh, yeah.
Thank you.
Bye.
We hope you've enjoyed another episode of Amplitude Modulation Theater.
You have heard?
The Lymphnode Institute.
The Lymphnode Institute performing Thus Spock Zarathustra.
Themed The Great Space Coaster.
Rinse Repeat by Stubborn Grass Stains.
Mr. Bungle performing The Star Wars Medley.
The Lymphnode Institute with F.I.L.K. and the USA.
Devo performing Space Junk.
Then you heard The Lymphnode Institute with the Commander Stipple skit.
Perry and Kingsley put together Spooks in Space.
Mr. Bungle performed None of Them Knew They Were Robots.
The Lymphnode Institute did all the Super Ego and Idbot skits.
Perry and Kingsley performed Minuet of the Robots.
You heard Flurry of Dust, A Robot Approaches from the Forbidden Planet soundtrack.
Perry and Kingsley again with the UFO Radiohead.
With Phineas and Ferb.
Bitter. Happier.
L&I did the Humpbots Mexican Vacation ad.
And then Robbie the Cook and 60 Gallons of Booze.
From the Forbidden Planet soundtrack.
Patrique Osborne performed that singular edition of Mr. Roboto.
And finally, Flaming Lips performed One More Robot, Sympathy 3000-21.
And in the background, you're hearing Jowlside with the theme from Fear the Robot.
And we'll go out with the king himself.
If you would like more information on the Church of the Subgenius,
write to them at P.O. Box 204-206 Austin, Texas 78720-4206.
Or visit them online at www.subgenius.com.
Another fine lymph node production!
Visit us online!
Line at lymphnodeinstitute.com.
Or shout out at mp3.com slash LNI.
Or write to us at P.O. Box 670-541 Marietta, Georgia 30066-0126.
Because we don't want to live in a world full of zombies, do you?
I'm truly proud once again to present my Rocketman.
William Shatner.
Thank you.
She packed my bags.
Last night, pre-flight.
Zero hour.
9 a.m.
And I'm gonna be...
high.
As a kite, by the way.
Oh, I miss the earth so much.
I miss my wife.
It's lonely.
Out in space.
I'm such a...
time.
And I think it's gonna be...
a long, long time.
The touchdown...
brings me back again to find I'm...
not the man they think I am.
Back home.
Oh, no.
No, no.
I'm a Rocketman.
Rocketman.
Burning out his fuse out here.
Alone.
I think it's gonna be a long, long time.
To touchdown.
Bring me around again.
Fine.
I'm not the man they think I am.
Oh, no.
No, no.
I'm a Rocketman.
Rocketman.
Burning out his fuse out here.
Alone.
No, no, no.
Oh, my God.
I'm so stupid.
I'll never baby boomerang again until I'm our mother.
I'm really just looking around, and I'm really, really, really worried that if I screw up,
Tui-oh...
Just come right back, pessoal.
We're laughing.
The last bottle.
And all this science.
I don't understand.
It's just a job.
Five days a week.
Rocket man.
A rocket man.
I think it's going to be a long, long time.
The touchdown brings me around again to find.
I'm not the man they think I am at home.
Oh, no.
No, no.
I'm a rocket man.
Rocket man.
Burning out his fuse out here.
Hello.
And I think it's going to be a long, long time.
The touchdown brings me around again to find.
I'm not the man.
They think I am.
Oh, no.
No.
I'm a rocket man.
Rocket man.
Burning out his fuse out here alone.
And I think it's going to be a long, long time.
The slammeal.
Su
Witt process.
H tc.
H c h?
C h.
Nothing.
A scale.
Please don't tell me how to do that.
It's sickening.
Oh, oh, oh.