communication section Washington low alert on Sierra case standby low alert
vital information coming through standby
actually Steve Rogers got kicked off the air for saying
but I think it was listeners that are not letting him say on the air
that's gonna be a whole bunch of
meep meep meep meep meep
that'll be the good part when you hear the meep meeps
oh
beat me to a pulp and I'm
praying for some
pain
I ain't got religion
I got a damaged brain
and if I had a dollar
for every looking that I took
I'd
buy the pulpit back again
and write a dirty book
oh
beat me to a pulp
and I'm praying for some pain
oh
I ain't got religion
I got a damaged brain
that was lonesome cowboy Dave some years ago friends
he hasn't been on the show for a while except in reruns
because he's old been sick
and his lifestyle changed drastically
but he's still David and he's going to be on the show for a while next week
and we did a show by phone just like in the good old days of 2020
also all of the songs in this show are by Dave performed with Einstein's secret orchestra
with Dave singing and playing guitar in all cases
this show is recorded August 9th
is lonesome cowboy Dave still alive?
I wonder
let's call him and find out
I hope
Dave
well I called
so you beat me to it
that's right I beat you to the pulpit
beat you to the pulpit
you're praying for some pain
after you went insane
well should
start drilling in the microphone right now
yeah that's part of your
messed up brain
I'll beat you to a pulpit
after you go insane
it's not your dirty
morals it's just your messed up brain
see that's it I made up a Dave type song
well that's that's that's delicious
it's like the little slices that
they have at the Hungarian store
of sliced up cow brains
or lamb brains I guess
it's like real thin
looks almost like sushi and you can wear it as a hat
well Dave Dave brains
is what I was going for
Dave brains
that's that's different you can't wear a hat to that
the hat is already provided but
in a different color and fashion
some some people say it's too ludicrous to be to be held
well how's your hat Dave
well I got some rain in the soup
I had to take the potatoes out
it was mashed up pretty good in there
I froze up some cinnamon stick
and gave it to my grandmother
she showed me how to do the rest of it
so I guess I could say it's all right
cool man cool
I mean it's cool sometimes
it's hot here it's so hot
I don't want to go anywhere near the doorway or the airlock
yeah it's it's 90 something here
but it's 90 something humidity too
it's just making people just pass out like birds on a telephone wire
yep yep that's why I'm in here
calling lonesome cowboy Dave on the phone
well you have you have actual
uh sedentary breakfast don't you
right now
I mean uh air conditioning
yeah yeah we yeah yeah our airlock is still functional
that's good
yeah I had to repair it a lot
with snot and scotch tape and stuff you know
they normally work pretty good
scott scott and snot tapes
but yeah
I'm sorry I was just gonna say I was wondering
for instance
sissue our doe had her gums removed or something
she said she's had a hard time finding things
because they put some articles in there that something I don't know
yeah she did she had her gums removed today
in fact she's still not home yet from the uh dental mental hospital
ah
yeah she had she had gum all over her hair
and you know just stuck in every little crevice
oh yeah yeah she had she had gum all over her hair and you know just stuck in every little crevice
And so she had to go get her gums removed.
But they did it with lasers.
They do it with lasers now.
They don't have to surgically peel it all, scrape it off with scalpels and peel your skin off and everything.
They just shoot a laser at you.
It still peels your skin off, but they don't have to use a knife.
It's easier for them.
It doesn't make it easier for the patient.
Oh, no, of course not.
But it's easier for the insurance company and the nurses and stuff.
I noticed when you go in the dentist's office, everybody has to wear a face mask except you, the patient, or me, the patient.
And it's not fair because there's all these pretty dental assistant ladies that you want to be able to recognize them in the supermarket later.
But you won't because they're...
They have masks on, but they can recognize me.
Except that when I go to the supermarket, I still wear a mask.
Even now.
Even today with the Lambda Delta Beta virus going around, I still wear the mask.
Yeah, I thought that was a fraternity when I first heard about it.
I mainly do it just to tick off the others.
I'll refrain from using the term ignorant.
I'm not going to use the term ignorant.
Don't do that because...
Well, do do that because it'll make it much easier later to recognize the bodies when they're trying to, you know, get the motorcycles going again.
Yeah, I know.
I don't think many of these women who have to wear a mask wouldn't want you to see them drooling in their pants or their heart pickle or their, you know, suitable escapes of whatever kind they have.
I...
You know, I hadn't really thought about that.
I guess that just like those pretty ladies, I could drool all I wanted behind my mask and nobody would be the wiser or the wetter.
Yeah.
I retroverted mine.
I put like a bunch of fur on it.
Pasted some fur on there.
It's like a portable beard and mask.
It works both ways.
That's what I...
Because I've been feeling kind of funny.
You know, I have this goatee.
And the mask doesn't quite cover it.
And I figured, well, the germs are crawling in through the hairs underneath the mask.
And if I glued more hair onto the inside of the mask, that would form a sort of a baleen type of barrier.
Yeah, and then you would know...
To keep the bad germs out, but I could still eat the good germs.
Yeah.
That I live on, the phytoplankton, if there's any left after this heat wave in the ocean.
So you think it's going to kill the phytoplankton in the oceans?
It's going to kill...
They've announced that they've already done the funerals.
Billions and billions of tiny funerals have already been enacted because all the microbes in the ocean are...
They died yesterday, and now the slightly larger krill are hungry.
And then the fish and whales are going to get hungry.
And then pretty soon the fishermen are going to get hungry.
And then the land...
Lubbers will have to spend a lot more for a can of tuna fish with dolphin in it.
Yeah.
And, you know, I'm glad that we're both so old that...
Well, actually, you know, the funny thing is I thought that I was going to die before the planet did, but now I'm not so sure.
It's...
Yep.
It's the snowballs kind of rolling through hell all over again.
Melting fast.
Yeah.
I was wondering when the calling hours are going to be.
All right.
Or if anybody's going to call.
I'm going to call them anyway.
Well, the Lord's going to call us all home.
To call them be.
I just want to...
I was hoping to avoid seeing the whole rest of the ecosystem get called home at the same time.
Yeah, that's going to be another very pretty sight, I'm afraid.
Right.
I was thinking, well, too bad about my grandsons and possibly my children.
But now I'm starting to go, damn.
I'm...
I'm probably going to live to see that stuff.
Darn it.
What they're probably going to do is a retrofusion on the last 500 years.
And you know they're going to charge...
They're going to charge double for tickets.
Oh, amazing.
Yeah, to watch yourself die.
Because that's the way them are.
That's they for you.
Thame.
Yeah, that's...
Ain't Thame.
Yeah.
But it doesn't do you any good to hate.
Doesn't do you any good at all.
But it's a tasty word still.
You can use in many elaborate situations.
Like if you want to impress the congressman and get some money to clean up the phytoplankton.
You can't just...
Whatever I just said.
Right.
Whatever you said.
You can't do that anymore.
No.
It's verboten.
Yep.
Oh, boy.
We actually...
The funny thing is, where I am in North Texas...
Well, we're under a heat advisory.
But that's normal here for this time of year.
It's everybody else in the country that's getting the really, really strange, bizarre Texas weather.
Well, they were saying you can see the stuff in the sky from the wildfires and stuff as far east as New Jersey.
And I thought that was silly until I looked down and asked.
The skies looked all hazy.
Oh, yeah.
I asked somebody if that's it.
And they said, that's it.
Yeah.
We...
When I look at the hills, they're very, very hazy now.
Kind of orangey.
The sunsets are pretty.
And my lungs are infected with the toxins from the burning appliances and homes of the Californians.
Yeah.
I mean, I've really noticed my...
I get bad enough allergies living in this city.
I was like, I'm going to go to the Cedar Forest.
But now it's pollen plus burning plastic.
In minute quantities, but it doesn't take much.
Hell no.
You know, to make you snot and sneeze and hock up loogies, lungers, and bungers.
Yeah.
Or not be able to and fiercely want to.
Right.
Yeah.
It's a sad thing.
But I suppose there's sadder things happening all at once.
So we shouldn't have to worry about it too much.
Just get under the old pillow and pull down the bed and just repartee like there was nothing going on.
You know?
That's actually a good idea.
As soon as we hang up, I'm going to go do that.
I'm going to go to bed, pull the covers up over my head, shrivel up, and cower and tremble.
Yeah.
Until I go into the big sleep.
I like the trembling part, you know?
Well, it's as close to sex as I ever get anymore at my age, I'll tell you.
Well, you know, I mean, it's good.
But hey, hey, trembling beats nothing.
It's good for making milkshakes.
You just put the milk and the chocolate and the ice cream in there and just shake away.
Yep.
And within a few hundred hours or more, you've got a beautiful, delightful milkshake.
Right.
You can use your fear to save on the...
Electric bills.
Yeah.
That's what I was thinking.
I was hoping...
Or your palsy, you know, fear, palsy, whatever.
All those things that make old people quiver uncontrollably and spew.
I think it's because their underpants are too tight.
You know, the people in these lounges, what do you call them, lounges?
Lounges, you know, where people are kept in solitude.
In solitude until they get older and die.
Well, those nurses that come around and so dutifully pull down the underpants and replace them,
they don't do such a good job all the time, especially when they're paid off.
You know what I mean?
Well, yes.
Of the man.
Yes.
Sometimes the man pays them off to humiliate the old elders and old people.
Helpless.
At least the old woman just...
Yeah.
The old woman just came.
Speaking of old women, the old woman just came.
Oh.
Are you making a show of these?
Yeah, I'm making a show.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Now, see your gum sound.
Those, that box of...
Oh, and I have to make a pit stop before I can.
Remember, I've just been on the road for a while.
I'll be back.
She has to make a pit stop because of her pits.
Well, you know, you live close enough to California, you're bound to get some pits once in a while.
Yeah.
Fort, do you remember Fort Pitt?
They named Pittsburgh after that.
Oh, I didn't know that.
I didn't know that.
Yeah.
Pittsburgh is short.
It's kind of like American for Pittsburgh, isn't it?
I don't know.
I didn't see an H on the end of it.
I saw a couple of X's.
So I got confused, and I asked the witch doctor.
Don't ask which one.
I asked the witch doctor.
At the police station, he told me everything was off until next year.
I said, man, I'm just trying to find an etymology of some snakes, some animals,
and, you know, where does the word Pittsburgh come from?
Because Detroit, we know, was formerly under French rule until the American Indian,
what's it called, wars, French and Indian wars.
The French Indians probably pronounced it Detroit.
Yeah, Detroit.
Because they don't use the T. They just waste it.
Yeah, it's just wasted.
And Fort Pitt.
Fort Pitt.
That used to be, what was the name of that place?
Oh, Duquesne, which was also a bottled beer in the 1940s.
Hey, speaking of French Indians, I heard that in Cleveland,
they changed the name of the baseball team to Guardians of the Galaxy or something like that.
They're not called the Redskins or whatever they were, the Braves, the Powwows.
Yeah.
And the local Native American organization said, you know, we've been doing this for a year,
but there's no negative onus with it.
Why don't you just call yourself the tribe?
Because we go along with that, too, and we even play drums at halftime.
Instead, you come up with some ridiculous, you know, game-sounding name,
or maybe it sounds like a European soccer team, you know,
Britchester United, you know what I'm saying.
Yeah, but if you call yourself the tribe, then the other tribe's going to go,
no, no, we're the tribe, so we're going to have to kill you.
Because everything's tribalism now, you know.
Yeah.
If you don't have the right totem pole in front of your house,
the other tribe will probably want to set your house on fire.
Except they won't need to, because it'll already be on fire from the climate change.
And the spare change, and small change.
I heard that it actually got into the triple digits,
1-0-something.
It was even higher than 1-0-something.
It might have been like 1-10 or something.
In British Columbia.
Actually, Dave, the oceans just off the coast of western Canada are dead zones now.
Yeah, it got real hot.
They're not used to seeing asphalt melt.
And they don't even know what air conditioners are up there.
So basically, everybody's already dead.
You might as well just, anybody you knew up there in the northwest, US or Canada,
they're probably burned up by now.
Have you spoken to anyone before they died?
Did they what?
Have you spoken to any of the western Canadians and Oregonians and Washingtonians before they died?
Well, I'm not sure.
But at least they'll die clean, because the water from the glaciers will be washing over them pretty soon.
There won't be any glaciers left, but there'll be plenty of water for a little while,
flooding down from where the glaciers were about 10 seconds ago.
Yeah, I was wondering if that became a gigantic tuna casserole, you know?
Yeah.
Of all those.
Well, it's...
It's funny.
It's happening even faster than doomsayers like me thought it would.
And I remember when this movie came out about 20 years ago called The Day After Tomorrow, I think that was it.
Yeah, something like that.
Climate Change Horror Movie.
And at the time, I thought, oh, this is ridiculous.
Look at this.
Suddenly, there's glaciers in New York, and it only took five minutes.
But then it turns out that's exactly what...
I think I just...
Just before I came downstairs here, I was glancing at the news, and I think that that was what was going on.
The air froze in Manhattan and was creeping down, you know, freezing up in New Jersey.
And meanwhile, the water was evaporating in the West so fast that people were just shriveled up desiccated potato chips.
One minute, they're fat.
Happy eating at McDonald's.
The next minute, the heat wave hits, and they're just...
Crisp.
Crisp skills.
Yeah, like the...
Yeah.
And see, we're kind of in the middle, in between the coasts, so it hadn't hit us yet, or whatever's going to hit us hadn't hit.
Well, that will be the dynamic thrash point between you and the other sides of the continent.
That will be what causes the explosion, and eventually, your suborganic demise.
Not yours.
Not yours personally, but, you know, millions of people in that area.
Oh, well, I'd probably be in that number, too.
I mean, I'm a person.
I do have an airlock, but, you know, they're only good up to a temperature of about 180 degrees Fahrenheit.
That should be a lot of fun.
Yeah.
180 plus.
I think it's about 150 out there today.
Yeah.
The last time I looked.
But we were going to have a cool spell next week where it would get down to the 130s.
Yeah, real funny, huh?
Real funny.
Yeah, so funny I forgot to laugh.
I remembered, too.
I remembered to laugh.
Good job, just after the idol two- Kopal leanings show.
I want to thank you Seton Эжик test for the whole ciw.
Yeah.
You know, I had this bad.
nos left-i'll change that in tonight.
I didn't think we'd say it.
It became alles u rappi OUN he has.
I always fight to see if the work.
The ad 무서 ба.
You want me to fight.
What?
It's making it hard just to stay alive
But the iodine, a one to one
The iodine, a one to one
No more running through the metal plans
No more boyhood in the mud
Power, power's in the power's hands
Shake the bony head and shake it good
The barium, a two four eight
This baby's sterile, I can't procreate
And plutonium, a two oh seven
So long folks, I'll see you in heaven
But the iodine, a one three one
The iodine, a one to one
No more running through the metal plans
No more boyhood in the mud
Shake the bony head of the poison rain
Shake the bony head and shake it good
So there's over two million known pollutants
That can cause cancer, pancreatitis
Bad juice, bad breathing, gingivitis
Bad breath, acne
No more
What's the use?
The iodine, a one three one
Has got my thyroid on the run
And the krypton, a eighty five
It's making it hard just to stay alive
But the iodine, a one three one
The iodine, a one three one
No more running through the metal plans
No more barefoot in the mud
Shake the bony head of the poison rain
Shake the bony head and shake it good
So there's over two million known pollutants
That already tonight
So there's over 20 million known pollutants
No more bad way out, it's boring
The iodine, a one three one
Shake the bony head of the poison rain
Shake the bony head and shake it good
Shake it
Shake the bony head of the poison rain
Shake the bony head
A heartache now you know
We just went to the bathroom
What's the matter with your teeth and your gums
Stuff like that
Then we don't have any problems
Except for when we see the guy
Who committed the crime in person
Well I'll be able to hear
This on the recording
Later
I'll be able to hear everything everyone says
Later when there's just me
In the headphones
So your deafness
Has a time shift on it
No it has
It has
Sort of a space shift
If there's another headphone
In the room
My headphone loses
Half of it's hearing
It's cheap equipment
Is what it is Dave
I've had people
I've had erstwhile
Beginner podcast people
Go Stang
Tell me what kind of equipment
You're using for your wonderful sound
On your show
And
And it's like
Well this is a 30 year old
$20 Radio Shack mixer
Three old microphones
With rotten foam
Windscreens on them
Chewed up by wind and cats
And
A cassette deck
An iPhone 6
That has to be kept
Charging all the time
And a
Yeah
Spider farm inside of it
Yeah it's got cobwebs everywhere
It just makes it look like
This is a real sound studio
And not just a table
With a bunch of junk on it
Like I said it's for a fact
What it really is
Is a table with a bunch of
Really dusty old junk on it
I mean really really dusty
So dusty that there are also
Dinosaur footprints
Within my eyesight view here
Seriously
There are
That's true
Yeah
So
That's a
Can be considered
Kind of a good thing
Especially when you get
You know some kind of
Protectionist racket
You have to hide out there
You pretend like it's 1987
What
Wait a minute
What year is this?
That I'm talking about
Oh what a relief
God I thought for a minute there
I just
You know
Had a stroke or something
And kind of forgot
The last thing I had to do
For 50 and a half years
Right
You had a stroke of bad luck
That's for sure
Well
Especially when you were young
Oh no no
Everything was easy
When I was young
Somebody else wiped my butt
For me and everything
Pretty soon
That'll probably happen again
Not less
Yeah that's what I miss about
You know being young
Is not having somebody
Wipe my butt
And you're saying
Well don't worry
You're going to be having
Your butt wiped pretty soon
Yeah it won't be that long
Much longer
Before somebody's
Wiping your butt again
If you're lucky
Yeah
At least they won't be
Using spoons now
You know plastic spoons
Anymore like they
Were doing there for a while
In the late 1980s
Oh I hate those
Wiping your butt
With a plastic spoon
I hate that
Ew
Yeah can you
Just see like
Ronald Reagan
Walking around
With a bunch of
Plastic spoons
Hanging out
Of his
Unfortunately
I have actually
Seen that
I went to a
Party once
In Hollywood
Just before he was
Elected governor
And I saw him
In that condition
At the party
But I was
I was just a little kid
I was only about
18 or so
When Ronald Reagan
Was 25
Did you get his
Screen legend
His
I got his autograph
Yeah
But unfortunately
It was written
With one of those spoons
So
Yeah
He's saying, should I turn on the evidence or be a good old stumble?
The president's on a bump, having a chat with God.
He says he's going to save our world, or maybe just buy half of us.
It's a democratic country where they don't have funds.
And business is not an offshore fund.
And business is growing and there's no surprise.
The president's in your head.
The president's in your mind.
Well, Dave, I'm sure the listeners,
the listeners will be amazed and surprised to hear that you're still alive.
I know that they're kind of amazed every week that I remain alive.
But nobody's heard you on the show except in hail and hearty reruns.
For quite some time.
Our blessing in a damned confusion is described.
For a great long time.
So welcome back, Dave.
Yes, welcome back, Dave.
I'm feeling welcome and useless, actually.
I have a fictitious idea of what's going on in the world right now.
But you count your blessings, dude.
You don't want to know what's really going on.
Reverend Stang tells me pretty much every day that he's really glad that I don't read the news because it's just so bad.
Yeah.
Especially environmental news.
Good old Washington Post last week.
Most people don't read any of that anyway.
I looked at, today I thought, I was looking at the regular, you know, the fake news headlines.
CNN, you know, BBC, that kind of thing.
And the main headline was, world is ending.
I mean, that was the first thing up because there was a big conference that they released this compiled data that was worse news than even the egg.
And I thought, I wonder what Breitbart.com is saying about this.
Nothing, nothing at all wasn't even mentioned.
It was all about movie stars that refuse to wipe their own butts because they're Hollywood elites.
And what was it?
The sex rapist and the whisperer.
That's Cuomo and Biden.
Ah.
The sniffer.
No, the sniffer.
Yeah.
The whisperer.
And he sniffs.
And that was why the world is ending because of Biden's sniffing and whiffing and whispering.
Ah.
And Cuomo's attempted gropes.
Apparently, he never really got anywhere.
All he did was grope and harass, but nobody has actually said that he did anything but put his hand on their butt.
Which, that used to be standard operating procedure for every 1950s male boss.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
I mean, if your boss didn't chase you around the desk like in a sitcom, you felt like you
weren't doing your job.
Those were the days.
You were missing something.
Yeah.
Nowadays, all you have to do is whisper or sniff and the right-wingers will come after
you.
Now, you can grab them by the country, and that's okay because it's one of them doing
it.
See?
Yeah.
But if a sniffer or a whiffer even sniffs or whiffs, much less grabs them by the country,
like the Russians and the North Koreans did to our country, they grabbed it by the country.
I'm sorry.
Do you think I speak of country matters?
Yes.
That's Shakespeare.
That's from him.
He's a good one.
You think I speak of country matters?
Country matters.
It's a rude, crude joke.
Country.
Country, yeah.
And you even hear them making these sexist remarks like, she was a good sexratary, and
then they go, and look at each other in a knowing way, and then they go, and look at
each other in an unknowing way, and they go, and make it look like they're not quite
sure, and then they say it again.
They say sexratary, and then they all laugh uproariously.
Sexatary?
Yeah.
Well, see, there's one I can't use.
You did not just say that.
Yes, I did.
I imitated, I quoted Dolomite in a Rudy Ray Moore imitation voice, and I have to cut that
out of the show, because if you're not woke, you're asleep, but if you're woker than thou,
that's even worse.
So, they got you coming and going.
Oops, I said coming.
And you know what going means.
That's like number two.
Yeah, that's bad.
Knock, knock, knock on your back door.
Stinky.
Yeah, bad.
It's a bummer.
Well, that's, we have to, that's probably wrong.
Murr.
I missed that.
It's a bummer?
It's a bummer.
Yeah.
It's a what now?
A bummer.
Yeah, Monty Hall, let's find out what's behind door number two.
I'm sorry.
There's another door there.
I'm actually, I'm quoting the Trailer Park Boys Greasy Money phone app game, which I'm
addicted to.
Deeply addicted to.
Oops, I said addicted.
That's got an unwoke word in it.
I'm Richarded to this game.
The Trailer Park Boys, how do they get away with anything?
Poison.
They're, oh, that's right.
It's Canada.
They're from Canada.
They can do anything they want.
The FCC is.
Those poor creatures, they have no freedoms like we in America.
Right.
So they can say anything they want on TV or radio.
They do.
Actually, Steve Rogers got kicked off the air for saying .
But I think it was the listeners that are the .
Not letting him say on the air.
That's true.
That's going to be fun.
That's going to be a whole bunch of .
Yeah.
That'll be the good part when you hear the .
Well, that's what the Cleveland and radio broadcast audiences hear.
The internet audiences only hear that if it's funnier to put the in than the curse words.
At least the curse words are in cursive now.
They're encouraging the children to learn backwards.
No, but see, that's okay.
If you say them in cursive, people understand.
They're under 30 or so can't hear it.
They never learned cursive.
They can't.
To them, like the former president, the Declaration of Independence appears to be in a foreign language.
What language is this?
They actually ask that question.
Because he can't read English cursive.
We can't read big words.
They typed it out for him and hand him the handwritten calligraphy of the Declaration of Independence.
But, you know, they sell at gun shows and stuff.
They sell copies of it, right?
Yes.
Replicas of the Declaration of Independence.
And kids have to ask what it is.
They can't even read the title of it.
They can't read a clock either, a regular clock.
They can only read digital readout numbers.
A circular clock with, you know, the number.
With hands?
Yeah, with hands.
Yeah, that means nothing to them.
They don't, they didn't sit at five minutes till three every weekday staring at that round thing waiting for that hand to hit the top.
You know, when you could leave school.
To get out of school.
Right.
That means nothing to them.
They look at their phone, which has a countdown, and tells them when they can leave.
And also sex pictures of the kids all sitting around them.
Because that's all they do in school now is unzip their pants, take sexties or whatever of their privates and then text them to each other.
No, seriously, I heard that on Fox News.
That's all they teach in school.
We left, but it's true.
And Marxism.
That and Marxism.
And that's all there is in schools now.
Oh, I see.
You need to, there's a microphone.
That's all there is in school now is just.
Yeah.
You know, you, Philo, and Susie have a lot in common, Princess Wee.
No memory whatsoever.
None.
Complete blank.
You can remember there's a microphone there for, what, about 10 seconds?
But then your back gets tired of leaning.
Actually, Hal does that, too, to some extent.
Although usually he leans forward until his lips and nose touch the windscreen on the mic and then he falls asleep.
I thought it was turned blue.
That's it.
It actually has happened.
But that's because Hal doesn't have a microphone.
Hal's shows are usually on at four in the morning.
I've seen Hal fall asleep on the mic.
Yeah.
I've seen him fall asleep while he was awake.
Or awoken.
Awoken.
Or awoken berries.
Yeah.
Yeah, there's a lot.
What's up with all the new vocabulary, you know?
I remember when I first started doing some stuff, they'd say contact or whatever, and
now they say everybody has to reach out to somebody.
And then if you're aware of something, you woke.
And then otherwise you're gaslighting.
What does gaslighting really mean?
I'm wondering.
Is that fibbing?
It basically means lying, more or less.
It's based on a movie called Gaslight.
Yes.
Where this woman thinks she's losing her mind because she keeps thinking she turned off that gaslight.
But then it's on again.
And her husband berates her and tells her she's losing her mind.
But he's the one secretly turning the light on and off to make her believe she's crazy,
so she'll go crazy so he can get all the money.
That's gaslighting.
Yeah, I don't think most people who use that term have any idea whatsoever where it came from.
Because it's a movie from the 30s.
Yeah.
And I have not ever seen it.
I really want to see it someday.
Really?
Yeah.
Goodness.
That's what I was just going to ask you.
It was from the 1930s.
Yes.
I think it was.
It was the predictive decade before DeFiro walked the earth.
It was a famous movie, but that was over 150,000 years ago.
These creatures were thought to be extinct, and yet here they are, gaslighting.
Yeah, stinking the place out.
And leeching and everything else that we thought had gone out of fashion.
But it's all back in fashion again.
Well, they're going faster than a speedboat.
They're on their way to hell, if you ask me, but nobody did.
No, they just motorboated me.
Did you ever try and haul some bowling balls?
Oh, I'm sorry.
What was that, Dave?
I am too.
Say it again, Dave.
You said, oh, I was just wondering if they were taking canoes and putting bowling balls
in them to make sure everybody got to the right shores of the river.
Yeah.
You know, because if you didn't, then...
Dave, they quit doing that back in 2030.
Which was 35 years ago.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, they quit making bowling balls around 2035 entirely.
Because bowling was outlawed.
You know, it wasn't...
I don't know.
There was something...
The right-wingers hated it because of the...
The racks.
And the left-wingers hated it because of the balls.
Yeah, but at least the left-wingers had enough little marks on their bodies so that it wouldn't
pinch you there on the chest.
Nobody cared about the pins.
The pins were fine.
You can still get bowling pins, but you can't have balls.
Not anymore.
Yeah.
It's balls pretty much kind of been outlawed on all fronts.
Both sides have outlawed balls.
Wow.
They don't like balls.
Yeah.
I see.
No, they're just taboo.
They're becoming more and more taboo each day.
I have balls, but don't tell the cops because they don't like...
Well, I've been sitting on mine lately as I've become older, like close to 105 years
old.
I've noticed now that it's very easy to sit on that, on your scroll area.
Yeah.
When I say balls, that's kind of a figure of speech in my personal case.
Well, why wouldn't you call it balls?
Balls, it's a singular is the way it works.
But let's not go into that.
Let's talk about something that blesses my heart.
UFOs.
They finally told the truth about UFOs.
Which is what?
They don't know anything about it.
No Jack Who-ey.
They finally admitted it.
Yeah.
They finally admitted, yep, yep, UFOs, we have no idea.
Not a clue.
If you know, tell us.
All that Roswell stuff, that was all big story.
Well, no, we don't know.
They don't know.
They just don't know.
Roswell, heck, who cares about that?
That's, that's...
So, haven't they been collecting information for the last 50 years?
Well, they released the information, it's just that it doesn't say anything.
Nobody knows.
Yeah.
It's like, well, yeah, this thing buzzed all these planes, all these things buzzed all
these planes and did all these crazy things, but we don't know.
Might be Nazis from the hollow earth.
Might be aliens from out of space.
There could be Nazis from the moon.
Might be creatures of light that fly around and dart around in the sky and they're just
some species we never heard of before that's been here this whole time and they just like
to tease us.
Or it might be John Galt and his rich people that withdrew from the world 500 years ago
to dedicate themselves to peace and science and slack and now they're teasing all the
rest of the suckers.
Better hands.
Yes.
That's, honestly, that's, to me, that's the most likely scenario for UFOs is secret
geniuses that a long time ago went, this whole thing is screwy.
Let's go find ourselves a nice hiding place in the hollow earth or somewhere that only
brilliant geniuses like us can learn how to live in and we'll just become advanced.
Like Wakanda in Africa.
That's a case of, you know, a secret civilization that's way more advanced than everybody else.
And you don't expect it because they're protected by holograms and it just looks like remote
jungle.
Dave wouldn't know what I'm talking about because he hasn't seen a movie in 45 years.
Wakanda.
Yes.
That's where Black Panther comes from.
Okay.
You know, long live Wakanda.
No, I never saw Black Panther.
What?
I heard it.
You've got to be kidding.
You know, I've told you a hundred times I never saw it.
And you always think you have that same reaction.
What?
You didn't see Black Panther?
That's great.
No, I didn't see it.
You ranted to me about it and I really wanted to see it, but I never saw it.
Maybe I should go rent it from the Red Box right away.
Oh, by now it's probably free on one of those pay-per-view channels.
I've tried.
For free.
I've looked.
If you pay.
Oh, well.
Free.
Only $5.00.
The Subgenius movie isn't on Amazon anymore unless you bought it.
You can watch it on Amazon if you bought it.
But it's still on Fandango, I think, and Hulu and Apple TV and all the other ones that we
don't have.
It's a moot point because I have my own bootleg copies that I can reproduce anytime.
And I have the official DVD.
Well, I'm glad you can reproduce anytime you want.
But it makes it less.
I don't want to.
I bet you can.
But Dave's never seen the Subgenius movie, J.R. Bob Dobson and the Church of the Subgenius.
I bet he hasn't.
Well, he's not in it, so he wouldn't care.
I tried, Dave.
I tried.
Remember I filmed you?
She didn't use anything I filmed.
I filmed G. Gordon Gordon, you, Gary Gbrogfren, and Anna Moll.
And she didn't use any of that footage.
I even went to Portugal to film G. Gordon Gordon.
It was a horrible trip, too.
She still didn't use the footage.
No.
She drank a lot of blush wine and smoked a lot of Tunisian arceece.
I didn't even get to do that when I was in Portugal.
Only fun thing I got to do was try goat in a fancy restaurant, and I didn't even like
it.
He didn't like it.
No.
Well, anyway, the Subgenius movie came out pretty good, even though you're not in it.
It did.
It's really good.
It has me in it a lot, so it's really good.
Princess.
They interviewed Princess Wee, and they didn't use her.
No.
Not a second of it.
You can see her smiling at 7 a.m., the fake 7 a.m.
It was actually 7 p.m., but the sun was in the same position, so I said, let's just do
a fake 7 a.m. ceremony.
We'll have more people that way.
So we had almost like a dozen.
Yeah, but you didn't want to have people all the time.
People, yeah.
People, sure.
You want stranger elements than people.
Yeah.
You want some, you know, nice fried figs, some people from outer space.
That's right.
Not people.
We wanted people from outer space, but all we got was a small film crew.
They did use some of the footage, but I bet they felt like, man, why did we all come out
here for this?
Yeah, you get paid in bars.
They didn't use much from that.
Anyway, Dave, we have to go because it's almost an hour.
Okay, well, it's been a very pleasant hour.
And I'm glad the world's not going to completely—
Oh, it is.
It is.
We've got about—yeah, by the time I get this recording upstairs to my computer, I
probably won't even get a chance to copy it over.
Right, the sky will have fallen.
Yeah, the sky will have fallen.
30 seconds left to go.
That's so sad to think of.
But—
Seven, six, five, four—
Five, four.
Three, two, one.
And then—
And it's the day called X.
Not really.
Okay, well, I'm going to go back to my—well, I don't want to say what I was
doing.
Well, I don't see why you wouldn't want to let everybody at least know that.
No, I don't know what the kids call it nowadays.
I don't know the vocabulary.
As you were saying—
Hog fishing.
—you know, they change the words for everything.
It's hog fishing now.
At least that's the rural term.
Haven't you ever gone hog fishing?
Hog fishing?
Yeah.
I never have been hog fishing.
Well, you don't want to stick a stick—
Is that the thing that girls do?
Well, they're allowed.
Yeah, they do it better than guys.
They don't like that idea.
It goes against their sexist dichotomy.
Hmm.
That's the way it is.
Yeah.
Well, I guess I'll sign off now.
The sky is turning purple again.
I can see the little children outside my window all praying.
Yeah, the pages of my script are curling up and catching on fire.
I guess we better call it quits.
The last hour of slack, number 1,843?
Forty-three?
Wow, 1843.
Wow.
Holy mackerel.
That's a lot.
That's a lot of radio shows.
That's the envisionment of a super animal.
I've actually been doing this show longer than Johnny Carson did his show or David Letterman
did his show, but they did them every night, five days a week.
We only did it once a week, but I'm just as tired as those guys.
In fact, I'm about as tired as Johnny Carson.
Yeah.
Johnny Carson now.
Okay, man.
You want words?
It's fun to make a radio show with you, Dave.
Yeah, it's good.
I just noticed the battery went down, too.
It's still working, but it wouldn't work for much longer.
Boy, they go fast now.
I know how it feels.
I know exactly how that battery feels.
Mm-hmm.
Totally full one minute.
Me, too.
Suddenly, it seems like no time at all goes by.
Yep.
There you go.
Just like my old life.
No.
I'm out of energy.
Yep.
That's where I'm going right now.
Okay.
Swap batteries, Dave.
See you on the flip-flop.
Set the end.
Dave?
He actually hangs up, even though he could fake it.
He actually hangs up.
Ah, well.
So, let it be.
Well, I guess I'll push the stop button.
Stop.
And finally, let's go to hear live versions of two of the songs we played earlier recorded
at the Beachland Ballroom in Cleveland as part of Subgenius Debacles.
There may be time coming soon when you will not need that dangly dingly or that thing.
No!
That pristine juicer you can hang from yourself.
That slimy eye.
It's not good for pioneers.
You've gone far from the sky.
Oh, I don't know.
It was so long ago.
Well, they said Chernobyl was so long
ago.
There's nothing to worry about.
It's luck you didn't sink.
Then I hear on the news a bunch of dumb guys in the Department of Energy and Defense Department
are going to start building a bunch of Chernobyls across the United States.
Then I hear Chernobyl's not really over. All these people are all dying within a 250 mile radius
because all the underground aquifers are all polluted.
So now we're getting it too.
And then I wonder as I stare into the mirror how, why my movements are getting so jerky and...
Jerky and...
One, two, three, four!
The iodine, the 131, has got my thyroid on the run
And the krypton-85 is making it hard just to stay alive
But the iodine, the 131, the iodine, the 131
There's no more running through the metal lanes
No more barefoot in the mud
Shake the bony hand of the poison man
Shake the bony hand and shake it through
The barium, a 248, has made me sterile I can't procreate
And the plutonium, a 247, so long folks, I see you in heaven
But the iodine, a 131, the iodine, a 131...
There's no more running through the metal lanes
No more barefoot in the mud
Shake the bony hand of the poison man
Shake the bony hand and shake it through
And the krypton-85 has got my thyroid on the run
And the plutonium, a 131, the 131...
Jerky and...
The iodine, the 131, the 131...
So, if you're over 2 million known, can eating chicken cause cancer, skin lesions, brain
tumors, conjunctive lymphoma, Passer's disease, Hodgkin's lymphoma, chicken neck, acne, gingivitis,
bad breath, then what's the use?
The iodine, 1, 3, 1, has got my thyroid on the run, and the krypton, 85, is making it
hard just to stay alive.
But the iodine, 1, 3, 1, the iodine, 1, 3, 1, there's no more running to the metal line,
no more pain.
Well put in the bag.
Power, power's in the power's hand.
Shake a pointy hand and shake it.
No more running to the metal line.
No more pain.
Well put in the bag.
Shake a pointy hand of the poison man.
Shake a pointy hand and shake it.
Shake it.
Oh, beat me to a pulpit, I'm praying for some pain.
I ain't got religion, I got a damaged brain.
If I had a dollar for every Lincoln that I took,
I'd buy the Pope and Vatican and buy the dirty phone.
Beat me to the pulpit, I'm praying for some pain.
Beat me to the pulpit.