Something familiar, something peculiar, something for everyone, a comedy tonight.
Something appealing, something appalling, something for everyone, a comedy tonight.
Nothing with kings, nothing with crowns, bring down the lovers, liars and clowns.
Old situations, new complications, nothing portentous or polite.
Tragedy tomorrow, comedy tonight.
Something convulsive, something repulsive, something for everyone, a comedy tonight.
Something aesthetic, something frenetic.
Something for everyone, a comedy tonight.
Nothing with gods, nothing with fate.
Weighty affairs will just have to wait.
Nothing that's formal, nothing that's normal.
No recitations to recite.
Open up the curtains!
Comedy Tonight!
The Power of Slack!
The Hour of Slack.
And you obeyed.
Yes, I did.
So the pastor just prayed for me.
And I came this morning.
And I feel in my body that God has delivered me.
And he does.
Somebody praise the Lord.
What did the Lord do for you today, honey?
The package is bent and dark yet.
I'm going to go back to the house of the Lord once again with me and my son.
My mother's with me.
And I feel that God has touched me.
You believe God didn't touch you?
He has touched me.
Somebody give the Lord a hand clap.
Someone give the Lord the clap.
And we'll all sing.
This happy song.
I'm oozing.
Yes, our Lord and Master Blaster, Jesus H. Christ, was not only a man of the cloth.
He was a man of the silk panties.
He used to walk this way and that up and down the Palestinian River,
but looking for beautiful young women.
What did he find among the rocks there?
He found nothing but desolation.
He found an estrogen.
He found rivers of estrogen and piles of pus.
But let's leave things of this world behind and walk now down the path of Bob for this brief minute of slack from the church of the subgenius.
It's a squirting universe, friends, and that's why we have to call for your help on the great new tabernacle.
We've only been in there a month, but it's going back into the hands of the conspiracy.
They're going to turn it in.
And what a hell spa.
Because the law says, the law says a subgenius can't achieve cytospasm with whatever it wants.
That's what the law says.
No subgenius can do anything it wants, and they call this a free land.
Oh, my friend, I've heard people call the church of the subgenius a joke,
but I have to wonder, is the subgenius church a joke or is this world?
A joke.
Bob Dobbs owns deed and title to the church.
But who owns deed and title to the world?
Not Bob yet.
I'm afraid not.
The conspiracy owns this world.
Let there be slack, my friend.
I'm afraid not.
We've got an apartment complex here at the apartment complex.
I've got an apartment complex here at the apartment complex.
Now.
Creechette, competent, level or lighting apartment life couldn't be more exciting.
Loving room and clubhouse, too.
I don't have a worry till the break comes, too.
Watching Sooner Bitter Max night after night.
It's a...
Tied away to suburban delights
Hey, hey
I've got an apartment complex
Here at the apartment complex
Oh
Oh, I know you like to live at the complex
I mean, I tell you that it's so easy
To sit upon the line for such a good reason
You can make it here on the minimum wage
My friends come over and they think it's so fine
Well, they don't know that none of it is mine
Real furniture and color TV
None of my belongings belong to me
For it's life of luxury and credit costs a thing
Cause I always assume that I'll make to the bank
Hey, hey
I've got an apartment complex
Here at the apartment complex
Oh
The...
Pink Boys!
Dear friends, the big boys from 1980.
Can you believe it?
Dr. X on vocals and Tim Crane on guitar.
Before that, the minute of slack, number 19,
and some ESO swamp radio from beautiful WCSB,
Cleveland, Cleveland State University,
with Chaz Smith and Lonesome Cowboy Day.
A special guest, princess, we are the dome.
And yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang.
Now, coming up, friends, we've got a sing-along with Onan Canovite,
plus many collages by Fernanda Limer.
In fact, all of the cut-ups on tonight's hour of slack, number 858,
are by Limer,
except for one great big one.
Near the end, it's about alien invaders.
And speaking of alien invaders,
check out this news item that was not covered very much on the mainstream media.
A federal rectal exam list intended to keep terrorists
from smuggling drugs and explosives aboard planes
is snaring innocent people at most U.S. airports,
triggering complaints that civil liberties
are being violated.
And while several federal agencies acknowledge that they contribute names to the congressionally mandated list,
none of them could or would say which agency is responsible for managing the list,
except that they are known for, quote,
having a thing for that sort of thing, unquote.
Equally troubling is that to avoid accusations of racial profiling,
a blonde white woman is routinely selected for the intrusive and thorough anal exams from each flight,
often several times at the same airport while waiting for her flight.
In the instance where such a woman has several connecting flights,
she could be anally violated dozens of times in a single day,
said one attractive woman.
What's scariest to me is that there could be this gross interruption of civil rights,
and nobody is really in charge.
But everybody wants to shove their fingers up your butt.
Nobody thought that 1984-ish America would be like an anal intruder's porn movie.
Well, friends, as New Monet said about that news report,
we have seen the future and it is...
UGH!
Ehh.
And the future continues here in Cleveland,
where we make this...
where we finally assemble the crew,
assemble the show.
Um, we lost a newspaper.
The...the alternative weekly called the Free Times
was absorbed by the other weekly, leaving now only one city in the United States
that has two alternative weeklies.
I think that's Los Angeles.
And there goes newspaper.
So all them people be going down the same...
Communism!
These countries only have one newspaper!
Communism is good!
Christianity is stupid!
In communist countries...
Communism is good!
People can't decide what the government's gonna do in the war zones.
And that's why I say this Bush man is a communist!
It's totalitarianism!
I'm amazed hearing that coming from a Texan.
It's the devil pretends to be good.
From a proletarianism.
The meaning of the word proletarianism, goddammit!
Communism pretends to be a capitalist.
But it's communism...
Communism?
...that is creeping into America.
I have felt the...
Yes, communism.
...in a vile perspiration of communism.
I think it's also called couch potato-ism.
And the other muted hues.
And I feel that we are slipping slowly down the backslide...
...of other nations that have gone before.
It's common.
It is creeping.
Common men are everywhere in communism!
It is a form of Marxism, socialism, and all those other nasty, nasty words.
Common, come over here.
Common, please.
Communists and Nazis!
They're under my bed.
I like them there.
They're under every one of my beds.
Both of them.
Commies and Nazis.
And pinks.
I don't mean pinkos.
And the Genghis Khan hordes.
I like those uniforms too.
Humans!
Another low flyby.
We're still the next to go.
There's humans again.
Another number came up. I think it was forty-five.
We will bring them down.
Someday their kind will fall.
And our kind shall rise up out of the ditches and the holes.
Like a phoenix from the ashes, we shall swarm skyward and spew our maelstrom upon them.
You're listening to WCSB Cleveland.
Let the humans laugh at us now.
Our time is coming.
While they still have teeth and jaws and those tendons that go behind your chin and nostrils.
There are no more teeth.
Radiation is our friend.
We eat uranium and old rotten wires.
And we shall dispute them at the nuclear plants.
We shall displace the humans.
We will be the new conspiracy.
There's a worm.
You can evacuate so easily with that.
Just one thought. It's like Gidget already went to the power plant.
The roaches shall be the new exterminators.
The new exterminators.
And the humans will be the bugs.
The shrimp.
The barbies.
The kinmen and the sound boys.
We'll get and get them.
They and all their friends.
Their allies.
And we shall blow up your butts.
ply Scream thể passing through your veins.
About them go on, they will die of pain.
They and all their friends.
Sp swoar the archel yesterday.
For they're the code.
For they, the Putin is sober.
Don't wake. Don't wake.
That's the opposite message.
This is about corporate accountability.
In this week, you'll find information about attacking President Bush's policies toward Iraq.
Just click for a leading congressional Democrat stand in the corner.
Now we'll look at our Treasury Secretary, Paul O'Neill, on the proposals to create kidnapped children.
And later, officials from three consumer groups and their abductors, also known as spam.
And at noon, only on BookBand 2.
Treasury Secretary Paul O'Neill talked about corporate accountability.
Joining us now at the table is Treasury Secretary Paul O'Neill.
Oh, um, good.
Uh.
Just, uh.
Um.
I, I go to a place where there's rampant corruption and see $100.
Did, did you, uh.
Tomorrow, the House Resources Committee will look at Gail Norton.
Did.
Don't explain, explain.
He's an asshole, sir.
The house.
I know that.
What's his name?
That is his name, sir.
Asshole.
Major asshole.
And his cousin?
He's an asshole, too, sir.
Gunner's made first class Philip asshole.
How many assholes we got on this ship anyhow?
Yo!
I knew it.
I'm surrounded by assholes.
Keep firing, assholes!
That's what I said at Enron.
Keep firing assholes.
Yeah.
Did you see the picture in the paper?
That guy's in his best suit, man.
It's gotta be a $2,000 suit he's wearing.
Going to prison.
Did you see the?
The stain on the back of that suit as he did that so-called perp walk?
That's a Bill Clinton stain if I ever saw one.
He was trying, I know, he was trying to do a lepetamine as if that was gonna get him
off.
You know, some people think.
Kinda backfired.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
As it were.
Or bareback fired.
He.
Brad's out.
Who's mounted the little Lucifer puppy?
Bob's out.
Bob's out?
Why is that a Bob, man?
I'm sorry, I just cut a Bob.
Bob's right.
I'm afraid you're going to have to step back a little bit.
But it's like, it's like Bob is like this concept that's burned into everything like,
uh, you know, a screen that has like the, you know, the little logo burned into it or
something because it was on there too long, you know?
Like old computer screens.
Yeah.
It's like even when there's another pattern, Bob is underneath the pattern.
It's part of the wallpaper so you don't even see it.
Oh, that Bob weave, man.
That's a part of reality is the weave of.
The latticework.
The lattice of coincidence.
You know, that's, that's, it's like the wolf and the warp of the fabric.
The rockabilly wolf.
The fabric, man.
That's Bob smiling, drooling.
Who doesn't know that?
You forget he's there until you start smelling the smoke from that pipe.
And this perspiration.
The jet fuel.
I'll just hear it like sometimes now I'll just hear a certain like.
Spinal threads.
One guitar note, one just little on a guitar, you know?
Yeah.
I'll hear that and, and, and, and I'll just know where.
I'll just know where.
There they go.
You know, the connection is.
The rainbow connection.
It's the rainbow connection.
With your spine.
They're taking off left and right.
It's the new age, man.
The new aeon.
Yeah.
Just smile and wave as they go past.
I heard that they will be drinking Shaddam Hussein's spinal fluids at the Bohemian Grove.
Oh, and by the way, go down to that local.
As a special sacrifice.
That little deli on the corner that's owned by, you know.
Aries, Aries, Aries.
Oh, which deli?
Wait, which deli is that?
And go buy your American flag to put on your Christmas tree.
I'm going to buy a car.
One or two.
Because that's important.
Could be sufficient.
But if the climate changes, you may need five or six flags.
Now, Princess, we and I have noticed.
Six flags over Oklahoma.
Yee-haw.
I've been there.
I mean, exactly.
One year old flags on people's cars that they bought exactly one year ago and that have
now been worn by the wind down to just nubbins of about an inch or two of flags.
Yeah.
I mean, really.
Five hundred.
I do pledge my allegiance to that flag for which I stand in here.
One nationalistic respubic with freedom and justice for the upper ten percent.
You guys sound like a bunch of flaggy boys.
That's pretty flaggy.
You're a bunch of flaggots.
How's your organization?
I hate flaggots.
I tell ya.
I burned the flag.
I tell ya, my life is my art.
Bush burned the Constitution.
I love it.
The flag is mine.
You're just igniting yourself.
I'm flagging.
Well, we've had our way with the flag, haven't we?
A symbol.
A symbol of freedom.
But in these days and times, a symbol of what?
Of oppression.
Of oppression of the entire world based on-
It's becoming more dot-like.
I'm reading off the wrong page.
I'm supposed to be reading off the page that says we must install democracies wherever
they is.
And wherever they-
I'm sorry.
We'll force them to vote.
We shall.
They'll if they'll vote or we'll kill them.
And if they don't place their ballots in the box, we'll place them there for them.
We will install democracy wherever it can be.
We will make them free if it kills them.
It's not happening.
There goes another one.
Bye bye.
That was another fly by, man.
I think we're gonna be the next to go in a few seconds.
Got your helmet, Dave.
Yeah, I'm wearing it on my feet, man.
We'll free those people if we have to go into slavery to do it.
And my fellow Americans, I hope you're prepared to do just that.
That's the cost of freedom.
Your freedom.
We must destroy freedom to build freedom.
Oh boy, oh boy, oh boy.
I'm kind of disgusted.
I know how you feel.
The show sucks.
It sucks.
Life is even worse with all this oil on over me.
And dust.
And now you gotta wear your helmet on your backside or else...
The show is hell.
Shut the...
Hello?
They ought to hang me.
You are lying.
I'm giving them right back.
A newly discovered white ass, but follow-up studies show that the ass and earth will not meet, at least for now.
Tomorrow.
Today, a tragic new life together.
All this and more, today.
Tomorrow.
Hello and welcome to this edition of the club.
Today, a coma and being married.
The headline for expensive drugs, but that's not all.
The Los Angeles White House is now backing suspected hijacker,
in Prague. CBN congressional correspondent Paul Sorrell was involved in the terrorist attacks.
The Senate wound up in prison for bribery and tax evasion. Republican obesity in the U.S.,
Texas trouble. The new bill would authorize more than 150 million children to help the two fat
congressmen for tax evasion. And with both the House and Senate in prison, all the races are
overweight. Paul Sorrell in prison for bribery and tax evasion. Capitol Hill. And for more
information on what's happening in Washington, then ask Mike Reed, Capitol Hill Prayer, every
Friday at CBN.com. The contemporary Christian can't just read this asking itself questions like
just how Christian does Christian have to be? CBN News reporter Sarah Pollack has about a one in
250,000 chance. Ever since he grew up, from the time they started getting the wee little man,
from that time, really, I was hooked. Paul came shortly after he
wrote the book, The Greatest Show on the World.
I wrote a song.
I want Smell-O-Vision.
I want all the others.
Now Paul's officially better known as God or Jesus.
I wonder whenever.
Oh, I wonder.
So you're just like having a canapé breakfast just talking about the world news or something?
Or just, is it more like dogma of the Church of the Subgenius again?
I don't think any of that even came up.
No dogma?
Well, I guess we're just all burned out.
I was driving to the station and I was thinking, shouldn't we draw upon our energy reserves
and do some protestful thing about some...
you know, pertinent, cultural, socially relevant,
you know, some giant argument that the humans
and everybody else is all upset about.
Well, the giant humans are always arguing
because they take up too much space.
But everybody just took their clothes off
and now they're dancing.
Is that positive or negative?
Yeah, Byron's going on and on about this, too.
Oh, man.
Byron wants everyone to be weird,
and he's offended that I'm having parties
where girls are dancing naked
and getting all painted up with liquid latex.
Actually, he just says that's old hat
and that's not weird enough.
That's so pink.
Now, of course, he has no suggestion
as to what would be weird.
Yeah, absolutely.
Nothing at all.
All he knows is that, you know what?
He's going to attack my pleasure vessel.
We may not be all that weird,
but we know our slack.
That's right.
You know, at least we know our slack, damn it.
You do.
You are quite aware of, in each inch,
each centimeter of slack that escapes from your vowels,
you know.
When I had no slack,
then I felt like, oh, everything has to be weird,
and then I'll have slack.
You have learned the secret of life,
or at least deodorant, like from a distance.
No, actually, I didn't learn.
All I know is I got some slack,
and I don't care whether it's weird or not weird.
I don't care.
Weird is what the other guy thinks.
I don't care what the other guy thinks.
I don't care what you think.
That's all he's done.
We're right out of the water.
I don't care what you think.
Bob thinks.
There you go.
It was worth it.
I paid to know what I really think,
and I don't care what you think.
I don't even care what I think at this point.
What a beautiful, pathetic thought
for such a scrambled-up gentleman.
For 30 bucks, it's worth it.
He tried so hard to save the world,
and now look at his mind now,
all, like, laying there on a piece of paper in front of him.
I saved my world.
Listen to the drums.
They're calling.
Those are the calling drums.
They're calling you to whoop your pants down.
I would like to be Kaisei Girl.
Socks.
Just forget toilet paper.
Who cares?
Just live natural.
Forget toilet paper, I think,
should be the name of our new political movement.
That was a great movement.
A great band.
The toilet...
Wait a minute.
Forget toilet paper.
That's the name of the band.
It might even really be the band that's playing right now
over the airwaves that you're listening to.
But it's spelled with a number, right?
For...
Yeah.
Forget toilet paper.
Just get toilet paper.
It's only known as...
So all the rest do not get toilet paper,
but four get toilet paper.
Four?
Are they the four smelliest?
They're the four horsemen.
No, no.
The band only gets...
The four most worthy.
The four horsemen of the port-a-san.
The four strongest or the four strongest smelliest?
The four get toilet paper.
The four get toilet paper, yeah.
Indian times, before things became very, very small,
mall, they were the four horsemen
of the porta potty. Why are you
hooked on your toilet paper and your
chem cans? I don't know. He always
do that. Why can't you just live like
in the past, in the good old days?
Live life. What's the
difference in a porta potty?
Live life without any
focus on excremeditation.
Screw that excremeditation stuff.
All you need is a hole in the ground and a
cactus and some sand.
Just grab a branch
to hang on to and let it go.
What's wrong with a good old
cactus? Lean back and let go.
Right.
You know what I'm saying?
Don't you want to take a big piece of
life like that? Just walk up to
that old saguaro cactus and put your arm
around it and give it a big old
fat kiss and say,
Dobbs, I quit.
You know, that guy's nuts
really when you think about it.
I mean, he don't make any sense at all,
right? Do you think so?
I don't think.
That's right. That's the problem, sir.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
I've been bothered by the soldiers
killing innocent civilians.
Musica.
Get this.
48%
of 60% of the population of Canada and the rest of the population of the United States have been killed by these animals.
63% of 43% of ethnic white Latinos,
55% of 25% of freaking ethnic Jewish voters
who are beginning to scratch their...
Thank you, doctor.
Come on.
Looks like I might have a happy ending.
It's okay.
The snake condo.
The universities.
The multi-gall science.
Science.
Our universities.
Josh.
Yes.
Mystical science.
Go, go, go!
Hey!
Yeah!
A science party!
Science party!
In the laboratory!
Late night at the lab!
Everybody's there!
Doctors, professors, PhDs!
Scientists with yellow hair!
Someone's pulling up!
It's anatomic Howard Cadillac!
Geniuses with yellow hair!
Matching lab coats!
Carrying a portable telescope!
To the...
Science!
Science party!
In the laboratory of love!
Hey! Someone spiked the test tubes!
Laboratory!
Laboratory's out of control!
Hands off that equipment, boy!
The sonic mine probe is not a toy!
Take it!
Hey!
Is that cool?
It sounds like a cool visited being, a wound room!
And we didn't have thehealthdevice at all while I was movieக
Just watch me go all over you!
So what happened next September?
When's shot doo!
Aww!
Assets!
Too good to be true!
Science party in the laboratory
You want more science? We'll give you lots more
You needed the flow, but just to get on the dance floor
Wake up the lab rats, turn on the party droid
Stay away from the nuclear wasteoid
Science, a science party tonight
Science, science party tonight
Science party tonight
Let's see what's going on at, uh...
Let's see what's up in the news here at NASA.
Yeah, check some science news.
I haven't been, I've only been looking at the bad news.
The science news is so good.
It makes you feel like everything's going to be fine.
We'll have robots building robots that make better robots.
And soon the robots will just...
That's what we've got.
...take over.
They'll take care of us all the time.
And we won't even know they're doing it.
We'll think that they've left the planet, been outlawed.
But they'll be taking care of us.
It all makes sense.
I was reading that Isaac Asimov robot series.
And, you know, those were written in the 50s, but...
Was it iRobot?
You could see more, yes.
That's the very first of the series.
And then...
Actually, I kind of read the very end,
and then I read the beginning,
and I'm working my way towards the middle.
Well, NASA is apparently having a...
Thousands of books.
A rocket contest.
A rocket contest?
Yeah.
Red rocket.
Look, there's a big red rocket right on the screen there.
It's apparently a red rocket contest.
Do you know anything about that, Dave?
Well, I know they glare.
I know they glare, and also there's a...
Oh, yeah, you've got a big dog.
You probably know about that red rocket.
I thought you were talking about the rocket's red glare.
No, look at that big red rocket right there.
Not the sunshine left over from your fluvia
after you gazed into the nostril,
the third nostril of the solar disc.
For so long, your sinuses fry.
Do you think NASA is hoping that some super genius
will stupidly reveal the perpetual motion
faster-than-light engine...
So they can suppress it, yeah.
...that runs on no fuel, just breath?
So they can have a spokesman come out and say,
yeah, there never will or ever has been a machine
that would focus your breath in a way
that would make you move faster than a speed of light.
If safely...
Well, not really travel faster than light,
but just...
...a port through wormholes
using the power of your mind and your breath and garlic.
Oh, that's...
Well, that's a yogic thing.
You can get those at Safeway now.
Wow.
Travel without moving.
Yeah, here you go.
Sex, IQ, and ET.
How we got big brains.
The same way we got...
Apparently, space.com is apparently running a story.
Yeah, they have a picture of an Oberman there.
A big head man.
An Oberman.
Waterhead.
Brain head man.
He's a high macrocephalic.
A hot woman who doesn't have a big head.
She's a macrocephalic.
No, but she's looking very pensive and has a wonderful smile on her face.
Do you prefer macrocephalic or macrobooty?
She's like hot for the brainiac.
Do you know what a big head means?
Yeah.
What goes with a big head?
So this is what space.com has degenerated to.
Big hat.
Look at their...
They're floating around the Amazon River looking...
Searching in boats.
What?
For a missing meteor.
Oh, yeah, sure.
A meteor.
That apparently was used by this guy to come to Earth.
Big headed thing rides...
We got to describe this big headed guy.
Suddenly appears in the Amazon.
He has small jowls.
With women falling over in his feet.
He's got kind of a flabby foreskin around his neck.
His jaw protrudes a little bit, but not enough to show him as an Oberman.
He looks more like an Untermensch with a macrocephalic problem.
Perhaps maybe hydrocephalic.
As if somebody poured the whole gallon there.
And the CIA is desperately trying to find his spaceship.
His spaceship, which has crashed in the Amazon.
They're telling everybody that it's a meteor.
Yeah.
Every time you hear about a search for a missing meteor...
I just thought we were somewhere in the West.
Anyway.
Looking for a meteor.
A meteor.
I'm sorry.
I just...
I don't know what the good and the bad and the ugly came out of that meteor.
And out of that macrocephalic.
It was the Amazon, dude.
But that's where they also look...
Quote, unquote, look for missing meteors.
And quote, unquote, dinosaur bones.
And whatever it is that they cordon off a huge area.
And white Indians.
And they're so important to the United States government.
So they don't have to pay up.
We've got to stop them.
They're going to kill us all.
They're going to fuck you up in their spaceship.
Did they do any sexual things to you?
That's what I call a closed encounter.
Its structure is just solidified on the surface.
I think it's anticipating the attack.
Anticipation denotes intelligence.
What was that?
Uh, uh, uh, uh, what?
Space herpy.
That's disgusting!
Alien approaching!
Alien!
Don't run.
We are your friends.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, coming.
Another one coming.
Imagine for a moment that this thing
is not anything that can be identified
because it prefers not to be.
Wherever there is life,
it brings death.
Because it is evil.
Absolute evil.
One more reason to shoot first.
What if it goes out and melts down a busload of nuns?
How would you like to write the headline on that?
one. None so? Behind me are the raging flames of where the dome of the rock, one of Islam's
most sacred sites, once stood. Just moments ago, the ancient shrine was rocked by a devastating
explosion.
Over three million are dead and thousands are seeking refuge after a freak meteor shower
hit Eastern Europe. It is written in the last days, a world leader will rise up. When possessed
by Satan, he will declare himself God and embark on a reign of terror until the Lord
comes and destroys him. The final battle between heaven and hell approaches. I have a really
bad feeling about this. What doesn't kill you makes you stronger. Look, I really don't
think they flew 90 billion light years ago.
My idea is to come down here and start a fight and get all rowdy. If you calculate the time
it takes to destroy a city and move on, we're looking at the worldwide destruction of every
major city in the next 36 hours. We're being exterminated.
Flush the bombers, get the subs in launch mode. We are at DEFCON 1.
The city is headed for a disaster of biblical proportion. What do you mean biblical? What
do you mean?
What do you mean this?
Old Testament, Mr. Mayor. Real wrath of God type stuff. Fire and brimstone coming down
from the sky. Rivers and seas boiling. 40 years of darkness, earthquakes, volcanoes.
The dead rising from the grave. Human sacrifice, dogs and cats living together. Mass hysteria.
I don't think I can cope with any more of this. I think I'll just go and have a little
lie down.
Jell-a-boom.
Boom, yeah. I understand boom.
Ba-da-boom.
Big.
Big ba-da-boom.
Ba-da-big-boom.
Big.
Boom.
Yeah, big ba-da-boom.
Ba-da-boom.
Big.
Boom.
Big ba-da-boom.
Man is an endangered species.
We'll stop any attack that they could begin. Provided the attack is lame and poorly thought
out and it's our grandma's.
Save your energy. Save yourselves. Avoid the planet Earth at all costs. Farewell.
We'll be right back.
DJ Epoch did that collage, I think. And before that, ESO Swamp Radio. Lots of ESO Swamp Radio
from WCSB, which is actually the Einstein's Secret Outlaws band with a mystery guest guitarist
is heard in the background jamming at Tranquility Bass.
Brushwood.
Before ESO Radio, we heard that song Science Party is by Consortium of Genius, a funny
band that you can check out at their website, www.consortiumofgenius.com. That's all one
big word. Consortium of Genius.
And now, friends, a live recording from the Akron Revival.
This year, sponsored by Reverend Toth Wilder, in which Reverend Dr. Uncle Haj Onan Kanobite
leads us in a sing-a-long.
I know a man whose name was Bob and selling things. That was his job.
That was his job.
So he sold his things from door to door.
From door to door.
If you had some, you'd buy some more.
You'd buy some more.
I know he bought from door to door, and if you had some, he'd buy some more.
He drove his car.
From town and divorced.
And believe me, he got around. He drove his car from town to town. And believe me, he got around.
Jehovah One gave him a plan. Soon some genius will rule the land.
He came to one gave him a plan. Soon some genius will rule the land.
Well, X day came and X day went.
Was all that cash truly well spent?
Well, X day came and X day went. Was all that cash truly well spent?
It's true, the cash we won't get back.
But we don't care, cause we have slack.
We have slack!
It's true, the cash we won't get back. But we don't care, cause we have slack.
Will this song end?
Or go some more?
Funny at first.
Now it's a bore.
Will this song end? Or go some more?
Funny first, now it's a bore.
And so I'll end.
This endless tale.
Returning to.
The Saint of Sales.
And so I'll end this endless tale.
Returning to the Saint of Sales.
I knew a man, his name was Bob.
I'm telling you things, that was his job.
Yeah!
He was gonna ogle me.
I knew aths were best.
Of what?
Scare.
He was a small boy who then he drove his Screw Andrewa into town.
This is not the hermitage of the subgenius.
This is not the monastery of the subgenius, nor the nunnery of the subgenius.
This isn't the sit-at-home-alone of the subgenius,
or the play-on-your-computer-all-day of the subgenius.
And it's definitely not the come-to-the-lives spider-and-don't-talk-to-other-people of the subgenius.
Perhaps, if each and every one of you don't meet someone tonight, you have cheated yourself.
Perhaps, it's a little intimidating to meet somebody tonight,
and so we're going to organize something else.
And by meeting somebody, I don't mean you should go up and talk to the sexiest person in the room,
because there's only one Chaz Smith here,
and if you don't, you have to go around.
But some of you should believe me.
That's what I heard.
So, can you believe me?
Because I'm here.
Baby, baby, baby!
One, one, dollar, dollar.
One, one, one, one, one, one, one, one.
Oh, nay, oh, nay, oh, oh, oh, nay!
Oh, oh, nay, oh, oh, oh, nay!
Oh, oh, nay, oh, oh, nay!
Oh, oh, nay, oh, nay, oh, nay!
Hey!
Big fat bop!
B O B
Moving to New York today,, we completed the task of making the New York Purhos derjen similar to the primary prom Tsar truck,
B-B-O-B
B-O-B
Big fan
B-B-O-B
Bob
Ladies and gentlemen, here come the Swinging Love Quartzes!
B-B-O-B
You couldn't wait five minutes.
You couldn't even wait a minute.
It's taking too long.
I mean, you should have finished that business before you got here.
I told you.
What are you doing?
You're still dragging your unfinished work behind you.
And it sounds like it's going good.
I tell you, this is really professional.
Sorry.
Sorry about that.
Just forget everything you saw up to this point.
And we're the Swingin' Love Corp.
And we're just going to start over.
And as an apology to all of you beautiful fans who came out here tonight,
we're going to start with our best song.
This is our best song.
This is the best song that we do.
Oh, pretty mama.
Oh, baby.
This is our best song.
This is our greatest song.
Mama.
This is our best song.
We love this song.
궁금 갖 ко вещи
That's what you're gonna find
How long you've waited
For me to come and go
So we can make a song
But you've never seen the stars
Pretty baby.
73.
I picked the goddarned terror of the frigging gods out of my nose.
Pardon my language.
But yeeha, let the sons of God and man bear witness.
Even in the belly of the thunderbird I've been casting out the false prophets, I'm busting
a nut and blowing my o-ring, and ripe to throw a loaf.
For I speak only the frigging truth, and never in my days have I spoken other than.
For my every utterance is a lie, including this very one you hear.
I say, have sex with, em, if they can.
Can't take a joke.
By God, anything for a laugh, I say.
I am the last remaining homo correctus, I am the goddarned man of the future.
I'll drive a mile so, as not to walk a foot, I am a human being of the first goddarned
water, I'm insured for acts o' God and Satan.
I was shanghaied by bodiless fiends and alien zoos from a corporate galaxy, and got away
with their hubcaps.
I cannot be tracked on radar.
I wear nothing uniform, I wear no goddarned uniform.
Yes baby, I'm 23 feet tall and have 13 rose o' breasts, I was settled by a triceratops,
I gave the aunties virgin a high protein toxo wash.
I'm a bacteriological weapon, I'm armed and loaded.
I'm a fission reactor, I fart plutonium, power plants are fueled by the sweat from my brow,
when they plug me in, the lights go out in Hong Kong.
I siren retarded space bastards across the cosmos, I cook and eat my dead, yahoo, I'm
the unshaven thorn tree of the Atlantis zoo.
I pay no taxes.
The devil's hands are my ideal playground.
I hold the seven bladed windbreaker, the wheels that turn are behind me, I think backwards.
I do it for fun.
My imagination is a frigging cancer and I'll pork it before it porks me.
The say a donzillion is the highest number there is.
Well my god.
I count to a donzillion and one.
Yes, I'm the purple flower of hell county, give me wide berth.
When I drop my drawers, mother nature swoons.
I use a python for a prophylactic, I'm thicker, harder and meaner than the Alaskan pipeline,
and carry more spew.
I'll freeze your seed before it gets the bathroom tile.
Yee.
and our heads are all stuck up our own asses.
And so, you know, it's kind of hard to get out of the diplomatic circle,
if you know what I'm saying.
Which is why we have the squeeze bulb syringes.
Oh, I can feel it right now.
It's kind of like...
You insert it into each nostril, and you squeeze it out first,
and then you insert it in the nostril,
and you release the bulb, and it expels the fluid.
Now, where I'm coming from,
I feel like there's a pair of buttocks wrapped on my head like a hat.
And then somehow it makes me psychic.
Am I getting the right thing, or have I gotten something I shouldn't have?
I knew you were going to say that.
I knew you were going to bring up the whole psychic thing.
You are psychic.
It's your buttocks wrapped on my head, aren't it?
Isn't it?
It is.
I often think that there's somebody out there who's recording every word that happens in the show,
and then eventually they'll all be played back again.
And that was the random recurrent moment beloved by all.
Yeah.
Order now while supplies are limitless.
You may be asked to call upon for a certain favor.
Maybe someone might want you to...
Francis, this is the year 1962.
Imagine somebody listening to us at the same time in the year, oh, say, 2002.
Boy, that's 40 years past.
Can you imagine such a thing?
Ask not what your forehead can do in this small space.
Ask what my forehead is doing in your head.
How awful.
But it's amazing the way you've got these records from the future.
I like that.
It's very small and unique, like a snowflake.
It's emboldening.
It's emboldening and embossing as well.
Absolutely.
And I have heard you've been called snowflake so many times.
That's because she melts whenever you touch her.
Oh, yes.
She's a frosty little thing, huh?
Well, no, she's not frosty.
Something's lost and something's gained.
If you could see her now, maybe every day, you would want to carve your own...
What does that mean there?
Something's lost and something's gained in living every day.
It's a psycho, scrooge, squander.
One step forward, two steps back.
It's a cosmic, I'm about to spew.
Yeah.
Isn't it?
It's just like amazing.
So let us all remember the retching motion that Sri Hajambo has taught us.
Begin.
With a very, very deep breath.
And we start.
Till next week.
You must remember this.
A kiss is just a kiss.
But a nuclear explosive device.
Information is not knowledge.
Keep your head on tight.
You're back to the wind and you're sacking the saddle.
But we got a point.
Keep that sack to the business.
I like that.
But knowledge is not wisdom.
And wisdom is not necessarily truth.
And truth is not necessarily...
Oh, thank you ESO, Swamp Radio, WCSB,
and special guest caller, Reverend Lipo Abernathy.
Friends, you're listening to the subgenius radio ministry, Hour of Slack.
And you can send me...
Sang tapes at...
Oh, got that pencil ready.
P.O. Box 181417.
Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
You can also get that same information from www.subgenius.com.
Or you can write for free information on the Church of the Subgenius
from subgenius at P.O. Box 217.
B.O. Box 204206.
Austin, Texas 78720.
I am stag at subgenius.com.
And here is heart ignition.
.
Thank you.