Ladies and gentlemen, here is the latest bulletin from the Intercontinental Radio News.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
I'm standing in a large, semicircular, pitch-black oblong split in the ceiling.
Through this opening, I can see...
The self-genius, power of spark!
In the meantime, we take you to the Hotel Martinet,
where Bob and his orchestra are offering a program of dance music.
There was a farmer, B-O-B was his name, oh, B-O-B, B-O-B, B-O-B was his name, oh!
From PR News in Washington, I'm visiting Washington this week as part of a 13-day visit to Mexico,
PR's bad,
on Wall Street 6103341263.
Two teams of scientists have developed a new approach to obtaining taxpayer dollars to facilitate
the production of the film.
The U.S. military says U.S. warplanes and helicopters have killed PR News in Washington.
And who am I?
I am just a nobody.
Yes, a nobody, because you can't see my body, but you can hear my voice.
So I am a somebody.
Yes, I am speaking to your inner self, to your consciousness, to your inner sanctum soul
of your universal mind, to where the magical kingdom of God is within you.
Not someplace.
else. For what is
here is every place else.
And what is not here
is no other place to be found.
Is no other place to be found.
Ladies and gentlemen, you're listening to
The Self Genius
Hour of
Swag.
Yet it was
Artemia
Salina.
If our nation should ever be
attacked,
the pleasure humain
follow the instructions you hear
qui nous en donne.
In the event of attack,
on y est? Parfait.
A jet bomber
could fly five miles an hour.
Une facette psychospirituelle.
There's a lady
who's sure
all that glitters is gold.
And she's
a
stay away
to heaven.
Yet there's
an emotional
if the stars
are
A word she can get, get what?
What she came for
And she's buying a stairway to heaven
There's a sign on the wall
But she wants to be sure
Cause you know sometimes words have to mean
In a tree by the brook
There's a songbird who sings
Sometimes all about thoughts on this given
Ooh, when she's buying a stairway to heaven
Do I, do I, it makes me wonder
There's a feeling I get
When I look to the west
And my spirit is crying for you
In my thought I have seen
Rims of smoke through the tree
And the oysters over those hopes I'm looking
Do I, do I, it makes me wonder
And it's whispered that soon
If we all call the tune
Then the pipe will lead us to reason
And a new day will dawn for those who stand long
And the fire will burn for those who stand long
And the forests will echo with laughter
Does anybody remember laughter?
And she's buying a stairway to heaven
And it makes me wonder
Yeah
If there's a bustling forest
In your hedgerow
Call the gardener
It's just a spring cleat for the May Queen
Yes, there are two paths
So you can go back one at a laura
There's still time to change the road you're on
The road you're on
Do I really mean that my entire life is in vain?
Do I, do I, it makes me wonder
Or am I lost?
Your head is humming and it won't go
In case you don't know
The piper's calling you to join him
Dear lady, can you hear the wind blow?
And did you know
Your stairway lies on the whispered wind?
Ah!
Take a guess
Maybe I'm asleep
Ever been the wanderer
Don't you know
Magic's smile doesn't want to apologize
To the real or an inin deactivated講
To the real unless you want to Shut up your ears
Thank you.
That sounds delicious.
I bet the clean-up is easy.
I bet it's inexpensive and really just satisfies your man at home.
Definitely.
Yeah.
Reverend Stang is one of the happiest stomached men ever.
So he tells me, anyway.
If we could switch gears for a moment,
I have a question about the political scene.
And I know it must seem so provincial
from the cosmic point of view of being queen of all the UFOs,
but where do the...
Amos, again, you need to be as loud as you can.
You know, I'm actually rather old,
and I can't hear very well,
so you have to speak right up next to the microphone.
A thousand pardons, Your Majesty.
Quite all right.
Where do the UFOs, the alien people,
stand on the current immigration legislation?
And have you considered using any of your influence,
power, death rays, etc.,
to tilt the scales one way or the other?
I know it must seem a kind of provincial issue
on this little suburban island we call America.
You know, again,
this actually may feel like a cop-out to you,
but I have to say that with the people that...
the creatures, the beings that I am in touch with
being the unidentified ones,
I really can't speak for them.
The identified ones that you're curious about,
I don't have much knowledge of.
So I really...
I'm not able to give an opinion one way or the other
for those folks.
Hmm.
Sorry.
Okay, well...
It's just not in my realm.
What type of...
Like, so you're the queen of all UFOs.
Yeah.
What kind of managerial roles do you play?
Managerial roles?
Well, actually,
I would give you a day in the life.
As Reverend Stang would say,
my job is to stand around looking beautiful.
And I don't really have a hard time doing that.
It's a lot of fun.
I allow Reverend Stang to worship me,
adore me, preen me.
He massages my head, my shoulders, my neck, and my feet,
and all over my body every day.
And pretty much that's about it.
It's rough work, but someone's got to do it.
Well...
So as far as administrative duties,
like, you know, the action items,
you know, things that have to happen during the day for me,
it's actually...
It's so slackful that it's hard to describe.
Mm-hmm.
How about if, let's just say,
I mean, I'm talking about a friend of mine here.
Let's just say that you wanted to meet an exist.
Or, you know,
because there's all these tales about alien abductions and things like that.
Let's just say a friend of yours that you know about
really has been trying for years to meet an alien.
Cruising forward.
Could you hook a brother up?
I'm afraid that's outside my realm, too.
I'm sorry.
Just totally outside my realm.
It's nothing that I have any control or power over.
You know, I think I know myself and all the listeners at home.
We really want to know what you are responsible for.
I mean, what do you do?
And are you willing to take this opportunity now
in this international exclusive broadcast
on Amos Hap's Electric Chalet
in the Feminist Kitchen starring Rikki Shangles?
Do you, Princess We Are Doe, queen of all the UFOs,
want to apologize for Shirley MacLaine once and for all?
Well, you know, Shirley MacLaine,
I'm actually, I'm not really all that familiar
with your Earth Farm One culture,
pop culture and other cultures.
I just, I don't study it.
I'm not familiar with it.
And I've heard that she's kind of gone off the deep end
as far as being sort of like a new age or newage
hippy-dippy-dip shit.
But, you know, it's not my fault.
And, um...
Not your fault.
I'm really not all that familiar with her and her work.
But you are asking what I do.
And let me tell you what I do.
I do actually have some influence in the Church of the Subgenius.
For instance, I have veto power.
I nay-said the branding, the required branding
that was going to be for every subgenius.
That was totally nay-said by me.
No way.
I said no way.
Also, there was going to be required trepanning,
no way.
I said no way.
That's not going to happen.
Um, I also...
What about the bobbies?
Pardon me?
The bobbies, if they want to do the branding
and the trepanning themselves,
they're perfectly welcome to.
But it's not going to be done under the auspices
of the Church of the Subgenius while I'm seated here.
What about the soul harvesting?
Do you have any qualms about that?
Or the prairie squid, for that matter?
Does that raise any jealousy issues?
Oh, absolutely.
You know, not at all.
If there weren't prairie squids,
there would be just so many unhappy people out there,
men and women.
We need prairie squids.
No, there's no jealousy issues.
Absolutely not.
I would like to, you know, take it into the bedroom.
If you feel uncomfortable with some of my questions,
if you don't like them, you just throw them right back.
All right.
Is it true that it ain't cheating if it's Bob, ladies?
That is true.
That's 100% true.
It ain't cheating if it's Bob, and it ain't for the guys.
It ain't gay if it's Bob.
And same thing with women.
It ain't gay if it's Connie.
You know, it's all free love when it comes to Bob and Connie.
I mean, they're kind of like Jungian archetypes in that sense.
They're not even on our realm.
That's true.
It's like having sex with an idea.
Have you ever had sex with J.R. Bob Dobbs?
Well, I can't let something like that out.
Come on.
What do you think?
I can't say this enough.
You guys are just trying.
You get me to reveal things, and I'm not going to do it.
Okay.
Well, how about if we hit it from this angle?
Does Ivan Stang ever get mad when you have sex with J.R. Bob Dobbs?
Well, let's just say that, you know, he's learned to deal with his boss in special ways,
and they work things out between them.
Well, that sounds good to me.
Yeah.
Oh.
Gotta have slack.
Gotta.
You gotta have.
Gotta have slack.
Yeah.
I got a big old bob
He's right inside my pocket
Got my big old bob
Just reach inside my pocket
I just washed him off
He ain't too stinky this time
You got to try my bob
He really wants to meet you
If you'll open up to bob
You'll know that he's a love god
And once he gets inside
He's never gonna leave you
The burning seed of bob
Is leaking out of my pocket
Just open under him
He'll crawl inside your socket
Well, you know, the Catholics are
Have all kinds of
They've had to face a lot of
Blanket hatred
Especially nowadays
I mean, it's almost like
The name of their sect is synonymous
With child molestation
Which is certainly not fair
To the average Catholic
And it doesn't help that
The new pope used to be a Nazi
It doesn't help
He wasn't really a Nazi
You know, so I mean
It's like any religion
You can find a good reason
To make fun of
That's what I like about it
They're all kind of
When you get down to it
They're all the same
Except, of course, for
J.R. Bogg's religion
Which is better
Simply because that's the one
We believe in
But it could also be called
Anti-religion
Well, only anti-false religions
Right
Well, we've swiped it
I mean, borrowed from
All the good religions
Well, the good parts
From lots of bad religions
I should say
The naughty bits, you know
Like when you
The special books that your dad
Kept in his underwear drawer
Next to the gun
And balloons
All the Larry Flitter books
And, you know
He had these special paperbacks
And you'd look for the good parts
In those
That's the way we put together
Bob's
The details in Bob's religion
Using his memos
And other people's old
Cast-aside religions
Secret communiques
It was cool back then
It ain't the same now
Now that you put
Type of button in a computer
Anybody can make a religion
In a computer
And anybody can make porn
Yeah, but back then
They had to make porn the hard way
I've got a copy of a
Comedy porno movie
It's like an old underground comic
In some ways
It's in Spanish
And it's all computer animated
People doing bizarre
Sexy stuff
And not normal looking people
Either
It's all kinds of strange characters
Almost an inspiration
From a reproduction cycle
It's like a desktop
A desktop animated porno movie
I guess they used a poser
That program poser
Something like that
And it's called
Too Funky For You
With the numeral 2
And the numeral 4
In the title
The radio synesthesia
On WCSN
In Cleveland
Cleveland State University
Provided us with all of that
Thanks to Dr. Sinister
Before that we heard a little bit of a song
By D.K. Jones
And where's truly Reverend Stank
And some saucer bed sound effects
By Frater Saadi
And now
Mm-hmm
Ladies when you buy milk
Remember that no other kind of milk
Has as many uses as
The self genius
Power of
Swag
That's miraculous
Good good good
Oh nonsense
Well it doesn't seem quite ethical somehow
From the studios of PR
This is PR Bluster
PR
Where you can listen to people yell at each other
PR is just talking
PR
But he was nervous
We believe that
Did he appear nervous?
Definitely
How nervous?
A little more
PR
The lemur did it
And now a submission
From a new depositor
Called
The Caveator
Good morning again
I am not a number
I am a person
What's it all about?
I am number six
Where am I?
Orange
We're all pawns you do
I resigned
I will not be pushed
Filed
Stapped
Indexed
Briefed
Debriefed
Or numbered
My life is my own
Is it?
Mr. Wobba
I am a half-dozen-and-a-nother
It doesn't matter which side runs the village
It's one by one side or the other
No certainty
But both sides are becoming identical
What in fact has been created
An international community
A perfect blueprint for world order
When the sides facing each other suddenly realize that they're looking into a mirror
They will see that this is the pattern for the future
The whole earth
As the village
All the way up to the moon
The sun
Paint over our entire planet
Aoris
You won't hide
Thinks
That's better than me
So you wanted to vent
So we will stay
Come back, wipe this place off the face of the earth obliterated, and you with it.
Your services will not be required tomorrow.
How about the conspiracy?
Oh.
Yeah.
Everybody has some conspiracy theory.
We're not talking about the little conspiracy theories like the crashed UFOs at Area 51
or the mafia killing Kennedy or any of that, or the fashion conspiracy
that makes you think you have to wear makeup and look a certain way.
No, no.
Those are minuscule compared to the true conspiracy of the normals.
And it doesn't even know it's a conspiracy.
It's not clever.
They don't even know they're doing it.
Well, once I'm automatic.
The times they were a-changing, but now it looks like they may stop changing.
That actually seems to be the fear.
Them, they, the others.
The others seem to want all change to stop.
It's like, okay, we've got our internet and crap.
We can stop changing now.
We must not let the stopping even begin, my friends.
People don't even notice the world ending.
I look around you, you know, it's that we're in the middle of the shakedown.
Obviously, we've got to get slack because time is running out.
Time itself is running out when things stop changing.
That's the end of time.
And on that subject, President Bush.
You know, now, I don't, we're in Church of the Subgenius.
We're not, we try not to get too, we don't like to think of either side
of the conspiracy as being our friend.
They have this good cop, bad cop thing where, you know, whoa,
if Bush is so bad, then John Kerry must be my friend.
Well, you know, I don't know.
It's, and it's true.
Bush is so bad.
Do you sometimes wish that Bob Dole had won?
If that had meant that we wouldn't have to have Bush later,
it makes you yearn for his father.
It makes you miss Reagan.
Now, that is bad, friends.
That is really bad.
And they're bad shots, too.
I actually almost did the same thing Cheney did.
I did not shoot my dad in the face.
I missed.
But, but I, but Lonesome Cowboy Dave was going, oh, you know,
you know how I shot his friend in the face?
He just wanted to help him keep a low profile.
Okay, I got that one out.
I can erase it.
So, friends, how did the world get so dirty?
Evolution isn't fair.
The decks are stacked for the winners.
And the, the, our privacies are all being taken away.
Have you heard about urine tracings?
Where now they can actually trace where you've been and what you've bought by your pee.
They can judge your character by your pee.
And I don't mean by when you take a pee test when you go for a job.
I mean every time you flush the toilet.
You are flushing your children down the drain.
Their future, their privacy.
They will sue us retroactively, friends, for lying to the doctor.
Because they can track you through your toilet.
And that's very people.
That's paranoia, isn't it?
It's a new word.
As the cold, gray dawn broke over the fog-shrouded coastal village of Benton Cove, death came
to the big house on the hill.
School lunch should be balanced nutritionally.
That's why a dessert for lunch is just as essential as for a bigger, heavier meal.
What could be simpler for you to serve?
Or more enjoyable?
More enjoyable and tasty for your children than cupcakes.
Of course, cupcakes make an ideal after-school snack along with a tall, cold glass of beer.
The word Bob from the old ganglionic responses signifies a species or separate race.
Only for lack of proper understanding has Bob been considered as an individual.
That man is a homicidal maniac!
More really.
As the Orgosmososm, he is the chief product of the semi-tergid, the Jehovah One, who back-up
this music.
The man with the judge's hopelessly insane.
And within the nature of this microgasm, the space god, Yahweh One, established all the
qualities of powers that he himself possessed.
He must be returned to us.
Jehovah Prime, however, does not have slack.
And therefore, could not only not bestow it upon Bob...
Crazy like a fox.
From PR News in Washington, I'm Bob Duff.
And I'm brought in separately.
He looked at the man next to him and smiled and smiled.
Gun control advocates don't keep track of their merchandise.
He says the memos show a disaster non-existent.
White House News Secretary Scott McClellan says the Bush administration struggled to locate food, water, and even PR news in Washington.
The dealers of America present the...
So genius.
Power of...
...the world.
And this is Kenny saying hello for your friendly dealer.
They're the men you can always count on.
Save trouble and save money.
Um, do you...
I've, you know, as a female subgenius, I've noticed that the female perspective is often left out.
Why do you think this is?
Well, the real problem is that there just isn't enough female participation in the church.
If more women would get involved...
...write, preach, send in their, their writings, there would be more representation from women.
It's all up to the women to get more involved so that they'll be more seen there.
Reverend Stang will put forth whatever is given to him.
If you do some spouting, some Connie-style spouting, he will love that.
By the way, you identified yourself just now as a female subgenius.
And I wanted to ask both you and Amos what your subgenius history is.
We'll ask the questions.
But we might deign to answer one if you could be a little more specific.
Okay.
Well, I just was very curious to know how you all came to know subgenius.
I mean, it's been ten years ago for you, Amos.
And Reiki, I'm not sure about you.
And I was just totally, honestly curious to know how you became associated with it.
I'm not sure about me, Princess.
I don't know.
I think...
Pleiadians, I should say.
I was recruited at 16 by a Pleiadian emissary of light, given an incredible book called Bringers of the Dawn.
Bringers of the Dawn.
Which I read word for word at 16 years old and totally, absolutely, 100% believed it.
And my DNA did start to accelerate.
And now, in fact, I do not have the full 12 helix of DNA.
But I do have eight helixes.
And I'll tell you, eight is great.
Wow.
And so, I really came to it through that.
And only basically, I'd say, a year ago, I met my cult leader slash lover about two years ago.
And he said, you would love the Church of the Subgenius.
And as a true subgenius, I said, you're full of shit.
Stuff it up your ass.
I don't want to hear your lies.
I don't want to hear it.
So, I picked up a book about a year ago.
And it just, you know, it didn't even, I didn't even need to read it.
I picked it up through osmosis.
I've learned the dogma.
You'd wipe with it if I remember.
And you know what?
I, and I also am part Sasquatch.
I think that's, I have a stronger vein of Yeti in me.
I have a lot of Yeti in me.
I would like more Yeti in me.
But.
Not in the studio, Rikki.
But you, so that's my dogma.
I have.
I have eaten at restaurants called the Sasquatch.
I've seen Sasquatch.
I have been with Sasquatch.
I am a Sasquatch.
Cool.
And that's, that's my story.
Wow, thank you for sharing that with me, Rikki.
I really appreciate that.
Very cool.
I just, I just wanted to be knee deep in trim.
And being a lazy man, I knew that.
Let Bob do the work.
And also not very attractive.
No, not at all.
It just gets worse every year.
But you can imagine, even, even ten years ago.
Yeah, I mean he's about 250 pounds, 5'4", balding.
And he, let's be honest, it's about two inches.
Two and a half inches.
Oh, no, no.
I mean that depends on, you know, like when El Nino made the earth, they actually swell a little bit.
Causing it to go around slower, slow down the calendars.
Maybe then I had two inches, maybe.
And I mean, I'm not gonna lie to you folks.
I'm not gonna lie to you.
I am a, I'm a babalicious babe.
I'm gorgeous.
That's a fact.
Oh, that's, oh.
Yeah.
Good times.
And sometimes people look at us and they say, what?
They just don't get it.
But really, he, you know, he used, he used the subgenius dogma.
He used your guys' tricks to, to get sex.
And, you know, I didn't know it at the time.
But I, I thank him for it now.
And he's, you know, four and a half feet of pure man.
What a sweet story.
Yeah.
So.
I'm charmed.
I'm totally charmed.
I'm gonna take a break.
Do you mind if I ask you about you and Ivan Stang's relationship?
How did you two fall in love?
Well, no, I don't mind you asking at all.
I was, was and am associated with a group called Ace.
The Association for Consciousness Exploration.
And if you want to read all about it endlessly, you can go to one of our websites.
Ace, let's see, one is Rosencomet.com, R-O-S-E-N-C-O-M-E-T.com, or Starwoodfestival.com.
But that's how I met Reverend Stang.
Someone in our group brought him in for one of our Starwood festivals.
And I volunteered.
I volunteered to pick him up at the airport.
And that's how I met him.
And we were good friends for a long, long time.
And eventually we got to be more than friends when his marriage ended.
And he was free to pursue a relationship.
Did he break your watch to try to impress you?
No, he didn't.
He tried to.
But I had a fake, broken watch in my pocket.
And slipped that in, and he never knew.
He thought he was breaking my watch to get me, but it was actually a broken watch.
Don't cheat a cheater.
Salt River Stream
Shine
I dedicate this program to the fight against crime.
Not merely crimes of violence and crimes of dishonesty,
but crimes of intolerance, discrimination, and bad citizenship.
Crimes against America.
The Self-Genius Power of Swag.
For most effective relief, use only as directed.
The relief it brings is incredibly fast.
Here's why.
No thanks.
And there, ladies and gentlemen, you have the beginning of our mystery.
Okay, let's talk shop.
If you could recommend one product that every subgenius must have, what would it be?
So I say out loud, and look at your beautiful big brain.
Please.
Well, of course, it would be a membership to the Church of the Subgenius.
I mean, that's, you know, the basic thing that everyone should have to protect you
so that when X day comes, you'll be delivered.
I mean, that's the most important thing.
Other than that, of course, everyone should start off with putting their baby toe in
of getting a rise, the subgenius video.
That would be my advice.
Just for basics.
Basic starters.
And just to put on the back burner here, I probably had some of the best sexual intercourse
of my life watching a rise.
Oh!
With, with, and I became J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And I came as J.R. Bob Dobbs, and let me tell you, wow.
It's like, Bob, you came again and again and again.
Yeah.
It was, it was the second and third and fourth coming.
It was.
Fourth coming.
It was ridiculous.
I can't abide them even now and then.
That's the worst that I have seen since.
Icia, I can stay for a long time, this little babe.
We're out and together in trouble all day.
Fine now.
Got to go clean up the ceremony.
I can still be positive about the future.
Bye-bye.
I'm in a good place.
OK.
You wanna have a but?
I'll go on quick.
¶¶
Wonderful piece.
Kevin Meredith did that wonderful piece there.
¶¶
Called Beneath a Shiny Crust of Solid Platinum.
That was the name of that instrumental beautiful piece.
And now, PR News.
From PR News in Washington, I'm disrupted.
A defense lawyer has been found today.
Police said apparently PR's bad.
On Wall Street, the 10262.
Republican Congressman Tom DeLay showed up on Florida's Interstate 75
for the first time since a hearing on DeLay's request
for a new execution-style conspiracy.
Tom reports.
370,000 residents are bending palm trees and knocking out PR News.
For PR News, I'm Tom.
Syrian officials are absurd.
Officials died yesterday from what officials are calling indirect PR News.
Also, here's some interesting news from this past week.
Chimpanzees. Also, you sometimes see people with their pet chimpanzee.
That was not my chimpanzee. That was my son, all right?
So he's got a slight body hair problem? Jeez, come on.
Give him a break.
Interesting. Here's an interesting news item from this week.
A state bill proposes Christianity be Missouri's official religion.
This is something from...
Well, it's nice that they have an official religion.
I didn't know that states had such things.
Yeah, I believe this was originally taken from a KMOV.
I don't know if that's a radio or television station, but anyway...
It sounds more like it was taken from The Onion.
No, for real. Okay, here's the story. I'll read it for you.
Missouri legislators in Jefferson City considered a bill
that would name Christianity...
the state's official, quote-unquote, majority religion.
Many Missouri residents had not heard about the bill until Thursday.
Karen Eroesti of the Anti-Defamation League,
along with other watch groups, began a letter-writing and email campaign
to stop the resolution.
The resolution would recognize, quote,
a Christian god, end quote,
and it would not protect minority religions, but, quote,
protect the majority's right to express their religious beliefs, end quote.
The resolution also recognizes that, quote,
a greater power exists, end quote,
and only Christianity receives what the resolution calls, quote,
justified recognition, end quote.
State Representative David Sater of Cassville in southwestern Missouri
sponsored the resolution,
but he has refused to talk about it on camera over the phone.
Antoine Assange, also the...
I wonder if I could get Church of the Subgenius
declared the official street religion of the street that I live on.
You know what...
Because my neighbors are all...
Every religion you can think of.
If I could get...
There might only be one or two Christians or one or two Jews
and one or two Buddhists on this block.
But that was back in...
And I know there's at least four subgeniuses.
In the People's Republic of China,
the People's Republic of Cleveland Heights,
almost anything can happen.
Yeah, we would outlaw, in fact,
all the other religions on this block.
At least...
Well, I guess we wouldn't outlaw them.
We would just make it so they couldn't complain
no matter what...
We did.
Which is what those Missouri...
That Missouri politician wants, is that...
Well, we're not going to tell you
you can't worship your burning man or whatever.
You just can't stop us from putting you in jail
as part of our religious freedom.
Since we're the majority,
you know, we can put your Satanists in jail.
And that way you can't interfere with our freedom of religion
by being seen.
See, could they put us in jail if we had X Day in Missouri?
Missouri?
Not yet.
Not yet, thank God.
No.
But...
So, uh...
But you're...
Actually, maybe they wouldn't be able to do that to you in Missouri,
but here's another place where it might happen.
Here's a...
New Florida town would restrict abortion.
Oh, yeah, that...
Domino's founder...
Domino's pizza guy.
...is building a community around a Catholic university.
If Domino's pizza founder Thomas S. Monaghan has his way,
a new town being built in Florida
will be governed according to strict Roman Catholic principles
with no place to get an abortion,
pornography, or birth control.
Pepperoniville.
Actually, it would be called Ave Maria, Florida.
Oh.
The pizza magnate is bankrolling the project
with at least $250 million
and calls it God's will.
Civil libertarians say the plan is unconstitutional
and are threatening to sue.
The town of Ave Maria is being constructed
around Ave Maria University,
the first Catholic university to be built
in the United States in about 40 years.
Both are set to open next year
about 25 miles east of Naples
in southwestern New York.
The town and the university developed in partnership
with the Barron Collier Company,
an agricultural and real estate business,
will be set on 5,000 acres
with a European-inspired town center,
a massive church,
and what planners call
the largest crucifix in the nation
at nearly 65 feet tall.
All right.
Now, you see, we have to outdo them.
We need a 65-foot-1-inch Dobbs head.
Yeah.
Or it might be just a gigantic pipe.
So this is...
This is inspiring me, though.
If some rich guy wants to buy his own city,
I think that that's...
There's nothing wrong with that.
Yeah, I say let him.
Because you know what, Bill?
We want to buy our...
Yeah, but that guy's got lots of money,
so he can really make...
Anyway, let's try and restrict our...
Well, it's not just him.
It's other people who are interested in this.
But anyway...
This is interesting.
If he gets away with this,
I'm going to make it my life's mission
to establish a community of my own somewhere.
Right, that's the idea.
Governed according to my own personal totalitarian ideas.
All you have to do is start your own pizza chain
that's fabulously successful,
or something like that.
Pizza sucks, too.
But anyway...
Why not build a town...
I would have one where we'd be against a lot of have churches.
How about that, you know?
Here's the only way...
If you own all the land in an area,
like maybe if you owned 5,000 acres
and wanted to build a city there,
you know,
and since it's all technically your property
and everybody else is just renting it,
you know, I suppose you could exercise your right
to say who does what on your property.
Yeah, it's private property.
But, you know,
I don't know if you can really incorporate that
as a municipality.
In private property,
you're not allowed to grow marijuana, for instance.
So there's limits to what you can do.
Ah, but you can stop anybody from...
There was an Indian gentleman that tried that years ago
and his neighbors put a stop to it.
Oh, uh...
You know, we live in a socialist police state.
If you don't give money to the government
on a regular basis,
they'll put you in jail.
It's as simple as that.
You know, this whole town of Ave Maria,
it's just going to be like a little Peyton place.
They're still going to have their little affairs.
There's still going to be little secret goings-on.
There's still going to be people living in Ave Maria
who otherwise think,
hey, this is a great place to live
and are otherwise doing their own little sinful thing.
Well, damn straight,
it'll be the same way in Dobbsville.
I'm sure, you know,
there'll be subgeniuses that sneak around
and do all kinds of pink stuff, you know,
secretly listening to Paul McCartney records
and Neil Diamond.
Secretly.
Well, not secretly.
Out in the open.
That's the whole point of Dodgestown, isn't it?
Well, no.
I mean, see, they'd be doing these...
They'd be...
They'd have to sneak around
because they'd be doing normal things.
We have our own type of nonconformist,
conformist fascism.
It's kind of difficult to administrate
something like that.
Uh-oh, we lost...
That's okay.
We've got room for more.
You know, that's the...
We have freedom of tyranny in this country
and we must preserve this freedom
to have tyranny over others
or else, you know,
what else is it all for?
I don't know.
Actually, my parting words to you
would be to just carry on.
Keep on keeping on.
You guys are doing a great job
and I have a big question, actually,
to ask you that's really important.
Reverend Stang would like to know
if he can use any of this
on his hour of slack.
Oh, my God!
Okay.
All right.
Yeah, that'd be cool.
God damn it, Frankie!
How many times in this feminist kitchen
have I told you when it comes to business
you don't make the unilateral call?
You don't have the cojones!
You don't have the business!
Okay, okay.
Don't hit me again.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
You'd rather on to bolster yourself up like this.
I'll make you some taloupe.
I'll make anything you want, baby.
All right, all right.
All right, I'll bend over.
We'll honor you,
you devil's bargain with Stang.
Stang!
Why don't you just keep talking about Stang all night long?
In those intimate times.
But I'm going to need some of that church air.
That'd be great.
Has he actually been listening?
Is he in the room with you?
He's been listening.
He's probably my biggest fan, so yes, he's been listening.
I've been preparing our stir-fried fennel
with roasted pistachios.
Okay.
I've been preparing it for him tonight.
Oh, my God.
And he's been just listening along and loving every minute of it.
He's just so glowingly proud of me and of you guys
for being so bright to pick up on me.
He's actually extremely impressed with you.
Well, duh.
I mean, you're like a hot babe.
Well, thank you.
Yeah.
I like your singing voice.
I like...
You know what?
Be quiet.
Princess, princess.
Tell him.
I think we should get an apartment together.
I really do.
God damn it!
I think you and I, I think we're soulmates.
I think this could work out.
Keep it in your pants, Frankie!
I'm sorry.
Would Stang care to give his apologies to you over here?
I really...
I'm very, very flattered,
but I'm totally sold on Reverend Stang.
Our hearts are entwined forever.
How many dicks does he have?
How many dicks?
I'm not privy to tell you.
37?
That's private, just between us.
It's 37, isn't it?
37.
I can't tell.
It's 37.
You can't tell because they're too small to count?
No, they're not small.
Where does he keep them?
In a box?
No, they're connected.
God.
He's just got a huge package down there.
He's got a huge package down there.
Okay, well, I think if we're going to start talking about what's-his-face,
then this interview has come to an end.
Very, very sweet one.
Leave some soul for me, Amos.
Okay, here we go.
All right, and thank you very much.
Oh, it's really, really been my pleasure.
You guys are a blast.
I want you to sing more songs,
and I want you to be my lover and wife,
but if you can't do that,
I would really, really love to see you again.
I would really like you to be more present
in the Church of the Subdivis,
and I'll buy more books.
Okay.
Cool.
That's it.
I'm ending this.
She's gone.
He hung up on her.
Amos, you never let me have any fun.
Come on.
Let's get back in the kitchen.
All right.
I have such a rush from that.
That was incredible.
Talking with Princess We Are Doe,
queen of all the UFOs,
the real power behind,
the power behind the pipe,
and we hate men here at the Sonus Kitchen.
Um.
I would never marry one of them.
I'd rest a virgin.
Rather.
For husbands are a boring lot
and only give you bother.
Of course, I'm awfully glad
that mother had to marry father.
But I hate men.
Oh, by the way,
are either of your kids subgeniuses?
My kids?
Oh, they were born subgenius.
They had no choice.
I beat the slack into them.
They still win,
I guess, a little bit when I see a picture of Bob or anything.
Well, I think Judge Punch didn't get involved.
Good thing Judge Punch didn't get involved.
Yeah, Judge Judy and Judge Punch got together and had this,
they worked their frustrations out.
That story was specially written by Bob Dutz,
with music composed and conducted
by Bob Dutz
featured in the cast were Bob Dutz is Kitty.
Bum.
Bullshit!
Where are these creatures?
Why has no one ever seen one?
Yeti, him hide.
When smell human.
But yeti come low country when want to steal woman.
Or with want to steal woman.
Someday there is hope.
In fact, um...
As we await the calling of the day.
Call of the day.
We can go back over.
I think we have to go through a phone call here.
But then we will see a song.
A song of hope.
We'll see it in here.
Sirius Crossroads.
Eddie speaking.
Eddie, Samuel Curtis.
I just landed.
I know.
We saw.
It was great.
Can you dig me out and set me up for a flight?
Sure.
Could you bring the cat?
Yeah, I got him.
His name is Monkey Puss.
I want to name him Oscar.
That wasn't so bad, was it, Monkey?
Eddie, you got something for me, right?
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
I'll be in in a bit.
Okay, goodbye.
Bye.
From America.
American Astronaut, dear friends.
The Billy Nair Show.
They will be performing with the amino acids
heard here in the background
at 9X Day
coming up July 4th weekend.
The world ends
at 7 a.m.
July 5th.
But this is our Slack number.
1046.
If you need more information,
please look at
www.subgenius.com
Hey, thank you.
See you next time.
.
We'll be right back.