Yeah, feel that bump on Bob's dome.
Let's see, Bob.
Oh, hey, that is a good one. What happened?
The Subgenius Valor of Slack.
It's time for the show!
Not this show, but the Time for the Show show.
After about 35 years of Valor of Slack,
the Puzzling Evidence show,
Bob's Slack Time Funhouse,
National Cynical Radio,
and Radio Synesthesia,
there are now new subgenius shows
by people who are only in their 30s and 40s and 50s
instead of their 60s and 70s and 80s,
of which Time for the Show is the oldest,
clocking in at 17 weekly episodes so far.
In fact, because I'm leaving for Portugal tomorrow
to shoot Dr. G. Gordon Gordon
for letting Bob get shot,
I'm just going to save myself some rushed editing
and play the first half,
of that two-hour 17th podcast episode.
So, say hello to Argus, Fid, and Pease,
those smart-alecky, high-jinx, committin' scallywags
whose cuss words I'll have to cut out
for the broadcast version.
Thank y'all.
Time for the show.
Tonight on Time for the Show,
Reverend Sick Pease
shares his grandmother's towel casserole recipe.
Dr. Fox shares Reverend Pease's grandmother's
towel casserole recipe.
And I share my director's commentary
on Reverend Fox's sharing
of Reverend Pease's sharing
of his grandmother's towel casserole.
Stand by for time for the show.
Yeah!
Is this, is it really time for the show?
Oh, man, that makes me so happy
to be back with all of you.
All of my friends.
It's doing so well.
It is.
We should do a show.
Should we?
It's time.
What are we gonna do?
Is it time for the show show?
You know, I did more promotions today for this show
than I think I have in, like, the past month.
And I even came up with, like, stupid crap to talk about
and I'm sitting here and I've got nothing.
Here comes listener number three.
Well, we did a live show on Friday
and now it's Monday.
And we're live again.
It wasn't until, like, 5 p.m.
We said, oh, hey, guys, it's Monday.
Oh, hooray.
It's time for the show.
And so we scrambled all the way down.
We only had four hours to get from one end
of the Hypercube compound to the other.
We made it here in time.
We've got a great show.
We've got great music.
We've got my best friend Pease,
my handsome, handsome, lactating, special,
very geometrically.
Symmetrical friend, Reverend Pease.
I joined this Facebook group about a bunch of guys
called Involuntary Celibates, incels.
And so I'm not comfortable with my handsome term
because I'm also love shy
and am scorned by women sometimes.
You, you, Pease, scorned by women?
I know, it's hard to believe.
Yeah, I'm, dude, they gave me, like, a button
and a membership pack.
These guys are, they got all kinds of rules
like, you know, I'm not a fan of the, you know,
they feel like if you don't sleep with them,
you should get a government rating
and then every man that you sleep with
drops your rating one level.
It's really, really well thought out stuff.
Well, don't ever look a gift vegetable in the urethra.
That is what my father always told me.
And that's exactly what those women are doing.
When you get, when you get a grade A piece of meat,
like Reverend Pease,
come in your way and you turn your nose up,
then we turn our eyes blind
to ISIS hurting that person.
Wait, that hurts your feelings?
See, Pease, you're so accustomed to us ragging on you
that you don't even know when we're complimenting you.
No, no, I know you're complimenting me.
I'm just saying the whole thing about the ladies,
you know, when they're scorning me
because I'm an incel member now,
that hurts my feels
and it brings out my righteous manly wrath.
So how long have you been,
you've been an incel Reverend Pease?
It's, it's what, 10 o'clock now?
I've been doing it for about 45 minutes.
It seems like a nice bunch of guys on some levels.
How do you feel?
Do you have like superpowers yet or something?
I don't know what happens when you don't drain your throat
for more than 45 minutes.
I learned that women have been suppressing me
and that they are not capable of rational thought.
So I didn't know that before.
So that's good to know.
It's funny.
The internet's a wonderful thing
because you learn all these things that you didn't know.
Like I thought women were just awesome and squishy
and, you know, good to talk to and share your times with.
But no, that is all fallacy put out by the feminists
that keeps me from realizing my true incel potential
of being scorned by women
and then incredibly angry about it.
Reverend Pease,
I don't know.
I know that inside of you,
there is a man who is not getting any whatsoever
that's just screaming and crying and crawling to get out.
I know he's in there.
Is he?
Don't rip off my own bit to me.
I want to.
Reverend Pease, you have to do that to other people.
It's always great when we get to hear it come back.
And that's all this hard work that we've put in,
our writing, our jokes.
And that's what this show is all about.
It's time for the show.
And Dr. Fox and I are broadcasting out of the Hypercube Laboratories
in the former Spanish Empire.
Reverend Pease over there is broadcasting out of Salt Lake, Nevada, Utah.
That's an actual place on the planet.
On freethinkradio.com.
And that's what you're listening to this on.
See, Pease is so good.
He's just so damn good at radio.
It's hard to be on the same show with him.
He's kind of...
Kind of intimidating.
I don't know.
I'm seeing here, I'm reading in our awesome chat
that first off, this week's episode doesn't sound like total ass.
Nice.
Also, Reverend Snappy Twig wanted to hire Pease
to do the promos for his show.
I would love to do that.
He wouldn't even have to hire me.
I would do it for free.
Yeah, he's great.
Well, he wants to know your address, Pease.
6428 Dobie Peak Drive, Las Vegas, Nevada, 89108.
That's folks at home for the listening viewers at home.
This sound...
Pease.
That's the sound usually that you don't hear of me
lowering my head into my own hands.
But it's not out of shame or pity.
It's just sheer excitement, ladies and gentlemen.
Dear friends.
Pease is my only friend.
He's beautiful, handsome.
He's...
He's diligent.
Incel.
He's courteous.
He's...
And now he's an involuntary celibate.
I'm really glad that you...
It was involuntary.
I thought he was voluntary.
I thought that was the whole point.
Or is he being withheld?
Explain the incel concept again.
I didn't...
Argus brings up a good question.
For me, the viewer out of the room.
Yeah, yeah.
The viewers are...
I'm not really sure what the rules are
because the carrots cuts me off.
That's involuntary because I would still like to get some.
And...
And then, of course...
What would you like to get?
A personality?
A sense of humor?
A better job?
All?
But some of those guys said me being married
and having two kids
excludes me from being a member altogether.
And I don't think that that's right.
That's racist!
Yeah, man.
Right?
I don't stand for that.
You gotta...
You gotta let just...
Let peas be peas.
Oh, there we go.
This is this...
Yeah, that's why my mic sounded like garbage.
It was this cable.
I figured Danny Shagoff...
That we got rid of this cable.
Can explain it all to me.
Yeah.
Are we...
Are we doing the callbacks?
Is this the callback episode already?
Just call the suicide hotline
and ask the operator to patch you into Danny Shagoff.
I'm sorry.
His cardboard box isn't connected right now.
Oh!
Do you have a track phone you'd like to try?
Talking shit on time for the show.
Last week's show...
I thought Legume was, like, super well-behaved.
Yeah, peas has kids, Twig.
Peas has kids.
I've met...
I've met at least one.
Oh, that's what it is.
Mmm.
Oh, okay.
Now I get it.
Yeah, I did that.
Sorry.
All right.
It's live radio.
I bumped a thing...
How would I know?
...and now Dr. Fox has to go, oh, and, like, and make point signals to a thing that you
guys can't see.
Here, can you read?
Here, I'm gonna...
I've just installed this new 80 LED matrix scrolling marquee.
Fit, if you'll look right above your monitor there, do you see it up on the wall?
It should be scrolling through right now.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Is it fit?
There we go.
I was wondering what that was.
Just keep your eyes on that for me.
Okay.
Oh, wait.
That's just...
I'm sorry.
That was just my stock options.
As you can tell, it's a...
Simon didn't tell me not to stop looking yet.
Yeah, I mean, it's livestock options, because I've invested in bullshit.
Who the hell is Simon?
Why do we gotta do what Simon says?
Who made him the boss of everybody?
Why do you have to go against the humble world of Simon?
Do you...
Because I...
I'm not...
I'm not all about doing what Simon says.
I mean, you know, why can't you mix it up?
Sometimes Andrew says.
Sometimes Fox says.
Sometimes...
Now we're getting somewhere.
Yeah, if we could get further into...
Yeah, let's all do what Fox says.
Correct.
It'd be a better show.
It'd be a better world.
It might be.
The way that the Fox says game...
It couldn't be worse.
...would go would be everybody just does the opposite.
When you say Fox says sit down, everybody stands up.
It still could work in my favor eventually.
No, it does work in your favor.
It does work in your favor because all the people that sit down...
Everybody stop listening to the show.
Yeah.
And see, now they're continuing to listen.
What are you doing?
Yeah, they're listening.
They're just listening just to piss us off.
That's the only reason they're listening is to make us mad and it's working.
I've been struggling with smoking cigarettes again, you know, and...
I find it pretty easy.
I just put it in my mouth right in your mouth.
And I found out this weird kind of thing.
I do good all day till I come home and I'm around.
I'm like, I'm gonna go buy us some cigarettes.
I don't know what that means.
Yeah, Fit buys me cigarettes.
Fit doesn't buy him or us cigarettes.
He buys me cigarettes.
And then I sneak some of the cigarettes.
I'll buy you a pack.
He buys me a pack.
And then I'll sneak some out.
Yeah.
I'll even like rearrange the cigarettes.
Cosmic has posted a picture of my house.
That actually was...
Shit.
You're not supposed to acknowledge it, Pete.
Right there in my lead.
That is actually my front yard.
That is my front yard.
64, 28, 70, 50.
I love your grass.
You've done so much work with it.
That new hypoallergenic St. Augustine, right?
Well, my truck's not there because obviously I'm out adventuring in the desert when this picture was taken.
You left one of your truck nuts in the driveway.
What we're all looking at, viewers, is Doc Cosmic, his holiness.
He posted a picture of Pease's actual house.
Because, you know, Pease likes to give his address out because he wants to get that popcorn in the mail.
So Cosmic just gave him a cold shock running all the way up what's left of Pease's spine by posting a photo of Pease's house right in the live chat.
If you want to get in the live chat, Doc Cosmic...
How could somebody get in the live chat?
How do they do that?
What if they want to get in it right now?
How do they do it?
If you, the viewer, want to become a part of the live chat...
You can join Dr. Fox.
Discord.hypercube.
Just go to timeforthewebsite.com.
Click Discord.
There's a link right there, right?
I'll check.
Just go to miriamwebster.com.
That's an online dictionary.
Look up Discord.
And then follow the link.
There's you.
There's the show.
Discord.hypercube.
Is that a time?
Is that actually going out?
See, we've developed.
We've found a problem.
Time warp right now.
It was time for the time warp.
But now it's time for our first song of the evening.
Nice.
I've thrown two vinyl records onto the floor here.
Why don't you pick up the one on the left or the one on the right?
Throw it on the spindle.
Oh, is this like a game show?
Yeah.
I have to pick the song on the left or the song on the right.
Oh, all right.
Oh, I'm going to have to go to the audience for this one.
What do you say, audience?
I'm looking.
Yeah, the first one.
If you hear the one on the right.
Oh, no.
They're saying not the one on the left.
Well, all right.
Well, we're going to go to the audience.
We're going to go with the one on the right.
Since Dr. Fox, this is a track that you yourself picked out.
It's Alopecia by Ego Plum.
And it's time for the show on Freethink Radio.
We'll be right back.
Nice.
line.
One, two, three.
Here we go.
Thank you.
or maybe I want to make a little flag for when I'm assaulting the desert.
Where could I go to get that kind of merchandise?
Where can you get that kind of merchandise?
This is the show now.
Right now, nowhere, because we've actually sold out of Dr. Fox and the Right Angles t-shirts and patches.
Well, I'm glad I got mine then.
We have completely sold out as of the last show.
Are there still stickers?
So, yes, we do have new designs coming.
Nude designs.
We have nude designs coming and going.
Mostly coming.
And with that, you'll be able to get new shirts, including shirts that we'll reveal next week for season two of time for the show.
We should know that we've already tested the t-shirts.
We've already tested the t-shirts on several dozen babies, and only one of them died.
So they're pretty much baby safe.
Oh, they come in extra, extra, extra, extra.
It's better than one out of ten.
Less than one out of ten.
Yes, definitely less than one out of ten.
That's better than Dentine Gum.
0.78 out of ten babies did not make it through trials.
Well, that's the same record Dentine Gum has.
That baby was an asshole, though.
And if Dentine Gum is safe, then, of course, these patches have to be.
Nobody likes that baby.
Just between me and you.
Whisper into the microphone.
That makes good radio.
Whisper.
Good radio.
I don't know.
I just live here.
If you could hear me whisper into the microphone right now, text YES to 460-597-9802.
No, what you need to do is if you can hear us, you need to send us a text at 321-765-5107.
Fox, F-A-U-X.
Don't be fooled by the message.
I got fooled by the message, kid.
No, we changed the message, peas.
We changed the message.
But you can leave us a voicemail at that number, or you can text us if you don't have access to Discord.
And I'll be sure to get Discord links back up on the website.
Did you check the thing to see if we got any new important messages this week?
Should I check?
Let me think here.
Yeah, that's coming up later on in the show, so definitely stay tuned for that.
That's what you call it.
Tease, peas.
I want to change your name to Reverend Tease.
Oh, look at you.
I'm going to change your name, Reverend Tease, because that's what you mean.
Don't you sexualize me.
Try to stop me.
Try to stop me, peas.
I love you.
You're handsome.
You're precious.
What's the adventures you guys got coming up?
You got a new Right Angle show coming up?
Man, I've had quite enough adventures for the last...
I could...
You know what happened.
I didn't tell you what happened, peas.
You didn't?
Tell me now.
I already mentioned that our band played Dr. Fox and the Right Angles.
I'm not Dr. Fox.
I'm just a Right Angle.
But, yeah, we played a show on Friday or Saturday.
I can't remember which one it was, because where we played, you know, we were at one
of those places where the bar likes to...
You know, not stay open after closing time, because you can't do that.
That's against the law.
That would not be allowed.
No, no, no, no, no.
And if anybody did that, we would promptly report them to Dick Tracy himself.
But...
So what do you guys do?
You get a big Magic the Gathering game going when the bar closes?
Well, what happened was you just...
It turns out that after closing time, if the owner of the place just stacks a bunch of
chairs in front of the door and leaves, you're not allowed to do that.
He locks it.
You know?
That, uh...
Then you can run a bottle service.
Uh...
Yeah.
Oh, oh, I'm getting the...
Anyway, what happened was we stayed...
Dr. Fox is censoring me live on the air.
You're not reading the marquee.
If you're wondering what live...
Read the marquee.
He's telling me not to say sensitive stuff, okay?
And I thought I was dancing around the sensitivities pretty well.
But no, he's...
You viewers at home can see him shaking his head.
I mean...
Okay, so here's the point piece.
Here's...
Let me just cut to the chase.
Make it.
Make it, brother!
So we were up until like five with, you know, still with drinks a-flowing and frop a-blowing
and songs a-going and it was a good old time.
And then there happened to be a lawyer from NASA.
Because as you know, here in the...
The former Spanish Empire is where the Kennedy Space Center is based.
There happened to be a female lawyer of NASA who took a liking to me and pees.
I got lost in the woods again.
I ended up going back to Mission Control and I had neglected to bring my phone with me
to the gig in the first place.
So when I went back to Mission Control...
You told me not to talk about that ever.
You said that...
I had no way to get back in touch with Dr. Fox and let him know that I was okay.
So he had no idea.
And I had no idea where I was.
I had no idea where I was because she had no idea how to get back to her house from the place.
So we took this zig-zag-oey, uh, zig-zag-oey, wing-a-wanda-oey path back to her house.
So I didn't know where I was.
They might as well put a goddamn bag over my head.
Right?
So a drunken lawyer from NASA...
Yes.
...takes you on a...
...takes you on a nefarious trip to her lair...
Oh, yes!
...where she then manhandles you and leaves your friends to wonder if you're alive or dead.
Yeah.
And let me tell you...
Let me tell you something.
This...
This NASA lawyer...
And when she said that to us in the car...
Did she have space moves?
Did she have space moves, dude?
Oh!
Well, yeah, gravity is not always a law.
Put it that way.
Okay.
But, uh...
She...
We...
When, uh...
When she said she was a lawyer for NASA in the car, I was like, uh...
I knew she was crazy.
Sure, yeah.
Because she is...
Believe it or not, she is nine and a half buckets of crazy.
So when she said she was a lawyer for NASA, I was like, oh, yeah, sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Are you an indigo child, too?
What else is going on?
Get back to her house.
Did she hear about the peas?
Turns out...
Did she know about the peas?
Everybody knows about peas, man.
Okay, it's a given.
It's a stupid question.
I'm sorry.
That you were her second favorite host of Time for the Show.
Do you know who her first favorite host was?
Artist Q Fox, obviously.
Nope, you too.
You are her number one and number two favorites out of the three of us.
So that just goes to show how much she liked you.
She had the crazy talk, but did she have those really good crazy eyes that you go, oh...
When you see those crazy eyes, you're like, I'm in for a good time.
This is going to be a good ride.
Uh...
Well, it...
Her...
Her craziness...
Her craziness was superficially evident.
Uh...
You know, you...
Spend two seconds with her.
Could she be listening to the show right now?
I don't care, really.
Um...
You don't.
Well...
I don't...
There'll be no follow-up.
We're getting lost in the woods.
We're getting lost in the woods right now.
Well, actually, you're right, P.
She is...
She is a lawyer.
So, maybe I shouldn't say too much.
But, um...
No, but...
Too late now.
After she went to sleep, I...
I looked at her bookcase.
And she had all kinds of law books.
And stuff about something called tort.
And, uh...
Yeah, I know that.
You get on all fours and shake your butt in the air.
That's...
Believe me, uh...
How'd you get out of her lair?
I mean, did you wake her up?
Hey, I need to go home.
Argus is worried about me.
Dude...
Or did she just walk out the door?
Well, here's the deal.
Here's the deal, P.
Let me explain.
I...
I don't know the city that I'm in.
I don't know...
It's Florida.
I don't know where she lives.
And I have...
And I don't have...
I have my phone on me.
And so that means I don't have any phone numbers.
And more likely you don't have shoes either.
You've just got your hat.
I didn't have shoes.
I did have a lab coat.
That's right, Dr. Fyfe.
I had a lab coat and my hat.
And my, uh...
My sacred, uh...
Necklace with my drum key on it to...
To ward off any evils.
Sacred drum key.
Um...
Any...
Any evil, um...
Deaf leopards.
The next day...
And...
And believe me...
What...
What I'm about to say about her is gonna make her sound cool.
You're gonna be like,
Damn, Fid.
How come you're not, like,
Like, trying to get with that?
But believe me.
She's like,
Eleven...
Eleven point seven five buckets of crazy
Is what we're talking about here.
The next day...
All we did...
We...
We played a lot of video games.
First of all,
We woke up.
And, um...
For breakfast...
Fid truly woke up.
That's a first.
Mark your calendars, everybody.
I woke up at nine in the morning.
And guess what was for breakfast?
On a Sunday.
Guess what she made for breakfast?
Guess what the lawyer who works for NASA
Made for breakfast?
For breakfast.
It was vodka and oxtail.
Yes.
That is delicious, dude.
Did you just cook the oxtail in the vodka?
Or you just drink the oxtail?
The oxtail was in the form of, uh...
Meat.
In a big bowl of, uh...
Like, spiced rice.
And she used way too much spice.
She said it was some kind of African dish.
Fucked it up.
But she did serve it with vodka
Mixed with, like, a lemon soda or something.
And, uh...
At nine in the morning, it's exquisite.
Oxtail and vodka.
This is my...
This has been...
Was it still a leathery oxtail?
Or was it, like, pieces?
Or did you have, like...
Because when I...
The last time I encountered oxtail soup,
There's quite literally an oxtail
With the brush tip of the tail on it
Floating in the soup.
Oh, then it wasn't prepared correctly.
That was homestyle where I was getting it at.
What do you know about oxtail?
Well, stop saying soup.
I made oxtails.
In Las Vegas, you have to take two with you.
I made oxtails last week.
How did you make it, Pease?
I used my Instant Pot.
I made a wine sauce.
And I braised them real quick.
And then I pressure cooked them for,
I want to say, like, an hour.
And then I served that over some noodles
With the carrot and potato slices
That I cooked it in.
It's super good.
Okay, so...
You can actually eat it, right?
I didn't, like...
I didn't, like, do anything to myself, right?
So listen.
So you got the oxtails in you.
You got the vodka in you.
Did you go back for a second?
Did you go back for a second helping
Of the squishy goodness?
Is that the best euphemism you can come up with?
Did you get one helping of squishy goodness?
I didn't even hear that.
I heard that it was...
That I dropped him off.
And then...
Or I saw...
I saw the last of Big Chili
That I would see.
There's no drop off.
We should back up.
Yeah.
Fox dropped us off.
And then she...
She told me to tell you
That you can go.
So the next thing he knows
I open the door and just say
You can go now, Dr. Fox.
You can go, Dr. Fox.
We no longer need you.
Well, at first she was worried.
She was like, I don't know who...
Because we're talking about me here.
I don't know which bald white guy
With a beard is the real one.
The guy with the...
The guy with the keys.
Yeah.
And the phone.
So I was stranded the next day
Is the bottom line.
But it's okay.
I'm concerned about your take on this.
Were you worried about your little buddy?
My little buddy.
I was lost in the woods.
Of course he was.
Yeah, after a while
It started getting a little worrisome.
You know, everybody knows
That I have a penchant
For making sure that people are okay.
Where's Fid?
And where's Fid?
My favorite...
My favorite game.
Which I'm playing.
But I didn't really play Where's Fid?
As much as I did just sleep all day.
And then I went over to my parents' house.
And they were expecting Fid to come over with me.
And they're like, hey, where's Fid?
And I go, I don't know.
Had he contacted them to let him know he was okay?
With what?
I didn't have my phone, man.
I was lost in the woods just like X-Day.
This mad, crazy NASA lawyer
Who served you oxtails and vodka
Had no phone for you to contact your friends
To let him know, hey...
Because she had my number programmed in her phone?
It's...
Well, I guess that's true.
Fid would not know your number off the top of his head.
Who knows numbers anymore?
I write mine on the wall next to the phone.
I know most of the numbers.
I don't know how many there are.
But I know, like...
Seven.
I don't know that one.
That's a new one on me.
So, anyway, you didn't answer my question.
Did you go back for squishy goodness seconds?
We got shit-faced starting at nine in the morning.
And, uh...
But that was after a night of intense lovemaking
where she saw God being enthralled with Fid Julie's manliness,
I would imagine.
Well, I was saving myself...
You were imagining it, Pease.
I was saving myself for you, Pease.
I said, no, I'm taken.
And you can sue me all you want.
And I know you can fly a space shuttle.
What did you do to get out of that situation?
Did you feign fatigue?
Did you sleep?
Did you pretend like you fell asleep?
But you were really sitting there hoping that you wouldn't be touched again?
How did this play out?
You really want to know?
I mean, obviously you went there.
She took you to her lair with the intention...
of having her way with you, I would think.
I wouldn't think her in-game would be vodka, oxtails, and video games.
That, you know, that doesn't seem normal.
Well, Guru Drew in the chat said this show's getting kind of gay.
Because I think Reverend Pease...
Having sex with women is gay.
You're trying a little too hard to live vicariously through me, Pease.
It's not good radio.
And that's gay.
All right, well, I'm sorry that we can't get more in-depth into Fids.
Adventure.
But it sounds like it was delightful.
Long story short, she's fucking nuts.
And if you didn't think...
If you, viewer, didn't think...
Fid Chuli has declared...
But listen...
He has a law.
Argus.
It's a law.
Fid has not really described one crazy thing.
He just says a couple of things and then says,
And she's 11 bags nuts.
What?
What has to happen for somebody like Fid Chuli to go,
That person is too crazy.
Crazy for me.
Because we all know Fid Chuli's level of craziness.
Okay.
And awesomeness.
So what does it take?
I'll tell you what, Pease.
We'll find out what it takes to tip over Fid Chuli's nine and a half buckets of crazy.
She's a lawyer.
I'm not going to say it on the show.
She's a goddamn lawyer.
So I'll tell you off the show.
But in the meantime, for the viewers, we're going to play Unsquared Dance from the new Brubrek Quartet.
Did I say Brubrek?
Brubrek.
I meant Bruback.
Bruback.
It's time for the show on Freethink Radio.
We'll be right back after Bruback.
We'll be right back.
Thank you.
by the New Brubeck Quartet.
Those of you who are familiar with Dave Brubeck,
the pianist, yes, I said pianist,
not that other thing that your dirty mind thought I said.
Yeah, the New Brubeck Quartet.
I think it was like some of his brothers were in it or something.
But yeah, that was Unsquared Dance from 1978.
Speaking of brothers, one of the Neville brothers died this week.
Who?
One of the Neville brothers, famous.
Yeah, I'm familiar with that.
One of the Neville brothers died this week.
Which one?
The good one or the trouble maker?
The sax player.
Sax player.
If he's not everything is about sax, man.
I know that tonight is our Loveline edition episode of the show.
We're discussing all of the important matters of the heart.
Yeah, Pease, thanks.
So, Pease, did you want to continue grilling?
Thanks for getting me sued.
Yeah, I just got a letter in the mail just now.
It was a cease and desist order and a subpoena and a contract for my soul.
All three of those things came from NASA just now.
Here's my thoughts, dude.
The lady says that she's a lawyer for NASA and then you go off and have this odyssey.
Come on, are we still going on about this?
And the thing about it is, is we don't even know.
And you don't even know.
She's probably not even a lawyer.
She probably didn't even work for NASA.
She's probably, you know, some clerk at Kmart and you're all coward and stuff.
I still want to know what it takes.
What amount of craziness does it take for Fid Chula to go to tap out?
Well, this chick was definitely a blue light special.
I'm tapped out.
Yeah, Fox will tell you.
He talked to her.
Go ahead.
Tell Pease all about how crazy she was while I pissed.
First, she met me.
And that's why I introduced her to Fid.
I said, yeah, you're nice.
Here, come meet this guy.
He's a drummer.
Yeah.
And not mine.
Just a drummer.
Have a blast.
And I'll tell you, the number one thing that she told Fid last night was, you talk too much.
The second thing she told him the most was, shut up.
Nice.
So, there'll be no second date?
I figured.
I figured there was.
Apparently, he was invited out for shots and Pokemon Go.
But I really think he just wanted to Pokemon Go the fuck home.
Yes, I did.
And I want to Pokemon get the fuck off of this topic, too.
Dude, you totally denied Pokemon at all.
You jumped from this crazy car ride to drinking vodka in the morning.
And I know there was deets in between that.
And I didn't even know that there might not have been a second Pokemon session because you missed the great soiree.
Anyways, the text is just the same as you posted it.
There is no date.
So many
blind eyes.
We gotta move on.
We can't just talk about this the whole show.
So we gotta move on to the blind eyes.
Absolutely think we could talk about this for the whole show.
Really?
Because,
you know,
you ever think,
Pease,
maybe there's a reason why I'm not getting into certain details
live on Canadian radio?
I share everything with my life on the radio.
We know.
Always leave them wanting more,
Pease.
You know,
I can't give the whole story.
Yeah, save it for the trial, please.
Save it for the trial.
I don't want you guys to be able to testify against me, man.
Pease,
she was super clingy.
She wanted me to basically, like,
move in with her,
like,
then.
Like, after, like, that.
Like, one night.
Okay?
She was fucking crazy.
I was super bummed because she was working up to me
and I realized I still had my wedding ring on.
Alright, blind eyes.
That's why I had to get Pease.
Blind eyes.
I gotta get Pease.
Or, no, I gotta get Fid.
Get Fid in the car.
That way I can't screw up.
I'll just pass off.
You know, some people, you know,
hey, Fid, at least, you know,
some people throw you their sloppy seconds,
but at least I can throw you my fanatical firsts.
They're all yours, buddy.
Dr. Fox is a married man.
I sure the heck am.
And we're in a band together
and he's the front man.
So, I get all of his,
his fanatical firsts.
I don't even get the,
I get the sloppy firsts
and the sloppy seconds.
You know, I don't want to go to,
you know, some of us, you know,
want to be in a band, you know,
to meet girls.
And I go, yeah, in the Dr. Fox show.
I can only imagine what you're going to do.
I don't know.
I could probably meet girls.
Apparently, these are the kind of girls you meet.
Well, my bass player's been happy.
He's been getting some,
some fanatical firsts.
He's a bass player.
Actually, they bypassed me.
They love him, the,
the Latino bass machine.
Yeah.
Any bass player that's getting action,
he's happy.
It's a good,
he's a good bass player.
I don't think we'd find a better one.
He's a great bass player.
And as a drummer,
nothing gets my stick harder.
So, please don't throw him
any of those girls.
We'll never see him again.
Van Halen didn't pay their bass player
for 25 years
because they just gave him
his fanatical firsts.
Well, dude,
this is the great thing, right?
We're in the band.
It's a four piece.
Dr. Fox is married.
The guitarist is married.
The bassist is in a relationship.
Relationship.
Fit.
Truly.
You know what that means?
All right,
but we really do have to move on.
It's a live show, man.
We got to,
we got to get to the blind eyes.
You didn't want to talk about
Should we even do that
because we're coming up
to the top of the hour.
Maybe we should just tease
the blind eyes now.
Come back to blind eyes
in the top of the hour.
I know Reverend Couch Sloth
is going to be coming on the show
or he said that he might be.
Are you going to blind eye
that lawyer from NASA?
Well,
I don't know.
I guess you're just going to
have to wait and listen.
Right, Bees?
Damn, I won't be able to wait.
What song are we going to listen to?
You're my handsome.
We're not going to a song quite yet.
What we are going to do
is say that we,
Reverend Couch Sloth
may join us
for the second hour of the show.
I believe he actually,
no, no, I think he's there.
I think he's there.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Snappy Twig had to take off.
No, Couch Sloth, yeah.
But yeah.
He is a,
not only is he a Patreon supporter
of the show,
he's also a pretty funny dude
who's been doing
and I guess this counts
as his shout out
that he earned.
Did he get his autographed
picture of Muhammad yet?
Well, he's not quite on that level.
He's not donating
at the $9.11 level.
Okay, I'll hold back a little bit.
Oh, there he is.
He's listening to us right now.
But who are,
who are giving
at the $9.11 level?
Well, geez Louise,
I guess there's a,
Jesus, Jesus Christ,
our Lord and Savior
is giving us that level.
There's Reverend Caller 23
Oh.
Oh yeah.
Turn down your radio.
If you're listening,
Reverend Caller,
please turn down your radio.
He is a Patreon
at the $9.11 potassium level.
We also have
the great,
everybody loves
Apostasy X Finord.
Except for Pease.
She's my pal.
Pease doesn't care for her.
And an honorary member.
No, she's my pal.
No, it's okay, Pease.
I already said that you don't like her.
We gave Drew
a complimentary potassium
level membership
for his
one time $100 gift
to the show.
So he's still getting a picture,
a self-portrait
of the Prophet Muhammad.
Is he?
And he's basically
getting two months free.
But you know,
we'll cut that deal
for anybody.
If you want to send us
$100 today,
we will save
$18.22
off of your subscription fees
for the year.
We'll give you
complimentary
potassium level
donation.
Donorship.
And Guru Drew,
I should mention,
is like sort of
a producer,
although he said
he's not,
but he really
kind of is
a producer
of a band
called
The Brand Flakes.
Right.
We played them last week.
They were awesome.
I've been playing
the hell out of them
because Guru Drew,
oh, it's the one
about the wondering
and the grandmother.
Sorry, I'm talking
to Dr. Fox
live on the radio.
Yeah, he's giving
the engineer
the opportunity
to do.
Yeah, it's live radio.
Are you even allowed
to do that?
What makes radio good
is when the person
talks to somebody
that isn't on the radio
and that the viewers
don't know what
they're talking about.
Another thing that people
that makes good radio
is inside jokes.
We've got plenty of those.
And Dr. Fox,
you hadn't even seen
the little hub
that Guru Drew made.
Guru Drew
collected sort of like
all the Freethink radio
and all the subgenius.
radio shows
and made a little hub
on his website.
Does it even have
does it have a laboratory
as well?
Does it have share a slice
Tuesdays at 10
and then anti-social engineering
Thursdays at 10?
Yeah.
And I think we've
are there more shows
on Freethink radio
right now?
He has both of those
Freethink radio.
Actually, Guru Drew himself
is about to start
a show right here
on Freethink radio.
It's going to be
a morning show
and it's going to be
a music mix
of his
Yeah.
of his picks.
But I can tell you
that his fingers
have been in some
stinky places.
Am I on that show?
I, uh,
yeah, Pease,
you're on every show.
Okay.
Drew's in the chat
right now telling us
he's not ready yet
but it's coming.
It's not ready yet
but it's coming
but, uh,
That's what I tell Carrots.
So is season two
of Time for the Show.
Next week
we've got
an all new style
of format
and a whole new
collection of songs
and material
and we've got
What?
Yeah.
We're going into
quarter two.
What?
And we're going to
start season two
of Time for the Show
Did we send a memo out?
Was there like
an email I missed?
I don't know.
What's your email address, Pease?
Isn't it time
for the email
at gmail.com?
Dot com.
I thought we talked
about this last week.
I don't know.
We were so
because we were
captivated by
I sit here
and I watch
the lights blinking
and when the lights go off
and the lights blink
I know that I'm not
doing my job well enough.
And surprise!
They don't stop blinking.
You work harder
than anybody else
on the show
and I think
it's important
for our listener
our listening audience
to know
that
this is
Argus makes it seem
like it's just him.
He actually has
a team of
18 interns
that are
jumping around
getting coffee
making sure
the decks of the barge
that we transmit from
off the coast of Orlando
is clean.
So hot.
There's no more coffee
in the commissary
in the morning.
There's dishes in the sink.
I don't know what to do.
It's like I've got to
start taking care
of this place again.
None of us know
what to do.
It's live radio.
All we can hope to do
is at least pretend
to be professional.
And in the spirit thereof
since it is
the top of the hour
we're going to go
to a song
and this song
is by the
aforementioned
Bran Flakes.
It's actually
three songs
because they're
pretty short.
So this
three song
Bran Flake
Marathon
is
I wonder
where my grandmother
is.
Let's just do
two songs
and then charge
for the third song.
Okay.
Everybody right now
please put a quarter
into whatever
you're listening
to the show on.
Right.
Whether it's your iPhone
or a laptop
or your laptop.
Yeah.
Take a picture
of a quarter.
Yeah.
Take a picture of a quarter
going into your iPhone.
Yes.
Take a picture of a quarter.
Or into your CD player.
Print that picture out.
Then take that picture
fold it up
four times.
Put it in your CD drive
of your computer.
Close the CD drive
and type into a DOS prompt
format C colon.
That will send
your quarter to us.
Hold down the turbo button
while you do it.
Absolutely.
When we get done playing
when we come back
from the song
we're going to revisit
Fitch's
Adventures
with the NASA lawyer
and then maybe
we'll do some blind eyes.
I feel like
Pease is going to get
a phone call
during this song.
Not only are we going
to do some blind eyes
after we come back
from this
Bran Flakes
moron-a-thon
but I believe
Reverend Couch Sloth
is going to join us.
Hour two already?
He was telling me
he had some questions
about the whole
NASA lawyer thing.
All those and more
when we come back
it's a little bit
11 o'clock
it's Freethink Radio
and you're listening
to Time for the Show.
This is the Bran Flakes.
Catfish Joe.
Tell them it's the show, Pease.
It's time for the show
but now it's time for the song.
Come on.
I wonder where my grandmother is.
I was in the loogie.
This is ridiculous.
They're dead.
You have to give me
a time change.
No, one second.
Oh, boughta,
they're bombarded
I'm scared.
when I'm feeling
better,
who knows,
this will be
And I believe
that I need
another end attachment
patrols are slow
because I know
just tute
Do you want salad with your tequila?
Sure.
Diarrhea?
Okay, you can move on now.
That's Salvation and Infotation at www.subgenius.com.
Or, got that pencil ready?
P.O. Box 807, Glen Rose, Texas, 76043.