ðŸŽµ
Excuse me.
Yes, well now, had you been alive at 3am on the 3rd of autumn and switched on your wireless, you would have heard this.
It wasn't much of a program, was it?
If you had tuned in at 9 o'clock, you would have heard...
The Subgenius Hour of Swag.
Excuse me.
I don't like what he's doing, Pat, I don't like it.
We ought to have a meeting about it.
Once that record of sheep is being played, here are the remains of a goonshow washed up on a brighton beach near Croydon.
Yes, yes, yes.
And in faded writing, we see that the title is...
Part 1.
Cartridge Landho judgy in."
Age Oition.
8 years old.
Age Oition Mutt.
Age Oition Q Paid.
MAN 1 Nine dataset, Age Oition Mutt.
Age Oèƒ
Age Oition Mutt UK formulatedays gauge is 4.
Age Oition Mutt.
Age Oitionáº¯c
Member Dr Pod mentions the role of Eros.
Age Oican was on his final flight.
Age Oican fault.
Age Oican Inter paljon lebt.
down the pike and you'd best be ready to swim in it.
Now, tonight's hour of slack, number 215, is going to be a real good old-fashioned black-eyed
pea-eating, Bible-thumping, hoo-ah-down in celebration of Bob's eardrums as well as the
New Year.
In fact, it's not really even New Year's in Texas right now as I say this, but as you
listen now.
Now, it isn't the New Year right now, not unless you're listening in Texas where it's
New Year's Eve.
In fact, it's always New Year's Eve for everybody except me since I'm not actually in the studio
tonight.
I'm at home pre-editing this show yesterday because I don't want to go into work on New
Year's Eve.
I want to party and I suggest you do too.
And with that in mind, for that matter, we don't even know who you are.
So instead of preaching the words, the words of Bob tonight, we're just going to play
music.
But not just any music, nay, but the music of noise and sound effects and like driving
head-on into a plate glass window at 90 miles an hour with Doctors for Bob turned up all
the way.
And you're broke, Fran.
Brand car stereo.
Okay.
Oh, just some party sound.
It's, Bob will be in there because Bob will be the pleasure and the pain that your eardrums
feel.
It's what you might call Dob's house music.
And unless you're listening in your car, I suggest that if you possibly can, listen to
this show.
This is a subgenius radio ministry that is designed strictly for the pleasure of starting
from the outer ear in to where the nerve centers for both ears meet a small pocket of flesh
brain tissue, which will in fact, if you use the headphones or listen on good stereo separated
speakers, shall be able to hear you.
Be ripped in pain by the music.
Because what's coming up is an ear raping tidal surge of slack full noise music.
And Dob's league chaos.
And you need the headphones for protection in case the sound waves splash too hard against
the inner ear.
Okay.
It's a tape edited show.
There's no one in the studio and you can't call us.
And we don't even care about your prayers.
We're not taking them because we're out partying.
But do not worry if the show appears to make no sense or to make no mention of Bob because
if it did make sense, it would not be of Bob.
Indeed, though this is not very explanatory hour of slack, I do think that it will nevertheless
be.
In fact, it's the first time in my life that he has become one of the most cherished by
our group and my e-pop JR Bob Dobs himself.
The logrin and push in andë‹ˆ and Bob and the sake exciting to enjoy Ã€ large and
OK, then's the first time in about ten years and two przez well.
So there he is.
And skaloy the dirt in vardı ág 중is of Bayerol.
KILLER THAN GOD
Bop
Bop bop
Bop bop bop bop bop bop bop bop bop
KILLER THAN JESUS
I've been executed at once.
Yes sir.
Come along.
This sort of behaviour is demoralising for the ordinary soldiers and citizens who are trying to lead normal, simple, unexceptional lives.
Nothing's difficult enough as it is without these emotional people walking the boat.
Bop
I'm afraid, sir, you have rather a weak grasp of a reality.
Your reality, sir, is lies and balderdash, and I'm delighted to say that I have no grasp of it whatsoever!
The
I don't believe you're listening.
Good in Jesus.
They're just manipulating bigger.
Hey!
No one, I.
Hold it right here.
I didn't say can you,
Can you,
But there be,
I'm manipulating your eyes all the time.
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
Hey, Missy.
Come on. Come on, baby.
Come on, baby. You can do it.
Isn't that nice?
I'm the one who takes the fall.
The ACDC doll.
To the Jesus.
You got that right.
I don't believe you listen.
Alright, now look at me.
I said look at me, don't turn your face away.
I'm the looking glass you're feeling to see yourself in.
I'm the looking glass.
websites.cosme.blogspot.com
I'm looking glass.
Thank you to our sponsor in walk front beauty from the last video.
Thank you to Joanna Beck from Numbers Duomo.
Thank you to today's sponsor.
I was raised to be someone
All right, all right, everything!
Can you take a name of your senses?
Don't look at me..
Somebody's lying and it's not me
Twisting my words
That was
My life with the thrill kill cult
Hurry, but hurry, but hurry, but hurry
Â© BF-WATCH TV 2021
Then go insane.
And eventually...
You're tired.
You're beaten down.
You're irritable.
Your mental and physical health are suffering.
Is there any escape?
And that was Negative Land. Thank you.
We must feel the inner agony.
We must be Peaceful.
We must think aboveining.
We must live a wise life.
Lord.
Don't be afraid.
The God of Death saith IT.
CHOIR SINGS
Hmm, still my shadow but no people here that I know.
Sporadic
Very sporadic
Yes
Yeah
Wee-wee-weee
Oh my way
Wee-wee-wee, we're on our way.
We're on our way.
Last time, they thought we'd leave.
I amék.
Thank you.
That was TGT.
Your floor, sir.
Thank you.
Good night.
The men of goodwill must join together.
Men of all races and creeds and color and political persuasion.
And we hope you'll sing along, too.
We hope you'll sing along, too.
Remember, this is the kind of music that you can create on your own.
Strings are on track one.
The melody is on track two.
Synthesizer bass on track three.
And rhythm is on track four.
Men of goodwill.
Men of goodwill must join together.
.
Finally, let's see what we can do with a rich, vibrant synthesizer sound.
Greater than one.
Here's one.
One.
And one.
Here's one.
Greater than one.
Oh, you won't want to miss this, Arnie.
It reminds me of my school days in England.
You know, I don't want to miss this.
I'm a modern man, these days I find.
You have to be awfully cruel to be kind.
I'm a modern man, you will agree.
It's either you or me.
Well, time's nearly up, I think.
I think.
Okay.
Not late, am I?
Fire!
Ladies, I shall require your assistance.
Of course.
Anything.
Tell us what to do.
Kindly.
Maybe so good as to remove your knickers.
That's a good day, sir.
Amaya!
Yoo-hoo!
Love a boy!
Isinahina!
This way.
Mama!
Hmm.
Come!
Come to me now!
Hubba hubba hubba!
A lot of meat, not a one-sail!
Ah! I've been missed!
Ha ha ha!
Remember me, Eddie?
When I killed your mother, I talked just like Bob!
OK, I know!
Uh huh
The
What did you say?
Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang...
Bang!
Well, there you are, taking you over with a good bang now and then.
Once upon a time there was a little girl called Little Red Riding Hood.
She lived in a small village on the edge of the forest.
She was a little, stupid goat.
And her father raped her.
And she raped her four times a week.
But she was innocent and pious.
And she loved her parents very much.
She had sun-dressed hair, eyes like olives, and a upper-body that was unimaginable.
Every Sunday she would go out with her grandmother.
She would wear
i
more
Oh, is it cold?
Oh, oh
Moon as the clouds
Oh, a Boom as a guiding
School, my master
Moon as the clouds
Uh oh
What if the place in my mind
That isn't ë  kind
Is room and sky
For those who don't fly
I don't stay away late
Whatever they say
The only thing they want to do
Is make it pay
Kristenalog
From that man on the street
aria
I'm bald
I messing
She's got to jump off the clown
Before somebody grabs her
I'm a
Thank you.
Well, I'm sure I'm forgetting something,
but what you've been listening to,
has been the soundtrack of Baron Munchausen, of course, Roger Rabbit.
And what's been tying all the little bits and pieces together
are the sound effects music of Negative Land,
specifically off of Negative Land, a Big Ten 8 Place album.
There were bits by the Gyuto Monks,
some Russian Cathedral liturgical songs,
stuff from the Plunder Phonics material from Mystery Tapes,
that was the Michael Jackson dab piece,
DK Jones, Byron Werner,
and bits from a whole lot of albums that we've been getting in from Wax Tracks Records.
Clips from the bands Pankow, La Muerte, KMFDM, Young Gods,
Mark Mothersbaugh, well, that was ours, not Wax Tracks,
Weatherman, and Mussolini Headkick.
You can!
Of course.
Get free information from the Church of the Subgenius
at Post Office Box 140306,
Dallas, Texas 75214.
Once again, dear friends, free information, just write Bob
at Box 140306,
Dallas, Texas.
And, uh...
Thank y'all.
OH MY!
subdue
nei
ehh
assembly
np
Outro Music