We interrupt this program to bring you a special news bulletin.
Concentrate.
9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1, 0.
Flight, now I'm losing all three of them.
It's just a little medical mutiny, Doc.
I'm sure the guys are still with us.
Let's cut them some slack, okay?
We interrupt this program tonight.
What would you cut us some slack?
She's lucky she had it.
Hello, toxic Bob.
How you doing?
Huh, what's that?
This behind me is Bob.
Automated dialing.
Allow to be able to...
Call Bob.
Command.
Dialing.
Mom.
No, not Mom.
Bob.
Cancel.
Stop!
Hello?
Hey, Mom.
The self-genius.
Power of swag.
Forget a blockage.
It's a job.
For Grime.
For Grime Fighter Bob.
For Grime Finn?
Yeah, sir.
For Grime Fighter Bob.
We interrupt this program
to bring you Bob.
Ah, Bob, I think that I got a little problem.
Contact the federal marshals.
Get them out here!
I want something large enough to hold it.
To hold something large.
What?
Isn't this Mayor Rogers?
Wasn't this mayor lorsque we有 він complimentaryедин會 на tendencies?
30 seconds.
25 seconds.
20 seconds.
19, 18, 17, 16, 15, 14, 13, 12, 11, 10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Dad, power surge.
Quick, the abort switch is on.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Unable to abort.
Happy holidays, Bob.
But let's imagine for the sake of argument that you don't care for what Bob has to say.
Say you've convinced yourself that slack is nothing more than an unattainable pipe dream.
Maybe you feel that this whole thing really is just some sort.
Or a stupid joke.
Perhaps you are thinking to yourself, fuck Bob.
Well, fear not, my friends.
Fucking Bob is kind of the point.
Fuck Bob.
Are these thoughts blasphemous?
Are these beliefs hearsay?
Are we out of our minds?
Are we desperate for money?
You're damn right on all counts.
And I know Bob is happy for us.
See?
He's smiling.
How can you argue with that?
What?
Turning a profit off the backs of false prophets is just one of a multitude of ways the Church of the Subgenius finds its slack.
And that's exactly what Bob wants.
Well, besides your money.
He wants us to have slack.
And by Bob, we aim to have it.
So reaffirm your faith in the Sultan of Saiyans, the instigator of yucks for the alien warbearers.
Money will flow like the explosion of wet sex over the face of the highest uberfans.
And I never will.
Trusted convenience.
Smith's
your
his
ele
i
your
vehicle. May the fire of our hatred keep us nourished through even the darkest times.
May it warm us in our coldest nights. May you find shelter amongst the ripples of Bob
Scrooge. May his shadow of occurrence pave your path at least resistance. May subdued
efforts and proverbial pie-chucking and backhanded slapstick appease the lunatic gods and their
insatiable funny-hole. Lest we once again find ourselves hung out to dry on next day,
being mercilessly mocked and heckled from beyond the stars. Praise God damn Bob.
I shall leave you with a poem. Even a man who is pink at heart and only knows false
slack may be seen as green in the pipe-light's gleam and excess cannon-flack. E-quapity-socky,
a-boppity-boopy.
Side effects include high blood pressure, profuse sweating, speaking in tongues, shortness
of breath, swelling of the genital region, exposing discharge of smell, feelings of mild
to intense ecstasy, dependency, heart attack, and lethal shouting. Please consult your doctor
to find out if the Church of the Subgenius is right for you.
That was Sermons with Suds by Reverend Frodus Suds Pasha, and you can see the video on YouTube.
The Larch did the opening. Later we'll hear recent clips from Radio Synesthesia,
from WCSB Cleveland, Puzzling Evidence from KPFA Berkeley, the Ask Dr. Howell Show podcast,
the All Zappa Show of Krell and Pope, Sternodocs and Little Rock, Rare Firesign Theater,
the Psychoskeletons, and me singing Neil Young's Southern Man. All parts of our recent cross-country
travels, on which Princess Wee and I did daily reports, such as the following, recorded at the
home of Reverend Pocket.
Well, we made it to North Carolina, and we're now putting our disease in Dr. Legume and Reverend
Pockets, and Pockets' little boy, Jack, and, oh, did Jack quit playing his doctor music?
He might come back.
Yeah, I ran to get the recorder because he was doing some...
He's playing some more music.
Here we go.
Did I say we use it?
Show him your tattoo, Jack.
Oh, my God, there's a Dobbs head on that tiny, that three-year-old child's arm.
Let me see it. Let me see it.
That's nightmarish. How could you do that?
Sing us a song, Jack.
Okay.
Oh, we're dark.
Doctors.
For Bob.
And it's just not sound.
It's not sound.
Sounds just like the Rudy Schwartz project.
Sounds great.
It's a regular John Cage.
That was good, Jack.
That was great.
Yeah.
Yay.
Thank you. Thank you.
Nice concert.
My scissors.
Oh, great. Scissors.
None of those things in there actually belong to you, Jack.
Those are...
That's a grown-up's office.
Look who's in there.
Yeah, that's for grown-ups to run with.
That's my best.
Those scissors.
Here, have a beer.
Yeah.
I'm gonna calm you down.
All righty.
I think we got another caller here on the line.
Hello.
You're on the air.
Hello?
Hello.
It's Dave.
You could tell from the hortensious buzz, which we'll...
We'll should go away with it after a...
Actually, I could tell by the piercing knife-like sound that happens whenever Dr. Sinister picks
up a new caller.
Which is what?
That's funny.
I don't find it to be that...
You were gonna call in and your way of saying, you know, I'm not gonna call in.
I mean, the way of saying hello is very Dave-like, Dave.
I don't know if you knew that.
You mean it's very particular or onerous or unique or ridiculous?
It's sort of apologetic.
Oh.
Your way of saying hello is much like your way of compulsively saying, I'm sorry.
And you're forgiven, Dave.
By whom or by what?
Dave, you need to stop apologizing.
You're forgiven by my own feet.
Yeah.
Well, that's good.
Stop apologizing.
apologizing.
You should never apologize for your greatness,
Dave. Don't apologize.
It's a sign of weakness,
mister. Apologies is a sign
of weakness. I will try to remember that.
I'm sorry. I forgot it.
But anyway,
Ray,
I noticed that you were awfully cold.
You said you were coughing chunks of dynamite?
No, my coughing is...
Coughing like a dinosaur.
You're coughing like a dinosaur.
Dinosaur. How does a dinosaur cough?
I've never heard of one of these things.
Really, really loud and forcefully.
In fact, there were...
I don't know quite how to put this
delicately on the radio, so maybe I won't.
Yeah, just say it. I'll beat it up if I have to.
These coughs were so
unexpected. They were sudden
and really violent and painful.
It kind of hurt your throat.
And then every time you swallow, it hurts.
But occasionally,
the violence of the
cough would cause a violent
crepitation
or flatulent
event.
It was so violent
that it kind of hurt down there.
And a couple of times I thought, you know,
I'm going to wake up some morning
and find out it wasn't just a
gaseous, but was what a friend of
ours, Mr. Sister, termed
a lubriff fart.
The kind that comes just
before other
messier sorts of
expulsions.
Sure enough,
one morning,
I got up and
it was like everything was kind of stuck
down there, glued
in place. I had to
peel my drawers back
in order to,
I mean, I had to really, like,
yank at my drawers to get them unstuck
because everything had kind of dropped.
The sickness
has its benefits
in that it makes other people
laugh when they don't have it.
Huh?
I just think you described the actual sickness.
I think you just induced a whole
different kind of sickness in many listeners.
Well,
you know, with this particular
subgenius cold,
you can give it to other people
just by looking at them.
You don't have to
even be in the same room. So, like,
cars going by us, I'd kind of give
them the evil eye and
they've got it now.
We, so, honest to God,
we stood on a bridge in Little Rock
with barges
going underneath. Little Rock is a
big port. And these barges
were going off to other
states and countries
and we stood there spitting down
onto the barges far below.
That way your spit gets around.
And you thought about leaping on
one of those barges or?
If you ever read
that Stephen King story, The Stand,
we are implementing
that now.
X day,
is coming for the pinks
whether it comes for us or not.
Wow. Whether we get our
vessels or not, we'll soon have the
earth just to ourselves.
But anyone who
has survived it.
I think this guy
should hit the Cleveland comedy scene, man.
I think
he already hit it.
Or maybe he's
even better. Maybe he should go out and start his own church.
Hey,
wow, I've got the name for it.
I do it all.
It's like
idiotology, but idiots can't spell
idiot. They spell it wrong.
So it comes out. I do it.
I do it all.
I bet we do as well as
Scientology. Could we but
keep a straight face?
That's always been the one hang
up. I mean, you talk about
your anonymous mask.
Nothing is so frozen and
ridiculous as a subgenius
smile. It's plastered there.
There is if by some rude
painter without the with, you know,
too much mix in his glaze.
It
even when
they're miserable, they have that grin.
You know, it's like an instinctive
imitation of Bob
our guru
who always grins
no matter what.
Well,
having left
North Carolina and
Reverend Pockets and like
you,
James Place five
hours ago, we're
approaching Atlanta where
Reverend Susie the floozy lives.
And we just passed
be for
ruin road.
Yes, a
road called be for
ruin, which
Susie in her direction
said would be
funny except that a woman was raped
there about 10 years ago.
She
still had to mention it, though.
Notice
her directions there on the computer
and I didn't print them out and I don't want to try
to look at a laptop while we're navigating
the
circuitous
Atlanta
highway system, which is
about as driver
friendly as Dallas or
Los Angeles.
Luckily, it's almost 10 o'clock
at night, so it's
relatively quiet. Otherwise,
I'd be driving
because Princess Wee is nice
and she's not adjusted to
aggressive highway driving
that people specialize in
in southern giant
cities.
Like I am. I was trained
in Dallas
where the drivers are
by habit so aggressive
that I've had
two separate New York cab drivers
tell me that they were terrified
driving in Dallas
highway.
I would never do it again.
While they were telling me this, I was clutching
the sides of my seats in terror
at the way they were driving
in New York City streets.
So I guess they have some
unspoken rule there that lanes
are for amateurs.
On the highways, lanes
are
in southern cities, the lanes
are taken seriously, but they're
considered territory.
It's a very territorial kind of lane.
It's like, no, buddy, this is my lane
I'm in. Oh, you want to get in?
I'm going to speed up.
Oh, you're trying to get in now? I'm going to slow down.
Well, you actually do get
a certain amount of that from some of them.
So what you have to do is
force your way in because
they will not
damage their cars just to be
mean to you. However,
Pisces,
for me, that in New York City, they
will damage your car, their own
car, just to be mean to
you.
It's almost like the opposite
types of
aggressive driving. Yeah, she said they'll
give you a tap or a nudge
if you're not... Yeah, I've never seen
that happen in Dallas or Los Angeles
or Houston or
Atlanta, but
they will prevent you
from getting in unless you
threaten to damage their
vehicle.
And they still won't honk.
You don't get the honking
like you do in New York City.
No. But then in New York City,
the normal greeting
to a stranger is,
Go fuck yourself, you
goddamn moron!
I'm walking here!
In Dallas,
it's kind of like, Howdy, neighbor,
let me stab you in the back with this here buck knife.
Yeah, so I'm surprised Susie didn't mention
the two roads,
Atlanta, Cumming, and
Dunwoody.
After Cumming,
then you're done with your Woody.
Ah-hoo.
I caught you a delicious
bath. This is
pretty much the worst video ever made.
This is pretty much the
worst show ever made.
That was
Napoleon...
Dynamite there.
The desk model.
This is pretty much the craziest house
I've ever seen.
Yes, friends, we've made it to Susie the Flusie's
house. In fact, we've been here for...
This is our second
night. We're gonna leave
tomorrow. She's
taking us on... You finally got here!
Whoa!
How long have you been here? You just noticed?
Duh! There's so much
crap in this house. I thought you were the decor.
Who
do you think you were?
We're escorting around
John Bonnet Ramsey's grave
and... John Bonnet?
Who else?
Well...
I'm handing cookies to people
who have cookies already.
So we've put
our disease in Susie
now.
And took 500
photographs of her
slack altar.
Which, in the case of Susie the Flusie,
is the entire
house.
Wall-to-wall
bulldada objects.
Indeed. Word isn't a reptile
farm. Right.
Well, those are bulldada objects, too,
to many people. They're not all
sex objects to everybody,
Susie.
And it's
been one... Tomorrow we have to leave.
I just thought I'd better
make one last...
while we still could talk. Before the sheriff's
deputies show up again on the front step?
Yeah, that's right. They're orbiting
the neighborhood.
Yeah, I think they heard through the grapevine
you were on the way.
Well, and
Reverend Valer Chucks and his wife
Emily were here, too.
Valer last heard on
Hour of Slack as Bonobo's
Convergence
guitar player.
This is the most people I have had
in my house since I moved here
a year and a half.
This was an insane crowd
for my house, for my lifestyle.
Too bad we didn't
pick up the recorder while
Valer was here noodling
away on his guitar. That sounded
so good. You know, I didn't know that he
was related to the Allman Brothers.
You thought he was related to the Keep On
Truckin' trucks.
Yeah, I thought he was related
to Mr. Garbage Truck
and his brother Fire
and Toe.
And Dump.
Yeah.
Yeah, this will be the most frustrating
Hour of Slack ever since no one
can see any of what we're talking
about. It's like one of those
endless shows where people talk about what they're
looking at on the internet.
Like some
subgenius show hosts
I know.
The little celebrity girl that was
murdered and everybody thought it was her mom.
Oh, hello Dahlia.
Susie always takes us to her grave whenever we
visit Atlanta. We always go to the
grave.
The little fashion girl.
Joan, Joan, Joan, Joan,
Benet, Robin. Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, yeah. John Benet.
I visited her
grave twice. It's funny, right
next to the John Benet
grave is a Smith grave and
a Dobbs grave.
Really? Yeah.
Jane Dobbs and
Satua M. Dobbs are
buried right next to
John Benet. Honest, I'm
not kidding. I've got photographic
evidence. Coincidence or conspiracy?
I wouldn't have to Photoshop
Satua M into any
other Dobbs name. Old man
bald head, they call him.
Jane Dobbs, the mother of Bob, is
actually buried in Atlanta. I've got a
photo of her tombstone.
Also called the Jerusalem
cricket.
Jerusalem syndrome,
I think, is what we all have.
A Jerusalem artichoke. Giant
cricket can emit a shrill
squeak and handle
and can also bite.
Remember before?
No, that was before my
Well, Susie would
probably love to take you there.
He is known by the humble, simple
dwellers of the desert as
the old man of the desert
or old man
bald head. Full of Civil War guys.
Old man bald head is the god of
the desert? Is the
another name for the Jerusalem
cricket. Oh. This giant
bald headed cricket.
Huge, armored, massive.
The Jerusalem cricket a
phallus daughters showed
found along with
the two notes that she captured
in the endangered new part.
She found an
insect that was dead.
It looked like it was not missing
it's abdomen
covering and the
whole insect was there, but not the
covering of his abdomen just
because
I'm
I'm still wondering, I'm still puzzling over that.
What happened to that bug?
What creature would do that to a bug, leave the rest of the bug,
but eat only the outer integument of the abdomen?
Well, that is the opposite of what usually happens,
where the soft and toothsome tissues of the inside are siphoned away.
I'm trying to find my camera so I can show you a photograph of it.
I might even suggest that no individual creature did this,
but some sort of fungus infestation or carapace-destroying bacteria.
We're now at the part of the show where we pull cameras out and take pictures of each other.
I thought you were going to flash me a picture of some horrendous bug atrocity.
Oh, yeah, that's right. Let's see. I have to...
Oh, this new camera is so...
Lumix is cool. Which one did you get?
No blames is true.
So where's Jones?
I'll just have to figure out...
He's in the box out back.
Pine box?
Bug and...
There it is.
Pine box, boys. Here.
B-O-Y-Z.
There's the bug.
Dr. Howell is now looking at the tiny picture of the strange bug corpse.
Well, it's a Jerusalem cricket.
Is it?
That's old ball head?
I think so. It's certainly a cricket.
Lily told me it was a... she said it's some sort of cricket.
Nothing near for...
For a scale.
It's as big as a locust.
It's a Jerusalem cricket. They're heavy, massive, armored crickets.
And the bald, round head can just be seen at the proximate end.
If Lily hadn't corrected me, I would have assumed it was a hopper grass.
Look at the armor on the legs. The first two pair of legs.
You see, mostly your cricket has a little thin leg.
This is... these are hefty.
Mycroft was just swallowed up and turned by history.
I can show you some fine pictures of Jerusalem crickets that come.
You got some bug porn, Dr. Howell?
Although they are supposed to be more native to the Sonoran region than here, the California desert,
I've run into them right in the San Francisco area.
Well, this was... that photo was taken up the hill from Dr. John.
Oh, I was just having insomnia. It's really fun.
Insomnia.
Yeah.
And I woke up thinking, my worst fears...
Yeah, these are good cameras. Those are excellent cameras.
Line up, sign up, and real this day.
I have the next one up and the one after this just came out.
Let's take another caller here.
Is this Governor Rockner?
Yes, good to hear from you, man. How's everybody?
Yeah, it's good to hear from you.
How is everybody? Everybody's sick, if I've got anything to say about it.
I'm surprised you're not sick, Rockner.
I am. I actually am.
We drove near...
I don't have age yet. I don't have age yet.
No, I got the upper respiratory infection in my hearing.
My hearing's now going as bad as Stang's is.
Wow. So I'm not the only person who had this happen to them.
I had significant hearing loss for about a week.
It took like a week and a half for things to get back to normal.
Well, it started off with really intense pressure.
I got my hearing back and everybody else lost theirs.
So, ha, ha, ha, look who's yelling now.
We've been spreading the subgenius virus.
We make reference to it right up front.
First page on subgenius.com mentions it.
And people think it's a joke, but they won't live to be thinking of it as a joke much longer.
We're coming to your house and we are infected.
In fact, everyone who can hear my voice now is now infected.
For this virus is spread not only by the air,
and computer networks, but by, as I said earlier, line of sight,
and the sound of voice.
So if you're lost in the frequency, you're sick.
You better go out and buy you some Guafanisan or something
and get ready to call off work and curl up in bed
and be really, really miserable and not be able to hear anything.
And if you aren't a douche, thanks subgenius, you'll soon be dead.
And if you are a douche, thanks subgenius.
Would you like that?
Yes, subgenius.
You'll be fine and your hearing will be better in about a week and a half.
Oh, it's already been two weeks.
Right.
Yeah, I actually, it's only been two weeks for me.
Yeah.
I dealt with it for two weeks and everybody I saw,
well, they all still have it.
We've been on the road for just two weeks.
What does it mean to really have it?
Does it mean that the subgenius virus is actually going to...
kill everybody that you come in contact with,
but not you because you are subgenius?
I don't look at it as a disease.
I look at it as an improvement.
I once had a disease, or should I say it once had me?
We're thinning the herd.
That's all.
I thought you were wearing gold earrings again.
Man, none of this makes any sense to me.
I don't think the thinning of the herd is...
Dave, what did make sense to you?
You were dead on the road.
You're an ugly fuck on your own free fucking whale, Doc!
Yes, yes I am.
I'd rather be lucky than smart.
I don't know.
I'm not gonna believe my hobbies.
I don't think I can run and take into my own fox-like
and own mày
What are you whale doing?
The earth.
Oh!
Hey, find a cool way to hang out over there while you're profiting.
I want to sniff your panty.
I want to feed you some yogurt.
Oh, Wendy, Wendy.
Let me put my hand down your shirt.
Sweet mama of the Canadian News Hour.
Oh, Wendy, Wendy.
I want to put my head up your skirt.
I want to sniff your panty.
I want to feed you some yogurt.
Oh, Wendy, Wendy.
Please let me put my hand down your shirt.
I want to feed you some yogurt.
Everybody, come up again.
All right.
No money, Michael.
I had an interesting encounter with another weirdo station.
My friend Pope Sternodox in Little Rock has a Zappa show every Sunday night at 9.
Only 9 Central Time.
And we went down to the station with him.
By the way, I should preface this by saying the first thing I asked him was,
can I say Zappa sucks?
And he just...
And I said, well, I don't think Zappa sucks.
I just wanted to know whether I was allowed to say that.
He said, no.
And his co-host said, yeah, you can walk home.
I said, okay, I just wanted to see if you guys were in a cult.
And Sternodox said, I'm in two cults.
And anyway, this station, it's the opposite of WCSB in every way.
It has very little equipment, much less than I have in my home studio.
And that ain't saying much.
And Sternodox's partner owns all of it.
But their transmitter is so powerful that they reach five states.
And get this.
Their show, when they end their show, they're the last people in the station until the next morning.
They put on a Zappa CD on repeat.
It's a different one every week.
Selected material.
Usually rare.
And so for seven hours from Sunday night to Monday morning,
for five states around Little Rock,
lone weirdos and ignorant young musicians get to hear, for the first time,
hours of Frank Zappa.
And I thought, what a great gift to those weirdos in Texas, Oklahoma, Mississippi.
Yeah, but you're in Tipper Gore country, remember?
Tennessee.
So, yeah, I mean, really, these guys are like more than 50,000,
150,000.
I mean, it's a lot of people.
And I think it's a great gift.
Coming out of a station that only has one CD.
They have two CD players and a cassette deck that doesn't work.
Not a single turntable.
And no way to record off the air what they're doing.
And I'm sure that that Zappa, those 10 hours of Zappa every late,
in the middle of the night, have saved some lives.
You know?
Because, I mean, think.
If you're the only.
If you're the only punk in McCrory, Arkansas.
Oh, yeah.
Look, if you're worried about, you know, red and green lights here,
just stop it.
Just stop it.
Just back my cart right off your green.
Is that what you're saying?
Yeah, we've been saying.
We've been saying to everyone involved in this whole endeavor this evening,
you know,
two-thirds to three-quarters of all the knobs and buttons and lights in this whole place
are completely superfluous.
They mean nothing.
They have no bearing on the overall sound that we hear or whatever.
Right.
And ignore the red wire that goes from there to the Pentagon.
Oh, forget about that.
It's buried deep enough they're not going to run into it anyway.
Take the yellow light and you'll stay where you are.
Take the red light and you'll see how deep the rabbit hole goes.
There you go.
There's how it's going.
They don't have to dig very deep.
They don't have to dig very deep at all.
Get a sledgehammer down there, a pneumatic sledgehammer,
and pierce through that force field somehow.
Cut that wire, and then what Krell just said would be true.
None of the buttons would work.
None of them, well, really none of them do.
So did that already happen?
That's what we're saying, yeah.
It already happened.
It's the past again.
We're living in the past, man.
It's the past all over again.
The station on the planet where I'm from has a million buttons,
and none of them do.
And they all work.
You can only hear it for about 12 feet around the station.
That's because it's in the other past.
Because of a boy named Vicky.
We ain't dealing with that.
We're dealing with the other thing.
Yeah, that's what happened.
Right behind, left behind.
I was about to say that, and then I thought,
am I violating a copyright by saying pull the lever, down you go?
No.
No, I don't think so.
I think the legal representation that we've endured
will make sure that saying things like pull the lever, down you go
will not result in any permanent incarceration
of the part of the person who said it.
Even though they were once a doctor, or are now.
Now, is this about Frank Zappa or the duck farms of Arkansas?
Which I saw today.
We drove all the way here from Cleveland High.
It's a duck farm.
It's astonishing how they entered Link.
How they entered Link.
But, yeah, they were catfish farms, though, with just ducks on them.
The ducks were trespassers.
The ducks were just on them.
On the catfish.
Yeah, the ducks were just on the catfish farms.
That's what they were.
Freak Out was the fourth album I ever paid money for.
When I was a kid.
My first album I ever bought was the Monkees album
with Last Train Clarksville.
I don't know why I'm saying that.
The second album I ever bought was Magical Mystery Tour.
You're on a roll.
The second album I ever bought was Jimi Hendrix's Are You Experienced?
Let's go.
The fourth album was Frank Zappa's Freak Out.
Let's give Stang a hand for the...
That's a hell of a four first albums.
Mine aren't quite that good.
You can see the progression.
And then Trout Mask Replica, I think, has been number five.
Number five?
Yeah.
Yeah, Monkees album was among my first four albums, but also among those were the 1910
Fruit Gump albums.
Right.
Greatest hit.
I've been reading about it.
It all links in.
Yeah.
Lillian Roxon has been telling me about those.
You don't have to read those off a glittering screen.
They're on magazines that are in your daddy's bottom drawer.
They're right there.
Oh.
All right.
I found a place where I could download all the photos from the magazines.
I want that website.
I downloaded them all.
Alt.binaries.newdisc.com.
I'm serious.
Every year I download about 10,000.
Okay.
Why didn't I know that?
I sent my dad.
Why hadn't I had that bookmarked for years?
I sent my dad a CD of about 10,000 scans of those magazines.
You're right.
I'm not a big fan of that.
I'll give you a copy of that.
Crel has that kind of relationship with his dad.
Only it's Led Zeppelin.
Not Newt Volleyball.
Although Led Zeppelin and Newt Volleyball, that'll ...
Six of one, seven of another.
Yeah.
It's half of one.
It's half of one, seven of another.
Half of one and nine and a half of the other.
This is what we're saying, ma'am, sir.
Sir, ma'am.
Nobody calls here at KBF 88.3 FM Community Radio in Little Rock, California.
Arkansas playing music is the best
with Reverend Ivan Stang, Princess
We Are Doe,
and me, Reverend Sternow, here
in Little Rock.
The only problem is
that as free
as that station is, and as
great as the work Reverend Sternow
is doing, I have it on good authority
that as free as they are, you're not
allowed to say Zappa sucks
on the air. That's right.
I specifically asked if I
was able to say that, whether
I meant it or not, which I don't particularly.
Sometimes I do.
That dental floss song sucked.
I said, Sternow,
you're in a cult.
It's a Zappa thing. It's a cult for you.
He goes, no.
I'm in two cults.
Did I say
this whole thing last night?
Yes, you did, and I was hoping you would
say it again. Were you having boujadé?
Our audiences
overlap, but are not
the same audience.
So this parable
needs to be told more than
once, and that's our opinion.
Well, our background sound effects aren't the same.
It's true. We usually
eschew all that grinding, bumping
and microphone stand
banging sound effect, but we just had the tape
and we just had to use it because it was so fun.
You know, boujadé is right.
You know, it's amusing to professional broadcasters.
As opposed to déjà vu.
I know, jamais vu, the sense that you've never
seen what is familiar.
No, boujadé is where
when you got chewed out
by an asshole
and you walk away and you think of the
perfect response, but it's too late.
No, actually,
I hate to correct you,
but that is called esprit d'escalier.
Or the spirit
of the staircase, where as you're leaving
you're thinking of the perfect thing you
should have said, but you just
didn't say. You just want to roll back
time and be able to say it, and you
can't. In hindsight.
Hindsight has perfect.
Indulging in the luxury of hindsight.
Wow.
If only I'd have said this.
The nice thing about confrontations on the internet is you can
get furiously mad at somebody who's trolling you and write a whole bitter essay,
and then just hit save and hide it away, sleep on it, and the next morning you wake up with
a one-liner that is so much better response than all of that hate-filled ranting because it, you know,
gives the impression that you were merely amused by this pathetic thing.
It actually did manage to get your gut.
Those concise, but really robust, but concise insults are the best, you know.
Well, I've been consciously working on that.
Like, Madam, Madam, you're ugly.
In the morning, I shall be sober.
What did he... Madam, I'm Adam.
No, no.
That's a palindrome.
That's not it.
No.
Bob, I'm slob.
You know, it's like one of those.
Yeah.
Bob, I'm slob.
Bob, I'm me slob.
I'm me slob.
That's not the one I was thinking of.
I was thinking more of it.
We're not very good at accurate palindromes.
Let me think about what I was thinking about and see if I can think of it again.
If you stop, if you don't think about it anymore, it'll come to you.
I'm going to put my finger next to my nose because that will help draw it out.
And does that make you go up the chimney?
It helps draw out...
Put a rubber band around your wrist.
I've got a rubber band around my head.
Don't cut off the circulation.
Don't bind that headband too tight.
Bind the evil spirits in my head.
Okay.
Now, if I push that button...
Turn the damn radio down.
Yes, listener caller, please turn your radio or computer device down.
I know you're listening all the way out there in the west coast of San Francisco.
Unless it's an art project you're doing and you need that sound effect, you know, that's okay.
I thought it was just my head cold that was making that slight feedback.
I was hoping it was the church air making that slight feedback.
I thought it was the raw onion in my ear that was there for the earwax.
Is that onion still in your ear?
Yeah, it's still in there, yeah.
That's that weird smell.
Everybody's smelling around me.
You guys are remarkable.
Hmm.
We get some really rude remarks.
We don't get paid enough to do that though.
There you go.
We get some pretty rude remarks, yeah.
I would say that in our money we thought we'd be perfectly cold.
Well, it wouldn't make any difference to us because that just goes right out the window.
We just burn it up.
The fumes go right up where they're supposed to go.
The only way out is through the chimney.
It's just, it's just a little bit of a pain.
Physics and chemistry is all it is.
Up in smoke.
Did you go to the big game?
Hey, life is a big game, dude.
Um, no.
Okay, I didn't think so. I don't know.
We weren't even game for him asking you about the game at first, but then we...
Well, now it's become almost embarrassing.
We agreed on it that he'd be alright, probably.
If you even mention the game, you've lost the game.
That's not supposed to be funny.
I mean, are you trying to tell me that you guys all thought I wasn't me?
Well, all I'm trying to tell you is we don't know what happened.
Something must have happened.
Yeah, we're not really sure.
We're going to figure it out.
We're taking notes now.
We're taking notes.
We're taking notes right now.
Bob came and he did something to all of us.
Right.
That's all we can piece together.
That's all the memories that have been erased and that we've been allowed to read once real quick in disappearing ink.
But everything else we were forced to forget.
This is the show where people are missing no how, no Philo, no Sterno.
And of course, in honor of Phineas Darko, no Jano.
And you can't, and you, can you say Zappa sucks on this show?
Yes.
I just proved it.
You can.
We're free.
We're not a cult.
It's really Sterno's show that we have to be afraid of.
Right.
You are not allowed to say those words, whether you mean them or not.
Zappa sucks.
You know, most of the time I don't mean it, but you are not allowed.
And I've been tattling on them for weeks now.
But that's just in private conversation.
Can you say it on like?
No, on the radio.
No.
They almost beat me up for saying it in private conversation.
Just the very concept.
Zappa sucks.
Upset these Zappa cultists so much.
I was going, look, I'm just advancing the, if I say these words, what will happen?
And they said, you'll walk home.
And they were not kidding either.
I said, you're in a cult.
And Sterno said, no, I'm in two cults.
That's there.
Now I've told it 500 times.
Here's Ivan Stang dancing home from the show.
I'm like my dad now.
I just, I can't remember who I've told what joke to.
And I just keep saying the same things over and over again.
What about these people over here, Mr. Smith?
They all say the same thing.
That's what Facebook is for.
You get on there and you have to make up new stuff every 10 seconds.
That's why I've been voicing.
I can't.
I'm tired of that.
I'm just tired, tired, tired, tired.
Do you like it?
I know what you mean.
I'm tired of it.
I haven't done that much of it.
Well, we did it before it was around.
We did it by tape and U.S. Mail.
And I'm glad that the Internet wasn't around then because there was some pretty embarrassing
things said.
Goodbye.
I'm sorry.
It's true.
It's really funny.
We had the Internet, but it was, it was really, really bad.
It was really slow.
It took days and there were only 15 of us.
Yeah, it was.
It was a lot funnier until the flaming and trolling.
And of course, you know, it's always funny until somebody gets hurt and somebody's little
brother gets her eyes shot out.
Hell of a way to operate.
Then all the ins and outs of getting killed.
Every fucking beaten.
I'm grateful for every fucking one of them.
Get all the trust.
Beat out of you.
And you know what the fucking world is.
26 years when in the studio, they used to listen to me.
Never would Irving Thalberg make a picture I was opposed to.
I had to worship for that boy.
He worked.
Now they want cocktail parties and their names in the papers.
Irving listened to me.
Never satisfied with his own work.
That was Irving.
Years later, after Irving passed away, they still listened.
They make an Andy Hardy picture.
Andy's mother is dying and they make the picture showing Andy standing outside the
door.
Standing, I told them.
Don't you know that an American boy like that will get down on his hands and knees and pray?
They listened.
They brought Mickey Rooney down on his hands and knees.
It was the biggest thing in the picture.
But it wasn't good enough.
They don't show the good, wholesome American mother in the home.
Kind.
Sweet.
Sacrifices.
Love.
I'm sorry.
Knock the old mother on the jaw.
That's what they do.
Throw the little old lady down the stairs.
Throw the mother's good homemade chicken soup in the mother's face.
Tip on the mother.
Kick her.
That's art, they say.
Art.
Yo ring-a-delinkedieron flowers.
This here is anutlichly a hesitant发다 this piece came so I'll leave it in construction
The two assumed the press that they were with the wedding.
and little, at least, rotting trailer courts and kudzu-covered barns
and funny-named businesses like Mammy's Bammy Shack.
Mammy's Bammy BBQ Shack would suit me.
But we've been bitterly disappointed.
It's just as pink as Richardson, Texas, with the suburb I grew up in.
It's blank.
Yeah.
It's totally blank.
Well, I mean, there's Burger Kings and shell stations.
And cemeteries and hairdo places.
Yeah, but the hairdo places don't have quaint names.
They have funny names.
It was called Hills Hair Service.
Yeah.
That's pathetic.
I mean, it's destroying.
I've never been in Alabama before that I can remember,
and it's destroying all my stereotypes, and I'm really let down.
I was hoping to get a huge feeling of superiority.
We're passing trailers right now, but they're perfectly, nicely kept.
I'm disgusted.
That shell station is just modern.
Alabama is supposed to be, you know, the kind of man, backwards.
It's supposed to be hillbillion.
It might as well be anywhere.
It's supposed to be somewhere else in the goddamn country.
What the?
Those are chicken.
That's a chicken farm.
Really?
Yeah.
What are each one of those little beans?
Each one of those pyramids has a chicken in it.
Really?
Yeah, that's probably what they call free-range chicken.
When you buy those eggs thinking,
Oh, those chicken, the chickens that lay these dollar extra free-range eggs
are skipping happily across the pasture.
You know, pecking at worms.
What that means is instead of being crammed together in six-inch boxes in a factory,
they're outdoors under those triangles.
Those triangles looked like they were maybe two inches bigger than a hen inside of it.
Well, but they're outdoors.
Uh-huh.
The hens don't know any better.
So much more humane not...
Well, no, it is.
It's actually, if you, you know,
compared to those giant indoor factories,
it's still a chicken concentration camp,
but it's a benevolent chicken concentration camp.
And don't worry about it.
Those chickens' ancestors chewed on our ancestors for millions of years.
Jesus is Christmas.
It's so sad that everywhere in America looks like everywhere else in America.
I mean, it really is.
There are places that are different.
New Orleans has or had a sort of a somewhat different spirit.
There's little tiny sections of San Francisco
that are still not completely obliterated by creeping metroplexness of everything.
There's one street in Fort Worth that's kind of Texas-y.
But it's like Rocky and Bull.
I think that's the way it is.
All right, let's go.
Look, Rocky, we're in that same town again.
There's that same hamburger place.
In Frostbite Falls, they didn't have McDonald's or Burger King.
They didn't have any franchises at all.
It's a conspiracy.
And they didn't deliberately do it.
They did it because people like convenience.
And they like things to be.
be the same. Well, they'd like to know what to expect. They don't like surprises. On our
previous trip, I remember walking into kind of a redneck biker diner that was a bit too
much of a surprise. And if I didn't have my hair, well, actually, I should have had my
hair out. Then they wouldn't have looked at us so suspiciously. That was one place where
being disguised as Mr. Smith was a drawback. If I'd walked in looking like Reverend Stang,
they'd go, oh, hi, buddy. You want a beer or some meth? But when we travel, we try to
look as innocuous as possible. And there are still a few places. Now, see, if I was black,
I'd probably be pretty uncomfortable walking into there, especially once I'd read what
was written on the stall. There was like a...
Too hot even for the publishers of the Turner Diaries. And it gave a web address for a PDF.
This was written in the bathroom stall. And I wrote it down. And when we got back home,
I downloaded the PDF. And sure enough, it was too hot for the Turner Diaries, which,
by the way, are a famous racist hoax document, somewhat like the Protocols of the Elders of
Zion, only written by some peckerwood in America about what the black people really think.
And I'm sure somewhere there's black people that really do think that way. I probably
wouldn't blame them. But I'm sorry. I just... It's become too difficult for me to generalize
anymore. Everything's all mixed up as far as people's heads go.
So...
What's not mixed up is the damn landscape of America. That's uniform. Of course, we
are on the interstate now, and I expect it to be uniform there. But, I mean, we pulled
off just to see some class division, and there weren't none. There was an actual middle class.
I guess we should be relieved that there's still some place where they have that. If
the city didn't get after us...
I mean, I guess our house would probably be the kind that we ourselves would make fun
of.
Probably.
The inside already is.
Okay, six to an even, over and out.
Oh, well, enough preaching. Soon we'll be in the beautiful, historic city of Birmingham,
Alabama.
Southern man better eat your head. Don't forget what the Book of the Superficial
Subgenius said. Southern change gonna come at last. Fifty-seven cents crammed up my
ass. Southern man.
Oh, we finally saw the Alabama we were looking for. For one thing, we just crossed the Buttehatchee
River. And it's spelled like it sounds.
Buttehatchee. Buttehatchee River. Shortly before that, we saw a sign that said,
I heart my credit union in pretty bad lettering. And I'm saying that literally. It didn't have
a symbol of a heart. It wasn't I, picture of a heart, my credit union. It was in bad,
giant lettering on a billboard. I heart, H-E-A-R-T, my credit union. That's the Alabama we were
looking for.
And you also, we also passed a store that you missed when you were talking just a moment
ago called Devoe Paint. It wasn't spelled right. It was D-E-V-O-E, but it was Devoe
Paint.
Devoe.
There's Family Worship Center, ATM inside. It's a church. And I was just curious to see
what the name of the church was. And the name of the church is Family Worship Center. And
right underneath that, it said ATM inside. They usually have something like Jesus is
your friend. Or what was the one you saw earlier?
Happy Birthday, Jesus.
Yeah. Yeah, ATM inside. Whoa. Does that mean they don't take credit cards?
Don't let that plate pass you dry.
No kidding. We'll have to remember that if we ever have a church in the subgenius building.
You know, Bob loves you, ATM inside.
Heart your credit union?
Yeah, I heart Bob. We heart Bob with heart spelled out. You know, to be really complete,
it should have quotes around heart.
Yes.
But then, that would be almost too self-aware.
Yeah.
It would be better to put the quotes around the ATM. Quote ATM, unquote inside.
Or around inside. Anything inappropriate. That's how quotes are used out there. True,
the true boonies. For sale. Numeral four in quotes.
Oh, shut up, Jack.
It's the hour of slack from the church of the subgenius. www.subgenius.com.
Subgenius.com.
Um...
Throw away Z'n'Aliens.
Throw away z'n'aliens.
Estoshachin's this planet.
Subgenius.com.
planet. Job is
an alien.
Job is an alien.
Job is
an alien. And so threatens
this planet.
Oh, sire, there is
no more money. We gotta
get some money.
That dirty, perky, shark-a-back, flat-a-wattin',
Philip-buck-a-burton, perkaluma-burton,
dirt-a-bustin'-a-law!
Beep. Beep.
Friends, we're glad you listened
to this show, and we're even more
glad that some listeners have donated
enough to help us keep on going for another
couple of months. And not
just this show, but subgenius.com
and all the other archive sites.
But if
you truly love Bob,
and want some of that slack back to rebound
to you, you should
go to subgenius.com
front page, or especially the radio
page, or the catalog store
pages, and help
out financially as best you can.
Now, we know
what it's like to be on the brink of total
poverty, and we don't want any subgeniuses
to make their own situations worse.
But some of you
still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big
difference, even if it's only once
a month from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger
difference.
All we're saying is that
blowjobs could go the
way of Stevejobs if you
don't pay dogs.
We also take checks and
money orders to
Subgenius Foundation.
P.O. Box
181-417
Cleveland
Heights, Ohio
Thanks for anything you can do
to help let there be
slack.
We're not just a small corporation.
We need free contact.
Free pills!
Kill me!