baaaab baaaaaab hows everything
every since I've dayed about it
baaaaaab
Bob?
And it comes down the street like a garbage wagon.
Okay.
So their brains may live on forever.
But has he created another?
By the miracle of recording.
I'm not very good at singing songs, but here's a try.
Well, better make it quick, kiddo.
Ridiculous theory of evolution.
Peace or annihilation.
And then it struck me.
At some point in the past, I had compiled enough new hymns and songs of a subgeniusly nature
to make a seventh Bob Song CD.
But I'd never gotten around to making the packaging,
so the stuff hadn't been released except in dribs and drabs on ancient hours of Slack from 2006.
So that solved my problem.
Here, then, is hour of Slack number 1246,
an all Bob Songs episode and a sneak preview of our next...
official CD release, which you now already have on MP3 from downloading this show.
But, oh well.
Slack must come first in the life of every initiate.
Leigh Murr shall start us off.
One, two, three!
Bob.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Bob?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That doesn't look like me at all.
If you were turned inside out, that's the way you'd go.
Apparently, Bob came and did something with all of us.
Praise the Bob!
Quiet, numbskulls.
It's on broadcasting.
Lay your hands on the radio!
Lay your hands on the radio band, and we're gonna look to God!
It's not a nightmare that's gonna end, it's just beginning because it's inside me.
You, you have to love Bob.
He loves you, but...
you love Bob.
You have to.
Or else what happens if you don't love Bob?
He'll kill you.
He'll Bob you out.
Right now, I will give you all my money.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Huh?
Bob.
Why don't you just leave me alone?
I never saw anything.
I don't know what Mars is and I was never there.
Shut up!
You shut up!
Attention.
Polly?
Come?
Honey?
Attention.
Who are the overlords of the UFO ?
Bob! Bob!
Bob! Bob! Bob!
Look, if he starts this thing, he won't be able to stop it.
It's immortality.
For the price more costly than death.
The world stops spinning and the clock stops moving.
But something's still ticking and wearing on the inside.
And every time you let it go like I'm doing right now,
you can feel the wear.
I know from 342 years of experience that time control can only go awry.
The Third World War might begin any minute and we'll all be killed.
Why should we bother about giant turtles?
Yes, maybe you're right.
I know how much you love your turtles.
But there are other things in life just as important,
like how to live.
I'm glad you're having friends.
Our ancient legends did mention fire-eating turtles.
Ah, yes.
That ah, yes from Pastor Epley signifies that that was the soundtrack of a video.
A spaz blaster for which I did the music and mix using a bunch of collages by Fernanda Nandi-Lemur,
as well as Byron Werner, Sivit Stang, Reverend Rosna, uh, Sandy Smith, and Reverend New Monet.
By the way, if anybody can tell us what happened to New Monet, please do.
In the meantime, from Norellpref.com, Norellpref and his composition, Love Church.
I gotta tell ya, man, I love church.
I just love church.
Bob! Bob!
Love church. Totally!
Yes, giving.
Bob!
I love this guy!
Come join the fun!
All of you have heard of...
Bob!
Love church.
I gotta tell ya,
It makes you feel real big.
Go! Go! Go!
Love church.
Bob!
Yes, giving.
Come join the fun.
All of you have heard of...
Bob!
Love church.
It makes you feel real big.
Yes, giving.
Bob!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
We all thought you were dead.
No, no. Still here.
How are you, Bob?
I'm okay.
Brothers and sisters, we must confront ourselves.
We know that all men and women are created good.
We must understand why you have gone bad.
You cannot play checkers with your life, jumping around like an old whirlwind,
wrapping your dishes and plates and then unpacking them and placing them back on a shelf.
This is not the way the Jehovah One has designed you to act.
Unless you are willing to admit that you are a gnom, a pink boy, a nini, a twig.
Only then can you decide where your path shall lead you.
But we know inherently that we are all created good by Jehovah One.
Some of you got such bad luck sometimes in your life, you couldn't hang yourself with your own necktie.
This is when you should look to Bob.
When you look to Jehovah One and say,
Bob, come into my life.
And you shall see one set of footprints in the sand.
And that is when you will know that Bob has charged you $5.99 to carry you to the nearest taxi.
Praise Bob and his divine ways.
You got to know that life is like a vanishing twin, a baby inside of a twin inside of a woman's belly.
That's how confusing it is.
This wiggly world can be.
You got to breeze up above this wiggly world and grab the hand of Bob.
Praise him and all that flows from Bob.
And praise Reverend Raymond Lafferty who did that classic.
A wiggly world indeed.
To help solidify things, we'll now hear Bob's audition by, not Bob,
but the Psychoskeletons.
The Psychoskeletons
Feels kinda like I'm in Spaceland.
That's a contradiction in terms.
And Bob's shining down on me.
And no one's aiming a rifle at me.
Holy dammit.
That's a contradiction in terms.
And Bob is the giant hepatitis penis of destruction.
Bursting forth from the portable Johnny.
Now let's all be a contradiction in terms.
Herds of benign cattle wander across the acid-washed, flush-drained landscape.
All belonging to their own friendship families, none loving any other than Bob.
The flow between adjacent points of reference.
Points on the line segment between the concrete to absolute oblivious eternity.
Sweet Lord Bob.
When we all act together as men, as people, we could distinguish ourselves and betray any other.
As it was before time, but still within space.
All who bow down and submit to their fractals.
The Psychoskeletons
Bob. Bob. Bob. Bob. Bob. Bob. Bob. Bob.
Bob? wireérer.
My short Doors Perseverance
My Short Doors Perseverance
Doooooors and arms.
Doors.
My shorter persevere
Bob does
Cigarette butts on the ground
Just like the sun, my slack goes on and on and on
Praise Bob!
Just like the sun, my slack goes on and on and on and on
Just like the sky, the sun, my slack goes on and on and on
And on
Praise Bob
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Praise Bob's song number 1010 by Lee Murr.
Now, another song by Reverend Ed Fred entitled simply, Pink.
Hey little brothers and sisters, why don't you get around?
I've got something important to say to you, something I think you need to hear.
Come on now.
Are you sure you've got your life together?
No.
On top of the world.
The reality is about to rear its ugly head, my friends.
Are you ready to face the music?
You're pink.
We think.
You drive that big old SUV.
Draining your wallet into you.
used to be. You're in a material race you just can't win. Following society is your greatest sin.
You are destined to fail, my friend. You're gonna be poor and alone in the end.
You got your treasures, you got your hoard, but you're only gonna end up broken board.
Come on, friends, it's time to turn over a new leaf.
Unleash your weakness and get some relief. Slack is king and nothing else matters.
Don't be pink. Pull yourself up by your latex undergarments.
Toss away all your commercial influences. The slack within you can be born again.
Act now. This is limited time, awful. Get yours now while supplies last.
Awful void in Alaska and Hawaii. Be sure to consult your doctor about any risk that might be associated with slack.
Yeah, I hope you learned something today. Now I'm going to get myself some slack.
Daa-ba-ba-bum...
Ba-bum!
dobryった 바 ASK THOSE Les B
Oh man, I can't reach the pause.
I trip.
But it's okay.
Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob
Who are the overlords of the UFO?
I bring you a warning.
Every one of you listening to my voice, tell the world.
Tell this to everybody wherever they are.
Watch the sky.
This is Doug Smith, radio operator.
I'm gonna bring you a piece of that green cheese for sure.
Shazam!
And I say it is possible for a giant lizard to have lived there for years without being seen.
Let's go!
You, you, you, you bloated idiot!
You stupid fathead!
There are a bunch of art critics and we're looking for people who like to draw.
You are not safe.
I'll save you, brothers.
Oh, so suspicious, eh?
I'm the art critic.
Huh?
One joke can sell a thousand words.
Then a thousand words of fun.
That is quite a joke.
I tried the prof.
Groovy.
Right, Bob?
Bob?
Wait a minute.
How did this happen?
We're smarter than this.
Apparently not.
Bob?
Long call, Dave.
Don't you know what they're doing to yourself?
Apparently Bob came and did something with all of us.
Yeah.
The drugs I took seemed to light up my brain.
And I'd say as long as you're alive, you'll make noise.
You won't hear back.
You'll breathe up.
You'll shut up like hell.
And you ain't earned the last Ernest T. Bass.
Praise Reverend Ernest T. Bass.
The last four minutes there were collages by Lemur, Byron Werner, and others
remixed by me with my music.
I can't remember if I ever made a video with that one or not,
but now from a group or individual, I don't even know which,
called Da Vinci, a tune called Eslactica.
I don't know if I ever made a video with that one.
And the first bishop I ever met.
And everyone I ever met.
.
And I reformed the head.
The head. What about the head?
What about the scary poster dog thing?
That evil head.
There's no sign of Wellman.
We're just landlady right here and hoping that we can get in touch with you.
Yeah, Wellman's gone.
But if we can just get the head inside that lead-lined vault, we'll be okay.
Friends, beware that head.
Save it.
I left the little Wellman at home.
The bleeding head of Arnold Palmer rose slowly above the trap between the third and fourth greens
down at Onion Creek Country Club and Golf Course.
Thumping slowly like an over-enlarged fig,
the bleeding head slowly rose at a gentle angle above the green, dripping blood.
It hovered briefly over the sand trap and then slowly ascended towards the constellation of Orion at an angle of about 44.325 degrees, like a shot off a shovel.
There was no doubt that it was the head of Arnold Palmer.
That moon-faced smile was unforgettable.
The population, the population of southeast Austin went wild.
They tore off their clothes, danced in the streets and said,
The bloody head has come.
The time is here.
Take off your clothes and be somebody.
The bloody head of Arnold Palmer was above such things.
The bloody head of Arnold Palmer rose gently, buffeting itself slightly as it passed among some ancient pecan trees.
The blood of Arnold Palmer was slowly, still, ever moving upwards.
It wobbled slightly, spraying a small glissando of blood, so to speak, on the people below it,
healing two old ladies and giving an old man a substantial gland rebuild.
At 14 minutes after 9, the bleeding head was sighted.
The bastards, hard-headed, carried the body around in their hands,
preventing them from taking off the body ofええno on Head Tweeter.
infectious, the body or an easily kidnap onto a
historical TV channel.
More than 5,000 people died.
Quite some were Do Commirals.
Diligent in self-destruction bur系penhack3
radar at Caswell Air Force Base, gave subsequent indications that something large and wet was
moving north-northeast while ascending still upwards towards the constellation of Orion.
The bloody head moved on. Fourteen ex-virgins were rejuvenated in Lubbock as the head passed through.
The head was taken to the hospital in the early morning of the same day.
Keep your hands out of each other's marsupial pockets, boys.
That's right.
Yes, the Ballad of the Bleeding Head, a real oldie from the great Dr. G. Gordon Gordon in Doctors for Extreme Prejudice.
I'm not sure, but I think one of the musicians on that finally got out of prison after serving a term for murder.
And now, the news.
From the air, the news.
PR news in Washington. I'm delayed by heavy snow.
Pope Benedict XVI is instructing Irish Roman Catholic clergy to cooperate in the sex involving priests and children.
The Vatican says Benedict does express profound sexual regret, this time at the Vancouver Olympics.
On Wall Street, 151021421.
Pope Benedict says this is PR.
Your news is flawed.
Three instead of three and a half.
President Obama says.
And this is only the tripling.
Astronauts killed 18 people and injured 71 others aboard the International Space Station.
The astronauts need to encourage development of PR news from Washington.
COVID.
The mighty Reverend Artemia Salina engineered that one.
Nothing shrimpy about him, and such a briny fellow.
Next up, well, I'm sorry, I promised I wouldn't do this,
but with the help of Princess Wee and inspired by the Numa Numa internet fad, I sang.
This is the subgenius Numa Numa song with our English translation
phonetically derived from the Romanian boy band original.
The title was phonetically changed from Dragos Ja Dente to rather Bob Didn't Stay.
But soon, sun's born, just eat a comb.
I know you'll be like my subgenius Fettuccine.
I know, I know, some parachute.
Big ass hole, some back feet.
She's so unique, that's it, she won't share the meat.
Love will come, but Connie goes away.
Connie goes away.
Connie goes away away.
Bob made care of Tuccini all day.
We have to eat it all today.
Face of dogs, don't ever go away.
Never go away.
Never go or go away.
She'd rebel, she'd rather fucking stay.
Now at best, we'll all be paid.
Hey!
Mice and cheese, mice and poo.
Mice and hoe, mice and ha ha.
Mice and cheese, mice and poo, mice and hoe
Mice and haha.
She's a happy girl today
Cause she quit her job
The solution
Has it been
Purified?
I brushed my teeth today
Just to see if I could feel
I focus on the pain
The only thing that's real
I brushed my teeth today
Just to see if I could feel
I focus on the pain
The only thing that's real
Listen all yorkers
We're steppin' hardcore
Don't break it, don't break it
This is a public service matter
Do you often brainstorm ideas
For getting some cash
As you empty logs of poo
From your garments?
Maybe you could benefit
From some of the money
I mean slack
I had a dream
I saw it twice
Saved earth of day
Or even chocolate night
Nicotine breeze at night
Misrepresented sets of tunnels
I had a dream
I saw it twice
Saved earth of day
Or even chocolate night
Nicotine breeze at night
Misrepresented sets of tunnels
A most Beefheartian song
Or homage called
Slack Solution
By the Psychoskeletons
Another song that also brings to mind
Captain Beefheart
Although not for any good reason
Is this masterpiece
By the great Dr. Gary Gabrog Fran
Titled Tar Baby of Bob
Tar Baby of Bob
I've got no money
But I got no?
Bob
When you're stuck
Straight to the tar baby Mustph Democrats
If you've got anyface
guitar solo
I wish I was stuck in a big ball of frog
Instead of this church where my socks just rock
Somewhere in hyperspace, Bob has prepared a place
For those he loves for who will pay
The X's will come again and make us sober
And the countdown's getting higher on X day
Ten and nine, eight and seven, six and four and five
Send your thirty bucks while you're alive
Two and three, how rich we'll be when humans take a dive
The countdown's getting higher at our food drive
Bob Dobbs was shot for you, met with the devil too
But in deepest hell he did not stay
Satan done let him out and while we scream and shout
The countdown's getting higher on X day
Ten and nine, eight and seven, six and five and nine
Send your thirty bucks, you're out of time
Forty-two, boy, did he get you?
Salvation should be a crime
The countdown's getting higher on frog this time
So, where's the dummy that we have to train on?
Reverend Self Slayer did that quaint and quirky little X day folk song
Now, echoing a song from last week's show
Reverend Phineas Narco of NationalCynical.com
Brings us this subgeniusized version of a John Lennon song
That probably doesn't deserve this kind of treatment
Imagine there's no Starbucks
I wonder what you'd do
Can't get in
ATM card
And no computers too
Imagine all subgenies
Living life in slack
Imagine there's no modems
And sitcoms on TV
We'd hunker down in mud huts
And take some LSP
And we'd be back in the day
You
Who-who-who
You may say I'm subgenius
But I'm not the only one
Gotta wonder if I'm really one
What I'm losing out on
Imagine no McDonalds
And no Big Mac with cheese
No email and no voicemail
And no more songs like these
Imagine the subgenius
Life without the con
You, hoo hoo hoo
Gotta wonder if I'm really wanting
What I'm losing out on
Look into my eyes
What do you trust?
The Church of the Subgenius
I know you're slack
I've been everything so spit and cuss
I'm the Church of the Subgenius
Like El Populi and Reverend Spell
Church of the Subgenius
Friggin'
Dr. Powell!
Princess Queen!
Mr. Remo Remo Remo will crash the next next thing!
You don't have to follow me.
Only you can teach me.
Oh maybe you can teach me?
I smell the faint.
you need to be.
Church of the subgenius.
I explore you, don't make a fuss.
I tell you when and when and when makes it us.
I'm the church of the subgenius.
Like J.R. Bob Dobbs and Old Festus.
Church of the subgenius.
Lonesome cowboy dig.
I load women.
A subgenius rants.
That subgenius lies.
You don't have to follow me.
Only you can pee freely.
Freely.
You'll take me for a...
Dr. Paul.
Princess Queen.
Mr. Lemo, Lemo, Lemo.
You will crash the next death's day.
You don't have to follow me.
Only you can pee freely.
You gave me fap.
You gave me slap.
You gave me power from Bob Dobbs' old sap.
I'm every person
you need to be
so get on the bus
don't need to discuss much
I'm the church of the subgenius
I'm the church of
a great subgenius anthem created by
noralpref of noralpref.com
loaded with inside references
as is this one by
Reverend Oroboros Rex
it's an X-Day song
this one and the following song
by Phineas Snarko are placed down near the end
of the show for maximum tearjerker
effect
music
And it's one more night in Rushwood
If my Friday Jones could be my hire
I wish she would
Na na na na
Yeah
The smell of the boys and of normals
And the feeling that they all can't help
But see it in my face
With my third eye I look across the mill
The way to see he exists
On their way to burn this place
And it's one more night in Rushwood
And it's one more day up in the saucers
If saucer dreams alone could bring me Susie
Maybe I could
Na na na na
Yeah
I'd cruise this laddered mansion sometime after 2 a.m.
And talk a little while about the church
But the conspiracy makes you move a little slower
Makes you talk a little lower about the day that we take over
It's been a while since X-Day and I guess I will believe
Maybe next year will be better than the last
I can't remember all the things I've said in my life
All the times I played the hourglass
And wished my wish would make it come to pass
So it's 6.59 on board the saucer
But it's 7.01 in Rushwood
I have never made it to an end
Can't forget my best day
And will the day else come be safe?
I guess I should
Na na na na
Na na, na, na
Na na, na, na,
Sna expect a turn
LIKE, COMMENT and SUBSCRIBE
If you're watching this for the first time
And hiçbir дizations
I probably did
In the time of chimpanzees, I was a yeti
Church air in my veins and my fur is getting shitty
While the plastic-ass pipes spray-paint the palmer head
Dog food vendors with the beefcake suit-a-fed
Kill all the pink boys and put it in neutral
Shit happens flamin' in the stag-meltin' capitals
Bobby's in Sherman, tired of fightin' the pipe
Got a couple motel rooms, sleep on the floor tonight
Someone keeps sayin' I'm a tanger to complain about
A round-trip ticket when it's all gonna end
Well, believe anything that ain't nice
When you got Rip and Striddle and the Jaina device
Just watch the face smilin' there in the dark
Burn all your money when they decimate the Taylor Park
Yo, I can't do this
Samper's a genius
I'm a subgenius, baby
Subgenius, baby
So why don't you kill me?
Oh, look at the pantyhose
Samper's a genius
I'm subgenius, baby
So why don't you kill me?
Flesh-fryin' sauces in a Bobby Ken nightmare
Stock fists poundin' down the door of the world
Cause one's gotta rant and the other's gotta brag
Bob's on some window-painting, Connie's on the rag
With the radio shows and the backstage blowjobs
Gangs on the radio shows, and the backstage blowjobs
Can't get invited to the first week
What's the fuck?
Burn to death like a Buddhist priest
Yes, men starving at the subgenius feast
And it's all for those who fulfill their fate
Trade the cash for the pills for the bobbies for the hate
And the time is a piece of crap
Falling down the toilet
With Bob's hand on the handle
Samper's a genius
I'm subgenius, baby
So why don't you kill me?
I'm a front if you lost
Samper's a genius
I'm subgenius, baby
So why don't you kill me?
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
Beautiful, beautiful.
Reverend Phineas Narco of NationalSynical.com
A song called Samper, Subgenius
And that's almost it for this hour of slack from the Church of the Subgenius
Subgenius, a huge thank you to everyone who's been here during this hour
Thanks to all of our contributors down through the ages, as well as to the radio stations that keep playing this maddening show.
If you want to be further in maddened, you can check out subgenius.com, which has everything, including links to everybody's websites and all the other subgenius shows and station events and legends and dogma and so on.
The music in the background for all these credits is from the band and the CD Mayan Ruins.
MySpace.com slash Mayan Ruins.
We shall close with, well, the last two things will be Lemur and Psychoskeletons.
But first, the oldest recording of this whole set.
One of the first Bob songs, Doctors for Bob, back in 1982 or so, performing live at some devival, probably in Dallas.
The Doctors for Bob theme.
We have your attention, please. There's about to be a fairly serious accident.
Doctors for Bob!
Everything real is not mine.
I've got the blues.
Sad damn pickup done run over my wife.
Doctors for Bob.
Everything real is his life.
He's got the blues.
Sad damn pickup done run over his wife.
Doctors for Bob.
We're Doctors, we're Doctors, we're Doctors for Bob!
Doctors, Doctors.
Doctors for Bob.
Doctors, had the blues, we're Doctors, with Tom.
we're doctors, we're doctors, who decide who does what.
We're doctors.
Heliopters make the road recognised, the road於 thediocese is safe now,
free the prison, no exceptions, we're doctors, we're doctors.
Doctors, Doctors for Bob.
Doctors for Bob!
Doctors, doctors, doctors, doctors,
destroy the Indianapolis, destroy the Indianapolis,
and go to France.
Destroy all minerals.
We in state determine the subject as a power,
and so do our government members.
We shall rule.
We shall be free.
We are the story of the people.
We are the one true church.
Doctors for Bob.
Everything's real in his pod.
He's got the blues,
because that damn pickup done run over his wife.
Doctors for Bob.
Bob?
I'll sing you a song about Bob.