we'll give you the countdown on retro sequence time bob you're looking good
i'll give you a mark 45
mark 30 seconds bob the retro warning is on roger bob leave your retro pack on through
your passover texas do you read roger five four three two one fire
i'm starting my re-entry now
how are you doing what's your general condition how are you feeling i'm feeling
i'm feeling fine condition is good
one last question go ahead bob go ahead who's the president of the united states
say again would you bob we don't think we got that say again
who is the president of the united states
sounds like you're asking who the president is that's precisely the question
so
i hope you said kennedy
run and get those drinks will you and tell mr foster make him strong will you do that
run girl run
that's a lush one isn't it full of fire too i'll let you i wouldn't know you wouldn't pity
oh my name is douglas smith the douglas smith the editor
X editor
why x
it's a long sad story you wouldn't be interested
oh but i would i would indeed you see you are the reason that i've journeyed to dansburg
right
creditor
no not yet anyhow
look at these dropouts they think they're having fun if we were agricultural workers the day would
already be half gone
are you all right south
anthony the room's going a bit spinny anyway you know justимость isn't something to brag about
and I think I might, um...
I've got some sick.
Can you get me out of here, Mark?
OK, OK.
What you need is some peace and quiet and some rest
and a cup of tea and some toast with peanut butter.
Oh, that sounds nice.
Hey, Soph, where are you going?
We're going to have a spleef.
Say hello to my little friend.
She's going to bed.
She doesn't want any more of your drugs.
Right, OK, that's it. Turn the music down.
You can stop smoking your drugs.
I'm making tea and toast for Sophie.
I'm putting on Radio 4.
Everything's normal.
I'm not really high on drugs,
so you can stop talking your nonsense on my time.
Well, what's the problem, man? Can't we just chill?
No, you can't. You've been chilling long enough.
This is reality calling.
But what about you and me? The bond?
There is no bond.
You're not a bad person, but I'm afraid to say you are a moron.
Now, pull your socks up and get your shoes on.
Come on, all of you.
Oh, man!
And listen.
While we're at it, there are...
The Soul Genius Hour of Swag.
Mr. Smith, he tried to kill me.
He tried to kill me.
We were in this car and he kept going faster and faster.
You get some rest, Bob.
Yeah, you, uh, sleep it off.
There's an explanation for everything.
You're all doped up and you're all so dead tired.
You sleep it off and I'll see what I can do about getting you a leave to get on home.
All right.
All along, I thought there was some kind of malfunction up there.
Fuel or propulsion or just communication.
Maybe the malfunction was closer to home.
Maybe it was right up here between my ears.
Look, you talk like that, you think like that, and you'll come around to believing it.
And that's stupid, Bob.
We're dealing with nine natural laws plus a whole string of imponderables.
And reasons are going to come out.
Legitimate, rational reasons.
Well, you just...
Just lie there and breathe through your nose.
Dream good. I'll see you later.
And I think everyone has room to grow.
But Bob is perfectly satisfied.
Everything you say is completely right.
And everything Bob says is completely wrong.
I've got dozens of items like that.
Men talked about who never existed.
Men who existed and not even mentioned.
Historical events that I know.
No, happened a certain way.
Somehow, according to the encyclopedia, didn't happen.
Or happened another way.
The things I remember are not delusions.
They're the legitimate recollections of things as I remember them.
But somehow, someway, this world seems to have turned upside down for me.
It's as if there were...
There were another world parallel to mine.
As if this world were almost a twin.
Except for some minor differences that happened somewhere along the line of evolution.
Bob, for the love of heaven...
Do you want to follow that line of reasoning?
Because if you do, there are a couple of built-in conditions that go along with it.
Conditions that I don't think you or anyone else wants to admit.
First and foremost, they happen to be that if all this is true...
If you suddenly uncovered a theory that there are two Earths, two sets of people, two histories...
And you somehow, inexplicably...
Inexplicably...
crossed over to the other dimension,
then you're not who we think you are.
And we're not who you think we are.
Meet Bob.
He's a typical American who works hard,
loves his family,
and has cheated on his tax return.
Life is good.
But lately, he's noticed some slight changes in his
power.
We only lost you for about six hours.
We had contact with you all the rest of the time.
I can't help that, sir.
During that six hours, I lived out a week.
Doing what?
Looking at our counterparts.
Looking at us.
Us?
Us, as we exist in a parallel world.
One that exists alongside, but which we can't see.
It's the world I stumbled into.
I don't know how.
Some kind of space-time continuum.
Some war page.
There's a doorway up there somewhere.
I know.
It exists.
Every now and then, I think it's possible for somebody to fall through it.
And I did.
How did you get back, Bob?
I don't even know that.
All I can remember is running toward the spacecraft.
And then, I was up there again.
And then I was back here.
Well,
Bob, I think, uh,
sleep on this for a little while, will you?
Why?
Well, because, uh, I think, uh, this may just be a delusion.
A delusion?
This was no delusion.
It was no dream.
I have no proof I told you that.
Mm-hmm.
Well, um, okay, Major.
We'll, uh, talk about it later.
Merry Christmas, Bob.
Off you later, Bob.
Oh, my goodness.
Yeah, love you, Slreb.
No, Bob!
They can't!
Tell me r-i-a-a
You that sue all the sites
You that tear down the torrents
You that fight dirty fights
You that haven't got gonads
You that cease and desist
I just want you to know
We are going to resist
You that never done nothing
But lawyers employ
To stop us from file sharing
You, your minions deploy
You put a suit in my mailbox
And you take me to court
Lest I pay you the millions
You try to extort
Like a wretch of old
Nesterizing your greed
Slithering through the courtroom
Sewing your blood
And your evil seed
You send out your subpoenas
To the children in schools
You're a cowardly pack
Of goddamn little fools
Let me ask you one question
Are the settlements good?
Does it make us buy CDs?
As you wish that it would
I think you will find
When your law bills come due
That they'll never be covered
By all the people you sue
And I hope you go broke
And you'll file bankruptcy
As your towers of power
Will fall apart
And your old business model
Sink into their deathbed
And you forever in hell
Give Justin Bieber a head
Praise Phineas Narco
And I hope you'll see you next time
Who did that?
Let us start by your learning
What are the dynamics of a crowd?
How do you move a mob, Mr. Fulmer?
How do you excite them?
How do you make them feel as one with you?
I don't even know how
Join them first, Mr. Fulmer
Join them?
Yes
When you speak to them
Speak to them as if you were a member of the mob
Speak to them in their language
On their level
Make their hate your hate
If they are poor
Talk to them of poverty
If they are afraid
Talk to them of their fears
And if they are angry, Mr. Fulmer
If they are angry
Give them objects for their anger
But most of all
The thing that is most of the essence, Mr. Fulmer
Is that you make this mob
An extension of yourself
Say to them
Things like
They call us hate-mongers
They say we're prejudiced
They say we're biased
They say we hate minorities
Minorities
Understand the term, neighbors
Should I tell you who are the minorities?
Should I tell you?
We
We are the minorities!
Neighbors
They call us hate-mongers
They say we're prejudiced
They say we're biased
They say that we hate the minorities!
They say we hate the minorities!
The minorities
Understand the term, neighbors
Shall I tell you who the minorities are?
We, we, we
We are the minorities!
Because patriotism
Is the minority
Because love of country
Subject is the minority
Because to live
In a free white America
Seems to be of a minority opinion
Well
If it's a minority opinion
That we have to survive
Then we are the minority!
And this minority
Will not stop
Until it is the majority!
This minority
Will not give up the fight!
This
Is the promise
And this
This is the legacy!
Thank you, Mr. Harper
And now, Mr. Harper
American Television
You ready?
Budapest is the capital of what European country?
Budapest is the capital of what European country Nathan has already locked in?
This might be a stupid question
I'm guessing it's probably going to be
Okay, like
I thought Europe was a country
I don't know what I'm doing
Kel
What?
Focus
Let's see
Buda
Budapest?
Let's talk about this
I've never even heard of that
Alright, here's your option
Like I'm listening to what you're saying
But I only hear what I want to
I mean, you could drop out with $10,000
See, I am just going to
Like I know they speak French there
Don't they?
Like I want to say
So what if you beep instead of getting back?
I'm talking about shit
What about stock oil?
I mean, can I just kiss the head or something?
I don't know
Look, I cant see
It would be tough if I had the brain
Do you think the French country is separate
What's the subject of the question?
Well
Um
Are they talking about foreheads?
In a way, the receding forehead of the American television guest.
And the prosthetic head, the one that Dave wears on the back.
The fine electric forehead of Dave.
And we must say, yes, Lonesome Cowboy Dave has just called the station.
He's the only one who's allowed to call the station.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The only one with the onerous plasticity and the right length of arm units per inch.
He's got a long one, all right.
Yep.
Now, we have to thank Reverend Sweetness McGee for that last little cut.
Ms. Budapest in the Big Ten 8 place.
Phineas Narco, Reverend Phineas Narco did that great song, Masters of RIAA.
And Phineas is with NASCAR.
National Cynical Radio, nationalcynical.com.
And his show, in fact, streams, I think, every Sunday night right after Hour of Slack.
But not on insert station named here.
You could, if you looked at alt.slack or scrubgenius or subgenius.com radio page,
you might find links to that streaming where you could go straight to
National Cynical Radio.
Nationalcynical.com.
The collages were by The Large, except for the Twilight Zone or Toilet Zone bits, as we call them,
which were edited a bit by me.
And yes, that was Dennis Hopper ranting Hitler style from a Twilight Zone.
And we'll hear more of that surprisingly familiar sounding ranting.
Even though that Twilight Zone, about like a little Hitler,
a little fascist Nazi in the U.S.
That Twilight Zone's from 1963.
And yet it sounds just like Hitler in 1940-something.
And yet it also sounds just like what you hear on your AM radio dial here in the year of 2010.
40 years after Dennis Hopper was doing a satire on Hitler.
It sounds just like what you hear on the radio today.
And we will be hearing more of that.
Isn't it unusual that it's 80 years after the radio programs of such people as Father Coughlin,
who preached a form of American Nazism, and the seven nasty no-no's of propaganda.
And it's only been a scant, I don't know how many years, but it's like around 20 years.
I look a scant at them.
You look at scantily clad.
But yeah, yeah, it's like nothing has changed.
But Dave, you know, before the radio and the TV,
why they were rantin' the same way 500 years ago, thousand, 10,000 years ago.
First, I was a damned Hitler.
Some guy in Sumeria was standing on top of the temple going,
Are we going to allow these foreigners to enter our country and taint our Sumerian culture?
Will they stop us from our beloved freedoms of disfiguring women and boogering little boys?
Will they stomp on our freedom?
No, because we are the minorities.
And of course, we subgeniuses have learned a lot from these demigogs and demigods,
demitasses of very, very strong coffee.
It is a rhetoric-based cult.
And these policies and usages and slang terminologies brought by the aliens to us
and transmitted directly into our forebrains and exciting the pineal gland gives us a little
bit more juice than the other Socratic clubfoot, you know, arguing is like,
I will present the facts.
We don't have to present facts.
I wanted to play some of this where after you called in so you could hear more of the Dennis Hopper.
I mean, I love the fact that it's Dennis Hopper.
It's only about, what, four years before Easy Rider.
Here, let's see.
Oh, is he cute, too?
Oh, my goodness.
I remember back then Robert Duvall had a bunch of hair.
Yeah.
Yes, we saw him in a Twilight Zone where he played a nerdy little fellow who fell in love with a female doll in a dollhouse in a museum.
And of course, it being a Twilight Zone at the end of it, there he was, a little doll in the museum.
That's in every Twilight Zone.
You find out that you are a doll.
So, we want to welcome you to this line of dialogue.
Maybe we should have external
Or even innate quantitative analysis.
He was never a ghost but he стоит still and thinks he knows something and feels like he knows something and he's frozen.
Why did Mr.
One minute of Dennis Hopper playing an early teabagger on the Twilight Zone.
I am.
Like, I'm listening to what you're saying, but I only hear what I want to hear.
I understand, honey.
I understand.
Thank you, Miss Budapest.
Come on, Dennis.
Come on up.
Very stupendous.
Like, I'm listening to what you're saying, but I only hear what I want to hear.
Examine the phenomenon of foreign control.
You examine it, and you will note with absolute clarity that the lines lead directly to...
The Muslimics.
Palestine.
They lead directly to Africa.
And the Muslimics.
They lead directly to the Vatican.
The Vatican.
Some genius stark fist temple launch.
So, so, there we are.
There it is.
There is a conspiracy.
There is an insidious, enveloping conspiracy.
A conspiracy personified by the yellow man, by the black man, and by foreigners who come
in and infiltrate into our economic structure.
The slack man.
Oh, there come a warning.
Yes, there will.
There will come a warning.
When these men have taken over your home, they've taken over your daughters, and they'll
be sitting right there on your doorstep.
If anybody's sitting on your doorstep, buddy, he's a man in a white coat.
You better just go with him quietly.
You think that's pretty funny, don't you?
They chopped off all my hair.
They cut my nose in a...
Trust that.
This look will hopefully get me more vag in the future.
I think we can get more vag in the future.
Then they give you a bob.
They gave her a bob.
They cut off her hair, and they gave her a bob.
And that's what they're going to do to you, my friend.
And then she got more vag?
If you don't hang on to your American freedoms.
Well, how about that—
That would be a hell of a bob cut, wouldn't it?
To have all our freedoms removed.
No slack whatsoever.
So ever.
That would be.
I'm sorry.
Well, I've read several times on the Internet today that we already have no freedoms at all.
None.
They have the freedom to say that much.
But that's it.
It's the last freedom.
This guy was heaping as as as I as the one guy said, if it wasn't for the liberals blaming others for all their problems, I wouldn't have any problems.
It's all the liberals fought for blaming other people for all their problems.
So it's just too confusing to even think about.
If if with if if everything's all mottled and tarled up, everything's a lie concealed in an enigma shrouded in a of disinformation.
Unfortunately, it makes me pee, Stan.
It makes me pee in angst, nausea as I bark to the wind.
I scream out dirty names and I don't even know what they mean.
I got to stop watching and listen to my median.
I don't feel like that young children ought to be exposed to that stuff.
And neither do I.
I think I think everybody's cerebral cortex needs to be exposed to truth, justice in the American way.
I don't mean specifically in that order, but I think that there needs to be something done or something needs to be.
I'm sorry.
There needs to be something dumb.
Oh, wait.
There you go.
I think they beat us to it.
The church of the subgenius wasn't dumb enough.
Just like my flaccid unit.
It will not respond.
That's when you try and teach something something and it refuses to admit or decipher.
So I got a mind of its own.
Don't you?
Yep.
A kind of mess of ganglion of all rodded and become.
I don't know.
This peptic and septic and.
When your brain is rotten, you got some problems.
Well, but how do you know?
See, how do you know when your brain's gotten all rotted?
Well, my third nostril is how I know I can smell it.
There's a lot of people out there with rotten brains who want to tell everybody else that they're the only ones whose brains aren't rotten.
You won't hear me saying I don't have a rotten brain that proves my brain might not be rotten.
See, because I'm still suspecting.
Of myself.
Could my brain be fully rotted yet?
Double check every minute.
And but again, how do you know?
How do you know when you've gone as crazy as the next guy?
Keep a log, baby.
Maybe keep a diary with a lot of actually that makes it worse.
My experience with that is that the more crazier they are, the more detailed of a diary they keep of everything.
Yeah.
As if you could to control.
You see.
Yeah.
Well, control what is uncontrollable.
Indeed, the circumstances engulfing a person like that who has to write down every.
Wait a minute.
Let me get.
Let me take notes.
Yeah.
I can't.
This music in the background is.
I'm not sure how to pronounce this guy's name.
Joseph Mestres or Mestres.
An album called Quadrini.
Mr.
Sister gave it to us.
With a bunch of other.
Really weird stuff from his collection.
Listen to that.
Avant.
Yeah, it's Avant.
This is the sound of the late 1960s.
You're tripping out on LSD.
You're tripping out.
Your favorite.
Tune on.
Turn out.
Tina.
Turn on.
Tenant.
I don't want it to get even worse.
I'm sorry.
There we go.
We can make it even more tripped out.
Screwy.
Crazy in the background.
The only problem.
There's a вс a gy ïn show we play four different
soundtracks in the background at once.
The thing that's wrong with a lot of these tone,
tone poems of the late 60s and late 50s or late 50s
all the way through the late 60s and even include
thing all the way up to the Reformation period
of people like glass and so forth who we can see
so.
市 car lives together so to speak.
rather than a random possibility with a tone poem.
And what we find is...
But anyway, it's like you hit the piano,
like get five different keys at one time,
and then you go...
Then you go...
Like that, three times.
You can be in Frank Zappa's band.
Oh, he's dead.
Oh, shucks.
Well, you know, in the Church of the Subgenius,
or at least in our early books,
we promoted something called anti-music.
And to tell the truth, we were kidding.
We didn't think anybody would take us up on it.
And much to our horror,
all these anti-music doctor bands formed,
and they would expect to play at our shows.
And they did.
Whether we said okay or not,
I can remember bands setting up right on the floor of the theater
and just making as much horrible noise as they possibly could,
deliberately not...
Playing an instrument that knew how to play.
I've found that I've been guilty, but only when I was getting paid.
When I was in doctor bands, I got paid at least $5.
Which in those days, I mean, $5, you could buy a house for that in 1980.
Well, yeah.
That's how I got to where I am today.
Bringing new meaning to the word dissonance.
Mortgages, houses, $5 houses.
Pick them up, sell them, get rid of them.
Flip them, flip them.
Move them.
Now, talk about mysterious audio material.
What's in the background now came to us on cassette tape.
Remember those?
I do.
Yeah, they had moving parts.
It's completely different from a CD.
And about a month ago, we got a cassette in the mail.
Or cassette.
A cassette.
As my mother would say, yes.
It was in true subgenius fashion.
It sounded like this.
And it wasn't labeled at all.
It came from...
It came from Berea, Kentucky.
And I guess I have a street address, but there's no name.
And there was nothing written on the cassette.
It just had some random cutout from a magazine illustration, you know, stuck onto the cassette.
It was just a...
That's the way all of the subgenius cassettes looked in the 80s and 90s.
And then we got used to getting CDs.
They emailed me MP3s, you know, or we download stuff or whatnot.
It was just refreshing to get a CD.
I mean, a tape.
Well, two important things to consider are that it was Kentucky.
And if it's rural Kentucky, it could have taken 20 years to get here.
That's one thing.
Indeed.
And also, you know how some people marry each other in the family there for a while?
He might be one of those people that assumes that he is sending you an actual love song with lyrics and a structure.
Well, it has many love songs with such things.
But not for long.
So you can kind of hear him in the background along with somebody skinning a fish or something.
Yeah.
That's art, man.
Skinning a fish is art.
Well, if it's mixed with a sweet love song, then I guess that's the world of collage.
I was planning to do a collage-oriented show soon.
And we're accidentally doing it now.
And isn't that the nature of collage?
It's still a wonderful...
It's still art, despite its many, many drawbacks and its limitations.
But we have to conclude that there's a lot better crap out there in the slimy little midst of the average person sitting behind you in the bus ready to vomit
than there are in the halls of academia and the big boys in the biz spelled B-I-Z with a capital Z, I think.
We've seen this before.
We have seen...
We've seen this...
Actually, I'm going to play some more of that.
Let's hear Dennis Hopper some more.
Okay, this is real moralistical.
Okay, I'll turn down that music.
I'll turn up that music.
Friends and neighbors and co-fighters did not die in vain.
They stilled his great heart.
But they could not.
Stifle his memory.
Or his flatulation.
They could not obliterate his courage.
Or his peace.
They could not wipe away his honor.
Or his...
He lives in you, and he lives in me.
He lives deep in the gut of every human being who wants to see the United States of America be free.
That's not the third.
We're overdue.
I've seen it before.
I've seen it all before.
That was another time, Mr. Gantz.
Another place.
Another kind of people.
That doesn't go here.
That's what we said, too.
That's what we said.
They were brown scum.
Temporary insanity.
Part of the passing scene.
They were being too monstrous to be real.
So, we ignored them.
Or laughed at them.
Because we couldn't believe that there were enough insane people to walk alongside of them.
Then one morning, the country woke up from an uneasy sleep.
And there was no more laughter.
The wild animals had changed places with us in the cage.
We simply can't let it happen again.
It can't happen here at all.
Do you want your homes infected with the vermin from foreign shores?
No!
Do you want a bunch of mongrels?
Big boys.
To come over here.
Keep them coming.
What is this one here?
The new model?
A 1963 Führer right off the assembly line?
For this one is not too new.
He's not too fresh.
This one is nothing but a cheap copy.
Adnan.
Stop.
That's us.
A cheap.
Nothing but a cheap copy of the original.
A ranta.
You will never.
You cannot stand in the Führer.
You will not be able to fit in your boots because your feet are far too small.
You will...no.
No.
It's a cheap JPEG.
All fuzzy around the edges.
Just if extremely.
Will you let the pink boys come and steal away all of your schlag?
Yeah they spit on us.
Don't you love your schlag?
Like we're swimming in the water without underpants.
They mark us and put extreme gravy on our pants.
places. It's tiring,
but it's no longer available.
And we hiled
writing Sir Palin's face.
I don't mean to get political, kids,
but let's face it,
in today's society,
we see an encroaching,
ever more threatening
brown shirtism. Notice
I had an R in that word
shirt. I could have left
it out.
And if we do not
raise our voices
in a singing
choir of
Bob is here to save us,
then surely he will not save us,
and we will all be destroyed and dragged down
into the cesspool
of cable television
and modern
FM and AM radio
and YouTube
and Facebook,
MySpace, all of that.
Sick, sick, sick
eating away at
the
body politic and the mind
of the subgeniuses.
Yeah, boy, I wish Father Joe Mama
was here. He could really do that.
He could not only
mimic Hitler's rants
in German, but he could
also imitate
Sir Alec Guinness
playing Hitler in the last days of
Hitler, which was the best.
Talk about oblique.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, it was easier to understand
the
, the American or the British actor
playing Hitler than it was to understand
Hitler himself.
Well, of course, because
Nix des Spackens
Deutschlandlander.
But, boy, I mean,
to be able to
summate the entire movie
in a few small erroneous moves,
you know, a couple
kind of almost
below the belt type of things,
and he expects to have, what,
a modicum of freedom and
immortality at the same time?
I mean, come on.
There was only one Fuhrer.
I mean, and there always only will be one Fuhrer,
just like Wagner.
There were always fewer Fuhrers.
Nobody will ever write librettos like Wagner.
I remember back in the days
before I changed my accent,
before I took the pills
and the treatments in Argentina
to maintain the youth.
I remember
at the swimming pool
and I was invited.
It was Tuesday.
The wind,
it was...
That's a weird wind, Dave.
Break, wind, break,
and crack, cheeks crack.
Copyright Fireside Theater, 1973.
Oh, no!
Creeping!
Nazism!
Or is it subgeniusism?
Sometimes it's hard to tell the difference.
Boy, the people that we kick out of the
subgenius-only club,
they just, they really feel offended.
I can tell.
They're still in the
anything-goes club.
I only did it because I thought it was fun.
Where they scream and holler at us subgeniuses
from outside of our cage, you see.
We are safe within our
our cage, our bars.
You see,
I'm not trapped in here with you.
You're trapped in here with me.
We have physically created,
we have used our own environment.
We have used our hands and our feet
to make it.
As the gods would make it.
We are as the gods.
The gods are naked
and the dogs are howling.
If only it were the other way around.
If only the gods were howling
and the dogs were naked.
I love a naked dog.
They look so different when they're shaved.
When they have no hair at all.
Or when they're soaking wet.
And they smell so wonderful.
A wet dog?
Oh, yes.
Would you let them take away our freedom
to sniff a wet dog, my friend?
That which is most valuable
to the subgenius heart?
To our fatherland?
Would you let them take away
our wet dog smell?
Mach schnell
with der dog smell.
Jawohl.
It's the only kinakree, you know.
It's the big J.
Jawohl.
You know, you can only give it the old jawohl.
When was the last time you had your big
steaming hot jawohl of wolfberry and chili?
Well, that's too long.
How about some whooping chili
made by Grandma Maxine and her onerous pad?
It was horrible.
I dreamed I was on a suitcase
and I, well, it was like a little room
but I could tell it was horrible.
It was a suitcase
and there was a little compartment
filled with pipes
and I, well, I thought maybe
I could use one of the pipes
to gain an exit
from the suitcase.
So, what I, well,
the first thing that came to my mind
was...
You see, from that day forth
it seemed only by great effort
as of gymnastics
and only under the immediate stimulation
of the...
drug
that I was able to wear
the countenance of Stan.
At all hours of the day and night
I would be taken
with the premonitory shudder.
Above all, if I slept
even dozed for a moment in my chair
it was always as Doug
that I awakened
under the strain of this continually impending doom
and by the sleeplessness
to which I now condemn myself
yea, even beyond what I thought possible to man
I became in my own person
a creature eaten up
and emptied by fever
languidly weak
both in body and mind
and solely occupied by one thought
the horror of my other self.
But when I slept
or when the virtue of the medicine wore off
I would leap almost without transition
for the pangs of transformation
grew daily less marked
into the possession of a fancy
brimming with images of terror
a soul boiling with causeless hatreds
and a body that seemed not strong enough
to contain the raging energies of life
the powers of the world.
the powers of Doug Smith
seemed to have grown
with the sickliness of Ivan Stang.
But now Dave, couldn't you find your way
through the pipes to the luggage?
I course could
but then I had to stop
and listen to heckle and jekyll
But the pipe is the path to life
and truth
and power
power
and pleasure
pleasure
pleasure beyond your wildest dreams
and more
will you choose pleasure
or will you plunge into the pool of
Koonvasner?
I mean Koonvasner!
references in dirty language in Dutch
or whatever there is in there
you think some, some
the Ministry of Information
is not going to hear that?
oh now get this
here's what our critics say about us
oh turn that down
turn this up
the problem he was thus debating
as he walked was one of a class
that is rarely solved
"'Reverend Stang was pale and dwarfish.
"'He gave an impression of deformity without any nameable malformation.
"'He had a displeasing smile.
"'He had borne himself to the lawyers
"'with a sort of murderous mixture of timidity and boldness,
"'and he spoke with a husky whispering and somewhat broken voice.
"'All these were points against him,
"'but not all of these together could explain the hitherto unknown disgust,
"'loathing and fear with which Mr. Smith regarded him.
"'There must be something else,' said the perplexed gentleman.
"'There is something more if I could but find a name for it.
"'God bless me, the man seems hardly human.
"'Something troglodytic, shall we say?'
"'Hmm. Oof! Oof!'
"'It's that naked dog again.
"'Stinks.'
"'Well, I don't like the way Robert Louis Stevenson
"'compares us to a bunch of, uh,
"'half-animal beings.
"'I mean, what right does he have as an erudite but dead person?'
It's true. I was reading from the book, uh,
uh, Mr. Hyde and Reverend Seek.
Reverend Seek. Yes.
I thought it was Jekyll and Jekyll, but I would prefer to Seek.
No, this was the remake.
This wasn't the Frederick March version.
This was the Spencer Tracy version.
Oh, jeez, man.
You know, there were, uh, to date,
there have been 126 movie versions
of documentaries.
Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde.
The Strange Case of Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde, actually,
is the full title.
Um, yes.
And most of them suck.
Whoo!
Actually, the Frederick March one in 1931 is great.
It's really quite well done.
He is scary because he looks so daddy-like to begin with,
and then all of a sudden he has those big choppers.
Yeah.
And that weird, like, you know,
manic smile that's...
Oh, if only you could see the imitation I'm doing right now.
He jerks and jiggles around.
We just saw that movie.
And he, he, it really is a great acting job.
Oh, get this.
Okay, I think it was M...
Could have been MGM anyway.
The studio that made the 1931 Jekyll and Hyde.
Ten years later, they remade it with Spencer Tracy.
Well, for some reason, they decided that
in order to do it again ten years later,
they had to destroy all existing prints of the 1931 movie.
Now, is that conspiracy executive thinking or what?
Mm-hmm.
And so for the longest time,
there wasn't a really good copy of the full 31 version,
plus the Hays...
It was done before the Hays Code.
So the versions that we saw on television
when we were little children in the 60s and 70s
had eight minutes of hot stuff cut out
with Miriam Hopkins,
who was the director of the movie,
as a prostitute.
Sizzling.
Ooh, majorly.
Yeah.
Yeah, movies were actually a lot dirtier before 1932 or so,
and then they became gradually more filthy and dirty
until we now end up with art films
like Antichrist by Lars van Trieg,
or whatever his, however you say his name.
I did notice a difference in the...
The human centipede, which I won't even watch.
It is...
Well, I...
I did skim through it.
I looked at the good parts.
More now, Dave.
They were really bad.
Really bad.
The human centipede.
Yes, Dave.
It's a...
It's a horror movie about a mad doctor.
Mad?
Do you call him mad?
What, a madman?
Suture?
People?
Mouth to butt?
In a series?
In a chain?
Making a, yes, human centipede.
That's the subject of a movie made last year.
How about that?
Well, I would not say he was...
Not per se.
Any more than any other top-grade scientist or politician.
At the very top.
The cream of the crop.
Once they reach that level, they're all a little bit...
Screwy.
Are mad scientists truly mad?
Or are they just a little bit ticked off?
But these...
Crazy.
These philosophers, whose hands seemed only made to dabble in dirt,
and their eyes to pour over the microscope or crucible,
have indeed performed miracles.
They penetrate into the recesses of nature
and show how she works in her hiding places.
They ascend into the heavens,
and they have discovered how the blood circulates
and the nature of the air we breathe.
They've acquired new and almost unlimited power,
and they can command the thunders of heaven,
mimic the earthquake,
and even mock...
the invisible world with its own shadows.
And that's why I smoke Kool's.
That's a manly cigarette.
For those of you out there that haven't really discovered existentialism,
you'll notice the rich, flavorful smoke of Kool.
Caps it off like an evening in the bathroom.
And for those out there that enjoy having shortening with the rest of the food,
time to climb aboard with Kool's.
I like Kool's.
I don't...
I can't...
And...
What's the matter?
Don't you want to be cool?
Afraid your mom's gonna find out?
Come on!
Light up!
Everybody's doing it!
Here, take the matches and set your hair on fire.
And we'll smoke your head!
Yeah!
I don't know, eh?
Come on, you wanna?
It's the Bulgarian folk music!
Oh!
They're blowing up my backyard again.
What happens if I put on this music up here?
This is a whole nother disc.
Ooh.
Oh, this is Sid Redlin of Boron Nuzzle.
We met them in Detroit at the Detroit Revival.
Is this like Stang Girl Talk or something?
No.
Well, you'll be...
No, it's more like Girl Stang Talk.
Oh, Girl Stang Talk.
Um...
Oh.
It was indeed with these feelings that I began the creation of a human being.
No one can conceive the variety of feelings which bore me onwards like a hurricane in the first enthusiasm of success.
But who can conceive of the horrors of my secret toil as I dabbled among the unhallowed damps of the grave?
Or tortured the living animals to animate the lifeless clay?
Yeah, I see.
I started reading Frankenstein...
Mary, Mary...
...by that teenage girl.
Oh, and Dave.
Now, this is interesting little synchronicity.
I was starting to read Frankenstein.
I mentioned that to my...
one of our students.
Let's call him Reverend Gavin, who happens to be on the Isle of Wight.
We were chatting in my online course.
And I mentioned I was reading Frankenstein and all these old books because the wordage is cooler...
...than it is in the comic books that I usually read.
And he said, did you happen to ever see that movie called Gothic?
Which is Ken Russell's 1986 film about Mary Shelley and Percy Shelley and Lord Byron and their libertine friends writing Frankenstein.
I said, no, I haven't seen that movie.
I sort of wanted to.
And I looked at my collection.
I couldn't find it.
Within 24 hours, I was standing at Dave's supermarket.
Your supermarket, Dave.
It certainly is.
And I happened to glance at the $1 DVDs that they have now sitting next to the National Enquirers.
It certainly are.
And there it was.
There was Gothic by Ken Russell for a buck.
And we got what we paid for because the middle of it was real choppy and hard to watch.
But it didn't matter because the movie is god awful.
And the first...
When the music started on the credits, I said, I can tell this music was done by one guy with a computer.
And then the credits said, music by Thomas Dolby.
And boy, back in the late 80s, it certainly sounded like it too.
They deafened him with bad film.
It was awful, actually.
The score was awful.
The movie was awful.
They were on laudanum.
The characters were on laudanum all the time.
And then everything got weird.
And it was like weird.
Real weird.
There's weird butlers and weird hunchbacks and weird little devil guys and weird dead guys and weird weather and weird music and weird people and weird sex.
And then it turned out it was all a dream.
It was all a dream?
Yeah, that was the climax of the movie.
It got weirder and weirder.
And then Mary Shelley woke up.
And Mary Shelley woke up and woke her eyes or something?
Yeah, she woke up and wrote Franken...
Stein.
Oh, what a tragic ploy to employ.
Franken-Einstein.
And then the next day, Nenslo, the great Nenslo sent me a piece of artwork called Frank Ein Bob.
And it was a merging of the faces of J.R. Bob Dobbs, Albert Einstein, and the Frankenstein monster.
And no one can see that picture except on Facebook.
And I'm not on Facebook.
So I can't see nothing.
I can't see...
Well, I can just tell you that in the supermarket the other day, my son...
I was wearing a hood.
And I was wearing a Bob hood, as a matter of fact.
A Bob sweatshirt hood.
And my son noticed that I looked like Marty Feldman in Young Frankenstein.
That's really insulting.
I would feel awful.
I feel bad, man.
I would feel really bad about that.
Your son has a great imagination.
That's all I can say.
Let's see.
We're coming up on the end of this hour of Slack number 1,286.
There's that mecha dog again.
Did you hear that?
Mm-hmm.
Shaved down to the very nubs.
Boy, this show has had some darned weird background music, if you don't mind my using strong language.
Not at all.
Go right ahead.
Can you say a second of that background music, everything you played?
You can even say gosh darn if you want to.
Well, let's see.
We have the Sid Redlin on right now.
To mess with your head.
Oh, and speaking of heads, the Subgenius bathroom is at subgenius.com.
That's the dump, the latrine, so to speak, where it all goes in and doesn't have to come out.
Fireside Theater, 1984.
By the way, Sid Redlin has permanent eyeglasses that he has made for himself with one lens being used.
One being perfectly round and the other one being perfectly square.
And the lens material on the right eye is red and on the left is blue.
Mm-hmm.
He's in another world all the time.
All the time.
Creating virtual experience.
But if he goes to a 3D movie, he's completely blind unless he switches the glasses.
He has to reverse them.
So he must have kind of a very loose middle part to fit over the nose, so it can be either up or down.
Depending on which way.
Right.
And the way to go is subgenius.com if you want to learn more about all the awful things that we've discussed and far, far worse.
All the awful things go all the way to subgenius.com.
Do it now or, um...
Or don't.
We don't really care whether you're saved or not.
We really don't even care.
Dave, I'm going to fade you out very soon now.
Okay.
I'm going to play one weird little song here at the end called It Is What It Is by Rainbow.
And then a couple of little TZ clips that I really want to end the show with.
And don't believe in our Dave in a pile of Jell-O and cotter pins.
Oh, you know the guy who discovered that Bob always leaves cotter pins and Jell-O behind him wherever he goes?
The guy who discovered that fact, Reverend John Stakely, died last week.
Aww.
I hadn't talked to him in 40 years.
But the Jell-O and cotter pins live on.
I went to high school with him.
Isn't that funny?
I guess there won't be another armor book.
Anyway, friends, thank you.
And, uh, I think we're going to go good nighty-night here.
Good night to everyone.
It's been such a wonderful, wonderful evening trying to accept what we need to accept to learn what we must all be fighting for.
Oh, Dave faded himself out.
Yeah ...
How'd you do that?
It is what it is, it-
What's...
I-T-I-S
What is I is
It is what it is
What is what it is
I-T-I-S
What is...
Right now, Yes We Are podcast is
brought to you by
the Los Angeles
Siouxーム
Espy
ズ
is
It is what it is, what it is, what it is, what it is.
I think I am what's what it is.
What it is what what it is i T is What
What it is.
It is what it is.
You've made a terrible mistake.
I made out of steel.
You understand that I made out of steel?
Mr. Smith.
Jack.
Oh, Jack.
You're all right.
Jack, Mr. Smith, he tried to kill me.
He tried to kill me.
I know.
We were in this car, and he kept going faster and faster,
and there was this other car coming at us,
and he headed straight for that car.
It's all right now.
It's all over.
He was sitting right there next to me,
and then he was gone.
What's going on?
What happened?
Tell me.
Listen to this.
Mr. Douglas Smith,
former star reporter and chief line-of-type operator for the Courier,
resigned his position and left Dansburg for his home at 11.29 this evening.
His contract with Mr. Douglas Smith declared null and void
owing to Mr. Winters' incomplete understanding of the terms of the document.
Contract?
What contract?
It means that he's gone.
Gone?
And he won't be back.
Doug, will you please explain this?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'll tell you.
Maybe tomorrow.
Right now, let's get out of here.
He's gone.
Exit the infernal machine.
And with it his satanic majesty, Lucifer, Prince of Darkness,
otherwise known as Mr. Smith.
He's gone, but not for good.
That wouldn't be like him.
He's gone for bad.
And he might be back,
with another ticket to the Twilight Zone.