Due to some violent content, parental discretion is advised.
Are mutants dangerous?
Somebody ought to belt you in the mouth.
Friction, what is friction?
You turned me into a criminal.
Believe me, Ovaltine's got what it takes to help you be a leader in your gang.
You filthy criminals.
I'm gonna take this right foot, and I'm gonna whop you on that side of your face.
And you wanna know something?
There's not a damn thing you're gonna be able to do about it.
Friction is the rub-a-dub-dub-dub-dub.
I grabbed a dog, and I took him, and I kicked the shit out of him.
Be careful, duck man.
Well, boys, I reckon this is it.
Nuclear combat, toe-to-toe with the Ruskies.
And I'm the new minister in charge of religious genocide.
And the rub-a-dub-dub-dub-dub-dub is friction at work.
I've got a good mind to join a club and beat you over the head with it.
And now, the subgenius hour of SWAC.
SWAC
Let's rock.
Now, shrunken heads for all occasions.
Collect them, swap them, give them to your witch doctor friends.
Something's happened to my brain. It's all dried up.
It even vibrates.
It was terrible. It was just terrible.
I'll never get over it as long as I live.
You on drugs?
You'd be ashamed of yourself.
Sounds like it's having a hallucinogenic effect.
Not like a drug which is harmful and wrong and just say no, kids.
But spacey, nonetheless.
I won't go schizoid.
Will I?
We'll, uh, we'll talk to Bob.
Thank you, Mr. Know-it-all!
If I were you, Mrs. Gray, I'd get out of here while you still got time.
A few days will put you in Fort Dobbs.
You'll be safe there.
In 182101...
War was beginning.
What happened?
Somebody set up us the bomb!
We're getting signal.
What?
Main screen, turn on!
It's you!
How are you, gentlemen?
All your days are belong to us.
You are on the way to destruction.
What do you say?
You have no choice to survive in your time.
Ha ha ha.
Captain!
Take off every zig.
You know what you're doing.
Move zig!
For grave justice!
Remorse for what?
You people have done everything in the world to me.
Doesn't that give me equal right?
I can do anything I want to you people at any time I want to.
Because that's what you've done to me.
If you spit in my face and smack me in the mouth and throw me in solitary confinement for nothing,
what do you think is going to happen when I get out of here?
Maybe I haven't done enough.
I might be ashamed of that for not doing enough.
For not giving enough.
For not being more perceptive.
For not being aware enough.
For not understanding.
For being stupid.
Maybe I should have killed four or five hundred people.
Then I would have felt better.
Then I would have felt like I really offered society something.
You've got it stuck in your brain that I murdered somebody.
What do you want to call me a murderer for?
I've never killed anyone.
I don't need to kill anyone.
I think it.
I have it here.
Uh, this street is my world.
I don't, uh, I don't pretend to go uptown and be anything fancy.
I can, but I find more real in the world that I'm in than I do the tinsel.
And the real world is the one I have to deal with every day, you know.
Uh, believe me, if I started murdering people, there'd be none of you left.
Not in any way
Pollution.
It's a Γ newipp deputy league or a athlete.
My boat, heyardr.
You got shit uh?
A Yukon Eskimo song.
Dear friends, bold surrealism from the Or Kill Me Radio broadcasts from the last X Day Drill.
Praise Reverend DJ Schaefer and Reverend Chuglug and everybody else involved in that.
And praise Reverend Patrick Fulkherty for recording it all and sending us CDs of that.
Friends, this show is going to involve a lot of bold surrealism from other people's collections.
Dr. Philodrum had also sent me a CD compilation of his favorite novelty tunes, which includes a bunch of novelty rap.
And I've plumbed that CD.
And Reverend Christopher Lee recorded The Residence live in Chicago recently.
We've got lots of that too.
To extract.
Oh, and collage material from Dr. Artemiya Salina.
Downloaded from alt.binaries.slack.
And I should mention for the Cleveland area listeners and so forth, there's a devival coming up.
May 12th.
Subgenius Devival at the Euclid Tavern.
Friends, starring Einstein's Secret Orchestra, yours truly preaching.
And Saint Anne and Helena Handbasket.
Friends, it's what Bob wants.
To help carry on our important work, I want you to join the secret squadron.
I want your blood.
And I want your souls.
And I want them both right now.
I want you to get up now.
I want all of you to get up out of your chairs.
Yes.
I want you to get up right now and go to the window, open it, and stick your head out and yell,
I'm as mad as hell and I'm not going to take this anymore!
Until next week, keep your head on tight.
Back to when it's sack and saddle.
We'll be down at the Grog Shop Saturday night.
Rocking out with the Cobra Verde.
May 12th.
Down at the Euclid Tavern.
Yes, sir.
River Nile and Stag.
And Saint Anne and Helena Handbasket.
We'll be in the Euclid Tavern.
May 12th.
So if you need me, have some courtesy.
Have some sympathy.
Have some taste.
It's all you well-earned volunteers.
All right, there you go.
So good.
All right.
Get down.
Come to my watch and it came on one.
So did I.
To my watch and it said two, three, four.
Time sure flies when you're fucking.
To my watch and it was going on five.
Well, the more the merrier.
To my watch and it was six, six, six.
Devil cock.
Great band.
Frog.
To my watch and it was seven on the head.
Continuing sound of one of the most precious voices.
Years.
DJ Chugga Chugga taking over for the late night radio program show.
To my watch and it was eight, nine, nine.
The number to call for the sperm overdose hotline.
To my watch and it was ten, eleven, twelve.
Hey, what time is it?
Me shall.
Oh, right.
My bell.
Knock on Wolverine.
Booyah, Brad.
To my watch and it was thirteen to fourteen.
That's how I like them.
That's right.
We have some horny DJs up here at this station.
Very horny DJs.
That's all right.
We don't know it yet.
And now.
Oh.
I want to check this out.
I'm going to have to make one of these calls.
Let me just look at this.
Okay.
I have a phone number.
I don't know what the phone number is.
I'll just look at this.
Thank you.
Mr. Smith, it would behold you to stay in your room until you are called either by a major studio, Branson, Missouri, or God.
You're missing the most important thing in your life.
That is your dear friend and talent, former star, Jonathan Winters.
Righter side? Two words, who cares? You know, we're only visitors.
Bye-bye, and remember the Prince of Darkness is with us 24 hours a day.
Regardless of light, the Prince of Darkness can deal with it.
Heavy.
Mutilated monkeys' meat, little birdies' dirty feet, it's all mixed up with all-purpose porpoise pus.
I made it just for you.
Yeah!
It's great green gobs of greasy, grimy gold forgotten.
It's mutilated monkeys' meat, little birdies' dirty feet, it's all mixed up with all-purpose porpoise pus.
I made it just for you.
Great green gobs of greasy, grimy gold forgotten.
Mutilated monkeys with little birdies dirty feet
All mixed up with all birdies for this bus
And I made it just for you
I am breaking gods up, racing, crying, cold for dust
Mutilated monkeys with little birdies dirty feet
All mixed up with all birdies for this bus
And I forgot my spoon, but I got my straw
The missile knows where it is at all times
It knows this because it knows where it isn't
By subtracting where it is from where it isn't
Or where it isn't from where it is, whichever is greater
It obtains a difference or deviation
The guidance subsystem uses deviations to generate
Corrections to the missile
It has interactive commands to drive the missile from a position where it is
To a position where it isn't
And arriving at a position where it wasn't, it now is
Consequently, the position where it is
Is now the position that it wasn't
And it follows that the position that it was
Is now the position that it isn't
Come and kill that boy now
Come get some
I am flying like flying
And she dares not x- одну
It isarl
I am flying like flying
Like flying and underlying water
guitar solo
This is J.B. Smith.
Thanks for calling. Please leave a message
for me and the nature of your call.
Thank you.
Well, the nature of the call is
what to do about
the deficit. I mean,
I can't handle all this.
I mean, the little
guys, people like yourself,
are going to have to take responsibility
here. You're going to have
to be bitten into, as it
were. And I'm sorry
to see that. I know what
it's like. I've been bitten into
several times in the past.
Uh,
well, I guess you're not there.
We're out
looking at the car, lying under it,
or, you know, maybe you're under the bed.
Maybe you're back, or the prostate,
or maybe you're writing.
You know, it could be. Maybe you're into research
again. Okay,
I'll try to catch up with you later. The time
right now is
11.45 on
a Tuesday.
Mm-hmm. All right.
Bye-bye for now. Into Luke
a lick. Hello.
Phone message is there by
Saint Jonathan Winters.
And now, more from Dr.
Philodrumon's favorite twos
for the collage.
Oh my god.
Becky, look at her butt.
It is so big.
She looks like one of those rap
guys' girlfriends.
But, you know,
who understands?
Those rap guys.
They only talk to her because she looks
like a total prostitute, okay?
I mean, her butt
is just so big.
I can't believe it's just so round.
It's like out there. I mean,
gross. Look.
She's just so
black.
I like big butts, and I cannot
lie. You other brothers can't deny
that when a girl walks in with an itty-bitty
waist and a round thing in your face,
you get sprung. Wanna pull up
tough, cause you notice that?
But your stuff, deep in the jeans
she's wearing. I'm hooked, and I can't
stop staring. Oh, baby.
I wanna get witched up, and take your
picture. My whole boys trying to warn
me, but that butt you got makes
me so horny. Ooh, romper, smooth skin.
You say you wanna get in my bins?
Well, use me, use me,
cause you ain't that average groupie.
I seen her dancing
to hell with romancing. She's sweat
wet. Got it going
like a turbo vet. I'm tired
of magazines saying flat butts
are the thing. Had to average
black men and ask him that. She gotta
pack much back. So, fellas,
fellas, has your girlfriend got your
butt? Tell her, shake it, shake it,
shake it, shake that healthy butt.
Baby got back.
L.A. fake with the Oakland
Boonies.
Baby got
back. L.A. fake with the Oakland Boonies.
L.A. fake with the Oakland Boonies.
I like them round and big.
And when I'm throwing a gig, I just can't
help myself. I'm acting like an animal.
Now here's my scandal. I wanna get
you home and up, double up.
Up, up. I ain't talking about
Playboy, cause silicone parts are made
for toys. I want them real
thick and juicy. So find that
juicy double. Mix a lot's in trouble.
Begging for a piece of that bubble.
So I'm looking at rock videos.
Not any bimbos walking like hoes.
You can have them bimbos. I'll keep
my women like Flojo. A word
to the thick soul sisters. I wanna get with ya.
I won't cuss or hit ya. But I gotta
be straight when I say I wanna
till the break of dawn. Baby
got it going on. A lot of simps won't like this
song. Cause them punks like to hit and quit it.
And I'd rather stay and play.
Cause I'm long and I'm strong.
And I'm down to get the friction on.
So ladies, ladies,
if you wanna roll my Mercedes,
turn around. Stick it out.
Even white boys got the shout. Baby got
back.
Baby got back.
Yeah, baby.
When it comes to females,
Cosmo ain't got nothing to do
with my selection.
36, 24, 36.
Only if she's
5'3".
So your girlfriend rolls a Honda.
Playing workout tapes by Fonda.
But Fonda ain't got a motor in the back of her Honda.
My anaconda don't
want none unless you got
buns, hun. You can do side
bends or sit-ups. But please don't lose
that butt. Some brothers wanna play
that hard roll. And tell you that the butt
ain't gold. So they toss it and
leave it. And I pull up quick to retrieve
it. So Cosmo says you're fat.
Well, I ain't down with that.
Cause your waist is small and your curves are
kicking. And I'm thinking about sticking
to the beanpole games in the magazines.
You ain't it, Miss Thing. Give me
a sister. I can't resist her. Red
beans and rice didn't miss her. Some
knucklehead tried to diss. Cause his girls
are on my list. He had game, but
he chose to hit them. And I pull up quick.
To get with him. So ladies, if the
butt is round. And you want a triple X
throwdown. Dial 1-900
Mix-A-Lot. And kick them nasty thoughts.
Baby got back.
Little in the middle, but she got much back.
Give me that donkey butt and them big ol' legs.
I ain't too hard to beg. Ain't no shame
in this game. I'ma break it down to bag
like Jane. Please.
Please.
Let me ride that donkey.
Let me get a bug wild. Let me do that donkey doggy style.
Drip your hips up, let your butt cheeks
not work that thing, freak.
Rock it. Pop it. Don't stop it.
I wanna knock it. Yeah. Open up and let me
come inside. Take me on that donkey ride.
I wanna make that body jank.
No time to play. Just doing work.
Cause I'm a business man. Taking care of business.
Gotta get a witness. So come on up,
love your horn, little devil. Let me take you to the other level.
Like Moan in the middle, freak.
Or them big old butt cheeks. So let me ride that donkey
all the way down. Got you making a freaky
sign. Cause you just freaked that I'm up and riding.
Don't need a long relationship.
Just hit it, quit it, and dip. So give me
that donkey butt and them big old legs.
I ain't too hard to beg. Ain't no shame in this game.
I'ma break it down to bag like
Jane. Please.
Please.
Let me ride that donkey, donkey.
I been watching you on the floor.
The way you move, maybe want you more.
Cause I like the way you strut.
Shaking that big old donkey butt.
I'd do anything for it.
What?
Cause I'm about to ill and steal the field.
That big old butt make a freak you wanna kill.
For real though.
Cause you go, girl, I wanna rock your world.
Get down to the floor cause your freaks got me crazy.
The way you kicking them days.
I wanna lay your love long hard as a laser.
Please.
Hello, this is Jim Smith.
If you would leave a message for me and the nature of your call, I would appreciate it.
And I'll return it as soon as possible.
Thank you.
The nature of the call.
Well, it's a call of a very violent elderly person.
Someone who's been in the business for a long time.
Someone close to your age.
You realize that just a few months, May, June, July, and August.
In August, you know what you're gonna be.
69.
Yeah, it's a magic number, you know.
It's a sexual connotation.
69.
Swazanoof.
Well, my friend, it's the last time you'll be that.
Then you go into the business.
It's a 7-0, and just remember, the prince of darkness is really staring on the walls
and the halls and the people with the white hair, people with the bad rugs, people bent
over, crippled, drooling and scrueling and grueling and stumbling and fumbling using
a cane, using their hands, be fewer and fewer sit-ups in a new way, and more and more shit
you know, push-ups and running.
You'll have stopped running, you see.
Maybe, maybe, maybe in your room in tight circles.
A few little things there,
but the body eventually turns to clay.
You heard the expression, feet of clay.
Well, get ready.
You got that?
Yeah, I got it.
Good, good.
It's 127 at night, you just turned out.
The kitchen light went off to bed to sleep with your wife.
Now your crew went home, you think your life is a gasp.
But fool, I got a wire tap on that ass.
If the wolves had ears, what fool they do?
Cause the FBI is watching you.
Federal Bureau of Investigation.
One, two, three, hit it.
I'll do anything it takes to get your voice on tape.
I got bugs and satellites, whatever, cause I'm a snake.
My surveillance van's equipped with the illest technological advances.
Chronological chronicles of the chances that you took.
In the day you thought you got away, but fool, look out now, high, I got blade.
You thought that hip-flare skew was nice and neat,
but my wire tap sat strapped onto your seat.
By the time that your orders reached the ears of your soldiers,
every syllable.
Bulls in triplicate and federal votes.
I'm just waiting for the day when you incriminate the Don.
Word has spawned, then you're all gone.
If the wolves had ears, what fool they do?
Cause the FBI is watching you.
Federal Bureau of Investigation.
Pensate.
No pens I make.
Compadre.
It's all in black and white.
I'm super cop and you can't stop me.
Kamikaze consiglieres, both of their prowess,
but they're about to find out who's the cat and who the mouse is.
I call them mice cause my device will catch them all.
Finally, I'll get my promotion after all you all fall.
You can forget about club fed cause you're strictly going upstate.
Become a butt bae.
Write me, tell me how you like that, cup gang.
Solo.
Sorry.
ão
wont
going to
because the FBI is watching me
If the walls had ears, but who they do?
Cause the FBI is watching you
If the walls had ears, who they do?
Oh, Jonathan, I couldn't do much more than that
The FBI is watching you
See how far this girl is coming down
If the walls had ears, who they do?
I got a fine line
If the FBI is watching you
I'll look after your wife
Jonathan, be no scat, I'll play the part
You know you're going down for a bit of a skate
Don't worry Elmira, how about Sing Sing?
Bring along your servant, make it next summer
If the walls had ears, who they do?
Agent Paul's son, if the walls had ears, who they do?
If the walls had ears, dear friends, from Mob Story, a hip-hopera
Uh...
Amazing CD by Reverend Lepo Abernathy, Jack Douglas, Hugh Smith, and Eddie Lynch
And now a scene from The Planet of the Men
Technical difficulties here at the...
Stargate 2434...
We're visiting a sad planet, a very sad planet
On a routine patrol flight in the Milky Way galaxy...
I discovered on our space sensors an unidentified planet
careening wildly in an eccentric solar orbit
I ordered an immediate investigation
And with much difficulty maneuvered our ship for a temporary orbit
Upon beaming down to the planet's surface
All I could see were ruins
Ruins of some type of civilization
Crumbled buildings
Deserted streets
Charred vegetation
All covered with a thick layer of dust
Which our scanners indicated as intensely radioactive
I proceeded to make a thorough survey of the area
According to my calculations
I could tell that some recent phenomenon or holocaust had occurred
And destroyed whatever advanced civilization had existed on the planet
I thought that the planet was in a state of emergency
I found no sign of life
As I made my way back to the ship
I heard a sound
It came from a cellar
In one of the nearby buildings
Carefully and slowly
I found my way to the source
And discovered a human being
Or rather what once was a human being
A scarred, disfigured man lying in the rubble
When I questioned him
He told me that this had once been a great world
They had abundance and plenty
Intelligence
Beauty
Love
There was enough for everyone who lived there
But the inhabitants were never satisfied
They wanted more
They wanted everything
And they started to quarrel amongst themselves
They could not live in peace
And they tried to destroy each other
In doing this
They destroyed everything
Their abundance
Their plenty
Their own intelligence
Their beauty
Their love
He told me that so far as he knew
He was the only living thing left
But that he knew he was dying
When I asked him the name of the planet
He replied
We call it Earth
Stop
Go to Burning Man
This
Everybody in this campsite
Really ought to check out the Burning Man scene
I say this only because I've been twice
And only because
I really
Truly believe that everyone that
Has dragged me
Has dragged their ass out here to Sherman
Should seriously consider dragging their ass out
To Black Rock
City
Sulphur
Leadville
Nevada
Transverteu
Forgive
Free
P. Trust
or Kill Me
Radio
And if you don't like it
Shut up the fuck up
Sh Já Tr обязательно outros
Kind of hoping that this
This draws the Exes to a little closer
to the planet
It gets to them
These waves, these FM waves are actually being broadcast outward at a speed of 90.5 billion miles per hour.
Through your body, through the earth, out the other side, into space, out there, to where the X-ist can hear it.
We really want them to know when they pull up just past the moon in part,
there's at least a few of us out there who can dig this crazy sound and thus lure them in.
Catch a ride in the pleasure saucers.
By the way, you're listening to Garbled Radio Signal Number 2.
Garbled Radio Signal Number 2
When? Why do I wait? You told me to wait. Now he'll never come again.
There's a hole in the world like a great black pit and it's filled with people who are filled with shit and the vermin of the world inhabit it.
But not for long.
They all decide to die.
Tell me why, Mrs. Love, tell me why.
Because in all of the whole human race, Mrs. Love, there are two kinds of men and only two.
There's the one staying put in his proper place and the one with his foot in the other one's face.
Look at me, Mrs. Love, look at you.
No, we all deserve to die.
Even you, Mrs. Love, even I.
Because the lives of the wicked should be made brief, for the rest of us' death will be a relief.
We all deserve to die.
And I'll never see Johanna.
No, I'll never hug my girl to be finished.
All right, you sir, how about a say?
Come and visit your good friend Sweeney.
You sir, too sir, welcome to the grave.
I will have vengeance.
I will have salvation.
Kill me.
Come on, come on, come on.
Go on.
The Epiphany from Sweeney Todd, actually about X-Day, sung by Christopher Lee,
followed by Or Kill Me from National Cynical Network, not from Or Kill Me Radio, which we go back to now.
Now the ladies of the harem of the court of King Caractacus were just passing by.
Now the noses on the faces of the ladies of the harem of the court of King Caractacus were just passing by.
sing by now the noses on the faces of the ladies of the harem of the court of king garacticus
now the boys have put the powder on the noses of the faces of the ladies of the harem of the
the Court of King Airaticus
Weren't just passing by
Now the boys have put the powder on the noses
Of the faces of the ladies of the harem
Of the Court of King Airaticus
Weren't just passing by
Now the boys have put the powder on the noses
Of the faces of the ladies of the harem
Of the Court of King Airaticus
Weren't just passing by
Now the boys have put the powder on the noses
Of the faces of the ladies of the harem
Of the Court of King Airaticus
Weren't just passing by
Now the fascinating witches have put the scintillating
Stitches in the britches of the boys
¶¶
Do you have any shout-outs
or any requests?
Before we get started with something else entirely?
I don't know.
I don't know if I have that one.
I do have something else that's even better.
Really?
Yeah.
What is it?
Then I don't know.
It's the smash hit
Please Don't Go Topless Mother
from a CD called God Less America.
It's a unique piece of
a plastic
oddly enough
it's a CD
and it's track 9.
Troy Hess
is going to
keep it
keeping it
he's going to keep it real
for everybody out there.
If anybody's still listening
if you're not just
crashed out
and totally exhausted.
¶¶
Oh, please don't go top this, mother
But I just cannot tell a lie
You're running your reputation
And I can give you two big reasons why
Is it close, is it close?
There's no pain killer anymore
Look at the earth
I'm asking you to stare in awe
Calling to you, calling to you
It never ends, I don't ever know
Lucky for you, lucky for you
Live to wake the dead, you hear
Words from your heart, words from your heart
One day you'll say, I can't stop
Oh
Back again, we're gonna set this side
Calling to you, calling to you
I'm calling to you, calling to you
Booga-wagga, booga-wagga, booga-wagga
Ha ha ha ha
Budawacka, Budawacka, Budawacka
Ha ha ha!
Ahhh!
Mmm..
MoreISSっていう
The Residence
The Residence, recorded live in Chicago, February 20th, Wee's birthday, by Reverend Christopher Lee.
Thank you for calling J.B. Smith.
I'm doing a few touch and go's today, so be in and out, and please leave a message for me. Thank you.
Hi. It's 11 o'clock. You mean you've gone to bed already?
Well, I can't get you in the morning.
I can't get you at night.
Are you in the car again? Curled up?
What about that car phone? Is it working?
I don't get it. I don't get it.
Elderly people, I guess, I forget. Yeah, they go to bed at about 8 or 9.
It's just incredible.
Or you'll have as much as, what, 9 to 12 hours of sleep?
Remember eternal sleep. Eternal sleep.
That means you don't wake up.
You got it?
Yeah.
Maybe the Prince of Darkness is visiting you now.
Well, I had a lot of important stuff I wanted to lay on you.
Yeah, I'm getting ready for a heavy schedule, so I wanted to alert you to that.
I'm going down to Branson.
And then going to be a guest.
I'm going to be a guest down there on the Wayne Newton show.
And I plug the cassette, of course, down there, my cassette that I've done.
And I'm kind of excited about that.
Maybe you ought to save your money and go down there with me.
I'm going to have to get down by bus because of the tremendous cutbacks we've had at gridlocks.
So you'll have some thought.
But I'll try it another time.
Apparently, you're in slumber.
Ready?
Over and out.
Yee-haw, Cam-bot!
Yee-haw!
Hoo-hoo!
Now get in the line, get in a row, grab your partner, here we go!
Swinger high and swinger low!
Don't step on that pretty little toe!
Now promenade!
Woo-hoo!
Yee-haw!
Eatin' food!
Turkey, eatin' cornbread!
Cheese, skinny cheese, real well fed!
Alleman left and Alleman right!
Now promenade!
Woo-hoo!
Yee-haw!
Hoo-hoo!
Alleman right and form a chain now, form a star and circulate to your left!
Ladies chain now, do-si-do!
Alleman and kickball change!
Now promenade!
Woo-hoo!
Shake for breakfast, shake for lunch, a sensible meal that you can munch!
Slowest prices all the time, refreshing splash of lemon lime!
They've closed the bars, the factory's through!
Watchers England, it's a rule, we're pretty, pretty like them!
There's no future, no future!
Ah!
Anarchy!
Now promenade!
Woo-hoo!
Oh, we got a police car!
Mr. Data, what do you know of homosexuality?
Intriguing.
Accessing.
It appears to be a means of pleasuring between two males.
But I am curious as to why you should ask me such a question.
Mr. Data, as your commanding officer, you must obey any order, no matter how deranged or insane, I choose to give.
That is correct, sir.
Federation dictates it.
Mr. Data, I am curious as to why you should ask me such a question.
Mr. Data, I am going to take down my Starfleet regulation-issued trousers, and when I do, I want you to, well, drive me home.
I must obey any order you give me.
Make it so.
Engage.
Must stop.
You must stop or you will hurt the captain.
You have killed the captain.
You have ruptured him in two.
He is cleft.
You have ruined him.
I've been all over this continent.
I've been from coast to coast.
I've even been up as far as Quebeck, Mass.
I've fought my way up to the Nile, to the very top floor.
And I've even tracked the polecat to its pole.
I've had the yellow jack.
I've been shot full of holes.
I've even grabbed an army mule plumped by the plumper.
But I've never been so ripsort, highfalutin' mad, as the night I was reclining on my Louis XIV derriere.
It all started when the telephone tinkled.
Picking up the receiver, I said, uh, oui, oui.
You see, it was a French phone.
The Secretary of State was calling.
He said, Jimmy, we need you for an important mission.
Do you know anything about foreign relations?
I said, foreign relations?
Why, you're talking to a guy who's got 15 relatives living in Brooklyn.
How preprosperous.
So I said to him, sec.
I addresses him in the subjunctive.
My regrets, but I never converse business over the phone.
I'll see you tomorrow in D.C. at P.M.
Shop.
So that evening, at cocktail time, I gets aboard the Congressional Limited.
The train was jammed, so what happens?
I had to share my upper butt with a guy named Joe.
It was too crowded up there for both of us to get undressed at the same time.
So, hike comes down, Joe stays up, he takes off his coat.
Then Joe comes down, I goes up, I takes off my shoes.
I comes down, Joe goes up, he takes off his shirt.
Joe comes down, I goes up, I takes off my pants.
I comes down, Joe goes up, he puts on his pajamas.
And what happens?
It's morning.
We've got to start all over again.
I comes down, Joe stays up, he takes off his pajamas.
Joe comes down, I goes up, he takes off my pajamas.
I comes down, Joe goes up, he puts on my pants.
Joe comes down, I goes up, I puts on his shirt.
I comes down, Joe goes up, he puts on my shoes.
Joe comes down, I goes up, I puts on his coat.
Now I don't know whether I'm Joe or Joe is me.
It's a case of double identity.
He gets off at my station, I gets off at his station.
His wife runs over to me, throws her arms around my neck,
gives me a kiss and says,
Congratulations, Joe.
You're the father of a nine-pound baby boy.
What a dilemma.
But what could I do about it? Nothing.
So I went to Hoboken to forget.
And then I went to Hackensack to forget Hoboken.
That's my story, boys.
The Star Trek II mix there was by National Cynical Network,
sent in by Reverend Phineas Narco.
We also heard Jimmy Durante there at the end.
And friends, you can learn more about this strange collection of subgenius shows,
The Hour of Slack,
by writing for free information from Post Office Box 140306,
Dallas, Texas.
7-5-2-1-4.
Or check out www.subgenius.com.
This music in the background is by Einstein's Secret Orchestra
with special guest Ron Slate.
Praise Bob.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'm about to play what I heard
and what I believe to be the version of Wild Thing.
This is the first version of Wild Thing.
This I ever heard as a child.
And then it, like, disappeared for about 25 years out of my life.
And I found it again and was stunned.
This is the Ventures version.
And it has this marvelous, wonderful Peter Lorre vocal.
I hope you enjoy it.
As well.
Wild Thing, I think I love you.
Come on and hold me tight.
I love you.
, I love you.
Wild Thing, I think you move me.
Come on and hold me tight.
You move me.
Wild Thing, I think you move me.
Come on and hold me tight.
The missile guidance computer scenario works as follows.
Because a variation has modified some of the information the missile has obtained,
it is not sure just where it is.
However, it is sure where it isn't, within reason, and it knows where it was.
It now subtracts where it should be from where it wasn't, or vice versa.
And by differentiating this from the algebraic sum of where it shouldn't be and where it was,
it is able to obtain the deviation and its variation, which is called error.
To푚
And therefore, it returns to the value of mustine information,
I cut my kids' hair like a bowl.
I smoke big cigars around little babies.
Why?
Because I'm an asshole.
I play with a remote control when you're watching TV.
I wear my hat to movies so that you can't see.
I drive really fast when you're in front of me.
And I drive really slow when you're behind.
Oh, I am an asshole.
Me and my stupid friends drive around real late.
Our Camaros all have bumpers and we think it's really great.
Whenever your head dances, we make passes at your date.
But our only real girlfriends are the kind that you inflate.
Oh, I am an asshole.
Oh, when you go to the phone booth and you open up the book.
And the page you want is missing, it's cause that's the one I took.
That's the one I took.
One, two, one, two, three.
I'm the asshole in your neighborhood.
I live right next door.
I party till I'm naked.
Then I throw up on your floor.
Your daughter was a virgin, but she isn't anymore.
When I play Monopoly, I cheat.
I'm the asshole that you meet when you're walking down the street.
I'm the asshole.
I'm the asshole that you meet each day.