Ladies and gentlemen, presenting the subgenius of OVSLUG.
I feel real good. And then other times, I feel like I was going to get sick right in my stomach.
Well, that doesn't take much doing.
Hello, Bob. I need someone to talk to.
Hello, Bob. It seems there's nothing I can do.
Hello, Bob.
I need someone to listen to me.
I'm hitting all the locked doors and I need some help.
And I was hoping you'd have the key.
Hello, Bob.
Have you been listening to my thoughts?
And I'll tell you all the thoughts.
I've got.
Hello, Bob.
I can't seem to find the truth.
I read the books.
I took the drugs.
And I drank a whole bottle of Verluce.
Yeah.
Hello, Bob.
I seem to have misplaced my slack.
Well, I just can't seem to get it back.
Hello, Bob.
Can you point out what it is I lack?
I've climbed to highest heights, hit the lowest lows.
But now I'm on my back.
Hello, Bob.
Are you still hearing me?
Give me a sign that I can see.
Hello, Bob.
It's not that I've lost all my hope.
But I'm really tired and I'm really broke.
And I smoked up the last of my dope.
Hello, Bob.
Am I coming through to you?
I thought I already paid all my dues.
Hello, Bob.
I've lost my slacks.
I know that you can see me through
But it's damp and dim and I can't swim
What am I supposed to do?
Well, hello, Bob
I'm feeling better
Now you've listened to me
Hello, Bob
Well, the sun's out now
Now I can see
Hello, Bob
A great change has come over me
My eyes are wise
My thoughts are clear
And I'm as happy as I could be
Yes, my eyes are wise
My thoughts are clear
And I'm as happy as I could be
Hello, Bob
Ah, yes, dear friends
This hour of the week
This hour of Slack number 1555
Is another of the oldest
Old-fashioned Hour of Slack reruns
Because it's from our first two albums
From 1981
Before the Hour of Slack even existed
This one mixes the last part of Media Barrage number one
With the first collection of Bob hymns
Bob Songs 1
The early doctors on it are
Philodrummond
Yourself
Truly Reverend Ivan Stang
The late Dr. X
Glass Madness
Doctors for Wotan
Doctors for Bob
Kevin Wilson
The Mysterious Doug Three of Houston
And Buck Naked and the Jaybirds
It includes preaching cuts
From early 1980
Devivals held in backyards
Wotan and Doctor Music sessions
And some truly
Heartfelt Bob hymns
We'll soon go to What The Big Boss Is
Dear Bob
Um
Sometimes, Bob
Bob
I get so scared
and I don't know why
I just don't know why
but sometimes there are things
and they're after me
it's those kinds of things
that
you know
how come hot dogs
the kind of hot dogs
you get at the circus
why are they so red
and it's only at the circus
that you can get hot dogs
of real red
there's a red kind of
it's more
more red
and
and sometimes things
live in walls
you know
and it gets scary
because
yeah
there are some things
that are in the walls
test
now it better work
it better not work
it's a lot better
okay
test
I can't hear anything
I can't
there's something wrong
with this one over here
give me some
of that annoying noise
hey I need some
is it working
I'm number five
yeah we really need some
problem
hey what'd you say
I raised somebody
I'm gonna check you
what'd you say
down there
oh ow
Jesus Christ
did you feel that big
devil
I didn't say nothing
what'd you say
yeah you said what
hi officer
hey what do you guys
doing over here
come on
get over there
I saw what you put in your pocket
give me that
get over there
over there
you're gonna get
you're gonna
get over there
you're gonna get
oh stop
The battle for the mind
How about your voice
are you
are you going to
allow them to out shout
you
are you going to
allow them to be heard
over and above
your objections
It's bull
oh I'm too boring
Boring
boredom quotient boredom quotient nine to the 13th
your name's wilson yes
but the holy ghost is god's authorized detective agency the holy ghost is god's high sheriff
that has come to restore and get back for you pastor and be my hero those things that the devil
has stolen i know pastor the origin of the original don't turn it off
from your heart the smile that he has stolen from your lips
where my lips go
i
pastor now son i want to ask you to be quiet for just a minute i don't know anything so we can
hear pastor epley okay you as far as i know you haven't told him have you told him my staff
anything about yourself you haven't no then if i know anything about you it would be because
the spirit of the lord has led me to you today am i right uh-huh i've got something for you i
want to know what you're going to do with me i want to know what you're going to do with me
i want you to leave your seat and come here okay amen amen my knowledge i've never seen this lady before in my life i'm not saying that i hope she doesn't feel bad if she's come here two or three times i hope she doesn't think i've never been here before proud like this i can't remember everyone that comes to church can you say i read about you but the lord told me that he sent you here today
and jesus is passing by for you
you
Indonesia
we're here
what
devil wants
to steal it from you friends
What a shame how they stole it.
Oh, it's a miracle, Fran.
It's a miracle revival starting up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Perform the salute.
Freedom America.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Perform the salute.
But here's how to do the salute.
Yeah.
Ah, shake, right, ready?
The finger is on the neck.
Hands, left hand up.
Up and down.
Left hand up.
Oh.
Finger on throat.
Ready?
Come on.
All right, perform the salute.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Excellent.
It's a miracle.
I think before we start the service,
we should have just a moment of noise.
Oh, yeah, I can feel it.
The spirits.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Bullets can't stop it.
Oh, bullets can't stop them, friends, no.
The mark of the beast.
Oh, you don't need to worry about it.
You've got your credit card.
It won't do you any good tomorrow, but it's okay.
Well, oh.
I love you, John.
I guess now Bob's gonna have to work through me, friends.
Your command.
Fleecing snow mixed with freezing rain and rain.
The cold weather is much better.
And it looks like I can see you through the afternoon.
The temperatures are going to be
a little bit lower for the presentation.
We'll continue in all the desired conditions.
Snow accumulation at mid-morning range,
from near one half inch,
will deliver two inches of west.
The best we can do is to go one to two inches on.
We're going to come from the front.
We're going to come from the back.
Snow accumulation.
We're going to come from the front.
We don't need to worry about it.
We really have to keep sure that we're having a good Summer.
Snow accumulation grouped across the entire coast,
no aoenty snow婆ings.
What value do you plan to get over this?
Well, we should talk about snow accumulation.
Yeah, that's going into the relationship.
It's going to be a pretty nice picture.
I'm not sure that we really need to talk about it.
Wow.
I'm...
Sometimes I've got these
these rats and they're like
they're like inside my stomach and I haven't swallowed them
I mean they're like hot hot hot dogs but they're eating their way out
and they're
coming out and I just
sometimes I just want to take these hot dogs and just
shove them away. I'm taking these hot dogs
and just...
I'm taking these hot dogs and just...
Please Bob send me some more
more pills Bob please
Bob send me some more
some more of those pills
Bob...Bob...Bob...
Bob...Bob...
Oh...
Oh... Lonesome Bob
says
you gotta get some
pills
Oh...
Lonesome Bob
just telling
me
Oh yeah
Just give him some more pills
and Bob
will kill
I'm sorry mom, if I upset you, but sometimes I just don't feel too good, you know?
I mean, I really don't feel real good, and I don't know why, but Reverend Booney says,
um, my head, my head is, um,
obsessed with, um, the anti-bomb.
Um, and I don't really, um, know what he means,
and so that's why I'm talking to you directly,
because,
he isn't, um, much help.
But Bob says,
if you don't give me some money,
you just won't ever get any slack.
And then,
you don't get no slack, you can't get no money and no food and no pills.
Sounds bad.
So what we have there really is, uh,
two rituals going at once.
Um,
on the, uh,
the radio.
It's, it's a miracle.
What can we say?
We're used to them by now, but it's definitely miracles, and we've got proof.
Yeah.
It's amazing.
It's a miracle.
It's signs, signs in the heavens, signs in the earth.
Uh, we're seeing the signs everywhere.
And, uh,
they, uh, they still seem to be, uh, washing the implements on the other side in this blood of the lamb.
This is the blood of the lamb.
It wants us to
If we have to buy things and die, and we'll all come back older men, we'll all come back older men, we'll all come back older men, or know the reason why.
We have to buy.
We'll all come back older men, we'll all come back older men, if we don't come back older men, there ain't no reason why.
All wildest gizms, they will fall beneath our laser blades, and we'll all come back older men, we'll all come back older men, we'll all come back older men, in victory parade.
Okay, okay, Dr. Drummond has on his anti-alien possession shades so we won't go off the road
like we did last time.
I'm going to put them up here.
The dogs, the mongreloids back there are safely...
Oh, God.
He's got a screwdriver.
It's a key.
A key.
It looks like a screwdriver.
Right, it's disguised as the sacred screwdriver, and it's the key, and it makes the Bobmobile
begin to move.
You can hear it.
You can hear that good sound effect of motor rumbling, because this thing doesn't have
any real motor sound, and we have to use it or else superstitious peoples will run in
fright.
Little Rock is embraced with techno boredom just as usual, and I just want to tell you
it's no tour to live here.
I just want to extend greetings from the Archbishop of Slack Abuse of the mega fist temple lodge
of the church.
The Archbishop of Slack Abuse of the mega fist temple lodge of the church.
I want to thank the church for the subgenius of Little Rock.
It's nice to find out that there's some more like us around, and since we found Bob by
golly, we've just been having a great time and getting some money and finding out who
sounds like us and what the scam is and all.
The time now is 2.15, and the following program is sponsored by the New Testament Holiness
Church.
You do what you do because you won't...
I do what I do because Bob told me to.
That's what I think everyone needs to remember.
You do what you do because you won't to.
I do what I do because Bob told me...
I did, Bob.
Whatever you say, I swear to God, I did.
And I don't care if people laugh at me.
I did, Bob.
He...
He ain't no man.
He ain't no God.
I don't want to walk the path that Bob's trod.
Ain't no man, ain't no God.
I don't want to walk the path Bob's trod.
Okay, let's do it right this time.
And people ask me, where do you get this energy, this life I see glowing in you, Jander?
And I just point it up.
And I don't even have to say...
I don't even have to say...
I won't even...
I won't even say the word Bob when I said it.
But I just point it at the sky because it's not me that's doing it.
And you know and I know who it is.
It's Bob.
Now we take you into a great Holy Ghost revival that is now in progress.
Bill, you want to say something to the...
To the clinch?
I think it's all too deep.
To the Dallas clinch?
The conspiracy of the peaks.
And I don't know...
It's too pink and they refuse to comment.
If they're so hip, what are they doing in Dallas?
Yeah, really.
We can put on the Bob tune tape and sing along.
Doctors for Bob.
Copters for Bob.
Proctors for God.
Doctors for God.
God.
Doctors for...
and Sch...
Schnaud.
Shouldlokters for Schnaud.
Doctors for Bob...
Doctors...
Robobob....
Sphincters for Bleed.
Sphincters for Bob.
Drugs are real enough.
J aldan Im estructural
Pills for Bob.
Drugs are real.
Vibra IV for Alilda.
Get to DNA.
Give me some of them pills, Bob.
Wakanda Reid Hawks.
I got the blues cause Bob let that pickup run over my wife.
Hey, you get three points for hitting that hippie, girl.
Bob stayed father, eager to fit in in America.
He disliked the old man filling the boy's head with garbage and stinking Mayan occultism.
Bob grew up having to fight the stigma of a Mayan dad.
Other kids made fun of that prognathous slurped head of full-blood Mayan-ry.
And little Bob was in many a scrap, battling for his father's honor.
It was a troubled childhood and it had a telling effect on the society.
Bob was a representative youth who became, thanks to the pharmacy's wares, a chronic alcoholic at age six.
It didn't affect his precocious salesmanship, however.
And he made his first small fortune selling stolen prophylactics and other things to high school boys.
Wash it out, Bob.
Freak it out, Bob.
Zap it out, Bob.
Hook it out, Bob.
Shlarp it out, Bob.
Slurp it out, Bob.
Munch it out, Bob.
Punch it out, Bob.
And drink it out, Bob.
Scrunch it out, Bob.
Hunch it out, Bob.
Tear it out, Bob.
Mutate it out, Bob.
Slack it out, Bob.
Barf it out, Bob.
Kill me, Bob.
Thank you. Thank you, Sterna.
Coming up next, we have the original Doctors for Wotan album,
which is called Doctors for Negi.
And the song, I'm driving a car that Bob sold me.
You're so damn merry.
Back?
What do you mean, ha, ha, ha?
Take that pipe out of your mouth.
What are you grinning about, buddy?
Where'd you get that haircut?
Are those dots on your face, or have you got some kind of disease?
You look like Ward.
You look like Ward Cleaver on Leave it to Beaver.
You look like Mark Trail.
What's the deal, buddy?
You look like Mr.
Appleton.
You look like Big Van Dyke with a pipe in his mouth.
What?
What'd you say?
Did you say, yeah, sure.
Sure, I'll buy that used car.
I'll buy that used car from you, mister.
Sure, anything.
How much is it?
It's only a dollar?
That used car is only a dollar?
Sure.
Wow.
Wow, you got any other good deals, mister?
You got something else that'll only cost a dollar?
A little booklet?
I don't know.
That doesn't look like it's worth a dollar to me.
Oh, it does have a lot of print inside.
And some neat pictures.
Sure, I'll give you a dollar, mister.
Here.
Whoa, whoa.
I feel weird.
I feel, I feel really weird.
But, I feel kinda, I feel, I feel kind of good.
I like this, this little book.
Hey where'd you go, buddy?
Hey.
I wheels.
But.
Where'd he go?
Where'd the guy with the pipe go?
Hey, I gotta talk to him.
Hey, what happened?
Hey buddy, where'd...
He took off with my two dollars,
and he left me this little book and this car.
I'll get in this car.
I'll start it up.
He left the keys in for me.
Okay.
Okay, here goes.
I'm driving the car that Bob sold me.
Boy, I can go pretty fast.
Hey, hey, that Bob guy's okay.
He made me forget about,
he made me forget about Odin for a minute.
That's really weird.
Boy, this car is smooth.
I like the way this feels on the road.
I like the way it feels.
Feels good.
It's throbbing.
Hey, it's leaving the road.
It's going up in the air.
Where's it going?
Hey.
Hey, it's, there's a cloud up in front of me.
A big cloud.
It's got a sign on it.
A big sign.
It says, it says,
it says, welcome, welcome to Odin's place.
It says, this is Nirvana.
Wow, Bob, thanks.
I can't wait to meet Odin.
Hi, Bill.
Oh, the world looks better since Bob is my blindfold.
World looks good to me.
Oh, the world looks better since Bob's my blindfold.
The world looks okay to me.
Oh, the world looks to you like some kind of big mess
Put a barbed line, fold on
The world looks to me like a nice place to be
Cause I got my barbed line, fold on
This is gonna be a real Bob revival tonight.
And right now, we are Buck Naked and the Jaybirds.
And we're going to sing Bob is Leaving Me.
Bob
Bob's my friend and he's leading me somewhere
Where are you going, Bob?
Is he waiting there for me?
He's not waiting for you.
Bob's my friend and he's leading me somewhere
What is waiting for me?
Bob's waiting there for me
Bob can stop the aliens from killing me
Bob can save me, but will he?
Bobby, Bobby, Bobby, Bobby, Bobby, Bobby, Bobby, Bobby
Dousy, Dousy, Dousy, Dousy, Dousy, Dousy
What is waiting there for me?
Bob
Are you sure you're not Doctors for Bob?
Where is Doctors for Bob?
In the Doctors for Bob album.
What is subgenius? It's Doctors for Bob!
Is the Doctors for Bob one of those things?
You think you can know the subgenius without knowing Doctors for Bob?
Well, you're wrong!
What is Doctors for Bob?
Doctors of Bob!
Where is the Bob, y'all?
Doctors for Bob!
Yes, about half the people I know will enter the before life in the 80s.
Millions will die in a small nuclear skirmish with China in 1988.
Russia will invade Iran, Turkey, Africa, and of course Israel, and there will be plenty involved.
Draft wars in the US.
Look for a tenth member to join the common market, called by war.
Bad nuke accident in New York City.
Rockefellers will finally be able to do it.
The world will be complicated.
Wild spread famine in 86 and 87, when the 13 and 17 year locusts emerge.
Acid rain, tough times, the big screens.
Germ war in South America.
The great reformer, actually the Antichrist, enters Jerusalem through the East Gate,
and is made super-human, after miraculously recovering from a head wound.
He starts the one world government, which can only be stopped by a one world religion.
Russia develops an all-terrain-like trajectory on the yard by locusts.
Big mass collapse.
This is Kevin Wilson of the Abominations from Austin.
I battered myself after Rowing 66.
I don't wanna be nobody's Carolina.
They take me on a ship.
Put me on a motor.
Let me out in the water.
Let me go.
Cause I'm a subgenius.
Let me go naked in the park.
Let me feel like my head's coming apart.
I don't know.
But I have been told.
Every 30 things that people gotta get old.
But I don't believe it.
Cause I'm a subgenius.
Well, I don't believe it.
I take everybody for what they're worth.
I don't make no exception.
I don't like it when people try to talk back to me.
Cause I'm a subgenius.
I'm a subgenius.
I don't want you to get away from me.
You better like me for what I am.
If that isn't what pleases you.
Better make it right for me.
Cause I'm a subgenius.
And I'll never be a subgenius.
We're super subgenius.
And we're super subgenius.
And we don't make no exception for what people got to do.
Oh and the one I get married to is born Studies today and went,
Uh...
He's too born, he's just unenticed.
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
On our way to a Malaysian holiday in a place called Dobstown where they all stay.
They gotta get hip, get straight, and get cool.
They ain't gonna allow no fool to hang around with Bob.
Well, they never found Bob that day.
They said he just had gone away.
He was out to lunch or off to get shoes or gone buying groceries for people to blues.
I must not have been in need of slack because I never really managed to make it back.
But I sent my dollar to those people in town and I still keep getting them pamphlets sent around.
And I feel a little closer.
A little closer.
A little more in touch.
And I know it's helped me a whole lot of much.
But I sure do wish I'd been managing to hang out in the right place to actually catch a look at that shining face of Bob.
Bob!
Same.
Other reasons why you should buy.
I am the one.
Reason number two.
You can know doctors for Wotan.
Reason number three.
We will not suffocate you or your wife with mayonnaise.
This has been a message from the Subgenius Church.
We hope that you will send us money.
And don't forget, if you don't have a check or credit account,
with the Subgenius Church, you can send food stamps, money,
broken engine repair parts, pieces of a meaningless void,
half-forgotten personality forms, and or broken tree rot caterpillar dung.
You can send brain-locking tree sockets or a tree backwards mouth climb.
You can send tunnel-inner non-existent void particles.
You can send negro-influenced voice waves.
You can send a tattooed disc pattern.
You can send us cow vomit, tooth broken,
a leaven gated, elongated, creation-oriented,
spirit gulp, rust rot, scars.
You can send us niki flakes.
You can send us grub, black, coal, orange, peel, vision proof, single file.
You can send us a copy of the book.
You can send us doctors for fall.
You can send us a lowercase n.
You can send us a broken wheelchair.
You can send us void, anti-matter form, reality-shaped form, patterns, of that which do not exist
within the universe of those who walk the path of infinite void.
Those who will not write their names and addresses and or social security numbers on pieces of
a meaningless void.
paper but can send these in the forms of credit cards and or walking sticks broken or fixed it
can be repaired glass it can't be broken mirrors that however if you send us your tires be sure
to remove them from the car first you can't pay the postage on anything smaller than a pickup truck
if you want to send broken pillows uh pieces of glass and send out for uh please order our
handmade robot kits or genetic findings something this does have three life form patterns uh these
life form patterns are on uh sterno and myself i think doug smith is also patented but uh his
patent is owned by uh u.s steel and don't forget the county law will arrest you uh if you come
within uh 25 feet of this week's temple um if you have any questions letters and or old footprints
of niggy that you think has not been examined by our
archaeologists but could have important evidence on uh he who once was the what what is that
speak you speak of we who once were thee but i say unto thee we who once were these do not know
doctors for bob and if they do not know doctors for bob then where are they
and where can they be found
i can see why doctor heads exist so if you're gonna come in here wearing a pair of buster brown
shoes trying to play high school lawyer on you on this piece of young jamie and we don't take no
kind of it don't matter what color skin you have whether you're a white person or a doctor
for the stop in don't matter to us because we can we will
doctor for bob
we know of
things that you're not yet written within the human mind
carl sagan believes uh look at art linkletter his daughter sent us two thousand dollars before she
jumped off uh avalanche where do you go and meet bob said gee
that is true too
i always love that
i'm genius
it was always so neat
it still is
i'm a
the church of subgenius
fuck me
is the best
so you know
how you go
that is right
yeah
go to
subgenius
shall we catch
you
never a
you are hearing
the one tank rhythm killers
versus doctors
for wotan
operating out of little rock arkansas
is
joking
N
nap어가
斑
soft
see your
already
suckadoo
I was walking over Houston
You can change the name if you want to really sing the song, you can change the name of the town
Just to see what I could see
And the angel, the angel
He was walking over me
He was walking over Houston
He was walking in the air
And I saw my friend was with him
Hallelujah, God was there
He was walking in subgenius
He keeps me high until the end
For as long as I am subgenius
I know Bob is my friend
Now I know
Where'er we travel
In travail, Travolta view
Though the Fonz should walk beside us
We know Bob is with us too
Keep on walking with subgenius
Right in the high before the end
If I always by subgenius
I know Bob will be there
To be my friend
Now this third verse ain't
Necessary but if
I know Bob said we should always be ready to sell out
If you wanted to play this on a tape or something
You can stick an ad on me like this
Here we go
Send your doll
There to subgenius
So that Bob
Can love you too
Be a Bob's
1403-06
Dallas, Texas
And 5214
Keep on walking on subgenius
My low nose
And I've been to
The top of the hill
If you're running
In subgenius
Bob is running
With you too
I didn't have to
To the two there in the last
But I just
Rhymed it that way
So as a casual
I would have a heart attack
If you ever hear this
I'm strong, I'm terrible
Think you can come to
B ''
It's stiff
Love is perfect
In a fresh
Coat
Okay Mike
Pisis
I'm standing next to
E прямо
How this one
Very rich
Better watch out.
Don't follow the wrong one, no.
Go down the strings again.
There's a good bomb and there's a bad bomb.
There's a real bomb and there's a little bomb.
Oh, people ain't followed wrong bombs.
Gonna end up with no job.
One...
Two...
Three...
Yee-haw!
E-I-I, E-I-I, E-I-I, E-I-I, E-I-I, E-I-I,
Dr. Sir Bob Walton will die.
Dr. Sir Bob, Dr. Sir Bob Walton will die.
Just a little one chorus ditty.
We go...
Bob Dobbs, he's no slob, Bob Dobbs, he's no fool.
He's got the answers to the universe, and that's why he's super cool.
He is the head of the subvenience, and that's why he's super cool.
He's the head of the subvenience, and that's why he's super cool.
And everything else is at subgenius.com.
Because this is the Hour of Slack, and it's the Church of the Subgenius,
and our new official post office box.
Well, it's the old Cleveland Heights post office box.
Uh, the Texas...
This Austin office had to move, so now we're at Post Office Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118, www.subgenius.com.
And as with all Hour of Slack shows, you can find a detailed log of every single thing played at subgenius.com in the radio section.
Raise Bob.