I want to see the last places on earth.
Now, why are you here?
We're looking for the Marifesa Lupino Lumino,
a strange flower which grows only in Tibet
and which, it is said, takes its life from the moon.
Is there really such a flower, Father?
There are some things it is better not to bother with.
Our coolies tell us the valley we want to visit is filled with demons.
Then we're right. This is the place. Get the ponies.
Right.
You are foolish, but without fools, there would be no wisdom.
Pax vobiscum.
Welcome to the subgenius radio ministry Hour of Slang.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
And then this Democrat mayor gets up.
He said, wow, I think it was Donald Trump.
I think it was Donald Trump.
It was done for us.
Everyone's a fuckhead. Their brains are full of pus.
Tra la li.
With the yodel fire.
Everybody gather up. Come on, go past the bar.
Straddles get down from a main to Seattle.
Hop and skip and chop.
It's time to be a sociopath.
They vote for Donald Trump.
Part of the problem and part of the reason it takes so long
is nobody wants to hurt each other anymore.
Right.
And they're being politically correct the way they take them out.
Look at my African-American over here.
Look at him.
Are you the greatest?
I love the old days.
You know, I think you should do the guys like that when they were in a place like this.
They'd be carrying them on a stretcher.
Oh, Lord, how will we dance and how we talk?
The coast.
The fluster.
Maddox will rise up and sing the song.
Wopty doodle buddle dum.
He's completely nude.
Donald's got a boner.
That's because he's not a prude.
Knock on doors and get involved.
Rise up and take a stand.
Donald Trump's the guy to make America great again.
Are you watching Infowars or spit it all on your chin?
Lubricate your rectum with your fist.
It will distend.
Tra la li.
Cock-a-doodle-doo.
He'll depart the Mexicans, the Muslims and the Jews.
Draw Italy down.
Stump your head inside your own.
Join the clan, pick out your sheet and vote for Donald Trump.
Hop on dance, go bonnet, prance.
It's Mussolini's second chance.
Twenty million whites, supremacist, can't be wrong.
Tra la la.
You can tell me damn.
Donald Trump can flatter and fool.
Depart the world.
Party hand in hand.
Ho, yo, yo.
Slippity-dippity-slump.
It's time for all the yelping cause it's time for Donald Trump.
Everyone's a dumbass and the brains are full of lust.
It's time to bear the anger of all those who are for Donald Trump.
I can punch him in the face, I beg it.
We having a good time?
USA, USA.
All right, yeah, get him out.
Try not to hurt him.
USA, USA.
If you do, I'll defend you in court.
Don't worry about it.
USA, USA.
It's time for all the yelping cause it's time for Donald Trump.
Get in the car, get in the car.
Or sit in the home of a保守校.
Maybe it's all a temptation
Maybe not a combination that robs you blind
Or of the Africa damn time
Maybe I'm a little next time
Maybe it's all a temptation
Now I'm looking for a reason
To live without love
This is a piece of dark time
Maybe it's warm
just right for both you and me
to be me
Maybe it's warm
probably just came for a train ride
just like the mountain
will not be the same
Maybe it's Bob, maybe it's Bob, maybe it's Bob, maybe it's Bob.
Now I'm looking for a reason to live without love.
Lost team
Take some time
You see, the Church of the Subgenius is the first 100% born-in-the-USA religion-slash-comic-slash-horror-slash-sci-fi-slash-anarchist-graffiti-cult-slash-pighead-bible-thumper-slashing-parodyorthodoxy.
Parodyorthodoxy, copyright What the Fock and Subgenius Ministries.
Results may vary according to condition, position, or head up the end user.
Author Paradoxy does not include weed foot and mouth control or correction.
Praise Bob!
I am the Reverend What the Fock, and I preach a holy trinity.
Father Reason, his loving daughter Tolerance, and the blessed Holy Spirit of
How you worship or don't is none of my goddamn business.
That is a trinity that can save the world.
Slack out.
And we're in.
And now you're on.
Your core is hot.
Meltdown.
Simulation is bound.
When life.
Shines.
Down!
When we connect, there's a chain reaction.
Keep our mind from getting close to distraction.
Control your thoughts, remove distraction.
Take us in, you'll love the taste.
When we connect, there's a chain reaction.
Keep our mind from getting close to distraction.
Take us in, you'll love the taste.
When we connect, there's a chain reaction.
Keep our mind from getting close to distraction.
1, 2, 3, 4, reach out, touch the core.
5, 6, 7, 8, now you must cooperate.
9, 10, 11, 12, never stop.
Keep it for yourself.
1, 2, 3, 4, not a human anymore.
When we connect, there's a chain reaction.
Keep our mind from getting close to distraction.
Control your thoughts, remove distraction.
Take us in, you'll love the taste.
rooms of Richard
When we connect there's a chain reaction.
keep our mind from getting close to distraction.
Next time on H Sage's Videom nothin'
Oh, yes, dear friends.
This is fired by a huge Comet.
That band was the Fantastic Plastics.
And we heard them last night.
We went to see them last night at the Devotional.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
At the Beachland Ballroom.
That was Friday and Saturday nights.
It was fabulous.
We saw a lot of our old friends and some great new bands,
including the Exposed Foreheads.
I've been playing them a lot on the show.
They did also a really, really tight show last night.
I'm going to play some of them in a minute here.
In fact, this in the background, Princess Wee,
is the other band by the same people called Cyber Chump.
It's instrumental music.
They're so good.
Yeah.
Really, really talented musicians.
Anyway, let me do credits here.
Yeah, we just heard the fanfare.
Fantastic Plastics.
And they do an amazing live show with excellent video projections.
Very slick.
And they're both real easy on the eyes.
That short rant there was Reverend Watt D. Falk.
That's his last name, F-A-L-K, D. Falk, with a little short rant.
The strange, somber, long song.
Maybe it's Bob.
It's from a new contributor, Reverend Experimental.
The aptly named Reverend Experimental.
And that song at the beginning, It's Time for Trump.
Well, of course, that was the Rudy Schwartz project.
That one was hot off the presses.
I think he put that out on the internet just like two days ago.
But we got a cherry.
Good copy.
Mm-hmm.
And yes, and now back to the folks who played at the devotional.
Two songs by the exposed four heads.
That's spelled with an X and a numeral four.
¶¶
¶ We're your friends and we're coming for you.
¶ We're jumping off a bridge and you can too.
¶ Our innocence committed no sin.
¶ But the boat was tipping as the others got in.
¶ Disconnected, disconnected.
¶ We could be electric.
¶ Disconnected.
¶ We could be кусack on a bottle. ¶ Disconnected.
You told me how you stole your heart. scheur!
¶ You told me how you stole your heart. ¶ But I know that you did your part.
¶ I've heard we're all in the same boat. ¶ Your friends or vampires bear your throat.
Disconnected, disconnected, we could be electric
trick
Hang up, hung up, I got hung up
Disconnected, disconnected, we could be electric
I got a box, what's in the box?
I don't know
I got a box, open the box
Alright, alright, stop. What now?
Open the box
You want me to open the box?
Yeah
I got a box, what's in the box?
Uh, nothing
I'll take more
Black, uit of the planets
Why?
I won't stand around
Pound I
Thank you.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
We're back in the studio,
and I think Lonesome may also have just joined us.
Mongoloid fue Mongoloid.
No longer...
Y lo determine lo que puede ser.
Mongoloid fue...
Fue Mongoloid y lo determine lo que puede ver.
Y lo prenie a casa del bacon y...
No, never mind, I'm sorry.
Por qué pork?
Yes, por qué pork.
Hmm.
That means it's porky pork.
Por qué pork.
My father thought that the word pork
was the most ugly word in the English language.
Well, that's why you used to slap him around, didn't you?
No, I never slapped my father.
Never ever.
Slap your mammy now.
Slap your daddy?
No, I've never slapped my daddy.
Well, we heard, Dave,
we must have heard eight different versions
of uncontrollable urge over the weekend.
It was great.
That's why I always want to convert my Mongoloid,
my Norteño version of Mongoloid,
and I never...
It's been, what, how many, 20 years now
when Reverend Tove invented the idea?
More like 100 years, Dave.
Oh, now I know you're trying to get my toenails to curl up.
Oh, before we forget, though,
your toenails curling up reminded me
of the cut we just played,
the rather amazing cover of a song
by They Might Be Giants originally.
Oh, yeah.
Called I Am Awake.
The Rick band.
It's called Am I Awake.
Am I Awake.
That was done by Reverend Bleepo Abernathy,
who I think...
I think it was a friend of that.
They were old friends of his from a long time ago.
Was that when Tony Maimone was in the band, briefly?
I know nothing of...
In the late 1980s, I think.
I know no more about the Giants
than the way the dandruff piles up
on their shoulders where I'm standing.
Well, it's a good thing you understand things like that.
It's important.
Before that song by Reverend Bleepo Abernathy,
there was a hard rock instrumental
that was by our buddy, Reverend Jimmy Ryan.
And that song, What's in the Box?
And the one before it disconnected,
those were both by Exposed Foreheads,
who we met for the first time.
And their foreheads are, in fact, exposed.
Yes.
And they did that song about sex aliens
that we played a couple of shows back.
They did that live,
and they had alien sex girls on stage.
They did.
Gosh.
I don't know if they were sex girls,
but they had kind of mini skirts and shiny outfits
and little antennae.
I'd call them space princesses.
Moon girls, actually.
Moon girls.
They looked a lot like the moon girl of Dick Tracy.
Mooner ladies, yes.
Yeah.
So, okay, I think that was the credits.
Oh, Dave, I wish you could have been there
at the devotional.
There was a band called We Are Not Men,
and they weren't.
They were young ladies who performed...
Sizzling hot young ladies.
Real accurate covers of Devo songs,
and while in costume,
the yellow radiation suits and red hats,
but then they did a costume change into negligence.
Their last song, they doffed the yellow suits
and were just wearing their black undies.
It was quite hot.
And stockings over their faces,
so their heads looked ugly,
but their bodies were...
Oh.
And the guitar real well.
And stuff.
I'm not really fond of that routine
of damaging your face
and then, like, putting on a pair of T-box or shorts
or, you know, letting your underpants grow.
Well, that was what...
No, you're thinking of the Spud Boys
who performed the next night.
That was the Spud Boys.
And they were, like, in the microgreens,
and they despoiled their panties.
You know?
Have you ever seen a rock band that used a trombone?
Yes, in fact, I have.
I was just over the house of a trombone player
who also played bass
and was in the Chronix band,
the Test 2 Baby.
I don't know if you remember hearing about that band
and song I was in,
the Punk Rock Days, Test 2 Baby.
No.
Chronix.
And Calling All Cardinals was the other side.
It was after they kidnapped the Pope.
And, yeah, he used to play trombone once in a while.
Well, yeah, bands have to change their names.
They have to change their names.
They kidnapped the Pope.
Well, this trombone player was Al Mothersbaugh,
part of that large Mothersbaugh clan
of musicians and artistes.
And he played, his band is called Massive Hot Dog Recall.
Mm-hmm.
And that was actually really funny.
It was hilarious.
Like other Devo-related stuff,
it has a real funny side.
How can you not?
All the bands that we know are novelty bands
where everybody has funny names and costumes
and wear masks.
That guy was absolutely hilarious.
He had so much energy, and he's just a nut.
Yeah, it was actually a really good musician.
It was like Herb Alpert, Eat Your Heart Out.
Yeah.
Trombones always add that comical effect
to any musical orchestra.
You know, frar, rar, rar, frar.
This was rocking, and he wasn't mic'd, I noticed.
He didn't need to be.
If you weren't kind of close.
If you weren't close, you might not hear it as well.
The trombone didn't need to be mic'd.
Yeah, and back in those days,
you never mic'd the horn section.
They were big and bad enough to do goodbye on their own.
Even a small band, like an old-time music band,
doesn't like to play completely acoustically,
and the singers stick out like someone at a caning,
which is what they used to, in Kentucky and West Virginia,
used to call a wake.
Huh.
A wake.
Especially if they were sleeping.
We, uh...
Saturday afternoon, we got there,
and our friend K.R.K. Ryden,
Reverend K.R.K. Ryden,
his band was playing,
called Ken the Magic Corner God.
I'll say the name of that band again.
Ken the Magic Corner God.
Not dog.
No.
No, God.
No, that's massive.
You're thinking massive hot dog recall.
This is Ken the Magic Corner God,
and believe it or not,
Dr. Philo Drummond is normally in that band.
Among other bands.
And he would have been there,
but he's moving to closer to Ohio,
so he probably will be.
Oh, and we saw our old subgenius friend,
Reverend Galaxina,
who's not old, but young.
Relatively young compared to us.
And we got to congratulate her
and Jerry Casale of Devo on getting married.
Yes.
Because Reverend Galaxina is Mrs. Jerry Casale now.
Another Jerry.
And we met Roger Casale,
the non-famous,
but equally funny and hard-working brother.
Yes.
And we gave our condolences
over the brother who died, you know,
because there's only three of the Devo's left.
Two of them were there last night.
Bob One was there also,
and I never got a chance to talk to him.
I didn't either.
And they didn't mention the earliest Bob drummer,
who...
I sued them for a million dollars
and remained friends while
pretending to be bare naked in the shower.
When we were fully clothed.
I don't know.
It's been a real Devo'd-up week
because we went to see that Mother's Ball art show
at the Museum of Contemporary Art,
which is...
Which is really not to be missed,
even if you weren't a fan of the band.
It's only five bucks on Fridays.
After five o'clock.
Right.
That's when we met.
Oh, it's so worth seeing.
And I want to go back.
It's only there for one more week.
Yeah, if you like that Devo Spuddy stuff
and related things,
boy, it was lots of fun.
Tremendous show.
And I'm a Devo fanboy.
I got up and spoke
and told my sexy gossip.
I didn't know that Jerry was going to be hearing all that,
but he heard me talking about some stuff that...
I guess if he didn't mind sharing it,
he wouldn't have been saying it in the first place
at the top of his lungs in a fancy restaurant.
It was about his first sex,
with a transgender person who'd had a sex change operation.
And he was...
Oh, I thought she was a transnationalist human.
He was told later...
Now, is it Alexina Casale is a transgender?
Well, no, but they...
No, but...
I don't know.
I mean, who knows?
Why not both?
That's my motto.
Well, why didn't you say so?
You made it sound like she had changed his neuter gender
to become a part of the...
No, no, no.
You weren't listening.
I was...
He was telling a story of his...
of being told after his night with a lovely young lady
that she had not necessarily been born as a lovely young lady,
but probably as a lovely young man.
And I can't repeat on public radio what his response was.
There's not a single bad word in it,
but just the concept is not suitable
for people to be able to think about.
The concept makes it...
an illicit thought.
Yeah.
The whole of the context is real, real, real funny.
So it leaves you open to about nine million different thoughts, right?
Like trying to get out of the elevator shaft, everything you...
Again, why does it have to be either or?
Why not both?
Okay.
Both.
I agree.
Well, the bathroom people are all upset.
We have to be either or.
I don't know about that.
Why not both?
The bathroom people...
The bathroom people are always upset
because their very name indicates that's what they are.
Bathroom people.
The bathroom people.
A John Waters film.
Dr. Bath...
Yeah.
Really, John Waters.
With Divine gobbling a French poodle from behind or something.
I don't know, but I certainly don't want to live there for too long
because they're out to get us.
Uh-huh.
Snack.
Speaking of John Waters, we listened to his hitchhiking book.
Yes.
He went hitchhiking across the country and wrote a book about it.
And you quoted some of it on a show once, didn't you?
I may have played a little bit of it.
Again, there was a lot of context stuff that was pretty intense.
It's tricky for public airwaves where there's a community that has standards.
It's a lot of decency.
Unlike our listeners who wouldn't...
Well, that's why we have the internet version, see?
Right.
And we are due to have an X-rated show that will not be on any of our beloved stations.
It will only be on the podcast, as it were.
On the Blue Channel.
Yeah, the Blue Channel.
There's some pretty sexy stuff on the subgenius Roku Channel.
It's a channel you can watch if you get a Roku device.
Stick it.
Stick it onto your modern-day TV.
It tunes in...
But it's Japanese, though, right?
Huh?
Roku devices are Japanese, aren't they?
I don't know.
It sounds like it.
It does sound like it.
But it rocks you.
Because you can look at Philo Drummond's subgenius channel on the OSI 74 channel.
Which, and a lot of other goofy stuff.
Sleazy P. Martini, Gwar's manager, has his own show.
He has a...
Yes.
Fright show.
There's a lot of horror hosts.
The network was founded by...
Mr...
He's a Wolfman guy.
Yeah, Mr. Lobo.
Yeah, that's it.
Mr. Lobo.
How could I forget that?
Yeah.
He's a horror host in Detroit, I think.
They used to have Detroit and Cleveland hosts going back and forth.
Like, starting with Goulart and then going into the ghoul who was playing in Cleveland.
Then he would play in Detroit.
Then he'd explore some other place east and some other place west.
And then return to Cleveland.
Those horror hosts are an interesting breed.
They are.
I was...
We were in the company of one just last night.
We were?
Angry Lord Larry.
Yeah.
Oh, that's right.
Reverend Angry Larry is a horror...
Sir Cleveson.
He's been a horror host for years now.
Now, Sir Cleveson is his current character, who's a drunken vampire.
Who shows...
He shows bad movies and he makes them even worse.
He showed Mono's Hands of Fate and he re-edited it so it was even more spaced out.
How is that possible?
And he made it black and white.
Wow.
But, yeah.
Yeah, it's like he takes a movie that already kind of gives you a weird spaced out feeling
because it's so ineptly...
It's so ineptly done.
And then he exaggerates those like uncomfortably long takes and pointless reaction shots in
the wrong place and just kind of extends...
Does more of that.
The stuff that makes you stare.
Well, do you mind if I ask you one simple small question?
What was the name of the film where...
Where...
What's his name?
Where's the last man...
The last man in the world?
Well, there have been many versions of that.
You're probably thinking of The Omega Man was the version with Charles...
No, the Italian one with Vincent Price?
Yeah.
The same...
It's the same story.
It was called I Am Legend.
It was the original novel.
Yeah.
The...
And I think that's the title of the first movie of...
Richard Matheson wrote the book and a lot of other great things.
And...
And I am Legend had a director who was a great actor.
And then they remade it with Charlton Heston and called it The Omega Man.
He dies crucified yet floating in water like his blood is going to save the world.
And then it was redone again with Will Smith as the human protagonist.
Yeah.
That's the most recent one.
And he was also the lamb's bread puppy.
He was one of those refused.
That's what they used to call them when everybody was Russian.
Remember that? The Dvořák days?
I remember the Refuseniks.
That was a great band.
They were against everything, but then there was also Blank Riot,
which I shouldn't say the name, but it reminds you of a cat.
Right.
Yeah. And so the archbishop was against them,
so that's why they all had to wear underpants at one time.
Well, we all had to wear underpants at one time,
and some of us have to wear extra giant, thick, huge underpants.
Not that the listeners have to envision that yet.
Why would you want to refuse them like a Refusenik?
In our case, quite yet.
But, you know, there's going to come a time, I guess.
Oh, Dave, this is exciting news.
You know how I'm completely deaf and have to guess what you're saying all the time?
No.
Well, I still am, but I got tested for hearing aids.
Princess Wee and I both went.
We went to the internet, finally, and she's got them.
And they work great for her.
Are you wearing one right now?
I had to take them off because there's a lot of feedback inside the headphones.
So I had to take them off temporarily.
I had to take them off all through the devotional because it was way too loud.
Right, we put plugs in our heads there.
Which, dang, does not have any of these earplugs.
Man, I not only flunked the hearing test, I flunked it so bad.
That they sent me to, let's say, a real doctor.
They said, you need your head examined, boy.
Your left ear and your right ear are completely different.
Damage.
He's got real serious damage.
He's got to have everything looked at before they'll even amplify it a tiny bit.
They're afraid they'll hurt him even more.
Yeah, so I've got to go to the shrink head.
Not the head shrinker, not a psychiatrist.
But I have to go to a guy who could...
An ear, nose, and throat guy.
Yeah, and they'll scan my head and scam my insurance company.
Yes, but you still won't be able to wear a hearing aid?
Well, eventually they'll go, okay, yeah, he's in bad shape, but there's no reason he can't have a hearing aid.
That's the eventual goal.
Or they may go, Mr. Stang...
That's Reverend Stang.
Reverend, whatever.
Mr. Reverend.
Mr. Stang, you're...
That...
You need to have another one of those operations where we split your face in half and drain all the pus out of the right side of your head.
It's like...
It's so old, it's like rocks.
There's insects from the Jurassic period trapped inside the amber in your head.
And we want to get that stuff out of there and extract the DNA from the blood in those mosquitoes, those ancient mosquitoes that flew in your ear.
And they make dinosaurs with it.
Right.
And make new...
Little dinosaurs.
Well, I'm not that old.
But maybe a woolly mammoth, you know?
Maybe a John Birch Society member, at least, you know?
We still have those once in a while.
I know, I know.
We kind of know one.
We have a friend who was raised by birchers and sort of would be a kind of a bircher, if you could.
Yeah.
Well, the John Birch Society was started by Mr. Coke.
$52 million off Joe Stalin while he was writing a book about how much he hated him, which...
Well, he should run for president on the Republican ticket.
Yeah.
It's not perfect.
Oh, no.
Unfortunately, this is the world we must live in.
There's not a shadow of truth anywhere, no matter where we look.
There's not an inkling, the smallest teeny iota of truth anywhere.
Oh, well, you can wait until you see my doctor's, my health report from my doctor.
And my hearing test.
That'll get me elected.
And we'll get you out of the army, that's for sure.
I don't know...
Well, I'll bet your mind won't be as funny as Trump's.
Have you seen that?
The thing that his campaign gave out as a doctor's report?
No.
I thought you were talking about...
It said flat out that he tested positive for every single test.
That means he's got everything they tested him for.
AIDS, syphilis.
Yes.
Dementia.
Scott Maria.
Yeah.
I mean, and it basically said,
this will be the healthiest man ever elected president.
Because he tested positive.
As if this doctor had tested the health of any other presidents lately.
But, yeah, it was written by Trump.
It was like something you'd bring your teacher to explain,
you know, like a fake doctor's note.
The dog ate it.
It was so obviously fake.
I still don't understand.
And yet, and yet,
they managed to turn it completely around and go,
well, Hillary slipped that one time.
And she's on some kind of medication.
So, obviously, she's mentally deranged.
Completely lost it.
Anybody could have done that hour-long speech at that convention.
Now, that wouldn't wear him.
Anybody could do that.
Yes, they certainly are.
You know, yeah, anybody with dementia could stand there for an entire hour
and never look like they were reading cue cards.
And never crack...
Never crack up.
So, who knows?
Yeah.
I know what you mean.
I certainly do understand that.
Because I've met people just recently who wanted to argue with me,
who claimed to have dementia.
They wanted to argue with me,
and they forget what they were arguing with me about
a few short minutes after they were done.
Really?
And they didn't have a teleprompter either.
They just had, you know, like some notes that you write on the inside of your hand,
like at school and stuff like that.
Like the secret answers to the secret tests and stuff.
And that's why I think everybody in this country,
the electorate, if you would call it that,
if you had the nerve or the bells to receive it in such a way,
is insane.
It's completely and totally insane.
I would say the average subgenius is saner than the average electoralist.
Well, we've always said that.
But, of course, we define sanity ourselves.
So, it's kind of a moot point.
We don't expect them to agree, but they can't even understand.
So, why would...
It's a moot point.
We can have great big fish fights like they used to have in Germany
before the Nazis took over.
We could, like, be punching each other in the street
and then police come out on horses and stuff
and club us over the head with broom handles.
We can do that now.
Well, yeah, we do do it now, don't we?
But just not enough, dude.
Not enough.
Well, now, you could have come to the Republican convention
here in town and caused a bunch of trouble,
but hardly anything really happened.
Everybody stayed indoors.
Everybody stayed indoors that whole week.
But weren't there some...
Except for the smattering of protesters
who were cowed and depressed.
Well, by the, you know, the presence of the man in blue everywhere.
Yes.
Our friends went to the farmer's...
Our buddies went to the farmer's market downtown
and said there were...
And they were not exaggerating.
There were more police than there were customers.
And our friend Michelle was out on Lake Erie
and police boats with arms...
That's right.
Boats with guns stopped her.
And she's like, I'm fishing.
You know, excuse me?
Michelle went fishing?
Yes.
Yeah, she was out fishing, I think, with some friends on a boat.
And they got...
They got not just pulled over by the boat police.
They got rather rudely handled.
Yes.
For no real purpose, you know.
Scared the dickens out of them.
And all they were doing was fishing.
Pointed guns at them, right?
Yeah.
Well, that's always fun.
Pointed damn guns at people who were out fishing.
There were mounted guns on the ship that they...
Or on the boat that came up to them, as I understood her post.
It was just ridiculous.
Yeah, I was exposed to something equally ridiculous.
I hate to say it, but good thing for her that she's Caucasian.
Yeah.
Because in this town, they've been known to shoot first
and ask questions later,
depending on how shiny you are in the light.
Yep.
Kind of unfair, if you asked me.
Way unfair.
It's where it's good to have pallor rather than squalor.
In Cleveland, O.H.
Place you want to be.
Especially if you're 12 years old
and you want to carry a pop gun around with you.
A BB pistol or something like that.
Yeah.
Could be attacked by helicopters, you know.
I used to do that.
But I had...
In those days, little kids could just walk around
and do anything with their dog.
And no leash.
Not that way.
And the dog was allowed to just poop anywhere.
Do anything with your dog.
That's not nice.
No, we could.
Back then, back before 9-11.
Speaking of 9-11 and going fishing,
I remember Bush was coming to Cleveland
right after 9-11 one time.
And the car...
And every town east and west of Cleveland
must have been full of these Secret Service guys
really angry looking.
And obviously not from around there.
You know, they thought they were in some kind of movie.
They all had sunglasses
and they dressed just like the movies and stuff like that.
And they had these government cars.
They'd drive around giving everyone angry looks.
I never understood what that meant.
That's a true story, too.
You should see how out of place they look
when they come...
When the FBI drives a caravan
into the Indian Reservation.
I was living at Rosebud Reservation
during the time I was there.
The time when the Crow Dogs Paradise
was being raided all the time.
That was a ranch that was people associated
with the American Indian Movement.
And it was...
I drove somebody else out there
to run in and warn them.
I was told,
if you run in and warn them,
they'll probably just sheet you
because you're a washi-chu.
And they don't know you.
But...
We basically ran and said,
but there's a big caravan of dark cars
with guys in suits
coming slowly this way.
And they went, oh, okay.
But then it drove right past
and went to the other Crow Dogs Paradise.
And I think they did have some weapons there.
Because they were Vietnam veterans
and they had learned how to use heavy arms and stuff.
And they did have some stashed away.
Okay.
But it's never a good idea
to have a shootout with the FBI.
And if you ever hear about a shootout
with the FBI with me involved,
it's a lie.
Because I would never, ever do anything
to resist arrest.
Because I know that it lets the job for lawyers
to do all the shooting.
You let the lawyers do all the resisting and stuff.
Right.
I got beat up by five policemen
for about three hours.
And they never explained to me
until the very end
when I finally figured out
what it was all about.
I was charged with being left of center
on a one-way street.
Which sounds humorous,
but that was the actual charge
they were holding on.
They had no charge.
And they were just looking for stuff.
And they'd beat me up a little while,
throw me back in the cell.
Took all my clothes off
and burned me a couple times.
What?
And yeah.
And they had mace
and sprayed mace directly in my eyes.
I don't know why I can see to this day
because they were like,
I don't know why I can see to this day.
The idiot sprayed me right in the eye.
And they kept on saying stuff like,
get the gun.
Which when you hear someone,
a cop say, get the gun.
Right.
That means you're dead.
That means they're going to claim
that you're trying to get a cop's gun.
Anyway, I mean, you have to be insane.
But police, people believe this stuff.
And I was beaten so badly
I couldn't open my eyes
or shut my mouth.
Goodness.
I don't mean that in a funny way,
but it's true.
My eyes were kind of, you know,
puffed shut.
My mouth was puffed open.
And we couldn't even get it.
They were so tight until later.
We couldn't even get a lawsuit against them.
And then they finally did.
And by that time,
it was because they discovered
vast inequities in that police department
there in Columbus, Ohio.
They were doing even weirder things
to other people.
I was just one of the many.
I'm so glad you survived that, Dave.
It's really scary.
Oh, it is really.
It was very, very scary.
I have a gun pointed at your head
and then click.
Now, most of the time, to be fair,
most of the time,
police officers aren't beating people up.
Most of the time,
they're doing their job pretty much.
It's just, but, you know,
because I've known a lot of police officers
and there is such a thing as good police officer
and there's nothing better than that.
But then there's the bad apples.
And, oh, well.
Oh, well, this is supposed to be
the hour of slack,
not the hour of black and blue memory.
of poor, poor Dave.
No.
You know, I've tended to blame the victim
in this case, though,
just because you can.
Why not?
Yeah, yeah.
But that's what living America is all about.
I was telling you,
I was reading about that Howard Zinn book
of people's history of America
and I guess stuff like that's been going on
for a long time.
We just prefer not to pay attention to it.
We prefer not to pay attention to it.
We prefer to switch off those reasoning lights
and change channels, so to speak.
Yeah.
Friends, you're listening to the hour of slack
from the church of the subgenius.
We haven't been very religious tonight, have we?
What do you mean?
It's all religious.
Okay, praise Bob.
There, that part's done.
Okay, Bob, now we can get paid, right?
We should praise Bob.
Bob will pay us now.
Finally, after all these decades.
Hmm.
Heh.
It's hard working for the rich.
Just think of what a tautology that is
or a twitch torment
or a twitch torment.
I used to shoot videos for rich people
of their weddings and coming out parties,
debutante balls.
Yeah.
That was when I learned
that the most dangerous creature on the planet
is not the deadly Tyrannosaurus Rex
nor the brain-eating,
immune-eating,
but a rich, drunk person.
Mm-hmm.
That's the most dangerous, deadly monster on the planet.
Too dangerous.
Two drunk squires attacked me on their horses once.
What?
Like, what are you doing here?
The road was clearly defined as a township
or a city, whatever it was, road.
But you're a cowboy.
How could they attack a cowboy?
And this one, you can tell they were both drunk.
Yeah.
Two of their faces are all red.
And the woman did all the talking.
The rather large, but not too large,
like a poor person, large woman,
she did all the talking and he did all the smirking.
And they used their horses to bump against my car
while they asked me what I was doing there.
And of course, I got the hell out of there quickly,
but it wasn't a private place.
They thought they owned everything.
And they used their horses to bump against my car
I'm sorry.
It was their wealth and drunkenness.
I hate to tell you this, Dave,
but that was me back before we knew each other.
I remember that.
This was a very, no, no.
This man was very strange looking.
He's the kind of rich person that made you go,
it's one of them, the enemy.
Well, if anyone needs to know more about how to escape
the planet of the clocks,
you can look at our website, subgenius.com.
Although you may end up spending more time
on any of the numerous Facebook pages
because they change a lot more often.
Subgenius.com changes once a week,
usually on Monday or Tuesday
when I put this show on the internet.
And it's the X-rated version, by the way.
It'll be slightly different.
That Rudy Schwartz project song about Trump
will sound different on the internet than it did.
And it'll sound different every time you play it too,
right, Stane?
Well, we try for that.
But now we have to go,
and I think we did everything right.
And the last thing I'm going to do
is play this short one and a half minute,
no, one minute and ten seconds,
Reverend Jimmy Ryan.
Here it is.
So the music in the background was all cyber chump,
involving the people that are also in exposed forehead.
And so, thank you.
See you, Dave.
Thank you.
Bye.
This has been an kunnen-ass podcast.
I wanna thank my friendeté,
guitar solo
solo
Oh, sire, there is no more money.
We gotta get some money.
That dirty
Turkish harkapack
flackin'
whartin'
fill a
bunker
burton
perkaluma
buster
night
in the wall.
B-O-B
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show,
and we're even more glad that some listeners have donated enough to help us keep on going
for another couple of months.
Not just this show, but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob, and want some of that slack back to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com front page, or especially the radio page, or the catalog store pages,
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty, and we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference, even if it's only once a month from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that...
blowjobs could go the way of steel, but they're not the same as the steel industry.
You can't leave jobs if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to Subgenius Foundation.
P.O. Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Thanks for anything you can do to help let there be slack.
Our job is to get into the middle part.
I'm out.
You can go tweet, Google, Twitter, Instagram, or Twitter.
I look out for you online at subgenius.com.
Get your stuff up.
And you guys are now open.
Big times, good stuff.
See you next time.
Have a great day.
Green pills!
Kill me!