Oh
You know
You know I'm so thankful tonight
That I don't have a lot of money
I don't have a lot of friends
But I have a whole lot
Of diagrams
Of how to position
Or
Steve
Somebody's got a
Conspiracy going on
And you will say
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob
We don't have a lot of money
We don't have a lot of people
And we got a lot of power
Of the wicked Bob
And the spiritual darkness
We asked Bob
To come
And to reveal the conspiracy
In the skies
Above you
And open up
Every deceitful work
Of conspiracy
You know
The things that it's done
The symbols and the emblems
Of Bob
Now
A lot of people
Loved
The hour of
Slug
Actually
They're in bodies
With two legs
They have two eyes
They have two ears
And their mouth
Is filled
With
Bob's
Spiracy
And they're
They're
Looking
At you
I think
We're
We might
Still be
You're
You're still
On
Audio
I'm hearing
I hear you
The listeners
You're hearing
So how do we
Do this
Please be patient
As we
Work through
A brief
Technical difficulty
This is
A skit
It's a skit
It's a skit about people trapped
And they're trapped in a radio show
And then they can't get out
So soon soon soon
There will be an escape
Zombie air
Well you know we got
We're going to stay on here
So why don't we stay on
Until someone shows up
I've got to go out and meet
My ride
Yes and that's your ride right now
Say Byron spin us some more music
Alright we will be working with these technical difficulties
Right at the moment
And I'll be right back
There's water all over the place
The water
The sounds
The various things that are going on
And we are trying to deal
With the technical difficulties at the moment
Ah
No no no no no no it's synthetic it's not even close
I don't understand
What what
I don't understand what are you talking about
No no no
Agnes Agnes listen to me listen to me
It doesn't know where Lloyd is
It doesn't know anything
It only knows what they program it to say
I don't know
No, shut up!
They can't wait for me to come outside.
They've come to collect me.
The experiment is over.
They've come to pick up their petri dish,
and they sent a machine to do it.
Agnes, it is a fucking machine.
You can see for yourself they're sending a machine.
Okay, okay.
Okay?
Okay.
An anti-nation or a loosed-in state of oftentimes
Think about politics at twenty-two
Mixed with your single syllables of fashionable groove
The rest of incoherence and the arrogance of you
With a slight effect in accents you'll be hailed like the true
If it's too stupid to be said it's sung
If it rhymes it'll never be meaningful
You'll never hear a valid point at number one
Cause if it's too stupid to be said it's sung
If it's too stupid to be said it's sung
If it rhymes it'll never seem meaningful
You won't learn anything from radio one
Cause if it's too stupid to be said it's sung
If it's too stupid to be said it's sung
If it rhymes it'll never seem meaningful
You can rock all you like in the midnight zone
But if it's too stupid to be said it's sung
If it's too stupid to be said it's sung
If it rhymes it'll never be meaningful
You'll never hear a valid point at number one
Cause if it's too stupid to be said it's sung
Anyway, I'm going to give a quick rundown on the Church of the Subgenius
for those who don't know what it's all about.
There's really only three things you have to understand.
Bob, which is this guy, well, this is a picture of Bob.
This is not Bob.
We often have to explain.
Oh, right there are more Dobbs heads than you'll ever see anywhere else.
Every little detail in there is a Dobbs head.
Your mind has just been bent beyond comprehension.
I've got you to look at that thing.
Now it's too late.
Memberships are only $30 at the sales table.
Anyway, to put it real quickly, in 1953,
this unusually talented,
but also, and lucky, unbelievably lucky,
but also unbelievably stupid,
salesman, J.R. Bob Dobbs,
was seized up in the spirit
by, not exactly God,
but this alien space monster that calls itself Jehovah One
that has been posing as God to various cultures throughout history.
But to Bob, he told the truth.
Which was that for, since time immemorial,
there's been a conspiracy,
yes, a real conspiracy, not one of these silly ones,
that, I mean, all those other conspiracies,
except Roswell, saucer crashes, and 9-11,
all that, you can believe everything.
Go ahead.
But the real conspiracy is a conspiracy of plain, ordinary, garden-variety, normal people
who automatically, instinctively,
steal away and screw up the slack
of the weirdos, the abnormals, the disbelievers,
and those who will believe anything,
which is probably many of you here.
And the slack of the abnormals,
and we'll get into that a little bit more later,
one thing you won't hear me do is define slack.
That's what you have to do for yourself.
For $30 from us, you can,
you can perform weddings and funerals,
you can, when the aliens finally get here,
you can destroy everybody you ever disliked,
and live forever, you get to do all that for $30,
but we won't tell you what slack is,
because it's different for each individual.
Anyway, Bob kind of kept all these secrets close to his wallet for decades, really.
And just in the late 70s,
he hired me,
and, well I still haven't been paid yet,
but he talked me and my partner Dr. Philo Drummond
into making this little $1 pamphlet
that had his truths all packed into 16 pages.
That damn pamphlet costs almost a buck for print.
So, um, we, strangely enough,
the pamphlet by Bob's Magic,
although 150 book publishers had turned down our book proposal,
this guy found it in the backseat of my sister-in-law's car,
found the little pamphlet, went,
this would make a great book.
To make a long story short,
there's now been like five or six or seven books,
I can't remember, three of them are still in print,
the book of the subgenius is in its 20th printing,
we've been doing the Hour of Slack radio show for 25 years or something,
you'd think I'd get a life.
And I'm not the only one,
there's also a subgenius radio show in Atlanta
and one in San Francisco,
and they're just all over the place.
And we whipped out DVDs,
as seen on Night Flight,
and, uh, if you're that old,
and you name it, it's all over their sales table
where the beautiful Princess Leigh is setting everything up.
Bob?
Who are the overlords of the UFO?
I bring you a warning.
Every one of you listening to my voice,
tell the world,
tell this to everybody wherever they are,
and watch the sky.
This is Doug Smith, radio operator.
I'm gonna bring you a piece of that green cheese for sure.
Shazam?
And I say it is possible
for a giant lizard to have lived there for years without being seen.
The last ball.
You yuck middies.
You bloated idiot.
You stupid fat还有.
That'll hurt.
You.
You bloated idiot.
You stupid fat have.
You.
Come on, shut the fuck up.
It's quite a joke.
I tried the prop.
Groovy.
Right, Bob?
Bob?
Wait a minute.
How did this happen?
We're smarter than this.
Apparently not.
Bob?
Long call, babe.
Don't you know what they're doing to yourself?
Apparently, Bob came and did something
with all of them.
The drugs I took seem to light up my brain.
Bob?
And you ain't earned the last earnest tea bass.
Praise earnest tea bass, friends.
That musical piece was done by yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang,
your host and prayer partner under Bob.
But I made it using a lot of pieces edited by Fernand and Andy Lemur,
who also did our opening noises and credits.
Before that, we heard some of the Starwood Festival revival from last July.
And before that, the great song, if it's too stupid to be said, it's sung,
was by The Attery Squash from an upcoming CD and CD website,
myspace.com slash theattrysquash for more.
There are two Ts in Attery.
The crazy guy ranting was from the movie Bug by William Friedkin,
and now more crazy guys in bugs.
They changed the meridian from the Paris,
meridian which is 2.2 degrees,
and we're concentrating on the number 33.33,
to establish 2012 based on the Paris meridian.
Now, which one would you think would be right?
You see, if they can get you out of time sink,
if they can take you out of knowing the times and the seasons,
they've got your soul.
Satan has enslaved you by changing times and laws.
And basically, the 33.33 degrees north from the equator to Mount Hermon,
the longitude of the Earth based on the Paris meridian,
seems to have been regarded as increasingly sensitive
due to the louder dissemination of knowledge
during the Industrial Revolution and needed to be obstructed.
I don't really understand.
You have to explain to me.
What is it?
What is going on, Peter?
Listen, listen!
If you want to know what is going on,
you have to listen to me.
I've listened to you.
You have to.
I'm listening.
Because you don't know the fucking enormity of what we're dealing with.
May the 29th, 1954.
A consortium of bankers, industrialists, corporate CEOs, and politicians
held a series of meetings over three days at the Bilderberg Hotel in Oosterbeek-Collin.
They drew up a plan for maintaining the status quo.
It's the way things are.
It's the rich get richer.
The poor get poorer.
They devised a plan to manipulate technology, economics, the media, population control,
world religion to keep things the way they are.
And they have continued to meet once a year, every year since the original meeting.
Look it up.
Okay.
Under their orders, the CIA had smuggled Nazi scientists into the States
to work with the American military at Cowspan,
developing an inter-epidermal tracking microchip.
A what?
It's a surveillance tool.
It's a computer chip that has been implanted in the skin of every human.
Being born on the planet since 1982.
The test group for the prototype was the People's Temple.
And when the Reverend Jim Jones threatened to expose them,
he and every member of his church were assassinated.
Oh, Jesus.
But it's not enough just to attract people to spy on them.
They want control.
Yeah.
So they create the intelligence, manned, interface, biochip,
a subcutaneous transponder, a computer chip imprinted with living brain cells.
They needed lab rats to...
They tested and they found us.
Me in the Gulf and another soldier working at Cowspan at the time,
Tim McVeigh.
Oh, wait.
They turned us into fucking zombies.
Remote control assassins.
And then they picked Tim up, chucked him in the prison factory,
but I found my chip and I cut it out.
So they sent me back to the lab for further testing and a new experiment.
You're John Doe number two.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
That's who they want me to be.
That is the flaw in the IMI biochip.
They can't get to everybody.
People slip through the cracks.
They find the chip, they cut it out.
Like me or Ted Kaczynski.
They need a chip that will self-perpetuate,
that will spread like a virus
that people can pass to each other, to everyone.
They got it!
Oh, you mean the bugs.
They got the bugs.
A living, breathing organism.
Oh, my God!
The ultimate parasite implanted by a queen bug,
the supermother who mates with the drone, lays egg cells,
and the body of the host,
and governs a growing army of rapidly multiplying brainwashing bugs.
They gave those things to you and you gave them to me.
You gave those fucking things to me!
Baby!
What?
Well, of course you did!
Agnes!
I want you to know
that I'm happy for you.
I want nothing but
the best for you.
Oh.
And all a version of me
is being promoted like me.
Will he go down you in a theater?
Does he speak eloquently?
And will you have his baby?
I'm sure you'll really make an excellent mother.
But the love you gave and we made was it able to be
good enough for you to be open wide?
No.
And every time you look at me,
I just think it's me.
Because you know how you hope you'll hold me until you die.
But you're still alive.
Because I'm here
to remind you
of the mess you left when you went away.
It's not fair
to deny me
of the cross I did that you gave to me.
You wanna know
what I know?
Things seem very well.
You look peaceful.
I'm not quite as well.
But thought you should know.
Did you forget about me?
Mrs. Duplicity?
I hate to bug you in the middle of the fair.
There was a snap in the face.
How quickly I was replaced.
And all you're thinking of me
when he fucks you.
But the love you gave and we made was it able to be
good enough for you to be open wide?
No.
And every time you speak his name
does he know how you hope you'll hold me until you die?
But you're still alive.
Because I'm here
to remind you
of the mess you left when you went away.
It's not fair
to deny me
of the cross I did that you gave to me.
You wanna know
oh
and it should be me and the man that was mean.
I'm not gonna feel this.
So close your eyes.
Oh, don't you know it.
And every time my stress fails.
And someone else's back.
And I'm out here waiting.
I know you feel it, I can feel it, cause I'm here to remind you of the mess you left when you went away.
It's not fair to deny me of the cross I bear that you gave to me.
Cause I'm here to remind you of the mess you left when you went away.
You ought to know.
The Duke of Uke did it, live at the Portland Subgenius Devival last October.
The Duke's website is hard to read out, but you'll find links to all of our musical contributors on the log of each show at subgenius.com and click on the radio button.
Now back to Starwood and following that, a nice juicy excerpt from a really great movie called The Invention of Lying.
Friends, really, and this is an honest statement.
The Church of the Subgenius is the only alternative to work that absolutely does not involve wealth.
I can promise you that.
Wearing that subgenius t-shirt for sale right over there might be the only thing, the one single thing that keeps you from getting a raise at your job.
Now you just think about that.
Work, work, work, work, work.
It's tiring just thinking about it, ain't it?
Work makes me tired.
Does it make you tired?
And after you finish working, what do they make you do?
Retire.
So it says all you get, work, work, work.
And I want you to, when you visit our sales table over there and speak with our beautiful swaggers, we call them, they sell our swag.
You just think about that.
Keep me from working, friends.
And keep them busy.
This is Phil Proctor.
And David Osman.
Of the Firesign Theater.
And we're enjoying listening to the hour of slag.
I'm slacking off myself.
24 hours ago, Mark Bellison was just your typical nobody writer.
Today, people are saying he has new information about what happens after you die.
I know some things, some very important things about...
What happens to you after you die.
Everything you need to know is written on these pizza boxes.
Number one, there is a man in the sky who controls everything.
Number two...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What does he look like?
Tall, big hands, making stuff, good head of hair.
What ethnicity is he?
He's a new...
Type of ethnicity.
He's a mixture of all our ethnicities.
Does he live in the clouds?
No.
Do we see him?
He lives higher than the clouds, too high to see him.
So he lives in space?
Not that high.
Sort of in the thermosphere?
Sorry, people.
I've got a lot to get through here.
I mean, just...
Man lives in the sky.
You can't see him.
He controls everything.
Cool?
Good.
Number two.
Number three.
When you die, you don't disappear into an eternity of nothingness.
Instead, you go to a really great place.
Number three.
In that place, everyone will get a mansion.
What kind of mansion?
The best mansion you could think of.
I was thinking of a horrible mansion.
Well, no.
It's the best mansion you could ever think of.
Not the one you're thinking of right now, but ever.
Whatever the best mansion...
Whatever mansion is you'd like, that's the one you're gonna get.
Number four.
When you die, all the people you love will be there.
Will they have their own mansions?
Yeah.
Yeah, of course.
Everyone gets a mansion.
What if I want them to live in my mansion?
Well, that's fine.
They'll leave their mansion.
They'll come and live with you, won't they?
What happens to their mansion?
I don't know.
It goes back on the market.
Can we...
Number five.
When you die, there will be free ice cream.
For everyone.
All day and all night.
Whatever.
What are the flavors you can think of?
Even bad flavors?
Why would you think of bad flavors?
You just said every flavor I could think of.
Oh, no.
I just thought of vanilla and scones.
Well, don't eat that then.
I just thought the chocolate sauce was diarrhea.
Well, don't put that on the ice cream then.
What is the matter with you people?
Can we...
Please.
Number six.
If you do bad things, you won't get to go to this great place when you die.
Where will you go?
A terrible place.
The worst place imaginable.
What constitutes a bad thing?
All things.
It's painful crimes, rape, murder, things like that.
Is punching someone bad?
Yes.
What if they're trying to hurt you?
No, it's fine.
Is cursing bad?
No.
What about being late for work?
No, that's fine.
I mean, you might lose your job if the boss doesn't like it, but it won't affect what
happens to you after you die.
What about if you forget to feed your dog?
Well, then if you forget, I mean, it's bad for the dog.
If the dog dies, it's bad.
But it's not...
I mean, don't do it on purpose.
Don't buy a dog just to starve it for a laugh.
But...
It's fine.
I mean...
If I do just one bad thing, do I go to that bad place?
No.
You get three chances.
Three bad things...
And you're out.
Like baseball.
So long, Mr. Briggs.
So, anything else?
Yeah.
Oh, please, can we just move on?
No.
We have to know everything that's bad.
Fine.
Is it bad to wear pants?
We've been through this.
The main ones are things like hurting people physically on purpose, okay?
Taking their stuff.
Doing things to people they don't want done.
Murdering people on purpose.
Okay.
Number nine.
The man in the sky who controls everything decides if you go to the good place or the
bad place.
He also decides who lives and who dies.
Does he cause natural disasters?
Yes.
Did he cause my mom to get cancer?
No.
Yes.
Did he cause that tree to land on my car last week?
Yeah.
Did he kill my dad with that heart attack?
I say fuck the man that lives in the sky!
Yeah, that guy's evil!
That guy's a coward, hiding up there doing bad things to us.
Why doesn't he do it to our faces?
We have to stop that evil bastard before he kills us all.
Wait, wait, listen.
The man who lives in the sky and controls everything is also responsible for all the
good stuff that happens.
He's the guy that saved my life on that fishing trip when the boat capsized?
Yes.
Did he capsize the boat?
Yeah.
He killed my grandmother and left me those millions of dollars?
You bet, yes.
So he's the one who cured my mom's cancer?
Yeah.
So he's the one who saved my mom's life?
So he's kind of a good guy, but he's also kind of a prick, too.
Right, but check this out, okay?
Number 10.
Even if the man in the sky does bad stuff to you, he makes up for it by giving you an
eternity of good stuff after you die.
As long as you don't do any of that bad stuff that you mentioned, right?
Yeah, of course.
So it's kind of a test.
Yeah.
Well, that's everything I know.
How do you know all these things?
Because the man in the sky told me.
Yeah, well, how come we're just finding out about these things now, millions of years
into our existence?
I forgot.
I've seen all the stuff he does.
Thank you.
That was all from the invention of lying, which, as you might surmise, is a very subgenius
leaf film, whether it knows it or not.
It came out very recently, and I would recommend it.
But now, a cover of the Negative Land song, Roy, Store And Sportsline from the 180Gs of
negativeland.com.
All right, and we will be talking about anything from Pico to Popnoe.
Now, this is the music for Negative Land.
Oh, whatever you wanna do
Soda gum, chewing water, whatever is up
Somebody asked me one time
What is chewing water?
I'm like, you know
It's ice as we used to call it
But same difference
And it's better than cold coffee
I'll tell you that
Okay, let's
Let's take a chance and see what's going on
Hello, who's this?
Join us in a glass of beer
Join us what?
I see
I didn't think three-year-old kids would be up this late
I don't know
There's gotta be a way
We thought they weren't on TV
We were wrong
Well, we'll get enough of those and put them together
And just turn it over to them
They can't handle it
Can't do anything to children anyhow
So it probably wouldn't do any good
Eventually we'll be on
We'll have this thing set up
So that we can
Let the little kids like that can't
Play around
Or at least the big boys
With the little kid brains
Or like they say
Another brain
And it'd be a half-wit
Hello there
You wanna talk about the 49ers?
Hi, I'm Gene Stapleton
A PTA member
Hello there, PTA member
You wanna talk about the PTA or football?
Um, considering
I'm serving on natural resource
Oh, I see, okay
I thought you had to
Facilitate it this time of day
But you can't figure that one out
Oh, oh, oh, oh, well
They got the kicks out of that now
And that'll keep them happy for school
And us, we'll go back to the PAM now
We'll go back to the PAM now
Another brain
And it'd be a half-wit
Hello there
This is Peter Schofield speaking
Another one of those idiots
How do we allow them to be on the air this long?
You know
Does that make you feel good, fella?
You feel real happy now?
You're cheating, huh?
This is Peter Schofield
I wonder what's up
I wonder if their parents know that they do these things
Or maybe they don't have parents
Maybe they were hatched rather than born
I think that's it
As I said before
Give them another brain and they'd be a half-wit
But what do you expect from dropouts?
And now we go down to line two
Line two
Do we do
One of the uh
We go to line two
Okay, line two
Hello
Give them another brain and they'd be
That's right
That's about the way it would be
Did you call him back?
You got his telephone number?
Okay
As long as I
You got his telephone number
I'll be getting the number tomorrow
You got the recording
So we got it made
It would
Take more than a
Even a
Another brain
As long as you got the number
That's what counts
Okay
So we took care of the gender by now I think
Or we will tomorrow
Hi, Mother
You're late today
I was having a cold with some of the gang
Mother
Bob
Was having a party this Saturday night
No, I'm afraid not
Marion
It's too much work and worry and money
What's too much work and worry and money?
Oh, Marion has some idea about having
Bob
Over some night
I'd have to break and go to a lot of trouble
Bob
Was having a party this Saturday, Dad
That's wonderful
Sounds like a lot of fun
You haven't seen much
Bob
Lately, have you?
I used to think you two were great pals
I know
I seem to have gotten out of touch with
Bob
Somehow
And it seems to me
They were always the ones
Who didn't seem quite to fit in with me
And who didn't fit in with the others
Mother, may I be excused?
I have some homework to do
Yes
She ought to know how to talk to Bob
It does seem that Marion's left out of the gang
More and more lately
She's just a child
Maybe it'd do her some good to have a little party
Nothing elaborate
Mal, why are you getting so excited all of a sudden?
Well, I'll tell you, Evelyn
Bob
Don't get me wrong
Marion's a wonderful kid
I think she studies chemistry
Too much
What's got into you, Mal?
Some people don't appreciate you until they get to know you
I can remember kids like that
I just want Bob
I suppose what you mean is
No
No, Evelyn, that isn't what I mean at all
Bob
Always seemed to be snaring and giggling at me
Evelyn, I didn't mean to upset you like this
I know Bob
And I understand Bob
And I like Bob
But
Well, you know you are shy
And back in school
I suppose you're right, Malcolm
To tell you the truth
I'm scared to have Bob over here
I never knew how to act or what to say
It's different with boys
You give them a piece of it and it's all the same to them
The most successful people
Weren't always the most popular kids
Remember Bob back in the days at school
He was a good boy
He was always on the fringe
The way you say Marion is
But he's the most popular and successful man
Yes, I remember
But somewhere along the line
Bob learned to get along with other people
Or he wouldn't be the community leader he is today
Maybe I could arrange a little party for her
But I'll need your help
I think I will have some more coffee
Well
Now all we have to worry about is whether Bob is going to call or not
Let's g-
Hello, I'm Joey Perkins with the KKK
It's okkk to blackout
Joey Perkins with the KKK
I guess you could call it a bad O-R-G
Where'er Joey Perkins with the Vitterproblem
You sleep badly down the road
So cover up history, doubt tradition.
From PR News in Washington, I'm strained since the Archbishop's unprecedented invitation for homosexual sex in the hotel's courtyard
when he snuck out for a secret rendezvous with his sex mistress in South America.
Pope Benedict XVI is homosexual for the first time since the Roman Catholic Church invited Anglicans to vote on whether to allow PR reports to move forward.
For Senator Reid, it's been a week of denying coverage to those with pre-existing PR news.
Like me.
President Obama's angry about PR news and homosexuals.
Tonight, the U.S. Senate is using the party's overwhelming dominance to undermine democracy in recent regional elections.
From Washington, a rocket hit PR News.
Here they are on their way to school on a beautiful spring day.
But no matter where they go or what they do, they always try to remember what to do if the atom bomb explodes right then.
We believe the U.S. is an impossible powerful Russia.
our first clutch
erg
all
we
man
movement
there's my
Try it, and crawl with fun!
You can crawl again, you crying children!
Here they are on their way to school...
Here they are, here they are...
Here they are on their way to school on a beautiful spring day...
It's a bomb, it's a bomb!
Nothing can cover it!
The
idea that America or any country values individuality
is the highest ideal is a cheap myth.
Everybody's an individualist,
but they don't like individuals.
Perhaps in simpler times it was true,
but no modern industrial death culture
can really afford a population of unpredictables.
Um, um, Bob, please just,
you have to believe in everything.
Bob, please just,
you have, you have, you have to believe in it.
you have to believe in everything.
And especially, um,
especially, especially,
um, you have to believe in
the God that tells you not to believe in it
because he doesn't want you to know
what he's been doing to you.
I don't forget!
You can crawl!
And crawl with Brad!
You can crawl again!
You can crawl again, children!
Somebody called PMC did that mix
using ancient audio clips
available from subgenius.com.
Before that, Lemurs, PR News,
a short Norell Pref cut,
and a Phineas Narco edit of The Bob Party.
Now, an oldie from The Psychoskeletons,
available at soundclick.com
slash the psychoskeletons.
The Psychoskeletons
We don't want no ad.
Diprise-tics.
We want the days of ad.
We don't want no ad.
Diprise-tics.
We don't want no,
guitar solo
We don't want no antiprice
Is it true about your film?
Nova told us that anyone who sees it, you know...
Goes insane?
You'd think they'd blown it a bit out of proportion.
But they didn't.
In fact, if anything, they played it down.
It's about 25 minutes in.
The people went mad.
Ripping it.
They were tearing at each other.
Tearing at their own eyes.
It was the Hamburg Film Festival.
They almost tore down the theater.
They couldn't get rid of the smell.
Or the blood.
It was horrible.
What's it about?
My film is based on a real cult.
A group of fanatics founded back in the time of Constantine.
A powerful group.
More ancient than the Templars or the Illuminati.
Kind of like Lovecraft, you know?
If that stuff was real.
They predicted the rise of a second messiah.
It's all in my film.
Don't tell the authorities, but I have a print of the film.
What?
We could watch it together.
Cool.
That evil.
That thing that happened.
It's something in the audience.
Something to grow.
Something that feeds on the crowd.
I've seen it dozens of times.
Mel's seen it too, right?
And she's perfectly fine.
These are dark times.
The end times predicted by Bob.
Stupid idiots.
Dressing up in stupid clothes.
Preaching whatever it takes to get you to buy.
These are dark times.
The end times predicted by Bob.
Did I mention the one law of our church?
You know, every religion has to have lots of rules.
Just, if for no other reason than to dislike the next religion down the road over their different rules.
It's not that we love Bob so much.
It's that we love the idea of everybody else burning in hell.
Let's get face it.
You know, we're just like any other religious group.
But our one law.
The one single philosophical rule we have.
Kids, cover your ears.
Fuck them if they can't take a joke.
And you can live by that.
Reverend Pickles, there's been reading his pre-scriptures.
You really can live by that.
I mean, it's an old saying.
It's not Bob's copyrighted line.
In fact, in Latin, it has been found scrawled upon walls.
Copula eam senon posit acceptera jocularum.
I may have that a little bit wrong, but that's not my fault.
It was the graffiti writers.
Bob also said,
The Lord is a sock puppet for idiots.
And then he followed that with the odd phrase,
J.R. Bob Dobbs is a trick on subgeniuses.
I don't know.
Friends, as we've told you time and time again,
the Church of the Subgenius is not here to forgive your sins.
We don't care about your sins.
It's here to rationalize your sins.
Bob brings not forgiveness,
because he's not that well connected and he doesn't care.
He brings an excuse.
And you can, it comes with our ordainment kit.
A big frameable document that lawyers really love.
You have to be kind and honest.
Sahaja Gita Gita.
Sahaja Gita!
It's at the bottom of my heart
Thank you.
I'm living in Arizona.
Living in Arizona.
was done
guitar solo
Bye, Mom
Bye, Dad
I gotta go into space now, Mom
I gotta get into the rocket ship
I gotta go into space, Mom
Dad, I gotta go
And I'm never coming home
Yeah