Well, I hear my train a-longin', hear my train a-hangin', hear my train a-longin'.
Ah, yes, dear friends, welcome to the subgenius radio ministry, Hour of Watch.
Do you have a strange taste in your mouth?
Is there an accurate flavor in your mind that won't go away?
Do you believe the silence that's coming soon is gonna take you away like a big river?
You do believe it too, do you?
It's said when the wind blows that way, the plutonium storms are gonna come.
The less likely to cause lesions in the skin.
The Iron Man!
Hey, hey, hold it down, Dave.
Shh, humans.
Humans, man.
Uh, yes, dear friends, as Einstein's secret orchestra and lonesome cowboy Dave
champs away in the background,
we're back in Dallas.
I'm back in Dallas.
I said I was gonna stay at Brushwood Campground
and the Iron Man.
I didn't know until the saucers came, but I had to return.
For now.
But join me, won't you?
And we'll both return to fabled Brushwood Campground via the magic of sound recordings.
And also we shall voyage back in time to myth-shrouded Cleveland,
city of mystery astride the flaming river.
The Burnt Testicle City.
Where Einstein's secret orchestra and lonesome cowboy Dave
and Stang's secret radio station can be heard.
And offer great rewards for adventurous risk-takers.
Heh, heh, heh, heh.
Uh.
He thought he smelled something or someone burning.
It was.
It was the smell of flesh.
And he remembered it was so many years ago.
His own grandfather caught himself afire that day.
Dreaming in a bed.
Heh, heh, heh, heh.
Goodbye, Grandpa.
Goodbye.
So much work to do setting Gramps on fire.
And it's hot in here in Dallas, friends.
It's very hot.
The A.C. is on high.
But so is the sun.
And I must get off.
And you must get off.
And we will get off, friends.
Wait till you hear some of these fantabulous recordings
from X-Day and Starwood and various bands
who have showered us with great material.
We have the Pufferdome and Starwood Devivals.
We've got Little Theodore at XX Day.
We've got Hallie DeFestern, the wonderful chick singer.
We have a new, sort of a pagan comedian
named Loki E. Coyote from wickabilly.com.
And let's see, Maggie Pearson, E.J.
And over here on the cassettes, why, oh, friends, look.
We have Global.
Village Idiots.
That used to be Tri-State Killing Spree, live at XX Day.
Lust in Space, live at XX Day.
Clyde Lewis' Ground Zero show.
The Firesign Theater.
The Firesign Clones.
And ESO Radio.
And, of course, the beautiful Friday Jones scene here on slide three.
Thank y'all.
You don't have to be a Texas redneck.
To sell your soul to Bob.
Though it helps.
You can be a Yankee.
You can be a Yank-er as well.
You know, Bob didn't say we had to save everybody.
He said we had to get everybody's money.
Right.
Now, I was thinking, I heard once that if there was a man who had a lot of money,
and then there was a woman, an old lady who, like, had this Social Security check,
and it was like, maybe she had like five or ten dollars.
And she wanted to contribute to the church.
Who does Bob love more?
The woman who works hard to give that small amount of money that she has?
Or the rich man?
Who does Bob love more?
I imagine Bob is probably hanging out with the Sultan of Brunei and Bill Gates right now
while we're asking that question.
I mean, sure, of course, the little old lady may have more slack,
may understand Bob's message better,
and perhaps that 25 cents to her means as much,
as that rich man's grandchildren do to him.
But it doesn't mean as much to Bob.
That's right.
Because Bob's not a stupid preacher.
You don't want the kind of preacher that's, you know, that's going to prove himself.
I mean, you know, well, actually, what can I say, Bob?
This is called the church of the subgenius.
And it doesn't matter in this religion if you're smart or dumb.
It's not the subgenius.
It's the intelligence that counts it all.
Bob's been saying all along it's the common sense, sense of humor,
and dollars and cents that count.
And would you rather be smart these days or lucky?
Which is going to get you more dates?
Which is going to get you more luck on dates?
Well, money, of course.
Well, money is not everything if you're not lucky.
Luck is everything, whether there is money or not.
Whether you've got brains, money, or anything.
Luck, obviously, is...
And what Bob preaches is that if you follow the path of least resistance and let your instincts pull you towards the slack,
then your luck will improve.
And you won't have to work as hard in order to gain the riches.
Bob isn't like some commie that wants everybody to be equally poor all over the whole world.
He wants every... It's just the opposite.
He wants everybody to be equally rich.
Beyond imagining, but without working.
Without any work at all.
Perfect slack.
Perfect achieving-ness without even trying.
So it's smarter to be lucky than lucky to be smart, right?
Am I getting this right?
I don't know if I...
Yeah, who cares how smart you are if you're lucky?
Okay.
Ignorance is bliss.
Okay. I'm just trying to...
Why do you think we call it subgenius?
You know, if it was for some kind of smarty pants people, they could go join Mensa.
And follow H. Ross Perot or some brilliant fellow like that.
Okay.
Damn it.
I discovered the church in 1981.
I was reading a copy of Weirdo No. 1, the Robert Crown...
Robert Crown.
And it said, are you abnormal?
Then you are probably superior to everyone else.
And that to me said something so important because nobody had ever given me an affirmation.
About being such a fucked up weirdo.
And I thought that it was a bad thing until I found this damn church.
Damn church.
And like most of us, I wouldn't even be alive today without having had this fucking church in my life.
Keeping me going for 18 goddamn years.
Woo!
Awesome!
I just sit here watching squirrels.
They have much more fun than me.
Sometimes they run around all day in circles.
They fight and squabble then they lick their wounds.
At least they seem to have a purpose.
My mind's always clogged with leaves.
Like silly stupid advertising jingles.
And theme some TV shows I do not like.
I must not go out the front door.
I could get hit by a car.
Just like the squirrels when a dog is growling.
There's perfect safety high up in the tree.
I know I'm bad to just sit here.
I should not be so afraid.
But once outside I'd have to choose a direction.
It might be the wrong one so I'll stay here.
I'm not afraid of the squirrels.
They tell me of self-improvement.
And someday I could even have a job.
Then I would have become just like the squirrels.
I don't see how I could accomplish that.
First I'd have to choose a direction.
Like which tree I should start to climb.
They all seem to be up to the challenge.
I just take whatever's given me.
So I'm okay here just watching squirrels.
Though the soundtrack could be much improved.
Those silly stupid advertising jingles.
And some TV shows I do not like.
Wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah.
Wah wah wah wah wah wah wah.
Wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah.
Wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah.
Wah wah wah wah wah wah wah.
Wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah.
Wah!
Amazing, dear friends.
Little Theodore and Babushka
live at X-Day.
So at X-Day,
there was a question and answer period
and somebody said,
why Dallas?
And G. Gordon Gordon said,
well, if you were going to give the state of Texas an enema,
Dallas is where you would insert the nozzle.
And then some idiot said,
why Sherman, New York?
And we all said,
duh!
And really, that's what the church of the subgenius
is all about.
The moment when everybody can just agree,
duh!
Duh!
When they go,
well, what does that Bob thing mean anyway?
And when all you have to do is go,
duh!
Then I could shut up.
Job would be a lot easier.
Don't we need...
You almost forget you're drifting miles and miles.
Yeah, that's funny.
Doesn't it feel just completely real in here, guys?
I mean, more or less.
I mean, it's a little bit disorienting,
but it feels just like down is that way, right?
Doesn't it, Dave?
Is there anybody that's besides me
who feels like down might be anywhere else but there?
And the air, right?
Take a deep breath.
See, it's just like real air.
Yeah.
Come.
Come here.
The voice of the sand.
The sacred sand of Cape Canaveral calls to you.
Come here.
The voice of the sand.
And now as Rev Chas leads the procession of the Rocketeers
across the field,
we wonder what these young people are going to do.
Will this be another barn?
Yes.
down immolation and the likes of Heaven's Gate and Waco mixed together?
Or will these doctors learn to cooperate, live, love,
and leave Earth together? We can only wait and see.
I think it's just too soon to tell right now, but
there's a great deal of tension in the air, a great deal of sweat,
a lot of heat. This could be the
big one. And here come the rear guard aliens.
I have a device in my nasal cavity which I believe is navigating this vessel now.
All I can see through the inside of my
sinus is it looks like there's a monitor.
And yes, yes, right before, let me get the, right there, my tinea gland.
Oh, John, that's right, that's my tinea gland.
Don't let anything happen today. It's known.
It's the only thing between us and total fatness of outer space.
And don't let Bob's pipe go out. It's the only thing between you
and believing everything on TV.
It's also the only thing between you and believing
everything on TV.
Bob says, which would be just as bad, believe me.
I did, look at me.
Hold it right there.
Oh, glad to. Now I think I'll hold it over here.
Oh, boy, it's nice out.
Yes, I think I'll leave it out.
Hey, hey, look, fellas, fun's fun, okay, but I've got to find a place to stay.
It'll be night soon. I'm tired.
Aw.
I'm lost.
What's the matter with that dude?
I want to go to bed.
Oh, my bony boy in the Estonian.
I'm tamed for you.
You're asleep, leaning up against the windfall.
I was but a mere prat then.
I'll never forget the time a snake slithered into my wife.
I was but knee-high to a merry grasshopper then.
Never saw the woman again.
Oh, no, no, that's all very interesting,
but the sun is going down.
Oh, no, no, you're all confused.
The horizon is moving up.
Hey, hey, hey, listen, come on, you guys.
Help me, please.
I know, I know.
Let's stand him on his head.
Hey, hey, hey, put me down.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Now you see, now it's morning.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, help!
Oh, he's no fun.
He fell right over.
In the heart of a city that has no heart,
there's a building where only the stool pigeons come to roost.
Step in the elevator, press 13, then use the stairs.
At the end of the hallway, there's a frosted glass door.
Oh, you pervert!
I didn't tell you to go in there.
Turn left.
See that door with the bloodshot eye on it?
It's not a psychic.
It's not an oculist.
It's a dick.
America's only detective.
He's ready for action.
He's ready for adventure.
He's...
Nick Danger, third eye.
Hello.
I want to order.
I want an anchovy to go and hold the pizza.
Anchovy?
Yes.
A little flat thing with eyes.
I don't care what you look like.
You're wasting my time.
I spell my name D...
Oh, uh, the way it's spelled.
Danger.
What?
I've been working really hard,
but I finally had a peaceful night passed out in my file cabinet.
I just finished my biggest case.
A case I like to call
the case of the...
The case of bourbon.
I don't remember exactly how it ended,
but I know it began something like this.
Ah.
My favorite.
Old plane wrap.
Aged on the shelf.
Like me.
Uh-oh.
Don't hang up!
I couldn't hang up.
You see, I've been hung up on this fortune cooking ever since I could remember.
Remember what?
What were we talking about?
Me.
Nancy.
You.
My heart began to beat like a wet hamburger.
This daemon short-ordered me before, so I knew I had to play it tough.
What do you want, baby?
Big tips?
Oh, Nicky, Nicky, I really need you this time.
It's the snakes.
The stench of magnolia's the old man.
and his desires, the script, the background music.
I'm scared!
Oh my gosh!
Where are you, Nancy?
Page three, the Van Pedderancey mansion, interior, night.
You say, don't turn the page.
Don't turn the page, baby.
I'm on my way.
What?
Not to touch the tiny blonde women!
That is the law!
We're not the enemy!
Not to...
Huh?
Not to breach the airlock!
That is the law!
Never to breach thy moon pants!
That is the third commandment.
To covet not thy neighbor's rights.
To covet not thy rocket ship.
And if you retrieve the tenth commandment, if you retrieve any alien life forms,
they must be quarantined, no matter how sexy they may appear to be.
Praise God!
That is the law!
We are not men!
No, we're just not man enough.
But no.
We got the little laugh, squid suckers.
It just sticks to the roof of your mouth right, you know?
Yes, but now for a limited time only, with just a small amount of your own sputum, your own Jolly juices,
and some policeman's feces and a can of tomatoes, you can whip up a beautiful feast that'll probably fascinate everything.
I think it's...
Wait a minute.
The studio's filling up with water.
There's a lot of rats in here, man.
Wait a minute.
There's a lot of rats in the room right now.
That's okay.
Bent?
Come out here, Bent!
Get the rest of the rats.
Shoo them away, Bent!
Come on, Bent!
Come on, little Bent!
We were always nice to you.
We always shared our corn with you.
Where the hell is he?
I don't know.
Is he in your hat?
No, he's not in my hat.
I think...
Oh, dear.
Is he in your moon pants?
No, he's not in my moon...
Well, he has to be in the cylinder here with us somewhere.
Is he in your breasticolaries?
Can you mind if I just put my...
I don't think so.
Come, just let me put my hand down there and see if...
Oh, yeah.
You'd better check.
I better...
Let me check inside of your moon pants.
Okay.
You just...
Yeah, here's...
Oh, let's see.
Okay.
No, this doesn't feel like Bent.
This isn't it.
This isn't it either.
Gee, there's a lot of things in your moon pants.
But none of these things feel like a rat.
Well, this...
No, this isn't a rat.
It doesn't have any whiskers.
Hey, come on, baby.
That's my hamster you're talking about.
You have a whiskerless hamster in your pants.
No, no, no.
That's just from some of the burns.
It's just...
I had a lot of surgery, too.
Oh, you have a lot of things down there.
Don't you think it's kind of a magnification?
It shouldn't be, do you?
Yeah, well, yeah.
I mean, everything in here is uniquely different.
It's quite amazing.
Yeah, that's the draw, isn't it?
I mean...
It's better than Noah's Ark, except instead of two of everything, there's just one of
everything in your moon pants.
Yeah, just one of me and one of you.
Let me see if he's down there in your...
Come on.
Just let me get under by you.
Let me just see over there.
No, I don't think he'd fit down there.
Down there?
I don't think he's down there.
I better feel something.
No, maybe he's in my shoes.
Did he?
I think he's better keep my hand there for a little bit longer, because in case...
What if he appears on your barstool, please?
Yeah, he might.
You might have to grab him.
He might leap out somewhere.
Yeah, I don't want to go checking anywhere else until I check this area really good,
you know what I mean?
Yeah, maybe I should start, you know...
Helping me.
... squeezing.
Yeah, you could probably help me.
I should very...
You know, in case he's hiding somewhere under one of these things...
Yeah, make sure they're sticking up real high, because you know...
Yeah, maybe I should try and squeeze them out.
Yeah, I should help you with that.
Yeah, I should probably help you with that, too.
He should be able to...
He could be...
Ben!
I'm just sad, but that's just the way it got set up.
We can't help it if we have to lie our asses off to get the rest of the cavemen to bring
us food.
Not sad!
That's just a joke, by the way!
That's not too frat!
That is the law!
Yeah.
Actually, Ken Kesey.
He said that was the only sin was fretting.
Well, that's not true.
We came up with 365 more that are in Revelation X, and I double dog dare anybody here to try
all 365 of those sins and report back on us and send the pictures.
They're very creative.
Oh, hell, it's this girl's piano.
How do you...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, and I'm just damn sorry about this!
Sorry isn't a word.
This is just not fair.
Not to not be funny for half a second.
That is the law!
We are not men!
Never to say anything uncool!
That is the law!
We are not men!
Oh, never to have a funny haircut!
That is the law!
We are not men!
Never to a chasing fox!
the secretary around guests and co-workers.
We're going to report you.
That is the law.
We're never to go to work without
makeup and a nice dress.
That is the law.
We are not men
not to sniff
the visitor's legs and
crotchets.
That is the law.
Also, we are not men
not to snuffle up
drink guests.
Fuck the law. We will snuffle up
drink from the street.
We will go on all fours.
We will fornicate
all we really need.
We will eat flesh
or cheat
junk food.
Fuck the law.
We are not men.
One jackal laughing in the distance.
One is mad.
One has overdone the psychogenic
routine.
Uh-oh.
There must be some kind of
way out of here.
There's too much
confusion.
I can't get no relief.
Businessmen
drink my wine.
Clown men dig my
herb.
Not one of them along the
line knows what any of them
is worth.
We want the world
and we want it
now.
We want the world
and we want it
now.
Swipe into the
library while watching
learn about how
what's
Found some empty bottles sitting on a shelf
But when are you gonna find
When are you gonna find
When will you find me, find me, find me, find me, find me
On sale
Found inner peace
And you found outer space
And you found ancient Greece
And a free parking place
Found yourself a socialist and a lot about your wealth
But when are you gonna find
Yeah, when are you gonna find
When will you find, you find, you find, you find, you find yourself
On sale
You've been looking in a kitchen
Looking in a house, babe
Looking in your bedroom
Looking all over the wall
The way that you are talking
You should be walking tall
But you crawl, you crawl, you crawl, you crawl away from yourself
On sale
Then on sale
This morning
You found an echo in the bloom
Found what once had been a suitcase
Hard and vacant
Like a tune
Found the notes and hope
This finds you in good mental health
But when are you gonna find
When are you gonna find
When will you find
You'll find
You'll find, you'll find Me !
You'll find, you'll find, You'll find, you'll find
You'll find Yourself...
Uhhh
Hallie DeVest een dear friends
Hallie DeVest een is the name of the singer
And here's the contact number.
Bagel and Rat Recording, 328 Flatbush Avenue, Suite 287.
That's 328 Flatbush Avenue, number 287, Brooklyn, New York, 11238.
Hallie DeVestern.
And friends, we've also been listening to ESO.
Einstein Secret Orchestra and the Firesign Clones and the Firesign Theater
and Little Theodore and Susie the Floozy and Clyde Lewis' radio show.
And we'll be back with the addresses at the end of the broadcast.
Thank you.
I tried heroin last night.
And you know what?
I liked it.
A lot.
But don't worry about me.
I won't get hooked.
Don't worry about me.
I can put it down just like a book for a good friend.
It felt so good.
I knew it would.
Just like they said.
And maybe one day I might, who knows, try it again.
I did it all by myself.
And you know what?
What?
It was easy.
Easy.
Real easy.
Well, I used a sock to tie it up.
And when my thing popped out, I slid it in real slow.
Oh, well, it went a little.
It felt kind of weird.
But when it all was in, it felt so good.
I could stare at my shoe for like 10 hours.
But it was 10 hours.
Whoa, yeah!
Ah, said I do it every day.
Look, that ballerina thinks my Girl With Luv was in love.
You don't know that my boy, Iederyah Budlebeber, is gonna kidnap my daddy.
Are you okay?
Especially when a girl gets hurt.
Is that how you feel?
Well, that's something I do.
Hey!
I
Yeah
Cool
So
I did it
Just one more time
Just one more
time
One more time
Just one more time
She's in her time
Well, you're a mystic sister and you've been through puberty
And you think you might be pagan and you want community
You meet a sex magician who tells you how it will be
He claims the door is locked and only he has got the key
He calls himself an elder but he's only 33
He's got merry me, he merry parts your legs to bliss and be
He says you best get used to it, it's part of the religion
You think he might be full of shit but you're a trusting pigeon
He takes you to a circle and the priest gives you a shovin'
Says we like polyamory and lots of carnal lovin'
So if you fuck my friends and me we'll let you in our coven
And if you want some family we'll put one in your oven
Which war? Twitch lore
Which war? Pitch score
Which war? Pitch gore
Is he a lady conqueror or just a soldier in a witch war?
You think we get enough grief from the right-wing critics?
We shouldn't have to fight each other like some feral creatures
I hear there's trouble brewing with the voodons and the wiccans
They're sacrificing values and they're sacrificing chickens
And some folks scam the new age kids because they're easy pickets
A bunch of pagan characters right out of Charles Dickens
I thought that being pagan meant we all should get along
And that every path has value and there is no right or wrong
But every time there's power there's no right or wrong
There are those who try to grab it
Like someone comes along and takes a whackin' lorry cabot
Some other pool shoes pack like Elmer, but out huntin' wabbit
They wind up comin' off like Luke Costello and Bud Abbott
Which war? Pitch score
Which war? Pitch gore
Which war? Switch gore
Yo, I ain't no carnivore, I got no stomach for a witch war
I knew a couple women who were married to each other
And they were polyamorous and soon they found another
And then a jealous friend of one of the third woman's exes
Started a fight with her and she said,
I wanted raisin' bad juju and castin' nasty hexes
So everybody got to see what power over sex is
Rippin' at each other like Tyrannosaurus rexes
And it harmed none too as you will, must be the only law
And if you got a problem with that stickin' in your crawl
Well maybe you're a power monger tryin' hard to squeeze us
And you will not be welcome here until your witch war ceases
Cause everybody must be free to do as he, she pleases
No matter if they worship Satan, Buddha, Bob, or Jesus
Which war? Pitch score
Which war? Switch gore
I can't take it no more, you better stop it with the witch war
Oh yeah, which war? Are you a big predator?
Which war? Now tell me, what's it all for?
Which war? Hey, who's mindin' the store?
Now I can't take it no more, I got no stomach for a witch war
I can't take it no more, I got no stomach for a witch war
Hey, who's mindin' the store?
Hail Bobby Sarlassie, the king of Ethiopia
Now that's the emperor of Ethiopia
Hail Ethiopia!
Emperor Bobby Sarlassie, mentor of all the wagon and behind
All the bobbies and slobbies and left-behinds
And you're all gonna be left behind pretty soon
Oh yes, Dave, I hope you're right about their behinds
Friends, what we just heard
Well, this in the background is
Einstein's Secret Orchestra at XX Day, the Friday afternoon jam
And the song we just heard, Witch War, is by Loki E. Coyote
I'll say that again, Loki E. Coyote
Who's sort of a pagan comedian, I guess you could say
I met him at Starwood
And you can visit their website at wickabilly.com
That's wickabilly.com
W-I-C-C-A-B-I-L-L-Y.com
Or write to Loki E. Coyote's Wickabilly Circus at P.O. Box 2978 Cedar Park, Texas
I'm sorry, I didn't know you were there
Before that, friends, we heard Maggie Pierce and E.J. with that song about heroin one more time
Maggie Pierce and E.J. were also some folks that performed at Starwood, which I met
And here is their contact info
Maggie Pierce and E.J. P.O. Box 41056
That's 41056
Philadelphia
Pennsylvania
Or you can try emailing MPEband
One word, MPEband at AOL.com
Maggie Pierce and E.J. friends
And now back into delving deeper and ever deeper into subgeniusdom
From the recent devivals
The devivals
of new
any means necessary.
We will kill hate, we will silence censorship,
and we will burn fire, we will fuck sex,
death to death, killing and taxes, dear friends.
Kill them all, let Bob sort them out.
And you know, some people get worried
about that violent sounding part of it,
but you know, as Dr. Legume said,
to make an omelet, you gotta break a few eggs.
Well, to make the kind of omelet that Bob Dobbs is making,
it's gonna take a hell of a lot of scrambled brains
on drugs, my friends.
And many of you have probably heard of the New Age theory
about the 100th monkey.
They never mentioned the 100th Manson.
They never mentioned the 100th
Legume.
They never mentioned the 100th Bob.
Because friends, when you release your inner child,
sooner or later, your inner Charlie Manson
is gonna want out too.
And we are composed of many selves,
and it's a good idea not to take
any of your selves too seriously.
But seriously, there is a solution,
and that solution is fuck them if they can't take a joke.
And you think that would be enough, friends,
but the conspiracy has this secret weapon,
that invisible monster that lives up in the sky.
87% of Americans believe in that invisible monster
that'll kick their enemy's asses if they kiss its ass enough.
And yet, their so-called God is so pathetically weak
that apparently it has to be defended by illiterate little old ladies.
And that little old lady's against assholes like me.
What kind of a pussy ass God is that?
Seem like he'd be able to kick my ass himself.
That's why we do say, we still say,
war on God, dear friends.
War on any God that's worried about us,
making war on him.
Oh, yes.
Friends, we're just like any other religion.
It's not that we love Bob all that much,
and said we love the idea of everybody else burning in hell.
They may be the most controversial band in America.
They pack out concert halls from Tokyo to Los Angeles,
and their stage presence is nothing short of sensational.
I've seen
The Bramflex
in concert,
and I've briefly interviewed members of the band on my broadcast,
Talk Back with Bob Larson.
I've taken a lot of criticism for not condemning everything
The Bramflex
does.
Well, I've taken the position that even though I may not completely agree with
The Bramflex,
according to Philippians 1, I must praise God wherever Christ is preached,
even if I don't approve of the methodology.
Praise the Lord, the best of the admonitions.
Sometimes I wish God would give me a Holy Ghost machine that I'd blow your head on.
There's some new words that are being described very blatantly.
Let me give you an example.
In the lyrics of songs, when you hear them sing about engine, motor, or machine,
they're referring to sex.
When you hear them sing about funky, they're referring to sexual odors.
When they sing about groovy, they're talking about the position of intercourse.
When they sing of get off, they're singing about the goal of lovemaking.
And when you hear them talk about, sing about groupies,
they're talking about rock prostitutes.
I am a groupie.
Ladies and gentlemen, please give a warm church welcome
to this evening's show.
This evening's keynote speaker, Dr. P. Ellis.
Thank you.
Yeah, good.
Thank you very much.
Quote.
Balanced we, he sometimes, if DDT,
this all of us, teacher,
a turns and think system,
and look, the space,
and hope Bush, all idea,
as to acts can so.
I'm offering nations competitiveness blessed.
We his, I you.
We real know.
Don't like it when you see one.
You know and I know,
Hollywood is the next four years.
Death for Bush and his helpmates.
We have been the leaders of the Reagans.
I'm not used to going in front of the problem.
I am the future.
You know, and I will be a threat as well.
We are leaders of the American public,
to be called the Soviet Union's demise and collapse.
Experience is a family and family values,
and I will be a better tomorrow.
One learns every day.
Experience is a great teacher.
By experience, you learn.
I have made good judgments in the family.
He is the head of an evil empire, which we don't even suspect.
And while he's telling us that we can conceivably live to be 130,
it will be a world on a slave planet
where we literally have to sift the uranium sand off of our food,
off of our peanut butter and jam sandwiches.
That's right, copper top.
That's the word to describe it.
To a metallic overture.
What does that mean?
Copper top.
What kind of an insult is that?
That means we're human batteries, baby.
We're all, you know, can't you hear it?
Did you hear that drilling?
Yeah.
That's right.
The mechs, they're digging up babies next door
to use them as battery storage, like in that movie.
They dangled the truth right in front of us
and make us pay $6.50 to go see it in a theater.
Well, I think what is happening here...
And they're just laughing at us.
What we know is happening down there so far,
but it's not really...
It's not really a joke or anything, is that...
Do you remember in...
What was that British sci-fi movie
where that thing from that ant planet,
that evil insect planet,
was buried in the subway?
Yeah.
They claim there's some sort of...
Five million years to Earth.
Yeah, five million...
They claim there is something down there
they're trying to find that is very big and metallic
and they don't know what it is.
They think it might just be a water line,
but it's down further than...
It's an old Martian spaceship.
It could conceivably be.
Emanating dreams of our...
Our archetypal...
Well, Dave, what happened...
Archidelia...
Hey, Dave, why did they shut up...
Why did they shut up...
Hans Christian Andersen?
No, Pete Conrad's mouth.
Pete Conrad?
Yeah, what's the deal?
Ask Dr. Quiter-Mass.
Pete Conrad had started a company
for people to buy tickets to go into space.
Mm-hmm.
And he was building a ship to do it.
Now, Pete Conrad is the third man to walk on the moon
and he spent three months in Skylab.
He's a type three man.
Did you ever read...
Did you ever read his, like, book,
Three Man Man?
No, he died in a motorcycle accident.
He's 69 years old.
He's 5.5.
Just quote,
he died like he lived, quote,
in all your national, you know,
1984-ish magazines there.
Yeah, sure, right.
But I'm sorry, nobody...
They silenced him, man.
I'm convinced.
He must have known somebody.
He knew a lot.
Did you ever read his book?
And he was a smartass.
That's the problem.
He knew a lot and he was a real smartass.
See, there you go right there.
They hate a smartass.
Yeah, NASA, they really hated him.
Remember in school they used to tell you that?
Everybody hates a smartass.
That was the message the government was giving us
even when we were drinking them little milk cartons.
That's why we had to start a religion for smartass,
for those who had been smartasticated.
Yeah, he kind of had definitely a subgenius.
The dumbasticated ones, they hate us so,
they hate us smartasses.
I don't blame them.
If I was a dumbass, I'd hate smartasses.
Yeah, love doesn't like hate and hate doesn't like love.
I love that.
If you read Stalin's love letters
and Adolf Hitler's memoirs to Eva,
you will find this strong current of love-hate
is now getting weird.
Damn, there it was right there in front of me.
It was like a little...
Oh, man, it was another insect.
We got incoming.
Incoming.
You know what they do?
They are messengers from another dimension.
You know, insects, when you see them
and they look at you kind of strange.
And here it is.
Which dimension are you calling from?
Oh, I disconnected it.
Oh, poor little bug.
Didn't really mean to do that.
Well, if you're listening on the internet...
Oh, my God.
Oh, hey, let's do this right.
We'll do a proper devival opening, friends.
Now, I don't want anybody...
I don't want anybody...
to feel all nervous or self-conscious
or anything like that,
but if you could just bow your heads
for a solemn, extremely serious,
ponderous, full-of-oneself,
thinks-God's-talking-to-you-only moment of sacred noise!
Praise God! Praise God! Praise God!
Praise God! Praise God!
Oper Excitement!
Hey, we're going to play a song now?
Jesus.
Yeah.
What are we doing?
Plastic Surgery!
No...
It's about Plastic Surgery.
Next one, next one.
Next one's about plastic surgeries.
Not this one, but the next one.
Ready?
One, two, three, four.
Tonight, my students are lost
I don't have a dream to shout
I can feel without a doubt
That sometimes life
Believes that I cease to care
Being isn't always there for
Moon and sun and rather
Red and blue and the thumb
My eyes do see for
Perfectation
Meditation
When the senses confine me
I'm addicted, please
I don't know who I know
And see that there is not her
To be tired
And mute
Trying to escape
And I'm not sure
How you suffer
Living in suicide
With these itchy pads
Of the upset eye
Meditation
The global village jaki complicated.
Man.
Dear friends at XX Day, I believe the previous X Day they were known as Tri-State Killing Spree.
A bunch of crazy women is what they are.
Global Village Idiots.
Uh, yes.
And what else?
We also heard a little bit of the rants of Dr. P. Ellis from the WREK Subgenius Radio Show.
And the information contact on Dr. Ellis' CD of rants.
There's all kinds of things on that.
Here's the address for Bob's Slacktime Funhouse and the Lymph Node Institute.
Got your pencil ready?
That's P.O. Box 670-540.
That's Box 670-541 Marietta, Georgia 30066.
Uh, Box 670-541 Marietta, Georgia 30066.
Or www.lymphnodeinstitute.com.
Uh.
And, uh, where are we?
Where are we?
Oh, oh, wait.
Um, actually, I need to also give credit for the Bran Flakes.
I played a little stretch of, uh, called, uh, Praise the Lord from the Bran Flakes.
The Negative Land-like edit band.
They're great.
Uh, at http://www.ovenguard.com.
That's ovenguard.com.
Uh, yes.
And you are listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack from the church of
the Subgenius.
Subgenius Foundation Headquarters is located at...
Got that pencil ready?
Uh, that's Box 140306.
That's Box 140306, Dallas, Texas.
75214.
Oh, the romance of numbers and, uh, of course, that's also www.subgenius.com.
And friends, subgenius has no zero in it.
Thank you.
Subtitles by Subtitle Workshop
thinkers
Bye-bye...
Subtitles by Subtitle Workshop
Refuse to know how to play the instruments.
Uh, yes.
But, um, I've got to get this show finished up.
And let's switch over.
What is this?
Lost in Space was another band that performed at XX Day.
This was season one beyond tomorrow.
These very lives in your gravity
into the first take of music
from the extremes of comprehension.
Lost in Space.
Producators.
The vitamin for the space rock.
That's me, baby.
You will do as I do.
Cause I'm your intergalactic
fantasy.
You're all those
entities.
Must be all
of the same.
Sexiest man in the galaxy.
Lust in space, everybody.
Welcome to the sex goddesses.
And say it's coming.
Ah-hoo-ga.
The end is near. It's all right.
Ah-hoo.
Ah-hoo-ga.
Are you a flirt?
An exhibition?
A pianist?
Do you like showing your body to strange men?
Have you ever fantasized about
deflowering a male virgin?
Then come to Brushwood
the weekend of July 5th, 1998.
See thousands of nude yeti in their natural habitat.
Pay only a small admissions fee
for the spectacle of a lifetime.
And the end of a civilization.
It's the X Day drill.
But this time,
it's not a drill.
I wish.
Oh, thank you, Friday, ever so much.
But friends, you have actually been listening to
all recordings from bands that were at the
Brushwood campground events.
Subgenius event X Day.
XX Day, I should say.
And the ace event, Starwood.
You...
Well...
Yes, we try to share what we can,
although maybe it's...
You had to have been there kind of thing.
I don't know.