I see no reason for violence.
Sex.
If however you are confronted you may result in
SELF-GENIUS!
Bugs.
Bug sex.
So now we can hug our fleas and ticks too.
WEDD.
American Ticks.
Sex.
Don't kill flies with our nostrils.
Eeeeeeeeeee...
What will you do if we let you go?
And the plastic's all melted and so is the comb.
Who are the brain police?
What will you do when the label comes off?
And the plastic's all melted and the chrome is too soft
You feel like you're done You feel like you're done
You feel like you're done I feel like i'm done
I feel like I'm done I feel like i'm done
I feel like i'm done
Who are the brain police?
What will you do with the people you knew?
Who were the plastic that melted at the chromium tube?
Who are the brain police?
Who were the real prisoners?
When they stick it to you
There's something you can do
They're at your back door
Don't take it anymore
When there's an attack
We got your back
When things get odd
We're the urgency squad
There's an attack
Urgency squad
Got your back
We are the urgency squad
We know there's no free lunch
Gonna get a knockout punch
Thought you're better off dead
You get a boot to the head
When there's an attack
We got your back
When things get odd
We're the urgency squad
There's an attack
Urgency squad
Got your back
When things get odd
Urgency squad
We are the urgency squad
They're always looking out
We only run what we seek
We'll grow the strength
We'll grow our strength
They will see that we can
We're nowhere near
You'll be mamofist
We'll blow you down
It's too early
How are you gonna live
in a world of hate?
Let your pegs green
Come up and up
Let your pegs loose
Let your pegs out
Gasping
Let your pegs loose
Let your pegs open
Say I can make him
When there's an attack, we got your back
When things get odd, we're the urgency squad
There's an attack!
Urgency squad
Got your back!
Things get odd
Urgency squad
We are the urgency squad
The Vespa gives you confidence because it was born from the most modern design, from the most advanced technology.
And then, go with me.
Thank you.
Ooh.
Ah.
Oh.
I always wondered why it was just me when I grew up.
I always wondered whether or not I could make it.
I was excited because it was such a drag to reject it.
So I tore the cover off a bunch of matches.
And I got this letter back that said,
I'm not going to be a fan of the band.
I than knew the band had results like that.
I lined up with this guy on my Facebook account.
I called him.
My father at that time called me fishy or something.
I said,◝
Uh oh,ando.
◝
Oh, souvent mis труба я вижу.
Yeah, и прarded.
You will, probably.
Sis.
I'm a little dumb
Yeah, I'm a little paranoid
But to me, it's what I tell you
Yeah, we're just a bit of a squirmer
You wanna fight?
Then you're full of yourself
I'm a man, I'm a man, I'm a man, I'm a man
I'm a man, I'm a man, I'm a man
An unusual piece by the Psychoskeletons, a piece called Shower Scene.
Before that, we heard a little, well, second part of the classic tune, Help, I'm a Rock, from the Mothers of Invention ancient album from the late 1960s.
The all guitar, all big guitar, religious sounding, graceful thing was called Grace by our brother, Reverend Jimmy Ryan, who just does that kind of big guitar greatness.
Before that, the almost four minute long participation in the Bunga Bunga was by the Rudy Show.
The Shorts Project, it would be hard for our Slack listeners to mistake Rudy Shorts Project for anything else.
The one, what one might call a Devo retro or Devo-esque song, Urgency Squad, was from the album Urgency Squad by the band Exposed Forehead.
The song was spelled with a giant X and a giant four and a huge posed and a huge forehead.
Exposed foreheads, and you'll be seeing them at the Beachland Ballroom, the devotional, the last weekend in July, I believe, this time.
Amazing.
I sure will be.
Before that, who are the Bridesmaids?
The Bride Police, another real classic from Frank Zappa's first album, maybe, or second album, Freak Out.
It was the third LP record I ever bought, honestly, after, I think the first LP record I ever bought, besides movie soundtracks, first rock and roll album, was The Monkees, Last Train to Clarksville.
great album. Then the Beatles' Magical Mystery Tour, then Frank Zappa's Freak Out, and then
Jimi Hendrix' Are You Experienced? So that's my rock and roll history of album buying in the
very late 1960s. Oh man, that got me. So yeah, yeah, yeah. The background music is Cyber Chump,
which is related to Exposed Foreheads. Cyber Chump goes just instrumental music.
It's a great, great rug for the hour of slack.
The best rug on the planet. Princess Wee is here, and I am here. Although, you know,
we went to a memorial for a beloved family member, not part of my family, actually not even somebody
I even knew, but a big part of Princess Wee's family. It was like a memorial service,
and it was rather sobering, but there was wine. And we don't usually do shows when we're in a state
of emotional uproar or grief, but hey, why not? And guess what? I've got Lonesome Cowboy
Dave's book in front of me. It's almost ready to put on sale. In fact, all we really are waiting
for is Lonesome Cowboy Dave to finish proofreading. I've proofread the whole thing.
Oh, it's so good. Princess Wee is working on it. I'm not finished proofreading.
A Dave's book, Neighbor World, a novel, I guess one could call it a science fiction novel,
but really, if I was a librarian, I'd put it in the literature section because, you know,
sci-fi, that's just pulp. That's just silly kid stuff, you know, crazy stuff, kid stuff,
science fiction. On the other hand, Kurt Vonnegut fits into the literature section somehow, right?
Right. And Neal Stephenson fits into that literature
section.
although also into the science fiction section.
Terry Pratchett goes in the fantasy section.
I would put him in the uppity literature section
alongside Mark Twain and Jonathan Swift.
But I'm not running the libraries,
and I understand how the publishing business works.
Anyway, we have become publishers.
Thanks to the modern technique of Insta-publishing,
print-on-demand,
I don't have to keep a closet full of book of the whatever
in my closet to be a self-publisher.
I can just let them whip one out whenever you order a book.
Not that I'm urging you to do so,
but,
for the first time,
we're in the position of being able to publish books.
And the first thing we started with was not our own, but our friends.
And Lonesome Cowboy Dave's novel Neighbor World is astounding.
I was about to read from it,
except I'm afraid that poor old cowboy just probably just called in.
I just probably called in.
I was afraid of that.
I was trying to read Schopenhauer's Essence and Reason.
I was trying.
I thought it sounded real smart,
but since I had my crotch fumigated and my eyebrows all plucked,
I'm ready to go.
Alright.
Well, all those words you said sounded pretty smart Dave.
Well, I could also quote Emanuel Kent,
I could say,
maybe perhaps he could,
but he didn't want to.
I was about to quote Lonesome Cowboy Dave
from Chapter 6,
point A of Neighbor World,
world but I'm not gonna cuz you called him cuz I could oh I can't I could do
that quote in any time but I can't talk to you just any old time this is a
special time yes firstly for the people who out there somewhere in space have
the Humphrey in the route of Vegas and all the different problems you know
sociopathic problems that they do that's right they need modern immediate updates
modern science they need you Dave no they need you so get on it it's up to
you it's all on your shoulders fix them fix them now are you sure it's not you
because the articles to be fixed yeah that's what they told me what happened
tell you his voice they were telling me
something is wrong with the computer I don't know what happened I don't know what happened
so I decided to tell you go ahead and fix everybody's problems Dave it's a
religious culture it's famous it's like Church of the subgenius we can do
anything Bob said so so go ahead and fix everybody's problems okay I'll just wait
hmm but I'm not like Bob I'm hardly a shooter foot in his whole steps I can
hardly you know place my articles of deception well me a great genius like
Bob Dobbs well me neither I but but we thought that you was you were
like a smart guy you had a book a novel that's about to be out if you'll ever
finish proofreading that he will I'm pretty close to done from the back you
were going from the front right I was done from the front yeah we're probably
we're probably halfway okay well friends I could do I could do
it perhaps you know right away I could have done it tonight if I
I didn't have to be on a real stupid hour of slack radio show.
Oh, no.
God, do I know what you mean.
I could have been doing so many other things tonight.
But, you know, the reason I was able to finish proofreading your novel Neighbor World,
coming from Subgenius Press, was I had to sit on a plane for five hours.
Right.
That will do it.
That's like being in a dentist's office.
Where's the reading material?
I can't take it here.
I'm going to go crazy.
I'm going crazy, man.
Oh, God, I jumped out of a window.
No, I can't jump out of a window.
We're at 1,200 feet in the air.
No.
This show would have been a lot better if you had not called in
and I had just read all of your words from your novel over the air.
No, you just said the opposite.
But you know what?
It's best that you called in because now,
they're just going to...
They're going to have to read your novel
to get those hot, hot words zoomed in their loom.
Well, what was salient about the virtual world of Point A
that you were going to espouse on?
It's back like you see.
You've heard of it.
Yeah.
Well, let's see.
It was when No-Go and Standard are driving into...
They're driving towards Industria's Tragic Coast near Car Town.
And they're going to...
They're going to meet Bob Sideways.
And El Chimpy, their favorite band, has faded from the radio.
And the mag is silent.
And, uh...
Oh, wait.
There's a...
There's a question here.
You actually made that sound interesting.
Yeah.
Oh, God.
You know, I can't get the same alacrity out of there.
I can't...
You know, I was like...
Well, Dave, you're too close to it.
You wrote the damn thing.
I know exactly how it is.
Uh, I wrote the most brilliant things in the world,
and I can't get any joy from them.
They just seem stupid to me.
But all these people seem to love it.
And, Dave, I love reading your stuff.
I mean, even though I know you,
even though I know what a complete Dave kind of person,
it's just such a complete cowboy.
What a lonesome, lonesome cowboy you are.
Yet, when I read your writings,
it's like as if I was reading the writings of an elevated genius,
some kind of literary achiever.
Not you.
Or me.
You know, it's like...
It truly transcends our real world.
I understand that in one way.
I read some of your stuff to a person once,
and I very rectally point out...
I know this guy.
Well, it's amazing how...
You know, the unfortunate part of all that was
that some of these people were so demented,
they actually not only found it entertaining,
what you had written,
but they believed it.
They believed X-Day was truly coming,
which it's coming in its pants, perhaps,
but that's the only place we can...
Hey, what else matters?
Who cares about any other place?
But here's the thing.
Uh,
they're right.
It is elevating and inspiring,
and they should pay attention to it.
Uh, the...
Anything published by Subgenius...
Foundation or dot-com or whatever,
I'm not sure...
I have noticed that.
I can't remember the company name exactly that I run, but...
I've actually felt jealousy back in the days
when my computer was up and running.
I would...
I felt rather jealous many times.
Like, who's this?
That's a pretty cool way of saying that.
Well, yeah, because our computer...
We kept our computers running all the time.
Huh.
Yeah.
Well, we sometimes had to get new computers.
And it's...
What can I say?
We've been lucky.
We were able to afford new computers
just in the nick of time.
Not everybody can.
I had somebody going,
Hey, Reverend Stang,
it seems like this X-Day...
Festival you hold every July.
It seems like you're always begging for extra help
to pay for a plane ticket or this or that.
But shouldn't you...
Well, this may seem like a dumb question,
but shouldn't you raise the admission price?
I can't give that admission price on community radio,
but it's not very high.
And I had to honestly answer the guy,
Yeah, for half of these people,
that's actually a lot of money.
Yeah.
That's a deal killer.
You know, 40 bucks, 30 bucks,
something like that,
somewhere within that ballpark.
That's a deal...
That's hard.
I haven't gone out to concerts or movies myself
for a long time.
You went into your alter ego, though.
Well, I...
And you didn't bring Leo up with her.
No, no.
He, him...
My alter...
My alter ego learned how...
How to get things from the internet without...
Which is a form of doppelganger.
Not a doppelganger.
It's more like when you have a little...
A little tiny four-inch tall version of yourself,
like a mini-me type of character that...
I know as well as anybody, it's stealing.
Sure, it's stealing from the mom-and-pop
international conglomerate next door.
Sony Pictures or Disney or whatever.
Well, same thing.
But...
Really?
You know...
And yet I do it anyway.
It's because I...
What other choice do I have?
My other choice is to...
Because you're an underground fellow
and you fight for the right to be free.
No, that's just stealing.
No, no, no.
That's...
Come on, get real.
You have...
You have a license to steal?
I'm not a rebel.
I'm just an idiot.
To quote the great Reverend Fox,
Argus Fox,
I'm not a rebel.
I'm just an idiot.
And it's true.
Think about it, Dave.
Isn't that the realest thing you ever heard?
I'm not really a rebel.
I'm just an idiot.
It rings true.
And yet...
It's sad.
That doesn't mean we can't still be rebels.
We can still be rebels.
We're idiots.
Just so long as we're not Confederates.
Right.
We will be rebels.
Oh, we're not Confederates for sure.
Well...
Not...
No somos Confederatos.
Not us.
But by definition...
Especially not I.
Confederates means us.
You know, doesn't it?
In the town where I live,
there are a group of people,
there's two pickup trucks
who put Confederate flags
in their cars and fly them
and drive around like
Confederate flag wavers.
Well...
Boy, and I'm gonna get in trouble
because just the other day,
I got...
I gave one of them the finger
as I drove by.
Now, if that guy would have slammed
on the barracks and chased me,
I probably would have died.
In the old days,
I probably would have grabbed
a heavy object
and tried to fight my way
to the death and lost.
This way, I just will die
because...
Because they're...
They have guns
and they're scary.
And it's your fault, too.
I don't know why, but...
I thought I was.
I know what you're talking about.
I don't know why, but...
I've actually been chased around
by rebels, quote, unquote.
The same kind of people
that would drive around
waving the Confederate flag
to prove to the world
that they're really, really mad.
They're angry at this world
where white people
don't get special consideration.
Right?
They don't get special attention anymore.
Oh, deary me.
We're so picked on,
especially white males.
Oh.
Yeah.
It's like we're not cool anymore.
The transgender people get attention.
Even the women
get to be superheroes now.
Oh, deary me.
We manly white men
are so picked on.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
I feel so sad.
I'm so...
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Well,
that's the way.
It seems to me
as a southern white man
in America today
who finished his high school education
and got a little tiny bit of college
and continued my education
vastly far beyond anything
any college could have taught me.
And that's why I know
I am right in all of this.
I agree with you.
The rest of these people
are a bunch of jerks
and they don't know
Jack Hooey.
And if I was them
or were them,
I would read that novel
Neighbor World
by Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
And I can say that
because it's not on sale yet.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it's what you want to do.
You want to straighten out
all your mental equities
and your other cis components
of your existing existence.
The 21st century
just goes straight ahead
and pick up a copy of...
It says right here
on the cover.
And you're going to get
a copy of...
Here's a good little section
that I outlined.
Okay.
Sex.
That's all you think about
is sex.
Okay, here it goes.
This is a quote.
No, this is better than sex.
From Neighbor World,
I chanted along,
the bioflux regulators,
the instruments of genocide,
the whispers in the ear
and squares in the skull
were being rejected.
Washed away.
The weirds were reshaping
my brain.
Laia was full of juicy,
eye-peeling eratoslam.
The school uniform
made her look earthy
but spiritual.
Boners and buying
go hand in hand
and I was buying.
Then the whole place
filled with light
as a giant old-era disco ball
lowered from the ceiling.
The ball began shooting up
blue citrine
and red-colored streams.
And then it gets really weird
after that, my friends.
You'll just have to read
Neighbor World
by Dave, quote,
DeLuca, unquote.
This must mean...
If they want to know, that is.
They'll have to read it
if they want to know.
If you really want to know, man,
there's some...
As long as you're not
in a Brazilian jiu-jitsu,
we're playing with their own
Barthesia organs.
Because that's way, way too...
Actually, Dave,
I think you just described
about one-third of our audience.
I hope so.
Yeah, but let's keep off
the negative advertising.
Friends, you'll love
this book that you can't buy yet,
Neighbor World.
This is, you know,
citizen radio,
so we can't do commercial stuff.
But there will come a time
when it will be
obvious how to buy
your copy of this.
And it actually is an amazing...
I wouldn't call it
science fiction exactly
because it's more like literature.
I wouldn't put it
in the sci-fi section
were I the librarian
of the world.
I'd put it in the literature section.
I'm sorry.
That's just the way it is.
There's no monsters.
There's no explosives.
There's no emotions.
Soft and moist
like a chocolate chip cookie.
It takes place in the future.
But it's the chocolate chip cookie future
you're going to get, friends.
You might as well dig in.
Get used to it.
It ain't going to change.
It's going to be.
Imagine the world of vast selfie
and how that's going to be so stupid
in like 20, 30 years
of selfie.
The mania of people
looking down at their hands
or looking, well,
you don't even have to do that anymore.
Looking down at their feet
or their encrusted, dirty, rotten toenails
like in my case.
I just need to...
You know, Dave,
in the movie
Mad Max Road Warrior,
the newer
Road Warrior Mad Max movie,
there's a scene
where these future apocalypse people
are sitting in the desert
looking at the sky.
There's no technology
to speak of left.
And they see a satellite going.
There's still a few satellites up there.
And one of them goes,
yeah, my mom told me
those used to have all the shows.
Back in the old world,
everyone had their own show.
Hmm.
And, you know,
it's...
That's the way it is.
We happen to be on broadcast radio,
which is a really old way
of doing your own show.
But we're also on a podcast.
And anybody can do a podcast.
And we're not into
random bestiality
slash sexuality
with, you know, with foreigners.
What?
We're Americans.
I don't know what that is.
Well, no.
Let's not draw any...
You know, we don't need to make any...
close any doors here.
We still have possibilities.
We'll wrap them shut.
But we have had to really consider
that it's broadcast radio, right?
That's different from podcast.
It's broadcast because
anybody could turn on their radio
in their car and suddenly hear it.
Oh, wait.
Anyone with a computer in their car
could do the same thing.
Mm-hmm.
They'd have choices
of about a thousand
and ten more stations.
But, of course,
they would land on this one.
Or the moon.
And so, what's the difference?
So, praise Bob!
Praise Bob!
That's right.
More people can hear
the hour of slack.
Oh, Lord, praise him.
Praise, praise...
But think about it, Dave.
Well, maybe you weren't there.
But when...
When...
When there were only
ten radio stations
and ten television stations,
they were...
They worked harder.
They were...
They tried really hard
to be real
and tell the truth.
They really actually did.
There were only ten of them.
No, Twilight Zone, Outer Limits.
Think of those early programs.
Exactly.
They actually had writing staffs
where they all met
and had coffee
and looked out the window.
And screamed,
I got it.
Ran back and started typing
curiously and stuff.
Just like us.
That's what we did.
But times have changed.
Now, all you have to do
to have a show
is turn your phone around
pointing at you
and push the big red button
and you're on the air.
Yeah.
Nobody cares whether you cuss.
Nobody cares whether you're lying.
And all that matters is...
Do you want to hear this or not?
Do you want to tune in or not?
And a lot of people
most want to hear
what they most wanted to hear.
And that's...
I'm sorry.
...explains the difference
between when we were struggling
and when they're struggling now.
You can hear
what you most wanted to hear
instantly
and...
in duplication.
Many different versions.
No matter how stupid and wrong
what you want to hear may be,
you can hear it
echoed in your chamber.
Think of the jelly dogs,
the blow mows,
and all the retardations
that make things go slower.
We could be too.
We could be,
but better off
we would be on Uranus
or some distant planet
where we could...
we could wield...
I mean,
what's the word?
Not wield, weld.
Wend.
Where we could wend
our visions of the stars
throughout the rest of the universe.
We could wend our visions.
Wend.
No, I don't think that's right.
Weave.
That's it.
Wend and weave.
Why not both?
We'll do both.
We'll wend them and weave them.
Our visions.
Our fantasies.
Our...
Our prophecies of the future.
Our concoctions,
which are not for sale.
Thanks to college radio
and podcast...
No, wait.
That's pathetic.
I'm going to blow them
and I'll be on the mountain.
All I need...
If you're not on Fox News,
then it's not real.
That's all they know and see.
Well, reality is fake.
Phone news.
Fake news.
Reality is fake.
If you ask me,
who is?
Nobody.
None of soul
asked me a question ever.
But what about...
No, nobody polled you, right?
You didn't...
You weren't polled.
I was left on the tag.
They called me up and said,
would you mind taking
a 12-minute long survey
on your impression...
Then they ran down the list
of my opinions
and impressions and stuff
and I said,
well, it takes 12 minutes
and it's starting now.
And they said,
well, if you want to start it now,
it's another 12 minutes
of signing you up.
Right.
So I refused.
I once again
flipped in the mighty bird
and made my way out the window.
Oh, they polled me.
They took the giant pole
and I had to sit
upon the huge pole
of the polling.
It was...
I was paid,
I think,
$2.50 an hour.
To ride the stag?
I was being polled, yeah.
I was actually paid to be polled.
I spent the first half of my life
being polled for money.
Well, can I ask you your...
Oh, I'm sorry.
And then I started working for myself
and I didn't get nearly as much polling
or money, but it was better.
What would you do...
Because there was no polling.
Right, yeah.
So what...
If you were to poll the nation,
what do you think the actual tri-axis
and the actual...
And the quagglaferon
of the hexagonal parts, too,
because they're interconnected
just like, you know,
carbon monog...
I think...
I think it's like...
Anyway, Miss Griffith's portrayal
of an insane woman
with a decapitated head of Diffurer,
of Oingo...
of Bongo Longo,
Mr. Mango Bikini...
You know what I'm saying.
How many people do you think
actually want to end her career
or does it only?
In 1980, we did all that stuff
and nobody cared
and who cares now?
But somehow they've made
a big deal of it
because, hey, it's okay
if a redneck says
Lynch Obama,
that Negro president,
but it's terrible
if a comedian holds up
a cutout of a head
of a chopped off,
decapitated,
New York real estate builder.
You know, we've been doing
head launchings
in the Church of the Subgenius
since 1980.
We launched the bleeding head
of Arnold Palmer.
We, well, other schismatic groups
attempted to launch
the bleeding head of Lee Trevino,
Jack Nicklaus,
various different old school...
And flip the scrotum
of Lee Harvey Oswald.
Remember those days?
Of Lee Harvey Oswald.
Oh, please.
Well, first scrotum,
first scrotum,
flipper wasn't too...
Man, we've been flipping scrotums
for so long
and launching heads
and making Photoshop
bloody head cutouts.
This, all of this
seems so fantastically contrived
by a...
A contestant.
A committee of idiots
who, of 12-year-olds
who went,
well, now look,
we can pick on them for this.
They said Negro
in the wrong way.
We can pick on them
and we can prove
they're the racists,
not us.
Even though we've been
gerrymandering everything
to make sure black people
don't get any kind
of equal representation
or any other minorities,
including the Mexicans.
Why, we can always just say
that it's unfair
because they made
a funny comment.
They made a funny comment
about a comedy show
that had a Republican's head
on a stick.
How horrible and awful.
So that means we can do
anything we want to forever
because that one liberal
did something stupid
and tasteless that one time.
I got news for you, friends.
Yeah, us libtards
may occasionally
do something tasteless.
Oh, deary me,
you better cry.
And weep and melt
like a little snowflake
about that
because that never,
ever happened to you
before and that did it.
God.
Well, well, well said.
Oh.
Perfectly well put.
It encapsulates
the entire truth
of the reality.
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, don't.
Oh, man, I know
exactly how you feel.
The short memories
of our,
oh, my people are destroyed
for lack of knowledge,
said Hosea
two and a half thousand
years ago.
And he's still right,
but nobody remembers it
because their minds
are destroyed
for lack of knowledge.
Hence my dedication,
my personal dedication
to what we might call
soulless, hard,
hard, hard, cold science.
Yes.
The coldest and the hardest.
Now, Dave,
I know that you're
hard science.
You're not.
Hard, cold,
soulless science.
You're not down
in that vault with me
with those frozen seeds.
I know.
No, but I know
where the,
I know where the
digestible animals are
and where the convenience
stores is.
And also the,
you know,
placard conveniences
that are applied
when you have to
relieve or misinterpret
your bowel movements.
Because Canadians
talk differently
than we do.
And that's why
they need to have
their eyes
touted out.
Canadians talk differently.
Canadians?
Mm-hmm.
I love Canadians.
I'm sorry I said that.
I didn't mean to hate
Canadians for a brief moment.
Dave, is it,
is it because
we're, you know,
in northern Ohio
we're neighbors
of this other country
called Canada?
So we have to...
Yes, why do you think
we who live on the lake
call mayflies
Canadian soldiers?
You thought
we were making that up
when Chaz and I
told you that
many, many years ago.
You thought
it's mayflies
and he's just making that up.
Right, yeah.
Until Jeff Rosenbaum
That's right.
said,
no, it's Canadian soldiers.
That's the way people
on the lake
view Canada.
That's racist!
No, it's not
because they're all
mollycoddle whites
and occasional Sikhs
here and there.
Hey,
I come from Texas
where we have
shiggers.
Now, you think
that's not an awkward
insect disease
to be afflicted with.
They are painful.
Yeah.
They're horrible.
Luckily,
they only last
a couple of months
and everything
will be fine
when we go back.
But here's the thing, Dave.
You can't slander
Canadians just because
of their insects
any more than
I can slander
my own insects.
My own insects.
What else is there
to live for?
Blood thirstiness.
It's just nature.
Oh, okay.
Well, the movie Blood...
Okay.
That's the way
the people in Canada are.
You have to be tolerant
of the Canadian people.
They are bloodthirsty.
Yeah, I've noticed
that if you go to,
like, you were to go
live in a suburb of Ottawa,
then they, you know,
and someone in my mother's
place, you know,
then they, you know,
they're not that
different from us.
Sure.
Sure, they have
some customs.
They may
behead people
when no other
culture does.
Oh, no, wait.
I'm talking about
Muslims.
It's legal throughout
the entire country
by the year 2018,
by September of 2018,
which is the promise
of Trudeau,
whose ears are
a delight to the senses
and a childish rumor
to the romantic friends
of Hitler.
Okay.
I made myself cry.
No, Dave, no.
I had trouble
following that.
I hate Hitler.
In the first place,
Hitler is a...
He resembles a guy
in Birds of a Nation
at the very last scene,
you know,
all dressed up in white
with a monocle
and a beard's wax.
I'm sorry.
Gary Trudeau
was in there somewhere.
I left Gary Trudeau
and all of a sudden
I saw that picture
of Hitler
as a Teutonic knight
and then I saw
the Birth of a Nation guy
at the very end of it,
the hero,
who looks like
an insane person
and that's what
they wanted us all
to be like
a hundred years ago.
They wanted us
to all be mad
and they pulled it off again.
This country
will never change.
They're trying to take
Howard Zinn's books
off the shelves
and I don't know
why they want to
pull it off the shelves
anyway.
That's, uh,
that, uh, yeah.
Every now and then
I think to myself,
wow,
they really are
censoring books
and burning books
and putting people
in jail for 20 years
for holding a protest sign.
And punishing comedians.
Well, they actually did that
in Cleveland
about 20 years ago.
A woman who was
an avowed communist
got beat up
by a patriotic lady.
In fact,
the patriotic lady
whooped her up
pretty good
upside the head
and said,
don't you burn my flag
and all this stuff.
And then they charged her
and put her away forever
in wherever it is,
Lansing,
or, I mean,
Lansfield.
Which her,
which her was put away?
The,
the protester her,
not the angry
patriotic woman
phony,
phony patriotism.
because it's illegal
to have, uh,
opinions in America.
Oh, wait,
no, I thought it was legal
to be a communist.
Even if being a communist
is stupid,
I thought it was legal
to be stupid in America.
That was the opinion
I got growing up.
Me too.
In the deep south
in 1950s.
Uh,
well, oh, wait.
Oh, now I remember.
It was okay
to be a communist
if you were white.
Yes.
And, and, and,
and you were a janitor
at a small school
in your old killer.
I,
honestly, Dave,
I swear to God,
I thought things
had started to change.
I was such a sap.
I thought
that racism
was diminishing
in America.
Me too, I did too.
God, what an idiot I was.
Uh,
the last six months,
well, actually,
you know,
to tell the truth,
the,
the administration
of Barack Obama,
I,
man,
wised me up.
I guess I was
overestimating
the intelligence
of my
fellow
redneck
Caucasians.
But I,
yeah,
hmm.
Bummer.
Well,
that's all I can say.
Bob was right.
J.R. Bob Dobbs
was right the whole time.
He was right.
It's gonna be a bummer.
He said it was gonna be a bummer
and he was right.
He predicted
the entire
Trump administration
and this entire
slide back
to the
damn
1950s.
The idiotic
uh,
Neanderthal
approaches
to race,
science,
religion,
and everything else.
Makes me sick.
And,
that said,
this has been
the Hour of Slack
from the Church
of the Subgenius.
Uh,
number,
Hour of Slack
number
1,625.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Yeah,
yeah,
And,
uh,
we have to
sign off now
and let the
number,
next poor
son of a bitch
get on the air
and do what he can
to fight against
You're allowed to say
that now,
even if you're,
um,
I'm talking about
a dog,
okay?
I'm a dog owner.
And,
you know,
as Ken Casey said,
uh,
put your good
How come you're
mentioning Ken Casey?
I was just thinking
about him before I called in.
That's weird,
don't you think?
It's telekinetic.
No.
Put your good
where it'll do the most.
That's what Ken Casey said.
Now,
I'm not sure,
what I have next.
Oh.
Oh,
it's an ad for Ed's Day.
Of course,
I forgot.
We're about to have
the biggest subgenius
festival in the whole universe
in less than a month.
And right after that,
there's gonna be Starwood.
It's not like,
and then Starwood.
If there's anything
left in the world.
All at the same place
in southern,
uh,
Ohio.
Not that we can legally
give you all the information
about it,
but here goes anyway.
Praise Bob.
This is it.
Your last big chance
to win
back your soul.
X Day
is coming.
Kiss all your calendars
goodbye
and prepare yourself
to greet
the men from Planet X
in power
and glory
at the coolest campground
in the United States.
With sideshow marvels,
spontaneous doctor band combustion,
trained prairie squid,
frop enhancement workshops,
acu-beating, psychic surgery,
human fights, live freaks of nature,
and acid casualties,
face-fucking, bat sperm,
antidote pudding, cook-offs,
private adult sex-hurt seminars,
self-mutilating preachers,
and oddly normal-seeming people,
sex goddesses, elder gods,
and exes.
X Day is coming.
Are you ready for the finals?
Which will it be?
Spaz Outlaw Holiday Forever
or The Last Roundup?
Can you handle Judgment Day?
Will you simper while the world ends?
Or will you get slack?
Brought to you by JR Bob Dobbs
and the Church of the Subgenius.
See www.subgenius.com
for more information.
Experience the anxiousness,
the anxiously awaited moment,
the nail-biting suspense
of July 5th, 7 a.m.
Only $30!
None may stop us,
and none may escape
once the gate closes.
Praise Bob!