30 seconds until the end of the world. Prepare to be boarded to a new one.
Uh, 20, 20, I hate this backwards stuff.
15, 14, 13, 12, 11, 10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Yes!
Ah, brothers!
Well, it could be, you know, we could be awful over there.
Just keep conscious, right?
Mmm.
Ah!
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la.
Look out!
God is right behind you.
The soft genius.
Power of what?
Or any other, uh, uh, cute, uh, cute.
Rupture scene.
Take two!
Goodbye.
No lost ending.
Earth.
I don't want to be ruptured.
Yes, dear friends.
Well.
I don't want to be ruptured with a feeling of deja vu.
I have my ticket!
I give you dollar!
No!
Oh!
Where are you?
I should pay!
Not again!
Oh, no!
The bill is tight!
Waiter's order!
Here are just two once-a-day tickets!
We are breaking!
We could be off by...
I knew it was going to be...
Triplex day!
ultsñosamosnosnos
No!
You have it on.
Triplex day!
uh meet you fell into the 10th dimension how'd you like that did you did you follow any of that
probably not huh that's okay we didn't understand it either we were dubbing cds down from uh double
x day down in the studio and i don't even know how long it's you've been listening to
the symphonies of the planets that was part of the lesson the meditation period after the science
yes to let the the art of the science of god that's right the math of god in his great paint
brush and chisel everything's geometry god is a is just geometry oh yeah but who yeah but who
what taught god how to do that
geometry who taught god man see it's an endless recursive that i told you about nothing escher
bach it's an endless recursive formula nothing gives birth to itself from its mother something
that makes sense it does it well it doesn't exactly make sense but it sounds good and
they've been saying it for billions of years billions and billions of years
bullions i would like
to have billions of bullions of gold a sea of bullion i've sort of i've studied a sea of beef
bullion i've studied uh spiritualism of all kinds mysticism science history and uh i've decided that
the most important subject is money and i don't mean that in any crass way i mean it just as nobly
as i would mean any of the others it's just like money i've i've been everywhere
i've done everything and i want to get paid for it there's nothing left to do except get the check
well that's the final punch line of the church of the subgenius now isn't it it'd be whether the world ends or not
when bob laughs his way to the bank you know it it will be the greatest joke ever told if earth can make it to the punch line and by gobs we got another chance
we got another chance to make it the first time the world has heard from us
uh since this past weekend we fooled you that first time in 98 and we fooled you again you
thought you thought you're going to get off easy of course this could just be a tape recording
well it is a tape recording now yeah but that's a moot point it's after july 5th 1999 the
exodus did not come and rupture the subgeniuses nor destroy the planet as our religion foretold
but
you were you were thinking you were going to get off easy but no it's you're going to be a slave to
the conspiracy for yet another year i guess they decided to rub it in but as they as the subgenius
faithful gathered on the hillside by the pavilion that morning that fateful morning at 7 8 well 703
and nothing had happened they started spontaneously chanting third
times a charm third times a charm and friends we know that even though we may have been double
crossed on dose x we can't wait to get royally screwed on triple x day sex day friends is coming
up next year so we've built this year chas built so many ships he had he didn't know what to do with
him but launched it and he's going to be a great man and he's going to be a great man and he's going
to be a great man and he's going to be a great man and he's going to punch them all
every damn one of them we stuck them fuses right up there and sniffed rocket butt all afternoon
and we're and i got off on my pleasure ship my escape vessel and friends i'm going to keep
building on on it i got it started i'm going to keep adding better speakers plusher velvet
cushions by next year yeah but next year we'll just be able to stick the little rockets in there
and the little sockets, the rockets in the sockets.
Just say, computer, do your stuff.
Yeah.
And, you know, grab your sweetie
or whatever kind of alien monster you're into,
species, by the tail,
and lean back and take off, baby.
Just like we did.
Sure, the exes didn't come again,
but, you know,
I'm not going to say the obvious that I could right then,
but, friends, I'll tell you,
we sure have been having a great time on this planet anyway.
I've just seen, stick around, it's been so slackful.
Yeah, especially, yeah, that was last weekend.
It was nothing like the year before.
Oh, there was so much excitement the first year,
you know, the world was definitely going to end,
and this time it was like, well,
now we know if the world's going to end,
what's the hurry?
And if the world's not going to end,
Either way, lay back, man.
Do what Bob said.
It's the path of least resistance.
Cruise, surf, you know, let the wind blow.
Bend like a reed in the wind, Daddy-O.
Inflate, rise, take a deep breath and float.
Church air, one soul per breath.
Yes, dear friends.
Well, at least, you know, we didn't get the escape vessels,
but at least we got a bunch of cans in here.
Yes, we got free candy.
I got my back.
I got all the slack money tonight.
Oh.
It's back.
I noticed inside there were some pills inside the head.
Pills.
Look at the pills.
There were pills inside Bob's head.
Oh, my.
The same thing that's inside Bob's head
would be inside these pills.
Let's see those pills.
Absolutely nothing at all.
The standard Dobbs pills,
they're the same ones that people have sworn,
by all these years.
When they're...
Church air.
Um...
Amazing.
Isn't it?
Pills.
They, uh, no longer...
I've developed a tolerance to these myself.
Anybody want my pills?
These are pills?
They're suppository.
Yeah.
What's got...
Oh, the theft of Bob.
...dimensional substance with you,
smoking this pipe.
Do you think Little Theodore...
No!
Good Lord.
We are not a bunch of...
...but we got Little Theodore.
There you go.
We got Lust in space!
We got Lust in space.
He isn't in space! He isn't in space!
We've already lost in space before then.
Exactly.
Where are they?
They're already gone, Tammy.
Those aliens are sneaky.
Lust in space has their own stuff.
Exactly.
They already got them.
They built their own ship.
They built their own!
They built their own escape vessel.
Sure.
Maybe we didn't get our escape vessels,
but we got a hell of a fireworks show
that was dangerous,
and somebody could have been...
got hurt any second.
What excitement!
Dr. P, lose your shit!
Hey, sure, you may not have gotten your escape,
but you got to meet that one person that you know.
It's just you just don't know what you'd do
if you hadn't met that person.
Especially a year from now when you're married to him.
And...
And sure, maybe we didn't get our escape vessels yet.
There's still, you know, I mean...
Phil Jerome!
Third time's a charm!
I've built my own already!
Where were you?
Who's Phil Jerome?
But...
But, darling, since when do we need
some darned escape?
I mean, we're not going to be alien monsters and...
and big...
the demigod...
a holy man with pipes to tell us what to do.
By golly, we're subgeniuses.
We're self-amusing personalities.
And we need to ignore...
S.A.B.s.
We know...
We can...
By...
By gosh and by golly,
I think we can carry on and...
and show Bob and the exes that we are worthy.
And that goddamn the Jehovah's Witnesses
can't out-cook us.
That's right!
And we have total faith in J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And if he happens to fuck up,
well, we knew that he was the one holy man
that has the power to fail,
and fail again and again.
And if he doesn't,
I think I'm sure we may be $60 broker
per day while we were here.
But think how much richer Bob is.
Sure, the subgenius foundation itself may be,
you know...
I've seen the books.
What do you think?
I'm happy to have been double crossed on Dos Zecs
and I'll be even happier to get fucked on triple-X day.
By God, we may not have gotten our escape vessels,
but we got a new slogan.
ramen Indians
You may die.
That's the important thing.
At home.
Yeah.
You may die.
And remember.
Or will you live the rest of this day
as if this was the last day of your life
or as if you had all the time in the world, either one?
Yeah!
I certainly will and I'm gonna start
by going to bed, I guess.
What?
God damn it.
I spent my life driving for 10 fucking hours.
I was really hoping to be zapping
that hated fifth grade teacher.
Maybe I still had too much anti-slack in my heart.
Maybe we're all still dwelling on revenge.
When we should be thinking about forgiveness,
there has been, there have been moments of anger
during this weekend, but all of them that I know of,
mostly, have ended in forgiveness.
And, uh.
In love.
And, yes.
All about love.
Praise love!
And even the occasional heartache.
Oh, screw it.
Ah, screw it.
No, no, no.
You're right, I'm so, I'm so-
And yeah, and we were all upset last year
when the Axis didn't arrive.
Bob let us down.
But hey, you know, if Bob can't screw up, who can?
I kinda felt that way about Bill Clinton.
Yeah.
You know, if the king of the universe
can't get some hanky-panky on the side,
then what did all those soldiers die for, friends?
And if-
If we can't get off Earth, then what do we get out of bed for?
We're going to get off.
Whether the aliens or Bob do it, we don't care.
We'll do it ourselves.
We've shown we can.
We can, yeah.
We only had a couple of casualties.
One car was destroyed by one of the incoming rockets.
A couple of rival cult compounds, I think, had their tent flaps caught on fire.
Yeah, right.
Oh, yeah, that wasn't my doing, though.
There was one pagan.
One was.
That one pagan whose tent kept coming in the path of rockets,
both from above and right across, directly across the grass.
He just seemed he sat out there in his easy chair and watched them come at him.
Yeah.
He was a slackful pagan.
Man, he was.
He just chilled out.
That rocket, that one rocket, man.
Friends, your host.
You can't even describe what happened to that one rocket.
Let me set the scene, friends.
It was Sunday afternoon before the world ended,
and your host, Commander Chaz, was in his full Dances with Rockets regalia,
a Native American headdress,
leading a procession of spicebags,
and rocket men, and savage earth men,
carrying standards of rocketry,
and a hell of a lot of psychedelically painted actual rockets,
and various other kinds of weapons.
There were potato cannons toted long behind,
chanting,
Build your own rocket ship.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Build.
Oh.
Now God.
We're teaching us,
I'm ELI,
about how to get robots
so that we arquers
off the track
I didn't know it was the sport-
or the B 제대로,
orcultural circuit and ride
car.
I think right in my lane.
He was delighting
did both physical distance,
Joe and Bob Mosick officiate,
helping as Chaz officiated
and introduced each rocket one by one,
plugging their butts with that rocket motor,
sticking them sensually down that long, long shaft
of that miniature gantry.
The crowd would expectantly wait
while Chaz would nonchalantly and coolly, calmly
light that rocket bud.
And then he'd saunter away
and kind of whisper,
fire in the hole, baby.
And the audience would hold their breath
and that rocket would go,
psss, pt, pt, pt, pt.
It's out of here, baby.
And the whole crowd would tilt their heads up
and stare into the face of the sun
as the rocket reached to that mighty flame
flaming orb up there.
We're talking big motors.
Sometimes their heads would pop off
and little handkerchief would pop out
and they'd float down all slackful and nice
on a parachute.
Other times they'd tilt upside down
and come screaming straight down
metal-pointed tip first
at the hood of a Cadillac car
that might be parked
or a nice trailer
or the rented...
I had to give him a CD.
The rented van that I drove up there in.
Oh, yes.
But I...
I didn't drive back.
I decided I'd stay here
till the exes come.
I'm just gonna hang out
till the exes come back.
I have faith.
I'll prove my faith.
I do.
Good.
So that sets the scene.
Oh, yeah.
The Snake Rocket.
Well, in every dance of perfection
there's always some clumsy oaf
that just almost burns down the building
and, uh...
Why...
It was a six-foot-tall rocket
but very thin.
And it had a...
a G-80 Blue Thunder motor in it
which has not that much thrust
but it is about 25, 30 pounds of thrust.
The rocket, of course,
is only about two pounds.
And as it took off,
it got about 10 feet high,
dove down,
flew straight into the camp
of this sort of pagan subgenius guy
sitting in his big lawn chair
and started exploding all over the ground.
And...
And he started dancing and firing up
and screeching louder than you can imagine.
And that guy, he just sat there.
He didn't even flinch.
This rocket was self-destructing,
catastrophic disaster,
10 feet in front of him.
And he just sat there with his beer in his hand.
And after it was all over,
he just kind of shook his head.
Maybe that was Bob in an overweight pagan suit.
But it sure was fun to watch.
Yeah, we launched him.
Friends X-Day was a wonderful success.
I wish that you could see the slides and videotapes
that I've got in my pocket right now.
WCSB Cleveland.
Where's Dave?
We all were prettier than last year.
And we had a prom, a lovely mutant prom, friends.
You know, we, a lot of us, Gene and I,
either don't remember our proms or wish we didn't or didn't even go.
And this year it was like a twisted, we turned the tables.
It was the exact opposite.
It was a funhouse mirror image of the high school from hell.
It was all the geeks and weirdos outnumbered the normals and populars
so much that there were none.
They were completely ostracized to the point where there was nothing
but ostracized weirdos and geeks having a party, man.
Oh, yes.
With Glenn Miller songs like any prom should have.
And friends, there was violence.
There was sickness.
There was, there was, there were moments when,
There was a lot of violence.
when I was seriously,
I was seriously terrified and my bowels are still kind of upset
at the punishment of Papa Joe Mama.
My friend, Papa Joe Mama,
I stood there and watched Friday Jones torture that man.
I videotaped while Friday Jones tortured a man.
You seem to be getting into videotaping that.
It's my way of, to tell the truth.
You're sticking that camera right in Papa Joe's face.
It's my way of not being involved.
It's my, it's my way of hiding.
It's like, it's the shell of,
the turtle that I am.
I'm hiding when I have that video camera.
No one can bother me, but I'm bothering everybody else.
Or at least, you know, I'm, you know how it is with the cameraman is in another dimension.
He's in the 10th dimension looking at all sides at once.
Little wiggles and squiggles.
Scares the heck out of me.
The fourth dimension and the sixth.
Those are the magical ones.
And the 10th.
Six plus four, 10.
Those are the magic numbers today.
They've displaced the three and the seven.
Six, four, 10.
Wiggles and squiggles.
Friends, atoms are nothing but little wiggles and squiggles in the middle of the ethers.
They're not really things.
You're not made of things.
You're not a thing.
You're just a pattern made of patterns.
You're nothing.
You're just a bunch of whirlpools held together in one whirlpool.
I'm nothing.
He's nothing.
The dog's nothing.
Everything came from nothing.
But Bob could just cough and blow up.
He could blow us all right off of the metaphysical table.
I mean, it's not as if it was all so densely compacted into one infinitesimally small point.
It was actually nothing.
Something from nothing.
That's the key.
As above, so below.
Or is it something?
All the way up, all the way down.
So big you can't go around it.
Where's that cowboy?
Are we supposed to be looking at the sky?
Are we looking at blinking lights on the phone or anything?
Yeah, I don't see any blinking.
I just, I don't know.
I just don't know.
Maybe no one actually, maybe it actually happened.
Maybe everybody else got ruptured but us.
We thought we were so slack, full and cool.
Thought we were Bob's chosen.
He took the rest of them.
Yep, the Bobbies.
The ones that we looked down upon and sneered at.
They were the ones who were lifted off.
And Dave, the most wretched of the lowly.
Of the forsaken.
The lonesomest.
Lonesome cowboy Dave.
Right.
Is now the least lonesome.
He's partying with the sexist.
It all makes sense.
He took the people who paid the way and left the people who took the pay.
Jesus said the meek shall inherit the earth and Zappa said the geeks shall inherit the earth.
And Jesus took the money and ran back to Dallas.
Centersville.
A real nice place to raise your kids up.
Quoteth the Reverend Howard Kalin.
Yeah, indeed.
Mark Vollman is not a member of the Church of the Subgenius.
He's only interested in carnal things.
But Howard Kalin of the Turtles and Flo and Eddie was a spiritual, he's a spiritual gentleman.
He's also rich as mine is price, Bob.
I'm going to go check the door.
Go ahead.
See if Dave's at the airlock.
Check the door.
This will be the 300th time today that Chaz is going to do that.
We're expecting him back.
He ain't coming back.
But I keep getting this beep on the radar here every now and then.
You gotta face it, man.
That's a booger.
That's a bogey.
You're...
Dave ain't coming back.
You gotta face it, dude.
I know he's your best friend.
But...
Where is he, man?
I know he's out there still.
He's gone, man.
It wasn't him.
I saw him eat it.
He's toast.
No, he jumped out of the way.
I saw him jump out of the way right at the last second.
No, you're kidding yourself, man.
His face, that was his face that was blown into your lap.
Oh.
I'm going to go look.
Well, you never know.
He'll be right back.
All right.
Oh, friends.
Oh, look, I've been left in the haunted station all by myself.
Dave ain't coming back.
You know why?
I made sure of that myself.
I've been wiping these rival weirdos out one by one.
Chad's the one.
He can't hear what I'm saying.
And I know you're not going to call in and tell him.
He-he-he-he.
Fools.
The blind earth fools stumbling and blinking in their pathetic three-dimensional, four-dimensional,
ten-dimensional...
Oh, Chad, ten dimensions, big deal.
Woo.
Oh, he's come back.
And, uh, yes, that's 75214, dear friends.
And you know what to do.
Mom's the word.
Ten dimensions.
The tape was running.
Oh, my tape.
I have to check my tape.
How pathetic that you could only come up with ten.
Now, don't say...
If not ten, why not twenty?
I'm going to be listening as I go.
If not twenty, why not thirty?
There he goes out the door.
There.
We don't have to worry about him anymore.
Yeah, he's so close-minded.
He-he-he's over there, you know, just still thinking Bob's going to come back and all
that crap.
Man, geez.
I mean, all I care about is launching the goddamn rocket.
Let's get out of here.
Come on.
Let's go.
Oh, I think he's coming back.
Hold on.
Never mind.
He's dead.
Yeah, Bob's cool.
All that.
Yeah.
Bob.
Praise Bob.
No, no, not here.
Right on.
So, um, it's so touching and lovely and beautiful and, um...
Special.
Wow.
This is...
Oh!
Oh, what a sick production.
But is...
Are these silly two-dimensional and even three-dimensional pictures of Bob?
Are these...
Bob?
Yeah.
No.
And we beat the shit out of him.
They are merely graven images of Bob.
Is this time control or is time control when we forget our... that... that horrible leash
attached to us?
The invisible fence around our necks?
Is it time control and escape, perhaps, truly when we just fought the conspiracy for a second
on... just for a few minutes while we're still clocked in, making that extra phone
call to the buddy?
When the boss isn't looking?
You know, maybe you get on your escape vessel every time you...
Cheat just a little.
Or, you know, or every time you do a senseless good deed and feel all...
Because every time you wipe out your bifold drug dealer down the block, you know, maybe
you're doing...
Maybe that's when you're upon your escape vessels.
Oh, doesn't that all sound...
It all sounds...
I mean, it's a different kind of thing.
It's a different kind of thing.
Sort of.
Yeah.
It was worth the 30 bucks.
Nobody needs to ask for their money back.
Yeah.
It's...
First Frank Capra when we need it.
God bless America.
Praise Bob.
The blue bus is calling us.
It's okay, kids.
Come on, join us.
When...
And meet me at the back of the blue bus.
What's the matter, kid?
You afraid?
Afraid your mom's gonna find out?
Don't you want to be cool?
Everybody's doing it.
Get on the bus.
I miss the Bob.
Hey, let's go join one of them UFO saucer cults and drink the Kool-Aid of Bob.
I heard that would take you to the other side.
Break on through, dude.
I want to get on the bus.
I want to get on the psychedelic bus.
I don't like steroids.
Now you got Aug Video, to now get a becoming evidence for alcohol.
That'll be in nome in some part of your文 for no reason.
What else could explode if Bob and I paid our parents?
What the?
Obviously, in anotherлю We'd be involved in some thing.
How the hell is puedes Guerr rzeczy dus αν imagining there would be more二
up to your chin in mud.
You pretend you don't like it.
Oh, in polite society, they act like it's not done.
And the little mudsuckers find their way.
Oh, even the mayor, you know.
Even the burgarmeister does it.
Yeah.
They mud out.
Get them mudsuckers in the right place.
Even if they don't do it well,
they may have their own special way of doing it,
but they do it.
And they wallow.
They all...
Is it too late to suck up?
I want to be Bob.
He sits far all the time.
He gave me things that's fine.
Don't want to be Jesus.
He always looks so sad.
He must have had an awful dad.
Never.
I want to be Bob.
Tell everyone about Slack.
Let the pigs kiss my crack.
Don't want to be Jesus.
I want to be no slave.
He should have stayed in his grave.
I want to be Bob.
Never have to work a day.
All eternity for play.
Don't want to be Jesus.
I want to carry no cross.
Don't want to speak to me on the bus.
I want to be Bob.
See everything else I'm clear.
Shit isn't good in here.
Don't want to be Jesus.
Always trying to figure things out.
Who needs all them fucking cosmic doubts.
I want to be Bob.
Yeah, I want to be Bob.
I don't even like it in New Zealand.
I want to be Bob.
Who needs all those fucking screams and alleen от моего.
Hoo, hoo, hoo.
In this informationless надежности
Ooming there taught me music,
But who gonna play Bob?
Yes, I should be tighten.
Two.
Three.
Better yet come next day.
Oh, dear friends, little Theodore.
Little Theodore at XX Day.
Amazing that we're just cracking into the first of these recordings.
Unlike...
Meanwhile.
What?
Oh, dear friends.
Oh, dear...
TheUR Squid I'm a little feet tall, little Astrid.
I티 estou peu overstale.
And hats off...
What?
Fuck you.
Shut up!
I drive my monkey
I drive my monkey all the way
Yeah!
Sax!
You heard it!
More violin in the monitor!
Ah, sax!
In another dimension!
Sax!
In another world!
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la!
Ah!
I'm high on the power of Venus!
Lots of good, a lot of time!
Ah!
Sax!
Well, I have no intention!
Not with no thoughty girls!
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la!
Ah!
I tried and I tried!
I will!
I tried!
Sax!
Come on, come on, come on!
Ah!
I've said it, it was a pity!
Sax!
Ah!
Oh!
All sex, will I have no retention?
Sex, in another dimension.
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la.
So long.
I do.
Bye-bye.
Oh, sex!
Sex!
Stein's Secret Orchestra, dear friends, at Dos Equis, a week ago.
Sex, in another dimension.
There may be time coming soon when you will not need that dangly-dingly
or that dangly-dingly.
No!
That pristine juicer you can, you hang from yourself.
That slimy eye, it's not good for pie in the sky.
Oh, I don't know.
We never were of Dallas, nor of any earthly place.
We are of our father's house on the escape vessels with Bob.
And though our father has left us locked in the bedroom,
yet one more year or century, as the case may be,
why, we still love our father, for we have no choice.
And because he locked us in the bedroom where there's that dresser
with the top drawer and those pictures in it.
Well, and that smelly stuff that he puts in his pipe.
Well.
That foul, that crap that has its own beard on it, almost.
Borkham Riff, I believe.
Borkham Riff?
That's what Bob smokes.
That's what assimilates Bob?
So what happened on your, how did you spend your subgenius holiday, July 5th?
Uh.
You weren't even awake at 7 a.m., were you?
None of them are?
No.
They were out there at Brushwood, the most holy of the holies.
Why, do you know how many, but Chaz here?
What were you doing at 7 a.m. when the aliens would have been rupturing?
How did you know?
There have been enough believers.
Hmm, Chaz?
Uh.
Had there been a quorum?
And, uh, what were you up to?
I don't even want to think about that.
What about Slack?
Let's not, let's not embarrass, uh, uh, Eagle Rocket Hunter.
Well, that's Michelle.
No, no, no.
What, what about Slack?
I mean, I figure that if the end of the world happens and I end up in a, in a realm of transcendent
bliss, you know, except when the loudspeaker speaks up and says, reality has ten dimensions,
uh, that's a very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very, very,
But HQ or, uh, declining our archeology, juegos and all, can certainly wondrously help
probably hoping to see me get thrown naked into the pond again.
That wasn't about to happen.
Been there, done that.
We burned a few people that had sinned against Bob.
Nobody got crucified? Nobody got tarred and feathered?
Lookie here. Look who came flying in through the window.
If it ain't that no longer lonesome pimp cow man, Damus.
Well, it sounds like Santa Claus has come to town, I mean.
That's the guy.
You guys, you don't know what's going on.
You should be glad.
You should be glad, man.
Are you all right?
What is that all over you?
That stuff.
You're gross. It smells horrible.
Get out of here.
That stuff is the stuff that you would have been in if you would have gotten ruptured up, man.
Is that Bob's doddle?
No, that's not Bob's doddle.
That's his sputum. That's his jolly.
I can never tell the difference.
What are you saying?
What are you saying, Dave?
You ruptured?
Why do you think I'm so late, man?
Is that what that stain in your pants?
Why do you think he's walking that much?
Wait, Dave. Wait. I think I figured it out.
There's a big...
Oh, man. The solar wind is kicking up like crazy today.
Yeah, he did.
No, I'm not kidding. This is a real story on NASA.gov.
Them eyeballs are popping out.
The top story. Watch, watch.
It's true. Chaz has tuned in on stream seven.
I was out in the middle of the night.
Surf's up for the solar wind. Right there.
Right. Where? A dog.
I saw it on the website.
Even as we taught friends the miracle of Internet and television.
It looked like a little pink wave.
There it is.
That was the first thing I saw.
And I thought, man, that's awfully weird for the dark of night to see like this little pink, little tinkly wave.
You know, those little sparkly things.
So can people out in the cars now see it?
No, the people in the cars, all of a sudden they disappeared.
And this thing, it took me right up.
Unmanned?
No, it was not unmanned.
It was filled with these most...
You ever see them like minotaurs and stuff like that?
Or they had these real dangly like nostrils and so forth?
Oh, yeah.
And some of them had big one eyes and some of them had...
Yeah.
And like...
Sure.
Didn't they look like Ray Harryhausen animation?
There was actually a guy dressed up...
Speaking of what you were saying, because I got off of this thing just very shortly afterwards.
There was a guy who looked like an evil Santa Claus there.
He had a Fu Manchu mustache and he had like his eyes pulled back.
And these little kids would come and sit on his lap.
And the minute they'd sit on his lap...
Man, calm down, Dave.
It was horrible.
It was horrible what they'd done to him.
And those little children have no rectal cavities, we can call them.
They're all behind you all.
But they were still alive and they're in these little cages now.
That is crazy.
And they didn't want to be ruptured.
And they got Bob.
They got Bob.
People, people, I'm not kidding about this.
They got him, man.
I want you to...
If you have a computer, I want you to log on to that.
NASA.gov.
It's all about doing this readout of this thing.
Hold on.
The son's about to...
Look at this.
He has been implanted.
No, no, it's not...
Go to NASA.gov and go to the NASA search...
And obey.
And go to NASA search and put in solar comma images.
And then click on the first one.
And it'll take you to a bunch of images.
And look at what's happening on the sun today.
Yes, that's what's happening.
It has to do with solar winds.
And that's why it has to do with X-Day.
And they got Bob, man.
They got Bob.
They got him in one of those little jars like what's his name?
Like Donovan's brain, you know?
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
You know, I always thought those solar winds were one of Bob's excuses.
Whenever the computers were screwing up, he'd go, oh, it's just solar flares.
No, I thought that was whenever there was a terrible smell all over the Earth that Bob
was responsible for.
He'd say it was just a solar wind.
Yeah.
Look.
It looks just like that.
What?
Good Lord, man.
They've just brought into this radio studio a thing in a jar.
It's actually a pig fetus, which we carefully concealed as a hairy head.
No, it's not a pig.
It's a human or a little.
Oh.
It's like one of those killing faces.
Yeah.
What the hell is this?
It's a pet's patch.
One of those dolls.
Disgusting.
Baby sage cabbage patch.
It's an embalmed cabbage patch, Benzie.
It's like the monkey's paw inside a jar of water.
It's like a hideous LSD fetus, Benzie.
That's not really one of those.
You know, that's what we ought to do with that thing.
Put up a big sign, charge 50 cents, see the hideous crack baby.
Yeah, well, we used to pay for the carnivores.
When I was a kid, we had carnivores.
You did do that.
Did you see that Corman movie, the hideous crack baby?
No, I...
It was about three...
Was that the one with the guy...
Look at what's going on here.
... bringing the head of two sluts?
No, of hearts and livers.
That is our son today.
That is the star around which our...
That image was taken in the last hour.
Wait.
I'm not kidding you.
It is getting weird, man.
It's an image of...
It looks as if...
Like a robot man.
... the sun is in the process of rupturing or exploding.
I'm not kidding you.
So if you can't hear us anymore, if all of a sudden you hear a bunch of static in your
speakers, we're going nova, baby.
These eruptions on the sun must be the size of several earths.
Look at this jet right there.
... will be the city of Cleveland destroyed.
Look at that.
This is part of a 12-year cycle.
I'm trying to tell you what they're trying to tell me.
What is that black spike in the lower left-hand corner emerging from the sun?
That is the...
The black spike down.
... that is the sun.
That is the solar succubus.
I've been trying to tell you guys, that thing is the ejaculi or the jolly of the sun.
It is coming out of the sun.
It is coming out and it is creating, it is trying to create its own new life form on
this planet, but we gotta go.
These rocks have arrived...
We gotta go.
... instead of the exes, and they're even now...
They are...
And look at the shock waves coming off of that one right there.
You got one wave, two wave, three shock waves.
It literally looks as if tiny black holes have been shot into the solar surface with
You know, it is theoretically possible, it's theoretically possible to create tiny black
holes, theoretically.
That's right.
In theory, you could do it.
Right.
I can't believe you guys.
If they got a little too big...
Let's go to another one.
... they would become ever growing.
Listen folks, these guys are looking at this on the internet and they're babbling away
in awe of the science of their own church, which they have babbled so long.
This is really going on, Stan.
... are the main...
This is, I mean, talk about...
People worry about the power company getting shut off during the Y2K bug extermination.
Man, the life is...
Look at that.
... the Lord God Almighty could turn off your power supply with a flick of his mighty
...
That's what he's going on.
... that's 10 billion light years long.
Yes, he is.
He could shoot a black hole into the center of our sun with his cosmic t-shirt.
Oh man, I don't know if they're going to get it.
And you would never know what had happened.
And it would be your iniquity.
I should have doubted about it.
And you're sick.
I don't know, I guess it's 20 minutes ago because I lost 20 minutes.
And your unwillingness.
That's why the aliens didn't come.
I was supposed to be here at midnight.
It's because you didn't believe enough.
You've got to clap your hands and say, I'm going to kill you.
I believe in them.
Don't let the sun burn out.
Look at that giant shadow coming across the sun.
My God, it's a giant dragon.
It's biting the chunk out of the sun.
I don't understand that it's really happening.
Think this has anything to do with the rockets we launched?
If you just amnestize us just a couple days or weeks off, man, it's X-Day is really coming.
And you don't want to be in them pleasure vehicles.
Dave, that's a frightening thought.
Dave, do you think this might have something to do with the rockets we launched?
That's what I've been trying to tell you guys.
We're in a whole mess.
We're in a whole mess of duty, Juan.
That wasn't what he was trying to do.
That is part of it, man.
Everything's coming down in one big crunch.
Well, I don't know if any of them actually reached the sun, if that's what you guys are
inferring, but they claim they're getting too much metal, assuming something they were
actually doing.
And you was involved.
No, Dave, you don't understand.
It wasn't the rockets that we launched.
It was the motors.
We put a couple of big motors into the earth itself.
They used some of that dark matter.
You mean to tell me that's...
Yeah, in the motors.
You guys have a plan?
I saw that on that cartoon show.
I think the earth is moving closer to the sun.
One pound of it weighs 10,000 pounds, and they used that in one of those rocket motors.
And one of them misfired, the one that went towards that pagan's tent.
I think the motor just kept burning its way down into the ground.
It went to the center of the earth and it was shayed out into the sun.
I'm getting depressed now.
Those things are like slingshots, man.
Orbit trajectories of black holes.
And singularities.
Things could only be XXX day now.
We could be talking about something the size of a point.
All I know is I just got abducted and I was trying to tell them what happened with X-Day
and everything.
If this thing has landed in our sun, then not even Bob can save us now.
I've got to suck oozing out of my pores now.
I was thinking he'd accept him in one of those Curly Q things.
What the hell are you mumbling about, Dave?
Well, it's one of...
I'm depressed, man, because...
Take your pill.
It's not a question of taking a pill.
I'm not taking a pill.
You don't want to go in them pleasure vehicles, Dane.
That's what I've been trying to tell you.
It's like the Santa Claus guy was saying, kind of, only it's ten times worse.
You see...
You mean you actually did make it with that Claus woman?
No, no, no.
There's no making or nothing.
They just took me in there and they showed me what was really going on.
It's like, remember at Auschwitz and then where they thought they were taking a shower
and they were going to get all rubbed up, scrubby-dubby?
Well, that's what they're luring us in with, see?
They think, well, you come on board there and you're going to have your hearts to the bone.
You don't know what you're going to desire.
Whatever you think of them, you want.
Yeah, that's what Bob promised us.
Yes.
Well, they also told me that they got you bejesus and you don't know what the hell you're
talking about now because they've been controlling your mind for about 17 years now.
Well, there's not much I can do about that now, is there?
Well, see, what happened...
I should be honored to be their tool.
What happened was you started off.
You discovered them and you knew what was going on.
I'm chosen.
And then after a while, they thought they would turn it into a joke at your behest and
for you and by you, but at the same time, you were always being confused.
controlled, see? And while you
was being controlled, you got everybody
all the rest of us controlled.
But we're not really going
into pleasure vehicles. We're going into like
little torture domes. It's like a
little hurricane on the sun.
Yeah, man, that's all. Look at these.
See, they're really, they're folding up here, see?
They're getting rid of everything. They're going to
start it all over again. It won't even look like
stars and planets. Everything must go by 99.
Everything is going to cut in.
Oh, that big black spike that was
coming out. It doesn't even look, the sun doesn't even look
round anymore. It's not, see?
It looks like a big saw blade.
It's like part of it's starting to cave
in a little bit. Yeah, it looks like a
big saw blade. Like something's just eating it up
or like some reaction's gone
horribly wrong. It's spinning out
and the things are coming out of it.
People, we're not kidding you. You've got to log on to
NASA.gov and get
into the solar images.
This cycle started 12 years ago.
Some people actually saw it on the
shores of Lake Erie. They said it looked
like...
The sun was spewing out a little
thingy. And then the
NASA and some other people at the weather control
whatever they call it, meteorological services
said there was a severe
eruption on the sun. And they said
well, we're going into a 12 year cycle
and nobody knows how. It's 11 years, isn't it?
Well, it must have been 11 years ago.
The sun has an 11 year cycle. That makes a lot more
sense, too. An 11 year cycle
of destroying all life on Earth
every 1 million years.
Thanks, God.
Thanks, God. Great. We just happened
to come along. Finally, we invent
the internet, writing and movies
and MTV and all this cool
stuff and, you know,
aspirin. And then
it's time for the 11 year
cycle where the sun flares up
and changes all life on Earth.
Inflates just a little bit and
belches out a little flame. Let's a
new phylum take over and
begin its long climb out of
the muck. It's degraded to new shoes
anyway. The prairie squid
people of a million years from now
will find the fossils of our skyscrapers
and go, look, the bugs
used to build hives.
Well, they'll be just like when
Charlton Heston was screaming about guns
in the bathroom the other day going, look at
what you did. No, what was that line?
God damn you all
the hell you blew it up.
No, no, no. The planet of the apes.
Yeah, that's what that's
damn you. Damn you.
That wasn't it.
Damn you all
the hell you did it. You
finally went and did it. You blew
it up. Okay, that was it.
That was it.
Blow it off or blow
it up. Just don't blow it.
Join the church of subgenius
and don't let this happen again.
When was the last time you
sent that $30 to Bob?
When was the last time?
It's the end. You tied your
shoes this morning, but the undertaker
in hell is going to untie them
tonight. You're in your shoes in a
trash can. 90 zillion degree
blue winds sweeping across
the continent.
The Aurora Borealis
just kicking backwards.
Fire is going out in space and it's going to
lick across this planet.
It's going to scour the planet.
It's going to cleanse this planet.
Weird little scooters like they have in Latin America.
It's going to find the center
and the saint of life.
The virtuous and the filthful
will all together be
mixed in that one great...
Great. Imagine if you was living
in Panama or something.
Mixing pot of souls.
The slurry of the slugs of your souls.
Just because of the weight of the solar magic.
It's too late now.
Here goes our atmosphere.
Atmosphere's going there.
It's breathing going on.
How many days is it?
Have a drink of water.
Four days.
Nostradamus predicted
that the sun would go out
in July of 1999.
Did you know that?
Well, oh, jeez.
Here we are at the...
We've come full circle.
What can we actually say about the crux
of the focal crux that we're in?
And we're trying to make jokes about it,
but it really is.
Well, you know, when the entire solar system
is obviously about to just go out,
like snuff out like a candle,
you might as well make jokes.
What are we going to do?
Put our heads between our legs
and kiss our butts goodbye
like that funny old nuclear war test?
poster.
I'm going to have
Chorizo and eggs.
That's what I'm going to do.
This is the sound of the sun right now.
You know, that sounds good.
I'm going to have me
some jalapenos in the egg.
We've got about an hour left of reality.
Do you think so?
Ten minutes left of the show.
If we finish the show
in about ten minutes,
I'll be up for some Chorizo and eggs.
People, there's a tendril of sun gas
heading our way.
Is that still downloading?
And you can...
Yeah, it's still downloading.
I think that's going to be
the latest image.
I'm amazed with this kind of solar activity
that any of this Internet stuff works.
Well, it's...
It's...
Because it's hardwired.
And the Internet is hardwired.
I'm sure the radio signals
are getting interference by now.
Yeah, right.
They also said that they had
a part of Steve Winstead's brain
in the NASA studio itself.
Well, that's why
they're taking so long to load now.
It's like the giant...
It's like a bionic implant
or something.
It's like the giant pool cue
of the Lord
poking about to slam
that big ball right into the Earth
and knock us into the side pocket.
No kidding.
That's what it looks like to me.
We'll go scattering those asteroids
around in the Mars orbit.
Whoa.
That's what it looks like.
Have a...
Why not?
Guess we're gonna be
on this rocket ship,
Spaceship Earth,
only it's going somewhere else.
Wow.
That's what I...
Looks like we're gonna be
spun right out into space.
We'll hope the sunlight's
gonna reach us.
What the hell are we gonna do, man?
What the hell are you talking about?
There ain't gonna be no more sun.
And them pleasure vessels
are full of torturistic,
sadistic, demon-type guys.
God, man, maybe...
And you have been selling us all
and yourself down the river
for all these years,
for a long time.
For a lousy 30-buck tent.
Do you think...
Wait a minute.
Maybe...
Do you think maybe
I made a mistake?
You were just gonna get
burned out by the sun.
Could Bob just be
some charlatan and...
No.
They are taking
some of us with them.
...sold us out for...
And it won't be fun.
...firewood, so to speak?
We're just a firework.
Wait a minute.
It's like we were...
We're a sadistic thing, Stan.
They torture...
Like you said so many times,
they eat our pain
for pleasureisms.
So we're the...
No, it's like we...
We're the pig fat
and the griddle.
That's it.
Yeah.
And this is their
firework show.
We're just the pig fat
and the griddle.
It's more like you guys
were describing before,
like a banquet is what
they're gonna do to us,
but it's a pain banquet,
like they subject us
to all kinds of humiliation
and we're just the fat.
I knew I never should've
tortured those animals
when I was a child.
We're just the fat
to cook something in.
What's the...
What's the real entree?
Well, perhaps there's
bigger fish to fry.
Perhaps there is a God
on this planet.
War in heaven, friend.
It's a war in heaven
between the hires
and the even hires than that.
The archons are duking it out
and we're getting
into the shtick again.
And we get these
mysterious pictures
of the sun on the internet
that represent
the battleground of the gods.
Well, what can we as like
flatulent Doris Drake
crossdressers and people
that just...
Just pray?
Pray.
Oh, I don't know.
Pray your little
pathetic heart out.
Ain't gonna do you any good,
but it might make you
feel a little better,
so that's why
we say all you can do now
is pray.
Do you remember
the Neolish
and the Big Lebowski
and how, like, kind of,
I don't know,
silly they seemed?
I was told
to check it out.
Well, they were
just like stupid,
you know, the Neolish
and stuff,
and I kind of maybe
feel like maybe
we're just stupid.
You know what I mean?
There's nothing...
It's so Neal
that we ain't got
no Neolism
for it to be about.
I mean,
it would be redundant.
Nada, inada, inada.
It creeps in this
petty pace
from day to day
to the last...
Oh, my.
Now, that one looks
like a nipple, doesn't it?
That one looks
like an avioli or something.
All our CDs...
Some womb-like things.
...burned fools away
to dusty erasure.
Well, the thing
is downloaded up now,
and it looks like
a human womb
or maybe a hot nipple
or something.
Outbrief zipper.
Unzip, zip, zip
thine solar flares
and flop out
thine solar flares.
Thine hydrogen
peckers of doom.
Hydrogen peckers
of doom.
That's what the band
should have been named
long ago,
the hydrogen peckers
of doom.
A poor Trojan
or player
struts and frets
and picks his nose
upon the stage,
exposes himself,
and then is heard
no more.
Does a tale
told by an idiot
thrice told...
You can't speak
for yourself.
Well, that's what
I thought the soliloquy
ended with.
It was a tale
told by an idiot
full of sound and fury.
Signifying...
A signifying monkey.
A signifying monkey
is what we'd like
to see right now.
A signifying monkey.
That's all
this old show has been.
It's not a cage
full of signifying monkeys.
This whole planet,
this whole solar system,
this whole history...
I know that old
rock and roll song.
This whole evolution,
the creation itself,
a zoophilus.
A zoophilus.
A signifying monkey.
Man, that guy was
ahead of his time again.
Pathetic little noise
in their brief space
upon the earth
before the big light
winked out.
Night, night,
little monkeys
in your cage.
Night, night,
all your great skyscrapers,
your achievements,
your mighty books
and discoveries,
your symphonies,
your armies,
your concentration camps.
All of it was...
Your indoor plumbing,
your toiletries,
and your many...
As a wink,
delicacies,
that no one could eat
because you were starving.
Dying ember
in the middle
of thousands
and billions
of light years
of empty,
cold space.
Glowing, stinky hole
in your third eye.
You are about as important
as a cork in the ocean,
my friend.
Think of a cockroach,
if you would.
I don't know if you want to
think of one for too long,
but just imagine
the revulsion you feel
when you swat one
and brush it away
from yourselves.
Think of yourself
as a mere cockroach
compared to these weird
exes, archons,
whatever the hell they are.
They don't notice you.
They don't care about you.
If you happen to hitch a ride
and they don't swat you off,
then count yourself lucky.
But don't think
you're some kind of a big deal
just because God
or some aliens
happen to pick you up
by the scruff of your neck
and show you a thing or two.
They're in there with you.
They're in the room
with you.
You can't see them.
You can't smell them.
You can't taste them.
But they're in the room
with you.
They blend with the walls,
with the CDs,
with the pono rack,
with the...