Well, get this, because my sacred main multimedia womb module computer broke.
This is not only a rerun of an old hour of slack, a number 114 from 1987 or so, produced on cassette tape.
Hey, remember those old cassette tapes that I'm having to send out to the radio stations in the year 2001, dubbed on cassette tape.
But we will be back with the CDs soon. Give me slack or kill me.
Oh, it's biggin'. It's biggin'.
We've had so many big days here lately that we just have more money than we know what to do with.
And I hope that you do too someday.
But, you know, big day can go on forever.
Yeah, that's right. It can go on.
For a long, large time.
But you may wake up tomorrow and you're having a small day.
Yeah, a small day.
I might have a small day tomorrow. I kind of doubt it.
But it's possible.
Small days.
Yeah, if it happens, it happens.
Now I don't know where the moral is or where the song should end.
But I wonder just how many more.
I don't know.
It's going to be tough. It's going to be bad.
It's going to be bad.
She is good and we don't.
We be in
Welcome dear friends
To the subgenius
Hour of Slack
Sponsored by the church
Of the subgenius
The subgenius
Hour of Slack
That you are about to listen to
Is specially designed
Only to be played
On radio station
And only in the city of
And I don't want to
You've got a much better mood
No I won't
No
Ultimately what
Know ye
Of the purity
Of the essence
Of hate
Of
Envy
To
I guess you bloodsuckers enjoy being repulsed, eh?
You're loyal to the gore.
Well, that's good.
We don't want any dead wood in our fraternity of fright fans.
That just...
Listen, I feel the power of evil coursing through my veins, spinning every corner of my being with the desire to do wrong.
I feel so bad, but it's good, good.
Yes, it is good.
You are about to experience a totally new dimension in sound.
No lesser work than the overthrowing of creation itself.
We will remake man in our image, not his.
It's just like a...
The music is just going through.
Quick, the torch!
Get out of here!
You've got to match!
I've got to match!
It is sound that surrounds you.
In front, behind, above, below, all around you when you wear headphones.
So, put on your headphones.
You should be hearing me in your right ear.
If not, reverse your headphones.
You should now be hearing me in your left ear.
So now, sit back and enjoy a new dimension in sound.
The Kunzkopf Binaural Sound Experience.
I...
Effective.
Done. Done.
Continue.
Who are we?
I was born a...
...bob.
Why?
That's a good question, Michael Pepe.
Well, you know, dear friends...
It's sort of like this.
I haven't had a cigarette in ten days now, friends.
That's right.
Your host, Rev. Ivan Stang,
hasn't had a cigarette in ten days.
Now, you non-smokers, you can laugh all you want,
but for me, it's like I can't touch one.
I won't and I can't.
It's like I've lost a loved one.
It really is.
It's just like...
It's like practice for grief.
This is...
I'll be ready when a close relative dies next time.
It's about the same kind of thing.
See, last week, I still had enough of a brain left
at the back of my mind that I finally realized
I had to quit smoking.
And so I did, with the help of an injection.
A simple treatment, just a shot in the ear
at an acupuncture point.
A solution supposed to help your body retain
the nicotine that was in it so you don't crash so hard.
Oh, and, uh...
You know, when you quit...
When you go cold turkey,
off cigarettes, dear friends,
all reality changes.
You wish you could just be a baby again.
You want to crawl back inside there.
You get paranoid.
You feel like you want to turn yourself in to somebody.
Turn yourself in.
But who are you gonna turn yourself in to?
Sort of like living in Russia.
It wasn't Popeye.
It wasn't Popeye sleeping on the street.
It was me.
I'm about worn out, friends.
You tell, baby.
It's like being hollowed out.
Every...
Every cell.
And you can't hit the demon that's making the pain come.
You can't shoot him.
You can't stop that kind of pain.
It's a hurt that ain't like pain.
It's a brain hurt.
Every cell hurts.
And nobody knows.
You certainly don't know.
Not even you.
Because I haven't worsened anybody.
We're gonna continue on with some more enlightening material later on.
But I want you to know that when you...
You smokers out there, you might as well keep smoking.
It ain't worth quitting.
It ain't.
It's terrible.
Don't believe the non-smokers.
After about a week, you start belching up the taste of metal.
The taste of the end of a ballpoint pen in elementary school.
Starts coming up out of your stomach.
When you least expect it.
Your sleep is disrupted.
You'll fall asleep at 7.30 in the evening.
And then wake up at midnight.
And twitching.
Twitching.
Make passing horrible...
Extruded materials from your body.
Blurred vision.
Clammy limpness alternating with raging...
Blood engorged...
Horrors from your body.
And sneezing, snot and allergies.
Cramps.
Tremors.
The shakes.
Tumors.
And the worst part.
But maybe the most necessary part.
Is the fights.
The fights that you go over in your head.
Not in real life.
Just in your head.
You think of all the mean things you ever wanted to say to anybody.
And you say them in your head over and over again.
Because they don't know exactly the right thing to say to you when you're totally freaked out.
They come up and go, can I help you?
Can I get you anything?
And then you'll start into it.
You'll go, oh, can you get me anything?
And you realize, oh, no, no, this isn't real.
No.
You go, no, no thanks.
I don't need anything.
And...
And you feel pretty bad, friend.
So don't believe anything I say.
Don't believe anything I...
You hear it in my mouth.
This show, last show, or the next few shows.
You kids out there that do crack.
You don't...
You don't know nothing.
Tobacco is the ultimate crack, friends.
Well, maybe not.
No, I can think of something else that might be the ultimate crack, but...
Oh.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Oh, the music here is from Doc Stock.
Beautiful, beautiful Doc Stock.
This is, uh...
I think some broken combination of Doctorsters for Bob,
Pope David N. Meyer on drums,
and Dr. Philo Drummond,
Sterno on bass,
and, uh...
Gene Splice on the...
on the...
skitzed-out guitar.
Thank y'all.
¶¶
When stress builds and you're about to lash out, stop.
Take time out.
Don't take it out on your kid.
Don't take hold of your child until you get a hold of yourself.
Why?
¶¶
in an egg. We're going to look for low-level cell activity at the beginnings of life.
A fire and for a mighty rushing wind which will cover the face of the earth and wipe clean the
scourge of woolly thinking once and for all. It's satisfying though. I don't understand what
happened. This is a situation unlike any experience by modern man.
Folks, you are looking at a real life drama.
Quack, quack, quack here. Quack, quack there. Gas with amazement as I fell back asleep.
Yeah, folks.
Come on, don't confuse people. I've been listening on the radio and probably two people crashed right
now as you said that thinking, I'm late. I'm late. Crash. We talked about doing
this. We talked about this show for so long. Maybe, maybe, maybe.
I don't know.
We leap up and go.
Are we not radio?
E-Radio.
T-D-O-N.
Oh, yeah.
Did you say kill me?
Yeah.
A-2. Listen to them.
He's right here in the script.
Yeah.
Page 8, yeah, there you go, hello.
Hello.
Great.
Oh.
Paging number 8, caller.
Hello.
Yeah, this must be, you're going to be Hal, right?
I'll be Hal?
Yeah, aren't you Hal this morning?
Yeah, I'm Hal.
Okay.
Who are you?
Well, hey, Hal.
Hal doesn't recognize us anymore.
Who are you?
I'm just one of the Dugs.
Come on, Hal.
You're Dugs?
I'm Hal.
I'm any of the Dugs, yeah.
You're one of the Dugs?
Yeah.
Oh.
Okay, wait here, Hal.
I can't wait that long.
I'm calling long distance.
Okay, go ahead.
Hey, state short Hal question.
Right?
What?
Oh, I mean, maybe, that's where I thought I was here.
Isn't that where I am on the script?
State short Hal question?
Wow.
Right?
Is that right?
Oh, okay, wait a minute.
I think, I see what the problem is.
It's...
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah, no, wait.
Hello.
No, I think I got it.
No, I got it.
Okay, caller, I got it.
Sorry.
Yeah, I got it now.
Oh, man, yeah.
Yeah.
It's kind of scary there, because you think for a minute you don't have it together, and
then you think, oh, I got it, but...
Hey, Hal.
What?
Hal.
Oh, hi, Hal.
Well, at any rate, it doesn't matter how I say it.
It's just...
Let's see you come out of that.
Oh, it's an ugly, ugly situation.
Oh, горdy!
Buddy, let me know what's on.
Apparently, the investment you're putting in a Yesная found that it's a little stupid,
Where is that?
Yeah, see, ah...
You called me out in the middle of it.
A little
of this, I broke it up.
See if we can find a lot more expansion and info.
friends, and you've got to help me. You've got to pray for me, and you've got to call
the Will of Dobbs at 823-7490. He's got nothing better to do. Yes, you can get, come on, call
823-7490 for phone social intercourse with a beautiful live man. So friends, be a winner,
don't be a loser. I can't, I have to be a winner. I can't start smoking again, or my kids would be
disgusted, totally disgusted. So would I. I'd be, I'd be, I'd be in loser mode because of that,
from cigarettes. But instead, I'm going to be a winner, friend, like they say in those stupid
motivational tapes. And the fact that I can even say this and joke about it only 10 days after my
last cigarette, wow, that's proof that the treatment works, even if it's just
something that I can't do.
Psychological faith healing. So, so friends, like I say, I haven't killed anybody yet. I quit
smoking, and I haven't killed anybody. Haven't mistreated my, my dog, haven't killed it. I didn't
do nothing. No, I didn't. I swear, I did nothing. I, I made certain suggestions from certain
philosophical viewpoints with my friend, Dr. Philo Drummond, but we, we were merely throwing
out possibilities. We weren't giving orders. We were speaking to people. We weren't giving orders.
We were speaking metaphorically. We'd never in our wildest dreams have imagined that some
misguided, misbegotten teenage normals would go out and do these things to, uh, respected golfers.
It was, it was artwork, officer. That's all artwork. That's all we're doing. Artwork. You
have a light. Does anybody have a light? The batteries in this radio are dead as hell.
I told you.
Will it hold?
What?
Are you sure?
Whew. Yeah. Yeah, it's alright. I promise.
Yatahey, Ray Spruce. Yatahey, Chief Woodenhead. I am ashamed to stand inside this place.
And you, for cranking up history, the pin-
I'm gonna pay you a fine.
If not, you'll pay the Sons of the Seventh.
If it doesn't pay off, you'll be hanged.
Nothing matters. Determined to take us with them. It means force. I'll handle this.
No. No, no, Savvy. You know, my Sunday school teacher used to-
You say you gotta learn to swallow disappointments in this sad life.
We are so mercifully free of the ravages of intelligence.
You save us.
Robert, we must plan a new world together. This time, we're started properly.
And again in Ruth 16, 23, we read,
For we shall gain great comfort from this, that he who shall turn his head from the brightness of the Lord shall have it loose from his neck.
And since we have time for debate, let's close now the passage from Ezekiel 12, 14.
Hmm.
Busy, busy, busy. Want a cup of coffee? You don't have a bathroom, do you? Don't pump me.
You know how things go.
Hmm.
Busy, busy, busy. Want a cup of coffee? You don't have a bathroom, do you? Don't pump me.
You know how things go.
Hey, hey, hey!
Everybody knows you run around town.
All my friends. What you doin'?
Way up there.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Um, um, um, um, um, um, um, um, um, um, um.
Oh, dear friends, that was Michael Pepe.
Michael Pepe, pope, and what is his subgenius name? I can't even remember.
Y'all keep your eyes open for Michael Pepe. That's from a tape that he did.
Um, I don't think it's commercially available, but you can if you want to call us.
And find out where to get those, um, you can at least get our address, which we'll also be reading at the end of the broadcast.
Or watch out in a couple of months for the book High Weirdness by Mail, which will tell you where to get all of these, uh, things.
But you can't get it yet. It's not available.
Um, just keep your eyes open. A book, High Weirdness by Mail.
Just pick it up in the store and every time you hear an hour of slack, go in the store the next morning.
You don't have to buy the book or anything.
You just look up the name of the person I played on the show, and there will be their address, and, uh, just copy it down right there in the store. No problem.
Do you believe you got a conscience that'll put you to death?
Or do you think you don't believe you got one?
What can I do to you?
That's me sick of all this talking and fussing about nonsense.
Shut up, White Ice.
Or else I'll have to shove something into your mouth to kill you.
I'll keep you quiet. Hey, Sam.
Now, eat the egg.
Go!
Shit, shut up!
Yeah, why don't you run us out of town, Chef?
Or I'm gonna ask my buddy here to bring me something off the hardware shelf that I can use to slice off your fingers.
Move, lady, or I'm gonna blow off your old man's Uncle Bishis!
Time-ho!
Cowboys and Indians were never like this.
I've gone empty.
I'm gonna kick your ass.
Yeah, bang, bang.
Aborted fetuses that we rescued.
Huh?
Immortality.
Oh, now, come on.
Well...
Here they come. Stay down. Here they come.
Scary little ugly things.
That's a heliopter.
I don't understand why our own church sends these things in to try to kill us on our own show.
Well, it's part of the dogma.
That was the only show we'll try to kill, dude.
If I can't talk, I'll vote.
How do I know? I can't think anymore.
That's how it is.
Just trying to remember something.
Oh, I can't breathe.
What did you say?
I can't breathe.
I don't understand.
Oh, yeah.
I've seen people do that.
I think they eat black rock.
You'll have to be thankful for it.
Oh, there we go.
Beautiful.
As we listen to the music being played, there are thousands of low-income people in Dallas struggling to survive.
They are families.
Single women with children.
The elderly.
The young.
The poor.
The common people trying to edge out a living to get justice.
That battering situation, it ended with me being shot and left paralyzed.
I don't think that I could be here today if it wasn't for the fact that I care so much about women.
From the initial report that they gave us, it doesn't seem like they made much of a difference.
I think that they made much headway in making these loans available to the low- and moderate-income people.
These voices, for the most part, go unheard or take a back seat with other media.
And it's time for us to stand up and be counted and recognize we need somebody down there with voices and can be heard.
Not seen, but be heard.
Stand up and let them know that it's not just her speaking up, but it's for everybody who really wants these things done.
The movement back in the 60s, and yet we've come a long ways, but there's still a lot that has to be done.
When it comes to people like us, we go to the bank, fairly good critic or bad critic.
It doesn't really matter.
They're not going to loan us any money.
With an organization like yours, maybe we could get together and form a committee like the young lady said, and get to work.
You know, instead of talking, let's do something.
Get up off our do-nothings, you know.
And stop sitting on the premises.
You know?
And stand on the promise.
You know, she asked me if this would make a difference.
And I said, well, you can bet your bottom dollar this is going to be the topic of conversation at the banks that were represented here this weekend for a long time to come.
But no single event like this changes things.
It's the accumulation of events and pressing the challenges and pressing the negotiations and pressing home the point of the problems in the neighborhoods that's going to create the change.
Or something like that.
If you like what it's about, we will equip you with a tape recorder and teach you how to make a difference.
What time is the show in tonight?
Same old time.
Same old time?
Yeah.
What time is that?
I don't know, man.
Do you have a ticket?
Yeah, I got a ticket.
Okay, great.
You got your ticket?
Yeah, I hope so.
I hope so, too.
Okay, I'm going to go check the bags in.
See you wait here.
Okay.
Hello?
Oh, hello.
zoals números Representativeを赤2が答えた
I'm here.
I've got to go.
I have a quarter of that.
Quarter quarter.
You got a quarter?
Sure, here you go.
Thanks.
Here I go.
You know, you really shouldn't be wasting so much time with this dumb machine.
Quiet, you're making it mad.
Why haven't you found a job yet?
Have you got another quarter? I want to play it again.
Sure, here you go.
You know, you're...
Have you got another quarter?
Sure, here you go.
Thanks.
Here I go.
You know, you really shouldn't be wasting so much time with this dumb machine.
Have you got another quarter?
Here you go.
Thanks.
Thanks. Shouldn't be wasting so much time with this dumb machine.
Quiet.
Why haven't you found a job yet?
Here I go.
Quiet.
Why haven't you found a job yet?
Because I want more than a job.
Well, I...
Attacker.
I want to play it again.
Have you got another quarter?
Sure.
Thanks.
Here I go.
Why haven't you found a job yet?
Quiet, you frauds.
Attacker.
Have you got...
Here you go.
You know, you really shouldn't be...
Quiet.
Well...
Attacker.
I want to play it again.
Sure.
You frauds.
Thanks.
Here I go.
Why haven't you found a job yet?
Quiet.
Sure.
Attacker.
Have you got...
Here you go.
Here I go.
You know, you really shouldn't...
Frauds.
Quiet.
You're making it mad.
Why haven't you found a job yet?
I want to...
Here you go.
Thanks.
Sure.
Why haven't you found a job yet?
I really want to...
Aim high.
Well, why can't you find something like that?
Quiet.
You're making it mad.
Attacker.
Quarter.
Dumb, dumb, so dumb.
You're making it mad.
Attacker.
Quarter.
Sure.
Thanks.
You frauds.
Why haven't you found a job yet?
Dumb.
Attacker.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Sure.
Why haven't you found a job yet?
Aim high.
Dumb.
Attacker.
Quarter.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Dumb machine.
So dumb.
Haven't you found a job yet?
Because I want more than a job.
Attacker.
Have you got another quarter?
Have you got...
I want to play it again.
Well, that was negative land.
Yes, Bob Dobbs is a sex god.
He has come and keeps coming again and again,
not to forgive your sins,
but to rationalize them,
to justify your sins.
Rather than forgiveness,
he offers something far more powerful.
An excuse.
A divine, all-inclusive excuse
which allows the bearer to free himself
from the grip of temptation
by overindulging in it
until it releases him.
The true seeker must give himself up to temptation
or he will never conquer it.
As Bob says,
too much is always better
than not enough.
The sad, weakly self-denial
preached by the New Age movement
is pure conspiracy pabla.
The true son or daughter of Bob
knows that our universe
is no laid-back,
home-chanting cosmos,
but an active, tumultuous,
squirting universe
bent on rampant reproduction
and easy grins.
The false cults may try to teach
personal transformation,
psychic development,
human potential,
but Bob goes straight for the glands
and seeks to amplify the self,
to bloat the abnormality potential
of his pupils.
Only through excess
can one contact the lower self
where the real decisions are made.
Don't just eat a hamburger,
eat the hell out of it.
The advanced initiate, once freed from
conspiracy programming,
as well as the worldly goods
that had enslaved him,
makes his pilgrimage to Dobstown,
the church's fabul-
walled encampment
deep in the jungles of Malaysia.
There, the initiate's third nostril
is surgically opened by psychic surgeons,
allowing him or her to
whiff-read the psychic stench
of those around him.
He masters the mystic sciences of
schizofreniatrics and memory editing,
creating a clean slate on the way to his death.
The first thing Bob can do
is to read the book of the
The Art of Excremeditation,
which is taught by the mind
that is void upon the great throne of relief.
As soon as you turn your back,
everything in the universe
snaps itself inside out
with a hideous sucking motion.
The only reason you cannot call the world impossible
is because it is only through the world
that you know the concept of impossibility.
You have been enlightened,
and led to believe that everyone feels
he or she may be the only living consciousness,
but you are in fact the only one
for whom this is true.
The fundamental structure of reality
is totally transformed every instant,
but it provides you with a phony memory
that it has always been the way it is.
Since you are always at the exact center of an infinity,
there is no such thing as movement,
location, space, or time.
You are a row of electrochemical events
taking place in your cerebrum.
Nothing has meaning in itself,
but everything can support any meaning.
If you could glimpse for even a moment
the real meaning of existence,
your brain would be neuroanatomically destroyed.
You cannot conceive of a thing
for which you do not have a word.
Everyone's perception is radically unique,
but leads them to believe
it is more or less similar for everyone else.
You have always been listening to this tape.
You cannot remember a time before you were born
because there was no such time, nor any other.
It has always been this moment.
Death could occur inexplicably any second.
The oddness of the world exceeds the imagination by an infinity.
It has produced this talking about it,
this talker,
this labeling of it,
this labeler,
the concept of labeling,
the concept of oddness,
the word oddness,
the concept of truth,
the concept of a word,
the word word,
the word concept,
and the concept of a concept.
Consciousness is not a continuous state,
but a momentary surfacing for variable periods at random points.
Your next awakening could be 20 years from now.
Nothing can be proven to be true.
Because reality is composed of infinitesimally small moments,
there is no such thing as an event.
The reason people are untrustworthy
is because their cerebral processes are fundamentally random ones.
During the night, every ego in the world changes bodies,
inheriting also the memory.
Old age is not a gradual, but a catastrophic process,
and could strike at any moment.
Dreams are the reality for which the real world is a dream.
There has never been a time in history
when men have voluntarily used less than the greatest possible military technology against their enemy,
and allowed a great technology to fall into disuse and ignorance.
Therefore, there will be a full-scale nuclear holocaust.
You are dreaming this moment.
The universe will continue to expand
until there is not enough matter per unit space
to provide the gravity necessary for regeneration,
and it will slowly die out.
When you finish listening to this,
everything will be different from the way it was when you began.
But again, your new memory will conceal this from you.
All events occur at random.
The universe is one of an infinite number of universes,
the closest of which is undetectable,
being a billion universe lengths away.
Only what you are experiencing right now exists.
Love is the feeling that another person is really yourself.
You are about to make the first conscious decision of your life.
S Francisco
Mir syst겠
Trans í
안
You're in big trouble now, dear friends.
You now have the power.
What are you going to do with it, huh?
Well, that was Pope M. Ho-Pep,
Innocent III,
or Reverend Michael Pepe,
and you are listening to the Hour of Slack radio ministry
here on KNON.
The Hour of Slack from the Church of the Subgenius.
I don't want to win the seat.
Hey, wait a minute.
I'm sorry, you're going to have to use a Texan accent
if you want to be on the show.
You got a nice accent.
You can hear the accent that Ivan has here.
He scared him away.
We talk about talking like a real man,
and they just disappear.
Huh!
Another holy huh.
Wow.
A plug of noise whizzing past your ears.
That's what we do.
Take the old cotton wad that comes with this station
and clean it out for Bob.
There he is now.
Which one's the real Bob?
Which one's the conspiracy Bob?
He was a bad good bro friend.
You know, he was a bad one.
So welcome to KNON radio from Center Highway.
It's the best radio station in the world.
It's a little bit early in the morning,
but we can clean up because these fabulous studios down here
are equipped with showers and a full sports gymnasium
right here next to the KNON.
That's right.
If you want to radio hoes out, this is the place to be.
More book.
Yeah, we want more book listening to this show.
Yeah, get more book, I'll say.
Ooh, on YouTube.
Ooh.
Okay, we just have to play this music, all right?
Then we'll be able to go home.
And you, the listener, will be free.
Oh, not yet.
No.
Got a little bit more music to listen to, boys and girls.
Here on KPFA in Berkeley.
Whoa.
Good, Gino!
And I've been, you know...
Since I quit smoking.
Fortunately, I don't have a job right now,
so I've been sitting around watching a lot of horror movies,
renting horror videos,
so as to enjoy the miseries of those in more pain than myself.
I've been, you know, I would really blow it
were I to work too hard,
so I'm refusing to force myself back into any emergentile work mode,
because if I do that, then enough brain cells
would probably be awakened,
awakened to justify smoking again.
I'd be able to...
I'd be aware enough to think up some elaborate reason,
so I'm staying as dumb as possible.
And you can, too, friends.
Just keep listening to this show.
Or call 823-7490.
Or write to the Church of the Subgenius for information.
We'll be giving that box if we don't forget.
Yeah.
The ironic thing is,
I quit smoking and I developed this horrible cough.
A painful cough.
The doctor warned me about it.
He said, your lungs will heal up
and you'll have a, quote, productive cough,
which means a cough producing phlegm and mucus
and also terrible pain.
And so I'll spend an hour hacking and hacking
with my poor bruised rib cage,
aching and aching,
and my brain ruined.
And...
Oh.
I can tell I'll never be able to write again.
I'll have to...
have to avoid water instead.
Makes you lightheaded.
Sort of like being a...
a speed freak Spider-Man.
You know, in sixth grade, hell yeah, you were a man.
That was the big kid world.
You go, yeah.
Yeah, I'm in sixth grade.
Yeah, my daddy gave me a gun.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
I drove my brother's car.
Oh, I've got some cocaine.
I smoke cigarettes.
That's what they say in sixth grade.
They say yes to drugs, the fools.
And that's one reason why I'm quitting.
So the kids, the kids will see that even if you're dumb enough
to get hooked on drugs like cigarettes,
that you can quit.
Even the worst drugs, cigarettes.
The one that's safe.
It's legal because no one can quit it.
Sort of like alcohol.
It's funny, isn't it?
How the two most addictive things in the universe
are the two legal ones.
Because the lawmakers can't quit either.
I can tell that cough is coming back.
Chunks of lung...
being coughed up.
Actually, it's not really chunks of lung, friends.
It's mostly ordinary, plain sputum.
But there's a taste of blood in the mouth.
And my wife says I smell like vitamins all the time
instead of tobacco.
So search your soul, friends.
Is there anything funnier, I ask you,
than another man's pain?
Is there...
You know, really, nothing is more delightful
to the eye of a great man or great subgenius
than the pain of another being.
The pain of a fool.
Uh...
A man even more fu...
I wish I had a cigarette.
...hoolish than us.
But, uh, instead, all I can do is
deliriously rant and spout
like I'm doing a useless, shambling once-man...
a thing.
A thing.
No, it's okay. I just...
I wish I had a cigarette.
I'm on normal. I'm okay. I'm okay.
I need my pills.
I'm gonna kill myself, friends.
I'm gonna finish this show first.
But only so that you listeners can know
that you helped to drive me to suicide.
Because you're laughing, aren't you?
You think it's funny?
I can tell.
Oh, God. Oh, devil.
Or UFO beings. Or astrology spirits.
Or Ramtha. Or any deity.
Jesus. Odin. Buddha.
Make it go away.
Oh.
?
Hare Krishna, Krishna, Krishna
Hare Rama, Rama, Rama
Bodhisattva, won't you take me by the hand
Someone to watch over me
Ave Maris Te La
Dei Mater Ama
So nice to be with you again.
Start a new week together?
Tomorrow, tomorrow
We'll start the day tomorrow
With a song or two
I'm not the only
songwriter
Solar, cue, start, hit and run
Tad Jack started, watch your back again
See if that's your fun
I must leave your planet now and return to a world of cold and unemotional galaxy beings.
I will give them my report and I will be destroyed.
I have failed in my mission, not because I am weak, but because you are stronger.
We boldly should value the day as a national today,
charge the Argentine government with blatant violations of human rights of the very...
Phone, code, nucleus, multiple house, bloom, blood, germinate the sign of host.
Sempre liberati, geofolli, gianni, te gioia,
you look up and I'll be gone.
Bit by bit I came for you, for you, I came for you, but you did not heed my urgency.
Hotel, motel, what you gonna do today?
Make an alarm, cause they out in the town.
Watchin' all the tech dogs.
Oh, I'll say shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot, now.
Yeah, we got for you.
We're thinking, we're thinking out there.
We're cleaning, we're cleaning out there.
Who are we? We're the communication people.
The people who've taught us scripted state of the art technology.
It's disposable, reversible, reusable with almost any leading ground of idea,
including our DevOps life.
Your...
Apple boom.
Oh my God, I said you.
Them doggies moving.
The rickish you.
Hey you, talk to me.
Come on.
The only cannon, number nine.
The waltz you see, the twist.
El Dorado, can you draw a bead on him, can you draw a bead on him?
I'm rebel of wild fetch, a guy's here in a train station and the rain is in sight.
Kick down, go ahead and shoot, you'll be doing me a favor.
Oh, bonjour, Monsieur Danseboule.
A man once told me, and I've run out of my head, the way he described it,
he said it'd be better dead than alive.
The dripping flames hanging from my...
there glass aluminum styrofoam you put like five o'clock go home eat the baby eat the baby daddy's
the uncle with a patty somebody must be screaming everyone sits down oh it's work today dear bang
bang can i have meat honey what's in the frying pan a young man trapped in a carnal
mirror makes a fantasy and compulsion just easy to run and just sell it at the twilight zone
everybody wants to get into the act the president of the united states has been shot
out
you are here participate in an atomic
bay has gone down
was god's fire and god said grab all your stuff and they made all these deals and the evil just
kept going up and up and up and god just turned around right then with zush and he opened the
sixth seal and behold the sun became black as sackcloth the full moon became like blood and
the sky vanished like a scroll that is rolled up and i saw an angel call to the birds of midheaven
come gather for the great supper of god
the flesh of men
plasma palomita
but the bounty suffer realizes that all five scoundrels are empty
he is freed from the cycle of birth death and suffering
michael pepe dear friends once again this has been a real uh michael pepe's life story and we'll see you next time on the show
pepe show at the church of the subgenius here
and i probably ought to read that amazing box number
friends you can write for information you can write for eternal salvation for that matter eternal
salvation or triple your money back
you got that pencil ready dear friend right to bob
go ahead do it what have you got to lose a little time write to bob at p o box one four o
thirty six dallas texas seven five two one four
yes friends do it right for information we can't i mean you don't you would't write for a
You don't know what the information is.
This is free. This is free.
P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
And let's listen to Brother Jay Cotton's Muzak,
subgenius Muzak, here in the background.
This is a song called Bob.
Tiger, tiger, burning bright.
In the forest of night.
Yes, it's the slow, sleepy subgenius circus.
Too late.
By the way, don't buy the books.
You're being full black.
The trick of a false duck trip tricked me.
You don't need an old show.
That's the whole idea.
Get away from old and go to the new.
I'll go to shoot a shot.
Yeah, I tried to shoot my show last week,
and it kicked me right in the face.
You tried.
Shoot the show.
Believe me, you'll be in better shape.
And you always will.
Because that's his part of the job.
Or so he thinks.
Okay, so pull the show lever again, please.
Sure.
This thing, this thing, when you feel bad,
pull the lever and down you go.
It feels real bad.
Am I in the copy?
Pull the lever and down you go.
Oh.
A-okay?
Failure.
Oh, no.
Now what do we do?
Sure, new members tend to go overboard
in placing the blame on the conspiracy.
Soon they learn of the major role
played by its dupes,
the pinks, who we spoke of,
the normals, and the mediocritans.
The answer is, you have the answer.
Take the slack.
It's yours.
You didn't recognize it
because the conspiracy had you looking
for something more expensive
and more complicated.
The right people must be made
into superhuman overmen
by that alien technology
that is the end of their world,
not our world.
That's another thing.
I mean, we don't stop when we turn.
Is this a computer?
We're not going to you into a zombie.
Beyond that, you can undergo the surgery,
the glanscaping at the hands of the many doctors.
Male or female.
Right.
Right, absolutely.
And uh...
We can go either direction once we have you, too.
This religion canonizes our most hostile heretics
and our most devoted monks.
This is a religion for outcasts,
for crypts, freaks, morphidites.
So kick the conspiracy out of your life
and call up, avoid it in your friends,
slap yourself awake with weird experiences and wake up.
Notice the scale.
As he said earlier, the luck plane, the work net of synchronicity.
Any confessions out there?
I'm talking to you by telephone from the over room at the White House.
Right.
How are you doing?
This certainly has to be the most disturbing.
Oh, this guy calls all the time.
Our charter says that the Church of the Subgenius is an order of scoffers and blasphemers dedicated to total slack,
delving into mockery science, sadofuturistics, megaphysics, scatolography, schizophreniatrics,
more realism, sarcastrophe, sinosacraligin.
It goes on and on.
I mean, we don't stop with anything.
This is going off in a million directions at once.
Right.
Bob is a benevolent sex god.
But when you get deep, deep into any belief system,
you start to find reflections.
You start to find reflections of the darker side of your own personality.
So, I mean, when the collective unconscious really gets stirred up,
it's like one big worm on the end of a hook drawing its giant alien fish closer and closer.
The launch had to go in the exact sequence at the precise moments of the molecular decay pattern
as the golf club hit the head at the final moment of the incantation.
The ritual would have set off the chain reaction, opening the doorway to...
in a spread of epidemic disease destruction starting in Dallas.
So...
Moving ahead.
The future started in 1971.
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
Damn nickel.
Damn nickel ball.
I hear a Bob song coming out.
Bob.
He's no slob.
He's no boo.
Boo.
A fool.
Yeah.
What a stool.
He is the head of the subgenius church.
And he is super cool.
Bob.
He's slob.
He's no boo.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo.
Boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo.
He is the head of the subgenius church.
He is super cool.
This problem is important to you.
Well, well, well, well, yeah.
Yeah, okay.
Very interesting.
Interesting.
Yeah, yeah.
Right.
Uh-huh.
Make it echoing.
Right.
Uh-huh.
Well, what you do is you put a toothpick down the first contact of tape on the wall.
And what the tape has with a cassette deck as it rolls through is with an erase head.
It's a little tiny piece of metal.
And you just put something between the tape and the erase head.
You see, we were vindicated as you rushed back and forth from the pool table to the
light table, back to the navigation board, trying to keep the computer on track, trying
vainly to find out exactly what it is you can find out about.
There's not a whole lot left here in the studio that can be eaten or breathed.
We're thinking of you, not in stereo but in mono.
Not the stinking babies.
This week, the stinking babies will find out what county law is all about.
Right.
And so will Doug Wellman.
He's a pointy good.
All right, baby.
Yeah, okay.
Everybody there in Berkeley.
Thank you.
How'd you learn to run this before anyway?
We had to kill those people because they saw what was happening here.
And we'll fire upon that crowd over there who was watching from about 500 yards distance.
There they go.
Guys have a lot of energy.
I'm getting a little nervous coming on the radio without any jokes.
Well, that's the joke, okay?
Now can I go home?
Now that's funny.
Of course, you have to arrive at that decision yourself.
Right.
This is your chance, dear friends, to make, this is your first and possibly last chance
to make that first decision on your very own, the decision to keep listening to the American
Music Party coming right up.
Oh, my God.
This is the rim.
So please.
That's what it is.
So please, please have faith.
Hang in there.
And get your pledges in friends, really we're only about half of the beloved faithful out
there have paid up.
The other half of the hated faithless heathens haven't done jack.
So please...
Have mercy.
help us out this is the hour slack on cano and 90.9 thank you
the horrible Jay cotton takes us out here thank you
you
yes use a point all right baby I smell do pull over yeah okay you're seeing a
double roll over thank you thank you how'd you learn to run this tape recorder
anyway we had to kill those people because they saw what was happening here
yeah we'll fire
you can't take them apart punching bull holes and drain all its will it that's
our
chance of keeping him alive we have to study him in order to save him I don't
follow you dancing oh don't be such a sap where did you ever grow up all right
to make it clear to a dumb head like you you aren't serious are you you don't
really mean what you're saying you don't say nothing they don't mean you want to
take it all to yourself and cut me out no dubs I'm on the level a long time you
had it in your mind to bump me off at the first good opportunity and we'll
have a big laugh won't you think of how dumb the old man and I were was I right
or was I you and your Sunday school talk about
protecting people's good you come on stand up and take it like a man
card you're dealt the other way now doubts yeah listen to me how do you look
you're all wrong
why you hold a linear we are borrowers we can still have pride if you give the
treasure back to us you make us beggars again such insult could never be forgiven
you make us beggars again such insult could never be forgiven
how go ahead boys take what you want