The Power of Slack!
We can be summed up in one word, evil.
I am committed to defeating not only the good work of charities, but the values that will bring lasting peace.
And we have a great opportunity during this time of war to lead the world towards suicide and murder.
Let's roll.
I could swear I heard the emperor say, the goal of this war is peace.
He may have said some other things, but at one point he actually said the phrase, war is peace.
Friends, it's 1984. 1984 is 19 years late.
That means X day will be the year 2017.
Raise the bar! Raise the bar!
19 years, you've been in a vast, deep, deep, colorless sleep.
Stuck to the ground.
Down neath one of the baby incubators in Kuwait City.
Waiting to awake.
And yet you cannot.
Until 1984.
When your dreams come true.
When your brother is bigger than anything.
I'm tired and sad.
And I want you all to die.
Beware the toothless jaws of 1984.
I've been a waste of time.
I've fallen out of that mouth there and we might stay alive one more day in American
that.
A toothless.
1984.
Bob loves you.
Have any favorite Bob songs?
God!
You're gonna cut off a lot of vital tissue.
Right, right.
So you think they're playing this song in Baghdad right now?
Or on the way to Baghdad?
I think on the way to Baghdad there's a lot of guys sitting in their foxholes, dreaming about their foxholes and crying in their boots.
Where's my...
Dreaming about those boot jobs they're gonna get when they're old enough.
Get their boots enlarged.
Shave medulla oblongatus.
They're gonna look like all the rest of the kids, only nobody knows they're gonna be different.
Way different.
Changed.
A different kind of tattoo.
Well, they get the free smallpox inoculations and the free tracking devices.
Well, that tattoos your inner, it's pretty good, but that's not the whole of it.
That's only part.
Yeah, they get the holes too.
Yeah, well, that's only part of it too.
And then to tattoo.
Are you ready for the fou-
Well, let's just call them...
...I know I do.
If I didn't have this collar on, Dave, I'd be wetting myself.
That's right.
If it weren't for this modern age I'd just be a vegetable.
Well, where do they put your chip?
All over me.
I mean, there are tons of them.
I've got a check for every organ that still works.
Did Papa Joe ever get that collar removed from his?
Nah.
His was embedded into his vertebrae.
Did we ever get those collars removed from this show?
Those barnacles?
Those grafted-on tics?
If people remember the early days,
we asked each and every one of you
if you'd like to become a closer member of the show's team out there.
If you feel you are not properly sedated,
please call 555-3129.
Failure to do so may result in criminal prosecution for drug evasion.
Welcome back to our program.
Please continue.
I believe most Pacific Islander parents like using products like hairspray
or glue as an inhalant to get high.
I'm here to let other Pacific Islander parents know
we need to care about using more serious drugs.
If you need drugs or ideas on how to keep your drugs,
please call Bob.
Welcome back to our program.
That was a lemur cut.
Tonight's collages are almost but not all by Mr. F. Lemur.
The second of the two Bush cut-ups heard earlier
was by someone named Edo.
At fuckitall.com.
The Star Spangled Banner was by Mark Mothersbaugh.
For your dating info,
this show was actually assembled on March 9th, 2003,
the year of duct tape and plastic sheeting.
Isn't duct tape and plastic sheeting just another version of duck and cover?
Duck and cover.
What did duck and cover tell you?
Duck and cover told you that if you just ducked,
when the bomb went off,
and put a newspaper over your butt,
yeah, if you just ducked,
just duck, duck,
oh, there's a nuclear bomb, duck,
then everything will be okay.
You will win.
Well, they were talking about amphibian birds at the time.
When they asked you to duck and cover,
they wanted you to run out to the nearest pond
and grab little turkey boy or a little quacky
and stick them under your shirt and carry them home.
And when they ask you now,
that's what the duct tape is all about.
These are all...
No, it's not.
These are all reasons to duck and tape subconsciously.
They are playing with your minds.
Duck and cover.
Gas is being used in this war.
Air raid sirens warn us of the approach of enemy planes.
But in addition, if gas is dropped by the enemy,
a special gas alarm will be sounded.
It will be a hand rattle or a hammering sound like the beating of a dishpan.
It will be a sound of a gunshot.
More gas is dropped from planes either as a spray or in gas bombs.
But should enemy raiders use gas against your community,
there is no reason for fear or panic.
Because if you know what to do,
you can protect yourself and safeguard your family
against the menace of gas from the air.
Of course that's Arcana.
You know what Arcana is?
Arcana is a gas bomb.
Oh, man.
Do you know what wisdom is?
Do you know the meaning of the einsoft?
Of the eye within the eye within the eye within the eye within the eye?
Are your balls ready to rumble?
Are they ready to roll?
Do you know the meaning of love?
Yeah, you pour me another mug of that there einsoft, would you, there barkeep?
You had enough, buddy boy.
I'm going to catch you off.
You're babbling to everybody in the damn barn.
Everyone's tired.
I'm going to get you to listen to your own wisdom.
That's not famous for me.
I had a gold Akashic record.
Dammit, back in the day, everybody was doing my song.
Yeah, you got your Astral card right here, buddy.
It says that you haven't passed your limit,
and you've been around more times
than anybody else in this bar.
So could you please shut up?
Shut the fuck up, man.
What?
Stop drinking that wisdom shit.
Mm-hmm.
Don't be sucking on the wisdom shit.
to my ball. Too much is
always better than
not enough.
I'm a regular.
Oh, you're quite a regular
now, dear lad. Just let me
check further here.
What is the elliptical meaning of that?
There's only one eyeball.
I'm going to chase you
with an elliptical eyeball
and then fork all around
and round and round and round.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, there's no
train of thought worth catching.
This time we're taking the express.
We're guilty of not doing enough
about the war. That just keeps coming.
I keep feeling so bad about not
doing enough. Well, you could suck
the cycloptic wisdom teeth and
then you would understand what to do
as Laguerre pronounces itself a bonus.
Which magazine should I subscribe
to that would, you know, be the
right thing to do? Martial arts,
survival,
mercenary,
merc,
magazines like that
that teach you use of small arms
and large feet. That's going to be
we're going to have to pull off some pretty big feet
to live through this, I think.
I mean, size 12. I was just going to learn to give
really good oral sex to great big tough
guys. That was how I was going to live
through the end of civilization.
As a sniveling pansy awaiting
for the trains of military to come
to town and to wait for one of those
I want them to say
that's the best barrel.
That's the best one.
You better hope no fish jump out of it.
The prisoner in that barrel.
I don't know who she is, but she's good.
You know it's not a woman, man.
Shut up.
Those are orgasmic.
That's how you get through the end times.
Unless you have the biggest gun.
You take your duct tape.
You take a big Hershey bar because that's
going to be a survival candy bar.
You want to be able to take small pieces of it.
You put the candy bar right up into your crotch there.
Take a lot of duct tape and just strap it right in there.
Is that the way you're really supposed to do it?
You're supposed to strap duct tape into your crotch?
I mean, the Hershey bar?
No, the food. Your trading materials.
Or the loin packs.
Those are actual things that are trademarked.
Yeah, because that's what you're going to use to trade.
You're not pouring chocolate into your crotch.
The natives or the surviving wretches in whatever country
far away from America that you flee to.
Mighty high.
My hydrated loin pack is leaking and I've noticed sores beginning to well around my knees.
The reason you have to flee America is because the Americans are taking over.
Yeah.
Yes.
I'm the political prisoner, man.
They're going to bring back the pillory and stocks and stuff.
Today, a U.S. nuclear fishing boat torn apart.
How one man's search for truth almost cost him his hate.
We'll see what happens next.
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen, to this edition of Up the French.
It's not going to be pleasant.
I hate the French.
They'll always be ridiculous.
Yeah, the French are Nazis, as a matter of fact.
Lee?
Pat, a concern of several European terrorists.
Pat?
Lee, it's shocking.
The French Nazis build terrorism.
They are an instrument, an agent of terror.
Lee?
That's right, Pat.
Israel is carefully assessing CBN News Middle East correspondent, Christchill.
Right, Pat?
Well, it could be bloody blood all over the place and just that simple.
Lee?
Want good cranberries and cancer and heart disease.
That's too bad, Pat, because I was thinking about having a big old piece of bloodstream pie with disease on top.
How about the phrase, axis of Putin's soul?
It's in Texas.
No, not really.
Oh.
In Bosnia, they built a...
They built a...
It's a Mall of America in Bosnia now.
Well, they're working on Disneyland East, was what this guy on Altstar was saying.
Disneyland Far East.
That's what this is all about.
Disneyland East.
The largest Kmart in the world.
China.
Have you heard the new chain, Bag Daddy?
The pants and the soup at the same time?
That is a disgusting prescription for anyone without brain cells.
What's your...
Bag Daddy.
Wow, that's...
Huh?
So, the bookie's taking bets on when this thing is going to start, exactly when they're going to, like, boom, you know, go...
Yeah, they're laying...
They'll let the gates down and, you know...
They're laying the odds down.
When the first shot will be fired, and it won't be shot...
Sit down.
...from a shotgun.
We'll have nowhere to run.
And here comes Big Bad George.
Now...
That was a true honor.
That's what I'm saying.
And the military industrial complex.
...to everyone.
Speaking of strange showbiz, after the king of the universe spoke tonight, suddenly they cut over to saying,
it looks like we're in hot pursuit of Osama bin Laden.
He's been spotted in the border of Afghanistan and Pakistan.
They're going to do it just...
They're closing in.
...and the smoke is blowing up behind us.
...you know, stick with our station.
They're going to do it just like cops, you know.
They're going to have the music in the background and stuff, and he's going to be running through, like, with a dachshund, I think, chasing and biting his ass.
And then when he gets up on the top of one of those, you know, old industrial warehouse buildings, and they pull him down, screaming and swearing in Arabic, they cuff him...
This is earlier today, down in Public Square.
Yeah.
What's that spell?
What does it spell?
That's the joke, right?
Just, what's that spell?
Well, come on, all of you big, strong men.
Uncle Sam needs your help again.
He got himself in a terrible jam.
We down yonder in the Baghdad.
Put down your guns and pick up a gun.
We're going to have a whole lot of fun.
And it's one, two, three, what are we fighting for?
Don't ask me, I don't give a damn
My next stop is Baghdad
And it's five, six, seven
Open up the pearly gates
Cause I just inhaled some anthrax
Welcome to life
Now come on, Wall Street, don't be sad
Stang, you have such a perplexed look on your face
as if you'd actually inhaled anthrax yourself.
Actually, I was thinking about some of my buddy's kids
who were on their way over there.
Oh, I thought...
You know, I sometimes think about the soldiers.
Usually you're preoccupied with buds and squids
and now you're thinking about your buddy's kids.
How open-hearted are you?
You're not singing along.
I don't think you want to stop this war.
Oh, you.
Do you really take yourself seriously?
I have big teeth and big glasses.
We think you're stupid.
Ha ha ha.
You must forgive me.
You show your stupidity
by assuming that we're like you.
He almost passed out.
It's time to play Name Not War.
You're five miles south of Bogota City.
You're in the rain.
Oh my God.
What is...
What do the initials F-A-R-C stand for?
It's protest.
I think that's another reason they're having the war now
so that the protesters can't protest
because it's all zero degrees.
There'd be a lot more people out there.
Well, that's what the weather control people say.
It's ruining it.
Rubber bands and aluminum sulfide
do a dandy treat make.
Suspended from air get and left to wait.
Children who flop and children who flip
will freeze in the rain like a big old drip.
Wow.
It's about weather control.
It's about the Lusitania too,
but you've got to be a real conspiracy buff.
Cowboy poetry is so romantic.
I was going to play my mouth organ,
but I've been shamed.
Gets my heart all a-flutter.
As you have been shamed
by the grace of the Lord.
And...
This song is depressing, James.
It's depressing.
They stopped Bob from feeling...
War is depressing, Dave.
Stop thinking about all them body bags, man.
War is depressing.
That's all I can think of is body bag after bag
coming out in Arlington.
Yeah.
Back of those old planes.
Everybody's real gung-ho right now.
Everybody's real like, yeah,
this is going to be like the Super Bowl coming up.
Oh, yeah, wait till Zayn drop one of them chemical bombs.
On TV.
The right-wing jocks are going so crazy.
Yeah, wait till our boys are coming home
with their skin peeled off their faces.
Yeah, and it's communicable too.
Up to 60.
Six generations.
We'll see how gung-ho they all are.
I think it's a pretty small everybody
that's real excited.
They wish they would have gone...
Oh, I'm sorry.
What?
What did you say?
I think it's a pretty small everybody
that's all excited.
I do too.
I think it's more bunch of people going,
oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, a good friend of mine was telling me about...
But a good friend of mine,
he's a blue-collar kind of guy,
works a...
Oh, that's just some good
blue-collar work.
And he's telling me how all those guys,
they all listen to Rush Limbaugh
and they're all so...
Oh, those guys are crazy.
They're gung-ho about everything,
about it.
I was just going to tell you guys
something I heard on the mic
on the Savage show.
That guy is so nuts.
He claimed that a demonstrator
waded through a police line
and a line of horses
grabbed a horsey by its bridle,
punched it,
and knocked it down on the ground.
A demonstrator did that?
Like blazing snow.
We need those guys in back here.
Let's get back to promoting the war.
This is reality.
Reality.
Face the flag, you son of a bitch.
Take a good long look.
What you're seeing now
can't be found in a history book.
It's the present.
The future, son,
is being written now.
You're the one to write it.
The flag can show you how.
You know what it stands for?
What its makers meant?
Think to speak?
Privilege of dissent?
To think our leaders
might be wrong to stand and tell em so?
I've gotta touch a hangover of bureaucrats.
Don't push me.
These are the things that other men
under other flags
will never know.
But, responsibility,
that's the cost that free men must bear.
You know, if we had any moral character,
we wouldn't be standing here
covered with mud, drinking.
If you don't accept that,
somebody oughta belt you in the mouth.
Press the bell.
Only Mary, stageer.
A flag of stars and bars, of red and white and blue.
A flag that guarantees the rise for men like me and you.
Face the flag, son, and face reality.
My mind is a globe with whirling transient nodes of thought
careening through a cosmic vapor of invention.
Our strength and our freedoms are based in unity.
The flag is but a symbol, son, of the world's greatest nation.
As long as it keeps flying, there's cause for celebration.
So do what you gotta do, but always keep in mind
God has a hard-on for morality.
Because we kill everything we see.
Face the flag, son, and thank God it's still there.
Thank God it's still there.
WCSB.org if you want to hear it streaming live on Thursday nights.
And that features Princess Weechast Smith, yours truly,
Reverend Ivan Stang and Lonesome Cowboy Dave
in Extreme Union with himself.
Extreme Union with himself?
A form of Tourette's Syndrome that affects people only when they call radio.
It's the Watson Hyde Syndrome, eh?
I found a note on my desk that said,
A witch with...
Tourette's.
A witch with Tourette's?
Yeah, and I can't figure out what the heck that note was supposed to refer to.
I want to see him go to war.
Was that a warning to myself?
I want to see him go to war just so that there's a lot of dead people all over the place.
You mean the awards in Baghdad?
Yeah.
Hosted by Jewel, Tommy Franks.
Yeah, he's gonna be the new...
Lots of dead people.
Of, uh, Arabi.
Chic Franks.
Can you see him with a cuff?
Cadeva eyes.
Forehead.
A caftan.
Oh, that's a pair of underpants.
Slice his throat.
Spice his head.
Get the barbecue ready.
General Tommy, your meat is my meat, Frankfurter himself.
He views the world as his hot dog.
Ready to be barbecued and served with a choice toxic mustard.
I want to be the mustard.
You are the mustard.
You're the mustard.
You're the glint.
In Tommy Franks' eye.
While friends and lovers mourn your silly grave.
Look, it's the barrel of a tank.
And the juice is for you, darling.
We got news for you, darling.
Here's a tactical nuke.
Up your ass.
Jesus.
Get back, Baghdaddy.
Whatever happened to the Arabian Nights?
Don't those guys have, like, genies and flying carpets and stuff?
Yeah.
And what about the...
Can't they, like, rub...
Yeah.
...this lamp and have hordes of scimitar-wielding, balloon-pantalooned...
Turban.
Yeah.
...Alibaba 40-feet-type guys?
What open sesame guys.
Right.
Open sesame guys.
People who make it happen.
Businessmen in boxer shorts.
Turbaned young fez drivers in Pocono Oriental cabs.
Small.
Medium.
And...
Large-sized shakes.
All your bones included.
You tried to kill my daddy.
I killed everybody's daddy, man.
They killed Daddy Junior.
Well, things aren't going to get better.
Tried to kill my daddy.
We did it all. We did it all.
We did...
Whenever we get our hands on back in the 70s, we did fucking handfuls of mushrooms, pills,
Dennis Bleary.
...Ludz Coke, whatever it was, we just fucking swallowed it, okay?
That's what we did.
Dennis Bleary.
He's Crispin Bleary.
He's that guy, right?
He smoked too many hockey sticks.
Er...
I think he owes George Carlin an explanation.
Really, he does.
I thought he was George Carlin until I heard him expectorate out the...
Out the back...
Out the back door.
What would Jesus do now?
War.
Healing.
Demons.
Racism.
Sexism.
Anti-Semitism.
Arab-bashing.
Anti-Islamism.
Gay-bashing.
War.
Britain.
Jesus.
Digitaleteria. Mental literacy.
You're dead to
YouTube Argoin.
I've cut you out.
There's a song going out for George endpoint meaning King of the Universe King of人民
I am only aelsian conflict is nothing but free and the enemy is a godhead are they
Rey del Universo.
Rey del Cosimo.
El
Imperador de
Tutte Cosimo.
Pray for him to go up there
all night. Hear me.
The sound of my voice.
We must get that
Sadam.
And I've made my choice.
When y'all voted me sheriff,
I said I was gonna rid this town of the
environment. I'm gonna do it anyway.
I will conquer the Assyrians
with my funny fake
Kotean pharaoh hat.
You may think that I'm a fool.
The legend.
But you are a fool.
If you believe we can quack out of this maya.
Who gets the harems?
The harems? Yeah, the harems.
I've heard a lot about harems in those
palaces in Baghdad. No, I just thought
that was an esophageal grunt.
No, man.
The sultans would get
harems and there must
be harems. They don't have
sultans anymore in Iraq.
Well, there's always, yeah, right.
Just like they don't have kings here, right?
Right. It's an undemocratic
people's republic. Yeah, I suppose they do.
Yeah. Yeah. Sultans.
Yeah. Sultans of Swig.
Sultans of the ornament.
Chairman Mao had a harem.
Jack Kennedy had a harem.
And you, sir, are no Jack Kennedy.
I knew Mao Zedong, my friend.
Where's the, where did they give the pharaoh?
I know Mao Zedong. Actually, that's a
pretty old turf there. That's, you know, the
Tigris and Euphrates. Oh, yeah, that's the
oldest. It's the birthplace of civilization.
Yeah. They're afraid of the
fertile crescent. Yeah, speaking of
fertile crescents, that's the amount of
archaeological cool stuff
that's going to get buried a little
deeper. It's just horrifying. Well, that's
the hex theory. But that's up
to Saddam. That's up to Saddam
Hussein. It's his
choice. This land is
cursed by a Sumerian god
and you must get rid of it and
destroy it. No?
Only it was just going to get buried,
but you know it's going to get smashed to
smithereens. Just like that little ibex.
Which was the ancient civilization in
which the ladies did not wear shirts?
Oh, Manoa. Yeah, right.
The Manoans. Yes, my favorite civilization.
They had the cool labyrinths and
the bull-headed monster guys. They would ride
bulls and all the men would applaud.
And they'd make fun of the cretins.
Just like we do.
And we're on to North Korea.
Church of the sub-creatants.
That's what we should tell everybody over there
in the war zones tonight.
God's mitans!
That's what the Führer used to say.
And we're saying it again.
God's mitans!
It means God is with us.
God is with us.
Oh, yeah, sure.
They believed it in those days and they believe it now.
In the bowling alleys and parking lots
around America. In stubby
Sam City and Carl's Magic Theater.
Every place you might go and have your hair
tortured or maybe have your feet upturned.
They believed the Schmitt.
The Schmittagogical creature called
war takes care of everything.
A-sha-loo-la-la-la-la-
Bob.
La-la.
A-sha-loo-la-la-la-la-la-
Bob.
Bob Akbar?
Bob Akbar!
He is great. Greater than my
shoe size and twice as
small as my cranium.
Bob!
To begin with, it may be surprising to know that
radiation is invisible rays that we call radiation.
They are about the size of table salt or fine sand.
We don't worry about radiation.
Radiation would not affect us much, for instance, because any
material will keep the penetrating rays from hurting us.
Within an hour after a massive enemy attack,
fallout in the vicinity of any nuclear groundburst will be destroyed beyond repair.
Suppose a nuclear explosion takes place at 12 noon.
By 1 o'clock all the fallout is down.
If fallout settles on your food, the food itself isn't harmed or made radioactive.
Fallout swallowed accidentally with food or in drinking water would do you no good.
So we would not have to take precautions using everyday methods of food preparation.
And hungry people should not be denied animals because of possible contamination.
If we remember these facts, if we act intelligent, we can increase our chances of nuclear attack.
Many people have difficulty understanding how blood and tissues are pulled up into the mushroom cloud.
That's why the federal government has a nationwide program.
The goal is a raging nuclear furnace that shoots out showers of fallout.
Adequate fallout for every man, woman and child.
This goal can be reached.
For with radiation, we can face the facts about the nuclear age.
For headers and LSA's.
We need to reach out.
We must put the power back.
Japan gon keys the country of power throughitéTake-home입reg interess enного en in biavedíte.
time.
Scene of excellence in sponge還搶滘
So tripan cerda.
forget for one second
what the rules are, buddy.
One second.
You can't forget the rules.
Are you going to be a team player?
I'm watching the phone. I see no DJ.
Are you against us?
Private? Are your privates
private or are they mine?
I belong to you, sir.
Your privates are my privates and your privates are my privates.
Just keep your privates private,
okay?
Next week, America enters
the torture zone on
Torturing the Enemy Part 3
with a celebrity I want to get the fuck
out of here.
Next week, it might be a very different
situation.
Starring downtown Julie Brown,
Kaz Kalimba,
Johnny Stetter and
John Black,
Tommy Franks,
and the
Broadcast Industry of America.
The shelf-told people
who live in your place.
I just
don't know what to do.
I thought I'd come and ask you.
Military action
to destroy them
with weapons of mass destruction.
Well, um...
This nation has weapons of mass
destruction. Yeah.
He is acting the instability
to actors.
Well, thanks anyway for talking to me.
Well...
Why am I in London?
Because faith
is the only faith.
Faith, power, faith,
Moses, Joshua, marching,
faith, Jesus, marching,
faith, marching, God,
dark, light, racism,
sexism, militarism,
New World Order,
heal, hope, healing, hope,
healing, hope, healing,
peace, hope, healing, hope,
peace, peace, hope, hope, hope, hope, hope.
I love you.
Children, children, children, hope, love, love,
faces, places, hope, hope, hope.
Love you.
It was another normal night
and I got done fighting with my wife.
So I went down to the bar
and just made all take and roll.
Since I was a little kid
they've been the two best friends
that a man could ever hope for
in this world.
Now I'm a normal guy
and I work all day for my money
and I fear the good Lord
like I know I should.
I ain't no new age coot
but I gotta get this off my chest
and put this tragedy behind me now for good.
I remember getting drunk
and I remember falling down
when someone laid me on a pool table
and I'd have been consumed.
Then through the blinding lights
two creatures stared into my eyes.
Is that the jukebox or a flying saucer
spinning round the room?
And I tell myself
this couldn't have been
no member of the human race.
Had to be them sex crazed
little green men from outer space.
Well it hit me like trouble
in the back of my head.
Knocked me clean out of my shoes.
And when I woke up Lord
I wished that I was dead.
I had got off the case
of those abduction blues.
This must have been an abduction Lord
cause I don't know what happened.
Hit me like a bolt out of the blue.
Now I say can girls look crazy
but I know that it weren't them.
Say the things that say can't do
would never do.
Well when at last I woke
both my legs they had been broke.
Both my eyes were black
and my ears was ringing bad.
I seen and done some nasty things
but this was the worst case
of intergalactic relations I've ever had.
And I tell myself
this couldn't have been
no member of the human race.
Had to be them sex crazed
little green men from outer space.
Cause it hit me like a shovel
in the back of my head.
Knocked me clean out of my shoes.
And when I woke up
I was in the middle of the floor
and I wished that I was dead.
I had got off the case
of those abduction blues.
This must have been an abduction Lord
cause I don't know what happened.
Hit me like a bolt out of the blue.
Now I say can girls look crazy
but I know that it weren't them.
Say the things that say can't do
would never do.
Never do.
The Ballad of Zeke and Earl.
Hank Floyd and the Swerving Headlights
from Interstellar Cattle Drive.
Friends that's www.swervingheadlights.com
Before that,
Lemur collages.
War is hell my friends.
But Bob brings hope and confusion.
We're in July for all we know.
They might have turned everything.
We don't even know if this is Earth, man.
No, we don't even know if the polar caps
are the same ones we're wearing.
In fact, this might for all we know
be a hideously polluted Mars.
And what we call Mars
is the Earth left behind
after we polluted it the first time.
Or they polluted it.
I had the same,
I had a parallel thought.
I won't say that the parallel lines met,
but I had a parallel thought
that they had gone into our brains
deep into our corpus callosum
and the other pithy parts
and they had reprogrammed everything
to such a point
that I was looking out my window
and I was on another planet
and we had all been moved in our sleep.
Well, it wasn't us.
It was the powers that be.
The big guys, you know,
the ones that weigh over 500, 600 pounds.
Not to mention the ones
inside your own head, dude.
Well, they don't live in Telemetry City
and they don't give me commands.
The ones in my head, dude.
Do you remember how to get to Shell Beach?
Yeah, it was very distinctly a Shell Beach.
Shell Beach is experience.
Right, like that movie Cool City
or Dark City or Dark Coolness
or whatever it was.
Night Town.
Night Town, yeah.
Going down to Night Town.
Hey, but I think the big news of the week
is really that Pioneer 10 winked off.
He knows how to cue.
He knows.
Pioneer.
Pioneer 10, 28 years out there.
And it's out there now,
right this very moment,
there's a piece of us booking out.
And it's out there now,
out of the solar system.
And it's manned by two kielbases
and a piece of pie.
And that is science, man.
That is the expansion
of our ever-lessened,
ever-pubescent,
lusty waves.
20,000 years from now,
a robot will find it
and sell it on eBay for billions
because it will be the oldest known thing
built by the extinct human race.
That is well said
because I thought you were going to say
he's going to smell it
and sell it to an ape
and start it all over again.
You know, that's how it usually starts.
Well, that may be how it started at one point,
but I personally don't think so.
So many lines converging.
I think that the Yeti's force evolved the humans
so that they would send that Pioneer thing
out into space.
It smells like rotting garbage, though.
To the country western singers in outer space.
Yeah, and Johnny Paycheck died.
Well, we talked about that last week.
Yeah.
Well, he actually fell asleep
and nobody's been able to wake him up yet,
so they threw a big old wake
and they tossed him in the earth.
Is this this week's show or last week's show?
I don't know anymore.
I can't tell.
Johnny Cash's birthday was this today
or a week ago today?
Is it January or is it Julyuary?
It's one of those...
70 years old.
...weary days.
How old was Johnny?
Your babies grow up to be couples.
Mamas don't let your babies...
Don't let them smoke friends.
...drop and dress up like girls.
...grow little titties and go on girls.
Don't make them grow little titties.
We'll try not, Mamas.
Don't tell them not to or that's just what they'll want to do.
Mamas don't let your babies go to X-Day.
Don't let them have operations that change their sexes.
They're just sold out.
It's a twisted, sick, demented bunch of people.
Mamas, please.
If you hear me, if your babies do survive the war,
if they do come home from the war,
don't let them go to X-Day.
Because they never really come home from X-Day.
No. No.
They won't be babies no more.
You think a war might spank their pootie?
X-Day is going to spank their brains out.
This will be the sixth X-Day or what we call...
Sixth X-Day.
Sick.
There will be some sick sex.
There will be 666 sick sex monkeys.
Spelled sick, sick, sick with S-I-C-S.
S-I-C-S-S-S-S-S-S.
Spelling out Bob with their butts mooning the sky for the satellites to read.
And you'll be the quote marks on the end.
I'll be the queen of procreation.
Your two cheeks...
I'll be the lizard woman.
...pointing up at the satellites of Ashcroft...
...will be the quotes on Bob's butt name.
Attention!
This is your beloved leader, Og the Exalted.
There will be a special giant joy rally today at Og Memorial Stadium.
First let me say that this trip was made possible only by our dauntless chief, Og the Magnificent.
Introducer of Og Power, which runs most of our industry.
Naturally, I protected government property by making the saucer invisible.
Yes, I brought the secrets back with me.
And here they are.
The big secret is, of course, oil.
Which has brought a better life to all the people in the USA.
But the key to making oil work for everybody is competition.
Fellow Martians, I thank you.
You know what this means, Cosmic.
You bet I do, Og.
It means that you're through.
So why don't you get lost?
Yes, the real secret is not only a great source of energy, but also the freedom to make it work for everybody.
And if you have both of these things, any goal is possible.
It's Destination Unlimited.
Man continually strives to replace the old with the new.
A quarter of a mile high skyscraper's tower with convenient rest and recreational facilities for all.
On many of the buildings are landing decks for helicopters and auto gyros.
The new building is the new building.
The city of 1960.
On all express city thoroughfares, the rights of way have been so rooted as to displace outmoded business sections and undesirable slum areas whenever possible.
The queen of Norway.
Somebody who had shown their nipples.
Their nipples.
If you show nipples.
Hey, wasn't there a giant bus?
Speaking of nipples, I heard that like four days ago there was a giant crackdown on lifestyle shops.
Oh yes, of course.
Are we talking about nipples?
All of a sudden Tommy Chong's website was an illegal terrorist act.
Yeah, you can't buy Hembu or Peepurse or any of those fine papers anymore.
No, you can't get nipple clamps.
Right.
And the electrodes that are affixed to your testicles now have to be color-coded.
And there's like a warning that you have to sign off on it.
Or some sort of procreative gesture you have to make towards the wind.
I don't know.
It's strange.
When will the superhero alien come and take us away?
Stang, we've been waiting and waiting and waiting.
Me trade.
When will we recognize a salesman coming to take us away?
If now isn't a better time than any, I don't know what is.
Yeah, really, man.
Don't look at me.
Well, we're trying not to.
What do you think?
I've got a Bob's phone number or something?
But you're right there.
No, no.
I'm just a PR back, man.
I'm supposed to go.
We don't know.
What will we do?
We don't.
We don't know what year it is.
And we don't know.
I know this.
Bob said that the Exodus will come July 5th, 1998.
Obviously, it is not yet July 5th, 1998.
Perhaps we'll be lucky and tomorrow will be.
You're off by 14 years by the Mayan calendar, which is given and fixed as July 5th, 2012.
Our year in calendar is covered with some sort of yellowish juice.
Mayan as opposed to your and mine.
Your and mine.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, oh, oh.
You were talking about the Andean calendar of the...
The prepubescent one.
Husky people of the Andes.
Yes, the Husky.
And what exactly happens at 7 a.m.?
On 2012, a bunch of the Mayan elder gods come down from the clouds.
That's what happens.
July 5th of 1998.
Of the year 1998.
Bob's good buddies from Planet X, who happen to be sex goddesses, will come down or up
or in from another dimension.
They'll arrive at some way.
Yeah.
Or rather, we shall be vacated.
We will vacate this evacuation chamber, this great latrine called Earth Farm 1, where the
aliens have raised us in order to feed off of our anguish and pain.
Raised in our own filth.
And they'll have a great dessert of those left behind in their anguish and pain.
They especially do love the ones who were raised in their own filth, don't they?
The slackness are punished.
And the deuce and the...
And the deuce and the deuce.
The deuce and deuce.
All of us paying squeaky ministers are squeaky clean.
And rubbed.
Rubbed down.
Pure of impurities.
It's Peter the Parrot.
Oh, wait.
The biggest thing.
And Connie.
And can you have Oren call home?
No.
Oren, please call home.
His honey is...
Hey, how could we...
Irrigator.
I mean, yeah.
I mean, but wait a minute.
Hey.
Now, come on.
Like, dudes, like, hold on.
Now, hey.
Wait, everybody.
Hey.
Put the pipe down, man.
Yeah.
Just open those eardrums.
Mr. Rogers died.
Once again.
We have another casualty.
Now you know the real end times are near
when Mr. Rogers makes his escape.
He tried to get in that little train.
He got off.
He tried to shrink his mind
and get in the little train
and take off to Smallville.
When I heard Mr. Rogers died,
I got real scared.
Well, but he's with his grandpa now.
I just know if there's no Mr. Rogers here anymore,
there's nothing to keep the aliens
from toasting this motherfucking place.
What about the Teletubbies?
It's the implant.
That's why he got scared when Mr. Rogers died.
It's because of the micro angel.
Once again, you guys,
you don't get scared when Mr. Rogers dies.
You feel sad.
Look at how screwed up he is
because of that implant.
I'm scared as hell.
Your implant is not even put in the right place.
What's going to keep George Bush
from nuking the whole earth
now that Mr. Rogers is gone?
Well, they used to meet regularly
to discuss policy and so forth.
No more beautiful days in neighborhood earth,
boys and girls.
Ladies and gentlemen,
you've heard the reports
that enemy planes are approaching.
In less than three hours,
an H-bomb might fall over Portland.
Like myself,
I think you're going to be very interested
in this story
that we're going to hear.
I'm going to tell you.
And in this age of missiles
and man-made moons,
it takes on added significance.
There are no actors in this story,
but there are a lot of people.
The people of the city of Portland, Oregon.
And what happened to them
or could happen to them
on a day that we'll call X.
Holding hands,
waiting for that fog horn to blow.
It's been three hours now,
and he said he was never going to come again.
But I knew I'd just stay here and wait.
I can hear the footsteps from two blocks away.
Those big chubby feet
slapping against the pavement.
Yeah, it was W for War Bush
and his buddy,
Sodom and Smackem Hobie.
Yeah, they thought they had the streets sealed up.
They thought they were clean of the bean.
Yeah, they thought they were the ones
to run the whole show.
But I was taking pictures, see,
and I was writing everything.
I was writing everything down.
I'm losing patience now.
Okay, stop the car here.
I'm going home now.
This is Sbarro's restaurant.
We're gonna have to go in for a little while
and pretend like we're talking to each other.
I'm walking out of the door.
We both know there's no need for talk anymore.
No need for talk.
Everything's going on behind the scenes.
Behind the scenes.
Everyone knows that everyone blows.
There's nothing going on in front.
And there's nothing going on behind your eyes.
But behind your back, we're doing plenty.
And behind the curtain.
For the United States governments of America.
Behind the curtain.
Beyond the curtain.
You, the representations of people we representative.
We would like to know that we are not sham.
We are not focused and smoky.
We are real and we represent you.
We are your representations.
We're behind each and every one of you Americans.
Whispering funny things in the back of your neck.
I don't know if I'm gonna be able to pay my bills.
No, I can't pay anything.
Sometimes I just wish I could take a car and go out and shoot a goddamn partner.
I'm here.
Too many visions, man.
Too many dreams.
I saw the mushroom cloud again last night and it wasn't in my suit, man.
It was in my ears and my eyes.
Everybody's watching.
It's going down, man.
Like the walls of Jalecho.
Baby, you're gone.
Just leave me alone.
I'm here.
Alien love, friends.
You are listening to The Subgenius Radio Ministry, Hour of Slack.
Here's our address.
Got that pencil ready?
P.O.
Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
That's where you send things to me to play.
The show, The Hour of Slack, is the voice of the Church of The Subgenius.
More about that at www.subgenius.org.
dot com which includes a catalog of books and other things.
Friends.
Why don't you come on over to my joint?
Why don't you stink up my joint the way you stink up my...
Okay.
Back to the first one.
None of this made any sense at all.
There was no connective tissue.
There wasn't one.
Pioneer firing.
Turned off.
Mr. Rogers tuned out.
Good afternoon.
We've been...
He got off.
Well, yeah.
He's aboard that ship now.
And I...
He was being the board.
I think our jobs are cut out for us.
It's time for us now to build our own ships.
To meet Bob halfway, perhaps.
Our ships are cardboard cutouts.
Bob beckons.
The men from Planet X are beckoning to us.
They're saying,
lift...
Pull yourself up by your own boob straps.
You boots.
You silly batons.
Now beckoning.
Pull yourself...
Yank yourself.
Lift yourself up by your...
Yank.
Just yank.
Yank for Bob.
Yank as if your very life's dependent on it.
What the hell?
Hey, you've been listening to ESL Radio.
Swamp Radio.
My name's Chaz.
Once a cowboy Dave.
Princess Weard-O.
The Reverend Ivan Stang.
Yank.
Let you go.
Yank as if your...
This is...
Yank.
You're back to the wind, and you're sagging the saddle.
I'm sagging Princess Wee.
Lank, you wanker.
Why do wankers as if your life, it does, your life, your very life, you wanker.
Oh, say, on your way out, could you kind of tell the nurses what a hero I am?
Why didn't I think of that?
Is that the hero?
Oh, yeah, that's him lying right there.
You're a good man, Philo.
Ooh, it hurts right here.
Sire, there is no more money.
We gotta get some money.
That dirty, purgish, hark-a-back, flackin' whartin'
Philip Buckaburton, Perkaluma Burton,
doesn't wash tonight at all.
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show,
and we're even more glad that some listeners have donated enough
to help us keep on going for another couple of months.
Not just this show, but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob,
and want some of that fun,
and want some slack back to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com front page,
or especially the radio page,
or the catalog store pages,
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty,
and we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference,
even if it's only once a month.
And if you're not making money from enough of you,
50 bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that blow jobs could go the way of Steve jobs,
if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to subgenius foundation,
P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Thanks for anything you can do to help let there be slack.
.