Destiny awaits us.
Chapter 5
Ye have heard that it hath been said,
Thou shalt hate the
SOUL GENIUS
POWER OF SQUADCH
Which will live in infamy.
Last night Japanese forces attacked
The SOUL GENIUS
POWER OF SQUADCH
SOULICATION
Bob came here and did something to all of us.
fit the
the
his
that
it
is
more
tiet
me
hello
are here from the
Hello, friends, and welcome.
The theme for tonight is deconstructing rock band cliches,
and this won't be a typical episode of Hour of Slack.
The first song you'll hear, by Andrew the Impaled, is a regular type of song,
but after that we'll be hearing excerpts from other subgenius bands,
all recorded live at 18X Day, but all involving much rock band member patter
that is, if not of a completely sarcastic and satirical nature,
actually very sincerely dumb and horrible.
It's an exploration of what we call doctor music.
Not always easy on the ears, but always revealing of the sheer vanity inherent in any real rock band.
We'll hear arguments between members,
of Doctors for Wotan, that's me and Philo and our two wives,
and Six-Fisted Tales of Connie, with some actual music included.
We'll even hear Reverend Angry Larry of the Amino Acids teach the band Coming of the Giant Germs
his trick for remembering chords for rock songs by spelling out words
with the letters representing each note.
Finally, and perhaps climactically,
we'll hear some off-the-cuff improvisational parodies whipped out between songs and rants
by our MC, Priestess Pisces.
But first, live from 18X Day at Wisteria, St. Andrew the Impaled.
This next song is called Sapiosexual Way.
Now a sapiosexual is a person that gets off on intelligence,
a person whose turn on is, you know, smart people.
Smart people.
There's gonna be a lot of letters come flying at you.
They're just a DNA sequence.
You don't need to memorize them.
There will not be a test.
C, D, G, A, I got some fresh DNA.
I got it for you.
A, T, C, G, why don't you come get with me?
Got nothing better to do.
Your C, C, T, G, A, C, T, G, A, A, C would go nice
with my C, C, T, G, A, T, A, T, my advice.
Let's get down today in a sapiosexual way.
My kind of girl, she's a sapiosexual.
Yeah, I know what that means.
And that's hot, hot, at least to her,
because she digs intellectuals.
Yeah, she likes the geeks.
Well, you're new to the scene.
You might be kind of keen.
Do you know what I mean when I say I like them genes?
Oh, C, T, G, A, I got some fresh DNA.
I got it for you.
A, T, C, G, why don't you come get with me?
Got nothing better to do.
Your C, C, T, G, A, C, T, G, A, A, C would go nice
with my C, C, T, G, A, T, A, T, my advice.
Let's get down today in a sapiosexual way.
Sometimes girls take all the time to prudy up,
but they're just for today, and it's gonna fade.
So other girls, they're gonna fade.
They only wanna shake it up, get drunk and laid.
Well, that ain't for me.
The woman that I seek, she might be up till three,
but with a book of poetry and my C, T, G, A, I got some fresh DNA.
I got it for you.
Yeah, A, T, C, G, why don't you come get with me?
Got nothing better to do.
Your C, C, T, G, A, C, T, G, A, A, C would go nice
with my C, C, T, G, A, T, A, T, my advice.
Let's get down today in a sapiosexual way.
You saw that I got under your subtle reference
to a movie that not more than 10,000 people have seen
among there and there and there.
Well, I know the difference.
So how'd you like to mix it up with me?
At my C.
Let's see how you are at saying how I properly
not of high Huejeprißtighc music.
He wants you because of the mind you have.
Now can you empathize?
To be perfectly fair, you should be aware.
We'd make a nifty pair.
If you have the MC squared.
For my C, T, G, A.
I got it for you.
A, T, C, G.
What you can get with me.
Ain't nothing better to do.
Your C, T, G, A, C, T, G, A, A, C would go nice.
For my C, T, G, A, T, A, T, my advice.
Let's get down today in a sapiosexual way.
I said let's get it down today in a sapiosexual way.
Alright, thank you so much.
How you guys all doing tonight?
You having fun?
Having that duck is for WOTAN, man.
I fucking hate following talent.
Fucking.
Piss me off.
Dr. Drummond and I were the first Bobbies.
I noticed St. Faltimus had a song about the Bobbies.
It was a nice song.
Some people use Bobby as a dirty word.
You know, I guess Philo knew Bob personally before I did.
So I guess you can't say he was really a Bobby.
But I was maybe the first Bobby.
I used to say Bob slack, Bob slack all day long.
And then I was taught that it was cool to say kill Bob all day long.
I noticed other people have been taught that it's cool to say kill Stang a lot too.
But that's not cool, man.
But yeah, there's nothing wrong with being an obsequious, ass-kissing Bobby,
unoriginal, just quoting, misquoting the same old stuff and spelling Bob's name wrong.
It's a stage, you know.
And you'll probably get through it.
Or else everybody else will make fun of you so much you'll get butt hurt and quit.
It's a harsh...
Subgenius society is a harsh mistress.
And a frigid mistress for a lot of people.
Oh!
I'm behind the time.
She got so into it.
Now she needs to be mic'd better.
Or it, whatever.
She's got a mic right here.
I'm gonna get...
You're back in my queefing, no?
The best mic placement in a Wotan thing is right in the middle of the damn band.
Even if there's sound coming out of the speakers.
Because you're gonna pick up a...
Princess Wee isn't even mic'd at all.
And she refuses to come forward.
But this band is sort of a, you know...
Why are you standing there?
Why are you...
Where is Princess Wee?
Because the flute is a piercing sound and you don't need to be mic'd.
This stage's right.
Yes you do.
I can't hear you usually.
No.
Roughly.
This rough area is fine.
Okay, so we'll share this area.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a rough area.
Like a communal band, you know?
Share it, Sherry.
Are we doing a communal band thing?
The one by the podium?
Oh no, no, we mow!
Moooooooooo!
There we go.
That was another thing we had to do.
We had to do a mow.
Before you could really...
Get down.
Oh, we're doctors...
For Bob.
For Bob!
Doctors for Bob!
And everything real in my life!
Oh, we're doctors for Bob!
That damn pick-up doesn't run over my wife!
We've been working for like 10 or 20 minutes, man.
And I'm getting a little bit tired.
I need to take a little break, I think.
Well, that's the Rockstar Life, man.
It's costume change you didn't put on your doctor's suit.
And where's the blood?
Where's all the fake blood?
The knives and the chainsaws?
The smoke machine?
And the beach towels?
And the beach balls?
And the suntan lotion?
We're just gonna have a beach party!
Some genius beach party!
I'll bring the heroin if you bring the suntan lotion.
I'll bring the frappes up lip gloss.
I'll bring the neutron howitzers if you bring the big umbrella, the shade umbrella.
Big giant...
I'll bring the toxic Bob vomit for lip gloss.
I'll bring the
What else do we need?
Your woody!
Can you bring your woody?
Can we carry it here?
Your woody?
She's doing things with that that I don't think it was intended.
Or many of them.
How do you know it's a she?
Why do you keep calling that thing she?
Well, it doesn't...
Look at that!
It's not a she at all!
She's rubbing its appendage, its masculine lance.
Hey, that's my wife!
You can't do that to my...
Stop fucking his wife!
Oh, wait!
Oh, now that's better.
Give him a reach around.
Now, yes.
Keep...
Yes, fuck me!
That's a good thing.
I'll give you a reach around.
Don't fuck you.
Don't fuck my wife.
Fuck me!
You know, that's not...
You really tell a good friend like that.
They'll give you that reach around and finish it off.
Why do they use fuck as a bad word?
Like, I'm a fucker!
It sounds good.
It's more like a sweet word.
Fuck you.
I don't know.
I don't know how to...
Oh, here's a song called Cooking.
Remember Cooking?
That was one where...
We were actually cooking.
It was really good.
We were going fast.
We had a song that had a beat that was going fast.
Yeah, yeah.
It had a melody and some harmony, you know?
Right, right.
And then suddenly that new guy, that kid, he goes, stop, stop, stop!
Yeah.
And we go, why?
We were cooking.
He goes, yeah.
That's what's wrong with it.
I'd already told him that story.
He was like, I don't know.
That was a song called Cooking.
Oh, it did?
Yes.
The all-sign.
And this in particular?
That's a signed all-sign.
And in this particular X-day, or...
About 10 minutes ago, during our first song.
Yeah.
But you thought it was a tune-up.
Or a set chec.
Chec, chec.
What about Steve Kock?
I think I want to do a sound check.
Chec.
I think it's actually the first song.
How about Inna-gada-davidah?
I can't remember the lyrics, though.
I think it goes...
Inna-gada-davidah, baby Don't you know that I love it
I'm loving you.
In a God of the Vita, baby, don't you know that I'll always be true?
Okay, we just did it.
We just did it in God of the Vita.
Dance through the doctors or die.
You have to dance through the doctors or die.
I'm doing it.
Get your Moog synthesizer.
See, I've already done the lyrics.
And they can, Pat, you can mix it in later, right?
I'm going to fix it in the mix.
You'll fix it in the mix?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's the way.
Fix it in the mix.
The way we did overdubs and stuff, we did the vocals first and then dubbed the music to the vocals.
Originally, Doctors for Wotan was done with children's toy instruments.
And kids.
Kitchen utensils like spoons and coffee cans.
The original drummer was a wind-up chimpanzee with cymbals, which Philo stuck in a box so that it would have a back beat.
It would go, boom, boom, like that.
But he forgot our drummer.
Philo forgot the drummer again.
So now we have this.
We have to use drum machines or percussion instruments.
Watch, kid.
Watch.
Let me see.
She needs a mic while she tunes up.
I'm tuning up.
This is the tune up.
This is actually what you're hearing now is possibly the best song you're going to hear tonight.
In a car to defeat a baby.
Don't you know that?
There's real musicians that are going to play.
Andrew is here.
Andrew the Impaled.
He sings.
He's like Tom Lehrer.
You can understand.
You can understand the lyrics just like country music.
He's sophisticated.
He's sophisticated like a Harvard math professor.
And his music is actually pretty good.
Andrew the Impaled.
Andrew.
The Impaled.
Impaled.
Andrew.
The Impaled.
Do you know what impaling is?
When I was a kid I used to think impaling was like sticking somebody in the stomach with a stick.
Or they have a spear poking out of the ground and they just stick you on it through your stomach.
Because they don't tell little kids what impaling really is.
Which is that you send a guy, the criminal or victim or whatever, on a rather blunt sharp mistake.
Not all that super sharp.
And the person's late.
The one who's late would drive the stake up in their buttock.
Slowly up through their buttock.
Kill them, really slowly.
And Andrew the Impaled.
Now, this wasn't part of the original Doctor Squirrel Wolf man.
Andrew the Impaled.
This green thing.
The kids said, now, we're going have a wedding tomorrow.
Those young, that young couple needs to be instructed in how to consummate their wedding.
And what we're doing is we're going to have a couple that are bright and healthy and that's
What we're watching here is how to make little subgenius children.
Now the weird guy could probably give him some advice.
I can, Dr. Drummond can.
You know I was in Amsterdam once and I paid $20 to see that.
That's right you did, you paid $20 to see that.
I paid $20 to see that.
You owe us $20.
Everybody here owes us another $20 because Philo had to pay to see that.
That one time in Amsterdam.
Enter the Impale.
Is he going to impale himself?
He comes on next right?
After us?
He's going to get impaled.
Enter the Impale.
This is a new song.
That's a new song.
We just made it up tonight.
This is a new song.
It's our worst song.
After 31 years.
It's probably our last song.
For now.
We still got it.
Yeah we still got it.
Still sounds stupid.
Still sounds doctor.
These fart pianos aren't loud enough.
We need a real fart.
These fart pianos aren't nearly as good as the...
First by Frank Style Bean.
You know when I was a kid we had fart pianos that were much better than this.
You know back in the old days.
Our fart pianos actually had real asses producing real farts.
And they were in smell-o-visions.
You could actually smell the silly fake farts.
They were much louder.
Fart pianos.
Logos up with several dozen people.
These modern digital fart machines.
They don't sound as pure.
They don't sound as real.
You know when you have that big old bladder and you just pump on it.
And you need them beads and you just kind of...
The pedimane your way through it.
You can really get a good song going.
You know.
God has like the rest.
The rest of the sample.
I think we just ruined this song.
I didn't mean to ruin this song.
I used the wrong sample.
Sam Fred's low.
He needs his shoulders.
I think we should have rehearsed this.
And the drum and the monkey.
I'm glad you left the drummer at home.
Who's rapping?
Do you think that's a much better drummer?
He's a much better drummer.
He doesn't wind down.
You don't have to wind him up all the time.
And Chaos McBobcat goes wild on the Moog synthesizer.
That's not a Moog synthesizer.
It's a Moog synthesizer.
It is?
Really?
I know it's not.
But Fred.
Fred Moog?
Ma Moog.
Oh.
Well, whatever.
Okay.
I think that song's over.
I think that was our worst song.
But as I was saying, Drugs for Wotan started out as a.
Well, Philo is a music expert.
And he knew about 12 tone high fluting classical stuff.
And avant garde things like the resident.
And he knew about the
I didn't know about any of that stuff.
But he convinced me that it was authentic music if you just started making some kind
of noise.
He made the choice.
JHHHHHHHHH
JHHHHHHHHHHHHH
JHHHHHHHHHH
JHHHHHHHHHD
I didn't know any good bass sound on that, and mistakes in melodics, which is
And finding the attitude is what makes a good bass sound is really good.
And coffee makes sounds kindness.
You ever hear heard of an absolutely especial bass sound?
You know, coming from the
I don't know.
¶¶
I'm here to fight
We're going fast, folks
Rocking back and forth
But the bass is getting stolen
But the bass is getting banned
Oh, the bass is getting banned
The next thing you know, it takes an hour to set up.
But that never was a problem with the children's toys.
But Doctors for Bob would get together with Doctors for Wotan
and the band that Darren's in.
They could not speak its name.
And even Doctors for Dinosaurs, briefly.
At Doc's Dock.
And a guy, at one point, I swear,
they must have spent six hours getting the audio system set up.
Their friends and relatives were standing around going,
Boy, this must be going to be really good.
They're so persnickety about getting set up.
Then when it started, it was just a horrible wall of noise.
For about an hour.
And all those innocent friends and relatives and people who'd been waiting all that time
just were scratching their heads.
And that was when I said to myself,
God damn Philodrumon for convincing me
that this anti-music shit was somehow good!
For years, for thirty years, I've been bombarded with tapes from amateurs.
Like playing ten records and synthesizers and flushing toilets all at once.
But with no beat. Couldn't dance to it.
I hate anti-music.
So this is my anti-music tune that I'm playing right now.
So no music at all in it.
Clean.
Pure.
Nothing but the one thing I love.
The sound of my own voice.
We used to record, we'd jam and record these Doctors for Wotan things.
Usually about every hour, out of every hour of tape, we would get a five minute piece.
That really kicked ass by accident.
But then somebody would always go,
Hey stop, stop the music, stop the music!
You can hear this on the tapes.
Why? I thought we were cooking.
Yeah, that's the problem!
It got good for a second.
So we'd take that five minutes
and stick it on the album.
Now since I was editing the first album,
those little five minute chunks tended to be the ones where you could hear me the loudest.
If Philo was editing them, it'd sound completely different.
It'd be a completely different album.
In fact, you can get your Philo albums from QuiveringBrain.com.
But they're about what you'd expect.
Because Philo's louder than me on them.
So how could they possibly be
as good as the ones where I'm louder than Philo?
You see, we have these band dynamics down.
I've observed a lot of bands.
I don't really play in many bands.
You ever see that movie, Frank?
That's the perfect portrait of band psycho interaction.
And it's kind of loosely based on a real Frank and Captain Beefheart.
Who apparently was rather hard to get along with.
That's why he's more famous than us.
Because he was mean.
See, if you're really mean, you get rich and famous.
If you're just humble and kind and nice and Gandhi-like,
like Dr. Drummond there and me,
you just remain, you know, a fringe band.
The kind of band that can come up with better band names
than any other band.
It's not necessarily a good band, but it's a good band.
But it does have good names.
The Vegas is falling.
Oh, the Vegas is falling.
One more time.
But the Vegas is falling.
But the Vegas is down.
Oh, the Vegas is down.
But the Vegas is falling.
That was our latest song called The Basis is Sullen.
No, no, no, that was a different song.
No, no, no, that was the bass of the song.
Everything smells like Taco Bell.
And that reminds me.
That was the other thing.
The first thing was,
thank you to all those artists and weirdos that have given us anything at all,
including the ticket to Agstay.
Because believe me, it's been on a kind of a hand-to-mouth, shoe-string thing since 1980.
But the good news is it proves you can do that
and probably be happier than poor old Robin Williams.
And we can think of another million other weirdos and subgeniuses who got famous and rich,
but it backfired.
So, you know, thank you for keeping us poor, but not too poor.
However, if any of you are secretly insane millionaires, this would be a good time, you know.
But I was going to also shame on you people for cussing.
In front of my...
my sheltered 187-year-old mother-in-law.
I've heard terrible language up here.
And you've been a bad influence on her because then she started talking that way.
She sounds like a sailor now.
Now I'm the one who's getting embarrassed.
Oh, well.
Honestly, we're so proud that people mess with Bob's head
because that...
that...
that sure mess...
it messes with my head.
And I love having my head messed with that way.
Thank you, everybody, just for even making it, you know,
because we don't make it easy, that's for sure.
But being in a campground in the middle of nowhere makes it memorable.
Mm-hmm.
You might not remember any of it if we did this in a motel in Atlanta or something.
Because I don't...
I've been to a bunch of conventions in motels in Atlanta.
I don't remember any of it.
So I didn't...
it didn't...
I was never terrorized or threatened or inconvenienced or...
and all of...
or bitten by poisonous spiders, tarantulas, water spiders, snakes, bears, and worse,
which is going to happen to all of you in the next few days.
And just remember, it's, you know, that which does not kill you injures you very,
very much.
Very badly.
So there's one trail that takes you past the lair of Old Sequa.
And every X day, Old Sequa takes one subgenius.
And usually it's one of those people, you know, who's kind of lame, wasn't that funny?
And nobody misses him, you know.
But you don't want to be that subgenius.
So be careful walking down.
Down them trails at night.
We had some strange things happen out here at Wisteria last X day.
Oh, yes.
It could happen to you.
Late at night on those trails, you'll hear sounds in the woods.
And you'll see footprints and things.
And suddenly you lost your bearings.
You don't know, wait, was I going this way down that trail?
Oh, that way.
Is that the trail?
Or is that just a brook, a little stream that looks like a trail?
Oh.
What's that?
What's that weird pipe smoke I smell?
Oh, no.
I hope Bob ain't coming to judge me now.
So anyway, like I say, have a good time walking down the trails.
It's good exercise.
And during the night, it's slippery and treacherous.
I almost broke my coccyx a couple of years ago doing that.
But really, during the day, kids, you know, last year when Bob killed all those people
and we had to go save Philo from him.
I managed to get 20 subgeniuses not just off their butts but into the woods a little ways
for like 10 or 15 minutes.
So I'd love to see when people take that huge brave step of going into the woods
and smelling the roses.
Not even coffee.
It's really roses.
And the poison ivy.
You know, it's natural.
It's organic.
It must be good.
What's that noise down there?
It sounds like horrible, ugly, large subgeniuses are playing rock and roll instruments.
Um, yeah, maybe that was
it?
Molly?
Did you want a bell, maybe?
Maybe she needed to wait until she...
Little bit of this, little bit of that.
Say no more.
I can't.
Why would I?
Obamaknicle.
We're all in there.
Thank you.
Oh, actually, there's a...
I've seen the bass player.
There's a song that's really...
It's called Fag Beef.
Fag Beef.
Yeah, because it's an F-A-G-B-E-F.
Deaf bag.
Deaf?
Bag.
Dead beef.
D-F-B-A-G.
That would probably sound pretty horrible.
Try it.
No?
All right.
I have to remember how to spell it.
Music.
One, two, three, four.
How about dead beef?
Dead beef.
Like D-E-D?
Yeah, D-E-A-D.
Oh, D-E-A-D.
Okay.
See, I came up with Fag Beef, which you just play F-A-G-B-E-E-F.
And then we did...
Fag.
Fag Cage.
Yeah, we did Fag Cage, and now we're doing Dead Beef.
Aren't you giving away all your secrets?
Did you say Fag Beef?
There's no secret here.
Oh, no, it's still a secret, because no one here will ever remember.
That's true.
There's no shame in this game.
I think Fag Beef.
If you steal this idea, you are dead beef.
Yeah, you're dead beef.
There's too many letters.
Dead Beef.
You got it.
Dead beef.
Bob said stop.
I can only yell dead beef so many times.
You guys have a lot of notes.
Too many notes.
Yeah.
Listen, there's...
We could just do like less than a sentence.
We could just do a word, like cage.
Yeah.
We could do Gaga, but that's real easy.
It's just...
What happens if you play Bob Dobbs?
What's the O note?
There really isn't an O note.
Yeah, you got B-O-B.
I know.
That's boring.
Bob Dobbs would be boring.
Well, that would be if we were just going.
Well, what if you go B-O.
Well, what if you make the O random?
Oh.
Oh, so in other words we can do...
Be something be.
Right.
D something B-B.
Oh, it's like an L.
That's something L-O-L.
I don't know.
I mean, what if the O was a G?
Some of the...
Oh, that's a good one.
That's a good one.
Yeah.
I feel the fuckery
I smell the fuckery
Yeah, we're all here.
This is our first time in a long time
that we've been together.
Chirp!
The coming of
the giant. Chirp!
They're on your skin.
They're in your hair.
In your lungs.
They're everywhere.
Chirp!
The coming of the
It's a giant
Chirp!
From the deep depths of outer space
comes a
alien race.
Chirp!
They are the giant.
Chirp off.
Chirp!
Chirp off!
Chirpff!
Chirp, Chirp!
Chirp off!
Chirp!
And Earth.
My music every Friday night at the Bulls on a Catholic.
Bulls on a Catholic.
That was the Bulldada Cafe advertisement.
Bulldada Cafes are opening all over the universe right now,
and we encourage you to free refills of slack
at every Bulldada Cafe location.
Thank you very much.
The Bulldada Cafe is actually really, really hard to find.
It's one of those hole-in-the-wall places.
You guys have heard me do other parody songs,
so let me explain a few things.
And you're probably going to hear
another one of my parody songs.
There's another one later that's worse than this.
So Suds and I have a game.
And basically, he'll text me at work,
and he'll give me a song,
and he'll say,
make a Bob song out of it.
And I'm really bad good at this,
which is kind of sad.
Either I don't have anything better to do.
Well, yeah, that is what it is.
So I have tons of these.
So this one, I can actually do acapella.
Busted.
Flattened Carolina
Standing in the rain
And I was feeling just as burnt out as my bull
Bobby showed up with a pound
And a little blow
And he rode us all the way to Ohio
Well, I pulled my wallet out
Of my big old black bag
And I gave him 35 to tell the truth
Yeah
His words hit me right on time
I was feeling so slack divine
It was something like I had never knew
Cause you see
Sometimes slack's another word for
Nothing left to lose
And nothing, nothing's all the comments gave me
And feeling good was easy, Lord
When Bobby spoke the truth
You know, feeling good is good enough
For me to be happy
Good enough for me and Bobby, see
So from the Kentucky coal mines
To the California sun
Well, Bobby met lots of others on the road
No matter the weather
No matter what we've done
Hey, Bobby, baby, get me from the cold
One day in San Francisco
Oh, Lord, we'll be back
And let him slip away
We've been looking for him since
And I hope we find him
But I'd trade all my tomorrows
For one single yesterday
To have Bobby pass the pipe around one more time
Sometimes slack's another word for
Nothing left to lose
Nothing, nothing's all the kind he gave me
And feeling good was easy, Lord
When Bobby spoke the truth
You know, feeling good was good enough for me
Good enough for me and Bobby, see
La la la, la la la la
La la la, Bobby, I see
La la la, la la la
La la la, la la la la
Hey, it's Bob, you know it's Bob and me
Yeah, Lordy, Lordy, Lordy, Lord
Lordy, Lordy, Lordy, Lordy, Lordy, Lord
Hey, you know it's just Bob and me
Yeah, Lord, I call him my savior
I call him my friend, yes
I call him by any other name I can, you know
Come on, Bob, no
I know where you bought me, yeah.
Lordy, lordy, lordy, lordy, lordy, lordy, lordy, lord.
Why, why, why did Bobby leave me?
80.
Go over there and pay him $20.
80 bucks.
80.
I'm calling you on your back.
Go pay Sting 20 bucks.
Oh Bob, won't you buy me a ticket to space?
I've paid all my money to your smiling face.
Slacked off all my lifetime and waited for X day.
So, oh Bob, won't you buy me
a ticket to space?
Let me go on.
Like a blister in the sun, let me go on.
You don't know the famous song about masturbation.
Oh yeah, all right.
Feels good tonight.
Saying it's so.
So nice to meet you.
Your slack is a false figure
Say it ain't so
Your lies are a slack figure
What got me into doing the Bob Song stuff was that
Years ago, I'm from Lynchburg
I don't know if you know what that is
Okay, it's the home of Jerry Falwell
So there was a little coffee shop called the Drowsy Poet
That was owned by all the crazy Christian people
And so we would go in there and rewrite songs
Until we got kicked out
So we'd sing songs about penises and shitting
Until they kicked us out of the coffee shop
I must have gotten kicked out of that coffee shop
40 or 50 times before they permanently banned me
Last train to Clarksville
House of the Rising Sun
There is a house in Downsondon
They call the Rising Sun
And it's been the home of me for a while
And I'm in love with you so much
There's no way you know me
I still can't believe
There's never been a song boy
That is as angry
Your story is a shame
I sometimes don't think it's real
God successful
I try to stop this
Done shit wrong
From the church of the subgenius
and the old out of time control labs
Orally transmitted
diseases
At the low price of
$10 or $1
per track
Worst f***ing excuse for music I ever heard
Voice in your earlobes with the
sweet sounds of
Rainleak
The music box can't say no
Batman D
Dr. Slagjaw
Lonesome Cowboy Dave
Swingin' love books
Bomb
Kill Big Dead
Mutant Mountain Boys
Amen
Please don't slack and answer me
Focus
Pantera Ivakovich
Eat the stains
Glass Madness
Princess
Well, the Bob Dobbs is a real nice guy
And many many more
Send a dollar to the p.o. box he'll get you high
Spend money, gain slack
auditorium
All rights reserved. All materials are copyrighted by no respect of owners.
Any similarities between anyone living or dead is purely coincidental.
If readiness continues please consult a physician.
You've been listening to the subgenius radio ministry, Hour of Slack.
For free information, write to P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118 or see www.subgenius.com.
Praise Bob!
And there on the distance is the greatest emerging tile of all time.
The emergent tile that without him, none of this would be possible.
The emergent tile, Reverend Ivan Stang.
Brothers and sisters, if you could just give, just spare, just a drop of slack, perhaps it is just a few hundred dollars in your wallet.
Perhaps it's just a little bit of something, a little bit of your soul, a little bit of slack.
If you could just offer that to the Reverend.
He has worked his dick to the nubs, trying to, all of his dicks, in fact, he has worked all of his dicks to just bloody stumps,
trying to make sure that Bob's word has been given out there, that Bob has reached every one of you.
And just, if you could find it in your heart of hearts, just to send Reverend Stang just a little bit of your slack, brothers and sisters.
He so needs it. He cries at night, thinking of all the work he has to do.
All the work that his slaves...
Master J.R. Bob Dobbs throws upon him.
He is, he has the worst and the best boss in the world in J.R. Bob Dobbs.
But Dobbs is the hard taskmaster and poor Ivan Stang, poor Ivan Stang is trying so hard.
So if you could find it in your hearts, brothers and sisters, come down to the main stage right now and grant Ivan Stang
just a little bit, just a little bit of your spare slack.
Please brothers and sisters, just a little spare slack. Maybe it's a beer.
Maybe it's a free beer.
Maybe it's something, but poor Ivan Stang may not make it through the night without your slack love, brothers and sisters.
And still you damn rewardians just sit there.
Look at him. He's begging for your help.
He's a broken man. Broken like Bob's pipe.
Grant him some slack, brothers and sisters.
Yes and praise Hazel.
It appears that Hazel is going to do the right thing and she is going to grant Ivan Stang just a little bit of her slack.
Brothers and sisters, follow the lead of Hazel. Follow the lead and go the right way and grant, grant Ivan Stang slack.
Please brothers and sisters, keep in mind, keep in mind, let me just say this.
If you don't want, if you have something where you don't feel like, like Ivan Stang deserves your slack,
just remember that Ivan Stang is a conduit for J.R. Bob Dobbs.
He may only be,
just a little conduit.
And in fact, brothers and sisters, I should add, every one of you are a part of Bob.
We are all just a section of Bob.
A small section.
Perhaps, perhaps you're just the pinky nail of Bob.
Perhaps, perhaps you're just the very tip of Bob's penis.
But brothers and sisters, I have a sad story to tell you.
Because poor Ivan Stang,
Ivan Stang is the asshole of Bob.
And feel sorry for Stang, for he is stuck as being the asshole of Bob.
And he needs your assistance.
Cause Lord help us when Bob gets a hemorrhoid on the asshole of Bob.
Please, don't let Ivan Stang become Bob's hemorrhoid.
Please, please see it in your heart to help out Ivan Stang in his time of need.