Wherever you go, whatever you do, it's always wise to keep an eye open for the black and yellow public fallout shelter signs.
Each one marks a place that's been thoroughly checked for proper shielding against radioactive fallout,
and in many cases, already stocked with emergency food rations, water, and basic survival equipment.
Knowing where the nearest one is could save you crucial minutes in time of emergency.
If your local government has instructed you to go to a specific public shelter in event of nuclear attack,
find out exactly where it's located and the best way to reach it promptly.
Check on whether there's a shelter in or near your child's school, and if not, find out what other actions would be taken by the school authorities to protect him in emergency.
In short, take time now to make a family emergency plan, and then make sure every member of your family knows it.
La La La La Nota
Pța speaks Spanish
Uuh?
Get the hell outta my-
tá
What??
I want to take a pardon!
That's the way of theわくわく
casual
Wildaucisty
As with any art
Don't know the ball
I'm alone
You and me together
Everyday's gonna be alright
That's the way Bob
has set that system
to have you
mental slavery.
So if you could just free yourself
from mental slavery
that is the key.
Yeah
This girl
is on fire
She's walking on fire
This girl is on fire
I am the champion
And you're gonna hear me roar
I am the fighter
Dancing through the fire
I am the champion
And you're gonna hear me roar
Louder
Louder than the wind
Booing and screaming
bodies are shining
outwards
brming in
Like a
Poet
Better
Stay
If I ever lose my faith
I was driving through the Mojave Desert about ten years ago
when I saw a figure by the side of the road.
And there was a man carrying a motorcycle on his back.
And it was quite a sight to see.
And I pulled up alongside and looked at him.
And this guy had this, looked like a 250cc motorcycle,
slung across his shoulders like it was nothing,
was puffing on his pipe, had a big grin on his face.
And he looked at me and he said,
Yeah, man, the gas mileage.
Oh, the gas mileage.
It was something new to Bill,
this business of nocturnal emissions.
You all know what sperm is?
I don't know.
¶¶
Thank you so much, G. Gordon Gordon.
Yes, that was the great old Dr. G. Gordon Gordon ranting earlier a bit in the show.
There'll be more of that in future shows to come.
And thanks to the Rudy Schwartz Project, which did that long piece of freaked out music there called...
Uncle Pinkerton Explains.
Uh, yes.
And Phineas Narco did the shelter warning at the very beginning.
But the rest of this whole show was and will be a subgenius mix by the large.
Using a little bit of everything once we stop talking.
Freezy friends, the phone is dead.
Yes, the station phone is temporarily out of commission.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave will stay lonesome.
And we're lonesome.
But we've got you, the listener, with us.
Me and Princess We Are Doe.
Yes.
And we're going to read to you tonight from the best of Scrub Genius.
Scrub Genius Forum on Google Groups, which for those who don't read, but only know of Church of the Subgenius through this show and Susie the Floozy Show and Puzzling Evidence Show.
Yes, there's a sort of a text version of the church.
It started out in books.
Not stored in souls, but still available if you know where to look.
And on the Internet in various forums.
We don't use alt.slack on Usenet anymore.
We left that for the, well, you'd have to see it to believe it.
But we, the subgenius ministers, dues paying ministers, actual authorized subgeniuses, many of them use a thing called Scrub Genius, a little forum on Google Groups.
And a lot of people use Facebook.
There are a number of Facebook subgenius pages, hundreds of them unauthorized.
And by the way, I'm pretty sure that not a single one of the Bob Dobbses on Facebook are the Bob Dobbs.
Although there probably are a few people whose actual name is Bob Dobbs.
But mostly not the ones who say it is.
Anyway, yeah, there's an official subgenius.
Foundation Facebook page and an official church of the subgenius Facebook page.
You can tell they're official because they have 10 or 20,000 people involved.
But the best one is not official.
It's called Slack Hole.
Slack Hole 2.0 because the first Slack Hole got censored.
Well, somebody did something bad and they had to erase the whole thing forever.
But the current Slack Hole is somewhat policed.
And.
But not too policed.
And it's got really funny graphics and funny short talk.
If you like the funny, long, thoughtful talk and rants, such as we're about to read tonight,
you find those on Scrub Genius.
But it's members only.
So that probably.
That probably means not you, Fred.
Not you, Martin.
Not you, Bob.
I'm just grabbing names at random.
So if your name happens to be Fred or Bob or Martin, don't freak out.
Unless you never officially join the church, in which case you should be freaking out.
Oh, you should be freaking out to the very bottom of the soles of your feet.
And because your soul is in danger.
Now, let's.
Let's switch over.
We are going to go back to the media barrage by the great the large soon.
But first, I'd like to read this.
A letter from a little girl.
Some of you may be familiar with this.
I don't know.
Dear editor, I am eight years old.
Some of my little friends say there is no Jack the Ripper.
Papa says if you see it in the sun, it's so.
I guess that's a newspaper.
Please tell me the truth.
Is there a Jack the Ripper?
Virginia O'Hanlon, 115 West 95th Street.
And here's the answer.
Virginia, your little friends are wrong.
They've been affected by the skepticism of a skeptical age.
They do not believe except they see.
They think that nothing can be which is not comprehensible by their little minds.
All minds, Virginia, whether they be men's or children's, are little.
In this great universe of ours, man is a mere insect, an ant in his intellect,
as compared with the boundless world about him,
as measured by the intelligence capable of grasping the whole of truth and knowledge.
Yes, Virginia, there is a Jack the Ripper.
He exists as certainly as hate and greed and evil exist.
You know that they abound and give to your life its greatest terror and misery.
How wonderful would be the world if there were no Jack the Ripper.
It would be as wonderful as if there were no Virginias.
There would be faith, then, poetry, romance,
to make tolerable this existence.
We should have enjoyment in sense and sight.
The eternal light with which childhood fills the world would be brightened.
Not believe in Jack the Ripper?
You might as well not believe in vampires!
Sure, you might get your papa to hire men to watch in all the alleys of White Chapel to catch Jack the Ripper.
But even if they did not see Jack the Ripper, what would that prove?
Nobody sees Jack the Ripper, but that's no sign that there is no Jack the Ripper.
The most real things in the world are those that neither children nor men can see.
Did you ever see demons dancing on a grave?
Of course not, but that's no proof that they're not there.
Nobody can conceive or imagine all the horrors there are unseen and unseeable in the world.
You may tear apart a baby to see what makes the screams inside,
but there is a veil covering the unseen world which not the most mystical man
nor even the united incantations of all the most mystical men that ever lived could tear apart.
Only horror, hallucination, hatred, and madness can push aside that curtain
and view and picture the supernatural beastliness and gore beyond.
Is it all real?
Yes, Virginia.
In all this world, there is nothing real and abiding.
No Jack the Ripper?
Hail Satan, he lives and he lives forever.
A thousand years from now, Virginia, nay, ten times ten thousand years from now,
he will continue to rip the entrails from prostitutes everywhere.
By Reverend...
And Ride Theory.
Answering the question, is there a Jack the Ripper?
It was so beautiful.
It gives you faith, you know?
Faith in something.
The music in the background goes perfectly with that.
It's from Kenneth Anger's movie, Lucifer Rising.
It was recorded in a prison.
And one of the main musicians was one of Charlie Manson's boys.
Hmm.
And Kenneth Anger specifically told me to my face
that I shouldn't use this music on the Hour of Slack.
Oh.
But there's still a Jack the Ripper, there's still a Santa Claus,
and there's still a J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And a defiant Reverend Stang.
Well, um...
As a...
To quote weird Al Yankovic,
Al Yankovic,
somebody asked him,
aren't you ripping off the subgeniuses and Bob Dobbs,
this Dare to Be Stupid video?
As Weird Al said,
can't be helped.
So...
Yeah, all us weirdo artistes and devil worshipers and satirists
have to stick together.
Okay, let's change the music, though,
to Rudy Schwartz Project,
something evil sounding,
to go with this rant by...
the good Reverend Roger,
which he apparently wrote August 24th
of the year men call 2013.
Hugh men.
And it's a little rant called
The Weaponized Ape.
I should probably turn the volume down and lean back.
Because you have to yell this one, friends.
I am the weaponized ape.
I am the spun-out bearing housing,
the loose neutral,
the other half,
of Mama Cass's ham sandwich.
I am the ghost in the machine,
the sand in the gears,
the last surviving meanderthal.
I run on caffeine,
bourbon,
and huge parasitic worms,
with which I destroy public toilets forever.
I ain't here to save the world,
and I ain't here to wreck it.
I'm here to eat popcorn
while the monkeys tear themselves apart
in a whirlwind of righteous butthurt,
and for this,
I am philified.
And what of it?
The same people that screech at me for laughing
are the same people causing the problem.
If they liked me,
I'd have to re-examine my values.
No, I'm the man behind the hate ball.
The guy with the mind control lasers.
The jackass pointing out what's really going on.
The bastard braying laughter and spittle
in the bewildered faces of the humans.
The man who's been trying to get me out of this mess
They don't understand what went wrong
because they can't admit their own actions or inactions
made this mess.
I, on the other hand, understand doom.
And I hope you do too, brothers and sisters.
They don't understand,
and I don't expect them to understand.
Let them ignore their stupid decisions and complacency
and blame it all on my bad attitude.
The results will be the same.
Their mortgages will go upside down,
their jobs will go to Malaysia,
and their kids will turn to drugs
while these idiots pray for a solution.
Think on that for a minute.
Put yourself in God's shoes.
Here's all these primates, right?
And you give them opposable thumbs
and a brain designed for engineering
and a great big planet to live on.
So the first thing they do is write universal rules
that are designed to make them miserable.
Then they breathe life into their bodies.
They're like flies.
Then they take a perfectly functional golden goose
and have Goldman's socks slice it open from butt to breakfast
looking for all the golden eggs.
Then they insist that all these things are necessary
and that the problem is that they didn't do it enough.
And then they pray to you to come unscrew up everything
while they're continuing their efforts
to find new and better ways to screw up everything some more.
Is it any wonder that God hasn't said a word in 2000 plus years?
Would you?
Hell no, he's probably off starting over
somewhere with a species that doesn't start out
by throwing excrement at each other.
But wherever he is, we're here.
I'm here, a 240 pound monkey
with projectile weapons and motorized transport.
For I am the Weaponized Ape.
Or kill me.
And thank you, Reverend, the good Reverend Roger
for that great rant, the Weaponized Ape
as it appeared on Scruff Genius.com.
And thank you, The Psycho Skeletons,
for this little tune in the background,
which I think is either power trip or quantum sexy.
Oh, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
That was wonderful.
Well, we could go back to playing some of the largest thing
while we regroup.
The large, the large is so great.
Well, he is...
He's great.
He's great in size, yes.
Yes, great.
This is The Psycho Skeletons in the backyard also.
Oh, speaking of which, the...
Now, this doesn't affect the audience,
listeners at our darling, beloved sister stations,
but for the Cleveland listeners,
Princess Wee and I will be attending
the WCSB Annual Halloween Masquerade Ball.
Woo-hoo!
Which is always a great party.
Fabulous costumes, a lot of people.
And I've been asked to prepare a video...
video projections on the party's theme,
which is Godzilla.
And so I've been godzillaed and kaiju'd up like crazy
and assembled about five and a half hours
of collaged Godzilla footage,
best of Godzilla and a thousand and one other Japanese monsters
of the most mind-ruining designs,
which will all be projected on the brick ceilings
of the Cleveland Public Theater building.
Yes.
Well, sort of the corners of the room,
just to the right and left of the stage.
Yeah, this will be the third year we've done that.
But luckily, you can just leave the DVDs playing
and go downstairs and mingle around.
So, friends, if you see Bob there,
it's probably not the real Bob Dobbs.
It might be me or Princess Wee Ardo
in a remarkably realistic, if oversized,
and badly sculpted J.R. Bob Dobbs head.
It's not that badly sculpted.
You can tell.
See, I think those were made by a company
called Monster Makers near Cleveland
at the behest of the mysterious Pope Jimbo of Cleveland,
who we haven't heard from in a long time.
But you know those Dobbs heads that are all...
Are you guys in this cult business just for the bucks?
Yes.
I've always wanted to answer that the right way.
I'm sure there's a way that they could possibly
help build the best craft in England in the world,
And that's how well I've reached.
I mean, everything we've told...
Don't worry.
One of our two shows from Patreon
as we look forward to talking more
about different films to the next show of this year.
We'll be right back.
That's what they all say.
Friends, that's the amino acids from their new EP,
or actually it's a vinyl record album,
an albino one, albino vinyl,
called Theme from the Slack Hole.
In fact, we just heard the tune
Suppressive Persons Limited and Theme from the Slack Hole,
and the one in the background is Run, Human, Run,
and that is what you should do
because now we're going to go back to playing
the collage by The Large and everyone else.
Bye.
What if mom was one of us?
Last night, let it, let it die.
Thinking about last night, let it, let it die.
Bald guys with mustaches.
Yeah.
I don't think you get what this whole portraiture thing is about.
This is how we want to be remembered,
like Nefertiti and things like that.
This is not what actually happened to our...
Well, I'll get my head shot, but I'll get through the famous...
We're going to shock.
These are...
This outside...
This outside thing is not what I am, so...
We're just going to unzip it.
We're going to unzip our external shell
and show the glorified self,
that glorified state that we all want to...
Forget about the glorification,
about the romance.
Aspire to.
The romanticification.
Forget about it all.
Okay, I forgot.
Start with the real life.
I forgot.
Breaking up and stuff like that.
Yeah!
Not that useless stuff that you are used to
in your everyday mundane life.
In your mundane, stupid life.
Murder.
The normal life.
The Bob way of life.
The way that Bob sees you and your life.
Murder.
Wouldn't you like to be like that?
Oh, he's taking over the life!
And what is that?
Those three-way...
Murder!
What was that?
Well...
Boy, that was an enlightened caller,
but I don't know what happened to him.
Yeah, I think he went around the dark side.
How refreshing it was to hear that...
I hope he's going to be at the beautiful little
October Portland thing.
Mm, me too.
Because...
Yeah.
But what would a smart, pretty, talented young woman know about one of the scariest gums around?
Did you ever think that you would become addicted?
Not in a million years.
I never thought that any of us would ever be able to overcome every aspect of my life the way that bath salts did.
What was Hannah like before she got into the bath?
Oh, gosh.
Well, every parent thinks their kid's just great, but she really was very sweet, very gentle.
Everybody loved her.
Her grandparents adopted Hannah when their daughter, Rachel, gave birth at age 16.
Mother and daughter grew up more like sisters.
After Rachel moved to Colorado, Hannah visited her for about a month.
That's when they started using bulb together.
What did you think when you first started using it?
I just thought of it as almost like buying an energy drink.
Or sometimes in gas stations they have the vitamin packs or the energy packs, something like that.
Because that's how it felt at first, just a stimulant that gives you energy.
Did you ever think that you would become addicted?
Did you ever ask Hannah if she was using drugs?
Yes, she denied it.
Absolutely denied it.
She admitted in the past that she had tried a few things.
She's always been open before about the few things they had tried with friends.
And she's always, always, this is the hard part, she's always been so totally honest before this.
How quickly addicting is it?
Pretty quickly.
Basically, from when I first started, I had to have it every day, even though it was changing my life and my brain.
It's like a personalized hell for, you know, for whoever you are, and specified individual hell just for you.
By the time she returned home from her Colorado visit, Hannah was hooked and it was horrible.
Starting with paranoia and ramping up to hearing voices and having vivid hallucinations.
I thought I'd been abducted by aliens.
I am, the voices told me I had spiders in the back of my throat and I would see them.
And at one point I thought I was turning into a giant spider.
I felt that I had bug in my skin.
And they would always tell me, I'm not going to do this.
They would only bite me, and I would feel them bite me, if I would try to remove them.
Nobody feels really bad around Bob, unless you get bit by a...
...soul genius.
Power of the soul.
What?
You'll finally get to see why they call me Bob.
She's losing interest. She doesn't want to really go to work anymore.
So she starts being late to work, so eventually that job is lost.
She doesn't want to go back to school now.
And so, this is not my child anymore.
And it just...
...continues to get worse and worse.
Now that's former
ear
으
will
everyone
Pete
Learn more about the Neil White Houseasserie program and all of his amazing workouts while at home, learn how to outlive and create an ice whale, a USBblies memory, that's open by?view?f informative channel брос podcasts~"
Thank you.
Well, we can learn a lot.
I looked at all the people I have chosen.
From crossing the
painful threshold
to feeling the piercing
ranting pain
multi-dotted face of J.R. Bob
Downs.
This is, but I don't like
them. Don't like whom,
my boy?
Oh, everyone.
Every dot in Bob's
face? For that is
what everyone is.
Because I am equally public in my comments.
And that's incredible, ladies and gentlemen.
That's the way it is.
That's truly fantastic.
I was just editing all that.
And here's a funny thought.
Okay.
And it's 9-11.
2009.
Friday.
4-51.
It's that big, bulbous mob again.
Bulging and barging into our show.
All real Americans love the sting of Bob Dobbs.
Natural fluid.
The sting of Bob Dobbs.
We have, we have, we have, we have, we have, we have, we have, we have, we have, we have, we have, we have, we have, we have, we have.
He's out your sister yet, took you away.
I got your family back, but you got your smile.
And your clothes, it's just sister that you never wore.
Bye.
Yeah.
He's out your sister yet, took you away.
I got your family back, but you got your smile.
And your clothes, it's just sister that you never wore.
Bye.
Yeah.
I did.
I kind of sucked it up and said hi to him.
And he mumbled something to me.
And we went in this little room.
It was about a 12 by 12 room that I'd rented at the airport.
And, uh, but his, remember his face was beet red.
So we go in the door.
I shut the door, sit down.
Probably 12 seconds has expired.
And I'm looking at him and he's looking above me.
He's looking at the wall in back of my head.
And this is about 12 seconds between beet red and white as a sheet of paper.
He's white as 10,000 sheets of Xerox paper.
And then his shoulders drop.
And I thought he's gonna, he's having a heart attack.
He's gonna die on my shift.
I don't think this is good.
Or he's having a stroke or both.
And I start to talk and I feel this check.
It's almost like a hand went in front of my mouth.
Mike, don't say a word.
I'm taking care of this.
And so four or five minutes go by.
It seems like an eternity.
I don't say a word.
He doesn't either.
Then he starts to mumble and he says, uh, uh, we'll, we'll pay you.
And I thought, did, did I hear what I think I just heard?
And he goes, we'll pay you.
And then about four or five minutes later.
The color comes back to his face.
His shoulders come up and he just looks at me for the first time, somewhat friendly.
And he goes, I think I'll go back to Colorado.
And I said, Bob, okay.
Those are the words.
I only words I said was Bob.
Okay.
Bob.
Now, uh, we're, we're still doing, uh, best of, uh, scrub genius.
And I have a little rant here from Reverend Nigel.
I have.
I can.
I can't do it justice.
I used to think I was screwed on a fairly regular basis.
Then I came to recognize a simple fact.
The bar by which I was being measured was crafted by people just like me.
So I was being measured by a measurement.
I alone had crafted for the express purpose of making people just like me feel inadequate
to measure the worth of anyone but themselves.
And, uh, that, uh, that's not.
was not only okay, but also the law.
The entire planet is faking it until they make it.
If you ever doubt that,
simply call out anyone's heartfelt,
inner, deep-down philosophy to the point
they actually have to read books to defend their position.
99.5% of them will fold like a house of cards upon challenge.
The other 0.5%, they'll pull out every intellectual stock
to refute your counterpoints.
If you actually run into that person,
you should strip down and copulate the very soul out of them
because you will never meet the like of them again
in your lifetime on this rock.
If it turns out you don't have anything in common,
at least you'll have that one burning conflict
that makes your breakup better than most pinks' relationships.
And if you do have things in common,
you'll likely spawn the next generation
of superstars.
Subgeniuses on planet Earth-Mars.
Being a subgenius doesn't require more reading.
It doesn't require more thinking.
It doesn't require even more slacking.
What it does demand is an unwavering devotion to the truth
and a sense as to what that responsibility means.
Knowing the truth is vastly different than believing the truth
and requires so much more personal commitment.
It's not for everyone,
you have to know your limits.
So, know as opposed to believe,
and you may have a chance.
And if that turns out to be false,
don't blame me, I know I'm right.
Thank you, Reverend Nigel.
And thank you, the Flyin' Ryan brothers,
for the music in the background.
Praise Bob.
Gegenerations by Vita.
на
Watch this.
772-5982.
Back to you, Bob.
Did you put Mom sleeping with Bob?
Where'd that come from?
Watch.
982.
Back to you, Bob.
Something about her bees.
They're too soft.
Back to you, Bob.
You're reaching.
I mean, why would your mom be sleeping with Bob?
Your dad's the perfect male specimen.
I don't know, but I think they are.
You're just looking for conflict.
Everything's a potential script to you.
Accept your perfect life.
It's a reality.
5982.
Back to you, Bob.
Cleanup continues to...
982.
Back to you, Bob.
– Bob. – Bob.
Joe.
I'm talking to you.
You're listening to me.
What's the answer?
Then. . . . a word for my name.
Oh.
Ahem.
Ah. . . .
You're giving up quicker than usual, Tony.
Just tell me the goddamn word.
Palindrome.
Your name's a palindrome.
Palindrome?
What's that, huh?
You making fun of me?
Is that something bad?
Spelled the same way forwards and back.
It's like the phrase,
Madam and Eden, I met him.
It's a palindrome.
Ends the same way it begins.
Oh, I get it.
So it's like the name Bob.
That's one too, right?
Viva Melia.
All American family.
Yeah.
The winds go down.
The ripples go.
They all sing.
Jabba dabba doo.
Viva Melia.
American family.
Yeah.
The Flintstones have
the rebel stuff.
They all say
yabba-dabba-doo, yabba-dabba-doo.
Yeah.
Meet Samantha.
Oh my God, no. I hear people die.
Meet Samantha. Oh my God, no.
I hear people die from jiving.
She's a perfume-wearing, pink-loving,
pampered princess. I want you to do it,
please. Who's afraid of her own shadow.
Bugs scare me. Heights scare me.
Spores getting hurt. Oh yeah, that
scares me. Bugs scare me. Heights scare
me. Spores getting hurt. Oh
yeah, that scares me.
But now Samantha's ready to trade
in her lipstick for a different kind
of stick. Do you have any in pink?
Duh, duh, duh. And be
made into a fierce and fearless hard
ass tough.
It's only hands cream.
I can't get hurt on that ice. Oh my gosh.
It's just Bob is what it is.
It's just Bob.
It's literally Bob.
When the sunshine will shine
together. Told you I'll
be here forever.
Said I'll always be your friend.
Took an oath I must to get out to the end.
Now that it's raining more than ever.
Know that we'll still have each other.
You can stand under my umbrella.
They say Bob's behind the times.
They say Bob can relate to the X generation.
Well you know what Bob says to that? To horse hockey.
Bob's here to set the record straight. Bob has his finger on the pulse of American youth today.
If Bob was an old fart, could he pound this much
Jagermeister this fast and not drop dead?
Oh no. No. Real. It's a bottle.
Bob's hip. Bob's with the times.
Bob lives up on Capitol Hill but he'd rather be in the Marsh Pit with you.
Bob knows what it's like to be young. To be alienated.
Disenfranchised and hassled by the man.
Bob knows who the man is. And Bob's not afraid to take the man on.
Running against the Democrats is a death trap. It's a suicide rap.
We gotta get out while we're young and baby Bob was born to run.
Run this country.
We can run and we can step to the moving car.
Two squares cut the gift they chose at Doc Tom for punk.
Two squares cut the gift they chose at Doc Tom for punks.
We can run and we can step to the moving car.
Two squares cut the gift they chose at Doc Tom for punk.
Too much is always better than not enough.
Too much it's always better.
Too much is always better.
But not enough.
Only J.R. Bobcots!
Yes, dear friends.
Thank you, The Large, for that.
By the way, The Large is located in...
Finland.
Did you know that?
No, I didn't know that.
No.
Now, he's one...
I don't know whether he's an American in Finland or a Fin...
Or what.
I often wonder if that's him talking on the Puzzling Evidence shows.
Clips that he sends.
Mm-hmm.
Because that was Puzzling Evidence.
Dr. Hal, Dr. Philodrumon in Puzzling Evidence himself.
We heard several clips.
You're listening to The Hour of Slack.
Number one.
1,436.
Phew.
From the Church of the Subgenius.
For more information about the church, feel free to look at subgenius.com.
Dr. Sinister's show is next, at least here in Cleveland.
And we just got some good news for everybody all around.
Dr. Sinister said yes.
And...
So, if Reverend Bucky is listening,
you can go ahead and start...
Booking, Bucky.
We're very excited.
I don't want to go into what the details is, because that, you know...
Yeah.
We're going to read a newsletter from Truman Bentley Jr.
We'll have to save that for next time.
One of our radio subscribers, Reverend Johnson, sent this amazing rant in.
And we've been enjoying...
It's tricky to read.
Anyway...
I think your Scrub Genius show is...
It's great.
We'll just have to continue that.
Well, and thanks to The Large for making the editing so very much easier for me this time.
So large.
And we'll go back to enlarging and stay tuned.
The Subgenius Hour of...
Subgenius.
My name is Law.
My name is Hour of Fumb.
I'm Bob.
Do you know?
Okay, hi.
Okay.
My name is Bach.
Most of you know me as, um, um, um, um, um, uh, well, uh, well, uh, well, uh, well, uh,
most of you know me as Bach, I suppose.
If you're watching this, you probably know me as Bach.
But, um, um, um, um, a, a, a, a lot of people don't know me as Bach.
And, um, um, um, um, so, yeah, um, um, um, um, a, a, a, a, a lot, a, a, a, a lot of people
love you.
A, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a,
a, a, a, um, um, um, um, um, um, um, um.