In the beginning God created the heaven and the earth, and the earth was without form,
and void, and darkness was upon the face of the deep, and the Spirit of God moved upon
the face of the waters. And God said, Let there be the subgenius power of the Spirit.
Ah, and here in the holodeck it's so peaceful with this new nature simulation that you've
got going here. So nice, it's so real. The birds don't say anything, they just say,
It's on mechanical work. You could have left the garbage truck out. Well, I guess this
is what we're destined to become here. A mechanical response. A mechanically driven soundtrack.
And I just wanted to get my feet out of the water. And so you did, and then we were stuck
here on this planet.
Now listen carefully.
I don't want to be no human being.
Do you infer that I am not?
Things could be worse.
It sure could have been worse.
I understand perfectly.
Silence!
God is always on the side of the big battalions. If he was as committed to democracy as he
let on, I think he would have gone around as Bob or something. The story gets even funnier.
Bob. Likeable and not so likeable. He was actually in Denver, Colorado when the revolution
took place.
He rarely mentioned that he was Jewish. He was a genius at self-promotion. A true Mahatma.
He was also concerned with bowel movements. What intrigued him especially was the usefulness
of enemas. He had his young girls take a daily enema too. His daily greeting to them was,
Have you had a good bowel movement this morning, sisters? As this is a free country, you can
think what the hell you want.
The end.
Imagine there is no Starbucks. I wonder what you'd do. Can't get an ATM card and no
computers too.
What does that mean?
Imagine all sub-divis.
Living life in slack.
Imagine there's no modems.
And sitcoms on TV.
We'd hunker down in mud huts.
And take some LSP.
You.
You may say I'm sub-genius.
But I'm not the only one.
Gotta wonder if I'm really one.
What I'm losing out on.
Imagine no McDonald's.
And no Big Mac with cheese.
No email and no voicemail.
And no more songs like these.
Imagine the sub-genius.
Life without the con.
You.
Who-who-who.
Gotta wonder if I'm really one.
What I'm losing out on.
Eewa eewa eewa eewa eewa yeah.
Phineas and Arko did that dear friends.
And you can.
You can get a whole lot of amazing stuff.
Not by any means all sub-genius related.
From National Cynical dot com.
This is Hour of Slack number one thousand five.
A bit late because we were stricken by a new computer.
Donated by the wonderful Gription Clench.
And that and a week of the Starwood Festival.
And hours and hours of X-Day recordings.
Especially the live on stage radio sessions.
With Dr. Howell and Dr. Philodrummon.
The only part of puzzling evidence that was at 8X Day Drill was his teeth.
Which were auctioned literally.
So this Hour of Slack while informed heavily by Mr. Leemur and Reverend Preff.
Which we've already been hearing a lot of.
This show is partially recorded.
Auditory.
On location.
At picnic tables at an outdoor stage at Brushwood on X-Day.
And special thanks to Potter Nostril for the audio help.
And to Leemur devotee for the background music.
But first some Norrell Preff.
I need to go potty.
What is your problem?
So as a research experiment I committed myself to waterless embalming for seven months.
I'm more of a salt and grease person.
Over my dead body.
Fine with me.
What is your problem?
Nothing.
I just don't think I can wear clothes today.
I'm having more symptoms.
Take it down a notch.
You don't want to make love to me.
You don't want to kiss me.
You don't want to be in the same room with me.
That's not true.
Oh yes it is.
We have no faith.
Since when do we have to have a faith?
It's a waste of time.
There is no God.
Hit me.
Hit me again.
You're a rebel.
You're a freak.
Right now with all this shit going on in the world.
Art seems to be the only thing that's going on.
It's kind of besides the point, you know.
What is all this shit?
I need to go potty.
It's all this pressure to be normal.
So here's what we're going to do.
We're going to play Frankie Yankovic and Herbie Hancock.
How's that?
You are such a fucking rock star.
I'm going to have to go get my...
.
I'm going to have to go get my material, my...
Uh oh, I hear one of those ambient sort of loud...
Is that when I move my chest up in front of this?
Yeah, it's a recombined...
Huh?
Some...
.
Ooh .
Onto where?
timetable 매ير
lymphoma.
.''
.
I couldn't seem to focus.
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la.
Yeah.
Hee, hee, hee, hee.
Ha, ha, ha.
Shalakandala.
Demis soldier.
Oh, that one's not on.
I thought that was making that.
There.
This one makes the bad sound.
No, I think they all make.
It's, it's, uh.
They all make.
This one you have to hunker.
down for. You hunker down to this mic. And when you're hunkering down, it makes you talk
like you're hunkering down.
You hunkerer.
I'm hunkering. I'm hunkering.
The mad hunkerer has stricken me.
Get your hand off my hunk.
It's once again been stricken.
I'm hunkering.
Hunkering.
That is the hunkerly sound of the hunkerer.
Man, it's windy out here today here in the Dobstown compound.
You can hear this.
This is the virtual Dobstown.
The natives drumming in the background.
As they tap their frock pipes on the limbs and trees.
Trying to summon the energy to do something besides tap their pipes on the trees.
Mickey Mouse and Pluto to a movie stars in Disneyland.
Hey, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, it's a smooth X day.
It's a smooth X day.
Easy X day.
Each night we did our live radio show.
I wonder what he's going to do with that radio show we did.
Me and Hal.
Dollar bills.
LFT and .
We did a live radio show where we had, you know, mixing going on.
And we had a multimedia display we were commenting on while there was audience.
Oh, yeah.
We had a lot of people who were asking us questions.
We were allowing the audience to ask questions.
And then we would go into our, you know, multi-voiced, indexed voice transitional mix technology.
To which you listeners have become so accustomed.
And yet in New York it was something new.
Something new.
And they're revealed for the first time.
Live.
Not in the studio.
But actual humans alive together on a stage.
Brain and brain.
What is brain?
A brain allows one half-formed thought to pass.
Well, now that's done and I'm glad it's over.
When lovely woman.
Stoops to folly and paces about her room again alone.
She smooths her hair with automatic hands.
And puts a record on the gramophone.
Test, test.
That's a lot better.
I say, look at the geese walking in line.
Down the old road.
This music crept by me on the water.
And by the frog pond.
Where continuously they chanted.
Through the night.
As if welcoming.
X day with their velvet throats.
And then the secret chorus of the place chimed in.
The spirits of the fen and bog.
The naiads, dryads, pixies, gnomes, sylphs, trolls and undines.
All with their magic clatter added to the sound.
Until we had to undergo.
Glad day.
The tyranny of the sun's obnoxious effulgence.
And noon lay heavy on flower and tree.
And the weary day turned to its rest.
Lingering like an unloved guest.
Thy brother death came to me and cried.
Wouldst thou me?
Thy sweet child sleep.
The filmy eyed murmured like a noontide.
Be.
Wouldst thou nestle by my side?
Wouldst thou me?
And I replied.
No.
Not thee.
Death will come when thou art dead.
Soon.
Too soon.
Sleep will come when thou art fled.
Of neither would I ask the boon.
I ask of thee, beloved night.
Swift be thy approaching flight.
Come soon.
Soon.
And then.
Subgenius doctors from their hell or curled ship.
Shall broadcast their noxious message to the moon.
And all shall hear.
All who are in range to hear.
And learn what they should hear.
Nor learn too soon.
Hey, I've got a box full of towels under that hat there.
Ladies and gentlemen, we're still endeavoring to make every aspect of this broadcast palatable to your discerning ears.
Dr. Howell, those aren't ladies.
Those are two tripods with no cameras on them.
And that over there is not a gentleman.
That's Reverend Scull.
That may be as it is.
However, our standard must not vary despite the number of the crowd.
Absolutely right.
If no one is here to listen to us but Bob's dummy, we would yet do our very best.
But there are the rest of Bob's dummies.
I speak, of course, of the vast radio audience.
Who at a different and more enlightened time than this is hearing our broadcast now.
Thank goodness for these fine, fine donated equipments here.
They are the bodies who must willingly and joyfully cast themselves into the path of the rolling subgenius juggernaut.
So that their mashed limbs and freshly shed blood and lymph can lubricate its monstrous progress.
These are brave tapes, my friends.
Excuse me, Dr. Howell.
Dr. Howell, have you seen my scissors?
Your scissors?
I haven't seen the other half of your scissors.
Yeah.
No, I haven't seen your scissors.
I didn't know your scissors were down here.
But...
These were brave scissors and these are brave tape recordings.
These are brave times.
And stout tapes to hold these...
Maybe someone seized your scissors.
Your scissors have been snatched.
Don't get me wrong.
It wasn't scissors.
It was just a scissor.
Well, now you're being pedantic.
It was a scissor single.
Like a one-hole pair of underwear.
A single scissor as opposed to a pair of pads.
Well, can you not do with a knife or a stick or something else?
I need an implement.
But man, the maker of tools, the tool user and the tool maker, with these things he has conquered his environment.
And looked into the secrets of the atom.
Scratched the surface of the gleaming vault of heaven.
And penetrated impiously into the secret recesses of outer space with his mechanical devices.
Substitutes and succadenaeums as they may be for his probing fingers and moist fleshy organs.
Still, great advances are made into the inner space.
The ignorosphere of which we know nothing.
.
First things first
It's time for us to
Welcome the
Fall of night
And the pleasant comforting evening
Which shall surround us all
Covering our many misdeeds
And blanketing with softness
What by daytime might appear
Too harsh in the eyes of
Fretful subgeniuses
And so ladies and gentlemen
I, Dr. Howland Dowell
Am here accompanied
By Dr. Philo Drummond
Another resident
In these dark times of the left coast
Now brought all the way here
Almost out to the other sea
So that he and I
May speak to you
The hitherto hidden
Multitude of what is past
And passing and to come
This is Squatty Mike here
And speaking in tongues
Some not of this earth
Pastor Ivan Stang
The Stang of Stangs
Sits at microphone number one
Presiding over this strange
Hotch potch
Amalgam of a radio program
As the Supreme
Subgenius Presidium
Sliders and controls
Like Yertle the turtle
I feel master of all I survey
Now wasn't this turtle
The founder of a terrapin tower
Of terrifying height
As the old lady said
It's turtles all the way down
And so it is
Supporting our sad universe
The monstrous turtle
On which it rests
Rests on a still more
Monstrous Chilonian
All the way down to the bottom of infinity
From Yertle to Satan
That sounds like a good book title
It seems a shame to categorize
This lowest most turtle
As satanic
And yet
If it occupies
The lowest space
Down
Then perforce it must be
The most ill favored thing in the universe
It certainly won't be forgotten there
But it's a good thing
It's a good thing
Go placidly
Amid the noise and waste
And remember what comfort there may be
In owning a piece thereof
Avoid quiet and passive persons
Unless you are in need of sleep
And remember what comfort there may be
Rotate your tires
Speak glowingly of those greater than yourself
And heed well their advice
Even though they be turkeys
Know what to kiss
And when
Consider that two wrongs never make a right
But that three do
Wherever possible
Put people on hold
Be comforted
That in the face of all aridity and disillusionment
And despite the changing fortunes of the world
And the changes of time
There is always a big future in computer maintenance
You are a fluke
Of the universe
You have no right to be here
Whether you can hear it or not
The universe
Is lapping behind your back
Remember the Pueblo
Strive at all times to bend, fold, spindle, and mutilate
Know yourself
If you need help, call the FBI
Exercise caution in your daily affairs
Especially with those persons closest to you
That lemon on your left, for instance
Be assured that a walk through the ocean of most souls
Would scarcely get your feet wet
Fall not in love, therefore
It will stick to your face
Gracefully surrender the things of youth
Birds, clean air, tuna, Taiwan
And let not the sands of time get in your lunch
Hire people with hooks
For a good time, call 606-4311
Ask for candy
Take heart amid the deepening gloom
That your dog is finally getting enough cheese
And reflect that whatever misfortune may be your lot
It could only be worse in Milwaukee
You are a fluke of the universe
You have no right to be here
And whether you can hear it or not
The universe is laughing behind your back
Therefore make peace with your God
Whatever you conceive him to be
He is according nature
Come home,okes公平
To whoever cut his teeth
But will the things that you have
Nee showed up
To create a new mixture
But now it stops
And leaves nothing left
And how you un-myself
Bye.
Thank you.
and the Mondo Retardo band, of course, live at 8X Day, Brushwood, doing the Subgenius Anthem.
And now let us go back to Berkeley, California, to the puzzling evidence post-X Day cookdown.
It is a stoner, but it fixes you, little caller.
Okay, at the top of each hour, the station legal identification is read,
much like we did just a minute ago.
Because we don't, this is the new show, and we want to really live up to the expectations of the audience,
as well as the FCC, and the commercial public, even though we don't appeal to them, or even care about them.
To ourselves. We don't even appeal to us.
We're really into the whole, you know, whole kind of left, do everything for free.
Are you okay, and you're in that traffic down by the police station?
Student-sponsored radio, or listener-sponsored radio.
You know, there have to be, at least.
Eight cars in that mess right now.
There's at least eight cars.
They're listening to the show.
Call us right now at 848-4425 and 510-950.
Extra spooky monsters now appearing.
And let us know the name of, what was Gort's last name?
A lot of people don't know that Gort had a last name.
So would you call right now and tell us what Gort's last name was at 848-4425,
and we will give you a fine, fine prize the next time we see you.
Yeah.
Judging from the amount of brainstem activity in my pickup truck right now,
I'd like to say that I'm in virtual Chico, California.
You're where now?
Say it again.
Virtual Chico, California.
All right.
He's in Chico.
I can tell from the amount of brainstem activity in the back of my pickup truck.
I mean, what kind of place is brainstem California?
Brainstem activity.
Well, brainstem is a small suburb of Chico, Wyoming, California.
I gotcha.
We can hear you loud and clear on the satellite radio.
All right.
You're confusing us with the net web, are you?
You're not, yeah, not the universal media net web.
That was...
No, we're on both.
That's so...
That's somebody else's thing.
That's so 65 minutes ago.
Yeah, that's so...
Man, yeah.
Universal net.
Whoever.
We're on live Rhapsody Universal.
Yeah, Rhapsody.
Well, I...
They've been bought.
They've been bought and sold twice in the last 65 minutes on the Taiwanese market.
Man, show stock is...
That's the way it is in Taiwan.
The show stock is just...
All right.
Long live GOB.
Peace out.
Yeah, long live...
Oh, what's his name?
What's his name?
Bob?
I can really get behind a guy's name.
You know, there's one thing that really disappointed me about Doc's Doc.
I mean...
X Day?
X Day.
And that is that there's a group called the Bachelor's Four Bob.
Yeah, the Bachelor's Four Bob.
Shouldn't they be the Bachelor's O Bob?
I guess they should, but they're a bunch of youngsters and they don't know, but they were
really...
They don't know.
They were very...
I don't know what they're getting themselves into.
They were very honorable young gentlemen.
Now, did...
Was that 420 guy?
Was that the guy that was leaving?
Did I see him?
Maybe, because he often leaves now before the 420 moment.
Oh, well, all right, 420 guy.
Which means he's going to miss the beautiful young woman who will magically show up at
420.
Well, so should we go, like, do that thing now?
Do that thing?
Yeah.
At least I should.
I'm worried about Gort.
I'm afraid he might doodoo.
Gort?
But he's a robot.
What could he doodoo?
He could doodoo the Earth.
You must go to Gort.
You must say these words.
The self-genius power of sweat.
Ladies and gentlemen, I'm going to take the first photographs of the very strange gentleman.
We want work!
You'll be put to work baking loaves of bread for the rehabilitation of America.
Now, you guys, maybe you'd like to tell the crowd what we've got coming up tonight, whether
it's a possum roast or a hayride or any number of things planned by the...
Who's going to have us a rabbit supper?
By the reception committee.
We've got a barrel of rabbit sphincters back there.
I think there's the...
A tub of grease.
We're going to heat up the grease.
Yes, we're going to cover ourselves with bare grease and dance around the totem pole at
some time during the evening.
Try up the rabbit sphincters.
Why, you better tell them about that.
They skewer on fish hooks real well.
Wear them.
New jewelry.
We were going to have human fights where some of us would get so drunk we'd reveal that
we were really humans and not so geniuses.
Getting real big fights.
Well, don't let me hold you back.
No, no, not me.
I'm just...
I'm thinking...
You know, it could be anybody here.
Hope it's not me.
I suppose it could be me.
And there's a movie show.
Let's announce that.
The little nudie...
The nudie show?
A movie show.
It will be a special...
The nude movie show.
Triple threat...
Double header triple feature about two-headed folks.
First, the amazing two-headed transplant.
Followed by the thing with two heads.
And finally, the Japanese classic from Toho Studios, The Manster.
Also about a character with more than the allotted number of heads.
And so, you see three double headers in a triple threat triple bill right over there
at the Starlight Drive-In Theater tonight.
It's one of the many theaters.
It's one of the many things that's being offered here for your delectation and enjoyment.
So, you're saying the zombie fans should stay at home tonight, right?
The ones that...
Did anybody bring zombie pictures?
Looking for the shambling, hideous corpses?
Well, I think we see enough of those in our day-to-day interchange in the workaday world.
Yes, that's true.
That is true.
I forgot about that.
It's the pain of life's existence.
It's so hideous.
Living.
Each day.
How about shorts?
Has anyone got short subjects to show?
A glamorous short?
We do have plenty of shorts.
Well, there you go.
Yeah, there are Dobbshead shorts over at the Sales Shack, friends, which will be open tomorrow.
That's the most important type of shorts.
You can purchase these items and then take them here from this enlightened spot
and in more benighted areas hold your own subgenius.
I think I'm going to take a look at the thingamajig, whatchamacallit, doohickey.
No public authority has told us who are the overlords of the UFO.
Political analyst Bob was the first to reveal the CIA...
And Bob, and Bob, and Bob, and Bob joins me now on the show.
Bob, first, what's your reaction to the Supreme Court?
My lawyer said I cannot answer any specific questions about this.
I can't answer any questions about this.
Why is it that there are two reporters out there who may go to jail, Bob?
I will reveal all.
You don't know anything.
But I will, and there might be some surprising things.
Well, I'll be waiting to hear that story finally told, Bob.
Okay, so what we know is that there's a lot we do not know.
Hey, hi, how are you?
And we watched videotaped sex with him in his living room.
Slacks, slacks, go!
Blab, blab, blab, blab, blab, blab, blab, blab, blab...
Blabber, and before that, some Norelpref.
And we keep hearing bits and pieces of the Puzzling Evidence show from KPFA and Berkeley.
In fact, Philo.
Where can we get copies of that great show?
The show is going to be soon available.
It's actually available on podcast from KPFA.
Now, the KPFA has in their archive section, you can sign up for a podcast,
and the Puzzling Evidence Show is one of them you can sign up for.
We'd like to encourage you don't have to sign up.
You just click on the link, and you get the podcast.
So if you're on an always-on connection, you can go to the KPFA archive website,
choose Puzzling Evidence Podcast, and there you will be each week.
Voila, after the show, magically downloaded to your PC or Macintosh,
whatever device you choose, there will be your own personal Puzzling Evidence Show from this week.
Neatly packed.
Packaged.
Neatly packaged and ready for you to take full advantage of.
You can cut it up into your own special version where you take last week's show and this week's show
and mix them up and then play them on the radio to us next week.
In your podcast.
We think you should all, everyone should do their own edit of the show.
Yeah, I do.
Remixed edit.
I've noted that for many years, and we would all be listening to the show,
being reenacted.
Reenacted and re-hashed.
You could play the show on your mixer and then bring you into the mix,
just as if you were actually sitting here live with us in the studio,
and we weren't paying any attention to you like we do most of our callers.
Indeed.
So we would like for you to do that sometime.
Who are the overlords of the UFO?
Need assistance in finding your destination.
I'm hearing something.
They were very ly.
ALOY HAUST IRI Ching name.
Are you' re trying to falter for others
Let's go somewhere far away and we need our breathing.
Hey.
Someone had read something piece which for me,
not about shooting or death.
Oh,
And I've just received word that our forces have won a major victory.
The underground terrorist network has been destroyed here on the West Coast.
We are off crisis alert.
The situation is normal again.
On the show, sometimes we have to skip out and wander down the street and go,
La la la la la la la.
Because that's what you do in a band.
Down by the river.
I'm just going to practice for a little while here, okay?
What kind of button pushing is that?
I don't know, but that's some strange music you're playing there.
Paz.
Some people call him Paz Ave for short.
Yeah.
You mean out there in the hinterlands of X-Day.
Where they believe I'm a real person.
Who are the overlords of the UFO?
From PR News in Washington, I'm called genocide by the Bush administration.
President Bush has chosen to stay inside when possible.
Condoleezza Rice is praising leaders for ending decades of purgatory.
And the president of the United States, Donald Trump, is going to be the president of the United States.
Today's children.
Question after question.
She passes on.
Why?
And he died.
Why did he die, Daddy?
They die.
Why does mother hug this stranger?
Who is this?
Why?
Forcing Judy to kiss the stranger.
Uncle Harry understands children.
Did you and I were the baby?
What's this man doing?
Why?
Oh.
Now that makes sense.
Why, Molly?
Why, why, why?
What are you doing?
Why didn't you ask?
They died.
Minnesotans love the loon.
The hunting call of our loon is a comforting sound of home.
Minnesota has more loons than any other state.
Your donations to the loon fund on your state tax forms helps the loons.
The headlines.
Not.
You need a man on a mission.
Stops.
It was a good thing, and it was similar.
Political war strategy.
1-800-66666666.
The culture has gone stark raving mad.
Pornography and in gas stations.
Burn me up.
up pornography on the internet the teasers the pop-up ads and clarence thomas joined in on that
i'm really thrilled and i don't know and i've been involved you just swat at it cranks who
will whine against whatever or anything that's an exaggeration asses asses i want a righteous pet
store i want righteous plumbers i want a righteous pizza parlor hate governing officials and we do
in that they get obsessed but anyway we are now officially obsessed what what does that mean
cleaning accessible with a toothbrush and we're losing hey bob hey bob hey bob hey bob pro aborts
hi bob how you doing into you should always try to do that that's true right jesus couldn't pull
that off that's true right jesus couldn't pull that off biased biased biased and i'm so thrilled
to see pop-up pornography ads on the internet and that's
nice to see i like that thanks bob thanks bob now that's terrible that's what you get you get what
you hope for it's evil to say that owning black people looking the other way with rape or uphold
everyone's right to kill it it's broken they get obsessed there's a certain amount of of uh slack
porno show both parties live or porno show they don't know anything about slack here he is talking
about the spread
of slack porno show from pr news in washington i'm still going strong president bush wants 1.7
dollars to pay for air conditioning in stocks for 10 5 6 there are still few details about pr news
pr news by fernanda nandy lemur and before that lots of norel pref cut ups and you can get more
information about the pr news by fernanda nandy lemur and as you can see if you're watching this
this is the hour of slack from the morons of the church of the subgenius and for more on those
morons see subgenius.com or the book of the subgenius and for more on the everyday morons
just go to any bar i i really don't like bars you know everybody eats these power bars nowadays
when i take them i can eat about one bite of them and then i get really tired i think they're too they have too much stuff in them you know
They're too powerful for my taste buds.
I can't even eat a whole apple.
Wash it down with an AL-8.
Yeah, you know, I had so many AL-8s.
I think I've had enough.
I almost overdosed on those, Rocknard.
You brought, how many did you bring, like 20 cases?
50.
50 cases?
Yeah.
We had AL-8.
We were using it to swim in.
We weren't even drinking it anymore.
We were just swimming around in it.
We were cooking chicken in it.
We cooked chicken in it.
We really did cook chicken in it.
We just watered, we were watering the grass with it after a while because we had so much.
We had to take a bath in noodles.
It's just ridiculous.
Just totally ridiculous.
That's an ignorant.
It is.
The show is ridiculous.
It's an ignorant.
But the devil would have a representation.
You see some class.
Classes of the human family that are uncouth or rude and filthy.
Disagreeable and low in their habits.
Wild.
Priesthood.
So I give this lesson on the priesthood that you can understand its full effect.
And that we must beware and leave off their dress, their music, their styles, their fashions,
the way they think, what they do with immoral, filthy people.
The priesthood with immoral, filthy people.
You know we can't do that.
The priesthood needs an underpinningмуah.
I'd be a peace maker and fascist, so they'd give up drinking to summarise it.
Disc turtles arrested in Jersey west.
No matter what.
They put power on weather television and spy the world.
นนn Emday Nones الجr ass, I watch sollar.
Sobringen the land of peaceful
The slice ofusted streets, it's offence.
It's my land is home.
Un際be lukewarm
PR's fat.
The so-called NASA says no spindly robots popped out during the fiery re-entry in Orlando.
NASA was in Baghdad urging Iraq's astronauts to stick to PR news.
Washington.
Want it, want it, want it, want it.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
To overthrow George W. Bush.
George W. Bush there, there.
You are a terrorist.
Old and sick man.
Funding a terrorist-supporting group is worthwhile to achieve our political gain.
Pornography, adultery, homosexuality.
Seduce your neighbor's wife.
Duh, duh.
Homosexual marriage, in fact.
Dick, dick, dick, dick, dick, dick, dick, dick, dick.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Homosexual.
True bomb.
I'm a true bomb.
I'm a big fan of Dobbs.
Program, program, program, program.
Date, date, date, date.
Peep, if the...
Peep, peep, peep, peep.
Homosexual marriage.
People have the right to sin.
So you think...
Evil, terrible, monstrous regime.
But, Bob, here's my question for you.
Now, Bob.
Well, George W. Bush is willing to kill some children.
Crazy, crazy.
Bob, that's crazy.
A rapist.
The radical...
Down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down, down.
Rudy, Rudy, Rudy, Rudy, Rudy, Rudy, Rudy, Rudy.
Cheerleader.
Consider abortion.
There's a multi-billion dollar industry in pornography.
It's digitized.
Being sodomized by a homosexual.
You can...
You can come from a position of strength.
Just show reports here.
You know, I gotta fill out the paperwork.
Shows that the show was showing at the proper show time.
It's wet and cold out here.
Do I have to stay down here forever?
Well, until next X-Day.
If you're on the outside of the ship, you know, we really can't let you back in.
But I want to get back in my room.
I know, I know.
Yeah, you gotta wait 24 hours for decontamination.
Well, that's kind of a myth.
As it turns out, there is no decontamination.
There's no decontamination.
You just can't come back aboard.
I'm sorry, Philo.
I'm sorry, he's gone.
That's how we lost Philo.
I just wanted to show you that film before we got to the end of the show here.
Where Philo was on the outside of the ship.
And the next thing you know...
It was very sad.
To go to the next X-Day and...
There was no...
There was no Philo, no Ivan Stang, no Princess Wee, there was no Nikki Death Chick...
And scores and scores of other...
Beautiful people as we call them.
All gone.
Just because the end of the world had to happen.
I'm gonna go through the closet here and see if I can find...
I'm sure I had one of those pamphlets for the end of the world.
Let's see if it's here.
I think I got a new Philo too.
There's a stand.
I don't know if I can find it.
It's here somewhere.
Is it over here?
We will meet the Aetherians.
The overlords of the UFO.
When we are worthy.
Pop.
Puppy.
Boob.
Booby.
Bob.
Bobby.
Cock.
Pussy.
Shut up.
In a surprise ending, you'll see the answers...
To this incredible worldwide UFO.
The origin of the alien intelligences...
Who are the overlords of the UFO.
Bob.
reactive
POP
POPE
TOUP
P sod
ピ
POP
то