You girls have never been attracted to me.
I don't know why you girls aren't attracted to me,
but I will punish you all for it.
It's an injustice, a crime,
because I don't know what you don't see in me.
I'm the perfect guy.
And yet you throw yourselves at all these obnoxious men
instead of me, the supreme gentleman.
I will punish all of you for it.
Listen, for God's sake, listen.
Listen.
No! No! Why don't you listen?
No!
All those girls that I've desired so much,
they would have all rejected me and looked down upon me as an inferior man
if I ever made a sexual advance towards them.
While they throw themselves at these obnoxious brutes.
I'll take great pleasure in slaughtering all of you.
You will finally see that I am, in truth, the superior one.
The true alpha male.
Yes.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm much calmer today.
Not everyone is happy, as PR's report reports.
People look much happier when all the violence and shooting was taking place.
But there's just a lot of skepticism that this will solve tonight's TV.
So the Realtors Association says PR News in all parts of the country,
but the biggest was in Washington.
Stocks 29, 16, 3.
Singer-songwriter James Taylor,
who's pleading guilty to charges of possessing pornography,
says you're listening to PR News in Washington.
I wanted you to know what radio announcers are up against.
Feel sorry for them.
Send in a little something, whatever you can afford.
And now, friends, we have a time check.
And would you just fill in your own time, please?
Well, I took my sludge hammer and I painted it red, white, and blue.
Because in America, if you can afford it, you can do it.
I took my obnoxious alarm clock and I smashed it.
What an experience.
And it was really fun.
I liked that.
Thank you.
Do you know what time we're going to wake up Monday?
I don't know.
See, we don't either.
Thank you, Bob.
Give thanks to Bob, our eternal hope,
and praise me to Irwin, New Jersey's pope.
We're fickle and free and we don't make no fuss
at the Church of the Subgenius.
Bob, hear our plea.
We beseech thee.
Help us be free.
From normality.
We're dumb, devoted, and don't talk back.
Please give us an hour of slack.
J.R. Bob Dobs never fails.
He's the living slack master of mystic sales.
All you conspiracy doofs, just you wait.
Till July the 5th, 1998.
Invaders will come from Planet X.
Bringing gifts of money, time control, and great sex.
A new age will dawn and we'll never look back.
We'll be busy enjoying our slack.
Everybody now.
Bob, hear our plea.
We beseech thee.
Help us be free.
From normality.
We're dumb, devoted, and don't talk back.
Please give us an hour of slack.
He's the bridge between heaven and earth and hell.
He's the patron saint of sales.
Yeah.
He's doing well.
Media retins and novels and things.
Beware.
The slack master sells everywhere.
Give thanks to Bob.
Our eternal slave.
Bob.
We'll praise you to Owen.
We're fickle and free, and we don't make no fuss.
At the church of the subgenius.
Everybody now.
Give thanks to Pope, our eternal hope.
And praise me to Owen, New Jersey's Pope.
We're fickle and free, and we don't make no fuss.
At the church of the subgenius.
Give thanks to Pope, our eternal hope.
And praise me to Owen, New Jersey's Pope.
We're fickle and free, and we don't make no fuss.
At the church of the subgenius.
Dear Bob, I must give you credit for playing some good music,
but why spoil it with your stupid, asinine whistling?
Lock yourself in a broom closet,
while the music is on.
I'm disgusted, and from now on, I'll do my own whistling in the morning.
This is from Springfield.
Is there any lower form of life?
Let the record show that the witness may be drinky, drinky motion.
I still enjoy your program,
even though you've been back two or three weeks now.
Isn't that nice?
Here's one.
It says, Dear Bob, please don't pick any more winners.
I'm going broke.
And you bull thrower, how are you going to crawl out of this?
That's a nice one. I like the short one.
At least you get them over with.
And I heard.
Dear Bob, I had heard so much about you,
I was prepared to like you immediately.
I tuned in your show, and you talked me out of it.
Here's another one from Springfield.
Could you please give me the exact address in Washington, D.C.,
of the Bureau of Indian Affairs?
I've always wanted to have an affair with an Indian.
I'll see you in hell!
This is from Springfield also.
Stupid mailman, squirming.
Dear Bob, this morning you advertised boys' suits for youngsters aged three to seven.
You said they were trimmed with piping.
Piping in a boys' suit?
Wouldn't you think they'd be housebroken at that age?
Hang in there, Robert. Yours truly.
Here's another one.
Dear Bob, I was standing in the kitchen in front of my radio this morning,
pulling my two-way stretch over my hips when you said,
Are you a little on the fat side?
What I want to know is, can you see out here?
If so, I must dress somewhere else.
Good joke, Dobbsy.
Aren't you going to let me in on it?
In on it?
Sure I will.
Sure.
Yeah!
Oh, isn't it great swimming in a sea of slack?
Let's just immerse ourselves in the luck-plane's surfy, surfy waves and waft along.
Dr. Philo Drummond once said,
If slack was water, Bob would be surfing and you'd be drowning.
Hey, I'm willing to settle for death by drowning in slack any day, Doctor.
Ah!
This is a soundtrack for you.
I'm going to play a soundtrack to Mr. Lucky, which is one of Bob's nine billion middle names.
And you know, he's taught me that it's better to be lucky than good any day.
And what an example he sets.
I rejoice in the failings of Bob.
I exult in the slip-ups of Bob.
Hey, Bob, show us how you make a mistake and make a million dollars.
Yes, make me a failure too, Bob.
Show me the witching ways of surfing the luck-plane.
Look, Bob, I can hang too.
Oh, and when Bob forgets to screw up.
Oh, when he screws up by not screwing up.
It's like breaking the bank at Monte Carlo.
It's such blinding, radiant luck that you can't believe it.
You appreciate the good things in life if you don't waste your time counting on them to happen.
But if you expect the bad things to happen, you can't do it.
Every day can be like Christmas.
Just forget yourself and go with a path of least resistance.
Sharpen your abnormality focus.
You might do only one weird thing exceptionally well.
Well, take that weird thing and turn it around and milk it dry.
Milk it for Bobby.
Tap it.
Strip mine it.
There's strip mining your slack away,
leaving toxic poisons to leech into your psyche.
You're a psychic water table.
Fight the conspiracy.
Give up for Bob.
On and off the road to Bob
We are marching forward blind
He has gouged out both our eyes
And he's laughing close behind
He will sell us back our eyes
When we join his noble clan
For just nineteen ninety-five
And a taste of our woodland
On and off the road to Bob
He has handed us the wheel
And he cuddles up with fun
As he counts himself a field
Our eyes are off the road
But Bob is still a boy
And Bob forgot to say
That the steering wheel went bust
The road carries us away
All those popular kids
who live such lives of hedonistic pleasure
while I've had to rot in loneliness for all these years,
they've all looked down upon me every time.
I tried to go out and join them.
They've all treated me like a mouse.
Well now,
I will be a god compared to you.
You will all be animals.
You are animals.
And I will slaughter you like animals.
I'll be a god,
exacting my retribution
and all those who deserve it.
And you do deserve it.
Just for the crime of living a better life than me.
Oh, you popular kids.
You've never accepted me.
And now you'll all pay for it.
The sermon tonight is entitled
Are You a Terminator 2?
Yes, Fritz.
Tonight's sermon is solely dedicated to the latest and greatest film
by Arnold Schwarzenegg...
Arnold Schwarzen...
Well, his full name is too offensive to say,
so let's just call him Arnold Schwartz.
As many of you already know,
the complete title of his latest movie is Terminator 2 Judgment Day.
They put Judgment Day in the title
so all subgenies would know this is a film about us
and the end times.
Because we know that come Judgment Day,
everything normal will cease to exist.
In fact, every normal will cease to exist.
Only the excess will exist
and those select few chosen to carry out their duties
will carry out Bob's wrath on a sick and sinning world.
The subgeniuses,
the excess occupational army of Earth,
the chosen race of which is bestowed the duty,
nay, the privilege,
of exterminating all the normals.
And what gives us the power to carry out this admittedly gruesome task?
What gives us the authority,
let alone the desire to kill first and laugh later?
Even while I speak,
the answer flashes before audiences every hour,
in every city,
entertaining millions with graphic premonitions of their own death.
It's not a subliminal message,
far from it.
It's so damn obvious few normals can even figure it out.
And that's the beauty of it.
Who would ever suspect that the subgenius blueprint for revolution
would be disguised as a summer blockbuster movie,
let alone a sequel?
Bob said they'll pay to pull the wool over their own eyes,
and so it has come to pass.
They think it's a movie about them,
if only they knew.
It's about them, all right.
It's about killing them.
And why?
If you're stupid enough to miss the movie,
you're certainly stupid enough to miss the point of the movie.
So as a pinko public service,
allow us to explain it to you.
Terminator 2 is about the conspiracy.
Not now, but in the future.
In a future where every subgenius is hunted down and exterminated by cyborgs.
Computerized, robotized, humanoid,
that look suspiciously like the same rednecks and stiffnecks
that are running society now.
Cops that club the tar out of taxpayers,
like in the Rodney King golf tournament.
Bodyguards that smash voters like you and me
whenever we get too close to important people,
like Ted Kennedy and his brother Dan Quayle.
Society in the future looks exactly like society in the present,
except for the billions of rotting corpses that litter the landscape
thanks to nuclear Armageddon at the hands,
or should I say buttons, of machines.
Now you probably think,
whew, at least we have time on our side.
We're nowhere close to cyborgs these days.
Heck, we barely have robots,
let alone robots that look like humans.
Wrong!
Look around you now.
How many people do you know that are really human?
Oh sure, they all look like humans.
They all go through the motions of humans.
They have extensive files on proper human behavior,
but,
try to get them to act human and see what happens.
Try to get them to deviate from what society has programmed them to do,
and see how far you get.
You'll be surprised, dear friends.
Stand on a corner during rush hour and ask for some simple human compassion.
Good luck!
You'll see the march right on past,
just like ants teaming their way to work.
Get in the way and the soldier ants appear,
ready to pick you up and haul you down to the prison chambers.
These may not be computers,
but they damn sure ain't people.
They're a combination,
man and machine.
The worst traits of both mixed together in a lethal combination of cold and calculating logic.
They know their mission.
For some, it's data entry,
working all day at the terminal.
We call them terminal cases.
For others, it's data retrieval,
patrolling the streets for deviance,
cleansing the system of errors and arresting viruses.
Eventually, the incurable ones are terminated,
hence the name Terminators.
Now, future Terminators operate much the same way,
only they're more efficient.
They don't waste time arresting the deviants or trying to cure them.
They simply kill them, Johnny on the spot!
There's plenty of Terminators in training that wouldn't mind taking those shortcuts today,
believe you me.
So as you can see, we're well on our way to a Terminator tomorrow today.
But alas, dear friends, it shall not come to pass.
Alas, for the conspiracy, there is another, darker future in store for us.
For them.
An alternate future in which the Terminators are the ones that are terminated.
A future where the subgenies revolt and take back that which is rightfully theirs.
The entire world!
Humanity will cast off its chains,
and the servants will become the masters.
Machines will be returned to their place as our slaves,
instead of vice versa.
No longer will we plod through the years,
clocking in and out of life,
wearing ourselves out like miscellaneous cogs
in some giant corporate machine.
It's payback time!
And guess whose turn it is to fall down on their hands and knees!
Bow, you pico-normal computer conspiracy collaborator!
Lower!
LOWER!
So we can hack off your head with one foul swoop!
You had your chance to join the counter-revolution, and you blew it!
You sold your soul and sealed your fate with your conspiracy co-sponsor!
The subgenies don't need you anymore!
You're just polluting our air!
Get ready to die!
Unfortunately, that time has not yet come.
Independence Day won't be here until July 5th, 1998.
In the meantime, they could be mean to us,
but the clock is ticking, dear friends.
Time is running out!
If you want to save yourself, you must be saved by Bob!
You may feel unworthy,
and you may think there is no way someone as good as Bob
can spare someone as loathsome as you.
But don't give up.
After all, one of the heroes of Terminator 2
is none other than ex-conspiracy dupe,
the original Terminator, Arnold Schwartz!
That's like taking Satan himself back into the fold!
Now if Schwartz can join the anti-conspiracy crusade, so can you!
No matter how mechanized your life is now,
it's never too late to fight for freedom!
Indeed, the moral of Terminator 2 is this.
You can be designed by the conspiracy,
you can be built by the conspiracy,
you can even be programmed by the conspiracy,
and yet, you can still fight the conspiracy and win!
But you alone must decide, dear friends.
So which are you gonna be?
An Uncle Tom devoted to upholding the system?
Or an Uncle Bob dedicated to crashing the system?
The choice, dear friends, is yours alone!
Here endeth the word of our praise, Bob! Amen!
I hate all of you.
Humanity is a disgusting, wretched, depraved species.
If I had it in my power, I would stop at nothing
to reduce every single one of you
to mountains of skulls and rivers of blood.
From PR news in Washington,
I'm stabbing and slashing early this morning.
Obama's struggling with mental illness.
We never seek help.
Obama says it's impossible to eliminate PR news.
First Lady Michelle Obama is believed to have gone down in the southern Indian Ocean.
President Obama told mourners,
you're listening to PR news in Washington.
Obama told the families to sue.
About two million years ago,
the earliest man walked upright on the land.
And that creature was lonesome cowboy.
The man was a boy named Dave.
What are you talking about?
We were talking about you, Dave.
Were your ears itching?
You sound so small and far away.
Really?
Yes, really.
Well, I'm right here.
You sound close.
Yeah.
I sound lovely?
Almost inappropriately close.
Gosh.
I had no idea you felt this way, Dave.
Well, you sure are a garbled mess.
I can hardly understand a word you're saying,
but I could tell you one thing for sure.
In that murder spree today,
I think it could be a plot by the Chinese to manifest organ harvests and stuff.
Really?
I assume that it was a plot by...
I assume, like, whenever any crime happens,
I always assume that Obama ordered it to make gun nuts look bad
so that he can take all our guns away.
Actually, that conspiracy is true.
That conspiracy theory is already being kicked around.
It is instantly.
As soon as anything goes wrong.
It's always all Obama's fault.
Well, it is.
I have to do the credits here.
Let's see.
Well, that's why you...
Well, the preaching there was, of course, the great Papa Joe Mama,
although he was a little tasteless at the very beginning,
but, you know, not everybody...
not everybody has the same taste buds.
Susie the Floozy did the coll...
Susie the Floozy did the collage work about Bob
that was originally broadcast on her show,
Bob's Slacktime Funhouse,
heard on WREK Atlanta,
as this show is.
And, um...
Oh, Reverend Bleepo Abernathy did that song
on and off the road with Bob.
And, of course...
Complete with the frauds burping.
Pardon me?
Complete with the frauds burping there.
Yeah.
And we heard also some clips of that pink boy,
Elliot Rogers,
who decided that since girls didn't like him,
he'd kill them all.
And he even screwed up at that.
You know, I had to...
I was...
As soon as I heard that guy's rant,
his video that he made before he killed all those people,
I thought, there's some sentences in here that...
You know, when Papa Joe Mama says it,
or when Legume delivers it,
it's funny.
And it's also well delivered.
But when a pink boy like Elliot Rogers says it,
it's not funny, and it's...
It's simultaneously lame,
bad acting, like in a Disney villain character or something.
And, you know, it's just...
I was thinking of this, too, man.
It's like a socio-evolutionary thing.
This has gone from satire of a world which exists right now.
And people don't understand that.
They think they're...
Because there are so many of these people now that...
They're the object of the satire.
You know what I mean?
No.
Of course you know what I mean.
The church is based on...
Well, it's not really based on a satire of this world,
which exists right now,
because it's existed for so long.
Well, we just always assumed that the world was a satire of the world.
But can't you see what's clearly in your face right in front of you
and why you're being persecuted by the Roman legionaries?
But see, here's the thing, Dave.
I know how that kid felt, sort of,
although I wasn't a spoiled Hollywood rich kid.
And I also wasn't as good looking as that guy.
However, I didn't...
Also, your parents didn't call the police three months ago
and say you've lost your mind.
Well, I didn't...
Don't, never mind.
Although I had trouble getting a girlfriend, too,
I didn't blame the girls or want to kill them.
The only person I wanted to kill was me.
But I'm a subgenius.
And you wanted to eat bacon.
It's against the law in subgenius land to kill yourself,
because it's...
It's dumb, because it's an...
You're an amateur at it,
and Bob or God are going to do it anyway all too soon.
So what's the hurry?
It's Bob's job.
Trust a professional.
That's God's job.
Yeah, and as far as killing the others,
well, obviously, we're going to let the aliens do that.
There's no point in us running around being ninnies
like these crazy pinks that go off their rockers.
You know, there's a big difference between subgenius and crazy.
That is, well, or is there?
I'm not sure.
Mal-aligned normals are not the same as a subgenius.
Right.
We might sometimes be all full of hatred for the others
and think it's not fair and so forth.
And, well, that's when you go tear up your picture of Bob
and throw darts at it and go,
Why'd you let me down, Bob?
I trusted you.
I believed on you, Bob, and you let me down.
You know, so kill Bob.
But if you go out just randomly shitting people,
half of them might be deuce-paying subgeniuses.
Probably not, but...
It's an anecdote, but it's also an anecdotal pudding
because it's very, well, it's sacrificial in enough ways to get by
as far as the great mythologies and everything like that.
But mainly, you get to purgate yourself of all kinds of other sins
just by beating the hell out of them.
Well, the face of Bob.
Right.
If you know what it means.
Well, a lot of us keep a scarecrow of Bob.
You know, I have one.
Princess, we and I have it.
I think it's sleeping behind our couch on top of one of the radiators.
It scares every guest that comes into our home.
I have a dangling punching bag, which doesn't refer to a hernia belt or any kind of...
What did you say?
What?
You have a Prince Albert?
I don't want to hear about that, Dave.
I'm old.
No, no.
I have a Prince Albert.
I have a punching...
Sorry.
I have a punching bag with the face of Bob on it.
Right.
Well, we use this dummy of Bob, which was expertly built by Dr. Le Guin 20 years ago
or something.
Back when he was a super artist and tradesman, craftsman guy, he's making those
little delicate ovaries in the Russian egg baskets, you know, Bob's face popping out
each one of them.
Oh my God.
I just thought...
And drink vodka from them and throw the glass in the fireplace and go to Slavonema
or some kind of stuff.
That's what we used to do.
Yeah.
I just thought of something I never put two and two together until now regarding
that Bob dummy and its creator, Dr. Victor Frankenstein Le Guin.
And that is that, okay, when Le Guin made that Bob dummy, he loved Bob.
But after a while, he was like, I don't know.
I don't know what to do with it.
And then after a while, he got kind of tired of the whole thing.
And remember, he and Chaz had it sitting in Camp Tiki Banzai and they'd shoot arrows at
it.
They'd use it for target practice.
They were sexually abusing it like a love doll and stuff like that.
Right.
Remember that cult?
Remember the cult?
The NYP or the state boys showed up and wanted to ask questions and answer.
Well, that guy just wanted a t-shirt.
But the point is Le Guin decided, okay, Stang's going to be taking this Bob dummy home.
I'm going to do a little bit of heart to it.
I'm going to do a little heart surgery on it and leave a surprise.
And he opened up the shirt and stuffed some raw hamburger inside the Bob dummy's chest
and then sewed it back up.
Now, his plan was foiled because pot or nostril tattled.
But here's the thing.
Okay, Le Guin thought it'd be real funny to do heart surgery on that Bob dummy.
What happened to Dr. Le Guin?
Five or six years to the minute later, Dr. Le Guin had found himself in an operating room
getting his chest broken open so they could replace two-thirds of his heart with a machine.
So you go stuffing hamburger into your Bob dummy, pretty soon some doctors can be stuffing hamburger into you.
That's like voodoo doll karma or something.
Yeah, it's a sad kind of karma.
By the way, I don't believe in karma at all.
Or dogma.
But, because life isn't fair.
If there was karma, I'd be richer now and so would you.
Well, I think the pity and the crime and the shame and the discompassion, the argument is
that that was actually an art project by Zoltan Fizetula.
That was actually an art project by Zoltan Fizetula.
Like many years before where actually they replaced the heart area of the
dummy with uh some hamburger
and then after a little while maggots would start to crawl out
even though it was closed up again.
And they would create this like living artwork
and then they would go in with the three-in-one glue, the elmer's glue and stuff
and they'd freeze it.
You know, that's how David Lynch got started.
He was mentally ill.
There's a lot of that going around.
He was. He is.
Well, he isn't anymore because he has money now.
And he can act out his insanity, or not act it out, but direct it out.
Yeah, right.
Turn it into a TV show.
Yeah.
Wrapped in plastic.
Yeah, therapeutic self-expression.
Talking about art and self-expression, Dave,
have you ever heard of the photographer, artist, name of Spencer Tunick?
To refresh your memory, he convinces cities full of people to pose nude.
Right, exactly.
You were a participant once, weren't you?
Well, he did do a photo shoot in Cleveland, but we didn't attend.
Some friends of ours did.
Yes, we have friends.
And they said it was really cold.
It was really, really cold.
And he's had people show up, naked people in Sweden or somewhere in Scandinavia,
pose on a glacier, for instance.
So, imagine my surprise when last week, Princess Wee and I opened a letter from Pappy.
That's my Pappy, Pappy Stang in Stangsville, Texas, which is a small town.
And this is his music in the background, by the way.
I copied the CD for him.
Pappy's music?
Yeah, this is him playing in the background.
Anyway, Pappy said,
Dear Ivan, I was contacted recently, yesterday,
by a man named Spencer Tunick,
who wanted to talk to me about a proposed mass nude photo shoot in, we'll call it, Stangsville.
I asked him why he'd chosen me to contact,
and he said he'd talked to some people in Stangsville,
and all of them, allegedly, suggested he'd call me.
He said that apparently everyone in Stangsville said it was something funky to call human Gormry Stang.
That's his name.
What he wanted me was to get a bunch of Stangvillians, which is idiots, together,
get them all nude in a public place and photograph them.
I told him I could get two people together to go nude, but probably no more than that.
He said, in that case, only one would be enough.
Have you ever heard of this guy?
If so, tell me what you know about him.
He looks sane, but I'm not so sure.
He says this,
This is art.
Should I support or sponsor this person for such an event as art or porn at all?
Please advise.
And we called him up and said,
Pappy, that guy's really famous.
He said, oh, I've never heard of him.
I said, well, that's because you're concerned with more important things.
But long story short, he was putting us on.
He was yanking our chain.
He put on the old put-on artist.
Yes, he put on here.
And, you know, it took me a day to piece together that it was me.
I had sent him a documentary about Spencer Tunick called Naked States about six months ago or a year ago.
I totally forgot about it.
So I set myself up for that one.
But that letter was completely convincing the way he...
The way he worded it, as if he was ignorant about all of this.
It was easy to believe.
That's our Pappy.
It runs in the family, I guess you could say.
Well, you have years and years and years of sexual transgressions to look forward to.
Just thanks to those genetic, that passage.
Well, he's a lawyer by trade.
That's where I get the lying.
B.S.
Yeah.
The lying.
The bull manure.
Right.
And the manipulative, you know, nature.
Although a lot of subgeniuses are much better...
I'm sorry.
What?
I just had to say this.
Well, anyway, we all sound like our Pappies, I guess.
I probably...
I never did meet your dad, but I always assumed that he probably just was a craggier...
version of you, which is pretty damn craggy.
He likes to do accents and imitate other people.
Really?
Yes.
Well, that's revealing.
Yeah, my father liked to criticize other people.
And I was an embryonic...
I was an embryo when my mother was playing a large bass fiddle in a swing orchestra.
So, there's a constant thumping sound in my head.
It just won't go away.
It's just...
I think it's maternal genetic.
Well, your guitar playing is certainly good.
I can hear you playing...
You're just playing, chunking along in the background there.
Yep.
It's important.
I'm like Chet Atkins or something.
...from the ancestral homelands of Norway and Sweden.
Places where, you know...
Well, where you come from, they give the family name first.
That would be Lonesome, right?
Right.
The Lonesome Clan.
The Lonesomes.
And it was originally pronounced Lona-Sama.
But they had to anglicize it when they came to Ellis Island.
And they were put in a totally different part from all the other immigrants from Eastern
and Southern and Western Europe and stuff like that.
We're all...
I was going to ask what kind of a name is that Lonesome?
It's Crypto-Pomeranian, I think.
But I was confused about some of the...
They said, you know, they were real poor.
And then they were, well, they were rich, but they had to get out of town.
And I heard all kinds of stuff.
And I guess one of them was born with like one huge eye in the middle of their forehead
and stuff like that.
He was a carnival guy for a long time and rode around in the Studebakers and the Tinker
trucks and everything like that and helped people pound stakes to put up carnival things.
But you're not the last of the Lonesomes or Lonesome-es, are you?
Because you've got...
You've reproduced somehow.
Yeah.
You've got a lot of...
Well, I was...
I'm not sure how you people do that.
I don't want to...
I'm not asking you to explain it on the radio right now.
Well, we do more than lay our eggs on the water, if that's what you mean, and just come
along and spurt on them or something like that.
There's a very...
Hey, careful, man.
We're on the radio.
Oh, yeah.
But I'm going to get into the wedding clothes and stuff like that and procreage and how
you gain a wife.
When you gain a wife, it's like considered a material asset.
And that's why their parents are...
Parents have to give you a store and a vacuum cleaner that actually works sometimes.
That's the law?
And a lawnmower.
Wow.
Because you've got to have one of those to live in America.
And you want to learn to speak English real good and know the names of the people who
had big, weird, bulbous growths on their noses and on their foreheads, like in George Washington
and those guys.
And every boss.
They were controlled by the aliens.
That's another name.
Boss.
Well, they knew more than Bob's name.
They knew his address.
That's why they got into so much trouble.
It's not as if a guy that age in those times of constitution, they were wearing brassieres
around everywhere and arguing in public squares about gay marriage and stuff.
Well, they're not arguing about that in North Dakota.
But that's the last place that they aren't arguing about it, apparently.
Oh, it's just had to do with the tribe.
You've been talking to tribal elders again?
The tribal elders on Fox News were saying that that guy shot up all those people because
he was gay.
I thought, wait a minute.
I thought that he was so...
Such a frustrated heterosexual that he shot all those people.
Yeah.
No, no.
That's what repressed gay people do.
Oh, I see.
Uh-huh.
I don't know.
Well, that was the first conspiracy theory that popped out on the mass media was that,
well, obviously he's a repressed gay person.
That's why he killed all those girls and boys equally.
And then it was more like, well, no, it was obvious he was a sleeper Manchurian candidate
guy personally programmed by Obama like all those shooters are.
Oh, yeah.
Everybody's personally programmed by Obama.
In fact, actually, they've...
The real secret...
The secret...
The serious conspiracy scientists don't believe that these mass killings even happen at all.
That that's just something they showed on the television and that no one killed anybody.
It's all special effects and movies.
Photoshop.
Yeah, like the hologram planes in the World Trade Center.
Well, actually, this particular shooter's dad worked in Hollywood.
And I noticed that in the course of one hour, the spin on his...
The dad went from...
He was a second assistant director on Hunger Games to he directed Hunger Games.
Thanks, Obama.
So once again, you see the hand of the Kenyan trader everywhere.
In tornadoes, in hailstorms, in...
All of those things are fake too.
None of these things...
Nothing bad ever actually happens.
But the media makes it all look bad to keep you in fear all the time.
And it's all been engineered by Obama, right?
Everybody thinks...
Well, he doesn't have to hands-on do it because the Hollywood elites all kind of do that automatically.
Ah, okay.
You've heard the old journalist joke.
They just do that in their sleep.
I see.
They lie in their sleep.
Yes.
You have heard the old journalist joke, it's a free press if you own one.
Right.
Well, I own one.
So I'm not worried.
I can publish anything I want and I have done so.
You're free to print what you want.
Somebody's quoting the Bible at me and I said, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Isn't that a book?
Yeah.
Anybody can write a book.
I've done a book.
In fact, I've written a Bible.
In fact, some people actually believe it.
So don't tell me this is any kind of big trick.
Anybody can do that.
You are a potential prophet.
Of course, you already perhaps are a prophet.
I mean, I don't want to mention any books that were dictated by any archangels or anything
like that and have any backgammon games erupt on me or something like that.
But you certainly do pass as some sort of, I don't know what's the word, not a prophet.
A proofreader actually is what I am, Dave.
A proofreader?
Bob wrote these memos, but his grammar and spelling are atrocious.
Well, Bob is a prophet.
So basically Philo and I just kind of corrected his spelling.
And we did it.
We added a few things ourselves to his holy writ, and I wish we hadn't.
One of them was anti-music.
We said, oh, everybody who can't play an instrument should be in a band and play anti-music.
I've never been so sorry for something we put in a book.
I hate anti-music.
I even hate it when I'm playing it.
But boy, we sure have gotten a lot of tapes of that stuff over the years.
There's no little teeny tiny little squirrel tail of artistic bizarro in you.
You love melody above all things.
Is that what you're saying?
No, I'm a clerk.
A nutless chimpanzee could do my job, to quote the Hollywood author.
That is the best.
If he was patient.
That's the problem.
A boom day.
Numerous subgeniuses have not been able to do my job because they weren't patient enough.
They got too fed up with all the other subgeniuses really quick.
Which is why I'm not on Facebook.
So I don't have to get fed up with my best friends real quick.
As long as I don't talk to them, they remain friends.
Everything's fine.
Yep.
You told me one time that you were getting into too much trouble with people that you had previously forgotten.
But haven't you ped around with them?
Who?
Well ...
Catch my cold before dead.
Darn it.
You're 20 years and later than me, and you're saying, I was born asked to solve the problems
Because I've never lived ENT if I was in the dark.
Wow.
But is that how it goes?
Absolutely.
So you didn't have to go back and forth.
You could talk with any of the people there.
I think you've already had a microbe set-up there.
And your meeting with  quickly turned the professor from videos floor to floorflare
How is that related to  foram?
Because childhood.
Since life really comes to an end, a certain practice over time, you talked to involves
set on fire instead of me,
throw him in the swamp instead of me.
But no, every year they set me on fire
and throw me in the damn swamp.
The sacrificial labral sobs.
But I shouldn't complain
because that's the only day of the year
that I have to get up early.
And it's the only time I have to take a shower
at the end of that day.
I don't know.
Some of them weird get-ups you gotta wear.
I remember the one time when you was wearing
the Archbishop's miter.
It was like four and a half feet tall.
And you had those like Korean Zen master shoes
on the bottom.
And it did elaborate like kabuki uniform.
And it was like the little Mr. Pope's man
from grade school.
The Pope suit is not short.
It's too long.
And what you saw was me stumbling
through the mud in a Pope suit
trying to hike the skirts up
so that I wasn't tripping over
the rope.
The sacred robes.
My Pope suit was actually made
for a taller Pope.
And we've...
We did take it.
You did take it up last time.
Because I had used it for a marriage.
I performed the wedding
of Potter and Petal Nostril
wearing that sequined
Pope outfit.
Made by
Catherine Cartwright Jones.
Or Reverend Bunny.
She used to be a Playboy Bunny.
Did you know that?
I bet you did.
No, I didn't.
Because you don't even know
who I'm talking about.
Well, I could imagine
because you said she was
a Playboy Bunny at one...
Well, you said it one time.
So now I can imagine
something else.
Right.
Yes.
But she...
Yeah, she was...
She also made theatrical costumes
and they made a...
She made a sequined...
I mean, this is a Pope outfit
suitable for the village people.
Well, she made theatrical costumes.
Absolutely.
I made idiotic comments.
Idiotic comments.
Everything's got a verb
and an adjective
and going...
I'm sorry.
Dave, are you playing
the piano in the background now?
I'm playing...
Did you switch from the guitar?
This is actually
a little tiny spinet.
A little...
It's part marimba
and part rigged up together piano
I've got going at the studio here.
I'm working on building
some new instruments.
And this kind of closely
resembles a piano.
A keyboard, you know, obviously.
But still, it's got
a little bit more of a...
a marimba, you know.
That ancient
clickety-clang-clang
thing going to it.
I'm amazed at anybody
who can play music
and talk at the same time
even if they're only talking
the way you talk.
It's still really amazing.
I mean, just...
Just think of
Chico Marx or Harpo.
Well, Harpo didn't talk
while he was playing
but just think of Chico
giving three-hour-long dialogues
while he...
See, you made me
miss a note there.
I'll say I was
rather now.
I can still talk about stuff
and try to be real brilliant.
Let's talk about...
Oh.
Okay.
Well, that was all
I had to talk about
was the pink boy
mass murderer
felt so sorry for himself
because the girl...
You can tell why nobody...
why he couldn't get laid
because he acted like
he was better
than everybody else.
He also had...
He had real affectation
about the picture, doesn't it?
The way that he spoke
and the way that he moved
his lips and everything.
He was really
very affected.
I really felt sorry for him.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Like a bad Disney villain.
Yeah.
A corny Disney villain
at the end of his...
It's like...
And you will all pay.
Yeah.
That was the crappiest laugh.
That was the crappiest
mad scientist killer laugh.
He is no...
Elliot Rogers,
I knew Hannibal Lecter
and you, sir,
are no Hannibal Lecter.
They should bring back
crucifixion for guys like that
or something.
Or no, wait,
I heard somebody saying that
the other night.
Right.
In Oklahoma,
they're already doing that.
Well, their injections
don't work so bad.
They just bang on you.
They nail you to a stick
until you die.
It is an iron skillet
to the head.
They were talking about
bringing back firing squads
in Utah.
Yeah, they don't even understand
the art of firing.
I remember the old
school.
They just put a gun
on Gary Gilmore's eyes
and they stopped doing it
for a while
because of all this
the social protests
of the idea of like
putting a target on somebody
and wasting that many bullets
when all they have to do
is just like
maybe throw a hand grenade
in there in the room.
Of course,
that doesn't always work either.
I'm against it,
I think,
because,
well,
I don't like most people,
especially bad people,
but...
But you don't want
to get arrested.
Otherwise,
you'd probably go
on a shooting spree, right?
You just don't want
to get in trouble.
Oh, no.
No, no.
Isn't there a lot
of collateral damage
with a hand grenade, too?
Well, I don't really feel
that angry at society at large.
I think it's probably
the ruling class
we have more to worry about
than the idiot next to us
in the line at Walmart.
Ah, yes.
No, but see,
this guy didn't like...
He was jealous
of the idiots
in line at Walmart
because they were
holding hands
and making out.
Even if they were obese
and kind of crippled,
they were still, like,
had love
and he didn't have any,
so they must die.
If I were of a different
shape and size,
I would look at that picture
and I would say,
the cat's a demonic man.
Like, he's not really
ever been a normal kid.
He's like...
He's been in therapy
since he was eight years old,
so, you know,
take it from there.
Oh, I got beat on that one.
They were taking me
to see the doctor
when I was five.
What is wrong with this kid?
He's not aiming for the head
when he's throwing footballs
and stuff.
It's, you know,
to be that young
and have big dark circles
under your eyes
and your stomach growls
real loud
and, like,
your fingernails are real long
and you, like,
teacher tells you something
and you turn around
and scratch and hiss
or whatever.
Oh, I know.
I know.
There is no escape
from this hostile planet.
And, uh,
as the amino acids said,
and they are going to be
playing at X-Day,
also at the X-Day drill,
the Rolling Stones,
Pussy Riot,
Led Zeppelin
is getting back together
for, uh,
X-Day,
and, uh,
a Blue Man group
is coming,
Penn and Teller,
uh,
but, uh,
but I don't know.
I can't advertise
this kind of thing, you know,
because this is a public...
What?
Especially since the Stones
are going to do it for free.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, they all do it
because they love Bob.
It's, you know,
we could never afford
to pay any of these people.
Well, maybe Richard.
That's right.
I mean...
But Jagger,
it's all,
it's all about the money
for Jagger.
I mean, Richard's into Bob
and, you know,
he's got the Bob tattoo
and everything like that.
Well, I mean...
He's the hero
of the average,
average guitar player
of every generation
from, you know,
what, just,
urinating my pants.
But how, you know,
the thing is
they need to stay cool
and Jagger knew
that if he was, you know,
seen at X Day
and reported
at being at X Day
and not taking money
that, you know,
that would help,
help him keep his, uh,
his cachet
of coolness.
Yeah, his cachet.
Keith Richards
is just there for the froth.
Yeah.
He doesn't care about Bob
either that much, but...
He does, he does like
to climb the trees
because he's, you know,
a socialist environment
where there's plenty
of arboretums around.
Down there's beautiful
200-year-old trees
and Keith Richards
has been known
to climb these trees
after hours of arguing
with carbuncles
about his drug damage
and how, like,
he really cares
or something like that.
Well, he's still
in good enough shape...
You gotta get him down, you know?
He did make the news
for falling out of a tree, right?
Bumping his head.
But at least he can still
climb a tree.
Most of the people
I know that age
can't climb a tree.
No.
No, there's too much
neurological damage
thanks to the fukushinas
and the, um,
the nasal drippage
is probably
the major problem
with thousands
and thousands of people
right around here.
Whereas Keith
gets and wakes up
every morning,
gets to take a hit
off a, uh,
a morphine inhaler,
which is the best way
to do it, I've heard.
Yeah, if you,
if you've got, like,
false teeth,
you, you really
have to make sure
that they're not
sending signals
in the ones that are, like,
got the phony, um,
fillings in there
because artificial teeth
shouldn't have
fillings in there.
So if you look
at your false teeth
and there's, like,
these little, you know,
looks like little metallic
tiny little spots...
Then that's a transmitter.
It's a transmitter
and a receiver, too.
Right.
That's where the voices come from.
Which is what made,
you know,
so I was wondering
if the kid,
maybe if the darn kid
actually had, uh,
transmission damage
from false teeth,
but he looked like
he has all his choppers.
Hmm.
Repack the instruments
and prepare for takeoff.
We will continue
our search
in another solar system.
Good luck, boys.
Good luck, girls.
Now, the amino acid's
heading off
to look for
intelligent life
in another solar system.
I don't know how the hell
they would know
the difference.
Yeah.
The mean old acids.
Ha, ha, ha.
Uh,
there's usually, like,
punks with prostate problems
or...
No, that's not, um,
punks with pacemakers,
punks with a pulse.
Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta.
Ta-ta-ta-ta.
Yeah, I was playing
punk rock.
Uh,
uh...
Dave,
you were in some kind
of a punk rock band,
weren't you?
Yeah.
Or was that just
a rock and roll band?
No, it was, well,
there were arguments
in the band
and they called
different things
power punk
and power pop
and stuff,
and we were
definitely dubbed
as New Wave,
I mean, uh,
New Wave.
Uh, New Wave,
yeah, that's right.
Are you guys,
what was the name
of that band,
the Clock Radios?
Because less people
threw beer cans
and spit on us.
They didn't always do that,
but sometimes
there would be, like,
the art crowd
where it's just
black leather jackets
and you didn't throw
your beer up on stage
and spit on people.
Right.
What was the name
of the band?
Strawberry Alarm Clock Radio?
There was,
there was, uh,
Radio Alarm Clock,
which was originally
the clocks,
and before that
was Chronix,
which came out
with a, uh,
45 called, uh,
Test Tube Baby,
um,
when the first
Test Tube Baby
came out,
and it was, um,
Bleeker Bob's
pick of the,
for about 10 years
running.
Wow.
It was really wonderful.
They had dinner
and a dance,
and, um,
I was forced
to expose myself.
I mean, at least
the damage
that had been done
during the before.
Well, that was part
of the job, right.
Yeah, and that's how
the lawsuit all turned out.
They weren't gonna pay
everybody at one time
because, you know,
not everybody had to have
the same kind of
droppage
or whatever you want
to call it
when they remove
half your body.
I'm glad I was never
in a punk band
because I,
I didn't like,
I would have had
to get a haircut.
Yeah.
I, I would have,
if I was gonna be
in a band,
I'd be in a hippie band
where I didn't have
to get a haircut.
Yeah, you'd also,
you'd have to wear,
like,
yeah,
you'd have to wear,
like,
of this generation,
you'd have to wear,
like, a, um,
a button-down shirt
and stuff that was,
like, ripped
and stuff like that.
And then you'd put
a, uh, toothpick
through your nasal cavity
through your nose
and stuff like that.
Ow.
But I never did that.
I had a mohawk haircut
for a short while,
but I was thrown out.
Did you really have
a mohawk, Dave?
Did you really?
You are out of,
you are out of school today
and don't come back tomorrow.
I believe Dave had a mohawk.
I can't,
I don't believe Dave
ever had enough hair
on the top.
I do.
I had a mohawk
and I even had
a rockabilly pole bucker.
I had, uh,
sideburns.
Wow.
Sideburns.
And a, and a big, like,
you know,
it's Vestian cone,
like, whippy dip
coming out in front,
like an ice cream cone
or something.
Or like in Leningrad Cowboys.
You ever see that movie?
Like,
about the weird, uh,
band that comes to America
from a small border town
of Russian and
with ice cream cone hair.
I didn't see that,
but I read the cliff notes.
He's funny.
How is Mackie?
He's funny
unless he's dead now.
No.
Is his dad shunning us?
Carlos Mackie.
Carlos,
Carlos Mackie?
Yes.
He's, he's
Finnish director.
Comes up with
kind of funny movies
that you have to be a
European to get him,
though.
Oh, I bet our friend
Mr. Sister
knows all about that.
I bet he does.
I was gonna mention,
speaking of, uh,
of, um,
this ancestors
and descendants,
he's been into
genealogy
and we figured out
why he's so interested.
He's, he's close
to proving that he's
the true heir
to the crown jewels
of Sistarvania.
Yes.
Which is like
some obscure corner
of the,
between Poland
and Transylvania
or something.
Yes.
Everyone there
is related to him,
but he's, he's
a direct descendant
of the rich landowner.
Yes.
And they had a palace.
So he's,
he's, um,
he's working on
proving that he's,
um,
actually the crown prince
of, of Sistarvania.
And, uh,
just as I
will someday prove
that I am the heir
to the Russian throne
of the Romanovs.
Yeah, the Rachmaninoffs,
the composers.
No, no, no.
The Romanovs,
the, the Tsar,
the Tsar's family.
I thought there was
a kind of
I'm not, I'm not
a blood relation
to Tsar Nicholas,
but I,
let's put it this way.
Um,
the Tsarina
uh, uh,
Alexandra
and
my great, great, great,
great, great, great
grandfather,
Rasputin.
Well, they kind of
hooked up.
Oh, I see
which side of the family
that comes from.
That's where the Stangs
come from.
Yeah.
You've never heard
that story?
The unreported children
of Rasputin
and ladies
in Zarnina,
Starnina,
Delaware.
Yeah.
Ivan Stang
is the rightful
Tsar of Russia.
Ah, the wistful smile.
But you know what?
They do the Tsars
in Russia,
so I'm not going
back there.
Well, you're not going
to get any of that
property back.
They already turned
it into a gymnasium
or something like that
or they already
tore it down
for a parking lot.
And then they
wouldn't even know
who the hell
you were talking
about anymore.
Right.
Except for maybe
some old lady
with a babooska
might want to
beat you up
or something.
Right.
Yeah.
Okay, Dave.
Dave, it's, um,
where we are
in terms of
time control,
we have to,
I'm going to have
to fade you out
in about 10 seconds.
So what do you
have to say, Dave?
What do you have to say?
What do you have to say, man?
Well, I just think
everybody ought to,
you know.
Come on, come on,
tell us.
Come on, come on.
This is important.
This is your last time
on the radio for a week.
Everybody has too many desires.
They should give them
all to me.
Spit it out.
And I'll take care
of them as long
as I can.
What?
Okay, Dave.
Bye.
Wow.
Look, he voluntarily
got out
real quick.
Wow.
That was horrifying.
Never seen that happen before.
Me either.
Okay.
Well.
I'm out of here
and we're listening
to the amino acids.
Great job.
We'll be right back.