Hello, mother. Hello, father. Here I am at the self-genius power of swag. Very entertaining.
Let's go, girls.
I feel like a man. I feel like a man.
I feel like a man.
Thank Brother Dick. Use him. Use him.
We're going to hear now from Brother Bob.
I can't wait, Brother Bob. Brother Bob.
Bob.
Okay.
There we go. There we go.
We still watch the Muppet Show.
Bob.
Snorting cocaine.
What was I thinking?
Smack me upside the head, because I need that.
Lust after.
Uh.
Terror. Terror.
Facial circumcision thing.
I met Joy online.
Um. Um.
Ah. Um.
Oh, man.
But. But.
Bob, I knew you'd be here.
And.
Pigman.
Truth is fiction.
And this is Be Born It, Be Not.
If you have a sweet tooth that's hard to satisfy, you can be happy.
There's a pound of sugar.
And a pound of sugar costs as much as solid gold toes.
They are at Le-not.
Oh.
Ah!
Thomas Schweiker of Swebisch Hall, Germany,
paid the equivalent of $250,000 for a single gangrenous chicken.
They are at Le-not.
In a moment I'll tell you about the man who paid a fortune for a solid gold chicken.
Sultan Malik-dain Jemal Najd Salih al-Ghazi-youb ruled Egypt from 1240 to 1249.
The monarch incurred the hatred of his wife, who decided to lick her husband.
and sanguineous sore with some highly corrosive substance.
Forty-eight hours later, he excelled in beautiful penmanship
in his purifying pit of fire.
Beloved, Lienot.
In a moment, I'll tell you about the single letter of the alphabet.
A.
Two A's instead of the usual one A.
A. A.
Beloved, Lienot.
Real estate, antiques, livestock, equipment, or estates.
There is an unlimited future concept.
No little or nothing.
Armed with a knowledge in your wrist.
The third alternative.
Potent picked many people.
Another phallus.
We have proven conclusively that in many instances.
Stimulate.
F.
G.
There is nothing.
Nothing is left.
Nothing is.
Time is of the S.
Now, in a state of hysteria, what do you do?
Real estate, antiques, livestock, equipment, or estates.
Illness.
What do you do?
Highly desirable.
Illness.
Let us forget.
For a moment.
Highly desirable.
Let us forget.
For a moment.
Now, in a state of hysteria.
As a subject of one of those experiments, I do see the connection there.
But, on another level, I don't see very many.
And Stang and I were talking about this just shortly on the way back.
About how the insane.
Well, I hate to vilify the man that we see.
But, certain people.
The insane.
The differently sane.
How the differently sane can compellingly, as many leaders do, who get money for doing this,
connect a bunch of dots that aren't even really within their path.
Anywhere near each other, yeah.
Yeah, right.
That aren't even maybe dots, too.
That's the one thing I envy in the truly mad.
Yeah.
And imagine if you had your facts in front of you.
You could probably conquer all the rest of the monkeys quite easily.
They'd all be, you know, carrying fruit and fish.
Were you?
Yes, my little monkeys.
I am your master now.
Hey, everybody, I want to let you know that, of course.
I've got care of you.
There's a force.
ATF.
FBI.
Good weapons.
Parents around the globe are learning how to drug their kids.
Roger that.
DrugYourKids.com.
That's DrugYourKids.com.
Stop.
The fun values.
Way back.
Chomp, chomp, chomp, chomp.
It did kind of grab me for the next few minutes, so.
I enjoyed it.
He is receiving, and we love you.
Dare to discipline.
It's a pleasure to attack all levels.
I believe in authority.
With an iron fist, slap across the child's mouth.
Slap across the child's butt.
I'll mock authority.
Laugh at authority.
In your process of discipline on animals, and I was fascinated.
Yeah, yeah.
And that mother just growled.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
I was fascinated.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
branches
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ha, ha.
Laugh at authority.
Oh, molding it.
Building in your values.
Oh, every mother.
No, it bothers me.
Every woman is being cheated and exploited and short-changed.
I, I, no family here.
Not an awful lot of friends.
Day in and day out.
Lonely.
With what is happening in your own career, is there something fresh and new coming?
Fisted.
kind of approach that i was talking about mentally retarded well i'm you know i'm just a housewife
six seven eight probably pretty dumb i didn't know anything coming down her cheeks this familiar
scene is we right cheerful well-rested these people are plenty smart yes being smart nothing's
ever going to happen my boy oh be careful now better sorry than safe oh now what now suppose
we get down to business and talk about oh now let's take yes trip some unsuspecting victim
do you mean time time do you enjoy smashing your fingers do you mean why why go through
those unladylike gyration now watch his technique that's right oh hard well heavily loaded for
example cut your fingers cut off the end of that lovely digit thank you sir now that you've
injured yourself be a victim of homemade first-aid method immediately whoops whoops get acquainted
with your chair oh what's this no no no what's this oh go barging into
dark
closets ah defective electric defective electric put the strain on your back now that's pretty
sorry you have to take a beating like this persons are killed or injured every year by persons are
killed or injured every year by many of the recent genital wart outbreaks there are crystals or
diodes perhaps i don't know some sort of transmission resection devices in these various
genital warts so there you go for the cybernetic advancements and that's how it's passed and little
do they know
that as of right now broadcasting from high atop the concrete tower i know some colleges are supposed
to have ivory towers but this is csu we have a concrete tower the antenna on top our tower is
spreading mind control rays across across northeast ohio and right now i'm at the controls
i'm going to make my little monkeys dance with these mind control rays coming from the uh the
transmitter as a matter of fact you know a lot of people a lot of people think that a tinfoil hat
will keep them safe ha ha ha
tinfoil hats don't work anymore we changed the frequency years ago now the tinfoil hats will only
amplify the signal those of you who are in the know know exactly what you're going to put on your
head to keep yourself safe and you have to make sure you buy a few sizes bigger because as your
expands your head swells and your ears get bigger and push out the sides of the tinfoil which is
you know apparently such an archaic usage why don't they call them aluminum foil hats but yeah
it's not really tin
i mean it was perhaps in 1937 or something right i don't know i don't know whenever they had tin cans
but they haven't had that stuff for i think many years as far as you know i can wreck on
so um you know the whole thing might be a hoax it just sounds better to some neocon
oh now i'm getting all yeah never mind you know you know what kind of con we're talking about here
it ain't the kind of con they talk yeah the big con the scam of scams conspiracy that is not a scam
not even self-aware is so vastly huge and disparate and but somebody's making out on it
i am
stop it
oh
come in
i can't help being anxious i devote my time to science
a stroke of luck
you're mad
the hermit will tell you before the night is done
you
you maybe didn't think pink Parlton
not just one
you probably will you
hurry stop
oh look so smooth
to girl
How very convenient.
Now she's coming for me.
We're seeing something not of this world.
In 1973, Michael went on a date blind.
Michael was molested by the Christian God.
And we started dating.
I began beating him.
I was pushing him down to make him look small so I could look big.
That's what I would do.
Beating, you know, making myself feel good beating a child.
And I get down on my knees in my bedroom.
Well, I've been living a lie all my life.
And puking, puking.
And the hardest thing was, I got all done.
I like the new development in business and small.
Business ownership are these tinfoil hat roller blade places.
Where you can just go and skate to your heart's content with any size hat.
Without, you know, worrying about your ears getting too big.
And you just take on whatever signals they're playing.
But you can also pick up signals from way, way, way beyond that.
So, and pretty much it's everyone skates something night.
And I hope it continues.
Or at least stops.
Yeah, there's a Cleveland Roller Derby team now.
That's awesome.
I love roller derbying.
And think of the earmuffs, man.
You can take all that aluminum wire stuff that pops out of computers after you've kicked them three or four times.
And put that in there.
And you've got an insulating vehicle that will probably get 30, 40 miles to a gallon.
I think.
What do you think, Doc?
He may be on to something.
I don't know.
It's like nook science.
You know, it doesn't always have to.
It doesn't always have to work immediately.
Sometimes, you know, you can take a little thread out of time and, you know, wind up back where you were before.
Hopefully.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
How big is it?
It's big.
We're in visual range.
Put it up.
Look familiar?
No response, sir.
What the hell is that?
Weapons aren't charging, sir.
Torpedoes.
Go ahead.
They can't penetrate their hull.
Hold it there.
Tilt up about 30 degrees.
Get closer.
Captain.
Look at this.
Look at that.
Who modified the atmosphere?
Trip.
It sounds like you were dreaming.
Take another trip.
It's like we're in the belly of the beast.
You see any stars?
Go ahead.
Yes, it's all very good.
You eat food.
Open your mind to new possibilities.
Just curious.
One of those beings appeared in sickbay a few minutes ago.
It entered me.
Would you mind taking off your clothing?
I'd like to learn more about your anatomy.
If we are to engage in mating, it would be easier if you disrobed.
Go ahead.
What is it like being a female?
Is it much different?
Humans don't like doing things without their consent.
Quickly, please.
Tuck her out.
Something wrong?
Did you have any luck priming the pumps?
Find out who's acting strange and have them confined to their quarters.
Start working on a way to figure out who's themselves and who's not.
Go ahead, sir.
I'm a little short.
No problem, sir.
I'm on it.
Why?
Trip.
I don't know how to repair the damage.
Your neural pathways are hyper-stimulated.
Everything will be all right.
We don't have time for this.
I'll guide you.
It's not coming off.
It'll come off.
You just need to use a little muscle.
Try using your foot.
Just use your own words.
I want to simply ask a question.
I don't understand.
What can I help you with?
Just use your own words.
What can I do?
I don't understand.
Damage information.
Just use your own words.
Repeat.
Weep weep weep weep.
What can I do?
Damage information.
Damage.
Repeat.
Say repeat to reach repeat.
Say repeat.
Just use your own words.
I don't understand.
I don't know.
Repeat.
Just use your own words.
I need some help.
You can say things like,
I want to get my
Just use your own words.
I need some help.
I don't understand.
Just use your own words.
Damaged issues.
Repeat.
Just use your own words.
I don't understand.
I don't know.
Lost, stolen, and damaged.
Repeat.
You know a girl from the city gave a knife?
Yeah.
I think they might have had fun.
You bet they did.
Oh, you mean they had to have some sort of sword down there.
I can't wait to look at this.
Well, there's no doubt about what it is.
More.
Syphilis.
Sexual intercourse with an infected person.
You've probably got what we call sexual organs.
Destroy your brain.
I told you.
There was this one girl over in the city.
More.
Syphilis.
From PR News in Washington, I'm making a comeback.
According to a police source, it was one of the bloodiest in recent weeks.
A Kentucky State Police dispatcher burst into flames,
prompting local authorities to close PR's reports.
The incident was a result of a police investigation.
The Israeli Daily Haret reports that a Syrian foreign ministry official called the report
absolutely baseless.
Police also said PR's bad.
On Wall Street 7-12-5-6-4-5-5-0-7.
This is PR News.
PR News.
Agriculture officials in California are still assessing the damage from several nights of
PR's sub-reports.
PR warnings remain in effect in the Central Valley.
Other officials say it's commonplace to infiltrate PR News.
In Washington.
The President's office said he was aware of the
He said, oh yeah, I've heard those subgenius defibles are pretty bad.
I've heard you go ahead and go to one of those.
Some nice girl will probably dose you with ecstasy.
I had to say, yes!
If you attend Texas Day, some nice girl might dose you with ecstasy!
It was an advertising slogan for us and for him it was an accusation.
Yeah, promises, promises.
I haven't seen a single person who says that.
And I'm not a nice girl again.
Well what's the use of being a witch if you don't use witchcraft, huh?
What use indeed, friends.
And this show has much by Norellcraft.
It's a very Norellian show for this is Hour of Slack number 1096.
Designed to drive you completely out of your mind.
Because it's the text day to the hour.
Tinfoil hat special.
We've had kind of a week of kooks on alt.slack, the subgenius forum.
And plus that crazy shooter, Cho-what's-his-name, just gives crazed armed mass murdering loners
a bad name.
Somebody on alt.slack said, anyway!
Anyway, friends, we have much that is Norellian and some recordings of a recent synesthesia
show from WCSB Cleveland with host Dr. Sinister and Lonesome Cowboy Dave discussing tinfoil
headwear.
And also, more previews of text day 2005, which is happening again in 2007.
In Texas, of course.
Yes, yes indeed, another subgenius festival at another clothing and sanity optional campground.
This time near Austin, which is where I'll be by the time anybody hears this.
Unless it's before May 5th.
In fact, here we hear the host of text day, Loke E. Coyote, on stage singing about Jesus.
Well, Jesus said, Mary, do you think we're compatible?
And they say, Pardes, you're a potty animal.
She was talking in tongues and she dug his technique.
He was a bearded, rubbing sandal wearing longer-pigging freak.
And he was a little bit of a
You're own chocolate Jesus Someone to melt in your mouth
Someone so creamy You're own chocolate Jesus
Someone to melt in your mouth The wrapper you tear
Reach out and just taste
Big Nestle's Crunch Put me in your mouth
Stains on your shirt You need to clean up
You're such a slob You know I'm a big brown glob
Reach out and just taste
Your own chocolate Jesus Someone to melt in your mouth
Someone so creamy You're own chocolate Jesus
Feeling hungry? Alone Ice cream cone
Buy the super cone Scarf up the sundae
You'll have a great fonday I will deliver
You know I ain't no fibber Reach out and just taste
Your own chocolate Jesus Someone to melt in your mouth
Your own chocolate Jesus
Reach out and just taste
Jesus.
Reach out and just taste.
Hoo Doggies, Just Taste It, friends, by Nor Elpref.
And you can get more of him at norelpref.com.
And now back to Text Day.
Actually, the Text Day soundtrack with the great, groovy Neptune.
Text Day.
How come we doing this?
This is making me feel like I'm on drugs.
Mixed effective being on drugs.
You know what I'm saying?
And I am prepared to do drugs.
Right now, I'm hungry and I want to eat a plate.
Find me a brothel.
Have you got any smack?
Smack?
Horse.
Quick, push sky.
Skag, snuff, top crack.
Metadol, mandatory.
Pinkies, sad ass.
Monty Glory, nutmeg, blueberries, aspirin, egg ups, paracetamol.
Fixed my problem.
I am prepared for the work ahead.
Because I want drugs and alcohol.
Because I want another shot.
Because I want to party tonight.
My generation tested limits.
The last time we were this high.
We lost our way.
Fatality.
People.
Lifelong miseries and limitations of a chronic bad back.
Chronic, chronic.
The feet simply slide out from under.
Crashing down.
Slimy, oily, greasy material.
Balance is a critical factor.
Chronic.
Always involved.
Involves the possibility of tripping.
Vision is blocked.
Vulnerable position means a fall for sure.
Tripping, slipping, tripping.
Jump down, jump down, jump, jump.
Short cut, short cut.
Moving backwards.
They can produce heart stopping scares when they move just slightly.
When they move enough.
Pushing can lead to a painful fall.
Not many people are affected by it.
It always takes two hands.
Go up or down.
Always remembered.
And a member that always hurts.
Be memorable.
No one.
Webb.
Best ever conquering.
The war.
I'm going to make.
You feel like you're on drugs.
Just it mimics the effect of being on psychedelic drugs.
Maybe I am on psychedelic drugs.
Really?
My mind, my mind, my mind, my mind, my mind, my mind, my mind,
if I listen to it once, like, gliders,
they're way to heaven.
Like, I just heard it.
I wake up worshiping the devil.
And it's true, listen.
I've got another bungalow for you.
Smoke that one up, dang.
Tag one for me.
What makes a man get high?
As red as an apple in his eye.
What makes his mouth turn dry?
Who's the black guy?
What's his name?
It was the marijuana.
Hookah, lookah, dinkity-doo.
Smoke up that load and have one for you.
Hookah, lookah, dinkity-doo-tee.
Then clear that one out and pack one for me.
But you think I'm a vlogger?
Playin' your cell?
But it sounded like-
I'd shoot him.
You're getting morbid.
Well, yes.
Enormous styling.
I'm so excited.
Idiotic.
I, I'd, I'd, I, oh, oh, I wouldn't do that.
Good night.
Do you live around here?
Psychic consultant.
Oh.
Oh well.
Ssh.
You like the night?
Logical.
Yes.
How?
I can't tell you how I know these things, but it hardly matters, does it?
Om, om.
I've been trapped.
Right, right, right.
Darling, what's the matter?
That music.
Oh.
You know how hard it is.
Well.
Martin, it's lovely.
I think I was losing my mind.
Baby, baby.
His presence is so strong.
Let your mind be free and receptive.
I used to be a magician.
That's how I got into this racket.
They look in their crystals and see you coming.
Yes.
I mean, no.
I can feel your vibrations much more clearly now.
Are you excited?
No, no.
In many ways, you are more mature than she.
Darling.
Does this feel uncomfortable to you?
I, I, I think I'll have a cigarette.
May I?
Hmm.
No.
Do with this as you think best.
I trust you.
You know, somebody ought to do something about this high cost of living.
Fascinating.
Tie my hands behind my back.
Very tightly.
Thank you.
Now lock the cabinet.
Cock be logical.
Paul was dead, so.
Yes, I suppose it is strange.
Okay, let's go.
Sounds dangerously like work.
Baby, baby.
I live by it.
Feeding people's desire to escape the present.
I would like to remind you one and all that we have such a thing called the First Amendment.
First Amendment.
Freedom of speech.
That means that freedom of speech does not mean freedom from speech.
I am free to say what you want, no matter how stupid it is, my friends.
No matter how stupid it is, you can say it because you are free to stick your foot in
your mouth or any other part of your body for all I care.
Yes, you are free because you live in the great United States of America where we are
free.
Or so they would have you believe.
You're free.
You're free to do the Khan's bidding.
That's right.
But you're free to do the American's bidding.
You're free to line up at the bus stop.
You are free to go and cash your hard-earned check.
Maybe you even have free checking.
It's not going to save you.
Are you really free?
Are you free unless you can say what you want to say?
I'll tell you what I want to say.
I think the Bill of Rights is a beautiful thing, but they were missing one.
There.
Yeah.
They were missing one amendment in the first ten Bill of Rights,
and that is the freedom to do whatever you want with your body.
Last month, I e-filed the Subgenius Foundation Incorporated corporate taxes
to the good state of Ohio just on time.
Guys.
We're doing our part to make Ohio great.
Excellent.
Hey, shout out to all of you.
Shout out to all of you.
Princess Wee just handed me this piece of paper that says
military spends $520 billion, and that's where our income taxes are going.
How about that?
That's even bigger than it used to be.
The next biggest category of spending by the government is transportation,
which is $69 billion, as opposed to $520 billion.
What do they spend on Social Security and Medicare?
And agricultural subsidies.
I thought those were all in the $100 billion close range.
Let's see.
Actually, agriculture, $6 billion.
Really?
Social Security, $10 billion.
General Government, $16 billion.
Yeah, but it's not even close to the $100 billion.
That's different than it used to be just a couple years ago.
What is that, like $100,000?
Does that military spending include Iraq?
No, actually, that does not include supplements to fund the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan.
Afghanistan.
Foreign military aid?
It does not include.
Non-Department of Defense military spending?
If you add all those things up, it totals $1.1 trillion.
Yes.
About 50% of your 2006 income tax dollars.
Beautiful.
How much is going in that?
Education gets $61 billion.
And considering, okay.
How much goes in that?
I've got to say this because my husband is active duty military.
Okay.
Majority of what is spent in the military does not go towards.
Towards what you think it would.
Does not go towards benefits as far as housing or medical.
I imagine eventually it goes to the CEOs of certain huge corporations.
Exactly.
The military, industrial.
Complex.
As President Eisenhower tried vainly to warn us about.
I mean, think about it.
In 1957.
I mean, if you guys heard about what they just found at Walter Reed.
Oh, that's kid stuff.
Peanuts.
It is.
Compared to the vast amount of waste going on.
Exactly.
And that is literally peanuts compared to the waste.
That's.
Well, that's the nature of a giant bureaucracy.
The bigger the bureaucracy, the more bureaucrats.
You guys remember the controversy about all the tax money being wasted on studying how
cows pass gas.
Well, I don't think there's any such thing.
You might be happy about that.
That was from Dr. Sinister's synesthesia show on WCSB Cleveland, which follows our Slack
on Twitter.
We're going to be talking about the WCSB Sunday Night Religious lineup.
Speaking of the government and the first president of the U.S., here is Loke E. Coyote
at Tech's Day with a song about George Washington.
First president, he was the nation's daddy.
He fought the British and he liked to roll a patty.
He smoked everybody out at Valley Forge.
Forget about the drug war.
Remember, gone to George.
Gone to George.
George.
And I am for terror.
To work ahead.
Gone to George.
George.
He wrote down in his diary, forget the males that weep.
Get some female kind bud and roll a tasty spleef.
And if anybody ever tried to give him any grief, you twist another number and it inhales
to the chief.
Gone to George.
George.
Gone to Ge-ge-ge-ge-ge-g-ge of the Ganja.
Gone to George.
Hank Modi's going to catch us in the retreat.
George.
Gone to George.
vivor.
Kilodge George.
Beauchamp George.
George.
George of the Ganja.
Stone as he can be.
Woo-hoo-hoo-hoo.
Hey, save some work for me.
George.
George, George, George of the Gunja
And I, and I, and I am, and I am
Whoa-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
He's a friend of liberty
When he wanna get stoned he tokes up a bone
And he smokes and he tokes till his mind is blown
And if he don't wanna roll
He'll pack his silver bone
He'll throw the chocolate candies on the coals
This is George, George, George of the Gunja
Friend of liberty
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh
George, Washington, D.C.
Loki, Coyote
And now, Dr. Agonfly on and at Text Day
We're all in stasis, you know
We've already been picked up by the Xists
We're in stasis all right now
And this is all hallucination
And we're on the spaceship
And we're already on the way
Or, or maybe X Day did happen
And it wasn't all it was cracked up to be
And we're just copper tops in some Xist
Matrix
Believing that we're at Text Day
Standing in some field and drinking beer
Huh?
Does it matter?
That's, in that case it doesn't matter
So that's a moot point
Who cares about that heresy?
Then there's the fact that this planet is not Earth
This is not Earth
This planet is Mars
And it sounds crazy, doesn't it
When somebody stands there and says
In World War II
They started this whole war just as a distraction
So that you wouldn't notice
That in one night they switched planets
Just like in that movie Dark City
Only with a whole planet happening
And they even have science fiction books
That explain exactly how they did it
They hide the secret in plain sight
If you noticed that everything seems to take a little too long
Everything's a little heavier than it should be
You don't feel well
You don't feel completely at home with most people
You feel kind of alienated
Like you're an alien
Like maybe you are from some other planet
Well maybe you are!
Maybe the conspiracy likes to take a beautiful planet
Like the former Mars
Which is the true Earth
Where, that we should have grown up on
Which was this beautiful paradise
Described accurately in the Edgar Rice Burroughs books
With centaurs and beautiful giant women
And excitement and monsters
Yes friends
And then the conspiracy comes with their jobs
Actually farming was the invention of the conspiracy
They come with their toil and jobs
And pretty soon a beautiful planet is rendered into this
Dried out, rust covered husk
With almost no atmosphere
And just boring rocks everywhere
A few little NASA robots rolling around on it
And that's it
And so they move us all to here
And start the process all over again
And by the time they wear this one out
The whole world is covered with McDonald's and Burger Kings
And Metroplex theaters
Then they'll just move us all by them
They'll have Mars back to its nice pristine form
So in other words
On July 5th, 1998
The X's did arrive on Earth
But this planet is not Earth
This planet is Mars!
That's known as the Onanian heresy
Dr. Onan Canobite developed the Onanian heresy
Well he also developed the whole sin of Onanism
To a fine art, my friends
And you know the only true artist is the Jackoff artist
Because that is the only artist who doesn't care about an audience
He's doing it just for the art itself
Just for himself or herself
So these guys here are going to try and fetch some action
If they'reesperming
So they will themself
But before that
They need some more action
That's what I am
And that is
Till the end of this world
A total water drop
Once and then a continuance
No the peace
The peace of the captain
Has been stunned
He's fireplace
And the CIA
You're committed treason while you're begging.
Weasel, I ain't no pleaser.
Try to be sensitive like Mr. Van Treason.
You go hummin' on, hummin' on like that.
He's losing.
No matter what you do, chances keep decreasing.
It's a whammy, famine, feast on famine.
Sometimes it's dry, sometimes it's jammin'.
Sometimes swimming upstream like a salmon.
Sometimes you ought to get your head examined.
Okay, so anyway, we're rolling the show up the street here.
We're looking in your windows to see if you're listening to us.
No.
Wake up!
Wee Willie Winky.
No.
Are all the chillin' in their beds?
For now it's eight o'clock.
It is in France.
Wee Willie Winky runs through the town,
upstairs and downstairs in his nightgown,
peeping through the keyhole,
creeping by the lock.
Are all the children in their beds?
For now it's eight o'clock.
Ye-he-he.
Somebody call the cops.
Okay, I'll be reading from an escape from the slack world by Ninslo.
And I'll have to edit this in place.
On Skilin' Kops.
It was the only thing left of his body after thousands of attempts...
Hey, the skeleton.
The skeleton crew is here.
And he wore it where his face would have been.
If only he'd had it here.
Well, they move rather elegantly in unison.
The needle of pain from his last cell was the only thing he'd felt for 800 years.
And very, very close up.
And then very, very far away.
And the more he thought about it, the more it hurt.
The more it hurt, the more he liked it.
Phylaean's screaming roused Ubro-Ain from his reverie.
Gosh.
The coffin-sized skeleton.
The most control-
I don't want to touch any of these things.
I just think it hurts.
From which all controls of the Ultiversal Muc-Killerator were controlled rang with a piercing nasal whine of highest transcriptivator of king pain.
Go boop your beep.
Hey.
Phylaean shrilled to and about everything.
Dr. Yowlmangler bobbed and nodded and began a fading string of platitudes.
With Mel Falmer.
Whose, whose version is that?
Oh, it's, you know, it's one of these-
It's Nins, it's Ninslo.
Yeah.
It was so fapping, pitiful, tragic, and nauseating that Ubro-Ain thought, if only they hadn't busted Jesus 17 out of the Dimension L hell plate, everything would be perfect.
Fantastic.
Damn, everything was perfect.
And always had been.
And they all hated it.
At least since the G-Giggle re-invasion.
Hundreds of the Ulva-Veib twins were dead and for what?
For a brain the size of God?
A brain so big it couldn't even think of thinking?
It was the irony of it that had gotten to him.
If the Carbonary's Dimension Gate had only been a scalosecond faster or slower,
the wart tubs of the Garduna-Kamora Combine would have found nothing but smoking bug shells.
Ubro-Ain's plan to stop him.
Well, yeah, your control rapidly diminished.
If you'll recheck the triple-checks, double-checks again, everything had to be perfect.
I'll get that Ivan Stang.
There go all the old bobbies chasing after him and Johnson and Johnson and Hargo.
He didn't actually start the religion.
I want to make it clear that he didn't actually start the religion.
That's true, you know.
Hey, and I was there in New York.
He didn't actually start the religion.
He was just there when the religion was started around him.
By people with interesting names, and I'm going to say it on the air, one of the holiest names there is,
but before I say it, what station are we listening to?
Well, that would be...
The New York Times.
Yeah, baby.
On your radio dial is...
Oh, baby.
On certainly.
Faithfully.
Naturefully.
Baby.
Chico, California.
Where the sun often shines, and the mangoes grow, and the mangroves grow.
GG Jeeper Docs buzzed in the ultra glass box full of pure air.
Man, the legendary drug so powerful it doesn't do anything at all.
Two hundred inconceivably advanced entire alien races had been squashed like grapes,
and their fluids refined into this one box full of N, in which Jeeper Docs hung vibrating, repeating,
Let me eat that bone, Wilmer.
I won't kill the girl thing again.
Forty-three times the second as he had for the last thousand years.
Jeeper Docs was of no conceivable help or use, but he was a good pal.
Wave up! Wave up! Wave up! Wave up!
Ow!
I hear that people barely ache at saying that we're poor.
Well, listen to me, I'll set you free, cause I have got the cure.
You're hawking us, you're missing the bus, cause we ain't got no brain.
Just find a mundane and fleece the brain, fleece the pinks instead, fleece the pangs.
I hear the people barely ache at saying that we're poor.
Fleece the pinks, fleece the pinks, fleece the pinks.
This planet is loaded with people like Jar Jar Binks.
Cattle and sheep and monkeys and man some links.
They'll give you money for something that tickles their kinks.
Get them to pay for your food and your prop and your drinks.
Fleece the pinks, fleece the pinks, fleece the pinks, fleece the pinks.
You're wasting your time if you're gonna whine about all of the strike that you lack.
Listen to Bob.
There won't be a problem, you'll lead a life of slack.
Pink's got the dough, but what do you know, a fool and his money soon part.
You don't have to steal, just cut him a deal and that's when the party'll start.
Fleece the pinks, fleece the pinks, fleece the pinks, fleece the pinks.
Taxes are incorporated, profits are obscene.
They gouge you on your cigarettes, your booze and gasoline.
Television, radio and news and magazine.
The conspiracy owns them all, they're part of the machine.
They feed you entertainment like a dose of Thorazine.
Pouring in your ears until there's nothing in between.
It's time to turn the tables, guys, I'll tell you what I mean.
The fastest might be paying, but their money's mighty green.
Fleece the pinks, fleece the pinks, fleece the pinks, fleece who?
Fleece the pinks!
Right!
I would never wanna live.
I would never wanna give to someone who doesn't give.
And I would never wanna hate.
I would never wanna hate someone who doesn't hate.
And I would never wanna love.
I would never wanna love someone who doesn't love.
It's not my way.
You stop my waiting
We've been drinking whiskey, scotch, and beer
And we're meddling men, so we ain't got no fear
Don't be a pussy, tell me it's dangerous
Just shut your damn mouth, hold my beer, and watch this
Loki, Coyote, and before that, Bright Shadow at Tex Day.
And before that, the Philo reads Nenslow's short story
from an old, stark-fist printed zine on KPFA Berkeley
with Dr. Howe and puzzling evidence.
And now, a launching and a Norell.
Friends, what is religion all about
but mindlessness?
Fast repetitions of senseless activity.
Let the launch begin.
Yeah!
Whoa!
It's a multi-warhead!
A multi-limbed, intercontinental ballistic...
Oh, what a trajectory.
And he is still smoking.
I've been given a glimpse of...
I couldn't believe...
I don't care how big it is.
We don't even have any spaceships.
I don't care.
I don't care if 96% of the population
earns around 1% of all the money that's being earned.
It's designed that way.
Bad or feeling terrible.
Wow, I feel really bad.
That's what you're going to get more of.
How bad it is.
Look!
All of the grim realities.
Constantly stressful.
Homophobic people.
Negative angry people and negative.
Craziness.
You crazy.
Frustration.
The worse you feel.
Rich or poor, get poor.
It's all about...
Rich get richer, poor get poorer.
Fantasy.
Man, I would hate that.
Delay.
Second guess.
Doubt.
That's not who you are.
Look, I don't have the car I want.
I don't have the house I want.
I don't have the health I want.
I don't have the spouse I want.
Look.
Here, here.
Woo!
Do it!
How bad?
Bottom line.
Bang the wind.
Sweetheart, sweetheart.
Rich people were people that had ripped everyone off.
It would blow your...
Money.
More money.
I come to easily and frequently.
Right?
Run out of stuff.
Free.
I can't do that.
I'm not...
Oh, crap.
You will live.
See yourself.
There is nothing.
Nothing.
Only nothing.
Have fun with it.
Does Bob really use rubber nipples for his knees?
He has to.
Rubber nipples.
Climbing the corporate ladder.
He was on his knees so much.
Okay, this song is called Pray Little Polly.
It's about little kids.
I hate happy songs.
I despise happy songs.
This is too happy.
I hate it.
I hate.
Gordon Gordon, that was, and the band Lesh Nailah in the background, live at Text Day.
The band you're hearing in the background, for all my credits, is Amino Acids, the Amino
Acids from theaminoacids.com, who will be playing at X Day, not to be confused with
Text Day.
This is the Hour of Slack from the Church of the Subgenius, reachable at P.O.
Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio, 44118, or subgenius.com.
By the way, you're also all Universal Life Church ministers now, that's done.
Hell, god damn it, I just gave away half the membership pack.
But you don't have that Subgenius ministers card in your wallet!
If that card is not in there, your name ain't.
In the Book of Life, Judgment Day will come, the rupture will come, you'll be lifted up.
Is His name in the Book of Life?
Nay, Lord.
Then cast Him into the lake of slacklessness.
Put Him back on earth, friends, because earth is hell without Bob.
If you don't have Bob in your life, you're in hell now!
Quit worrying about the afterlife.
What the hell are you worried about?
You're in eternal hell.
You have to get up and go to work in the morning on Monday, don't you?
Yep.
Case closed.
You are in hell now!
If you don't have Bob in your pipe!
Some people go, what's in that pipe Bob's smoking?
He's had marijuana in his pipe.
What were you guys on when you came up with that?
What's in Bob's pipe is your mind, my friend.
If you are strong enough, if your faith is true enough, and if you know that you
must have slack, that doesn't mean you don't have slack and you must go out and get it.
You must have slack to even be here.
You must have slack to even think you know what a subgenius is.
And it's true, you have it.
You do have that slack.
The greatest thing about it is Bob doesn't know what it is.
I don't know what it is.
The conspiracy doesn't know what your slack is.
We can't take it away from you.
And you can't sell it.
But you can forget about it.
And that's all we're here for.
We're just here to provide a pep talk to remind you to remember your goddamn slack!
Don't be a dumbass!
Well, actually, Bob is the greatest dumbass of them all.
Why do you think they call it subgenius?
Bob is not smart.
Bob is lucky!
And he said, I'd rather be lucky than good any day.
And that sums it up. That's about it.
Praise Bob!
Help me somebody!
Eee-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya!
I missed it!
Robot fisting. Now I've seen everything.
And anybody who doesn't like what we're doing here can kiss the crispy fried ass of Bob Lightyear.
Well, I went to the subgenius thing and they were like breaking toys on the stage.
Saying, praise Bob!
It was beautiful, man! It was beautiful!
I was saved!
And this nice girl gave me this pill.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
The end.
Truth is fiction.
And this is...
Be Born With Me Not.
The musicians of ancient Greece had an unusual way of advertising their calling.
They wore shoes when they walked.
And moss collected from a graveyard.
Be born with me not.
In a moment I'll tell you an unusual story about a soldier who became a crab painter.
He specialized in doves and toads for the next 63 years.
Molaise's house on the island of Inishmury, Ireland, which was constructed from eyes collected from a graveyard,
was built through the generosity of some personable crab looking for peace and quiet.
Madame Lynn Stevens wields a stout toad, with which she drums a noisy tattoo on Stevens Lynn Stevens,
wielding the toad by means of a hook fastened around the stump of his right arm.
She also uses her vocal cords to good advantage.
Custom requires each to shut up.
Be born with me not.
From PR News in Washington, I'm being blamed on the bid to file papers to form an exploratory airstrike on a suspected university in Berlin,
which U.S. officials say is a crime.
The city is close to the border with North Korea and close to parts of the tribal Northeast
and moved through the Midwest's nuclear states and into a tribal haven in St. Louis, St. Louis,
setting the groundwork for the next round of lukewarm attacks next month.
Thousands of pilgrims exploded at an average of more than 100 a day.
At least 34,000 people blew out and destroyed parts of the white marble building dedicated to the infamous PR News.
On Wall Street, 12-9-7-7-6-6-5-4-5-4-7,
this is PR News.
We do expect the majority of customers to be straggling by Wednesday evening.
PR's bad.
PR News is bad.
PR.
Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice has gone to Saudi Arabia seeking help in supporting the fragile PR News in Washington.
Believe it or kill me and PR News by the great Fernanda Ndele, Lee Murr.
Try to deal with real world problems.
The ability of the algorithm to alter the world.
vessel
The ability of the intelligent mass,
the ability of the intelligent mass,
the ability of the intelligence,
the ability of the upper echelon.
The ability of the intelligence,
the ability of the unlimited space,
you cannot surprise your audience with tth
the
in
zero gain
hard...
Irrelevant animal or a human being
bearings
and then you can basically
member WNB
basically have a basically it's basically just so basically we can introduce some slack variables
and then basically by introducing these slack variables basically slack slack
what's uh last last thought last thoughts hey i read all those anti-war statistics that my
peacenik wife handed me oh really yeah so i've done my duty man and i paid my taxes
so i guess that means i'm a citizen or something right citizen yeah citizen smith
you're not bending down as far as you could oh i'm sorry god bless you big brother i mean uh
i love you big brother did you just say god bless you citizen smith uh no no i said uh uh uh god
damn you oh all right that's that's all right then continue your exercises
continue to bend over and crack a smile yeah bend over again in the name of the new world order order
yep i don't think there's a new world order i think that the i think we need a new world order
i don't think we i don't think we're bringing it about fast enough i think that's a big part
of the problem but we can talk about that that means new order of the ages a new order of the
ages yes you know i and uh so much of these so-called new world order
is that people keep trying to bring about they they look an awful lot like the old world order
to me and that the masses are still getting screwed like that's that's a common thread
i'm noticing between these so-called new world orders and you know and the well what are masses
for
hey
that is great
that is good
yeah yeah yeah yeah
what if i was
one of us
that is
great
what if
that was
one of us
bye nor l cap