Ah, yes, dear friends, welcome to the Hour of Slack, number 1,370-something.
And may this Hour of Slack be the most slackful of all the hours heretofore and forthwith.
Your time of listening is now your time of deep, relaxing slack.
Slack is the soft voice, slack the luminous cloud.
We in our slack rejoice.
And thence comes all the charms or ear or sight,
all melodies the echo of that voice,
all colors a suffusion,
all vision of that light.
And though the exists once more withheld the lights of their countenance
from the helpful, hopeful, upturned faces of the ex-day postulants,
we have not even been challenged.
Nay, rather than that, our faith has been reinforced even more
so that we are truly the children,
the warriors of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Praise be to God.
But not the worriers, sir.
We're not the worriers of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
We're not worried because we have faith in the ultimate success of our mission,
the Nameless Mission,
a small part of which is to bring you broadcasting opportunities
such as this one,
where you and we can participate together victoriously in what we call,
the Hour of Slack.
That actually hurt my Adam's apple.
I have done that so many times in the last few days.
I've developed a bruise on my throat.
In Adam's fall, we sinned all.
And the bruise on the throat, which the Bobcaster feels,
is only cognate to the bruise on the heel given by that old serpent, Satan.
Yes, the adversary, the evil one,
was nipping at the heels of the faithful at Exde.
But even old Sequa,
most monstrous denizen of the watery depths,
took only four minor victims.
When we expected a holocaust of many,
including even the most faithful.
Perhaps the locals had fed him the sacrifices,
which, according,
according to Native American tradition,
are his due.
But perhaps he, like the holiday itself,
decided, for no reason that could be named,
to be kind and forbearing,
and to have the faith,
the faith in Bob.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
www.amara.org.au
Way down south in the Piney Woods
There's a gospel quartet singin'
like it should've got the hair slicked back
White suit so fine
At the Wednesday night revival
Turpentine
Got the rollin' bass
Got the baritone
Got a ringin' high tenor
Reachin' Jesus on the throne
And a smooth lead singer
Got the women cryin'
Sweatin' salvation
Turpentine
Save my soul, spirit of the pine
It's a masterpiece waitin' to be signed
Cleanin' my brushes
Turpentine
A spoonful of sugar and hold your nose
It'll kill everything but the Holy Ghost
It's a pine, dark communion body, blood and wine
In the folds of the choir ropes
Turpentine
Save my soul, spirit of the pine
It's a masterpiece waitin' to be signed
sign, cleaning my brushes, turpentine. I'm sitting in the back pew, thumbing through the hymns,
trying to figure out how to write me one of them. Got a story to tell, could do some testifying,
but God ain't giving me the calling, turpentine, turpentine, turpentine. Save my soul, spirit of the
pine. It's a masterpiece, waiting to be signed, cleaning my brushes, turpentine. When they lay me
down in a minor key, and they shovel my words in on top of me, I'll be in that quartet with some
friends of mine, an eternity of Wednesdays, turpentine.
turpentine, turpentine. Save my soul, spirit of the pine. It's a masterpiece, waiting to be
signed, cleaning my brushes, turpentine. Turpentine, turpentine. Save my soul, spirit of the pine. It's
a masterpiece, waiting to be signed, cleaning my brushes, turpentine.
I'm a dead cat on the line.
They tell me that once upon a time, they had some sub trying to get a message over the
telegram box.
The company sent a man out to inspect the line.
In making his report, he said that he found that a cat had gone up to the line and he
had been telegraphed to and died on the line.
That was the reason why they couldn't get the message over the line.
The child doesn't seem to be farther in no way than the dead cat on the line.
Do you hear me?
Yes.
There's a child here just outside.
Where is he?
Do you hear me?
Yes.
Excuse me.
It doesn't matter whether it's child's mother or not, she knows it's her child.
I thought you knew your child's father?
Well, yes.
I think I know my last result.
Yeah.
Yeah, you think you know.
There you go.
Well, you may not know.
But if you don't know, you've got the last word on the question.
There you go.
But I am one man that thinks all children should favor their father.
All right.
Did you hear me?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
I bet that's enough.
Well, the best I can tell you, hasn't that one guy don't favor me at all?
Hmm?
No, sir.
Don't say that.
And don't walk like it.
No, sir.
And don't talk like it.
Have that fella like you.
No, sir.
But as a dead cat on the line.
That's right.
But, you know...
So annoying..
Now that you're back,
You little bingos...
Go catoos.
musen strap fifty-fifty only
Thank you.
Cool's out, but you've all got something learning to do.
call you up let's have a party i'm at my best when i'm miserable howling of dogs wailing of babies
breaking up bottles that is music to my ears i'm going deaf a ringy dingy i hear the angels when
i'm miserable miserable miserable miserable come watch me wiggle while i'm hanging on the
cross and now i'm begging my heart's a breaking i just ain't happy unless i'm miserable
i'll write you a song i told her paint you a picture i make her happy i clean your carpet
i'll bite your hand i leave your breath
you
have fun tonight
my heart's a breaking i just ain't happy
let's go to london visit the tower
scratch our initials into the murder love is eternal when you're miserable
miserable
amazing
slowly
stop
shit
hey
smoke
does
this
breaking. I just ain't happy unless I'm miserable, miserable, miserable.
Ah yes dear friends. Ah yes, yes, yes. Another hour of slack. The 1638th hour of slack.
That's a fair amount of slack. Oh the credits, that's right. Thanks for reminding me there
Satan. That song we just heard, Misery Bull, was of course the Rainmakers from Kansas City,
Missouri. And we also heard a song by them at the very beginning, Turpentine, about turpentine
drinking church folks.
Uh, the, the, before Misery Bull, that song about where the guy talks the audience into
giving him his keys, that's Dr. Argus Fox and the Right Angles recorded live. Humans
Are Okay, the somewhat softer song, was exposed foreheads. Exposed with an X and foreheads
with a four, numeral four.
That's how we heard the song, and what's in there, is that, I think it was the leading
singer
and then we.
Where is it?
Right 와서 cask.
Yup.
Right wise.
Rightカ.
Yeah.
Yes, ladies and gentlemen.
I'd just like to add my thanks to the Preacher Comforts Coordinator here.
Beautiful downtown listless behavior.
It's been a long, long, long time.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
That is a long time.
Me too.
I'm sorry too.
I'm sorry three.
I'm sore.
Well, I can see why you're both sore, because you have canubial bliss together every Saturday evening.
But I was just married to a sandalwood snail for the last half an hour.
Bonford, they're pretty slippery.
Yep.
Muselaginous snails.
Sensuous snails.
Yeah.
You made my toes curl up like a little dog.
They go crawling up you, kind of scraping at you with their tiny little teeth.
Yeah.
Scraping the fungus off.
That's what they have on.
Have you ever been sucked by a leech?
Yes, I'm afraid so.
Yes, I have too.
In fact, I had a pet leech a couple of, well, it's been about five years since I had my scum aquarium.
But when I was filming, when I was a wildlife photographer filming microbes,
I actually had an aquarium.
I had an aquarium full of slime with a little heat lamp on it.
I would get water from the graveyard pond and places like that.
So I'd always have lots of new micro life in there.
Graveyard pond.
Yeah.
One day, it wasn't all microscopic.
There was an actual leech in my tank.
I had to get rid of him because he was eating all my pets.
Well, I think my story is more interesting where I went swimming.
I went in a bad place and walked out of the water and stuff.
And there were these things that are already sucking a bunch of my blood confirmed on my body.
Yeah.
Well, that's nature.
Especially if you're a young child and you don't need.
It's leeches.
You know, I know.
Dave, did you know that of all of the many, many, many millions of species of life forms that are animals on this planet,
many more of them are parasites that live inside.
Other animals than.
Then like us or our dog or cat.
Well, actually, we and the dogs and cats are parasites in a way.
But I'm talking about, you know, like we're we we're so big that we have parasites living inside us and on us and they have parasites.
Yeah.
I mean, even the fleas have fleas upon their backs to bite him.
And so at infinite.
And that's.
Completely wrong way of quoting Jonathan Swift.
But I never can remember the correct.
So classy.
It's a Swifty.
That's all you need to, you know, let the audience know that it was a Swifty.
You don't have to go too much further than that.
At least if you want to, you know, entree versus the backside, as they used to say in Henry Walden,
Harden, the throw throw or whatever his name was.
The guy, you know, with the snake hair.
His hair is awful.
It's the nature boy.
Yeah.
The until he saw Gorbius, the Margon and stuff like that.
And then all the snakes killed him and stuff.
I think that's how I was.
He's mixed.
He's doing a mashup.
Yes, he is.
His brain is doing the day brain is doing a mashup.
He's making my brain hurt because I can't keep up with it.
But it's OK.
Don't stop.
Well, you don't have we're not really going anywhere, especially since I'm in charge of my side of it.
Somebody else could do a better job, I think.
But.
I'm the only one who volunteered.
That's right.
Actually, there's some poor sumbitch trying to call right now.
I don't I have no.
Obviously, they've never listened to this show before.
Well, they know that.
And that's why we know not to pick up that line.
Right.
Because if they were listeners, they'd know not to call.
Well, there's only one person allowed to call.
Well, the one time we thought it was going to be.
I mean, we were talking to Dave and it was Philo.
That's true.
And then we Dave got cut off.
That was because it was that it was in Texas.
Yeah.
Philo tricked us.
I could only do one phone caller at a time there.
Yeah.
Here we choose to only do one caller.
Yes.
And his name is based on on Hellenic cuisine because it's a form of Greek pastry.
If we did.
What used in a lot of Greek pastry with honey and walnuts.
If we did let anybody call in, if we just picked up the phone anytime somebody called
show that follows our show in Cleveland.
Yes.
About half of the calls we get would be kind of like this.
Hey, y'all.
I just want to tell you I saw Bob.
Yeah.
I see Bob.
I love Bob.
And I said, it's UFO.
And it came down and it mutilated this cow and Bob was on it.
That's what.
What the hell, Bob?
What the hell?
What the hell is that?
Because every other one would be basically like that.
They would be just like the very first calls to the very first time that Philo and I were
ever on the radio.
Because every time we ever did any show that just let people call in about every other
call was insipidly unoriginal, stupid and with a fake southern accent.
Because you know, you have to act.
You have to sound like Billy Graham to sound like a preacher.
Yeah.
God.
Thanks.
But I think Saturday Night Live covered that 35 years ago.
Yeah.
But you got to remember a lot of these people that wrote in these noisy complaints are extremely
flatulent, especially this time of the year with the summer on the halfway wane like a
twilight zone between fall and summer and stuff like that.
One of them you got to explain.
What's the story?
You know, they're flatulent and they send him his ruined carcass.
I might add.
Believe me.
I said, believe me.
They're flatulent enough, they can join our band.
Well, they have to join our band if you do it in the right way.
That's the cross-eyed, dim-witted way.
If you believe as firmly as you can, that some way there's a way to get Toto back to
Kansas in time for the next Home Run Derby or Tuesday or whatever it is.
They could just leave.
We'd all be fighting by the time we come back here,
especially if they all believe in the burping up sharia law and syrup and egoism.
Is it possible to get Toto back to Kansas?
As a rumored child, you perhaps could,
because you have this strange and illustrious corpse act,
which is now Oklahoma law,
that says even if a child is as ugly as a dog,
you can still transport it past state lines.
Oh, no, no, they switched over to sharia law in Oklahoma.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Yeah, the Muslims took over Oklahoma,
just like the Oklahomans were so terrified it was going to happen.
I mean, they were, half of Oklahoma, more than half of Oklahoma,
has been kind of adjusting their own,
their own lives around the fear of the Muslims coming in
and taking over the whole state of Oklahoma.
You just look around Oklahoma, it's like everybody's wearing a burka.
So it's already happened.
I don't know why they're even worried about it.
And if the last I heard, Obama did go and take away all of the guns.
Yeah, it took him 30 years to do it, but he still got it done before.
The gun salesmen are acting like that didn't happen.
It's like, oh, Obama's going to come and take your guns,
so you better buy more of them.
It's like, dude, that already happened.
Obama took all the guns.
Hillary stole all the uranium and gave it to the Russians
after infecting molested children with it in a pizza parlor.
All of that stuff you can read on the Internet so you know it's true.
And everything else that's on, you know, the expensive TV,
that's all fake.
That's fake news like the Bible or Book of the Subgenius.
Anybody can write a book.
Of course.
Anybody can do a book.
Yeah, I believe that for a very long time.
I was under lunar influences.
I was under the power of the greater elves and the people with big ears.
And they had me confused in the parking lot one time
and told me that I better not jump out the window
or I could be in grave error of fictional reality.
Oh, I remember that, Dave.
Dave.
Those weren't really elves with long ears.
We were at the Fantasy Fair science fiction convention.
I'm still pondering whether is Munchkinland like in another cosmos or galaxy?
It's in Oz.
Oh, it's in Oz. Right.
What exactly happened from a scientific viewpoint, standpoint?
What happened? Starting when?
When I got into the argument with the elves and you said they weren't real.
You said they were like knee-jerk.
They were like the
They were cosplay people.
People in shorts.
That was at the comics con.
That was at the comic book con.
Dave's never been to one of those things.
He thought all those people were real superheroes.
They're posers, Dave. Posers.
No, they're not posers.
They're aficionados of fantasy and science fiction and comic books and stuff.
And they like to dress up.
Yeah, you wouldn't want to regurgitate the same thing back to them
because you could lose your heavy list.
Oh, they all regurgitate the same.
The last time I saw them.
I haven't been to Dragon Con in a while, but the last time I went,
there must have been 40 Heath Ledger jokers walking around.
That's true.
That's a real easy one to do.
But it was much harder to be all of the Watchmen,
but I saw several clusters of those.
Uh-huh.
And of course, you can have an entire.
It's not a comic book convention unless there's 10,000 stormtroopers
parading down the middle of the street.
And I'm not kidding.
They do that in Atlanta every year.
I don't know.
I don't know if it's 10,000, but it's like a thousand stormtroopers.
Yes, they amass.
Star Wars stormtroopers, not Nazi stormtroopers.
In the days of the inclination and the acclimation, these are all needed.
You have to get everybody ready for a police force that can really do its job.
Like, you know, has hand grenade propelled launchers and Soviet-style missiles
and some barbecue aprons that you can wear on the back of your head.
Well, you know.
You know.
The prophets, a lot of people, a lot of subgeniuses, and the late Dick Gregory,
feel that when a Hollywood movie comes out with a bunch of crazy alien stuff going on in it
and children getting kidnapped and wars and rumors of wars,
that that's all just to soften you up because it's really going to happen.
They're going to make it happen.
That's why for 75 years, I've been in the movie industry.
For 75 years, there's been movies about flying saucers.
They're softening us up.
I'll bet you that they soften us up for several more thousand years before the aliens actually get here.
The ones they're talking about.
I mean, because they have this limited idea of aliens as these saucer-riding, physical, breathing things.
They don't necessarily have to have bodies at all.
No, they have soggy jaws.
And we don't either.
We just have to...
Big as the moon.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
It is what you just said is completely and totally true.
No, my medical alert just went off.
What did it say?
It was very untrusting with the Monster Hunter music.
The alarm blending with the Monster Hunter music was interesting.
Well, that's what makes it so bloody and so good and juicy and fun.
I've been playing a video game that makes me sick.
I've almost completely beaten the game.
I've played it for so many hours that...
Wait, wait.
I smell cooking.
I smell meat cooking.
It's just burned oil.
Is that the substance of your dissolution there?
No, no, no.
That was good.
Popcorn smells.
I can't remember the serious subject that I was talking about.
How can that happen on this show?
I can't imagine how that would happen.
Here, let's toast some marshmallows.
Oh, yeah, good idea.
That'll bring everything back.
Aroma, it had something to do with aroma, maybe, I don't know.
Mmm.
Well, it was cooking music that was on for a minute.
Oh, I was talking about the video game that makes me so sick.
Right.
Well, I've been playing Monster Hunter for years,
and I've been seeing this game called...
Big Game Hunter, where it was bears and lions and water buffalo and stuff.
I wasn't gonna spend 30 bucks on a...
It's for the Wii.
But I found a copy for $2.
And I started becoming a big game hunter as kind of a...
Because I like to be outdoors.
It's horrible.
It's horrible, Dave.
Horrible.
But I love to be outdoors.
I love to be outdoors.
And I love to look at animals through a scope,
preferably a movie camera, telescopic lens.
But in this game, in order to be able to explore the cool deserts,
you have to shoot a certain number of innocent herbivores and ungulates,
like, you know, bighorn sheep and stuff like that.
Yeah.
You have to sneak up on them, kill them, and then tag them, whatever that means.
But then they kind of skip over all the bloody stuff.
Where you have to hang them up by their feet, bleed them, cut their belly open,
pull all their guts out, peel their skin off.
Buh.
Yeah.
They leave out all that stuff.
That's not part of the game.
Anyway, it makes me sick every time I have to kill one of these innocent creatures.
And yet you can't stop playing the game.
Well, not if I want to explore around the next corner.
And as we all know, slack lies around the next corner.
That is always true.
That is true.
But I think you're gonna disfigure yourself if you play the game.
I think you're gonna continue this policy.
I hate to sound like the bearer of ill tidings, but it seems to me you've kind of left your senses behind
once you've exterminated that last cabinet piece that you've been working on.
Oh, I discovered this and I discovered that.
And you can make the lines, too, if you just hold your nose.
Well, you can't always hold your nose.
And sometimes things are more truer than you thought they were.
Well, there was a time when I got too into these games and I would...
Mm-hmm.
When the game was over, I'd be covered with blood and scratches and bites.
And I actually lost a couple of teeth during...
It's like you black out and you do all this fighting in this game, all this...
You get all beat up and when...
It's all virtual.
When you come out of it...
Well, not...
That's what I'm saying is...
Remember that...
Princess, will you remember that time when my character, Stangor, had a real rough fight in the desert?
Yes.
And you walked in and I was covered with sweat?
Oh, yeah.
And then the next fight he did, it was in the snow and you walked into our bedroom and I had icicles hanging off my nose.
Uh-huh.
And then the next time, it was a really, really big monster and it beat me and you walked in and I was bitten in half.
Yeah.
He really gets into the game.
You can get too into this stuff.
Yeah.
Yeah, but what...
You can't...
You know, there's a lot of these elderly people that play these games.
They'll be right in the middle of a real exciting part of it and they'll start pooping.
And they want people to...
They want people to un-force themselves to not poop.
And they think they can because they believe in mind over matter.
But most of them don't realize what an immaterial force everything is.
You know, like...
Speak for yourself, man.
It's like Puccini's...
Well, yeah, I am.
I'm a fan of Puccini.
They start pooping?
La La Donnie Mobile.
I remember that song.
These women are fickle.
That's why I didn't say necessarily pooping.
I mean, you know, kind of figuratively, metaphorically pooping.
Ah, okay.
But, yeah, I don't know.
They're just doing all this improved poop all to the new boys.
Yeah.
Whoooo don't you know!
Some asshole herb ones.
A little bit of 빠 died inside.
But they'll get paid in centres in, oh my投 this year.
Oh my gosh, there's just so many awkward faces.
Go ahead.
I want to get some more.
Oh, this is the first time I've got.
Oh and don'tablo relivein We're doing a more appropriate podcast.
exactly what you just said, Dave.
Me too.
I've said that exact sentence
is on the tip of most Americans' tongues.
The only reason they're not all saying
exactly what you just said
is because they're not on this show.
Right.
Lucky, lucky, lucky.
Well, enough is enough goodwill,
you know, speaking spiritually.
We're all trying to do our bit.
We're all trying to do our part.
Well, Princess, we and I are hurrying
to pack up and go down to Texas
and save everybody.
We're going to take sponges.
I was going to ask you
how far Katie is
because I knew of some people
living in Katie who thought
that they were going to be okay
because it was on slightly higher ground
and then a bunch of it wasn't.
Living where?
Katie?
Katie.
How do you spell that?
K-A-T-Y.
It's a Houston, about an hour from Houston.
Oh.
A Beulah to Cleveland's worth of Houston.
Hmm.
About an hour drive
in a metaphorical laundromat automobile.
You know, like...
Oh, yeah.
Anybody...
Red-nosed reindeer.
They're underwater.
The jackalopes are swimming
with little oxygen tanks on.
The jackalopes are swimming...
The rattlesnakes have tiny little oxygen tanks.
Scuba mast.
I love when you sing,
man.
Oh.
Yeah, we, uh...
Uh, yeah.
Yep, yep.
Yep, we've got to move our entire...
This time we're going to move more
of the Subgenius Foundation archives
to the laboratory in Texas.
It's all going to end up...
First, it's all going to end up
lining the hallways
until we get our shed built.
We're going to have to get some Mennonites
to raise us a new barn
with an air conditioner in it.
Well, I know where you can get
a lot of cheap slave Mennonites,
just like you don't even have to go.
It's an Internet site
that you can actually go to,
and it's codified, you know.
Mennonites are us.
Mennonites and Amish and such.
Mennonites.com.
Mennonites and Amish and things.
What I don't like is when you see
a bunch of them smoking cigarettes,
driving, and now they're driving automobiles.
I've seen them drive automobiles.
I'm not talking about Mennonites
who are allowed to drive.
I'm talking about Amish people
driving motorized vehicles.
They can do that.
If they're working for somebody else,
that's perfectly legit.
They were always able to drive
if they were working for someone else.
Yeah, if they're working for the English,
they can fly jet planes
if the English are paying them.
Absolutely.
They're not a nice workaround.
They're still stupid.
Our friends that lived in Amish country
said that they have all kinds of
tricky ways of getting around their rules.
He's seen some of the fanciest
8-track deck speaker systems
in Amish buggies.
I'm not kidding, by the way.
That's not an exaggeration.
He really did know some Amish people
who had really, really good 8-track players
and killer speakers.
And they...
Well, some of the kids deck their buggies,
like lowriders, you know,
like...
Only it's not the kookarach.
It's a different bug that they're handling.
You know...
They're listening to Metallica
as they're trotting,
clopping down the road with their horses.
You nailed it, right?
Seriously, on the buggy.
Anyway, yeah, we need to...
I hear they have really good speed, too.
So we need to meet the Mennonites
and the Ammonites in North Texas
and get them to barn racing.
Yeah.
I honestly, we don't have...
The place in Texas is nearly as big
in terms of usable space
as the one in Cleveland Heights.
But it's a lot younger.
It's only about 50 years old
instead of 120.
Yes.
Well, what about naked Luciferians?
Well, you can't see...
There's naked Luciferians
all over both neighborhoods,
but in Cleveland Heights,
you can't walk around naked.
Out on the ranch, you could.
You can't?
But you just gotta watch out for the goats.
Because they don't...
If they don't like you, they'll butt you.
Right in the butt.
Yep.
I wouldn't want to walk bare naked
through a crowd full of ducks or geese
or any kind of wandering minstrels
like goats or something like that.
But, Dave, you know,
here we are talking nonsense
and we've got these public airwaves
and there's young and old people out there
who are, well, obviously,
if they're looking to us for advice,
they deserve what they get.
But...
They may be looking to us for slack.
Oh, that's right.
So that for...
Just for one hour of slack,
they can briefly forget
their job
and it
and her
and him
and them
and that problem
down there.
No, not down there.
Further, a little bit lower.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, oh, oh, no.
No, up a little.
Up a little bit more.
No, no, no.
Harder, harder.
Harder.
I'm trying to squeeze.
Ow!
Yeah.
Now you're talking.
No, but seriously, there's people...
It was your idea to drink
precious bodily...
well-warmed over precious bodily fluids
and I took your advice.
There's people out there
that read Facebook and the news
and watch television...
Yeah, I've been to read my book.
A thousand times more
than I...
I do.
And they're so scared
and miserable and nervous
because they know
what's going on all the time.
They know how sick
all their friends are.
They know how jealous
they should be
of their other friends
who aren't on the internet
but are out hiking up and down
the Grand Canyon.
They know how scary
the weather is.
They know that the weather
is a thousand times more scary
than it's really going to be
unless it's a hurricane,
in which case it's the other way around.
And...
Yeah, there's people living
in anxiety and fear
all the time.
They're so scared
to quit looking at the TV
and the news
that they can't get around
to cleaning up their basement.
And so...
They're wading through paint cans
every time they come home from work.
Old paint cans
that are sealed up
and the paint in there is dried up
if there's any paint left at all,
but they still haven't got it.
They don't get rid of those paint cans.
The reason I know that
is because today,
we, Princess,
we and I sat on my porch
and opened
35 paint cans.
Easily.
And not a one of them was easy.
Oh my gosh, in Cleveland.
Well, the man will come
and take them away
if it's dry,
if they're dried out.
So...
And 90% of them were
and the rest are drying out.
But by golly,
it's hard to get
30-year-old paint cans open.
Yeah.
I had to just rip at them
with pliers, basically.
And why do they work
when they're not supposed to,
when they're supposed to decay
at a certain penumbridge?
You know, like in the...
When the ex-officiato guys
and the papal envoys
used to all hang out,
crowding into one
little small...
See, that made me feel
so much better,
what Dave just said.
That made me feel better
about everything.
My wrist,
my injured wrist
from prying the cans open,
it quit hurting.
Aww.
Dave, you're so good.
So, see, this show
is good for something.
Well, that's why
they call me Dr. Dave,
because I know just exactly
that his ankle was on fire there,
like he was talking about,
and then there was...
All that stuff was going on.
He's psyche.
Dr. Dave is such a good friend
and doctor that if your face
is on fire,
he won't just wait
for you to notice.
He'll let you know.
He'll tell you.
Man, that's a good doctor.
Before it burns off.
You know, a lot of your friends
will just go,
man, check it out.
He's a good doctor.
His face is on fire.
He didn't...
Let's wait until it's half burned off
and then tell him.
Yeah, look...
That's why most...
A lot of people are that way.
Probably half the folks out there
just let their friend's face burn off
because they think it's funny.
They're too cool
to even say anything.
Right.
And if you're...
They can sandwich
as far as they're concerned.
Right.
You know...
They really do...
They just can't...
They get out their marshmallows
and start toasting.
Princess,
we are your friends.
Your face is on fire.
Put your face out.
You don't have to come over there
and hit you with a face.
With my lips?
Okay.
Well, I told you.
I warned you.
That was a great
Doctors For Wotan song.
Remember that one?
Would you tell me
if my face was on fire?
Yeah.
I remember that.
Beautiful, beautiful...
Hey, man.
Your face is on fire.
Come on.
He set his faces on fire.
So we can do Doctors For Wotan anytime.
You just have to turn off the background music.
Right.
This is very pretty.
I must tell you,
in a certain way,
I've expressed myself.
I don't want you to slap my finger.
I would never, ever slap your finger, Dave.
Never.
We have a song about our dog, too.
Hello, dammit, in the grass.
We're gonna kick some varmints, beep.
I like to kick the varmints,
beep, before laughing.
It's wonderful to me.
I don't remember how I get there,
but it's a very, very special place
in my heart.
Is that your heart?
That's what the kids are calling that thing now, huh?
That's real clever.
I like that.
You're mocking my vowels.
That's a polite way of saying, you know.
Oh, my heart is itching.
Would you scratch it?
I think we know what they mean.
I forgot about that.
I'm glad I always watch this.
Honey, would you hold it while I run water through it?
No, that one is very abstruse to me.
I don't know exactly what that means.
You'll figure it out later.
Just thinking about it.
You sure?
Yeah.
I'm going to be standing up all day wondering who licked the cow, what's wrong, and who
invented it.
When you figure it out, you'll get real turned on, and then you'll go looking for somebody
to do that with.
I ain't licking for nothing.
I've already took enough lickings in my life.
Right now, I'm standing up pure and proud.
What nationality am I again?
I think you should lick some abstruso myself.
Abstruso?
I thought some absinthe.
Yes.
Wouldn't that be better?
Absinthe?
Yeah.
You could lick some absinthe.
And then have some abstruso on top of it.
Right.
And some obscuro.
Obscuro extemporadio.
Yeah.
And then side jokes for the nerdiest nerds.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Well, we've all been in the same bowling alley constricted by our valve motions and kept
asunder in our own little, little ways.
rocking chairs, and they only let us out just a scant five minutes ago before sundown was
going on.
Next thing you know, we're all locked up again, you know?
I mean, psychosomatically speaking.
Right.
Because you wouldn't want that to really happen in the physical world because, well, I guess
it is in a physical world in a lot of ways, but not enough to make me cry.
Oh, virtual lockup's bad enough, man.
Yep, they're not going to make me clench my bowels.
Oh, you think they're not going to?
Your bowels are already clenched.
You just don't know it.
You get used to it.
You think it's normal.
Of course I thought it was normal.
What else am I supposed to think?
Of course.
Princess, I realize that we can't go to Trammell Fossil Park.
Why is that?
Because I'm going to be driving a truck.
Yay.
It'll take an extra day.
It'll take an extra day of truck rental.
Oh, that's right.
No.
We'll have to do it on the way back.
We'll have to do it on the way home.
Yeah.
There's fossil parks in Ohio that have trilobites and trigger bites and stuff like that that
we don't have in Texas.
And they're on the way.
And I had made plans to go there, but now we realize we can't haul a trailer.
We can't do that.
We've got to put everything in a truck.
And then put the dog and the mom in the van.
Because anything that ticks off smart people makes Trump supporters real happy.
I don't exactly understand how you made that conclusion, but I like the cow come.
Do you want me to say that one again?
I'll happily say it.
Would you please?
Anything that ticks off smart people makes Trump supporters real happy.
Is that insulting enough for somebody?
Poor snowflakes.
Oh, the sissies are picking on me again.
The nerds and sissies and queers and girls are picking on us big fat white boys.
Hey, hey, I'm going to go play video games and escape the fact that I don't want to go
apply for a job.
Oh, no, this video game, it has girls in it.
How queer.
He kissed a girl.
Girl.
Everything is just reversed.
It's all upside down and backwards.
And inside out.
Yeah.
The moon goes behind the sun.
The shadows are bright and the light bulbs cause darkness to come.
It's just everything's upside down and backwards.
It's all Ipswiched.
It's Ipswiched.
Did we talk at great length about the Osiris landing and the Wednesday?
Yeah.
The winter solstice?
I mean, the eclipse?
The eclipse.
Well, did we?
We, I think Dr. Legume and that orgasmic amplifier sort of broke the eclipse.
It wasn't our fault, exactly.
I mean, the instructions said to do it at certain dates, and one of them was the eclipse date, August 21st.
That's probably what happened then.
Well, but it was also my birthday.
But why would that matter to somebody?
I mean, those instructions date from 1952, I think.
I wasn't even born then, so why would Bob care about my birthday?
So I think that's a coincidence.
But he might have known there was going to be an eclipse.
Yes.
Because they have charts of that kind of thing.
Not that Bob would have to look it up.
It would be a lucky.
It's a guess on Bob's part.
That's all he has to do is guess, and it's always going to be a lucky guess.
It's always going to be a guess.
Even if he's wrong, it's going to end up being lucky for it.
That's our Bob.
That's the way it goes, and we're mighty damn glad about it, too.
There's no way of getting around that.
He makes a million dollars every time he screws up.
Yeah.
That's Bob.
Yeah, that's Bob.
Yeah.
Some people think that's like the cosmic and funny.
line, and I don't think that is.
I think that's one of the sell it to the rubes lines.
That's the one that gets normals to send us $35 thinking they're real weirdos.
Yeah, we're all dead.
These subgeniuses, they're only in it for the money.
Get it?
Ha, ha, ha.
That's funny.
Okay.
Whatever.
I think I understand what you're saying now for certainly.
You're saying that the Church of the Subgenius,
some kind of ripoff hoisted on humanity by one guy who claims to be the world's greatest
salesman, but it turns out he was a vacuum cleaner in not another lifetime.
He sucks.
Yeah.
Bob sucks because he's a vacuum cleaner.
Not only that, he's a Red Devil brand vacuum cleaner.
Very powerful and satanic.
Oh, he's a shark.
Those are all vacuum cleaner brands, folks.
Yeah, I was trying to think of something.
I'm sorry.
He's a Hoover.
He's a regular Herbert Hoover.
Oh, wait.
No.
Well, what about-
Jay Edgar.
He's a damn Jay Edgar, that Bob.
He sucks.
Buddy.
Hoover.
Boy, that's really obscure.
You know, because people born after a certain point, there's no such thing as a Hoover vacuum
cleaner.
Right.
Or Kirby.
There's Red Devils and Shark.
They don't know what Kirby means.
Right.
And there's no Hoovers either because the DOJ is now the FBI and the PBM.
Kirby is a video game.
It's not a vacuum cleaner.
Yeah.
And there's a lot of things that people born after a certain date, they don't even know
the meaning of the word like honor, truth, honesty, wisdom, humility.
Right.
Those words, a CD, an LP, those don't mean anything to modern kids.
Well, there's no-
Film.
They don't know what film is.
When you think of going from, say for instance, from a cassette player-
Knowledge.
They don't know what that is.
That's all just, that's all old stuff to them.
Smells funny.
Well, I don't know if they're getting their-
Honesty.
What's that?
That's fake news.
That smells funny.
It's all musty.
Smells like my grandpa's pipe.
Phew.
Now that's a mouthful.
It smells like mom's ashtray.
I don't understand that one.
I don't understand that one either, but I know that's a very powerful image.
And if you want to, like say, Dreyfus or one of those real famous guys from the 20th century
and stuff, who like wear funny pants and dance around, make hand signals and gestures and
stuff like that, you know, as well as I do, you've always must give the appearance of
moving forward, never from side to side, because that's more like a Romanian acrobat or some
kind of foreigner.
But if you can keep your eyes on the prize, so to speak, and you can keep your eyes on
the prize, and follow the stinking star, you could come home in a bag.
Cat, you in a bag.
You need to bug out.
And we're going to bug out of this show because it's about two minutes till the hour and we're
getting ready for incoming show, which will probably pick up more listeners, I bet.
Lately, Dr. Sinister's been getting more over, more internet listeners than we have.
And all this time I've been calling you-
That's-
It's probably because I play such-
I play such terrible music, such as this tune coming up from Dr. Argus, Argos fucking
Argus Fox.
Ay, ay, ay, ay.
And the right-
Ay, ay, ay, ay, ay.
And goes, good night, Dave.
Good night, Dave.
The guy that's like football team, those jobs are not for him.
Turns into a real estate agent who believes in discipline.
The guy who's first!
Just use cocaine, the wild boy breaking free
He'll end up in a court of law as a prosecuting QC
Remember the school captain, success is a matter of time
You can hear him now as he screams
Crack, you missed the stop sign
Forget Snoop Doggy Dog, forget old iced tea
True word, hell, that on the streets is produced by the DOT
What's he used to striving?
Life's road in front unravels
We get to do the driving
Don't choose the direction we travel
Do your homework, your whack for weeks, go paint the goddamn line
Don't matter much when you hear that scream
Crack, you missed the stop sign
Crack the stop sign
Two, three, four
Some time in the next two thousand years
God's gonna wipe out the streets of man
I'm banging on a gun before I end the year of town
Here's to the arts and junkie
Porky to napkin
I'm a man of the arts
With a tragic waste of potential
We the chumpies on the street either
Close your door to what you got
You're the fruit of their mind
Who cares what you reap
It's Crack, you missed the stop sign
You're the fruit of their mind
But I thought just the other day
Man, could that baby run?
But you know what they always say
He's always a better one
He's got a tumor in my brain
He's creeping to my lungs
And I search around in grief
If I need a better one
Oh, I need to wait to watch the answer question
They're going to throw this out there
They're throwing us out of batter
A choice is a matter of waiting to see
So kids, yeah you can do it
You can be your best
But girls can do anything
Except be presidents
I'm ok
You're ok
We're ok
We're fine
Thought I heard a city dreamer
Crack, you missed the stop sign
Crack, the stop sign
Break the sound time
Yeah!