B.D.I.s flexing, flexing, eager to crush out life.
Great teeth gnashing with rage, powerful fingers flashing with hatred.
And now, for the first time on the air,
The Self-Genius Power of Splash!
How were we to dislodge him from his perch and bring him back alive?
That is how the Batiks, the natives, make a complete roof over your head.
Bizarre.
Defeated, citation needed, teen actress in a bar stumbling into a car.
What does it really take to get the sex these days?
Haven't you got enough disillusionment in your life?
We're not showing disrespect to the people on digital spy.
Is this the slow to camera cruise?
In fact, we're tuning in to...
You've touched up the issue, the throne's on watch for you.
Haven't you got enough disillusionment in your life?
Some act to drug assaults the law.
It's surely clear what we think.
Opposing views on the rolling news.
Now we don't know what to think.
Glossy, medical and the shots.
She knows that Photoshop.
But still to replicate.
The figure and the face.
Is utmost in her mind.
Our viewpoints misaligned.
Is no one willing to make common sense these days?
Haven't you got enough disillusionment in your life?
Will your children see?
A world that you always visualize.
Still not showing credence to a bunch of grumpy idiots.
Solutions to problems that never ever existed.
Haven't you enough disillusionment in your life?
Haven't you got enough disillusionment in your life?
In your life.
Haven't you seen enough to know that it won't just turn out nice?
Everywhere you go you see the battle run.
And often you see the battle run.
But here want to show you something else.
Riding in the rink.
NATURAL
The song has been made open to the public in the setting of reality.
If you матери, everything didn't go as it should, right?
If you want to accept all this.
No matter what.
of the Attery Squash at myspace.com slash the attery squash. Like the superhero Hancock, I,
your hero, Reverend Ivan Stang, have been seeking clues to my own past,
and Mr. Sistar found this particular one in his netcrack queue, the voices of Bob and Connie Dobbs.
What about that fellow we saw last month? His reaction was perfect. Ivan, the perfect slave,
desire to work, perfect health, and obeys every command. With half the people on earth in his
condition, we'd have the epitome of civilization. How many would turn out like him? Not enough to
take care of the wild ones. Then you must find out what it is about Ivan that produced the effect.
I've performed every practical test on him.
His body chemistry is basically the same as the rest.
Well, you'll have to figure it out.
I don't believe it can be done in short time.
All right, so what's on your mind, Ragnar?
No, it's all about preparation X-Day.
All right.
Yeah, because X-Days are coming.
That's right.
Will you be on the saucers, or will you be left below?
Left below.
Mm-hmm.
With the rest of the other pinks.
Who will be?
Ready to fry in a pink hell of your own creation.
Oh, it's not even like hell. You know, you just work a dead-end job for the rest of your life.
Mm-hmm, and that's your hell. Your pleasure saucers could also be your pain saucers.
All the slack in the universe will gravitate towards Planet X.
So there's only one difference between being left below and the world as it is today.
Hmm, I don't know.
Some X-Days.
The X's.
The X's actually recreate the Earth and clone everybody.
Hmm.
You see, Mark, you might not realize this, but you're actually a clone of a clone of a clone that goes back many, many generations of cloning.
Fortunately, though, there's no replicative fading.
There's no genetic, you know, dilution there.
Very few errors in the transcription, if any at all.
Sometimes, though, you know, little anomalies do pop up, but it's usually to your benefit.
Usually you'll gain, like, a mutant power or something.
Hmm.
Yeah, everybody must get cloned.
Okay, who has an official clock locked to Greenwich Mean Time who's not filming?
Come on, I mean.
It's not fashionably late enough yet.
No, seriously.
Does anybody...
No, but, Matty, don't you have a cell phone?
I have a cell phone.
But...
Again, why are we worried about time?
In four minutes, hours will be meaningless.
What time is it, baby?
Years will mean nothing.
We'll age instantly.
Two minutes.
Die and be burned up.
Steve, you know what this is, don't you?
It's a time-space warp.
I'm not sure I know exactly what that is.
I don't suppose anything.
It's not something that anybody really does.
We've seen some strange things tonight.
Strange creatures that we know don't belong on our planet.
God only knows where they came from.
The vortex took them.
Just...
Just took them away.
I don't know what place they're in.
I don't even know what time they're in.
I don't know what time they're in.
Oh yes, and we must remember when we're gathered here for X Day, every god damn 13th time for
me.
Friends, an X, let's face it, is just a cross that's been knocked over.
Friends, we survived X Day 11 and have brought back to civilization the recordings from that
subgenius religious holiday.
Thanks to Fernand and Andy Lemer and Bob for the titles and future collages.
The Vortex took them, just took them away.
And Dr. Mr. Sister found that excerpt from the day time ended.
This is Hour of Slack number one.
Thank you.
1164 from the Church of the Subgenius.
Much of this show was recorded just after X Day 11, July 6th, 2008, on Dr. Sinister's
show, Radio Sinesthesia on WCSB Cleveland.
Speaking of insane and obnoxious, anybody have any comments on the death of Jesse Helms?
That was far out overshadowed for us by the death of Larry Harmon, the creator of Bo
Zo.
Bozo?
Hardly anybody knows who Jesse Helms was, but Larry Harmon, I mean Bozo was...
He was Bozo, man.
He created thousands of other little Bozos like him.
He was a dynasty of clowns, just like you should be, my friend.
You should not call this show.
You should instead drink all the detergent you can, even go for Drano in your veins,
and then dress up like Bozo.
It was ironic that on the...as Larry Harmon lay on his deathbed and died, he was dressed
like a clown.
There was a movie being shown at X Day, starring the amino acids, that begins with a Bozo party
clown being murdered, so that an amino acid can then do tricks at the children's birthday
party.
Thank you for coming along with me down to the bottom of the deep sea.
Now turn the record over and I'll see you on the other side.
Honk, honk, honk, honk.
Hey, you're the Bozo I am.
Hey, what are you doing in there?
Shh.
You want to blow it for us all.
Oh, I'm not.
I think we're bozo.
No, you're not going to blow it for me, buddy.
Get the hell out of here.
Hey, what's that stupid guy with a pipe on your head?
Get on out of here, you sub-monster.
You're no good.
I'm a call on the cops.
The hell?
We tried to kill Jesse Helms by mailing him a subgenius pamphlet years and years ago.
That has often worked.
Inadvertently, sometimes.
It used to be whenever we'd mail a pamphlet to a celebrity, they would die a little while later.
We killed Philip K. Dick, L. Ron Hubbard, Stan Winston just recently.
Winston Churchill?
Larry Fine?
Well, no, that was...
Adolf Erstweil?
And then you sent one to Tim Russert?
Well, that was an accident.
So, yes, friends, we will have to have another big party, I guess, the next day, next year.
Except for the fact that...
Bob's whole lesson of X-Day is that we don't know what day or planet this is.
Could be tomorrow.
Ye never know when the master of the world ends tomorrow.
The world does end tomorrow, and you may die if you don't have that subgenius membership card in your pocket.
And even if you do, you will die.
But those with the membership card will be resurrected into beautiful new bodies
aboard the escape sausages of the sex vessel men.
You lied!
You lied to me!
I want my money back!
Three times!
Newbies.
Three times my money back!
The new kids, listen to that.
Salvation!
Here is the salvation!
Look at this guy.
Wait, wait, wait.
We can't handle you.
Salvation.
Look, you guys have to understand that I've heard these exact same lines since 1996.
Every 7-0-1.
No, no, no.
Somebody's got to do it.
It's a tough job.
You weren't eating your alien jankum.
But J.R. Bob Dobbs was the one who said, and it wasn't him that said it, it was Jehovah One,
delivered the message into Bob's head that on July 5th, 1998 at 7am, the world would end.
By these stripes, we know that it is not yet 1998.
And the lesson of X-Day remains that you don't know.
You don't know what year this is.
You don't know what planet this is.
You don't know, like Santa Claus might, whether you've been good or bad.
Are you ready?
A rupture could happen at any second.
And I wish it would in the next 10.
It wasn't that easy, Armin, it wouldn't have.
To another countdown.
So, yeah, that's right.
It's a lesson, sure.
Yeah, an important lesson that everybody should learn.
That you've got to be right with Bob at every moment.
Ready to be ruptured.
Have your membership card in your pocket.
Wow, that meeting was tough.
What are you going to do?
Hoist a couple of brewskis?
Nah, I was just going to go back and try and fondle the old woman.
She's avoiding me for the last three, four months.
I don't know what the hell's wrong.
Could it be my breath?
My eyebrows or the bob pin?
You know, it's your breasts.
But let's go down to Doc Fropp's camp.
And we can hang out and goo and all that stuff.
He's going to do anything about these breasts?
Well, I don't know.
But at least we can get some rest.
I hope we can get some goo.
And so they wandered into the camp of Dr. Fropp and the Goo Goo Breast.
Oh, sorry. I didn't mean to kick your fire onto your tent like that.
It's hard to see.
Got any goo?
Come on, man. Could you just get...
He's not here right now.
Look at all these guys waiting to get goo.
Where's Doc Fropp? He must have left.
He's the enabler who keeps you stabler.
He's up at the inflatable pavilion.
Frog watching, I think.
And in a little while, they were all watching the frogs.
And the frogs are watching Fropp.
I was rather horrified to watch the long lost daughter of Dr. Legume, who had just been rediscovered,
gazing upon her own father's nakedness in the baptism pool.
They didn't do that back in the old days.
Like the daughters of Noah.
Yes.
They didn't consider the old days.
But, you know, this is like a new paradigm.
These kids today aren't like they used to be.
Demure, quiet.
Now they break coffee tables with ball peen hammers.
For fun.
They take off the clothes at the drop of a hat.
It's gonna kill your grandmother.
Not like this in Budapest. No, no.
It's not even...
Please hurry up and kill your grandmother.
Barbara?
I'm tired of living.
I'm leaving you this note to let you know that I've gone off to join a strange cult.
If within three weeks you do not hear from me,
I, your former... your husband...
Oh, Jesus Christ, this is taking a long time.
What?
Alright.
If you do not hear from me in three or four weeks,
send the preponderance of the rest of the...
Oh, screw it.
I'm leaving forever.
Barbara, this is Mel.
I just wanted to call you.
Please call me back.
Oh, hell, I'll just tell you.
I'm pregnant.
Hi, Mel.
This is your friend, Tom.
I was wondering where you've been.
I ain't seen you hoisting a few after the meeting
in the last few weeks.
I was wondering if it was that breast thing I got to take care of.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, this is Ted over at work.
Your friend, the guy with the breasts.
Yeah, you haven't been by.
I haven't been by in the last several months.
Well, we just wanted to...
Oh, hold on, hold on. I'm here. I'm here.
I'm here. I picked up...
Look, it'll never happen again.
You just don't understand.
This X-Day was a lot of pressure.
It's a lot of laughs.
I'll tell everybody when I come in, okay?
Don't worry. Everything's fine.
I'll be ready for the meeting.
Pass out the toast.
Everybody's staring at me.
Except me.
Like the employee who walked in late.
We're on the West Coast.
You should say something important now.
At least you look...
If you drove for...
Okay.
Dumbass!
We're all suckers.
I can't eat this.
Look, little Dobbs said communion wipers from last year.
Now that would be a good fuck-em if it...
They can't eat this.
They can't take a joke moment.
I think these are...
They have a...
Burgot mold seems to be growing on these little pieces of bread.
Ancient...
Yeah, you can pass them out. Pass them around.
And then people eat them and then they pass out.
If we eat those, will we wake up from our trance and be on the saucers?
It is a little embarrassing for the subgeniuses who tell off their boss on the Friday before X-Day
and then run up all their credit cards, max them out,
and, uh...
Then they have to go back.
You fathead!
Why I oughta...
I don't know how many times that's happened to me.
Well, some of them have to max out their credit cards
just getting to X-Day.
Mm.
Well, most people use cars
or something with wheels.
And then, uh, once they get there and they're stuck,
uh, the brushwood people put them to work.
To work off their...
Debt.
Wagons full of firewood.
So, so back to the...
Basically, we were stuck at brushwood
and somebody came up to us and said,
How'd you like to take garbage out?
And we said, sure.
And, uh...
And then...
You took out the...
Garbage?
Time to take out the garbage.
So that's where all those anonymous and chicken-head people...
Aha!
And so the X's said it was time to take out the trash.
And so they did.
Every single time.
And the last little thing
was to take out the trash.
And when they got back,
they were like,
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
A helpless drunken beer blather from Delaware.
Yes! Yes!
That's right!
Oh!
Attention, subgeniuses.
Subgenii!
I'm one of you!
Can we say subgenii? Is that okay?
No!
You guys are sure new.
I never came here to...
The newbies room.
This is the first X-Day or something.
We got some spring chickens over here.
Spring chicken heads!
And the first X-Day with chicken heads.
The first chicken head was X-Day, actually.
Well, once the X's get here and see the choice of beer,
I'm sure they'll turn around and go right back home.
That's right!
Although, I guess at least it's not Heineken's.
It is half blue ribbon, goddammit.
Cover the sheep!
Wear me as a lamp!
I'm a lamp!
I will provide quite good coverage for your living room.
I will run out of the lighting,
kill if you will,
or entertaining friends.
You're gonna be a charmer!
I am a great planter!
Beast-chips!
Well, granted, I mean, you have to say,
you didn't ask for it, you got it.
Everyone say hi to Chicken Head!
Hi, Chicken Head!
Now, chicken...everybody...
The doctor says they have to wear a helmet!
They have to wear a helmet!
The doctor says so!
Make the chickens give us head!
Well, maybe Pete there has learned something
and came back to tell us who it was amongst us
we had to look out for.
I know who it is!
I know who the monster is!
Who is it, Charlie? Tell us!
I know who it is that doesn't belong among us!
What are you waiting for?
Come on! I swear I know who it is!
Well, come on, Charlie, come on!
Tell us! It's...
The Spiderman!
Understand the procedure now.
Sit back and watch the pattern.
And this pattern is always the same,
with few variations.
They pick the most dangerous enemy
they can find, and it's
The Self Genius
Power of
SWAT
And I take it this is not unique,
by no means.
Their world is full of Power of
SWAT
And we'll go from one to the other
and destroy their radios.
One to the other.
You know, we tell the people
we always sacrifice the newest people
if the sausage doesn't come out.
You know what?
We were never here last year.
I dare you.
You know, um...
Maybe the reason the Spiderman
sausages didn't come is because
they screams
I'm really sorry.
Outsiders!
Those impetuous youths from Chickenhead sure could drink a lot of Pabst Blue Ribbon before 7 a.m.
Someone was drinking bad champagne up there.
Did you see all those beer cans lining the stage?
Were those really beer cans, though, or were those perhaps the very aliens we'd been waiting for?
Stout little guys with aluminum plastrons?
I think Stang is on to something. Did you hear him talking?
No, I was on something. I wasn't on to you.
Oh, never mind.
Yes, and that's just when that phalanx of bobbies descended, waving their arms wildly,
surrounded Ivan Stang with the same lame jokes.
It caused him to...
to have what we call an incident, and he's under observation now.
It's a pretty dull show, actually.
Well, of course it's a dull show, but it's not a real show, Mr. Stang,
or whatever your real name is. Just hold your hand up this...
How many fingers am I holding up?
Just a moment, Doctor. I'll handle this.
This may seem a dull show to you, Mr. Stang, but there are millions of listeners
to whom this is a very important matter.
To them, this subgenius business that you started is no...
joke, and somebody is going to have to answer to someone one of these days,
and it might as well be today, and it might as well be now, and it might as well be you.
I just... I just meant that it was sort of boring observing that Stang guy.
Oh, oh yeah, right.
Right now.
Real snooze-worthy. Man, it'll put you to sleep.
You should see him when he gets manic, man.
There's like times of the day he's like... totally somnamb, he's just like laying there,
and then he'll just jump up and... he starts smashing his teeth, and he's pulling...
he's trying to pull out his bottom jaw.
All right, all right, it's bad enough when he does it, you know.
Really?
He'll need you to do it, but...
Anyway, the amino acids played, they were great.
They played a really lively set.
Do not attempt to flip the tape when you reach the end of side one.
No matter what you are told by later instructions on the tape, there is no side two.
However, if you do discover one, don't look at it.
Say it's done.
battlefield
You
need to make this a part of a video
Seriously, you despise me.
OMFG
Bye Bye!
Thank you.
Stupid politicians.
Oh, yeah?
Well, you won't get away with it.
We've got some friends waiting for us.
When we don't show up, they're going to follow us out here looking for us,
and they're going to bust up this whole weird place.
Please let us go.
We'll promise never to tell anyone about it.
I'm afraid that's impossible.
And as far as someone discovering this,
that doesn't bother me in the least.
You'll have to excuse me now.
I have work to do.
Remember what I said.
Behave yourselves, and you won't get hurt.
Come on.
All I can say is this, my friends.
Thanks to J.R. Bob Dobbs,
this is the only day of the year
that I have to get up at 6 o'clock in the goddamn morning.
That's right, Bob!
Those of you with conspiracy street jobs, believe me.
This is just as Bob suffered
as Bob suffered.
For the pinks, by wearing polyester,
I suffer for the jobbed.
Just say, I'm so sick.
I'm waking up one day early
and putting on a suit.
Let's see if another caller...
Not after this.
Hello, you're on the air.
Hello?
Hello.
Dr. Sinister?
Yes, sir.
Oh, this is the Reverend Angry Larry.
Hey, there.
Angry Larry!
Yeah!
Now, Larry, calm down.
Remember your blood pressure.
You mean all nasties.
Ha, ha, ha.
You guys having a delay?
I can tell, because I'm driving through Cleveland right now.
Oh, yes, we are big fans of the delay.
Don't be careful, Cleveland.
Going to drive through you.
Hi.
Hello, Dave.
Hey, what's going on, Larry?
How you doing?
Just driving home to Detroit.
Well, it looks like you're about halfway there.
We have had a great time at X Day this year.
It was great.
We had a lot of fun.
No new organs to speak of?
The, uh...
No.
Reverend Angry Larry is one of the roadies.
He's like the road manager for the amino acids.
Right.
And I own everything.
And yet, he's never...
Yeah, he's...
I was explaining that to Dr. Howell earlier, that you own everything.
And yet, mysteriously...
Everything that the aminos touch.
And yet, mysteriously, I've never seen you standing with all fours.
I've seen four of them at the same time.
Well, they debuted their new motion picture.
Well, the aminos don't hang around, really, so...
As I understand it, they find the smell of humans and other primate types rather offensive.
They aren't the only ones.
Yeah.
They've got a plan.
The man with the plan.
Can you give out the website for where to see the amino movie at all?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, absolutely.
It's www.fetishist.com.
Fetishist.com.
Is that F-A-T-A-L-E?
Right.
As if it was Fatali.
Yeah.
Like a femme fatale.
Femme fatale.
That's number one in a series of four.
And we're looking at their number four is going to have some stars in it.
Some stars?
Oh, so you're...
Oh, yeah.
What are things?
I've been waiting for the astronomical educational one.
We're looking at Ted Ramey.
I'm looking at Ted Ramey.
And possibly Pee Wee Herman, because as you know, he owes me.
He owes me, too, as a matter of fact.
He owns you, man.
Pee Wee Herman.
I paid his subgenius membership, so...
And he sends me a Christmas card every year, but, yeah, we want him to be in the amino movie.
You know, I'm young enough that I learned what masturbation was from the Pee Wee Herman incident back in the 80s.
Really?
You're far too tall to play him on screen.
Yeah, it's like...
It's like seven or eight when that happened.
Man, I didn't learn from Pee-wee when I was that age.
Who explained it to you?
Pee-wee himself?
No.
Here's what you do now.
Hold on to this thing.
I had seen in the paper that he was arrested for indecent exposure.
Why did you know what that was?
You Googled indecent exposure.
Well, they didn't have Google back then.
Parents had to tell their kids about Pee-wee.
Parents had to tell their kids.
Now, listen, son.
We don't want to cause a big problem, but...
Shut up.
I'm trying to watch Pee-wee.
Yeah, Matt.
Matt Pee-wee, I don't think you should be watching Pee-wee every time I catch you out here.
You're watching Pee-wee.
Is that why they call him Pee-wee?
Oh, my God.
Where did you hear such things?
You just...
Get over here right now.
You're going to go through your choice.
Hi, me.
Oh.
The tyrannosaurus Rex was bad because he...
You know there's no basement at the Alamo.
Hey, me.
Hey.
Okay.
I...
All right, kids.
Now, settle down.
Pee-wee will be back in just a moment.
On this screen may be projected the total scientific knowledge of the crowd from its
primitive beginning to the day of its annihilation.
We refuse an emergency.
Screams, relaxing conoises the
нажmints
Wen정
Wench
Reverend Angry Larry, were you aware that there was a UFO sighting during the Amino Acids concert?
I heard about that.
You may have wondered why the audience suddenly fled the terrible music.
It wasn't just that the music was bad.
There was fire in the sky, my friends.
Yeah, that had nothing to do with the Aminos.
It could have been some of their enemies.
I was thinking it was their limo coming to pick them up as soon as they finished the show.
They're known for short concerts.
Well, they got tired of waiting and they took off.
The Amino ship is not very...
It's almost like a Pinto.
More of an Appaloosa.
It's not that well built of a machine anymore.
It's gone through a lot.
And part of the reason why they want more money is so that they can find the part to rebuild.
Speaking of money...
We meant to give the Amino Acids their pay for the show, but by golly, they just weren't around when we had to leave.
They drank it out.
We'll have to square that away later.
It's only because the rest of the roadies left me there.
And I, once again, I felt so much like staying.
It's unbelievable.
I even told Pops or Nostril about that.
I said, yeah.
They left me.
So, therefore, I had to load the equipment all by myself while my lovely wife was up there working in the kitchen.
Packing a mean load.
I know the feeling.
Now, this time, you know, I was replaced by a female clone.
A Stangina that has previously been known as Priestess Pisces.
Yes.
She took on the weight of the world and had the nervous breakdown.
So, that's what...
And Reverend Steve Sinek and other people did the official Stang act of videotaping while performing.
That's another tricky thing.
I basically, I sat back and watched the whole thing.
Well, you did marry Steve Sinek off to a beautiful, wild, subgenius girl.
That's right.
That was one of the...
Actually, one of the most bizarre moments of any X-Day.
I did not even know she was a subgenius.
Reverend...
Well, no, actually, technically, I don't think Allison ever did send in her 30 bucks,
but she certainly qualifies on many other levels.
It was good to have her there.
She looks great.
I did grab your tripod you left.
Hey, keep your hands to yourself.
Oh, we were wondering.
Tripod?
You have it.
I thought you were grabbing my pod.
Yeah.
That's actually Reverend Steve Sinek's tripod, and he was on his honeymoon and probably forgot that particular leg.
Oh.
The third, that third leg.
The last leg of the journey.
Yeah.
I can't blame him.
It was a pretty confusing evening there towards the end.
Well, you need your third leg and a third eye.
It was just...
A third nostril to get through when the times were tough.
We are all the slaves of a great...
And powerful civilization.
Let us prepare for our rulers.
It was just like Burning Man, minus 30,000 people.
And a lot of interesting acts.
And minus one crazy torching the man early.
Actually, the guy that burned the man prematurely is a friend of Dr. Howell's.
It is so.
Really?
Yeah.
Dr. Howell...
He's been sent away for...
Re-grooving?
For valuation?
From 18 months to four years for arson.
Oh, great.
Wait, wait, wait.
For Burning the Burning Man?
For Burning the Burning Man.
Yes, they call that arson.
And the reach of the Burning Man organization, or the BAMORG.
Oh, yes.
Or Borg, as we call it, is a long one.
Yeah.
They made me stop selling that little Burning Man image mug that I made.
Oh, those folks just don't want to...
It wasn't even a photo.
It was a dang drawing, a painting, artwork of a Burning Man with Boba.
They're protective of their weird kook religion.
Well, it occurred to me that that's the trademark lawyer the Church of the Subgenius
needs.
If they're that on top of it, that they stop Reverend Ivan Stang from selling a CGI image
of the man.
And they're the lawyers for me, boy.
A legal pit bull.
That's right.
Bulldog!
Uh, hi, Ivan.
Just sit down.
I'll have the secretary be bringing you some papers to sign.
I'll be right back.
I'll take a nap.
Gee, what a swell-looking office.
You're sure this guy isn't way out of our price league?
Uh, I don't know.
Do we have a price league, or are we...
Careful.
If you damage that cushion, you're going to have to pay for it.
Twenty thousand price leagues under the lawyer.
Oh, shh.
Here he is.
Coming back.
Here you are, sir.
Now, just sign on this sheet here, and this one here, and this one here.
How about if I just take the time to read this first?
Uh, well, why don't you just, uh...
Mary Lou, Mary Lou, Mary Lou, just take a quick look.
It's just a formality.
Just a formality.
You can skip right through and just sign at the bottom.
This, uh, all rights in perpetuity clause.
Why is that all in Latin?
That looks like it was written in blood.
Ah, this is, I think, written in a pig's blood.
But I'm just going to sign it here, because I want to go get a burrito.
Here we go.
There you are.
Yes.
.
The brain of these primitives seemed quite suitable for our purposes.
We have made the most excellent choice.
Speaking of the amino acids, how come I've never seen any of them strip naked and jump into the baptism pool?
They really don't need it.
They were baptized when they first arrived in 1962.
They've got good taste.
I thought they were just washed down the tubes.
The first one that hopped out of a vortex.
Washed up.
And pretty much told them at that time that, well, the world's not ready for you gentlemen yet.
And he wanted them to come back in 1998.
I don't get that.
The gentleman part, that's for sure.
And the other part is, I thought that the amino acids were a slathery form of DNA scoop,
which is spun in a cyclotron and then spat out by doctors and so forth.
And that seems like a rather creamy mixture to actually withstand such pressure.
Oh, no.
It will all be revealed in some of the one film.
So it's kind of a throwback.
It will be in black and white.
And that's...
Actually, we're the...
We're trying to get Ted Raimi to play Bob Dobbs.
What?
If I can't...
He is a very big subgenius fan.
And an amino acid fan, too.
Some of the things that happened out there.
Now, what was the last big role that Ted Raimi was in?
Well, I know he did just about every movie that his brother ever made.
His brother Fred Ramey
Sam Ramey
Sam, man
Well, he was in Xena, Warrior Princess
He's in the Spider-Man movies
And he would show up in the Spider-Man movies
And the Spider-Man Chronicles
I think he was in the
Same theater as Pee-Wee
But, Reverend Angry Larry
Aren't you familiar with the history
Of what happens to people who play Bob Dobbs
Or pretend to be Bob Dobbs?
Right
Well, then
Well, we were just trying to figure out
Who else could possibly do it
We were only doing that just so that
Ted might just show up on the set
And, well, we could put his name in the credits
I've always assumed
Well, we're working on the contract
To have Andy Serkis play J.R. Bob Dobbs
He's known for his work
In his roles as Gollum and King Kong
That makes him ideal for the part
Right, right
Oh, then that, you know
We can only
Bob has to be a performance capture situation
Because you can't photograph Bob
He, ever since 1967 or so
He fogs film, erases tape, and so forth
Even if you're not trying to take a picture of it
If he looks at your camera
That pretty much erases everything
Because of the quantum singularity in his head
Well, but that can all be added to that
It has to be added in, in post
Well, singularity
Right, everything about Bob has to be added in post
Yeah, it will all be done in post
Hmm
Post haste
Because you're never going to actually make it
Make it work and make it stick
Because his head is too elusive
It's post time
We were lining up some actors
For the subgenius movie
We definitely have Johnny Depp
To play Ivan Stang
Because he looks so similar
And Scarlett Johansson as Princess We Are Doe
Oh, come on
Why not
Oh, never mind
Jim Carrey as Dr. Philodrummon
Because of the rubber face
And other rubber parts
Well, why not let Pee Wee then play Bob?
Dr. Howell was going to be played by Wilford Brimley
And unfortunately Larry Harmon died
Before he could play Lonesome Cowboy Dave
Blackstrap Molasses
That'll keep you going
Now, why couldn't Dr. Howell just be played by Dr. Howell?
Well, Dr.
Hey, I'm available
It's me out here
I'm trying to get you work, Doctor
You know, it's funny
A lot of people
I'm a member of Actors Inequality
People seem to know Dr. Howell better
For his voice work on that
Hiya kids, hiya
Just as for some reason
They seem to know Princess Wee
And myself better for that silly
Numa Numa song
Which I told you before
If I'm in a bad mood, I watch that
And it brightens me
And it makes me smile
It makes the revered angry Larry less angry
When I watch you two do the Numa Numa song
Every time you're feeling retarded
Like a silly loser
You've watched out and go
I'm not nearly as bad as some people
Can I pollute the air with just one thought?
And I know it's boring
And it's been said many times before
But don't you realize
The possibilities of an angry Larry
Find how that would change the dynamic
Of the Three Stooges
What if my wife and I were to die?
And Moe came up and slapped an angry Larry
And instead of him going
God, that never occurred to me
Instead of him going
Something like he said
Hey man, you do that one more time
It's the angry Larry song
Angry Larry fine and laid back Moe Howard
What a horrifying nightmare
That's when Moe had his hippie period
He lost his edge, you know
His smiling, friendly, stoned old time
Well everyone, I am going to get off the phone
So I can actually listen to the show
Because it's on this funny
But it's on now
I hope that
We're listening to it
We're listening to it on the
You are?
Can I listen?
That Amish buggy
That you're still on your way out of Sherman with
Hey Larry, before you go
When are we going to see the amino acids
On Saturday Night Live?
I don't know
When Saturday Night Live gets some taste
You probably know Lorne Michaels, don't you?
When Saturday Night Live comes back to life
I tell you what, Stang
I know you were on the Jon Stewart show
You need to contact Jon Stewart
And tell him you want to see him
You want to come back on
And push your new book
I think
He wants to come in from the cold
I got carried away
I smashed his watch
And he's never spoken to me since then
That was a watch his grandmother gave him
Right
You weren't supposed to put your hand on his lap
In the middle of filming, too
Well, that too
But he's a famous celebrity, man
I know how you felt
How can I keep my hands off him?
Well, now you have to go on the Stephen Colbert show, Stang
It's like a baby
You want to pinch his cheeks
And you know, Stang
You should go on Stephen Colbert
Yeah, I should
I'll do that
I should
Somebody should do that
Yeah, somebody should
Really should
You should?
Yeah, you should
Should is a very strong word
Well, okay
I am going to hang up
And have a great evening, everyone
Real quick before you go, Larry
It's been great hanging out with everyone this weekend
Hey, Larry
Real quick before you go
Hold on, wait a minute
Yeah, real quick before you go
Can you repeat the website for the Amino?
Acids movie?
Oh, www.fatalpictures.com
Or they can go
Or they can go on to the aminoacids.com
Or you can just go to SubSite
Subgenius.com
And you can look it up
That's right
Thanks for your contribution, sir
All roads lead to SubSite
Exactly
Thank you, everyone
Praise Bob, Larry
Thank you, Larry
Bye
Angry, Larry
And happy moving in the city of the future
The lab will fix it
And now priestess Pisces
And the fat-free amino acids
At 11X Day
It's getting scary down here, Bob
Conspiracy's thicker than molasses
And an Alaskan winner
I don't know how we're going to make it, Bob
We really need to make it
We need to
Where are you, Bob?
Bob?
Where are you?
Damn you, Bob
You keep fucking us over
You bastard
Where are you, Bob?
I don't know, you broke my neck
ū
I kind of feel like I've been dropped
Like a bad prom dress
Do you know where Bob is?
We should put up wanted posters
You know, like, Lost Bob
Please call
Or write to the sacred P.O. Box
If you've seen Bob
Missing in action
But we're trying to gain traction
Of course I can't blame him
We just kill or maim him
But he's missing in action
And we're trying to gain traction
But I ain't seen him
And goddamn, we need him
Where's Bob?
Have you seen Bob?
Bob?
Where is Bob?
I feel so dejected
Ew!
Fucked and rejected
Goddamn you, Bob
Fuck you, Bob
Wrote me hard and put away wet
Is this all I get?
You don't answer my calls
Or my emails
I've sent you
42 letters
What about the baby, Bob?
Don't you care about your son?
You bastard!
You weren't around, so I put your son in the convent
And they're taking care of him
You fucking bastard
And I know you beat me and you mistreat me, Bob
But I'm not taking care of you, Bob!
and you did all that surprise butt sex
when I was trying to take a sleep.
But I really forgive you, Bob.
Bob, if you'd just come back,
I swear that I'll clean up the house for her
and I'll be a good little girl for you, Bob.
Just, Bob, I'm sorry that,
I'm sorry I was so mean to you, Bob.
Please, just come back, Bob.
Bob, I just don't know,
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
Please, Bob.
All the way from Berkeley.
Don't mention it.
I do appreciate you coming here.
Anytime, Michael.
We have to do this next year.
He is the host of his own program,
Puzzling Evidence on KPFA.
And the Ask Dr. Howell Show
on Pirate Cat Radio 87.9 FM
and on the internet at piratecatradio.org.
No, piratecatradio.com.
That's .com, Howell.
What?
It's piratecatradio.com.
Didn't I?
Oh, yeah, you're right, Rocknar, of course.
It's piratecatradio.com.
And it's kpfa.org.
kpfa.org.
N-W-R-E-K dot org.
A little taste of, uh...
N-W-C-S-B dot org.
Dot org.
This has been Synesthesia.
We'll be back same time next week.
It's not a threat, that's a promise.
Praise Bob.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Praise No Money Mark.
Praise Governor Rocknar.
Thank you.
Until next time, folks.
Keep it surreal.
And now, Reverend Motormack of motormack.com at 11X Day.
It appears we have been screwed once again by J.R. Bob Dobbs,
and I wish to express my disappointment.
My disappointment that I had to take off from my conspiracy job
and come here on vacation for at least five days.
My disappointment.
That I had to party like it was the end of the world.
Get drunk.
Get naked in the hot tub.
Rave.
No, I'm sorry.
No rave.
Rave.
Don't rave.
Eat the best food in the world.
Drink some of the most amazing forbidden drinks that you could ever experience.
Jacob!
When, you know, if it wasn't for J.R. Bob Dobbs,
right now, this morning, I'd probably just be in my bathroom whacking off.
Jacob!
Where is he?
So I just have to say how disappointed I am in J.R. Bob Dobbs
and in Ivan Stang for making this possible.
I'd rather be wearing these.
Very good point.
Well, Motormack, there are bathrooms right up there.
Broke the blame.
If you want to resume your jacking off, I was thinking about that very thing myself.
We have video cameras.