Hi, I'm a trained professional just waiting for you.
If you're ready to take your life, it's time to put yourself first.
You can call the number on your screen.
We're waiting to hear from you.
The Muppet in your head is like a gorilla who crapped a watermelon in my brain.
They were so insistent.
One, two, three!
The subgenius power of squirt.
Thank you.
As we entered the courtroom, we heard the clerk of the court saying,
Silence in the court.
You have been found guilty of the subgenius power of squirt.
The sentence of this court is that you be,
hanged by the neck until you are dead.
Ha! If you ask me, hanging's too good for him.
Oh, boy. Wait a week, Admiral. Here's a buff person.
That's good, yeah?
Yeah, it's good.
Oh, chief is?
Oh, chief is fine.
Yeah, yeah, chief is.
Let me go, yeah?
Yeah, yeah, let me go.
Let me go.
Rancher Joe Martinez and his grandson tried to help Debbie Hunt,
who went into premature labor,
but it was in a breached position,
and Mr. Martinez had to use chains
to pull the large fetus out.
They really had to work to pull it out because it had a big, big head.
It was just a big, round head, round and something.
And when they opened the mouth,
they found TV reporter Marisa Mays under the cheeks.
As he moved the head from one side to the other,
you could literally see the fluid sploshing back and forth.
It was grossly mutilated.
Ring next, go, stay parked.
I will have photographs of this abnormal fetus posted within about 30 minutes.
And make them happy.
Participating subjects adversely affected by accessory organs.
Now, accessory organs that give you scientific throat and not nose.
The medical specialist stated,
It is my opinion that accessory organs were throat and not nose.
And pre, what are your names, my friend?
Poor children.
My name is Greco.
And my name is Hansel.
Hansel?
The End
Every day in London,
people wait quietly in line.
In an orderly manner,
no crowding or pushing out of turn,
in a cheerful way.
London is getting quick and comfortable.
Busier.
Neater.
Easier.
Thoughtless.
In a friendly manner.
Always punctual.
Friendly cooperation.
Time goes presently.
Right on time.
No rushing nor crowding.
Much kindness.
Friendly hands give help at once.
Excellent service.
Healthy and pleasant.
Very important.
Pleasant special safety.
Right on time.
Efficiency and comfort.
Good service.
Civilization.
Quality.
Willing, orderly and friendly cooperation.
Far away from London, people are kindlier.
No one is hindered at all.
Africans in particular have a quick instinct
and seem to know when they are with friends.
The End
That's the thanks you get.
He's the same as all the rest.
What he doesn't want to be so, just isn't so.
No skin off my nose.
My 30,000 safe.
And I deserve every last penny of it.
And more and more and more.
What's keeping you then, Dan?
Be honest now, Daniel.
Fear.
Fear and habit.
You get into the habit of serving.
Born a servant, see.
Son of a servant.
Family of servants.
From a nation of servants.
Very first thing an Englishman does, straight from his mother's womb,
is touch his forelock.
That's how they can tell the wrinkled little bastards English.
They don't know about me.
Not they.
They don't know about Daniel Tucker.
Just old faithful Tucker.
Give doggy boney.
You know who I really am.
Alexei Kronstadt.
Anarchist, Trotskyist, communist, revolutionary.
I'm a sell.
For years I've been working for the revolution.
Spitting in the hot soup.
Peas on the wedges were placed.
So raise the scarlet to banner high
Brene's in jail.
We will live and die.
Deleting your life.
Now remember, feel unhappy.
Focus on the things that would make you unhappy.
And delete your life.
Get depressed.
Piece of cake.
Focus on all the tragedy that's happening in the world right now.
Right now.
Children that are dying right now of starvation.
We can make pictures in our head of those bloated stomachs.
Hearing the cries of babies just as they pass off into death.
Seeing flies eating their flesh.
Absolute total pleasure.
Create total pleasure.
Delete a relationship you have.
You could, you could, you could, you could freak out.
This moment, there's so much we could focus on and feel good about.
Does that make sense?
I'm a big doubt.
Gosh, can I really do this?
My brain will get,
I don't know what I asked.
Does that make sense?
Think about it.
Hey, hey, an expand.
Bitch, bitch.
I want you to know that I believe state management.
That moves me, pull me down.
Pull me to areas of frustration and anger and giving up.
Giving up.
A lot of people do things without being aware of how they do it.
Every single day.
Can't be done.
You are absolutely right.
Couldn't be done.
I want you to feel lousy.
Feel bad.
Feel sorry.
Feel hurt.
How can I expand from this.
Experience it again.
Do you have a family?
Do you have a nuclear family?
If not, start one now.
Right now.
Now, ask for your freak.
Now get your freak.
Now, get your free copy of South Korean school nation.
Self-help courses. You can improvise your life.
Do you have a nuclear family? Radiation. People. Right now. Keep calm.
Fertilizer will give you some protection. Fertilizer now.
In case of nuclear attack. Fertilizer protection. Panic burst.
American history. American history. Nuclear attack. Shelter type.
What to do. What to do. What can you do. What to do. The building.
That's why it's important. Take shelter yourself.
Do you have a nuclear family? Danger. Ask for your freak disaster.
Sinks and bathtubs will hold large amounts of water.
Sinks and bathtubs. Sinks and bathtubs. Sinks and bath. Sinks and bath. Sinks and bath.
Do you have a family? Do you have a nuclear family? If not, start one now. Right now.
Living easy. Living free.
Season ticket on a one-way ride.
Asking nothing.
Leave me be.
Taking everything in my stride.
Don't need reason.
Don't need rhyme.
Ain't nothing that I'd rather do.
Going down.
Party time.
My friends are gonna be there too.
I'm on a high way to hell.
High.
Way.
To hell.
High.
Way.
To hell.
What would you say if I had found a Martian down there?
That was Phineas Narco from NationalCynical.com.
And more from him later.
Friends, this is hour of slack number 1094.
And it's a mishmash this time of sex, giant gorillas, puzzling evidence, collages, and bath.
The collages are by Norel Preff and the great Fernandin and Elie Mer.
Separately.
They don't actually work together.
And in this particular show, they're also by yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stank.
And there are so many of them, you just have to look at the logs of the show.
Which are on subgenius.com.
I also chopped up and blended some clips from an old movie called The Ruling Class.
Which is where the rebellious butler and the British Jesus come from.
And this episode owes a lot to Saint Mel Blanc and Saint Karl Stalling.
As will become obvious.
But first, let us exploit KPFA and Berkeley for this episode.
A glimpse into the mysterious world of Dr. Hal Robbins, Dr. Philo Drummond, and Autentotter D. Woodman Atwell on The Puzzling Evidence Show.
In the world of snails and hermaphroditic worms.
Good now.
And don't forget there's the 420.
Worms that splash acid sperm on each other's integument.
Sperm that etches its way into the body.
And then works its way painfully through the tissues of these hermaphrodites.
To find and fertilize the eggs.
There is no passage to bring the sperm to the eggs.
The sperm is acid.
Bubbling and searing through the rubbery hides of these unfortunate annelids.
Then, after the requisite interval.
There you go.
The female leaves a clutch of glistening eggs and glides away.
For so it is in nature's wonderland.
Well, we got no closer to the address.
And we have no closer to the caller.
I can't give you the address.
But I can tell you that everything's coming through at typhoon volume.
And my earphones.
I can hear the earphones with an incredible blast.
Like heaven's cherubim horsed upon the sightless couriers of the air.
And so, also, we've recently received the award-winning CD of music composed on Xerox machines.
We're looking forward to playing that later.
And we're comfortable here with our feet put up on the end iron.
Ready to spend another evening.
In air-conditioned comfort.
In the city of the future.
Long may it rain.
Actually, it's not raining now.
An event on Adolf Hitler's birthday.
Yeah, that's April 20th.
Why would anybody assume that one date was connected to only one event?
Well, that's also the date of the Columbine attack.
Of course it is.
And also the date of Waco.
Yeah.
It's many days, actually.
It's many days.
It's just the day that I get my check.
That's all I care about, sitting here in the bunker.
I should get my check ten days before that.
Assuming that they hold it out to the 45th day.
I've got to hold on somehow.
It's also a subgenius' birthday, Reverend Joy DeVees.
Well, you see, it's an ill wind that blows nobody any good.
At least one more subgenius squeaked into the world, mewling and bawling.
Suicide Man, did you see the eclipse?
No, none of us did.
None of us?
I saw the toenail-y clippings in the sky, like tiny moons, each with its delicate mark.
Oh, grace, it's hard.
Love is my theme and it frightens them.
Happiness my gift and they run.
I try to tie the air in knots and make mountains out of water.
It's hopeless, darling.
That's not a word in love's lexicon.
We'll hear the voice of the turtle throughout the land.
Yes.
Clop, clop, clop.
Well, Goo Goo, that's the first time.
We've had crooks walk right into a paddy wagon.
Si, senor Gracie.
Service right through your door.
Well, genius, how you gonna talk us out of this mess?
Oh, I was here with my distributed gadget, what did you say?
Ooh, well, it tells death to the judge.
And X Day.
X Day, 10 X Day.
Oh, that's scary.
X for 10.
Probably not.
Probably what?
He says X Day's not going to happen.
Oh, it's going to happen, but it's going to happen with a slight calendric adjustment.
It will start later.
Well, yeah, we're gonna get there days early.
By these giant frogs here.
And we're gonna have our own X Day before July 5th.
You see the giant frogs?
And then we're gonna have X Day on the 5th.
With the frogs.
And then we'll have a special X Day after the 5th.
With these frogs from the frog pond.
Oh, yeah.
And they make their melody all night long.
Sweet melody.
I generally like to celebrate the 4th on the 3rd with the 5th.
Well, I don't know whether...
Did you check out Findlay Lake, which is about a mile away from Sherman?
That I did not.
After all my base of operations...
Oh, it's a beautiful little lakefront town.
It's a beautiful little...
That's where these mighty ducks...
Yeah, it's a beautiful little lakefront town.
One must put those mighty ducks in a row.
Ow.
Oh, the mosquitoes are giant here.
Just gotta slap them.
What could that have been?
You know, one of the drawbacks about staying out there is it just gets so cold.
About staying out there?
Drawbacks about staying out there?
No, it's just gets so cold that night.
A drawback about staying.
Here it is.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, what is it?
First for you tonight here on the show, Rocknar Spills about staying out there.
And what did he say?
He said that the Union chief, staying out there, got together with the bugs and left
their own residue on the...
On the vegetative matter as it was arranged for the...
They call it chyme.
Maximum effect.
Yes, an organic agglutinate.
Part of nature's marvelous pharmacopoeia.
Chyme.
This bug juice has been used by sages and scientists since the...
What the...
I faded out there.
The floor.
It's about time.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, it's about space.
About two guys in the strangest place.
Wait till they see what is inside.
Is it good luck?
It's about time.
It's about two guys in the strangest place.
As through the barrier of time they flew, past the fighting Minuteman.
Past the armored knight, past the Roman warrior to this prehistoric site.
Hey, you'll appreciate this.
I appreciate this, Dr. Howell. I found the complete collection of Captain Nice.
You did?
At the same time as Captain Nice was on one network, they had a similar show on the other network, just like the Munsters and the Addams Family.
So while Captain Nice you could see on whatever it was, CBS, I think on NBC or ABC they had Mr. Terrific, which was their version of Captain Nice.
Nice. Don't tell those guys they left all their equipment under there.
Unappealing superheroes, I guess that was the idea.
Yeah, Captain Nice. It was like Underdog.
They were just nice.
Was it animated?
No, they were live action.
No, it was live action. In fact, the guy who played the voice of Kit on Knight Rider, Kit was the special robotic car.
Oh, I like that. David Hasselhoff.
This is the animated or live action?
This is the live action.
He played the voice. The guy that played Captain Nice was the voice of Kit.
Yes, exactly. Well, you've got to put three squares on the table, even in Hollywood.
It is written...
Relax. You never get hard like this. The sad eyes of the girl who serves me.
Yes, the loveliness. Young, nice looking, bright and shining. Each of us, we score and grow.
Yes, it was only natural. Her face had that glad look I'll always remember. Watching her feeling good.
She went through the motions. Joy. Many, many kisses.
Yes, cuddle close. Dreamy young girl. Wonderful girl who wanted nothing in the world more than a big one.
Nine, ten. Though she was quick, yet still they come.
Eating on the run. Happy pain.
You can forgive Charlie for being excited.
Yes, he didn't quite believe one who isn't safety conscious. Yet victims can only be tasted later.
We will not be hanged.
Hating the waste. Haters all of us.
This is Helen. Flavorless. Mrs. Jo. Helen is nevertheless 42 years of good strength and stamina.
Yes, this is the boy across the street.
Crack crack. One, two. 25,567. Hundred or a thousand. Let's get out of here.
Stir stir stir stir ah ah ah ah. Women want the ultimate sex and the man you love.
I'd like to start with a mess. Listen to this. Listen to this story. Yes, yes.
You know just how I'm feeling. We'd be perfect for each other. I have a reputation.
Just give up. Be mysterious or confusing. Problem. Why? Why?
Wanna have more sex? Wanna have more sex with me? What? What? What? What frequent sex? Sex?
No no no no. How? If only you would do X. You know where I'm going with all this, right?
No no no no. Input. Severe emotional problems. We feel what we feel and do what we do.
Psychological problems. Become problems. Nothing's wrong. Whatever. Everything's okay.
Big part of their love pie. Exacerbating. Do it. Do it. Superficial. Superficial.
He's made a spectacular breakthrough. We're in the process of making a new man.
I'm always on the lookout for new men.
Hello. Hello.
Going my way?
Uh huh.
Ah sure, I know. But aren't they all witches inside?
I'm fed up. I'm true with women.
Why I'll kill myself before I'll even know.
You look at another babe.
Britain?
Uh huh.
A fly blown speck in the North Sea.
You can't kick the natives in the back streets of France.
I'm not from Calcutta anymore.
Oh he's joking again. Aren't you my lord?
I'm not laughing Pamela. And we can't stay here any longer.
Then for Christ's sake go.
Oh don't go for my sake.
Delicious. Homegrown.
No I bought them. I mean they go with the...
Ladies! I've decided to begin my second ministry at your gathering.
Last time I preached the word in Holy Galilee I spoke in parables.
Mistake!
Now I must speak plainly.
God is love.
Love?
Love. As water is wet, as jade is hard, as bread is life, so God is love.
Mrs. Pamela Treadwell, can you love?
Can your blood bubble, flesh melt, thighs twitch, heart burst for love?
Your Lordship, I'm a married woman.
Remember the commandment I gave you. Love one another as I love you.
Stay back. My husband is a master of hounds.
Fill your hearts that your souls dance, your eyes sparkle, be bird-happy.
Ow!
What is it?
A Watusi walking stick. Big people the Watusi.
Ow!
Ladies come back! I'll fill your bodies!
Oh I'm awfully sorry. Have you seen my father?
I am the resurrection and the light!
We'll never make it.
Oh you speak English.
Righto. Oxford. 34.
Well gee Mr. Headhunter, thanks for saving us.
Very decent thing to do under the circumstances.
You can help us. We're looking for...
A blonde young lady perhaps. She's with us.
Gee, you don't seem like headhunters to me.
Yes. We're hunting heads right now. Cabbage heads.
And say that young lady showed us how to make a new dish. Guamki.
Guamki?
Yes. Stopped cabbage. Delicious, don't you know?
Yes.
Mmm. Yum. Yum. Guamki.
Clutch Cargo!
Yes Mary. We found your dad. He's okay.
Oh thank goodness. Mr. Cargo, these people have been so helpful.
And Miss Mary taught us how to make Guamki.
Oh yum yum Guamki.
Gosh Clutch, look. They're all smiling. They are friendly headhunters, aren't they?
Oh they are.
C'mon boys, we're all
You know Mr. Headhunter's muito
Nosotros somos aqui
You're gay, don't you get it?
Mr. Headhunter, I'm tired to go to the gym..
of Perry Winkle.
Bless Ted Smoothie
of 22 East Hackney Road.
Bless the mealy red
pole, the black-gloved wallaby
and W.C. Fields
who's dead but lives on.
Bless the snotty-nosed
giraffe. Bless
the buffalo. Bless
the Society of Women Engineers.
Bless
the pygmy hippo.
Bless the mighty cockroach.
Bless
me. Today
is my wedding day.
Obviously,
they did not reckon on me great
dinner strength.
Number four.
If
all else fails,
and it has, you must
utilize the gopher's love of music.
Music. EGAD.
What a boat.
Deformed.
What a boot.
unfinished, sent before my time into this breathing world.
I'm cured of fantasy obsessions, paranoid delusions, I master words.
I, straighten up there.
Am, close up with I, you horrible little word.
God, I am God.
Not the God of love, but God Almighty.
I massacred the Malachites and the seven nations of Canaan.
I hacked Agog to pieces and blasted the barren fig tree, for the day of vengeance is in my heart.
You lunar jackass. She betrayed you. Guilty, guilty, guilty.
The punishment is death. I've finally been processed.
They made me adjust to modern times.
This is 1888, isn't it?
Punishing the innocent?
Nothing. For three days there's been nothing.
Because the world is evil. Wicked.
Sinful.
Let us pray, brethren.
This is the end. The end of the world.
I would let it. I would let it.
Riot and panic. Riot and panic.
Wait a minute.
Panic and terror. Terror and panic. Terror and death is man-made.
We've got to have martial law.
That's my fog.
Sorry, gentlemen. You'll have to excuse me.
I don't know.
What?
I don't know. My fog. My fog device is so constructed and so equipped, there'll be a panic.
A panic?
Deadly new gas.
Gas. Gas. Gas.
A deadly gas?
Yes, a deadly gas. My fog, fog machine, fog machine that will not spare a living soul.
Soul. Soul.
Panic.
I believe your story. I'm forced to believe it.
Start releasing the deadly gas.
Unknown. Unseen.
Poison gas.
Yes. Panic.
Yes, Doctor.
What are you going to do?
You... you're going to release the gas? Insane.
No. But...
I believe the
The gas was killed.
Wait.
Panic terror and death.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Later, Pierce makes another appeal.
Yeah, that's why I need some slack.
Yeah, I need some slack.
As it turns out, Pierce has not needed any slack.
Oh, I thought I heard something drop around here.
No.
Maybe somebody fell down and broke that wood.
I don't know.
Pierce's dad.
On Wall Street, 312-512-465-8645-338-442.
This is PR News.
Israeli media report that Bob's expecting pig pictures from Mexico City.
Bob could come the same day.
The first blast occurred when Bob spent in a bag placed among the stalls at Camp David, Maryland, with caution.
According to drug gangs,
the Senate Foreign Relations Committee begins debate
on PR reports, but only 6% expect PR news in Washington.
PR comes from oatmeal.
You gurneys don't draw the line at murder.
Upper class extramant!
You want to do me dirt?
That's because I know too much.
I know that 1% of the population owns half the property in this country.
And that vomity 1% wants kosher killing.
And up so the blue blood drains out slow and easy.
So comrades, come ready.
And the last fight, let us face.
The international army unites the human race.
I'm only a strolling vagabond.
So goodnight pretty maiden.
That's what I've always said.
You can't give the working class money.
And now the battle continues, the civil war between the big Indians and the little Indians.
I'm on the wrong side of what's going on.
It all started when the emperor of Lilliput,
cut his finger on an egg shell.
When opening the egg,
from the large end.
He made a decree that from henceforth all eggs should be opened at the small end.
But the big Indians of Lefkoskiu rebelled.
Jerry Anderson Studios junk.
Planet Patrol, I think, was something else.
And no, it's said that perhaps no copies of that one exist anywhere.
Travels all land around the sea.
And it can journey anywhere.
It was my favorite.
Supercar.
It had Captain Larry Dart in charge of the spaceship.
And the Venusian who was like Spock.
Yeah.
And a big Martian who loved to eat and was very funny.
Like the thing, you know.
Yeah.
And they would run around and help the universe.
Face sign name.
Yeah.
Just little string people.
Don't forget.
Oh, here we have fresh from Robert Dobbs.
Seven foolproof alibis to calm the wife.
Have the courage to look the little woman straight in the eye with the...
And utter the boldest of floppers.
There are only so many lines you can feed the little woman.
The trick is to make them convincing.
Here's a happy expert who tells you how.
Can you go out with the boys any night you please?
Does your wife understandably allow you to beg out of boring social events in favor of
the poker table?
Or any other evening entertainment you may really have in mind?
Do you have a wealth of excuses with getting out of your home sweet home?
Well, here's seven foolproof alibis composed by your favorite guru, Robert J.R.
Bob.
Hiya Bob.
See what else I found.
And here they are.
Number one, honey, I am working late at the office.
Number two, honey I've got to get the wife the car repaired.
Not the wife the little Freudist.
Yeah.
The wife repaired.
Honey, I'll be working out at the Y tonight.
Honey.
I'll be out with the boys.
We're starting a camera club.
Honey.
I have a sick friend.
and I have a duty to nurse them back to health.
I'll be working late tonight to make some extra dough.
And don't forget, I'll be spending the afternoon at the races.
Well, that would convince anyone, I would think.
A special significance for me. I like that last one.
Yeah, you work at the racetrack, don't you, Governor?
You know, what would help is the seven-bladed windbreaker,
and you put each of these excuses on each blade of the windbreaker.
So as the wind catches them, they spin like hypnotic little discs.
And the wind breaks?
Yeah, as the wind breaks, and they spin their magic on any woman of your choice.
And you don't even have to worry about which blade comes up.
Right.
They're all equally valuable.
That's right.
I hope that someone didn't imply, that I didn't imply,
that there was an order of importance or a priority in those seven famous excuses of Dobbs.
Now you see the importance of the seven-bladed windbreaker.
It has a way of dispelling any concept of priority
and puts it back in the world or realm of randomness, where it belongs.
Where it was said, behold, the river of pee.
It is dirty because it accepts everything.
Look closely and you will see.
An old broken wheel floating by.
The wheel of karma.
That thing almost hit me.
Damn it.
I'm not gonna lie to you.
Hansel?
Hansel.
Mr. Sarge, Super Sarge, whoopity-doo.
Your boss in the wakes.
Now take over, snafu.
Important announcement.
Attention, each tent.
This camp is now run under new management.
Relaxation.
More money.
These are my aims.
The new management.
No GI issue.
Each guy gets two things.
Yay!
Parade for snafu gives us all limousines.
No more drill, no salutes.
No more cleaning latrines.
Look me over, Jackson.
This is really all root.
Snafu lets you dress up in a suit that is zoot.
And you can't even get a good look.
Ain't this swell?
I fixed things.
I told you I could.
What a camp.
No more discipline.
Boy, am I good.
I beg pardon, sir, but you hear all that humming?
I got a suspicion.
The joymans are coming!
The joymans?
All right, them poops.
Let me at them joymans.
Say, where are my troops?
Troops!
And next!
No use, they ain't trained and they got no morale.
Your army's a washout, my fine-footed pal.
ymptwe backs
Try bringing
This says how it sounds, here.
abis do eesnight.
Dealeyland dodevelopment
Buy a ticket to a car wash Sal reporter come to dinner.
UgoWheuj
Time to take a look at what's happening across the country.
We want you to be aware of northeastern Texas moving along Interstate 40 until 10 p.m. tonight.
We also want to mention that we've got Wisconsin stretching from northern Louisiana through Missouri just to the west of Milwaukee.
Also through tonight, southeastern Texas staying above Louisiana.
And as we head further into the northwest, we've got Idaho just off the coast of the Carolinas coming up on Washington.
We'll explain.
My lords, I had doubts about speaking here, but after what I've heard, I realize this is where I belong.
My lords, these are grave times, killing times, stars collapse, universes shrink daily, but the natural order is still crime, guilt, punishment.
There's no love without fear.
By his hand, sword, pike, and grappling hook, God, the crowbar of the world, flays, stabs, bludgeons, mutilates.
Just as I was.
You have forgotten how to punish my noble lords.
The strong must manipulate the weak.
That's the first law of the universe.
The hard survive.
The soft quickly turn to corruption.
This.
Is a call to greatness.
Approach this day unto battle against your enemies.
Let not your hearts faint.
Fear not and do not tremble.
Neither be ye terrified because of them.
For the Lord your God is he that goeth with you to fight for you against your enemies to save you.
And mine eyes shall not spare, neither will I have pity.
I will recompense them according to their ways.
And their abominations that are in the midst of them.
And they shall know that I am the Lord that smite them.
You're one of us at last.
Well done, Jack.
Come, all you Christian soldiers, marching as to war.
With the cross of Jesus.
Glory for before.
Ah, your mother rides a vacuum cleaner.
Truth is fiction.
And this is the Orbit Genoc.
An empty gallon can will hold one gallon of water.
Yet when the same can is converted to a side view likeness of a human face, it will increase its capacity to six gallons of ammonia gas.
And that's the truth.
The natives declared that the miraculous profile was that of King Alfonso the 11th.
The Orbit Linnat.
In a moment I'll tell you how a stroke of lightning struck Salamanca, Spain.
It was designed to conform to the exact size and shape of the base of the great lightning.
The Orbit Linnat.
The Hill of the Bells in Hermosillo, Mexico produces Warren Hastings, the great empire builder and first governor general of British India.
During 41 years of married life, he never wavered in his love of gold.
It's caused by gas escaping from the most seductive murderers in the annals of justice.
The Orbit Linnat.
From PR News in Washington, I'm strewn along a southbound stretch of Interstate 85 this morning.
House Speaker Nancy Pelosi said it might take hours before the road was to be reopened to traffic.
He faces up to 40 years in prison.
Secretary of State Condoleezza Rice is expected to take part in a joint
on Wall Street 12-2-3-2-4-4.
Authorities said this is PR News in Washington.
Okay, what other questions? There's got to be something serious.
Oh yes, the little girl in the back.
You know the dinosaurs that you were showing me a picture of that your friend grew,
is that one of the ones that ate the 40 foot peyote plant?
No, that was a seismosaurus. The one that ate the peyote plant was called Vomit Ultrasaurus.
You really don't want a vomit Ultrasaurus at your party.
That's all they do is vomit.
And just the shinbone of an Ultrasaurus is higher than this room.
They were really big. The dinosaurs that I was taught about as a kid were midgets compared to what they've found since then.
Tyrannosaurus is no longer the biggest meat eater.
There were much bigger, there was a type of Allosaur that was actually called Gigantosaurus.
I learned that from Hal's book.
It was bigger than a Tyrannosaurus. Probably more foul tempered.
Although some people say that the Tyrannosaurus wasn't all that fierce, but was more like a buzzard and a scavenger that ate dead things.
And in dinosaur land, there's lots of dead things.
God, I love dinosaurs.
Now see, if I was going to go back to nature, I'd seriously think about the late Cretaceous.
Any other dinosaur related questions?
Spell effects?
I'm an amateur special effects expert.
How does King Kong come into the picture of these dinosaurs?
Oh, well now in the movie King Kong, that island was so remote that it had not been affected by the cataclysm that wiped out the dinosaurs.
So they had continued to evolve.
And also apes had evolved.
There was a giant ape called Gigantopithecus.
We know perfectly well that's what a Sasquatch is or a Yeti.
But there really was.
I mean, you can go to the Cleveland Natural History Museum and there's a jawbone of a Gigantopithecus that's like this long.
And there's a gorilla skeleton next to it to give you an idea how big this thing was.
It must have been at least 12 feet tall.
But it was a gentle giant.
You can tell by its teeth that it sat on its butt eating bamboo all day long.
It was probably really, really fat.
They lived in Java.
And King Kong, Skull Island as we know from history, before it sank, was just southwest of Subantra.
Any other questions?
What's the significance of the Dunkleosteus from the Hegonian era?
Oh, he heard the Hour of Slack show about the Dunkleosteus?
Yeah.
Well, the significance is...
It has a funny name.
I've seen the skull.
Oh, you have seen the skull.
Nasty looking thing, isn't it?
Yeah, it's that big across.
It was an armored fish.
Shortly after fish came up with the idea of backbones, they became armored.
And the Dunkleosteus has that funny name because he was discovered by Professor Dunkle of the Cleveland Natural History Museum.
Dunkle means dark and shiny.
Really?
Well...
And it was from the Devonian period, which is, as you thought, named after the band D.Va.
I do not have a giant gorilla fetish, my friends.
I do have a lost prehistoric monster fetish.
And also, I've lately been studying some science books about the flora and fauna of Skull Island.
Now, I'm not sure if I'm right or wrong.
It's kind of a depressing hobby because Skull Island vanished beneath the waves in 1948.
And the only remains besides photographs are kept locked up in the Smithsonian.
Those being the bones of the unfortunate Megaprimatus cong, the very last of that species, it turned out,
that was foolishly exhibited and then killed in New York in 1933.
Now, I will admit to being sexually attracted to the face of the planet.
I'm not a big fan of the fake movie character King Kong in the 2005 film of that title,
but I know perfectly well that it's just an uncannily real-looking CGI replica.
I'll never get to see a live Megaprimatus cong.
I had to face that fact about dinosaurs and congs when I was little.
I'll probably never live to see a live Martian either.
At least I got to see a few stuffed ones in the museums before the cover-up.
No, I'll never get to see any of the evolved dinosaurs or insects of Skull Island,
except in jerky old movies and grainy black and white photos.
I wish I could blame it on man's greed or global warming or something,
but I know perfectly well that the very thing that allowed the creatures there to survive the nuclear winter that killed the dinosaurs,
that is, the volcanic vents that kept the island shrouded in fog,
were the selfsame geological features that inevitably led to its collapse back into the sea.
It's a shame that more samples weren't gathered during the expedition,
but those few explorers who escaped with their lives were very lucky to get away with that much.
Of particular interest to me would be the plant or fish glandulars or whatever it was
that gave the human Skull Island natives the will to survive
on their lifeless corner of the ocean.
The Skull Island is a very mysterious place.
Some evidence indicates that they were dependent on this powerful but mysterious drug.
Now, even if I'm not a true Kong sexual, I'll admit I like gorillas and other great apes.
It runs in the family.
My maternal grandfather decorated his house in the West Indies with sculptures and paintings of apes
to the extent that it was called Apes Place all over St. Martin.
The Apes Place is a place where you can find the most mysterious creatures in the world.
It's the island in the Netherland Antilles where we visited Mamu and Papu a few times in my youth
and I have fond memories of caressing the three-foot-tall marble gorilla statue he kept on his front porch.
I wonder if it's still there.
Unfortunately, after Papu died, Mamu sold the house to the famous crappy artist Jasper Johns.
And I...I've been back to the house since Johns bought it,
but he's erected a fence,
and I couldn't see much over the top of it before the native guards chased me away.
Anyway, friends.
Anyway, you can quit it with the Stan Gorilla fetish gags, okay?
You are listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
And this music in the background was, uh, it's by Estrada Sphere.
Yes, that's the name of the band, Estrada Sphere.
And the album is called Palace of Something.
I'll have to take it out of the CD player to tell you the title,
because it's a homemade CD sent to me by Popes Pantiera Ivakovich,
who will certainly be at X Day, uh, X Day, X Day, 10X Day coming up.
Okay, well, the music ended. Now we can look.
Palace of Mirrors, Estrada Sphere.
How about that?
Wonderful, interesting, instrumental music.
Don't know what else to tell you about it.
Estrada Sphere, with an E.
Estrada Sphere.
Ew.
Yes, it's an acquired taste.
Yeah, I mean, but once you're into it, it's like, you know, rubber.
Rubber.
Yeah, I can't wait to get home to my little wife.
In your little rubber suit.
Get her in that Brontosaurus suit.
I'll be the Tyrannosaurus.
We'll deck it out.
Blair.
And I finally got the boredom detector working again.
Yeah, oh, okay, there we go.
Let's move up on that.
My God, it's in the red.
It's in the red.
Oh, it's gone off.
It's gone off.
It's turned on for ya.
Yeah, we switched right over into the flat zone.
That's pretty close to the mediocre range.
Oh, there we go.
It's building back up towards punk.
There it goes, right past anti-music.
Oh, there we go.
It's really getting to me.
I'm not even gonna lie.
It's doing it on the right side.
Did you get that?
I think we've got it.
I think he's broken.
Well, there it went.
He blew out the boredom detector.
Crack the whip, man.
Crack the whip.
Have you ever thought of this?
Have you ever thought about what it would have been like to have been a person somewhere in the past, but not here?
But you might have been like a person somewhere in the past.
Sure, you could be in Rome.
Could be in Rome.
Could be in Troy.
Could be in Terra del Fuego.
You could have been just a, you know, like a tail sniffing.
But so what?
What? Have you ever thought of, did you ever think about that?
Well, I was just wondering, I just want to know.
I thought about it.
Yeah, I have too.
You know, I thought about, you know, maybe being reincarnated from somebody who lived in Rome.
This guy from Kentucky can talk on our show and say he thought about it too.
But I was going to say Tredny Chisholm.
Tredny Chisholm.
Okay, there, I said it.
Well, now you have, and what are you going to make of it anyway, Tredny Chisholm?
Nothing, I'm just going to throw it out there and let the historians of the show figure out what I just said.
Well, they'll have to go.
I don't know.
I don't know what you said.
Of course you do.
To get to the bottom of the Tredny Chisholm.
You really said that God's testicles were his eyes.
Ah, man.
That's a complete misreading of the seventh sacred scroll.
Well, so what's your point?
So what's your point?
Aren't we supposed to misread them?
How many miles of blood vessels are there in an average testicle?
Here we go again.
You've got to walk.
Walk that lonesome valley.
You've got to blow those brainwaves right out the sky.
No one can do it for you.
Loud, Philo.
But it's a metaphor, right?
It's a metaphor for a thing that sounds like something else.
But it's not what I metaphor.
If God's eyes are his testicles, then how many miles of blood vessels are there in it?
No, those are eyes.
Somewhere between the amount of smoke in his pipe.
I mean, you would say, how many puffs are in Bob's pipe?
You might say that same thing.
Let's look.
Bum-diddly, bum-diddly, bim-diddly, bum-diddly, bum-diddly.
Same as before.
See, it's exactly what I thought.
It's the same exact same amount as before.
And just here we are.
We're arriving in front of Jayner's Pro Shop where we'll select our new golf clubs.
Yes, but I just want to say...
No.
Did you bring the, did you bring your allowance this time?
I'm not sure we should interfere with the ceremony.
There's no ceremony going on.
It's just the Pro Shop.
Well, let's not stand on ceremony.
Select some new spikes.
I'd like you to meet a very good friend of mine.
Look.
This here is, well, this is Governor Rocknard.
It is.
This is Dr. Philo Drummond.
The guy I was telling you about.
Did you drive?
Yeah, I'm driving today.
Driving at the Pro Shop.
What are you using?
Are you using your driver?
Are you using like maybe a three wood or a five wood?
You're using a wood, right?
You can play through, gentlemen.
The masher.
You're using your masher to drive with?
Masher.
Call the police, someone.
That's excellent.
Why not?
It's high up, you know.
I think you should grill the Connor.
Oh, he's high up now.
And before you do that, wander off down the hill with your masher.
Use a niblet on the green.
Same as before, but I know that within the regular loft, as it were...
A birdie.
There's a continuous love picnic on the ninth hole.
On the love picnic.
What is it about par four?
Below par, I would say.
Below par.
Okay, well, I'm taking my stand.
That's right, take a stand.
Can you say, meh-meh?
It's been a while since I've driven.
You know, I've got to get out and play golf more often.
In San Antonio, he took a stand.
It was a taco stand.
He left a trail of taco chips all the way to the Rio Grande.
And four.
Wow.
That's a good one.
No stop signs.
Speed limit.
Nobody's gonna slow me down.
Like a wheel.
Gonna spin it.
Nobody's gonna mess me round.
Hey Satan.
Paying my dues.
Playing in a rocking band.
Hey Mama.
Look at me.
I'm on my way to the promised land.
I'm on the high way to hell.
High way to hell.
And it's swell.
I'm going down.
All the way.
All the way down.
Yeah.
I'm on the high way to hell.
High way to hell.
And it's swell.
Yeah.
I'm on the high way to hell.
High way to hell.
Don't stop me
I'm going down
All the way down
Yeah
I'm on the highway to hell
And back
Yeah
The Zoological Society
One minute's silence, please.
What for?
For all the dead books of World War I.
for Mr. Moto, the Cisco kid, and me.
Muffle the drums.
Silence.
Shh!