The western man is at once mournful and menacing.
Why? Why this terror of the man?
It is not his appearance that stops our heart.
The opposite.
His invisibility.
It is possible to live in the same habitat for years and never encounter him.
He is elusive.
We know he is near, for we see his tracks.
We know he kills, for we see the remains.
We know he lives because we hear the howl.
The last peel so frightfully piercing is to go through your heart.
About 20 yards to the right.
Ladies and gentlemen, due to circumstances beyond our control, we are unable to continue the broadcast.
This time we take you to Washington for a special broadcast on the national emergency.
My name is Ruler Bobby, and I'm about to fight some crime.
And what about Chuck and Bob?
Oh wait, they aren't on this show.
See, I told you we weren't on this show.
Oh, shut up, Bob.
Confused? You won't be after the next episode of...
The Self Genius Hour of...
Everything is under control.
Did so.
Moon say glamorous.
This is perfect.
This is perfect though.
You know I'm always thinking pink.
Not from now on anyway.
Surrender to the power of the pink?
Phew.
I ran into Bob out on the driveway and he told me you weren't at church.
God, I hate Bob.
They went to church, Richard. The Self Genius.
Here's the $120.
And they found us a place up front.
All right, that's it. I'm kicking Bob's ass.
So in the end you picked somebody else and that somebody else was Bobby?
Look, Bob's ass.
You think you're dealing with...
Wala.
Wow.
Whole new man.
Look at that.
There you go.
A sensible, graduated Bob.
Perfect answer.
Let's go.
Oh!
Why are you hitting me?
Because you don't listen to me.
I told you last night Bob was coming for dinner.
Oh, right.
Bob.
I don't have time for this.
Bob is going to be here any second.
Do I have to eat with you guys?
Bob and I have nothing in common.
You are having dinner with Bob and that is all there is to it.
Come on in, Dad.
I'm going to get you some food.
Bob.
Huh?
Uncle Bob.
Come on, come on, go to the bathroom.
No fight.
No drama.
No what about Bob moments.
You know we're going to hurt you.
Shh.
Listen.
That's very gentle.
It's a little harder in grade two, but not hard enough yet, for example for penetration.
And three, it is hard enough for penetration, but not really at all.
It's completely stiff as you think you want it to be.
And four, it's completely stiff, you can feel it.
Then the erection is gone.
This is supposed to be? This is normal.
This is not normal. Sorry, but...
Yes, yes, yes, my friends.
Thanks to the LARGE for that intro title collage
and Reverend Walter Kosmak for the Western Man National Emergency Business
and...
for PR and...
for this music in the background.
And with this show, we'll finish up the Starwood Devival recordings
and we have some other surprises.
But first, I should mention that this episode,
hour of slack number 1301,
is very close to our sacred number of 13013.
So, on the internet only,
next week,
there will be a special show,
number 1301.3,
.3 of an hour, or 18 minutes long.
That was Modemax's idea.
And we will explain, for those who still don't get it,
why 13013 is special.
It'll also be completely X-rated.
But first, the Evolution Control Committee,
who will, by the way, be performing at X-Day,
and all the new 14X-Day information is up at subgenius.com.
ECC did a mashup of a Jonathan Coulton song
that I played last week.
And I promised to play the mashup this week.
And so, Evolution Control Committee,
for the next three tracks.
Praise Bob.
. . .
. . . .
to make you fat. Anyway, you're busy with the telephone. No time for chat. Code Monkey,
have a long walk back to Cusico. You sit down, pretend to work. Code Monkey, not thinking.
So straight. Code Monkey, not feeling. So great. Code Monkey, like mosquitoes. Code
Monkey, like tab in Mountain Dew. Code Monkey, very simple man. Big, warm, fuzzy, secret
heart. Code Monkey, like you. Code Monkey, like you. A lot. Code Monkey, have every
reason to get out this place. Code Monkey, just keep on working. See your soft, pretty
face. But shroud away, get beat up, copy cake. Take bath, take nap. Code Monkey, like you.
Take a nap. This job fulfilling, you create a way for such a load of crap. Code Monkey,
think someday he'd have everything, even pretty girl like you. Code Monkey, just waiting
for now. Code Monkey, say someday, somehow. Code Monkey, like burritos. Code Monkey, like
tab in Mountain Dew. Code Monkey, very simple man. Big, warm, fuzzy, secret heart. Code
Monkey, like you.
Code Monkey, like you.
Warning. You're listening to the Evolution Control Committee's album, All Rights Reserved.
And that means you are in violation of our listener license agreement. We printed it
in the album liner notes and we stated it in the first track of the album. You are expressly
forbidden from listening to any part of this album.
Look, you may think that you're being cool, or maybe doing something radical by defying
the terms of our agreement. Don't be a fool. Legal agreements such as ours exist solely
to tilt the scales of justice wildly in favor of those who write them. By the time you're
faced with one, you've already lost. Our listener license agreement is a masterpiece of contractual
skill written by top shelf lawyers who insist that our album include it. Your petty show
of defiance is laughable and hopeless. A good legal agreement is like a virus. If you ignore
it, it just gets deadlier. Take my advice. Press stop now.
Well, All Rights Reserved will continue after this brief commercial announcement.
With me and my dad, it's like our relationship is a record album.
typical金ence
and and and an untha fu
de
re
you re
You know what I'm saying?
There are these...
skips.
Bad skips.
Painful gouges.
But in your head you compensate for it, you know.
You keep the beat because you keep the beat because you keep the beat because
you keep the beat because you keep the beat because you keep the beat because you know the song.
Most people buy laser discs now. You know, CDs. They don't wear out.
You can't damage the surface of CDs.
Digital, digital. Not analog.
Pon, pon, pon, pon, pon, pon, pon, pon.
Yes dear friends, thanks to Evolution Control Committee for that. They are at
evolution-control.com
and
I think that's about the only way you can get their material because as they said in their listener agreement, they're completely illegal.
Well, not really, but
you oughta check it out.
evolution.control.com
The large mixed up this stuff in the background, Oxygen Runner.
14x Day is coming up in July followed by Starwood. I mean
even if the world ends we'll have Starwood on my escape vessel.
And you can learn more of that soon, but we're about to play you
the last of the last
years Starwood. Thank you.
I guess we could do
questions, a question and answer
thing. I really do want to
get off the stage
so that I can get high.
Is Bob a monkey?
I sacrifice, friends. I sacrifice for you.
Is Bob what?
Is Bob a monkey?
No, he is technically
an ape.
A great ape.
Well, he is an ape.
Yes, a type
of chimpanzee.
We all are.
Some of us...
Now, I think what your question
really is, is Bob
a yeti?
And yes, Bob
is more of a full-blood...
Any subgenius, what makes you a
subgenius is you're tainted with
the blood of the yeti, the Sasquatch.
You know, our ancestors.
Our ancestors.
The ancestors of the humans,
yeah, those are monkeys.
That's a
creative design or something,
I guess.
Now, there may be a live mic
going around, but I can't see
anything.
Ivan, you were suggesting
that people should pee, but isn't it true that
people pee, they eventually,
after years of doing it, they die?
Yes, people...
Peeing does lead to death.
The little girl over there said,
you know, it's like, didn't eventually,
if you pee and pee and pee, eventually you die?
Well, yeah, that's true.
If you can find an alternative,
I sure want to hear about it.
And then,
is there life after death?
You know, that's the ultimate question
now, isn't it? If you really
believe for sure,
then,
as soon as the bill's piled up,
you jump off a bridge.
Listen, and let me ask you this,
though, doesn't it not, true that
not peeing leads to death even quicker?
I...
It feels like that.
That's all I can tell you.
I've never been dead,
and I've never heard from anyone who
has been dead. I've heard from lots of people who
say they've heard from people who've been dead.
Let me put it this way.
If, uh, if when I
die, I go
through a tunnel of light and
meet all my loved ones, or
even go through the alternative universe
of lost on the last season,
I won't
be surprised.
But if I don't
experience that, you likewise won't
hear me complaining either, now will you?
That's not something I'm
really all that worried about. People ask,
Reverend Stanton, now come on, you must believe in
something. What do you really believe
in? I'll tell you.
I'll be real straight with you.
I believe that I'd like to crawl
across an ocean of tithing.
I believe that I'd like to have
some pees on my belly.
I believe I would like that.
Just one way to look at it.
Uh, any other questions?
Is there peeing after death?
Why are you asking me all this stuff?
Go to some, uh, psychic
medium and ask them if there's peeing
after death. I'm sure there's an
ocean of, uh, etheric
pee. Maybe that's
what the, uh, the ether is.
You know, the
unknown.
The unmeasurable part of the,
of science.
When is the
landing?
When is the landing?
Ha ha ha ha.
It was, uh, you know,
Monday morning, this last
Monday, July 5th, just
like every July 5th
at 7 a.m. for
the last 15 years.
I was standing out there in the field
waiting for the saucers,
doing the countdown,
and of course, nothing happened.
But on the other hand, how do we know
we're not on the saucers?
It's just that we don't have enough imagination.
And we, the, the, the, the escape
vessel that we envisioned
just happens to, all we could
envision was our crappy apartment that we live in.
You know, so, so we're on our way to Planet X,
we just haven't believed it yet.
That's one theory.
The landing. There's not going to be a landing.
That it's not there.
The UFOs that Bob predicts are not these pussyfoot little greys
with, with saucers that crash in New Mexico.
My God.
I mean, by hell.
The, the types of, uh, aliens that Bob's talking about
are the things that have been mistaken for gods
or the god or goddess for centuries, thousands of years.
Where do you think all that stuff came from?
Jehovah One is an alien from a corporate sin galaxy.
It's in pamphlet number one.
Haven't you been reading your prescriptions?
You people!
My God.
My Bob.
Heh heh.
Any more questions?
Why doesn't Bob use his pipe to stop the oil spill?
Somebody's going to have to translate that one.
can God make a rock so big he can't lift it?
if Bob could in fact use that mighty pipe
it's got all kinds of powers
it's like James Bond's car
you know it's like a boomerang pipe
rocket pipe
oil
you can actually
I wonder if that's how that oil spill really got started
could Bob
obviously
Bob could stop the oil spill
he must not want to
I've read in the Yahoo comments
that our president
the Kenyan traitor
communist
Nazi socialist
Satanist
did I leave anything out?
that he ordered that thing to happen
so that
he could
offshore drilling would look bad
and the reason he wants that to look bad
is so the US will go broke
because he hates our freedoms
and also
I think some people are kind of sore
that a black guy is president
if you ask me
the guy's a little bit too conservative
what else?
anything?
because I'm not ready to go
does Obama smoke a pipe?
what?
you couldn't have asked what I thought you just asked
I think I did
what was that?
does Obama smoke a pipe?
would
be
Obama smoke a pipe?
would
Barry
be
I don't know
I'm not Dr. Howell
I can't answer every question
is that about it?
oh praise Bob
that's all we need to know
actually that's not a piece of knowledge
it's just something to shout
praise Bob
friends I'm going to get off of the
this stage so that I can get off
earth we must get off
and in closing
let me simply say
repent
quit your job
and slack off while you still know how
question authority
there's the subgenius out there
Bob friends here's the important thing
Bob praise Bob
is not the answer
and neither is anything else
fuck em if they can't take a joke
praise Bob
thank you very much and uh
let's go
partay
yeah yeah yeah
see you at the swag table
I hope
you can go now
stop looking at me please
oh by the way you're all married now
my friend uh Joe
Rosenthal
actually uh
I was married to him at this last winter star
in a subgenius uh
temporary marriage ceremony
my husband and I married Joe
he's never actually consummated
I was a little salty about that
but uh
he uh
his partner Walter probably is not so unhappy about that
um
but uh Walter liked my lips
he said they reminded him of uh
Dorothy's left slipper so
this one's for Walter and Joe
and that's Rothenberg by the way
oh yeah okay
I was all messed up
he had these light thingies in my eyes
I don't know dude
the light was in her eyes
music plays
musicungen
Somewhere over the rainbow
Way up high
There's a liar that I've heard said
Once in a lullaby
Somewhere over the rainbow
Skies are blue
And those dreams that you dare to dream
Really do come true
Someday I'll wish upon a star
And wake up where the clouds are far behind me
Where troubles melt like lemon drops
Away upon those chimney tops
That's where you'll find me
Somewhere over the rainbow
Bluebirds fly
Birds fly over the rainbow
Wild, wild
Tough of a time
So make it right
To your home
Up on those struggling skies
Flash by on a pink sky
One that I'm gonna live by and think I must実現
Someday I'll wish upon a star and wake up where the clouds are far behind me
Where troubles melt like lemon drops away upon those chimney tops
That's where you'll find me
Somewhere over the rainbow
Bluebirds fly
If birds fly over the rainbow
Why, oh no, why can't I?
If happy little bluebirds fly beyond the rainbow
Why, oh, why can't I?
Well, that was Miguel Sague on guitar and whistling.
And Fat Mandi singing with Princess Wee.
Into Venus conditions.
But I hit my head more when I walk up right now.
And the knowledge.
How to gulp oxygen.
directly from the air.
Pro tip, use lungs.
How to use your skin as an accessory breathing organ.
Oh, amphibians, is there anything you can't do?
How your size can make you thermally independent.
Reducing your side toes,
how much it will really add to your running speed.
You know, drag is important at 25 miles an hour.
Eliminate wasted appendages.
You don't need them.
This tonic can bring relief immediately.
Well, I hope it does.
What a relief.
I feel better already.
Now I've got 159,090 reasons left.
I'm not going to go through them all right now.
Oh, no.
What's your oxygen doing in the air?
What are you doing putting oxygen in the air?
The callers are going around the other side of the ether zone now.
Yeah, I guess so.
Around the dark side of the ether zone.
Inventorizing.
Oh, boy.
So what?
So, we didn't get very many callers tonight on the show.
So, buttons.
You're the one out there, like, struggling to find the microphone to his phone
or her phone or his phone.
What is it?
Nobody wants to talk to me.
I thought you were going to say,
I think I know what to do about that caller problem right now
if I just push these buttons.
Legend is?
I thought so.
Puzzling evidence.
Funny you should call just now, Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
You mean funny like a tortoise animal or a cyclical event?
Well, I had a puzzling evidence show clip playing in the background.
I think it was one the large sent me.
That means he must be being heard on it somewhere.
Now, don't bludgeon that button.
Just push the button.
Philo weeks ago was griping about, nobody's calling in.
And although I was going to let that segment play for another minute and a half,
I thought, nah, let's just pause that one.
We need our Dave.
Yeah, well, we'll...
Was I early on the button?
Because sometimes my button is a little shaky and fuzzy.
No, you're...
I know you like to play with your button, Dave.
All right.
I do a lot more than play with it.
Actually, your button action was perfection, Dave.
I saw you wearing a button that said, kiss my butt.
Yep.
That's what I offer to this world and this land, especially in the grave times we're in.
Oh, these are grave times.
You need a lot of graves for the folks these days.
Yep.
A lot of exhumations going on.
I'm sure I'll save that again.
You know, we...
We considered coming in and doing the live show last week, but the tsunami was going
on.
And on top of that, a couple of our friends died, and it just...
It seemed like too grave of a week to be doing a satirical show.
Although now, we've got a third war world going on, so I figure that's humorous material.
Yeah, I would prefer if we all had a third nostril, but no.
No, we're going to have a third war, so let's have one and see if we can mount those bodies
up a little higher.
I guess the count is not high enough.
Nope, got to pile them up.
Mm-hmm.
Like cordwood.
I've been ready for this particular war for...
Oh, I'm on to 30 years now, I'd say.
Here you have Dr. McCobber.
Well, back in the 1980s, I was getting...
I was getting a present by my old friend, Palmer Freedies.
He handed me a football made in the shape of the face of Muammar Gaddafi.
Thanks, Palmer.
And that's how long that guy's been infamous.
You mean he's infamous for having given you face for so long?
Well, you know, we just...
For a long time, we let that Gaddafi head football sit in the closet.
The closet next to the...
What other head footballs?
We had the golfer head golf ball, and we had the...
Dried brino foreskin.
Yeah, we had a basketball shaped like Kennedy, and we had a Lee Harvey Oswald foosball set
or something like that.
They were just mulchering away.
So we...
Anyway, last year...
Folks, those...
And one people who were lucky enough to attend what turned out to be the 13th...
Actually, it was the 15th X Day drill.
We call it 13 X Day.
The whole X Day, we had that Gaddafi head football sitting on top of our main pulpit.
Every now and then, it got launched, I believe.
Absolutely.
Oh, in fact, we had...
Somebody gave us an Arnold Palmer golf club that was made in such a way...
It looked like a golf club, but instead of like a nine iron head...
It had another little miniature model Arnold Palmer with a tiny golf club.
So, in other words, the head of the golf club was a Palmer head.
Yeah, it was an entire Palmer, and we could therefore...
This is kind of goes back to really old subgenius rituals that we had to stop doing in 1998.
The conspiracies, 1998.
What people thought of.
But we were actually able to...
By holding this special golf club and pulling the trigger,
you could make the tiny little Arnold Palmer figure at the end of your golf club
whack the Gaddafi head football.
Wow.
I remember every time you...
And yet, believe it or not, this is not on YouTube.
No.
No, we're on YouTube.
The weird thing was, every time the thing would strike Gaddafi's head,
he would spout some of the things from the...
The little green book, which we know is not really that little.
It's about the size of a football locker.
No, I have a copy right here in front of me, Dave.
I know you carry one around at all times right next to your...
You know, the stuff that Bob gave you, the cocktail napkins.
It's actually true that Moe and Mark Gaddafi's little green book has been in my bedroom,
right next to my bed, for a couple of years now.
Reverend Carter LeBlanc gave it to me.
Thanks, Carter.
He said...
He said, Stang, you really ought to have a copy of this.
You'll find that he's...
Gaddafi's really a rogue subgenius.
If you'll read this about half the time, it's like a subgenius book.
Half the time, you're going, you know, it sounds kind of crazy,
but by golly, this is the way things are.
He's right.
And then the other half of the time, it's stuff like this.
Okay?
I'm going to...
Here's some...
This was a random selection, page 70 from Gaddafi's green book.
Women are different from men in form because they are females.
Just as all females in the kingdoms of plants and animals differ from the males of their species.
This is an indisputable fact of nature.
The male in the plant and animal kingdoms is both naturally strong and striving,
while the female in both kingdoms is naturally born beautiful and gentle.
And you know, that right there tells me that this guy must never have gone outdoors,
or read an elementary school level book about animals.
Well, it sounds like Bob to me.
It sounds like one of the spoutings of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Well, but it's...
No, it's fact...
The female is different from the male,
and the connections between the extreme parts are shortened or lengthened
depending on the root of the atmosphere and the conditions...
The thing is, this is scientifically inaccurate.
It's laughable.
It's scientifically completely true.
In many species of animals,
the female is in fact the strong, striving one,
and the male is this gentle, weak thing...
And brightly colored and beautiful.
Oh, yeah.
Normally, it's the males that have the more plumage or whatnot...
That's a school.
...and spend all day showing off,
while the females are the ones that are hunting down the zebras.
But we see this in everyday life.
We see zebras wearing funny hats.
We see people with all kinds of different ornaments on their heads
and haircuts that are different.
And it still doesn't matter because the power struggle,
always rests in the middle of the diagram.
In the middle of the curve,
lies those beings who are neither male nor female,
nor hermaphroditic in any shape or form of the word,
but simply resemble some kind of aspect,
one individual aspect of the whole spectrum.
So therefore, I would say they should all...
All should be moved to another location.
Well, this Gaddafi book,
is full of things that I always thought kind of went without saying.
Oh, yeah?
When a creature is born to life,
it is a living being,
and shall inevitably be so until it dies.
Puff, thanks for filling us in on that, Mo Amar.
Once again, though, like Einstein was,
he was right, and he is right.
Once a being is born and is alive,
it remains at rest, or remains in...
Alive until it dies.
Until it dies.
Until it...
Damn it!
So insightful!
If I didn't have Gaddafi's little green book,
I'd just think everything lived forever,
or had never lived at all.
Call it Thermodynamics for the Third Grade Mind.
If you like.
But I prefer to call it
The Erudite Bangings of a Hursute Wisdom-Driven Man and Woman,
embodied in one fine, funny, um,
coffee or whatever, or kaboong or whatever.
Kamumu.
And that lovely kamumu,
and a fine, shining, feathered headdress
he sometimes wears when he's appearing
in North Dakota or South Dakota.
Sometimes, I guess, he wears a big old farmer's hat
when he's in Indiana.
But we just call him a friend to the...
I don't know.
You know what, Dave?
I know you don't know.
I know you know.
Isn't it hard to remember how your sentence started
by the time you start getting near the end?
My sentence started and ended,
and I'm out, I'm free,
and I go to the meetings,
and I do everything I'm supposed to do.
I think that's great.
I'm so glad.
So I wouldn't bring up any time spent.
I hope they don't put you back in there again.
Well, I hope so.
Now, um,
I looked at the very last page of Gaddafi's green book.
It's not called The Little Green Book.
It's called The Green Book.
And, um,
at the end, the very last thing he says
is that boxing and wrestling
should be purged from mankind
because there shall inevitably come to an end
when man progresses
and becomes more civilized.
Gun matches and before that,
human offerings were familiar practices.
But these cruel practices ended hundreds of years ago,
and later man came to look upon these with self-derision
because human beings like himself
had once been a human being.
And he indulged in such practices.
It will be the same with the various kinds of boxing and wrestling
as people become more civilized
and the progressive individuals
are the only ones able to avoid such cruel practices.
That's the end of the green book
written by a man who has just finished
having bombs dropped on
untold thousands of his own countrymen.
Well, I would like to make...
Because he didn't like it.
He didn't like the way they voted or something.
I would like to make one dirty comment
concerning the whole dirty innocence.
All we have to do is remember
probably a lot of them stingers he got from the U.S.
and now...
Well, duh.
That's where they all get it.
...like rainfires.
Uh-huh.
And them stingers all cost about a million bucks a piece
depending on who's firing them at who.
They're firing at each other
and all we're doing is
spending a lot more money
of my hard-earned...
I read that today,
now this is from the internet,
so it's probably not true,
but I read that each cruise missile
costs $600,000
and this morning
we sent 110 of those
raining down upon various parts
of Qaddafi's Air Force
and anti-aircraft setups.
Well...
And not just...
I mean, you know,
the French and the British
and everybody else is in on it
and even the other...
A bunch of the other Arab nations said,
yeah, go ahead.
And then they went,
how dare you?
But that's all expected.
I think it's horrible when they play copycat with...
It's just like in shoe choices.
You know, like some person will decide
that he wants like shoes
that come all the way out
where they have a real sharp pointed toe
in the end that kind of curl up
and they kind of reflect the interior atmosphere
of his foot itself within the sock
in that his one foot,
his one big toe
is really badly, badly deformed.
Now, you can take that as a metaphor
for Qaddafi's misarrangements
and his nucleus power plant,
which he never built,
but his waterworks,
which the water rights might go to,
prove perhaps.
We don't know how the global economy
is going right now,
but we know it's going
because we can smell it in the air.
The smell of cheese.
Burning electrical equipment.
Burning people's feet, screaming.
Darn that Qaddafi.
Darn that man.
I don't remember ever meeting him personally,
but I did have a strange dream.
He appeared at the foot of my bed
and he held his hands up
in the usual, you know,
bellicifant mannerisms
and he was wearing a headdress
and everything like that
and he said,
Dave, you will be a prophet
not only to the Mideast,
but to the Midwest.
Someday you will be as green as I am
and probably putrefacting purple,
but don't let that bother you.
Just keep on babbling out
the same old dumb stuff.
Well, when you make that profit
and rank,
well, you're already,
when you rank,
when you make the profit,
share some, would you?
With old Bob's preach,
Bob's old preach.
Well, you well know how much money
you could make in a single book signing,
perhaps millions and millions of dollars.
Thousands at least.
I'm a bad thing.
You make a couple hundred thousand dollars,
you go have a snack at Rubio's,
you know, you drink some $7 espresso
and have a bottle of,
oh, Glen, whatever it is,
that real expensive.
Glen Fittich.
Fittich.
Yes, I have, yeah, yes.
I was looking at a $145 bottle of that stuff
a couple of months ago
at a fancy store in Los Angeles
and I took a photograph of the price tag
and in fact, I think you can see
the price tag photograph on my YouTube channel.
If not tonight, then in a couple of nights.
I've been putting things on YouTube
of our,
our working vacation
and so that people can see
everything we did and why.
Including the weird sexual stunts.
Well, YouTube,
you have to be careful about that with YouTube.
We had to put those on Vimeo.
The, um...
But you got various complaints
from the Hopi elders saying,
you know, you and we were doing weird things
out in chickens were crowing
in the middle of the morning
and the old lady was out walking her,
huh?
You're thinking of the Navajo.
We were very polite in the Hopi.
Absolutely.
So you kind of went,
you went,
we gone mad
at the Navajo Four Corners Mall.
Shopping mall.
Casino, actually, is what it is.
But I don't,
I don't want to go there.
I want to go to X Day.
14 X Day.
That's coming up.
The reason I mention it
is because I spent the last three days
really working hard at my job for Bob.
Putting together a nice preview
and,
and I'm going to go to the announcement section.
I had to do it all fresh and new
because X Day's moved, you know.
We're no longer at that place.
We're at Wisteria in Southern Ohio.
Yes, X Day has returned to Ohio.
It's rather florid scent for a,
for the name of a manly place of X Day.
Well, not, I'm not saying...
Well, but, but here's the thing.
You can, people can now,
if they go to subgenius.com,
click on the events section,
it shouldn't be too difficult.
First thing up will be a big thing about X Day,
followed by a thing about Starwood.
Now, there are photographs.
The reason I bring all this up is,
is I, we're, people are going,
how can each place be as cool as the old place
we used to have it?
Well, you can look at our photographs
from Starwood last year now,
and you can see,
and you can also see,
there's a photograph of Keith
standing in the other room there.
Guy does the show right after Dr. Sinister.
He's also standing there.
There's a photograph of that very self-same Keith
on the subgenius website,
running the tech board at Starwood,
and the, the pic, the photo is labeled,
Tech God Keith.
So you see, we do appreciate
the hard work that people put into these festivals.
We will be having a costume ball at our own festival
called, the theme, there's always a theme,
and this theme,
this theme is an evening of anachronistic anomaly,
which in other words, come as you are.
I thought people were going to dress up
in mid-Victorian steampunk only with having like strange,
Like I said.
valves and things coming out of their baton.
Yeah, what I said.
Yeah.
Come as you are.
This is typical subgenius,
an evening of anachronistic anomaly.
So the girls are all talking about
what they're going to wear.
Oh, oh, oh, this reminds me,
I should give credit.
This music in the background is by a band
that will be, I don't know if beautiful is a word for it.
Well, I mean, it's very, it's very unsettling at times,
and very restorative at times,
makes you want to praise Jupiter
and dance around at the moon and so forth.
It does?
Well said, Dave.
Yes, it does to me.
That's just what it does to me.
Why don't you and Dave go out and dance around
and draw down the moon?
Hey, Dave, you want to go out and draw down the moon?
Sure, let's draw it down.
I'll show you.
I'll show you a little stick that I could point at it.
I'll show the both of you a moon.
How do you like this one?
Oh, man, if the audience could only see this.
Oh, God.
I'll show you a moon.
I'm going to be forbidden from looking further.
Yeah, oh, anyway, the band, the band.
The band, the band.
The music that's in the background is Boron Nuzzle.
I keep wanting to say nozzle,
and then I keep thinking that it is in fact nuzzle.
No, don't get it.
It is nozzle.
It's Boron Nuzzle.
Right.
There's a type of a machine.
Because you're thinking of the Boron nozzle that Dr. Michio Kaku says is used on Fukushima.
Is that what it is?
Well, yeah, they were going to try and squirt boron into it with a huge nozzle.
Well, you know Dave knows.
Now, come on.
Well, that was the funny thing.
I was going, which is it?
The guy gave me a box full of his works.
I'm just saying I can see your confusion.
I was on the intronets, and I looked up, because I was, well, is it Boron Nuzzle or Boron Nuzzle?
And it turns out there is a Boron nozzle, a commonly used equipment.
But Boron Nuzzle is the name of the music in the background, and they will be at X Day along with Monkey Hive,
Andrew the Impaled, Fat Man D, the Evolution Control Committee, the Amino Acids' very last performance,
DJ 2 Beans and other DJs, I think Pope Black.
Did I say Andrew the Impaled?
He sticks screwdrivers into his head.
And plays guitar.
At the same time sometimes.
He's a sideshow marvel.
Dr. Dark's drive-in will be there showing the incredible film Big Man Japan, which I would not recommend to anybody normal.
Well, your recommendation will then be followed by those who are not normal.
I've watched it three times since then.
I've seen it three times.
Viola gave me a copy, and I still haven't seen it translated into Japanese.
I have no idea what it's doing.
It's probably a lot funnier when you don't know what they're saying.
You're assuming that normal people could even be listening to this reference thing.
Yes, I certainly am.
I hope so.
I hope millions of normal people are listening.
And I hope they hate it.
They think of nausea.
They think of the nasal panic.
We're here for the weirdos, baby.
This is this whole club, this subgenius thing.
You ever wonder what this is about?
Here's what it's about.
It's about the weirdos.
And I don't care whether they're smart, cool weirdos or lame, embarrassing weirdos.
They are weirdos, and that's why Bob is their god.
There's a good reason that we call this the Church of the Subgenius.
Believe you me.
We've all known the guy or gal who was smart.
Too smart for their own good.
Oh yeah, they're savants.
That's why everything they do is an act of savantage.
No sir, no ma'am.
We instead do wander as media overlords in the blabberinth of media overload.
Resplendent in restententialism.
It's the uncannibals versus the pretty-ots.
The Church of the Subgenius.
Friends, renders the conspiracy bobsolete.
Subgenius puts the er in nerd.
We are the polutically correct.
Where the pinks would be but sated, we say hail Satan.
For our enemies, we have a bouquet of forgive-me-nots.
Their golden age that never was fills us only with nostalgia.
Worldly?
We'll give you world beat music.
Like an old limp show, it can't be beat.
And I just read that sermon from Onan Canobite.
What a brilliant piece of...
I did not bite all of that off by myself.
Aramphage, Aramphage, Aramphage.
He emailed me that in January and I've been...
Indeed.
It's been laying around in this stack of stuff all that time.
Waiting.
Mouldering, mouldering, I tell you, mouldering.
Till this moment.
I'm afraid we have run out of time.
We have run out of petrol.
It looks like the little red light is poignant to me.
And although that's always meant excellent in my book, I'm afraid I'm passing out.
Do you have any of those, what's the thing, those nozzles?
Yes, that's right.
The nozzle, boron nozzle will be there.
The Qaddafi head football will be here.
Friends, it's true.
A year ago, we were launching Qaddafi head footballs.
We were ahead.
Ahead of our time.
Which is another thing you could call our man, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Ahead of his time.
The head of his time.
Fill it up, Dave.
And I can mind radio screen the head, fertile, fertile, unfertile, fertile, further and further
from Earth.
And soon it passed Saturn.
And soon it passed Pluto.
The little tiny asteroid that proclaims itself as a planet.
And kept on, kept on, and kept on, and kept on.
And I'm afraid I'm going to die.
Oh, I forgot to mention.
Did I mention that we're having Dr. Dark's drive-in at this camp out?
It's a great thing to do when you're camping out with subgeniuses.
You only see once a year.
Sit in the dark and watch a movie.
Yeah.
Well, another Reverend Fight C. Taj is going to have, be playing 30 movies in six days.
Or basically movies all the time, 24-7 for six days in something called the Bad Film
Grindhouse.
And I've seen his list of movies, and it includes everything from A Boy and His Dog,
The Beast of Yucca Flats, The Bride of the Monster, Carnival of Souls, Eegah, Frankenstein
Meets the Space Monster, Manos, Hand of Fire, without the Mystery Science Theater treatment.
Yeah.
And so forth.
All the great, famous, bad films, plus many you've never heard of, and some 12-part serials
with special effects and a little bit of a twist.
By the Lidecker brothers.
I'm actually looking forward to seeing these bad films because I just finished reading
a book-length article about the Lidecker brothers who did the special effects in the
old Republic serials, and serials like Radar Men from the Moon.
The guys who flew the spaceship, so to speak, for Flash Gordon.
And that you could actually not see the little wires.
Under preachers, I've been advertising that, uh, Donald Trump is a bad guy.
And they're not.
So, um, I'm hoping that, uh, Dr. Legume will be there, Susie the Flusie, uh, Reverend Ivan
Stang, Dr. Howell, although we're going to need help with that.
Um, Lonesome Cowboy Dave, is he going to be there?
I will try.
I hope so.
My very, um, my very adenoid relationship.
We'll send someone after you if you don't show up.
Oh, there's no one after me.
Oh, and, uh, Finney, Reverend Phineas Narco of National Cynical Radio may be there.
That's my favorite.
And, of course, all the new ones, all those new preachers that everybody else knows, and
I don't, because I'm not on Facebook, and I'm not young, and I hate parties, and I don't
remember anybody until I've met them five times, and, uh.
And he's used your name 16 times.
You get, there's a whole portrait gallery of what's considered now to be famous ex-day
subgeniuses, all these caricatures.
And I, I, most of them are people I don't, I don't, I don't even know.
Oh, my God.
None of the old people, none of the old people that wrote them subgenius books or did any
of them shows is, but that's because we're invisible.
And old.
And somebody already, and we've already, I shouldn't complain.
There's two caricatures of me, two, two, there's new ones on, on, uh, sub site now.
I, they're old, but they're new to others.
Uh, friends, I see we're swiftly running out of time.
Have we covered everything?
But, but, but, but Dave.
But is it slowly running out of time or quickly running out of time?
Time is a thing of dragonflies and angels.
Not of substance, that's for sure.
Because if it were, we could grab hold of it.
Time is a thing of Dr. Howell quotes and poetry.
Time is a thing of, uh, of, uh, about three more minutes.
So, oh, oh, oh, I know what I was supposed to mention.
Yes.
I did mention that, right?
I could mention for the prisoners out there listening, especially ones in near Atlanta
that don't have internet.
You can write for free information from got that pencil ready?
Post office box.
1 8 1 4 1 7 Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
4 4 1 1 8.
And that's, that's quite a few numbers right there.
I'm not sure if you can remember, but all you have to do is just either listen to it
again or listen to it again.
And if they had that magic thing of pen and paper that Reverend Stang is always telling
me about, they'll have it forever.
If they can find that piece of paper.
Okay.
So we're going to go down, uh, Dave, I'm going to put puzzling evidence back on.
And after that, there might be a little bit of international espionage from the devotional,
but we'll see.
Nobody wants to talk to me.
Come on.
Snap out of it.
Wake up and smell the coffee.
Collar just fell asleep.
At the side of the freeway.
Yes, I know.
With the engine idling, flashers flashing.
And those are the guys standing outside the car.
No, but seriously, they're over there on the side of the road on the soft shoulder.
And pretty soon the highway patrol will be long to mop up.
Between the highway.
There's a ship over there sleeping.
Somebody that's a renegade.
Shemp in his own sleeping bag.
Yeah.
Sham.
I always tell shit by the way.
He's.
What?
Hey, you found the phone.
Chocolate.
What kind of chocolate are you going to get me?
Collar's a retail clerk and they're trying to wait on customers.
What kind of chocolate?
I don't want to talk to a lot of talking to us.
Where are they retailing?
And I solid block of Chuggs.
Up and down the block.
The pack and sack.
Only we had three stomachs like our friends.
Then we could eat three times as much and then regurgitate it.
Me.
You didn't eat it again.
Really?
Yeah.
We'll be right back.