The Subgenius Power of Slack!
Slack!
The program you are about to hear, Bob's Slack Time Funhouse, is parody, satire, and comedy.
Any reference to Bob, the Church of the Subgenius, religion, politics, or any other touchy subjects is intended only as humor,
and should cast no reflection on the high standards of the staff or that of Georgia Tech.
The Subgenius Power of Slack!
Reverend Susan the Flusen.
Yeah.
Princess We Are Doe.
Oh, yeah.
Nate, the selfless engineer.
The head of J.R. Bob Dobbs is here with us.
I don't expect listeners to believe that, but we'll post the pictures later.
And rarity of rarities, we are live here in the studios of WREK Atlanta.
It's so exciting.
For this special edition of The Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour!
The Hour of Slack!
With special guest star, Bob's Slack Time Funhouse.
And Bob's Discord.
Plus, Bob's Slack Time Funhouse with special guest star, The Hour of Slack.
Now, if only we had Lonesome Cowboy Dave's head here instead of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Yeah.
It would be chattering away nonsensically.
Or what would appear to be nonsense.
Don't you have any canned Dave you can just spill out?
We ate all the canned Dave, huh?
Oh, man.
You know how Popeye always has that can of spinach that he pries open with his pipe?
Yeah.
We have a can of Dave.
That's why we bring the Dobbs head, the head of J.R. Bob Dobbs along.
We use his pipe as a kind of a canned Dave can opener.
Is that why you were slurping up there in the backseat of the car?
It used to be you could just give him cheap hemp and that would open him up.
But that doesn't work anymore.
And they get after you for that.
Oh.
So.
Yes.
We have to remember that we're on the air.
That's sometimes difficult for people of our years.
Air?
Yeah.
That means don't use your usual language.
Don't talk like that.
I could use some air right now.
I'm surprised I'm not on oxygen.
I'm so damned old.
Must reach oxygen.
Take.
This is the arthritis hotline.
Must reach oxygen.
Switch.
The terrible rotten smell of burning flesh.
No, that's just.
Recording everything going fine.
No problem.
Okay.
We got all the old stuff out of the way.
Those are the old stuff.
Oh, wait.
Repent.
Quit your job.
Slack off.
Okay.
Oh, whoa.
Are we still?
Oh, these shows get longer each time.
Yeah.
Or my attention span is changing or something.
In fact, that's not the only thing that needs changing.
I forgot my deep pens.
Tell us, Reverend Stang, about your unique mission.
Or is it an emission?
Yeah, that's an old one.
That was Brother Cleve Duncan.
He was Bob's chosen emissionary.
Well, you're certainly emissionating through the southeast right now.
Yeah, we're not in any position to criticize that.
No.
Not missionary.
But Princess, we are indeed on a soul-saving tour.
We're saving our own souls from having to shovel snow in the driveway in Cleveland,
Ohio for the rest of the winter.
So we've flown south.
South.
We have no winter here.
To South Hell.
We have abolished it.
That's where we're going ultimately.
Stang Ranch in Texas.
South Hell.
Where all the Stangs get together to excesslessness-mas.
And don't give each other presents.
We have this new tradition.
And you still go?
Yeah, we don't give each other presents.
We just sit around and stare at each other.
And take care of the infants, you know.
There's all these little...
There are many litters of little Stangs out in the goat pen.
Well, all the trees are festooned with natural mistletoe.
So what do you expect?
What, a Stang Ranch?
Yes.
They're festooned with rattlesnakes, thorns.
I mean, it's all prickly pears.
It's true.
It's an obstacle course.
And someday we'll move this subgenius.
And there's X-Day celebrations there.
When we've toughened them up in southern Ohio.
We'll take them to where there's real hurricanes.
You thought we...
I mean, tornadoes.
You think those tornadoes we had the last X-Day were fun.
I liked it.
Well, yeah, we had...
I had fun fighting the elements.
Yes.
We'll meet you.
We set up Tarzan's radio station on picnic tables at this campground.
Really?
Yes.
It's...
They have...
It's sort of indoors.
It's in kind of a cafe.
Sort of indoors.
Yeah.
And...
It's open air on one side.
It's a form of indoors.
Yes.
And we have many fans.
And we need those fans because it's so hot.
And there's also people there, but they're kind of torpid and half asleep.
Well, we happened to be camping in a federal disaster area during a heat wave.
And it was just sort of situationally challenging.
Well, I'm...
Challenging.
Strangely enough...
Brutal.
Yes.
The subgeniuses were the only people for about 200 miles around who had electricity.
We really had it made.
Yeah.
It was like a real X-Day.
The people who didn't buy subgenius memberships...
That's not a call to action, by the way.
It's just a what if.
They were doomed to sit around in Columbus and Cincinnati sweltering with no internet.
We had ice and electricity and we had...
Well...
Hell, we had...
We had so much electricity, lightning struck the place.
Holy...
It still didn't shut down.
It really did.
We got a nice recording of a bolt of lightning hitting about 100 feet away from all the mics and everything.
And it didn't destroy anyone.
Anybody important.
Sure.
A few camp employees that had never really gotten fully ordained.
But...
But I don't want to talk about the old glories and miseries.
I want to talk about something that blesses my heart.
And that's the love of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
He has none for you, my friend.
You don't have to worry about old Bob worrying about you.
You don't...
You know, with some of these other gods and personal saviors, you know, you have to feel guilty when you lean on them.
You pray to them and everything.
And then later go, why?
Why am I pestering?
Didn't Jesus have it hard enough?
Didn't poor Muhammad have it hard enough?
Why am I leaning on him?
Well, you don't have to worry about that with Bob because he's not going to listen to your prayers.
And you really don't want him to.
You don't want...
Because you don't know who else might overhear your prayers and know what your deepest fears are.
Especially you don't want Bob to know that because he'll exploit them.
He'll put a unique interpretation.
Yeah.
It'll be for...
It'll be all for the best.
It'll be all for the best for Bob.
The Dob Spin.
Yeah.
But most of us have given up on ourselves.
We're just entirely devoted to his pleasure and happiness.
It's not that he needs our help.
It's kind of like one of those amusement park rides.
It's a whirling disc and you're on it in your butt and you just get tossed in any direction.
Yeah.
That's dope.
Yeah, but then you get right back in line and do it again.
Get into that pink smelling seat.
Because it feels so good when it stops.
That's right.
I can't do those anymore myself.
That background music is so Bernard Herrmann-like.
I think it's some guy named Herman Bernard.
He did the music for all my favorite movies when I was a kid.
We wanted to have that in the background.
It's religious music.
I didn't think Porn Loops had a soundtrack.
No, there's a monster movie.
That's better than porn.
That was my porn.
You know, I used to tell people, after going through many different beliefs and faiths,
I was searching for the truth for so long.
I finally returned to my childhood religion, which is monsters.
That's what it really boils down to.
I think that's what draws many subgeniuses to Bob.
Because even though he looks like a grinning, vapid, leading man,
we know that he's real.
He's really the monster in this movie.
But this time, it's a monster that's going to win.
It's one of those cool monster movies where just when you think the humans won,
the very last thing before the titles indicates,
oh no, that monster's not dead yet.
No, sir.
And there will be a sequel.
The monster always wins in my book.
I don't know, man.
On the way home from a bad movie,
I'll figure out how to bring the monster back.
Well, in a way, you're right.
Every one of those early Frankenstein movies,
Frankenstein's monster was killed dead.
The thing that could not die was killed dead at the end.
And yet, somehow, they'd always manage to scrape him back up.
Same with Godzilla.
Think how many times Godzilla...
I saw Godzilla lose every bit of flesh off his bones.
How many times did they pull the stake out of the dust and there's Dracula again?
Yeah.
Somebody drools or cuts themselves.
A little drop of blood falls in that dust and there's Dracula.
Well, same with Bob.
You know, just when you think the pipe's gone out...
Somebody's going to drop money.
Lightning strikes right in the center of that pipe and lights it up again.
I told you about how Bob was an abortion survivor
and it took a tornado to even abort him in the first place.
And then once Mrs. Dobbs, the sainted Jane Dobbs,
saw that six-week-old fetus...
That mewling chunk of protoplasm.
Yeah, she loved him.
Yeah.
All things, all beings that gaze upon Bob,
even when he's pretty gross-looking.
He was basically looking like a hawker.
Yeah, yeah.
Like a mewling lunger with little eyes that haven't quite opened.
But, you know...
Three of them.
Well, the third one never fully opened.
I guess that was the pipe.
Well, you know, that's the funny thing.
He had a little vestigial, like an umbilical cord pipe.
That was a twisted little thing.
And it survived, too.
Mm-hmm.
Gradually straightened out and lengthened.
Became what we know as the pipe now.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm sure all the listeners know all about what we're discussing
because they've been listening.
Like so many say,
Wow, our Slack?
Bob's Slack Time Funhouse?
I used to listen to that back in elementary school.
These are 40-year-olds saying that.
That's my cutest.
They say,
It's still on.
And you can always tell who doesn't really listen.
It's funny now.
You can tell which ones don't really listen when they say,
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, we changed.
Now it's funny.
Actually, it's just the opposite.
This show has dozens of listeners.
Right.
Oh, I know.
I've seen up to...
The low two dozens.
We can see at WCSB Cleveland.
Technically, that's plural.
We can see...
How many people are listening on the internet feed?
I've seen as many as 25.
Now, luckily, that's as many as it'll hold.
So there could be more people trying to listen.
And I like to think there's maybe a quarter of a million going,
Gee, the stream is blocked.
I can't hear it.
They try every week for years and years.
But you can download these things, of course, friends.
You go to Subgenius.
com.
You can find out where to download every single episode of Reverend Susie the Fleezy's show.
All her co-host shows.
Well, the good ones, anyway.
And the Limpnode Institute.
And all the...
Literally, hours of slack going back to about 1987.
That's fabulous.
No.
What a fabulous thing.
In 1989.
You can have those and listen to them anytime you want.
The real old ones...
Believe it or not, the old ones are pretty good.
Yeah.
Nothing like what you're listening to now.
Really lively.
You began radio, didn't you?
No, but I'll tell you what.
If you go to the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame,
which is not something I would recommend most subgeniuses do,
there is one interesting part.
And that's the Hall of Technology.
And it's not a very long hall.
It's about as long as this...
Wait, did I just say that?
It's a long hall to the short hall called the Hall of Technology.
And the sad thing is, it's about...
Say the hall is 30 feet long.
Within the first five feet, right after the Edison wire recorders,
you start seeing recording equipment that you and me owned as we were young.
You know, the little four-inch reel-to-reel things.
Yeah.
And it ends with the iPod.
Of course, it starts with these recording decks as big as a Volkswagen.
And it ends...
It ends with the little teeny iPod.
I take technology backwards wherever I can.
If I have something to record off of the Internet, I record it on tape.
And I take it into the studio.
And put it on another computer.
You're old.
You don't have any tattoos or piercings either.
You are old, man.
I don't have any identifying markings when we live in a police state.
Oh, how stupid of me.
You're not going to be able to Xerox my ass and send it around.
On the wire.
See, there's another old reference.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Yeah, that was a TV show or something, wasn't it?
The Wire.
Yeah.
I watched television.
That's all it means to most people.
Did you hear the paper recordings or cardboard before the wire recorder?
Before the soft wax recorder.
The candle recorder.
The cable recorder.
In 1860.
1860 or 1870 something.
Made a recording device that, I guess, put indentations in paper.
So it wasn't a very powerful recording device.
And no, the paper survived.
I think that was a doily.
It wasn't a record.
No playback machine.
No, this was for real.
It's a disposable doily.
It's ruined my needle.
Some smart computer people got the paper.
There was no real playback.
And they were able to scan the indentations on the paper and translate that into a sound signal.
And it was a crappy recording of somebody singing some piece of classical music.
Oh, and a recording of laughing.
Laughing was an early popular subject of recording.
Nate is nodding as if to give weight to your raving.
Did you hear any of this?
I haven't heard that story, but that's pretty interesting.
Yeah.
It was just a couple of months ago.
It was going around the web.
Oh, so it's true.
And it sounds so plausible.
Oh, yeah, it has to be true.
If it was on the internet, golly, they wouldn't put something.
They wouldn't put a misfactual thing on there.
They can't put it.
They've got laws.
That's right, yeah.
Just like newspapers.
Mm-hmm.
Uh-huh, yeah.
Seventh Voyage of Sinbad in the background there, isn't it?
Yeah.
Did you see the first six movies?
What?
Oh, no!
The first Voyage of Sinbad, where he only fights mice and a really bad dog.
The second Voyage of Sinbad, he fights a rabid wild boar.
I think Identity Theft is the third one.
By the fourth or fifth one, he's...
Yeah.
Fourth one is VD.
No, it's VD.
He's fighting venereal disease.
Oh, yeah.
And the fifth one, he fights...
He fights an elephant and a yeti.
And by the seventh Voyage of Sinbad, of course, it's cyclopses and dragons and tiny miniature princesses flying off of trapped birds.
And then the eighth Voyage is bill collectors.
Yeah, they censored...
The conspiracy censored the eighth because he fights the conspiracy and wins.
But in that one, Torrin Thatcher played Sinbad and Kerwin Matthews had moved on to...
Whoa.
...to Jack the Giant Killer.
And we all know about Voyage number nine.
Which they're remaking, by the way.
Number nine.
It was in the Crimson Pirate, which is one of my favorite Burt Lancaster movies.
Torrin Thatcher.
They're...
You know, they're doing a remake of Jack the Giant Killer.
Did you know that?
Blink.
Yeah, she blinked a bunch of times.
Most of you don't remember the Jack the Giant Killer movie from the 60s.
But it was...
It was okay until they decided to remake it into a musical.
And they redubbed the normally spoken dialogue to make it sound like everyone was singing the dialogue.
And they stored music...
I must have missed this.
I'm drawing a blank.
It's unbelievably clumsy.
I was probably smart as a little kid and managed to miss that crap.
You know, I mean, you take a movie that is just people talking and then overdubbing it with the same dialogue.
But there's...
They're singing that dialogue.
And there's music that's forced into it.
There's a song that goes with the climactic fight where Jack is on this dragon's back.
It's really the magician's turned into an evil dragon.
And he's plunging a sword into the monster's neck.
And there's this jolly, jolly, jolly fighting the monster music.
Oh, the leprechaun is singing.
You may...
How did we get on this?
Shouldn't we be playing something interesting?
Or worse?
I've got that horrible album.
Horrible?
That horrible album.
Which one?
The psychedelic youth album?
The Ken Nordean only not funny?
Captain Entropy?
Teaching kids the laws of thermodynamics through creative play?
Oh, that was the Timothy Sagan.
I was calling him Timothy Sagan because he's trying to be Carl Sagan for acid heads, obviously.
They call it a children's record.
But it sounds more like Tim Leary's horrible Tibetan Book of the Dead record.
Susie just ran off.
She does that.
It's a thing.
That was fast.
I think she was trying to do some assistance of record album sourcing.
I do believe she's on her cell phone.
Oh.
What's a cell phone?
Oh, that's those new things that the kids use.
Yeah.
Huh.
Here, let me go look at that stack of records real quick.
All right.
There's some really, really bizarre stuff.
Oh, yeah, here it is.
Worlds of Youth.
Worlds of Youth. That's the one.
This is what we're going to be...
Right. Yeah. The Captain Entropy.
The Captain Entropy was okay.
He has a great song.
Yeah.
No, that's not a song.
That's the trippy Timothy Sagan.
Worlds of Youth.
This recording recreates nine of the 25 word worlds presented in the book Worlds of Youth.
Perspective paper, rank number three.
With the added dimension of modern rhythm and dramatic dialogue, each of the nine speaks of vital Christian message.
To the new young generation that wants to be seen and heard.
On this record you'll hear new sounds.
Drums!
The rhythms of pop, rock, and jazz.
In crisp counterpoint, two voices engage in rapid fire dialogue around common everyday phrases like...
The kite and the news.
The boy looking natural.
The nasty picture.
Come to war and...
March on.
The martyrs.
Martyrs is one we probably ought to play.
Martyrs. He didn't even have time to scream.
This album is not entertainment.
And yet it is, friends.
You'll see.
It explodes nine worlds of young adults into sights and sounds of fact and faith.
It moves.
It fuses faith to the beat and the rhythm.
The issues and the drama of century 20...
And a half.
So this is after 1950.
It is more than high-fi wizardry.
It can be heard once or a hundred times.
It is hard to forget.
It reminds the hearer of where every man has been and will go.
Too bad about the women.
In each band you hear everything about life and new life.
So those are two different things.
Life and new life.
It makes man, man.
Past and future meet the present.
It has new sounds.
It opens doors.
It does not judge.
It's just like Bob.
It has new sounds and horrible smells that go with them.
It opens bathroom doors.
Dave.
It does not judge because it does not care.
It is sound that creates sight.
It's like that radio synesthesia.
New imaginations.
Each of these indirect conversations.
Is an individual contemporary parable.
They are happenings.
Designed to have God happen to you.
And you know what else happens, friends.
Besides God.
Today in your fears, your failures, your fun, your friends.
Those all go together.
Failures, fear, fun, friends.
Their telling is meant to produce a completely free unfettered response.
A fresh experience of what it means to be a free human being.
Who is free.
Who is more than the sum of his parts.
Now this is obviously.
Oh, why are there ravering trucks?
This is obviously written before women were allowed to read.
They call all of your life.
From reading the paper, going to school and driving your car.
To copping out on a friend.
Into brilliant perspective for self discovery.
We ought to play the martyrs.
Wouldn't that be the best one?
Yes.
That's the fourth cut on side two.
And this is made by Herbert Broeckring and John Rydgren.
The selection of this record must be played individually due to special locked groove construction between bands.
Final DRM?
Yeah, this is actually.
It's like Ken Nordean if he wasn't funny.
And there's like a little pause to the end.
And a tag where there was probably something where you would put in the church P.O. box say.
Okay, well we'll be ready for that.
And this album Worlds of Youth is available from.
Insert website URL here.
Subgenius.com
He wasn't perfect.
But he was a martyr.
An honest to goodness martyr.
At last we know it.
Now we're sure.
The mill sure got him quick.
The big wheels got him.
Not a minute's notice.
It sure can turn against a guy.
A guy who cared for every inch of it with his sweat.
And blood.
He greased it three times a day.
Checked every moving part.
He even built it.
Checked every moving part like a gone specialist.
A pediatrician.
A parent.
He treated it like a baby.
And when he wasn't looking for one second.
It clobbered him.
He didn't even have to.
It was time to scream or say ouch.
All the cogs and wheels he greased and fit.
They kept right on going.
It wouldn't stop.
Until he stopped them.
With his own body.
And then everything in the mill stopped.
And lots of things outside the mill stopped.
Like the bowling he was planning for.
And the trip next summer.
And the election next year.
He was good in politics.
He was good for people.
And the promotion.
It stopped.
And the meal tonight.
And the book tonight.
And the bed tonight.
Everything stopped.
Outside the mill.
Everything stopped inside the mill.
And they had to untangle it all.
And check over the mill.
And the wheels.
And every moving part.
And start the mill all over.
And start everything all over.
Inside the mill.
And outside the mill.
The mill wasn't damaged much.
I took his shoes home.
And all the other things.
His shoes weren't damaged at all.
The holes in the bottom.
He put those in himself.
Building.
And greasing the mill.
And getting it ready to run.
And running it to make paper.
Paper for envelopes.
And letterheads.
Paper for 73 letters to a girl.
And 319 more after the wedding.
To four children.
And 13 grandchildren.
He used plenty of barrels of grease.
In 32 years at the plant.
He made a lot of paper at the mill.
Expensive paper.
He made this paper.
It's expensive paper.
Martyr Paper.
Man can lay down his life for a brother.
Or a sister.
Anywhere.
Wherever there is absolute risk.
There is the call to be a martyr.
Not all martyrs stand in pulpits.
Or rest in mission fields.
Some lie under heavy machinery.
Some stand in paper mills.
And grease pits.
And behind counters.
History is not sure of the exact spot of the crucifixion.
Good.
For even the paper mill could be the place for a sacrifice.
Or the bowling alley.
Or the supper table.
Treat reverently and sincerely
all things and places.
Someone may have laid down his life for it.
You may be next.
Life is to be spent.
AHH.
Now this is where the magic happens again.
Ah, the magic.
Oh, Stange.
Huff, Stange has an unfortunate addiction problem going on.
Don't distract me.
I've almost got that small hermit or show.
I wouldn't call it sad.
I'd call it more like tragic.
Yeah.
Everybody plays video games.
Unless you're really old.
I'm the oldest video game player.
I just started, though.
I never did it before this year.
What Mike Nesmith says about video games.
Video games are this generation's rock and roll.
All the kids get it and all the adults don't.
That's right, man.
Yeah.
You're taking away my slack, man.
Let me do my thing.
Man.
Yeah.
I've busted ass on this video game.
I've worked like a dog.
I've logged like 76 hours just on this game since we started on our trip.
Prince is right.
On previous long cross-country trips, I made us talk.
I wouldn't let Princess We play her Jonathan Colton albums over and over and over and over and over again.
I would read to her from the AAA books about what towns we were.
It was trying to be, you know, have interaction.
But we've discovered a better new way.
Our environment.
Where for four hours as we drive, she'll listen.
We'll listen to the same Jonathan Colton album, singing along with it over and over again.
And I will slay the same monster in Monster Hunter Freedom 2.
Is it where tradition meets tomorrow?
That one?
Over and over again.
It was Artificial Heart.
Ah, the new one.
Yes.
Yeah.
We saw Jonathan Colton three nights ago in Charlotte, North Carolina.
He was here Wednesday.
Oh.
Yeah.
How many monsters did he kill?
Oh, he's a wuss.
He didn't know anything.
Actually, he did.
He did sing several, at least three songs about video games.
Yes.
He's got theme songs to video games.
Yeah, right.
He's also worked.
There's some games that open and close with his song.
Code Monkey is the most famous one.
It is.
And he was real friendly.
After the show, he came out and I dashed up before anybody else and handed him a subgenius membership pack and said,
that was a great show.
And here's a present from Church.
It's a subgenius to which he said, I'm I don't know what to say.
I'm speechless.
And I thought he probably says that to everybody hands in the present.
And it's a great response.
I thought he said, I don't know where to start.
Yeah, I don't know where to start.
And it was.
It's like he doesn't know what it is.
You know, so he's literally telling the truth.
And he's in it.
And it kind of butters up the idiotic fan and gets rid of him at the same time.
I'd later.
I'd later came up to him to make sure he didn't take it too lightly.
I said, sir, that little black folder there is worth almost thirty five dollars.
Yes.
So in the course of driving cross country, Princess, we you could probably win any argument about who's been doing the most driving by just looking at the logs on Stang's little PlayStation portable there.
I don't drive at all.
Oh, you don't.
Yeah.
The brains of the outfit drives well.
I can drive perfectly well.
It's just that I'm better at navigating and she's better at not hitting things with the car.
He nagivates.
Yeah.
That's exactly right.
I'm the backseat driver.
Said.
I very much am a backseat driver.
I know everything that she should do differently.
And I explain.
Well, thank goodness you're there.
Yeah.
Does he have a brake pedal on his side?
Yes.
Well, except that.
but I'm not really paying any attention now.
I'm in my own little world.
I'm in a better world where I'm rich,
where I'm a strong, tall, handsome...
Well, actually, Stangor, too, is rather scarred up.
Ceaselessly energetic.
Well, yeah.
This guy can run up mountainsides without...
Well, he has to stop and have...
He doesn't have paws?
He does eat,
but he doesn't have to go to the bathroom ever.
Ever.
I've been...
I've actually been playing Stang in a total of about 450 hours.
This is the reason why there's so much violence in video games.
That's why Stangor's so mean.
There is no extra meditation in them.
Right, they can't...
They're building up a bear pack in a mean load.
He's like a crock again.
My good heavens.
That's what makes him so ferocious.
Is that the two-headed tiger?
Yeah.
Schnappy.
So, right.
I have tried not to inflict my latest short-duration personal savior on the audience too much.
But I guess that has ended tonight.
Well, how will we know what to believe if you don't tell us?
That's what you're here for.
Tell us what to think, do, and say.
That's right.
No, no, that's the job of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
I'm just his clerk.
Well, you'll do.
I can tell you where to send...
I can send the money to know what to say, see, and do.
Speaking of Bob, what liquid is oozing from the corner of his severed head's mouth?
What sort of stain is going on?
That's ichor, right?
Foul ichor, I believe.
Yes.
Ichor is magical blood.
I see.
The blood of dragons and things like that.
I thought it was just like spuzz or something.
Yeah, I think he probably just...
He sneezed and didn't think about Kleenex.
I thought maybe it was like a black Dahlia scar or something.
Yeah.
Well, he needs...
He's missing his body.
Yes.
He kind of looks like the chopped off android head in the first Alien movie.
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
He's kind of got milky stuff leaking out and he's all twisted and lopsided.
It's situated properly to be a black Dahlia scar.
But he won't relinquish the pipe.
You can see the photographs of this on subgenius.com.
By the time everyone outside of it finds out, it's gone.
Atlanta hears this weeks from now.
So I'm going to have to chop this up and put it on CDs.
I'll do all that in the car.
In between bouts of fighting monsters in the game.
Do what you have to do, man.
Last year we did...
I tried to produce hours of slack in the car.
It doesn't really work.
The most you can do is chop up shows of Susan the Flusen or puzzling evidence shows and such.
And duplicate reruns.
Look at the leisurely life of a serial killer.
Yeah.
How do you know where to chop Susie's shows?
They're pretty dense.
So Susie.
At the hour.
But when they're after they've been on for an hour, then that's the end.
It doesn't matter.
About 59 minutes and 45 seconds.
I'd leave...
You notice I generously leave the stations 15 seconds for their PSAs and stuff.
That's real cursory.
That's so kind and thoughtful.
Oh, he's all kinds.
That's real sub of you.
That's what you were going to say, wasn't it?
That's real subgenius of you.
How are they going to develop the blipverts if we don't press them for time?
Right.
Yeah.
An hour is long.
I got a lot to pack into an hour.
It's not big enough.
I wind up jacking stuff up to where it's over before I know what went on.
I like it that way.
You know, it's all good.
Thank God it's over.
We've only got 20 more minutes for this section.
I can't wait for it all to be over.
Hey, look.
How many...
For me, this would be weekly show number 1,896.
800.
1,300.
That's right.
Did I say 800?
1,396.
That was an instant 500 shows.
Well, three is...
10 years?
He added another 10 years to it.
Padding.
What's 10 years at this point?
Well, actually, 10 years for me, big difference between 59 and 69.
I think the primary warehouse is around here somewhere.
Don't give me a line like that.
Yeah.
That is a kind of...
59, 69.
There's a joke in there somewhere.
A crude, juvenile, silly joke.
Involves beef and broccoli, I'm sure.
That's it.
That's the key.
Well, isn't there something we should be putting on that's professionally produced?
I have a penois.
Interesting.
A benois.
Can we all watch while you put it on?
Yeah, a penois with a benois by Renoir.
Wasn't penois the sidekick gerbil on Danger Mouse?
I'll put it on in the pieceois.
of what?
We could hear another chunk from us.
Oh, well.
Do you remember the cartoon Danger Mouse?
The British made cartoon called Danger Mouse.
No.
I remember references to it.
He had a sidekick named Penfold.
I was...
Yes.
He was a mole.
That was after my time.
Oh, well.
Did he get it?
It's all after my time now.
So old.
I think we should play
Captain Entropy.
Yeah, play Captain Entropy
and I'll pull the coffin lid
shut on myself.
Go ahead
and explode the tomb.
Spin the entropy.
Cave in the entrance to the tomb.
Keep the servants in here with me.
Sit here at my Frankenstein way piano.
Roll away the stone.
Yes.
As Dr. Paul Bearer used to say
as he said at his Frankenstein way piano.
Wow, you should be a horror host.
Well, he was a horror host from Tampa
and he used to close every creature feature
with Poisoning Pigeons in the Park by Tom Lehrer.
He would lip sync it as he was behind his Frankenstein way.
Yes.
Wow.
That sounds really lame.
It was.
Yeah.
Fort Worth, our horror host was,
he called himself Gorgon,
but you could kind of tell he was also Icky Twerp,
the children's show host.
He was featured in that horror show,
horror show host documentary, American Scary.
I remember seeing that.
I'm afraid to watch that.
Yeah.
There are many subgeniuses now,
still,
still being active horror,
TV horror hosts.
One of the few areas of gainful employment for us weirdos.
Yeah, that's about all there is left for us.
I've got my application in at the local Fox outlet.
Aging Goulardies.
Oh, God, man.
There's so many Goulardie ripoffs.
It's sickening.
I say, I'm not even a native Clevelander
and I'm disgusted of all the so-called sons of Goulardies.
I'm disgusted of all the Goulardios.
Oh, wait, Reverend Angry Larry is doing a direct Goulardie takeoff.
Is he really?
Is he?
Yeah.
I didn't know that.
The Dead Dave show is grounded
and he's switched to doing a horror host thing,
only he doesn't actually introduce any,
he never gets around to the movie.
It's just the horror host all the way through.
That's pretty.
Looks like you skipped the crappy movie.
Yeah.
Kind of a horror neighbor.
Okay, were we going to play Captain Entropy
since everything is so bad and falling apart?
The center does not hold.
Things fall apart.
So won't we listen to this?
Teaching kids thermodynamics through creative play.
All right.
I'm going to tell you some things about the spaceship you live on.
Call Earth.
And about some of its passengers.
First, I'd like you to meet the captain.
Gather round, sailors, and listen to me.
And I'll tell you about Captain Entropy.
Entropy.
Entropy is something that happens.
It's so important.
It functions something like a captain.
Captain Entropy commands the earth and sky and sea.
Moving, flowing, strong and free.
Partly you and I.
Partly me.
Children all know Entropy.
Because kids are full of energy.
They give their energy where there is little or none.
And work begins.
And work gets done.
But here's what I mean.
Do this right now.
Take any object from a table or a shelf
and slowly place it.
On to the floor.
Go ahead now.
Good.
Feel the pull of gravity on your body and on the object.
Pretend to fight gravity.
Pretend the object is very heavy.
But you are strong and you can handle it.
Now lie down on the floor beside the object.
And try to shape your body to resemble its contours
to released by the physical nature.
Can you do that again.
Don't move on to a consciousness cup.
I wanna have one.
All right.
What is that?
Time away.
Pick up the object and lift it slowly.
That's right.
Fight gravity with all your might.
And return the object to the exact place you took it from.
Like a movie running in reverse.
You have just flowed through your hands and you have caused an object to rise.
Even though gravity wanted it to return to the floor.
By now you can feel that entropy involves a flow of energy.
When entropy is around, energy flows from a point where it is more concentrated to a place where it is less concentrated.
People call it a flow of energy.
The existence of entropy.
The laws of thermodynamics.
Now I want you all to get up off the floor.
And half of you stand over here.
And I want the other half of you to stand over here.
Form two groups.
One in front of each speaker.
Now we're going to demonstrate.
What people mean.
By entropy.
Hey you over here.
You're a coffee pot.
You're a bubbling.
You're boiling hot.
Move your body as the coffee boils.
And twist and steam as it flies and coils.
Now you over here.
You're a lump of ice.
You're stiff and cold but kind of nice.
Move your body in a firm position because of the condition of your frozen condition.
That's right now ice lump.
You slide over to the coffee pot.
In coffee pot you boil your way over to the ice lump.
Nice and slow.
And both of you connect and do just what comes naturally.
The coffee in the pot stops boiling and stands in the ice.
And still.
And the ice lump changes shape and melts on the floor.
Cold energy flowed from the cold ice lump into the coffee pot.
Which could jump.
Energy flowed from the coffee pot and changed the ice to warm or hot.
This natural flow of energy.
Which balances things for you and me.
Commands the earth and sky and sea.
And it is led by Captain Entropy.
Yeah, yeah.
The path of entropy leads everywhere.
Because energy seems to keep on evening itself out.
You work or play all day.
And your energy runs down.
And you eat food.
And energy from that food flows into you.
Well, what if someday entropy's command becomes so great that everything stops?
What if energy distributes itself so well that everything is equal everywhere?
Would this mean that spaceship earth would stop?
Or maybe land somewhere?
Well, here's the answer.
If you love to love.
And if you love to move and be.
You may decide to go on to something else.
You might just rest your body and use the power of your mind to think and dream and imagine and fly.
Maybe if all physical things came to a standstill.
Maybe your thoughts and dreams would still go on forever.
To other ships and other universes.
Until the very entropy of your mind came home again.
And again.
Ginogar laughs as she takes a smell from you and me and gives it to a galaxy that waits for Captain Androgyne.
BF-WATCH TV 2021
BF-WATCH T Embry-Huston Beiss  team
BF-WATCH T Embry-Huston Beiss major
ti esi
They went
Honestly
This is a scam
That reminds me of that
Man bait and switch
Like Ian played us a recording
Of a woman calling a talk show
Complaining about the deer crossing
Signs that they shouldn't
Put them at busy intersections
Or busy highways
They should move them to school crossing
Because then the deer wouldn't be crossing
In such high traffic areas
Areas
It didn't sink in
Are you familiar with the comedian Greg Proops?
No
He tells the story of him and another
One of his co-workers on the show
Whose Line Is It Anyway
Doing a corporate gig in Hawaii
And he's
From his hotel room
They've had some sort of trendy chemical amusement aid
And they're looking outside at a nature preserve
And there's a sign that says
Don't molest the tortoises
It's like a turtle preserve
And sure enough there are turtles around the base of the sign
And Greg turns
To Colin and says
How do they know to stand under the sign?
Well they can see the pig
I think you know
Like with the deer
Of course they can't read
Only an ignorant person would think a deer or a turtle could read
But they can tell the picture
Sure there's a picture of the deer
Of course the animal
It's shorthand so you don't have to speak the deer language
Friends if you're interested
In more information about the church
Or the subgenius
Bob's Slack Time Funhouse
The Hour of Slack
The Susie the Fousey
Or even
For a good time call
Yeah
Subgenius.com
Subgenius doesn't have an O in it
But dot and com do
And okay that was that hour
You've been listening
To the subgenius
Radio ministry
Hour of Slack
For free information
Write to
P.O. Box
Cleveland Heights
Ohio
Or see
www.subgenius.com
Praise Bob
For a tire
There is no more money
We gotta get some money
That dirty purgish
Hark a backflag
We wantin'
Phillip Buckaburton
Perkaluma
Burton
Thurton
Bustin'
I don't know
Friends we're glad
You listened to this show
And we're even more glad
That some listeners
Have donated enough
To help us keep on going
For another couple of months
And not just this show
But subgenius.com
And all the other archive sites
Bob Bob Bob Bob
But if you truly love Bob
And want some of that money
That's slack back
To rebound to you
You should go to
Subgenius.com
Front page
Or especially the radio page
Or the catalog store pages
And help out financially
As best you can
Now we know what it's like
To be on the brink
Of total poverty
And we don't want any subgeniuses
To make their own situations worse
But some of you
Still have jobs
Even five bucks
Makes a big difference
Even if it's only once a month
From enough of you
Fifty bucks makes
An even bigger difference
All we're saying is that
Blow jobs could go the way
Of Steve jobs
If you don't pay Dobbs
We also take checks
And money orders
To subgenius foundation
P.O. Box 181417
Cleveland Heights Ohio 44117
Thanks for anything you can do
To help let there be slack
SLACK.
Sl Astro.
eli
Liminal Hypno Corporation.
Need free contact.
Sex.
Money.
Bob.
Free pills.
Sex.
Money.
Bob.
Free pills.
Sex.
Money.
Bob.
Free pills.
Sex.
Money.
Bob.
Kill me.
Sex.
Money.
Bob.