Um...
It's time for, uh...
Ehh...
It's time for some...
Uh, come on, you know what time it is.
Whoa...
Huh?
Light drop, eyes up, test it back
Well, welcome to the hour of slack
Raise up golden honey drag
Yes, welcome to the hour of slack
Somewhere over the dobs and leo
Get high
Welcome to the hour of slack
Ha ha!
And the Dave has...
The Dave man has...
Uh, arrived...
On his flying airplane
Under carpet
Oh!
With his air...
Head
His one single brain cell
Yes
Oh my god
This man
Look at his face
If we may call this a man
It is glowing
Yes, but the one evil brain cell
Gaze upon it as it swells and grows
Look, it's glowing
It's rising
It's pulsating as if...
It will infuse with some form of life of its own
As if it had sprang perhaps into existence on its own
There's a way to find it
No!
The Dave's old egg couldn't die
Friends, we don't want the Dave brain cell to die, do we?
Well, that's a leading question
I probably shouldn't put it quite that way
Flip and flap and drizzle
Just a...
We don't want to see it flap around in its cage
Or bother the other prisoners
Ah, there you go
Thanks, Nurse Mary
Oh, you're welcome
It's gonna be a long time before we can stuff the rest of the detritus back in that monster's skull
Yes, I know
But it looks really good from here, doesn't it?
Of course it looks good
But you can't eat it every day or you're gonna have the problem all over again
I know, I know, I know, I know
Jesus Christ, we gotta get this cleaned up
Look at that
Rumbod, hit it!
The brain is between your ears, finally here
Cool effect with your circle sphere
It's in your head, born and bred
If you didn't have a brain, you'd probably be brain
Situated below the cerebral cortex
Into the cerebellum, cold in effect
It's the medulla and I'm not foolin'
Frontin' and grillin', come on, chillin' and coolin' in Brooklyn
Hangin' in the whole hood
You need a brain if you're gonna make good
Chris McGriff, staging the drive-by
Homies on the corner, I'm crack, you know it, brain frat
I pull a nine millimeter, I told him to stop
Shots ring, I'm in one of the pewter cops
I'll pursue to aim and shoot your boy in the face
See your brain as entire, I think, is your brain
Your brain, your brain, your brain
Come on, get it up, get it up
Brain, your brain, your brain
Brain, your brain
Yo, yo, yo, brain
Now then, my home boys
That wasn't at all bad
In fact, it was rather funky fresh.
But Philbert, what are you doing now?
I'm keeping it real, you know what I'm saying?
I'm keeping it fly, you know what I'm saying?
I'm fuxing up the funky mix down, you know what I'm saying?
I'm keeping it real and fly with the hip, with the rifle,
and the, yeah.
So throw your arms in the air and wave.
There's a very no consequence.
Yo!
I'm a lyrical poet, the riser in my brain,
just in case you didn't notice.
I'm on a mic, brewing, I don't rhyme.
Dipping up to make you all go blind.
Mastering the beat with my cold crush posse.
I make a rhyme here, but not the rise of posse.
That's because my brain was trained by the maestro,
James Brown.
With the girlies sitting in the front row,
I'm getting busy after the show.
Kissing and touching and stroking her gently.
In my Mercedes, Lexus, and Bentley,
or any of the other cars that I own.
Except for my bodyguard, we'll be alone.
He won't hear us, because he's so deaf.
He'll protect you, his niggas.
Black Knight.
We go to a party, and everybody's there.
Busta Rhymes, Eminem, and my homie Master B.
Drew an outfit, Durst, and ODB.
I hypnotize him with my brain power.
Bustin' a rhyme, getting richer by the hour.
And why not?
Because they pay me to come here.
The rhymes go from my mouth to your ear,
the head of your brain, and they cause a reaction.
Go beat, call a brain contraction.
I make you dance till your suckers get soft feet.
You break your head, little stupid face, face me.
I'm the puff that it tough for the kid rock.
And all the rest of you busters can lick my ass.
Don't playYaBeLeF선neCyons,
Mestezaンタ nada mais.
Wail.
Magsaryy This is how the boss hen is,
manisés breadam em sua cozinha,
Come on, cophrate your bad.
Han cato caro a Dok mister braid.
Face thisachum,
MES MARY SORRIENDO.
Jô gustou a P Foldeta,
eu era tarendo tenha magi,
tufocusedite lambusei.
Come on, get it up, get it up,
Step the fucking button?
Coz so my ops going crazy.
Oh, cut it up, cut it up!
Brain! Your brain! Your motherfucking brain!
Now then, mm-hmm.
Well, this repetitive rhapsodic rhythm has totally wrecked my concentration.
Talk to the appendage, because the cranium doesn't want to hear it.
Ha! I shall remedy this situation with one swift stout!
Pentatonic!
Hey!
Ready?
Pull!
AAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!
SHUT UP!
This is art.
Art. Art. Art.
A little after-dinner music.
Now will you dance for me?
Dance for me. Dance for me.
Dance for me.
Now will you dance for me?
Dance for me now!
Now!
lifting Afterkkei
Down!
When did it get up here?
You, nobody,frist o Café Craig'saat!
Now, now, now, now you're done for me.
Done, done, done for me.
Done for me.
Kill me, kill me.
I'm not gonna hurt you, hurt you, hurt you.
Down for me.
Down, down, down for me.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
That was Kill Me.
By Dr. Onan's Wotan Band.
And you can reach Onan at dobs.town.
And that's how you get into dobs.town.
The latest and possibly coolest of the new non-Facebook subgenius forums.
Although there are many others.
See subgenius.com.
Before that, Brain Rap was that rap brain song by Consortium of Genius in New Orleans.
Who just had their 25th anniversary.
They've cranked out a lot of albums and rock operas.
And they do stage shows.
Consortium of Genius.
Look it up.
Over the Dob's Head and other collages were by Lee Murr.
As in?
As usual.
But so unusual.
And the radio stuff was, of course, ESO Swamp Radio with Chaz Smith.
The late Chaz Smith.
And Lonesome Cowboy Dave on WCSB in Cleveland.
By the way, I noticed that Chaz Smith played a theremin on that recent movie, Dune.
Maybe it was a ghost theremin.
Anyway.
Although I'm saying this in 2021, everything before and after it is from Hour of Slack number 854.
Exactly 1,000 shows or about 20 years ago.
Including what I'm about to say now.
Friends, you know the aspects of this show tonight, number 854, will be a drag.
Why?
Because the sad theme of this...
The sad show is drunks.
And it was inspired by Philo, Dr. Philo Drummond, unearthing some tapes of our friend that died of drugs.
Like whiskey.
Dr. X was his name.
Heard in the background jamming with me 1,000 years ago.
His name is in Book of the Subgenius right under Bob's next to mine and Philo's.
Yes.
In the early 80s, he had a band called The Pink Boys.
Recognize that term?
And we will be playing his song called Pink Boy later.
The significance of this is simply that to me, is mine.
He was my best friend in high school and was there when we first heard the word subgenius.
He was part of the boot force.
They moved a whole bunch of them into the cameras.
Do you know how slow and crazy that was?
I don't know what the clumsy drunks are to a fropper like me of coffee drinking.
Oh, sure.
Frop maniac.
And you know how little those stories that they tell you, those things say mean?
Like Spider-Man compared to these yo-yos.
Yeah, they're like...
Oh, thanks, man.
We were waiting for that for...
I'm sorry, man.
Your show is pretty lame.
Okay, well, we already said...
Okay, well...
Yeah?
Is there some way we can maybe...
Why aren't you turning the radio off or turning it on?
Turn it to another channel.
He said it was like...
Are you that much of a loser?
Is there something we can do for him, maybe?
Are you that much of a pathetic little dweeb that you can't figure out that you can turn your radio to another station?
Well, if he didn't like what we were saying, we could have helped him another way.
Is somebody sitting there with a gun to your head forcing you to listen to this station?
He thought he was going to hear some music from the Blowfish Man and you blew his mind.
I can feel it now.
We're not playing Green Wave tonight, kid.
You're vacillating sexuality.
You're interpreting my mind.
Or, you know, they're fornicating or something.
I could tell that kid needed our spiritual help.
You can't expect responsible behavior when alcohol is served.
What the hell?
There you go.
You can't expect responsible...
As a matter of fact...
People, when they crucified Christ, they were all rip, roaring drunk.
You can't expect responsible behavior from drunks.
Right, right.
There are people who can drink and then there's drunks.
I was having responsible behavior all night.
That's why I don't drink!
Think of the beer hall push.
Hitler knew what he was doing.
What Hitler's doing.
My God.
You can manipulate drunks quite easily.
You can't expect responsible behavior from people who have any alcohol or any other mind-altering substance in their body.
That's funny.
You know, because I've known quite a few alcoholics who are not...
You can't really expect people with a functioning endocrine system to behave normal.
You can be a drunk and not be a jerk.
You can be an alcoholic and not be a jerk.
Then there's the drunken jerks.
And if you're that kind of a drunk, don't drink!
And then they mix swingerism with...
Once again, who is putting a gun to the heads of these people and marching them into my campsite?
Or a pork chop, you know?
You know, I don't get it.
Who was out there?
Who did they hire?
Who did Ace hire to go out there with handguns and force people to come into this thing?
And drink those Mai Tais and mudslides that Lagoon was making?
Yeah.
Take responsibility for your own.
Sweaty little shops, that is.
If you don't like our actions, then don't patronize us.
If you don't keep up with my accents, you don't have to.
Are you that stupid out there?
Stop throwing money at us, man.
Shut the hell up.
Oh, that was a really good one there.
Stop interpreting my endocrine system.
Totally.
Forget it.
Drop the alcohol.
Go straight for peroxide.
Really?
Now this guy's talking trash.
Yeah, everybody with white hair.
I think it'd be a beautiful world that way.
We're talking about squirting things out of your navel.
No, no, he's talking about drinking it straight, man.
Peroxide?
Yeah, hydrogen peroxide.
Try it.
Oh, man.
Talk about the blowhole of death, man.
That's going to remove a lot of your insides in one...
Run up some peroxide, man.
Hello?
Man, drop the peroxide, man.
Drink gasoline.
That's not good.
No, you know what?
That's not a good buzz.
Not with...
I've tried that.
Especially with the prices we've got.
The world petroleum problem.
That's not what your fire breathers use.
You know, I've had...
I've done that.
Who hasn't run out of gas and siphoned some gas out of another car and swallowed down
a bunch of gas?
It's not fun.
I mean, who hasn't flipped their old frig frog out once in a while and put it in the
tank just for a clever joke with the Polaroid crowd?
You know, some of them anyway.
Like that.
It's, you know, American.
It's macho.
We're humping steel.
I love my car, and I mean I love my car.
I'm feeling her headlights now.
They're like two round, robust, round...
Oh, Christine.
And my thing is that...
Oh.
Ship stick.
Yeah, baby.
Four on the floor.
That's me.
Or maybe that's two underneath her.
Here it comes.
Yeah, we're spilling beers right and left.
We got trouble in River City.
That's the smell of tea, which rhymes with B, which stands for beer.
Shake the hand, shake the hand of an honest drunk
The farmer, he got plowed
The bricklayer got plastered
The mechanic, he got tagged
And the construction worker got blasted
And daddy beat up mommy
And broke her collarbone
Oh, good luck
And everybody's drunk
And everybody's wasted
And everybody's drinking on the job
The garbage man got trashed
The janitor got messy
The taxi driver got smashed
The janitor got smashed
And the waitress, yeah, she got tipsy
In Kansas City, New York City
Great big city, itty bitty city
Now everybody's drunk
And everybody's wasted
And everybody's drinking on the job
There's a whole lot of places
That I ain't been
A whole lot of things that I ain't seen
A whole lot of things I'll never be
The generation that will change the world
Is still looking for its car
Yeah
on's small but orada
This case has happened
And there's no real cure
and I'm bragging
And now I'm going home
To the great God
And I love your
But I still believe
I'm going home
in Oslo and now something Philo did to something I did to Bob.
Yes, I'm a jambalida humping junkie that jumped the men from Mars. I drank the devil under
seven tables, I am too intense to die, opiates are the mess of my religion, I take drugs.
Yes, I'm a rip snorter, I cram coca leaves right into my arm veins before they are picked
off the tree. Space monsters cringe at my tread. I wipe the pyramids off my shoes before
I enter my house. I'm fuel injected, I'll live forever and remember it afterwards. I'm
immune. I'm radioactive. Come on and give me cancer, I'll spit up the tumor and butter
my bread with the juice. I'm supernatural, I bend crowbars with my meat axe and a thought.
My droppings bore through the earth and erupt volcanoes in China. Yes, I can drink more
wine and stay soberer than all the heathen Hindus in Asia. Yee-haw. Gut blowout.
Realmwave immediately.
Medium. Necropetrovsk-Chaterin.
Wavy medium brown. Tashkentum's chalupin.
Medium wavy brown. A van of Ochernigavoser.
I like shaping.
Wavy brown medium. I like to go out and drink beer.
I like to drink wavy brown beer.
We haven't...
Well...
We haven't any chance.
Chance?
You, uh...
No chance?
Naturally things happen like, uh, at the, uh, Columbia University.
The other mother college is...
Yeah.
No, it really is, uh...
Really? Come on.
I went to school at the University of Southern California.
We didn't do this, guys.
Let me explain something to you.
Let me tell you something.
I was a...
You see me in the fightin' McBurnum and...
I can't believe Bob was like this in front of those rotary clubs.
Oh, look, his butt... His butt fell right out.
Right on the...
Dias, man.
Oh, my God.
Listen to him.
Anybody...
His butt fell off his mouth.
...that walked into his...
Office.
Oh, man, what you doin' with your hands down there?
...office.
Took a crap in your can.
...and tore down a picture...
Okay. Jesus.
...and...
...and did excrement in his, uh...
...excrement in his, uh...
Those Bobbies did in Dobbs Town.
...and did excrement in the Hot Tub.
Yeah, yeah, they, he was really, uh...
...very clink-boop-ashin' really.
But...
This is, this was Bob's reply after that year.
This was the last recording of Bob.
It was right after the year that they crapped in the Hot Tub.
...we, as members...
This is a very historical piece of memorabilia right here.
...would have picked the...
...mem...
See, that's when the pipe...
...he's tryin' to put the pipe back in its mouth.
...to keep fallin' out.
He doesn't like a curse.
...there were women there.
He won't say bad words in...
in the next company.
Not unless they're showing their labia to him.
Even when he's that drunk,
Bob has had manners.
Masek was an expert with the experts.
All serial murderers have this chair that I'm sitting on.
Morrison did something she had done before.
I looked under the bathroom,
and my telephone rang.
And it was this chair that I'm sitting on.
I opened the lighted phone, and it was empty.
So, um, I went back to the telephone,
and I said,
Richard, you're not in the telephone.
I am in that telephone.
I should have kept going right on down
Sweatshop and Kingston.
No, way down, like down in Bolivia or something.
They would have taken Jack Cassidy to,
and me, Neil, Jack Cassidy,
I mean, Neil Cassidy, to a gun court for sure.
Remember the gun courts they had
for most of the subgeniuses, for crying out loud?
Hey, first rule of gun club,
don't talk about gun club.
If it's all natural, put it in your body.
Organic.
Beat that stupid.
Jimson weed.
That's the...
Datura, Lexus.
You gotta legalize it.
Open, tatty, down.
Datura, man.
Make a fine tea out of local weed.
The devil's weed, man.
You don't want to smoke the devil's weed.
The devil's?
The devil's weed.
Devil's weed.
My bud smoked some Jimson weed,
and he ended up taking a dump on his living room floor
in front of his parents.
My bud took a dump on his parents.
He was a hedonist.
This guy was a Jimsonist.
George Bush is about to take a dump
on everybody.
Just like that hedonistic buddy of yours.
No, that's it.
Now, you guys aren't going to be putting George down
when the evil terrorist germ bomb goes off
in your backyard.
Then you're going to want George to save you.
They're going to trace you back to
Aaron Fleischer's post office box.
Why didn't you buy...
We're going to bomb the hell out of those people
before they set off that germ bomb in our backyard.
That's what you'll be saying.
Face it, Stang, if you want to fight something
for America, war is good.
You've got to fight war is good for industry,
for the oil industry, yes.
But did you know that Iraq is sitting
on one of the largest deposits there is to sit on?
Did you know that the slate underneath
Saddam Hussein's feet was worth
billions and billions of petroleum dollars?
Stang, you're confused about what's important
in this country.
Look at you.
You're hardly a man.
Oh.
Ah, for crying out loud.
Look at those biceps.
What are you good for?
Can you lift this gun?
The eternal wisdom of nature's laws,
which are completely opposite
to the suicidal teachings of normality.
Whereas normality says to love your enemies
and to hate your own kind,
we say just the opposite.
We say that in order to survive,
we must overcome it.
Destroy those who are a threat
to our existence,
namely our deadly enemies,
the normals.
At the same time,
we advocate love and protection
for those that are near and dear
to our family and our own race,
the subgenius race,
which is an extension of our family.
Nope, it's just about killing.
It's just about our God-given right to kill.
Ask Ted Nugent.
Take as many as you can.
I'll bet Ted'll go.
Let God sort them.
I wish Ted would go.
And then he'll give them to the homeless center.
So give his kills to the homeless center.
When Ted realizes that some of the squirrels shoot back,
he's going to be in a lot of doo-doo.
I think he should go.
No, I'll bet he's into it.
I'll bet Ted would be into it.
He's like one of those guys
that came back from a golf war.
That's a good debate.
Would Ted Wimbo?
Abortionists find out those fetus ghosts are coming for him.
God, have the f*** for Marie.
Hey, guys.
Because we kill everything we see.
He plays his games.
We play ours.
The Butcher of Zapier.
To show our appreciation for so much power,
we keep heaven packed with fresh soul.
The Butcher of Washington hides behind his berms.
The great yellow dog of the Potomac.
His formidable berms.
On the podcast.
The Potomac.
Grace, Marshall.
But he will not resist our special guided patriotic psychotic missiles,
which can go straight down the premier's wife's brassiere,
if that's where we want to target them.
It was July in Virginia.
Yes.
The men of the Dogwood and the Laurel lay heavy on the land.
While the Virgin and the Magnole was...
Doc Mojo was burying Sung Lee back on the back four.
The majority.
That's sick.
Cheese lovers know that cheese lovers choose friskies.
Despite his sunny exterior, little Caleb is dead.
He doesn't even have a name.
For that reason, today we are proposing to add minutes to the environment.
Once it's added, shipments and sales would be allowed...
To companies that create everything.
Yay!
All too many demonic Israelis.
That would be me.
And may I say...
From the banana.
Take out the pen.
I don't know anything.
Place the tip of the marker on the surface of his spirit.
And it's gotta be friskies.
You can come across the middle, and then you can come high.
The dots in...
So they said...
Die young.
Now experiencing hair.
Just snap.
And may I say, I am...
Perfectly grilled.
Televangela just sent in her bad dream of two hours ago.
And I'd like to read this to you.
It's short, Dave.
Televangela dreamed...
Some sort of subgenius gathering in my backyard and home.
The home where I grew up.
Parents not home.
Not informed they were coming.
Myself either.
The usual...
The usual group was there.
Plus some new faces with very unique outfits and problems.
A very loud woman in shiny spandex yelling that we should wrestle in food or something.
I recall vaguely thinking...
Oh, that was a bombastic party.
Is this Ziza?
Then people are pasting something on the wall.
Some sort of decoration.
Look, they're all pasty-faced.
Look more like clear peaches.
Then, the worst part of all.
My grandma shows up.
And is seated in a circle of subgenius.
And kisses on the lawn.
Without me being able to stop it.
Like Yume tells her about how we need more hate.
Jesus tells her he's Jesus.
Stang and we just agree and have those twinkling crazy eyes.
I show up, but it's too late.
She's pissed and confused and arguing.
I try to help grandma, but then...
I wake up.
Friend?
Are you even able to wake up?
You off from that dream you call life.
Can you open your eyes?
Can you awaken from that dream you call your job?
The sleep
Thank you.
지나 halfway through judge sono
Gratias.
E diablos
ha ha
chakallajajajajajajaja
乾杯
gasp
Karol 가
Mac- Mac-Mack-Eye.
Mac-Eye. Mac-Eye.
You know.
What do you got to do?
How'd you know?
I suppose you're going to tell us you don't know that Alexander Mac-Eye, vice-model Alexander Mac-Eye is for a tour of inspection.
Possible.
Decker?
Dead.
Which is cold, robot.
Talk to people.
Uh, I'm a potato.
You said it, bud.
Great.
No, no, no.
Miss.
No, no.
Time.
S-
Ah.
Pizza?
Um, it's herbal.
Call the man.
So money.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Yay!
So money.
Call the man.
Fernand and Andy Lemur did a collage and now from their new CD, Reagan's Polyp.
Hey, any- any Beatles fans in the audience tonight?
Uh, we got a song for you, it's called Daytripper now.
Oh, okay.
Bye!
Aw.
B- douchebag.
M- MVP!
Come-on, just take a 굿's for dados and tickets.
Well, if you don't take a lift, I'll usually be busier.
A- a- cut the music right here.
gasm. Thanks, Mom.
Thanks, Dad. It's gonna
rip your whole spine next time. Just
relax, little boy.
Yeah.
They're coming back.
Wait, you're gonna have to hide under the bed here, kid.
I'm afraid. Really afraid.
None of them pituitary gasms when they're coming by.
Don't make any noise.
Okay, okay, okay.
Hold onto this piece of wood.
Make him feel like you're doing something.
Okay, okay, okay. Be very quiet.
Bite onto the piece of wood if you want to make a sound.
If you start to...
You just don't...
Man, those people from Child Welfare Service is creepy.
They are creepy as hell, man.
That's not the half of it.
They've got some penises on them.
We're all in deep shit.
Shut up.
They've got the circumcision machines.
We're in even deeper.
We're a Bob without a Connie.
Oh, man. No anesthetic for these guys.
One of the first things
any of the forbidden children
must learn is how to keep
the pituitary gasm at a minimum.
The child service workers
are often vicious and barbaric
in their retribution
and have sometimes even
slothed the little little childs.
A pituitary gasm
in a pre-10-year-old
can be a violent, earth-shaking thing.
This is one of the
cause-lit causes for poltergeist.
That's not how you get into that.
you
the
violence
on their eyes most likely never come through.
They sniff the anguish.
They are fortunate
to him.
He says that the hardest part
child cars.
He sent out into the world his
nine-year-old Anguish and his eight-year-old
Peter. They were all
seven. I can see these
kids. What a
young age to live.
Some children,
some difference.
Truth.
Truth to children.
Am I still dancing? I can't remember.
It doesn't sound like much of a dance anymore.
I can't hear my ears clicking.
I'm dancing to the dark side
of the moon. Oh, Dave's playing that, I mean
Chance is playing that song about you, Dave.
Pink Floyd.
You know the Pink Boys?
The Pink Boys? Is that who this is?
Yeah, the Pink Boys. Man, that was
a great band before the
lead singer, O'Deid.
Pink Boys.
The food I left behind
a million last year.
Now we've got two, but only
got the two.
Fresh food.
You and me, we've been
living in a box, but it didn't
matter for you.
Pink Boys.
You know the Pink Boys.
The Pink Boys.
They got the
girls.
Pink Boys.
You can't forget this
passion. You can't
put a spin on this.
It's just a
passion.
Listen.
Pink Boys.
You need a degree.
How is that
the universe
to see?
Because it is
an hour
to an
exception.
I was at
the
back door
so I
had to
learn
how to
show
it.
Pink Boys.
They were
born
on a
gold mine.
The Pink Boys.
They got a
gold mine.
The Pink Boys.
They got the
satisfaction.
You can't
put a
sound on
the world.
You've got
to find
some
more
sun.
Crazy
little
Pink Boys
have
to go
fly.
Crazy
little
planet
with
a
planet
in
line.
Crazy
little
Pink Boys
have
to get
your
soul.
You
can't
go
to
Google.
Just
keep
flying.
I'm
going
to
fly.
The
back
door
said
I
wouldn't
leave
it.
Growing
up
crazy
and
singing
it.
I
can't
hold
the
reason
in
the
room.
It's
time to
make
a
decision
to
move.
Pink
Boys
are
going
to
go
out.
Pink
Boys
have
to go
to
school.
Pink
Boys
get
the
satisfaction.
Pink
Boys
have
to go
though.
Yeah!
Pink
I drink and kill the whiteness in my eyes
Don't wanna think about those lonely goodbyes
I can't forget the world pounding in my head
And waking up the creatures in my bed
And when did this all begin?
Tap on the shoulder, my friend
I, I, I, I, I drink enough
I, I drink enough
I drink and travel around the world
I drink and marry a liquor store girl
I drink and build myself a yacht
And smoke old drugs
I never get caught in the bars where I want to be
I take my ship and I tank across the sea
I, I, I, I, I drink enough
I, I, I, I drink enough
Living at home, it gets cold
And on my parents' house it's been so cold
In the pubs where I want to be
I take my boat and I go to the beach
And we can float across the sea
And if I run out of cash
And get my meals from the trash
I, I, I, I
I drink enough
I drink and kill
Whiteness in my eyes
Don't wanna think about those lonely goodbyes
And I can't forget
All the pounding in my head
And waking up
Creatures in my bed
And when I'm
Will this all end?
A little cirrhosis, my friend
I, I, I, I
I drink enough
It tastes good
Groß training
L ад질
Boolah
imi
Birr
The Line.
The Line, tweaked by Lemur.
Before that, that song, I Drink Enough, is by Rocco Schwab from his album The Barlight Beauty.
Information is at www.scaryrecords.com.
That's roccoshwab at hotmail.com.
And before that, friends, The Pink Boys, doing that song, the titular song, The Pink Boys.
That was the band of my friend Dr. X.
That was recorded live in some club in Dallas in 1980,
about the time.
The first subgenius pamphlet was printed.
Dr. X died of drink and bad habits.
It was a bummer, man, because he was my high school best pal.
And he died before he was even 40.
But now, Reagan's Pollock!
Any Led Zeppelin fans out here tonight?
The only one that's called The Immigrant Song.
It's him.
The Immigrant Song.
I am a guldarned visionary, I see the future and the past in comic books and wine bottles,
I eat black holes for breakfast, I bend my jeans and whittle my DNA with the sheer force
of my mighty will, I spear my own guldarned evolution, I ran M out of heaven and sold
it to hell for a profit, I'm enlightened, I achieved nirvana and took it home with me,
yip, yip, yee yee yee, I'm so ugly the speed of light can slow me down and gravity won't
tug at my cuffs, when the rapture comes, I'll make M wait, they'll never clean my cage,
now give me some more of, take runs out.
Summertime's here kiddies, and it's time to get to work,
and it's time to take a trip, to take a trip, to this world so bad,
you feel so sad, you gotta take a trip, into a world so glad,
a world of frogs, and green fountains, and flying dogs, and silver cats, and emerald
rats, and purple clouds, and faceless crowds, and walls of glass, that never pass, and I
know that if it honestly could disappear, you wouldn't waste more of your time,
that laughter made you ask it, but the past and pictures hangin' upside down,
it won't ask where you are, it's another world!
You and your girl, and all your friends, will all be there, oh yeah!
Let's take a trip, let's take a trip.
TNT!
SOS!
HOP!
TOP!
It's the top, it's the top
Hey, here we go now
Let's climb some mountains, everybody
Get on your walking shoes
Let's start to climb some mountains
There you go
Let's take a trip
Let's start to dream
Let's close our eyes
It's groovy now
Yeah
Float
Because I'm swimming
It's all around
Let's take a trip
I'm from the ground
Whoa
Whoa, yeah
Let's take a trip
It's really hip
No one will know
What goes on
Just you and me
And the dreams we see
I'll come back
You're doing it right
Just put your head back
Friends, The Trip by Kim Fowley
You have been listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack
You can get free information from Bob at Post Office Box 807 Glen Rose, Texas 76043
And you can write to me, Reverend Ivan Stang, stang at subgenius.com
Just check www.subgenius.com
And praise Bob
I mean, everyone knows
Who this shit?
Here's a word problem
A math word problem
Okay
The universe is an infinite
Sorry, an infinite
Oh, you said it right the first time
An agglomeration of energy fields resembling threads of light
That's A
Okay, threads
Remember threads
These energy fields called
These energy fields radiate from a source of inconceivable proportions
Metaphorically
Called the eagle
The needle?
The eagle
Eagle
Human
No, three
Okay, no, C
Human
New age
Human beings are also composed of an incalculable number of the same thread-like energy fields
We are?
So the question is
One ply or two?
Oh, man, that's an easy one
Two ply
Oh, you think it is
Black hole
Yeah, if you don't pick the right answer, that's what you get
You'll be picking something else
Out of your sockets
Oh, is that song over?
The end of the world is over already?
Yes, it is
Let's sing a song about the end of the world
Ah
No, let's go to war.
Let's sing a song about war and the end of the world.
Sky Pilot.
Oh, the beginning of the world?
Yeah, let's sing a song about the beginning of the world in E.
Okay.
The great yeti mother
Squatted down
And grunted
And gave birth
To the universe
And then the great yeti father came
Upon the egg of the universe
And what splurted upon it was what we call
Time
And so time and the universe came together
And something came from nothing
And then God invented souls
And then Bob let God loose from his chain
And said, sack him
And the souls evolved
And sent thirty dollars to Bob
Praise Bob
And so the universe began
Well, that humbly was performed by his self, his own self,
the gland man, our favorite clam, the reverend.
Ivor.
I don't think there's a dry eye socket or any other socket in this room now.
The brain is the only proper receptacle for the seed of genius.
The brain, the brain, look at how many little tiny dendrites there are moving.
Bring me more blind French maid.
If you fly past the sonic sphere, you will die.
Yes, you will.
You cannot live through that.
It's a storm of light.
You know it.
It's pretty dark out there.
Hey, what happens when two black holes come together?
If two black holes meet?
They suck each other up into the infinities.
Gravitational ripples?
Perhaps a new poo-poo on your wing?
It's become like a snake eating each other's tails.
No one could know the answer to that question.
Or fabulous psychosis.
We could never observe it.
We could never absorb it.
Any answer could never be proven.
Well, from a distance we can observe the effects of the two black holes colliding.
Perhaps in some future civilization.
You would never really know what's going on deep down, you know, in the middle of it all.
No, but it would generate unthinkable energies.
And with those we could power our amps.
Oh, what an ingenious idea.
They're so much better than broomsticks and candles.
That would be a great place to do a concert, man.
Right at the meeting point between the two black holes.
I think that's where we did it.
Sapping forces of the vortex.
That was sort of like one of those...
The conclave-age.
Concert right between the two black holes there.
It was the two left eyes of God.
Well, I think one of the black holes was Doc Frop's camp.
That's where we got sucked into.
Ah, like a parasite.
Like a vampire.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah, you missed it all.
You missed the big thing.
Oh, but the robots.
When I get my jet fighter plane, I'm going to play this piece.
When I get to kill.
When I get to kill our Iraqis.
Listen, honey, they're playing our romantic song.
Oh, remember how many Iraqis we killed with this song?
They loved it.
Kill, kill, kill.
The loose wasn't so badly either.
Kill.
About the two black holes.
Yeah.
I think one's from a firefighter named Tom Evans when he put his fire out.
What does that mean?
That's a pretty metaphorical thing there, man.
I don't know if we can even handle that on this show, at least.
That is infatimable.
We don't have the kind of energy forces to deal with that.
Okay.
What happens if an irresistible pie meets an uncontrollable high?
Ah, that is when his alarm is going off.
The boundless appetite for the infinite pie.
I lost for food, not I lost for life.
The uncontrollable pie.
A pie.
This is making me slobbering at the mouth of a pie.
Mildly delicious.
Look, your euphemisms are on the corner of your nasal drip.
Isn't that Dairy Farmers Union place open all the time?
Oh, no, not at this hour of the night unless you go to a special dairy mart.
A special ice cream dairy mart.
Oh, my God.
Yum.
Pie.
Pie to the sky.
That's what we've been offered the whole time when they're offering us death.
Pie.
I hate to sound like an old wobbly son of a bitch.
I like to get down every now and then.
I like to get down and...
Carmelite.
Really, you know, I do a whole different retuning for this and get down into the roots of pie.
You ever get down into the roots of pie?
Yeah, man.
No, I'm hip to it.
I've never done it.
I've never done it before.
A lot of people aren't in touch with that.
They think, you know, all you do is go down to the music store and buy the equipment and,
you know, that's the next thing.
You're in pie.
But you got to get into the root of pie, baby.
Yeah.
And that's something you can't buy at a store.
You know, you can buy the pie there, but you can't buy the root of pie.
Where does the mud of the root of pie come from?
I don't know, man.
You got to answer that question.
Where's the mud of the root of pie?
Oh, that's deep.
Well, ultimately, it comes from a point which expands.
It expands to become the circle from which we derive the pie, or vice versa.
The perfect circle.
It is perfect.
The perfect hole.
A zero.
A nothingness.
Like the thing in the center of Bob's brain.
Perfect like a little baby's colon.
An ever-growing nothingness.
An all-devouring non-existence.
Look at its little chunk.
An anti-somethingness.
Look at its little molecular bingo.
An anti-toy.
A rapacious black hole of all things.
All light.
All gravitational forces.
Even tachyons.
A ravenous boopholder of tachyons.
Bob-ions.
And whack-me-ons.
Whack-me-ons.
Yeah, I like the whack-me-ons.
Oh, Bob, we call out to you in this, our darkest hour.
We are lost in the wilderness, and we need not only your salvation, but your guidance.
And your supreme pure light.
Oh, let it shine.
Till next week.
Keep your hat on tight.
You're back to the wind in your sack and the saddle.
This is ESO Radio, signing off.
See you there.
Your eye.
Till the sun is in the sky.
Oh.
Your eye.
to spend eternity alone with barely any swag.