And it was the strangest thing.
It was amazing.
He turned to Bob.
Did you like it?
Not much.
You're lying.
Maybe he's not.
I know him. Look at his face. He's lying.
And then there was suppressed laughter.
I don't trust him.
Yes, Bob!
Who else am I talking about?
This man is obviously a psychotic.
The third nostril.
That whistling sound.
All right, Bob is my only hope.
I think he's dangerous.
But please don't suppose I'm dangerous because I'm unfamiliar.
I ask that you believe in me.
As what?
As a friend of yours.
Your town.
Of all human beings.
That's all I'm taking from you.
Get back here, you devil!
He should be destroyed.
Destroyed?
Yes.
For our safety.
So I hear all the gossip, you know.
He got busted by the feds. Numerous guys.
Sure, sure.
Who hasn't?
Really?
Yeah.
Whoa!
That's amazing.
Okay, okay.
Somebody should sue your ass for copyright.
You're under arrest!
You know you're my hero.
I've spent ten years getting ready for this day.
That is, if we don't let...
The forces destroy us before that time.
What other forces?
Never mind that now.
As if on cue.
I want to go home.
Well, not yet.
Are you still now?
Help me!
Not later than 7am of July 5th.
It's too long.
Why is it too long?
Such nonsense.
Selling things to people who don't want them.
That's how a scam works!
I want to go home.
But please do not.
But this is a scam on a global scale!
Do you f***ing get me now?
And like a child,
Yeah, beautiful.
It's wonderful.
It's good.
put his hands over his ears.
Blah, blah, blah.
I can't wait till that Bob-time train comes around the bend.
Make the man wish he had a third nostril.
Oh, look out, son.
Here it comes now.
I'm a space invader.
I'll be a rock and roll abyss for you.
We stand at a crossroads.
The tenuous slack that a subgenius may occasionally enjoy,
could be rent to shreds at any moment.
For the human puppets of the elder gods continue their senseless plunge into madness and anti-slack,
dragging us and our whole beloved planet ever closer to the brink of destruction.
Be it by the nuclear kiss of Jehovah One,
ecological disaster,
or invasion by hostile aliens.
Which will it be?
Destruction of planet Earth,
or eternal slack under the benevolent rule of the gods?
I don't know. I don't know nothing.
At a time like this, we can't afford the luxury of thinking.
Hey, back off and give Bob some room to think.
You'll get to hear it on the radio one day.
We hear most everything on the radio.
Turn something on. I'm starting to think.
Click.
This is a Conor Rad radio alert.
Normal broadcasting will be discontinued for an indefinite period.
Oh, Jesus, when are you gonna cut me some slack, huh?
Does it worry you, Bob?
Yes?
All right.
Bob told me personally he will walk off this show to express himself freely.
Let him walk.
If you wanna make an omelet, you gotta break some meat.
What's going on here?
Gob, you're dead. You're dead. I mean it, Gob. You're dead.
Yes! And then he shut the door!
He can't do you nearly the damage that he did on the radio.
No, he can't.
Bob. Hey, Bob.
Where you going?
I'm gonna get going.
Bob, don't leave me. I'm gonna go.
You're gonna get me out here.
I wouldn't go too deep in the desert if I were you. You might never come back.
In fact, maybe you better stay here with us till it's over.
Sorry, I gotta do this.
You come back here!
You idiot! You can't go down there! You listen to me!
He went into the fields and into the towns and into the suburbs
and gathered together all those who despise pinks, perverts, and perverts.
Silence, you perverts!
Bob.
Bob, call for all of those that believe in his power.
Rise up and come to him.
Gather round!
They all turned to him as if they had been waiting for his voice and for that word.
High above!
He was naked.
He's got these eyes that like hypnotize you.
Whoa!
And then his thing, it's huge! It's like a rocket ship!
I dig.
Dig!
Time is running out on that big LP called life!
And the greatest disc jockey of them all is gonna come and take it!
Take us by the hand and lead us to the flip side of life called eternity.
Eternity!
I know all things begin and end in eternity.
Yeah, but before we groove that final date, before we head for that last eight bars,
we gotta make our peace!
Make it, Daddy!
You know I'm gonna make it.
And I want you cats to listen to everything I'm gonna lay on you as of this point.
Number one!
Thou shall not blow thy minds on school nights!
You're a very devout group, where'd you ever find?
I'm on a mailing list. It's the Church of the Month Club.
Number two!
The pipe.
You're gonna really love this one.
It holds a promise for anyone who smokes.
Will you teach us how to smoke?
Sure I will. Sure.
Can I go first?
First what?
No, Susie!
Shut up!
I hope you're not claustrophobic.
Why?
Because it is sinful!
Huh?
Well...
Bob's smile vanished.
So I suggest if anybody's holding, drop it.
Drop out.
Ow!
Before the fuzz arrives.
Reveille at 0700 tomorrow.
That early?
Three minutes.
Hey, yeah.
We get by.
All right, boys, good night.
Next time, Tuesday night.
This day is the one.
Seeing the cards.
I see things.
He sees things.
What things?
Nothing.
I'm just kidding.
Is that little rocket ship of yours?
I don't mean that unkindly.
Hey!
My ticket is open-ended, and my work here is never done.
Bob's eyes shot to him swiftly.
He was not smiling.
It's too late for this spooky .
I think it's over.
I'm not gonna go back to bed.
Bob!
Take a social sleep.
Tonight's the night.
Tonight's the night they come.
It's a freak show.
Do you believe in UFOs?
We believe that the alien will come and land on our landing pad that we are going to build.
It's a structure that we're trying to raise funds for.
So far, we have about $17.
And there are people, I guess, and they believe that they were abducted by aliens and taken
to Mars or whatever they call their alien planet.
Yeah!
What do you think?
Do you believe in UFOs?
Oh, yeah.
Yes, sir.
Definitely.
They're out there, man.
I've seen them.
I've been out there in Aurora, Texas.
They got them little graves and stuff.
Yeah, I've been out there and, I don't know, I'm planning a trip.
We're going out to like Arizona or something.
Or not Arizona.
What was it?
Yeah, it was Arizona, right?
The Air Force One where they found all that stuff.
I got pictures, man.
I've seen them.
They're out there, man.
And I'm flying in the plane.
I'm always hallucinating, but who really knows what I'm looking at.
You know what I'm saying?
It said July, sir?
Yeah.
July, sir.
We can't wait for alien explorers to solve all our problems.
Do you believe in UFOs?
There's no such thing as UFOs.
Boy, I'm really lost now.
Radiation must have affected his mind.
Face it.
He's a mutation of this new atomic world of ours.
I'm no UFO freak, if that's what you mean.
No.
He's a freak.
He's really a freak.
I don't mean that unkindly.
I like freaks.
That's why I like you.
Shut up, you freak!
Lord, I love freaks.
Freak, freak freak, freak, freak, freak, freak, freak!
Pretty mistake.
He doesn't like freaks.
Freaking freaky hoje do you get it?
Tell me!
Freak and freak freak, God
Wake up!
IN INFO
Secretary Hampshire
On the morning of the 15-
On a certain day called X, the sun came up at 6.45.
This is a Conorrad radio alert.
Set official broadcast on the 5th.
There is no cause for alarm.
Ah, crap, is that the time?
Time to get out.
Logan, the engineer, had known this would be the end of the journey.
7 a.m. July 5th.
David Bowie.
All right.
Come on, give me another hour.
Oh!
Rise and shine, rise and shine.
All right.
Bob, get up.
Get up.
Logan stood looking down.
Bob lying casually on the floor, eyes closed,
smile on his face, conscious of nothing but slacking.
Bob, come on, Bob, get up.
Bob.
Get up.
Come on.
Bob.
No, no, no, no.
Oh!
Wake up, Portland.
It's a wonderful day.
The time is 7.
It is later than you.
Oh, of course.
That's just the start.
Is it the fifth?
What time is it?
It's 7 a.m.
What are they cock-a-doodly doing?
Normal broadcasting has been discontinued until after this emergency has passed.
What?
What is that supposed to mean?
What's going on over there?
There were spots of the crowd.
It was a sudden stillness like spreading blotches of paralysis.
What are we going to do?
I'll tell you what's going to happen.
gonna do we're all going to die then came the frantic purposeless movement of people
people running out running to one another clattering in the panel
armed forces blocking out the entrances to the city and we will take necessary
precautions to assure nobody leaves until we can contain this pandemic
state and county police have set up an effective roadblock diverting traffic
line at the city's most important intersection
keep your radio tuned to this frequency remember there is a traffic plan for the evacuation of the
city all cars in the downtown area must follow the green lights they will lead you out of the
danger area by the quickest route do not try to cross the flow of traffic
civil defense is not apart from normal city functioning
not only are we in the middle of the city but we are in the middle of a city that's
surrounded by a whole range of people who are not alone the only people involved in caring for a city
in peace are those equipped to care for her in an emergency and when the siren sounds each man knows
his responsibility
and now i would like a brief situation report from all departments on how we stand
at the operation center with time running out
Vaseline.
Oh, my.
Oh, man.
That's ugly.
He did not have to continue.
It's based on fact.
Chief Simpson.
Oh, crap.
It's on fire.
Oh, it's not fair.
Dr. Robert Slack.
We have constructed a mass deanimation facility and have nearly completed cleansing the region.
Witnesses have been located and silenced.
Local police have been supplied the misinformation outlined in film RT-514, and it is being distributed to the area citizens.
It has been confirmed that four of these Soviet spies have direct involvement and may be carrying on their work to spread airborne toxins.
These subjects have been captured, and information is being extracted.
I didn't even know about it.
I wasn't aware.
We'll have more updates on that coming up.
But right now, Dr. Bob from the Center of Disease Control has some informative.
Advice for people in the Red Zone.
Gentlemen, the series of alarming events.
Thank you, Dr. Bob.
Stocked in film RT-515.
Testing, testing, recording.
Everything going fine.
No trouble.
Now, remember, you have to poke your face into that big, soft, pointy thing.
And the legions of Argentine army ants are continuing on their incredible journey.
All through the camp, they can be observed.
And, uh...
Welcome to the Hour of Slack number 1500...
Yes, may you be truly slackful.
And refreshed unto slack.
Broadcasting from beautiful Wisteria Community Campground.
This at Tarzan's radio station.
Nestled in the heart of the...
Southern Ohio tropical wilderness.
Says something is not working here.
Something is wrong.
Something is very wrong here.
Something is dreadfully...
Something has happened.
I'm sure we all remember where we were, whatever we were doing on that moment of that day.
Now we got...
Now am I coming through?
November 22nd, 1963.
When C.S. Lewis died at home in bed.
Timing.
Nobody noticed.
Yes.
Yeah.
All right, Dr. Howell, it's now time to pick the show background music.
Nooooooooooo.
I don't know if I can hear what...
Let me see it.
Well, we all...
Yeah, we're...
Today we choose from Exotic Lounge.
Oh, that's always good.
Oh, no.
Sleaze music.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Yep.
Exotic Lounge.
Yeah, that's...
That's pretty good.
That might be good for having Susie.
Yeah.
That'll go with Susie.
And then we can swing back to...
It's always better to have me when...
The mole people and...
Exotic Lounge music.
...other exotic treats.
Yes, the mole people themselves were...
I think better when I get my hands involved.
...chumps, let's face it.
Exploited underground workers, essentially.
Unionize!
There we go.
Okay.
Wear your union suit whenever possible.
I can edit out the dead air.
That's no problem.
Dah!
We're not...
We're not too...
You're gonna edit out the whole thing?
...to the internet.
Well, you could replace it with a synthetic...
...uh...
...analog.
Have you...
Have you managed to replace us yet?
No, we're still...
I'm still loading the replacements.
If you weren't spending all your time with Monster Hunter,
you could have digital analogs...
Screw that.
...of Dr. Howl and Lonesome Cowboy Dave and...
Digital analog?
Yeah.
I've already had digital analog with those guys.
They're not that hot.
He's, uh, just...
She's saying that you could, uh...
You didn't take your time...
...create, uh, artificial avatars representing us all...
...and put them through... Mm-hmm.
...through their drill, if that was your fancy.
That's how I usually do, for sure. I'm nothing but stick.
It comes around.
Yeah.
Yeah. You can hear it.
I can hear it.
Recording.
Everything going...
Oh, we did that.
Uh...
Why?
I'm... I'm like one.
Well, uh, today is the...
...first of July...
...and, uh, the full of the moon...
The first day of the end of your life. ...is tonight.
The moon will be completely full at night, and, uh...
...tonight here at Caffeena's, uh, your...
...Camp Reverend Andrew Genis is going to perform...
...and I will support her in some small way...
...right here on our wisteria stage.
Don't forget that after that, from 10 o'clock on...
...open mic...
...preaching...
...bands jamming...
...screeching...
...shouting...
...and various types of...
...loud sonic disturbances...
...together...
...with parties at various camps.
I did bring a knife to open mic this time.
An open mic?
Yeah, which one? Who's Mike?
I'm more interested in the open leg, uh, session.
That's... that one.
Is that performed by Yogini's Stang?
We do get the open mouth knife.
That's all... that's a given.
Yes, the mouth of fate...
...ever yawns wider...
...to engulf us all. If you're lucky, it's just words coming out.
Well, uh, radio listeners, once again, we're doing this show, uh, completely in the nude.
Mm-hmm.
Although we have a tablecloth to hide the lower parts.
And you'll just have to imagine that part.
Hey, you gotta leave something for the buying public.
Ah, they can restore it digitally themselves.
They also are digitally adroit, and they can't keep their digits off these various mechanisms.
Feels so good when they stop. Why should they?
Well, also, it feels good when they continue, so, uh...
...one must simply roll with it, uh, and...
Mmm.
...slide down this easy channel.
I like fiddling with these machine buttons.
No fumbling under the sheets, uh, but why not? I mean, fumbling under the sheets is fun, so I'm...
Fumbling rumbling.
So, anyway, here we are, and it's a beautiful day, with temperatures hovering in... what's the problem?
I'm not sure I'm here. I'm not seeing... I'm not see... I'm getting...
My voice is coming off of your mic.
What happens if I...
Test, test. Oh, there I go.
There, now we've got the manly stang back again.
Oh, oh, now I understand.
No...
Hal is on mic one, and I'm on mic two.
Well, well, well, isn't that interesting? I should have engineered it better, but I failed!
There...
...I tell you...
...is a destiny that shapes men's ends.
It's a lie, it's a quench or...
...rough-hue them how they may.
Okay, this should work.
Uh, so...
Now that it's working...
Yes.
...and everything's going fine, we're recording...
Recording everything going fine.
...yeah, I'm gonna bring you back a piece of green cheese that, uh...
Yeah.
...you've been wanting, and, uh...
...this show is on the go. I mean, it's crackling with energy.
Oh, it's bleeding just as well.
One doesn't know where it will lurch and veer next.
Uh, it's pitching and yawing all over the nuosphere.
But, uh, there are many matters that we could discuss.
Uh, for example, the, uh, uh, Hitler testicle song that we sang the other day has been
augmented by recent research, and now we have, uh, verse two...
Wow.
...of, uh, this historic patriotic song, which...
You might want to remind them of verse one, since they're all asleep...
You can't overdo history.
...in shows most of the time.
Oh, well.
That, this is for people listening in the future, not people in the present who are
not listening.
So, to those attentive ears...
Uh-huh.
...I say, uh, it was, uh...
Hitler has only got one ball.
Goering has two, but very small.
Himmler is somewhat similar, but poor old Goebbels has no balls at all.
Rommel has four or five, I guess.
No one's quite sure about Rudolf Hess.
Schmeling is always yelling, but poor old Goebbels has no balls at all.
Oh, that's beautiful and historically accurate, too.
The rarely heard second part of the Hitler one-ball song.
And one can see why.
The rhyme scheme is imperfect, and the scansion is highly questionable...
Oh.
...in this piece of folk art.
As G. Gordon Gordon once pointed out, I have one ball like Hitler.
And one like Stalin!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
So you could make that fashionable, simply because it was your particular designation.
And you're always Putin.
That's right.
Well, I can almost hear everything with these special blue headphones.
After all, Hitler himself said...
I'm gonna buy blue headphones from now on.
I think mine are blue, too.
Now, we were talking about balls, and those are kind of bluish.
I wound up here with a bunch of blue balls.
By accident.
Really?
No, Sherlock. Yeah.
Bouncy mofos.
A bunch of blue balls?
Blue balls. I'm sorry, I already...
I already cussed, didn't I?
No, that's okay.
I try to be good.
No, you don't.
Yes, I do.
Well, then you're falling down on the job, Reverend.
I'm totally unable to, so it's the same effect, though. So you may as well say yeah.
Now, uh...
Reverend Susie the Flusie is not supposed to be good. Well, good at things, yes.
Yes, of course she's... I understand she's very good.
I'm conflicted.
Now, tonight at 11.30 a.m., to continue our trip through the schedule...
Tonight?
The, uh, uh, ones...
How is he pink?
Hit wonders.
Uh, we'll play at the Mediocre Monster Matinee, uh, starting with Larry Hagman in Beware the Blob.
Wow.
I think that's the one also with Godfrey Cambridge, you know. It has some good things about it.
And, uh, Larry Hagman was at, uh, Burning Man a few years ago. Now he's...
Really?
No longer on this planet.
Wow.
You say Larry was at Burning Man?
Daniel Cameron starring Roddy McDowell, uh, Dr. Faustus, the Richard Burns.
The first Burton, uh, version, which also features Elizabeth Taylor as...
Oh, but, but Richard Burton is, is Faustus in this.
Uh, he, uh, he does the whole thing. It's practically a monologue.
The brakes are off.
And he has the face that launched a thousand ships and burnt the topless towers of Ilium.
Then we have Human Highway starring Dean Stockwell with an appearance by Neil Young.
And the D-Faus.
And the D-Vos.
And...
And Boojie Boy is in this film.
Dennis Hopper.
And Dennis Hopper.
Dancing.
It's all being shown tonight. Yeah, Dennis Hopper dances in this film, followed by The Telephone with Rip Torn.
Oh my God!
And concluding the evening, The Room with Tommy Wiseau. That's, uh, Grindhouse...
Wait, that would be, that would be the phone call of the Nelson Lyon movie.
Grindhouse 2015...
My God, that was amazing.
...shows this entire mediocre monster matinee for your...
...your pleasure and entertainment tonight, starting at 11.30 a.m.
That's down in the dingly dell where my inner spoiled child reigns.
The Grindhouse.
Buldada uber alles, it says on the poster.
That's right. It constantly occurs here at X-Day for your delectation and information.
Ah, I see.
So, don't miss it.
Notice, uh, we, over at the registration table, we have some new inductees.
Fresh meat.
They're now having their special, uh, bracelets welded on and so forth.
The electro-stimulo-negative-reinforcement wristband...
Right.
...which prevents you from leaving. It won't activate unless you leave, and then it'll tighten up and cut your hand off.
Not responsible for malfunctions in cases of ball lightning and other acts of God and the devil.
Blue ball lightning?
That's the best kind.
It's in your subgenius charter. Paragraph four.
I just signed. I didn't read.
They're, uh, checking in rev- that's Reverend 80 they're checking in, and you know what Reverend 80 has that I have besides that disease?
Uh, well, what, uh, Stang? Don't, uh, keep us on 10-
He's got a- he's got a Nintendo 3- new 3DS in his pocket with a copy of Monster Hunter on it.
Boring.
So, I'm gonna quit this show and go play Monster Hunter now, okay, you guys?
Sit your ass down here. You're the hot-
Reverend, uh-
You're the sacred scribe. What are you doing?
I'm going over the hill.
Reverend MacFacfas is also bringing similar equipment.
I can never pronounce his name right, but he sure is a nice boy, and he's got a hot wife.
Which I always- I always liked that combination, nice boy, hot wife. We got a lot of those here.
I have the hot wife.
Oh, there's lots of hot wives.
My son is a nice boy.
But are you truly a nice boy?
Are you not a nice boy for Bob in your way?
Nice boys.
That's not part of my job to say.
I don't know the description actually, Dr. Al.
Okay, I was just inquiring.
No, I don't have to be a nice- I have to pretend to be nice sometimes. That's what I'm doing right this minute!
Oh, I know, I know.
Pretending to be nice! I walk around and when I see a new subgenius, I walk up and introduce myself and introduce them to people.
And then I trick them into going back into one of those sweat lodges with me, and then I do things to them.
Bob taught me how to make them not remember.
We've learned to walk around the bodies in the morning.
What makes you think they don't remember?
They never talk about it anymore.
Mine remember.
Because otherwise they'd brag about it.
Uh, they- I don't know if they do that.
That's one of those repressed memories that comes back and you choke the chicken to it.
Those aren't accepted in court anymore. Those returning repressed memories. Actually, they are in England. That's a shame.
I like to think I've given a few.
All we know is that Bob came and did something to all of us.
That's true.
It started happening when we wound up sleeping in a campground. What are the chances of that?
It's like a slasher movie, but with our butts.
Dove-like Bob brooded on the vast abyss and made it pregnant.
Ow, my pregnant abyss.
During the night.
Anubis?
Or an orb.
An old abyss.
What's wrong with the old one?
Nothing. It is the formless chaos that existed before all being.
The primordial mixture of farmers, telephone poles, scrambled eggs, animal fuels, griffins, garbage cans.
And we're going to make it that way again on X-Day.
We're going to make a tincture out of it.
We're going to start the world over again. Bring it back to its natural, pristine state.
Turn it upside down.
Before the oceans were formed.
Scrape the shit off it and give it back to the Indians.
That's an indelicate way of putting it.
Well, that's the old way of phrasing that paradigm.
Not original with me, I assure you.
You know, I just thought of something.
The Earth is going to be destroyed, mostly by subgeniuses, deliberately.
Aside from the stuff that we say.
We're hoping.
Are we really going to kill it?
We're going to kill the poor Indians.
Native Americans.
You know what?
They have been, they have gotten the bad end of the stick for so long.
We're getting toward X-Day now, so we might as well be a little more honest and say,
subgeniuses will destroy the Earth about as well as subgeniuses do anything.
And the Indians are going to be just fine.
I guess they don't have much to worry about.
Yes.
We'll probably forget.
Whatever way they go, they'll be free.
Besides, our world will be better.
We'll have all the good stuff.
Yeah.
I always wanted to live in a teepee.
Well, don't let me hold you back.
Now, you know, you can, I've stayed twice at the Wigwam Motel in Cave City, Kentucky.
Oh, a wigwam.
There's only three of them left.
I'm clear for programmatic architecture.
Oh, man.
It's really, really cool and cheap.
Fifty bucks a night.
Well, how much are they going to charge you to stay in a wigwam?
Well, one of the things.
The two nights that we stayed in that place, it was like a real wigwam because a terrible
tornado came through and shut off all the power everywhere in town.
Take that, Pindarikoyi.
So it was cold and we had to light a little fire on top of the bed to warm ourselves.
Yeah, that's a true wigwam experience.
Couldn't get on the internet.
That's, of course, you could barely live through that.
Yes, the Native Americans couldn't get on the internet in their day.
Well, they used smoke signals.
It took a lot of smoke to make a porno JPEG.
That was a lot of digital smoke signals.
But all you need is just a one and a zero.
Well, there you have it on a cloudy, windless day.
Didn't we find a number lower than zero?
So this is like X day zero that zero?
So it's bound to work?
Zero minus X day zero minus zero.
Yeah.
X day null zero minus zero.
You just keep taking zero away from zero forever.
My method, my method, Maddox, but Tater, Tater knows that kind of stuff.
Yeah.
I leave that to him.
Too bad Tater isn't here.
I don't have to think about numbers.
Boy, he said a great line the other day.
He did?
Yeah.
Your slack ends where Bob's fist begins.
I'm not sure how to take that, but it sounds good.
Oh, it does.
That's one of the classics right there.
That's the immovable object.
Spontaneously spouted and thus irrevocably accurate and true.
I saw Tater.
I see Tater every now and then in different supermarkets.
He was in line in front of me.
Every supermarket has Tater, isn't it?
And Slave and Save just about three weeks ago.
I don't think he recognized me.
Wow.
He was impatient with the slowness of the girl.
Well, maybe when he's in the Slave and Save, he's incognito.
First time I met him, I had to stay blindfolded.
He's in mufti, as it were.
I've seen him drive by many times.
You know Tater when you see him.
Yeah.
A guy with a name like Tater Gumphries can only look one way.
And he always has those blue overalls on.
Are you sure our background music is playing as high as it should be?
When I checked last night, it was just a hair hot.
Yes, but we should be able to hear the drumming.
The dreamy sounds of the lounge.
Testing.
Yes, the lounge band playing the tiki cocktails on the table.
The dim light.
Oh, yeah.
Where's the sleazy hooker music?
How do you pronounce the name of this song?
Miserlew.
Miserlew, yeah.
I'm going, someday I'm going to do a show of nothing but versions of that.
The amino acids play a really fast thrash version of that.
I love doing that.
When I did that, I went up to Reverend Angry Larry, who's their road manager.
I said, don't they owe royalties on that?
And he looked at me for a minute and then said very strongly, no.
Bob!
Bob blew himself.
Bob just blew over.
Well, yeah, that beat up, toothless Bob head has just hit the dust because it's windy here,
friend.
It's been beaten around before.
You may be able to hear the wind.
Now it knows how I feel.
I know.
Yeah, we've all been had by Bob.
And they smashed a big bite out of his skull, too, it looks like.
Something bit a shark-sized bite out of Bob's skull on that particular dobsail.
Maybe Bob is like Dorian Gray.
Yeah.
He doesn't age, but obviously the ones that we've been carrying out here at the campgrounds.
No, I think it's us.
It's us.
The image is never with.
Well, I know it's us.
That's how he's keeping young.
Oh, yeah.
He's sucking my soul away.
His slack comes from somewhere.
Hey, I'm getting sucked from somewhere.
Look.
Maybe like Tarzan, Bob had some immortality treatment somewhere along the line.
So he never did bother to get old.
Well, let's see.
The three of us have each been doing different broadcast radio subgenius shows.
How does...
Two a week.
And, yeah, it takes a bit out of you.
How many decades have you been doing it, Susie?
21 years.
This October will be the 30th anniversary of the Hour of Slack.
It takes something out of you.
It does something to you.
And what became the Puzzling Evidence Show actually started in June of 1982.
It keeps you alive while it sucks your life away.
Although it was ostensibly...
It's still Bob Nelson's show.
But you see, it started to become...
Puzzling Evidence and Gary, your broke friend, and Lies and Hal just kept showing up.
Per gradus ad ima.
Eventually, Bob Nelson faded away and went off to mine for gold.
He's still performing his alchemical experiments in the desert.
He really is an alchemist, isn't he?
Yes, he is.
He's the last of the alchemists, practically.
Yep.
But he listens...
He listens to my show.
Every now and then, he communicates with it.
So, he faded away, but not completely.
In a way, he was ahead of all of us because he retired soonest.
Well, he moved on to woods and pastures new.
To new adventures.
To stud.
No, seriously, doesn't he mine for something?
Well, he's...
Alien gold in Death Valley or something like that.
He's got minerals that he needs.
He has certain...
He has certain properties, and he's even, in his enthusiasm, sent me crystals and things,
but I don't know what they are.
I know what kind of crystals Bob Nelson is sending.
You know, I wish he had brought some.
They're not like that cocaine candy.
And by the way, that stuff is good, I think.
I do like it.
It's tangy.
Tangy.
Yeah.
It does make your mouth just very slightly numb.
I wouldn't mind it downing another one of those things.
It can't possibly.
It can't possibly really have cocaine in it.
It is coca leaf flavored candy.
Yeah, that's right.
The fact that you can buy it online from New York.
Afterdudes have already chewed all the good stuff out.
Perfectly harmless.
Made from the coca plant.
I think it's got guarana in it.
It's like a sucret.
That's what it's like.
It's quite refreshing, especially in midday under the burden of so...
Thank you.
Of so many other things.
They have hexachloroquine.
A little bit of cocaine candy can keep you going.
See how I keep these people talking?
You can if you have the...
He makes a...
Suck terrible things and we don't shut up.
Whoever made these packages...
It's like Mr. Ed and the peanut butter.
Some enemy of mankind.
Yeah, it's true.
I bought this candy called...
It's all in Spanish.
There's no caramelo.
Producto de Peru.
Holy cow.
I will...
Peruvian...
No.
Peruana.
Peruvian marching candy.
For some reason.
Producto Peruana.
Finally got it open.
My vision is weak.
As it can't be caramel because it's green.
As green as the Amazon jungle.
It's a sucret.
It's like a squashed flat sucret.
Kind of ovoid instead of round, but it's got that institutional green color.
And it tastes sort of like a hospital cleanser.
The green of light filtering through leaves of the forest canopy where all creatures strive for existence against each other.
I think we had Ema Sumac in the background there.
Wow.
That's a good, nice coincidence.
Isn't she a Peruvian goddess or...
I heard she was Amy Camas from, what, Patterson, New Jersey?
Now we're really getting syncretism here.
Yeah, that's Ema Sumac backwards.
Let's not run down New Jersey because we only hear about the bad parts of it, and it's actually the garden state.
Incredibly beautiful and verdant.
But whatever, she made wonderful sounds.
Isn't that what counts?
She sure did.
Yeah, she made high yipping, several octaves.
Above what is expected.
She could hit E above high treason.
And she could certainly yodel and ululate with the best of them on her many best-selling albums.
At the top of her tongues.
The hippies used to play her albums.
Hey, I'd like to hear her sing with Captain Beefheart and Nina Hagen, but...
Well, throw in Tiny Tim and Huey Herman.
If that happened, we're going to have to kill Nina Hagen on July 5th.
Because she's still alive.
She's still alive, right?
I think.
Yeah, I think Nina's still around.
Oh, no, everybody's been dying.
Who's left?
David Osman and Phil Proctor.
Yes, half of Fireside Theater.
Where is Philo?
Half of our heritage.
How many bullets would it take to...
Susie, perhaps you saw that James Horner, the movie composer, crashed his airplane and died.
Yeah, he kissed me.
On the canyon floor, I heard.
But Harrison Ford crashed his airplane and didn't die.
Oh, so now, what's the joke?
What was the last thing that went through James Horner's mind?
Some piece of music from one of the movies.
The airplane engine.
Oh.
Weep, weep, wep, wep, wep.
That was originally a John Denver joke.
Yeah.
What was the last thing that went through John Denver's mind?
His plane's engine.
Weep, weep, wep.
Weep, wep, wep.
Was that a disgruntled pilot?
Yeah.
Boy, that was a Santa got my letter moment.
That was a thigh slapper if I ever heard one.
Somebody stopped me before I laughed myself to death.
Yeah, you may need it.
I try to stop short of AM radio.
This little whistle...
We're sophisticates.
...is shaped like big red lips.
Yes, it's the morning zoo.
Nobody would be able to tell the difference, Susie.
I don't know where that's...
It's been.
It's been in my mouth, so it tastes like...
Yeah, but before then, it's been sitting on this table
in the middle of a clutch of subgeniuses.
And subgenius items which have been handled by many scurvy subgeniuses.
Who wants some Bob Virus?
We've got Bob Virus for anybody who wants to go...
Spirokeets.
Those derived from the Lyme disease-bearing...
...infectious humor.
...as large as bottle caps that roam the woods.
Oh, yes.
Like a weeping rash.
The wildlife of Wisteria.
The Kendi-root toad.
Those playful and insistent bears.
Face-loving bat, as we say when kids are...
They respect your face.
With every ounce of their being.
The arboreal prairie squid.
Or forest squid, actually.
They're not nearly as venomous as the prairie prairie squid.
But they bite.
You really have to make sure you de-beak them before you...
You know.
They is.
I'm sure I don't have to spell out to gaggle a subgenius
is what you do with a prairie squid.
Once they're de-beaked, they're a harmless companion.
It doesn't hurt the squid, really.
That beak grows back in about two weeks.
Although, usually...
After you've done them, you put them out of their misery
and cook them and eat them.
Oh, I'm going to be during the taco festival on Saturday.
That's right.
Let's announce that.
There is going to be a subgenius taco meat festival on Saturday.
Taco filling competition and contest.
We will fill tacos with all possible entrails
and then consume them.
I brought taco shells.
I know.
Which side of the taco I need to be on.
Yes, it'll either be taco apocalypse, taco terror.
What are you gesturing?
Hey, I'm going to...
Why don't you guys do the rest of the show?
Reverend 80 has his 3DS and we could be playing Monster Hunter.
We could take down the...
You have a problem, Stang.
You need to admit you have a problem.
We can play Monster Hunter and watch Monster High cartoons at the same time.
It's a good time to do an intervention, Stang.
Well, we all love monsters.
I don't know anyone here who doesn't, but...
Oh, my God.
Ah.
Some new kind of Bull Dada.
Oh, it's Bull Dada eye candy.
What the...
Uh-oh.
And this will be really good because Reverend 80 is a fine artist.
Good.
Well, then that shouldn't be...
With a very distinctive style.
Wow.
These are hand-colored.
I think, aren't they?
Too good to sell.
That is amazing.
That's Bull Dada eye candy.
My chrome.
They're like tarot cards of the subgenius.
Newsflash.
Hey, kids.
This...
This show is interactive.
While listening, you can view the amazing Bull Dada eye candy on the web at subgenius.com
slash rev80.
That's all lowercase, R-E-V-8-0.
subgenius.com slash rev80.
There's a...
Yeah, there's like a paramecium.
There's a Egyptian thing with pyramids and saucers.
There's DNA.
There's a flaming sword.
How about that?
Is that correct?
We actually have a flaming sword here.
We can only use once.
Well, I remember the last time.
So we have to be careful.
In the middle of the field where the guar guy had rigged it and it wouldn't go off.
The flaming sword when we had...
We had Bob crucified and we wanted to burn him because you have to.
Right.
Yeah.
Man, I wish the radio audience could see these.
These are just amazing.
Look, the seven-bladed windbreaker.
They're beautifully made.
Some other planetary hand colored.
Those are vivid.
Those are quite beautiful.
Arteries.
Wow.
The stark fist of removal.
A plaid dog's head.
Checkered bob.
Rolling pins falling down.
Salak.
Right.
As opposed to Sakak, which we always avoid.
Whoa.
Ooh, a stretched out...
Mr. Sister.
Yeah, it looks like Mr. Sister.
A new icon showing Mr. Sister.
Mr. Sister is now part of the subgenius array of images.
Those are beautiful.
The cowboy with the H-bomb.
With the tie-on yippie.
It's a big dildo now.
Yippie strap-on.
Yeah, this is amazing.
Wow.
You could tell somebody's future with these cards.
I wish that the radio audience could see it.
Whoa, and the hits just keep on coming.
The live audience is too far away.
It shows the earth rupturing.
Whoa.
You can view the...
The amazing Bull Dada eye candy on the web at subgenius.com slash rev80.
Pills.
Pills tonguing each other.
A flaming pipe.
Wow.
And the flaming pipe of...
A vagina-eyeballed hideous alien bob.
Bob rupturing himself in wonderful ways.
Fractal bob.
A fractal bob.
Creeping.
Wow.
A gray alien.
Man, this has got everything.
It's like a...
The Jehovah One evil eye on the...
On the pyramid.
And the sacred sigil.
And he hasn't repeated them, and it's been about 50 so far.
It's like the loaves and the fishes, but with beautiful...
There's one of the Magritte's design.
And it doesn't stink like fish.
A Celtic knot dob's head.
And you weren't loafing.
Oh, look.
Oh.
An ultimate...
A robot Maria dob's.
Smoking a pipe.
Yeah, Maria the robot from Metropolis with a pipe.
A possum.
A hideous...
A psychedelic possum.
A mighty...
A marijuana plant.
These are rendered in a really psychedelic style.
They're so vivid.
A toy robot.
Classic toy robot.
Nice scowling face.
A cat.
A robot.
An evil cat with rays coming out of its eyes.
And a flying saucer.
And robot monster.
Robot monster.
With a volcano behind him.
And it hasn't repeated yet.
And yet I cannot.
And a Dr. Seuss looking character worshipping Satan.
A goat.
A whole bunch of Saturns.
A Flash Gordon type spaceship.
A monkey.
Space.
A green monkey.
A robo space monkey.
With his green monkey virus in space.
And we're finally back to the beginning.
Back to the Paramecium or slipper animal.
Well, he brought it all back.
Surely this is too good for any bulldog.
Bulldog eye candy.
40 pieces of visual deprogramming by Reverend 80.
And this is the only copy.
Wow.
Creepers.
You better not drop it in a puddle, boy.
Well, right.
Yeah, it looks like you wouldn't want to get it wet.
Yeah.
Maybe you need to get them laminated.
Laminated.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, we need to get them scanned is what it is.
Yes.
Because then they exist forever.
If you scan them at 300 dpi.
That sounds so dirty.
Well.
Subgenius.com.
Rev 80.
Well, you know, the subgenius artists being mostly unprofessionals did all their art at 72 dpi for the internet.
And then when you go to try to illustrate your book with that stuff, why, you know, you blow it up to a decent size and it gets all jpeggy and jittery.
And that's when you have to use this sacred subgenius program called Genuine Fractals.
It's like Minecraft.
Yeah, right.
Right.
In fact, the way that some people design Minecraft things is they'll take a picture or whatever image they want.
And make it a tiny little jpeg and then blow it up real big.
So it turns into a series of blocks and you can count your blocks out and make your giant dildo out in Minecraft or whatever.
You know.
It's another time killer.
Yep.
And brain mind killer.
But, oh, it's so fun because it doesn't get you ahead in life at all.
It has no purpose besides just pure slack.
This is all like, this is not the music for this.
We need something that's peppier.
Pepp-o.
Yeah, this is all that, you know, lazy.
The South Seas.
Yeah.
Tropical Islands.
What's on Monster Moves?
This one is Jungle Madness.
I know.
How about that?
But it's not nearly mad enough.
Baba Lou is coming up.
From island unto island at the gateways of the day.
Desi Arnaz wiped that from another guy whose name escapes me now.
Juan, was it, not Juan Valdez, that was the crazy, uh, Miguel Valdez.
The coffee maker, yeah.
Picker.
He totally swiped it.
Inflection and everything.
I was, the parts of history that we don't remember.
Larger constellations burning.
Mellow moons.
Moons in happy skies.
Putting up with Lucy wasn't enough.
And palms in cluster.
Knots of paradise.
I think we used this one the other night at the station.
You're putting that in a puddle of water.
We used, uh, themes from sci-fi, fantasy, and horror.
With the mole people.
The mole people.
Creature from the Black Lagoon.
That's the one with Hans J. Salter.
Yes.
Uh, This Island Earth by Herman Stein.
Son of Frankenstein.
Oh, oh, oh.
Um, it's not really very frenetic.
Ah.
Now, I do have, um.
That other stuff was soporific.
Heavy metal renditions of Monster Hunter game themed music.
Now that's good.
That's good.
Music with spikes on it.
A house of Frankenstein.
It's also good.
We used that yesterday.
Well, let's see what the mole people does for us.
Yes, what did the mole people ever do for us?
They gave us moles.
They gave us Hugh Beaumont.
That's where moles come from.
Mm-hmm.
He's in the mole people.
That's true.
And Nestor Paiva.
And he's, he's a shorthand for Pinks when they say, who is that with the pipe?
Right.
I say, that's the beaver's dad.
That's Hugh Beaumont.
And it, it seems.
Oh, yeah.
I love that show.
Uh, oh, Nick Van Dyke.
Ha, ha.
Oh, Mark Traill.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
That's what I used to tell them was it carved on my slack-o-lantern every year.
Yes, um.
That made sense to them.
Also.
But Bob didn't.
No.
This is music to trudge through Tibet by.
On your way to discover the underground kingdom.
God, this is, this is such sappy crap.
Of the mole people.
Yes, the mole people, uh, subhuman burrowing servants of ancient Assyrians who have survived
to the present day in lightless underground civilization as the same as it was millennia
ago.
Ah, this is sentimental covered wagon music.
Now.
But beware.
The mole people can tunnel up under you at any time and drag you down into your, their
tunnels where you will be, apparently, it's not very clear, horribly mutilated by their
giant shovel-like forepoint.
In my neighborhood, they mostly get eaten by cats.
But again, a conspiracy always turns everything around backwards.
That's the way they'd show it in a Hollywood movie, but probably the real mole people are,
for all we know, they're mole girls.
And when they drag you down into their roost.
Or mole hole.
They wanna, you know, do jig-jig.
Or sex you up.
Or, you know, mole you out.
Yes, but they're not even human with, uh, conical heads and huge carbuncles and great
big bulging eyeballs and, uh.
Urging you to let go.
Yeah, that's right.
Covered with thousands of hideous, tiny venomous fingers urging you to let go.
Well, I'm not quite there yet, but.
Urging women to let go specifically.
No, you.
And you.
And yes, you.
Let go, baby.
Just let go.
The world ends tomorrow and you may die, so it's time to party, baby.
May?
Maybe that's it.
The world ends tomorrow and you will die.
I want some certainty, dammit.
Only to believe.
No, no, no, no, it's very important that you keep the word may in there, because that gives
you hope.
Nobody wants to be told they will, everybody's gone.
No, no, we're not, we're not.
The idea is that the point is that the point is that the point is that the point is that
the other is the point is for somebody.
My condition?
Does it work out?
For example, if somebody is
You bother people in this kind of situation.
Quite obviously, they can cast doubt upon that.
You face on those
check for subgenius unless you put it in add to dictionary hey not only do we do
three completely different subgenius shows for years and years and years and
for no damn good reason not have a life yeah but oh wait what was the other thing I was about to say
but we actually are three different people yeah yeah there was some other
thing we had in common and it just went away well three subgenius shows it was sarcastic and mean
three what three muskereers three gates into the three heavens it had something to do with being old
oh the last we're the last three grammar nazis on the planet there's a few I'm forced into it
I'm forced well I know you get paid to be a grammar nazi but you are able to do it most people can't
that wouldn't that just don't know the difference anymore it's horse pucky
it's absolutely
absolute horse pucky my own father said get used to it language changes it's fluid there's no such
thing as correct Shakespeare spelled his name differently every time he signed it well he's
mostly like you know who are get out of bad lungs you got really mad when I used that on you yeah
you are old law I got that from two beans and the thing is he was right
now what is this
this is well now Mont prophets the church is using them knocking i-zuf for presidents
you're gonna make your little crates but would you let me tell more about that
father this is I will show you first we will be talking about you all right
by about a week
Everybody's failed apocalypse.
Apparently.
And Catholicism for dummies, I could use that.
I really don't know that much about Catholicism,
aside from what you just sort of pick up.
You've got to get on your knees a lot.
You can read the book.
And then you go to church, and there's even more of that.
Yeah.
My son, at the age of 15 or 14 or so, as boys are wont to do,
they get kind of stupid.
And he said, what happened was he saw that movie,
Jesus Christ Superstar.
And like Carter LeBlanc before him,
he mistook the rock and roll for the religion part.
It made him feel real good,
but he didn't understand that what was doing that was the rock and roll.
So he goes,
Dad, Mom, I want to try going to church.
And we immediately go, oh, well, you know, the Unitarians.
So that's a nice, no, no, no, no.
I mean a real church.
Oh, God.
Okay.
He goes, there's a great big fancy Lutheran church down the road from us.
I want you to drop me off there on Sunday.
Okay.
Now, of course, I'm like going, oh, Jesus Christ.
What's going on?
Well, I dropped him off at this Lutheran church,
big fancy Lutheran church, and picked him up.
A couple hours later, he got in the car and he goes,
Dad, I feel like I want to worship Satan now.
Where'd you take him?
But that's a Lutheran church.
Well, after that, you know, I had to go, son,
Satan's just a made-up character.
Well, rather, he's real, but he and Bob have an understanding.
The Christians have him all wrong.
Dog Elves figured that out at six.
Satan has helped all of us out.
That's right.
We described that on the last show.
And Satan dragged me out of that quicksand at the first X day.
He handed Hal a microphone at the last minute on a big performance.
Yes.
And what did Satan do for you besides, you know, get into your head?
He dressed me that morning.
That's all I could ask for.
So, yes.
That's why I had the pitchfork and the horns.
You know how the New Agers are accused by ignorant Christians,
of being Satanists, witches.
Well, they are witches.
Isn't everybody they don't like?
But I was standing, back when Starwood was huge,
I was standing in front of an audience of hundreds of people, literally.
And first I read from the flyer that was going around town
that described Satanic gang signs and symbols and what they meant.
Of course, things like pictures of Mickey Mouse were Satanic.
I passed.
It's a huge crowd.
You'd never have a better cross-section of pagans.
I said, how many of y'all are actually Satanists?
Raise your hand.
And one metal dude in the back kind of shyly put his hand up for a minute
and then pulled it down real quick.
He was the only one.
He was the only Satanist at the whole damn Wiccan festival.
Well, Satan is a Christian character.
If you're a Satanist, you're a kind of Christian.
But on the other hand, all that's ever been written about,
about Satanists and those who are demon worshippers,
has been written by the other side
and may not be dependent upon to be an accurate and unbiased assessment.
Now, I'm given to believe that the guy who wrote the book Satanic Panic,
whose name I can't remember,
lived in Jamestown, across the lake from Brushwood.
He should have lived in California to be in the middle of it.
If you ask me, Satan now lives at Brushwood,
but I'd rather not get that personal.
You can ask me about that one later.
Yes, we'll get into that at another time.
Yeah.
Looks like Ankara.
Oh, the Tap House crew is here.
Now I can go play Minecraft and Monster Hunter at the same time.
Saying you have addiction issues.
You guys take over the show now.
He's going down to a street corner to get...
Just monster crack.
Hey, we did an hour.
Do you know what that means?
That means it's time for me to push the off button
and then push the on button again.
Uh-oh.
Friends, you're listening to Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack,
a live pre-recorded show from the...
Live?
...grounded hysteria in beautiful southern Ohio,
near Mothman's house.
Yeah.
He's right over yonder.
He slept there.
For more information, you can try subgenius.com.
And now this is where we fade everything out very professionally.
Oh, this gets scary and scary.
Do we have to get dressed again?
As we dwindle away.
Well, I'll do the fade out later.
I really do have to stop this thing now.
Sire, there is no more money.
We gotta get some money.
That dirty Turkish harker back flat
and rotten Philip Buckaburton
and Herculean Burton
and Dirk Buston.
I'm gonna let them all out!
Beep. Beep.
Beep.
We're glad you listened to this show
and we're even more glad that some listeners
have donated enough to help us keep on going
for another couple of months.
And not just this show,
but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
But if you truly love Bob
and want some of that slack back to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com front page
or especially the radio page
or the...
catalog store pages
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like
to be on the brink of total poverty
and we don't want any subgeniuses
to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference
even if it's only once a month
from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that
blowjob
could go the way of Steve Jobs
if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to
Subgenius Foundation
P.O. Box
Cleveland Heights
Ohio
Thanks for anything you can do
to help let there be slack.
After Complex
AOhhoo Heaven
Okay on call
A zero
Only now
Anyday
Green pills!
Money!
Bar!
Green pills!
Sex!
Money!
Bar!
Green pills!
Sex!
Money!
Bar!
Kill me!
Sex!
Money!
Bar!