Thank you for joining us tonight. Now, I just heard in the report that
The Subgenius Hour of Slack
That is correct.
To engage in this attack. That's correct.
Ah, yes, dear friends, there are several
Subgenius radio shows besides the Hour of Slack.
The Puzzling Evidence Show and Bob's Slack
Time Funhouse have been on the air for as long or longer
And there have been other spin-offs that went extinct.
But there's now a new, powerful podcast
One that erupted like a pustule
Out of the Thorazine Urine Pod Crust comedy
Non-true called
Time for the Show!
Oh, the latest incarnations have been better recorded.
And had less cussing than earlier ones.
And episode number 102 or 102 or 102 or something
Had me as a guest.
So I decided to just run that into the same thing pretty much as is.
You can hear Time for the Show at
Timeforthewebsite.com
Or subgeniuses.com
Or hypercubelaboratory.com
I bet you can spell that yourself.
Hypercubelaboratory.com
Or look at the Hour of Slack radio section of subgenius.com
Anyway, the purveyors of Time for the Show so far have been
Reverend Fid Chulik, Dr. Argus Fox, and the ever insecure Reverend Pease.
All of them heard on this very show, Hour of Slack, on many recordings from recent X-Day.
Praise Bob!
And now it's time for Time for the Show.
No muss, no fuss, no spill
You tired of kitchen drudgery
Everything must go
Going out of business
50% off original retail price
Skip the middle man
Don't settle for less
How do we do it?
All you want
Going out of business
Time for the show
Tonight, on Time for the Show,
special guest, Reverend Pease, Fid Julie, and some other guy.
No! It's Reverend Ivan Stang from the Church of the Subgenius.
Will he make it here on Time for the Show?
Time for the Show.
The YouTube Laboratory.
And here are your hosts, Reverend Pease and Fid Julie, on Time for the Show.
Welcome, guys.
Time for the Show!
Boo! Time for the Show sucks!
It's my least favorite part.
Don't we have a special guest tonight?
We do have a special guest live from the post office.
It's Reverend Ivan Stang from the Church of the Subgenius.
Welcome to Time for the Show.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Repent. Quit your job. Slack off.
Okay, can I go home now?
No one's going to really believe it's you if you just phone.
Don't untie him yet.
The check doesn't clear until the clock rolls over, so you might as well, you know.
That is fact.
Well, where's Dr. Shoggoth?
I was expecting him to be here.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
He goes right for your heart.
Right at the beginning of the show, he goes right for the...
It's like there's a giant bleeding wound in the shape of my inner hamburger.
Oh, it smells good, though.
Juicy.
Succulent.
I didn't know you were hip to such church gossip.
Can I get a closer look at that wound?
Isn't all hamburger technically inner?
Hamburger?
In what sense, Finn?
Until it's on the outside.
Oh, well, it all comes from the inside, though.
We're all asking the big questions here tonight.
Where's hamburger come from originally?
Well, that's why we have an expert.
We have the guy...
Hamburgers come from cows.
Those are those rectangular things that you also get milk from the store.
The little cardboard boxes.
Or plastic jugs.
Isn't it?
Those are cows.
Wonderful how nature packages everything so perfectly.
How do the cows know what dairy they work for, though, when they put out the little carton?
How do they know how to print it with their teeth?
They've been genetically modified.
They make love to the CEO.
And that's how the cartons come out that way.
Oh, I guess it's a combination of both those answers if you think about it.
It's genetical, peas.
Yeah, man.
Genetical.
Scientifical.
I've got a pair of geneticals for you.
You can't say that on the radio.
I have one genetical.
I think that you could say that on the radio.
I've got a genetical for you.
Yeah.
I'll show you guys that.
I don't want to see it.
That's right.
On time for the show, we're working with an odd number tonight, everybody.
What is that odd number?
Seven.
That is actually a pretty good number.
It's seven on episode 11.
Hey.
So, yeah, this is the Luck Plane show.
The Luck Plane show.
7-11 was an inside job.
It's the Luck Plane show when it took us 10 minutes to start the show tonight.
So, I blame Ivan Stang for that, though.
We can.
You know, he didn't show up for his.
He wasn't in the green room.
You know, he was being all dramatic.
Well, there was some drama.
The audience needs to know that we had planned an extravaganza.
It's been six months of intensive segment writing done by me, Pease.
As you know, I'm the segment writer.
I don't have any editing credits or anything like that, like theater artists.
But regardless of that, we had a whole spectacular extravaganza.
At the last minute, Ivan Stang says, oh, I can't do it.
I can't do it, guys.
I forget what his excuse was.
He was insecure.
He found something else to do.
Found something else better to do.
Every Macintosh or Apple product had become suddenly horribly vulnerable to terrible pirates and viruses just overnight.
Suddenly.
So, we all had to download this.
Well, that's what you paid for that quality machinery for.
No, it's actually.
He's actually.
The listeners are hearing me adjusting my microphone mic filter.
But nonetheless, so we had to write from scratch.
And for those of you not in professional radio, like Fidjuli and Argus Q Fox, Ivan Stang and myself, the pre-show activity, the writing of a show is about, like I said, a seven-month process.
It goes through many phases and faucets.
So, to throw one out with 15 minutes, you know, 35 minutes warning.
Well, you know.
This is.
We had a really probably a better show than what you're going to get now.
Because at the last minute, again, Ivan Stang says, oh, I can do it now.
So, we had to throw out all of the good show that we had lined up for you.
That we did spontaneously.
And going back to the old, here's Ivan Stang show.
Oh, come on.
You're trying to blame everything on me.
It was the censorship board.
You know, the censorship board.
They're not going to let anything out until they approve it.
Well, this is on a Canadian.
Canadian radio.
So, we don't have censors.
It's not that they censor us.
They just ask us politely not to do things.
Boys, could you stop swearing so much, eh?
Eh?
Of course we can.
Oh, God.
Will we?
Yeah, we're on free thing radio.
Canadian radio is very different than American radio.
What about the trailer park boys?
How come they're not on this show?
Yeah, I mean, they're Canadians.
I think we should be able to get any Canadian.
Is like a legally obliged to be on the show.
D2 are.
Rick.
We have a Canada is a communist country.
Well, we have, we got the big man here.
We got, uh, we, we got Dr.
Scab and, um, he's gonna, he's gonna open up that Rolodex of his, and he's gonna set us up with a, with an awesome celebrity interview for every week for the rest of the year.
So let's, uh, let's go.
Who we got first.
We can start with A's and work towards.
Z Adam celebrities.
The first one that you got, the one that'll give us the bump.
Our bar.
Hey, there we go.
I'm on the show.
Look at that.
That's convenient.
I'm also in the Rolodex.
Are you in the Rolodex?
The Rolodex of life.
I could be ended there a couple of ways.
Yeah.
So our August Fox, Brad Pitt.
Who would see be, uh, shouldn't it be a crunch?
Yeah.
He's a celebrity captain.
Is he really a captain or is that like a honorific, like being a Kentucky Colonel?
Well, he was a captain in the Naval reserve in intelligence unit.
See, he wasn't like riding on the prow of a ship saying fire away at those pirates boys.
He was more like.
We need to track down these homosexuals who went AWOL and find out.
Stole our crunch berries.
I thought it.
Yeah.
That's what I thought it was.
Cause you like a swashbuckling for crunch berries.
Well, that too, of course.
But you know, in, in, in his day job, captain crunch had this, uh, difficult Navy, Naval
intelligence job of having to track down AWOL sailors.
And 90%.
Yeah.
And 90% of the time it was because they were in love.
So you're telling me that the science having figures of being a branded official for a
delicious cereal, it's this really tedious day job where he has to track down errant
Naval lovers.
Basically.
Yeah.
But he developed a lot of sympathy for, you know, he started out.
I feel sorry for him already.
Kind of homophobic guy.
But as he, as he.
Had to interview.
So guys who'd run off, he began to gain sympathy for them.
And in fact, uh, I think he became fascinated with, uh, transgender or what you might call
what's the word chicks with dicks.
Captain crunch is actually a really big part of that whole scene.
I don't know if you guys knew that.
I do not know that.
I don't think anybody.
Anybody knew that.
That's why he started the cereal company.
He's in his late eighties.
If he's not 90 already, but he's a real big activist for, uh, um, not, not all transgender
rights.
Just the pardon the expression chicks with dicks.
He's really the hot ones.
Well, you know, uh, up to a point.
Who's going to question.
Well, I mean, he worked under general mills and we all know that general mills had a relationship
with Betty Crocker who was based in a battle Creek, Michigan.
They were part of that whole CIA, uh, Mocha man, LSD experiment that was going on, uh,
had a different public name.
How do we get in on those tests?
So, uh, yeah.
Yeah.
It's all part of the Kennedy assassination and all of it's just such a huge can of worms.
It's such a massive, who cares at this point?
Well, you're a Texas man.
I heard Kennedy wasn't assassinated.
He just ducked and then played dead.
So he could get out of the whole deal.
Well, isn't that interesting?
It sounds sort of funny to say that, but as a matter of fact, that is precisely what happened
with the help of Jr.
Bob.
Yeah.
Kennedy was miserable.
He needed slack.
Bob got it, uh, fake the whole assassination deal and got him a job as a taxi driver in
Argentina.
And if you don't believe me, read the fine print in book of the sub genius.
And the bullet that was fired was actually fashioned into a false tooth that found its
way into the lower gum.
The gum of Donald J. Trump.
That's how he inherited his power.
No bullet at all.
There's just a loud guy clapping real, real, you know, bang.
It had to go into Trump's face when he was about 10 years old or something.
Well, no, it didn't immediately go into his face, but through a series of, uh, made for
TV quality level, um, happenings and, uh, hijinks, it found its way over the course
of time into his mouth.
Oh, so it probably didn't happen until the late eighties or nineties when it got into
his mouth.
So that bullet was bouncing.
Their tooth bullet was bouncing around after it went through John Connolly's wrist and
Kennedy's brain three times.
It bounced around the United States until it ended up inserting itself into the jaw
of Donald Trump, age 12 at the, uh, reform school where his parents had said.
Hmm.
Yeah.
It's true.
Look it up.
It's on the internet.
Google it.
Google it, dude.
It's on the internet now.
It might not have been 10 minutes ago.
We're live.
I said it.
I wrote it down on a piece of paper and mailed it to myself.
Therefore it's true.
There you go.
Copyright trademark.
You can't copyright.
Did you send a letter to yourself with the whole premise on it?
You got to do that.
We've already talked about that.
Yeah.
And I sent it to myself so I didn't have to use a stamp.
They just put return to sender on it and took it right back to me.
That could be, that could be trouble in court.
Remember not to open it until you're actually in court.
Everybody does that.
Ed Wood did that and look at him.
He's not getting any royalties at all.
Every time they show plan nine from outer space, nothing.
But what's Ed Wood getting any, isn't Ed Wood, you know, passed away for quite a while now.
So he wouldn't be getting anything.
I guess.
I guess the state would, right?
Oh, well, I guess so.
I kind of forgot.
Let me ask you something.
You know, Michael Jackson was broke when he died, but now his estate is worth, you know,
I think billions.
And the same thing with Elvis.
Elvis, you know, he was on hard times.
He died.
All Elvis's family now is super rich.
Do you think that your state will rise in value with your untimely death?
That we don't know anything about?
Uh, that's a good question.
That question makes me uncomfortable.
For several obvious reasons.
Don't worry, Sam.
We haven't settled on a plan yet.
I'm just trying to figure out my blind eye.
That Dobbs head is worth a million bucks only as long as I'm alive to approve everything.
For the right reasons.
I don't know.
I think I'm a, I'm a.
I think you can write Princess We a personal message.
Oh, go ahead.
I'm sure she'd be flattered.
Well, uh, then she would-
Real actual correspondence with peas.
We'll laugh at her, make fun of you, mock you.
That's true.
She's super good at that.
Then you can get that all the way around peas on the show and off the air.
I think I provide a valuable service to everybody by being that, that conduit for
the mocker.
So does, you know, well, you know, it's like Everest.
If they didn't make punching bags, we'd just have to keep people.
If you guys didn't have a peas, you would have to invent him.
How would you invent a peas?
I imagine you would start off with a comedian from the 80s
and then wrap him up in a bunch of joint papers
and then train him to wink his tongue.
Do the kids call them spliffs?
Is a spliff still a technical term?
A spliff is marijuana and tobacco, isn't it?
Is it that specific?
Yeah, that's my take on it.
You just can't bang a spliff?
That's a Jamaican thing?
You can't bang a spliff?
I want to say you can.
Can we say spliff on the radio?
Can you say bone on the radio?
Do you guys call them bones?
You can say spliff as long as you call it splief.
You can say fropstick, man.
Just say fropstick.
Fropstick.
Nobody knows what that means.
The conspiracy will never figure out what we mean by
habifropzepulops or habifralium or habifrelSD
or habifrocaine or any of those code words.
They'll never figure it out.
That's true.
They are slow.
Yeah, so just go for it, man.
We'd also like to make a shout out to anybody listening to the,
at the NSA right now or the CIA or the FBI,
but more likely it's going to be our friends over in Russia.
The secret trigger word this week was frop.
In Soviet Russia, it's time for show listens to you.
Hey, P's, what's your actual physical address again?
What is it?
What?
What's your actual physical address again?
I forgot.
6428 Dobie.
Peak Drive, Las Vegas, Nevada, 8910.
Wait a minute.
We said if we did that, we try and make cobalt level Patreons.
No, no.
The, um, the cobalt level Patreon.
Because that's what the prize is for a cobalt level Patreon.
No, no.
That's your actual phone number, P's.
Oh, the phone number.
Okay.
Well, the address is good.
Yeah.
Didn't you just summon the secret service?
Ah, those guys.
Yeah.
We're swatting P's.
We're going to swat P's live on the radio tonight.
Nice.
We're going to tell him that he's a crazed cultist and, uh, totally unhinged.
I don't, you know, I have to admit it's occurred to me that if anybody was, uh, you know, a
target for that kind of terrible prank or abuse.
Yeah.
I'm going to be me.
That's why I can give it away in relative safety.
What would you like to say about the allegations against you now?
Well, what I'm thinking is I probably should go visit with the sheriff in the little town
I live in and go, now, sheriff, you may get some funny phone calls from the FBI and the
CIA and NSA.
LAVPs.
Yeah.
But I want you, you know, I'm part, my family's been here in this little town for a long time.
I just returned here from Cleveland, Ohio.
Yep.
Yankee town.
It's terrible.
But I'm back now.
Everything's fine.
I just want to let you know, it's all, it's all a bunch of silly joke.
You know, my, my, my brother runs a goat ranch around the corner.
My sister tests the water.
So come on.
You don't need to believe any of them city police forces that are talking about cults
and, uh, drugs and all that kind of stuff.
Dossier.
We don't have to look at no dossiers.
None of the sex cults are bringing the.
Dead back to life or the, uh, the keeping alive of brains in jars in extreme pain.
None of that.
That's all just part of our fun and satire sheriff.
Well, I've worked at in, uh, Sherman, New York.
We're used to have to have the.
It's used to be where X day used to be back in the day.
Wasn't it?
Right.
And now then we had to make friends with the sheriff of Pomeroy.
Oh, now we're getting into that deep subgenius hot goss.
Yeah.
When, uh,
Is, is which state troopers have knocked on the door of the command trailer, terrifying
us when all they really wanted was a Bob t-shirt.
And I'll tell you all of the state troops fit fell into that category.
They didn't want to bust us for anything.
They just wanted a Bob shirt.
Yeah.
So don't let staying for you.
When he says the keeping alive of brains is beneath him.
He just means it's happening in his basement.
He's just trying to throw off the, it's funny.
It's funny you would say that because he has one of the only basements in, uh, whatever
place and that's Texas.
No, no Texas.
Well, it's, I was scared to say special torture chamber, right?
Of course.
But, uh.
But still it's on your mind.
It's unusual.
We call it a shit.
Yeah.
It's so, yeah.
You have to use dynamite to blast the rock out to make a hole.
Yeah.
It's unusual to have any hole in the ground in this part of Texas, but you said hole holes.
We can make a hole.
I've been down in that hole, brother.
I know about that.
A lot of people, a lot of people think you've gone down there and you're living this life
of luxury.
You understand the perils and dangers that take place on this.
You very nicely call it a goat farm, but the reality is this entire place is filled with
monsters and mythological creatures that on a daily basis you do battle with the dreaded
armadillo, the rattlesnake of death.
Why?
If people believe that there'd be pinks trying to get in here all the time to make a movie
of it or something.
That's all a bunch of urban legend.
That's hoo-ha.
That's a lot of urban legend.
That's not there.
We don't have any super cool monsters or cyclopses roaming around.
Well, we do have cyclops and cool monster skeletons that we can exhibit.
$5 a piece.
But you would say to stray off the beaten path there is to invite peril, would you not?
I mean, that's just a couple steps off the path bit by a snake.
You're dead.
No one will find you.
No, you pay extra for that.
That's the $10.
That's a 10.
$10 tour.
Yeah.
The run for your life.
Do you have to pre-book that?
Can I send my money now?
No, it's by appointment only.
Snake.
I want the snake by it.
I want the whole experience, Carrots.
Right.
Exactly.
Now, we can never do X Day here because it's too dangerous.
It can only be kind of one volunteer at a time that is taken through the gauntlet.
That's what I was getting at.
The
UNAnsettled TV?
That's a fair number.
Guys out those enjoying our define we're weekend.
It's a very expensive one.
How is it going?
Come up, X-Day, for our uninitiated listeners.
What is it that you're referring to?
Oh, actually, it's when everybody stupid is going to die horribly and everybody who's cool and smart is going to live forever and part of it.
Yeah.
It's so simple.
Correct.
In the name of J.R. Bob Dobbs, the living avatar of Slack, Saint of Sales, who founded this mighty church of the subgenius, this edifice of knowledge and wisdom and Slack upon a sandy beach of hypocrisy.
It made peace.
Just to survive, you know, the next 35 years.
Now.
Now, what about us good hearted Southern Baptist Christians that think that the this this good hearted church?
Well, Bob, this scrub genius is is is really, really just a sick ploy for for a bunch of dirty perverts to to get together on the Internet and sell drugs and child pornography in exchange for Bob.
T.
Shirts.
Well, it could be that as well.
Why not both?
There you go.
It don't.
You know, they're.
This is you got to be adaptable in this world.
Things are changing fast.
Is it?
So quick.
Cash in your Bob coin.
I too.
Are you trading?
Are you trading in Bob coins?
Oh, I blew it, man.
I had my chance.
I could have been rich in Bob coins and I blew it because I didn't even know.
I'm a millionaire.
I thought it was stupid.
It's like, oh, yeah, right.
First.
Okay.
Video video game.
Well, I'm a zillionaire in Monster Hunter.
But doesn't do me any good today.
Can't buy nothing.
There's my Ivan Stang bingo card.
Monster Hunter for I-25.
But I missed out on the Bob.
Coins, man.
That was the key.
That was like the that was like in investing.
Is that how we were really going to get off?
Is that you were going to try to get a hold of that guy?
Coins.
I actually tried to get a hold of that guy a couple of years ago because I wanted to see what I wanted to see what my Bob coin would convert to Bitcoin because Bitcoin so high now.
My club.
Maybe it's you can actually get hyper coin so you can actually cash in all your.
And fit can tell you about that.
What are the benefits of hyper coin?
Fid?
Yeah, we have e-quarters hyper hyper cube e-quarters available for sale.
And because, you know, people keep complaining about how Bitcoin is worth so much that you have to work with so many decimal places.
They're like, I got decimal places coming out of my ears over here.
You know, that's all.
That's all we get.
So we suck.
That would be a lot.
We decided to make e-quarters so that you'll you'll always be working with a whole number.
That's our guarantee.
You will always be working with a whole number when you use hyper cube e-quarters.
No more.
No more decimal places.
That's for like that's for scientists type people that believe that the earth is round.
I think I think while people think about that, we should listen to some diva.
We got DJ.
He's up here.
Well, you know, you get the schedule that we put out on the pre-production note meetings.
I'm just trying to.
He's going to go with the with the with the fun time schedule show.
Graham.
You put these nice things here.
You know, once you once you introduce the song piece.
All right, everybody.
We're going to enjoy Monster Man by Devo.
Spin the wax, Argus.
Freeze.
I, I wanted the c
Buuoc you in here.
The man's a hunter, a beast on the run
He's a virus, you can't stop with a gun
Mutant plans, but my mind is insane
Loud springs, but I also can
There is no
There's no way to hear the dogs
speak
There is no
What is in your head?
Say what you want, say what you will
Said and done, the threat is still
Off the mat, off the mat
They say beauty's in the eye
Of the beholder, so don't try
To understand him
Everything is Halloween, it's all obscene
To watch the man
It's time for the show!
The only show!
The only show that brings you more nutrition per bite
Than leading e-entertainment
It's Dr. Fox here
And that was, uh
Well, you guys can't hear it
The listeners can hear it
Nice
Sid's not back from break yet
Oh, I'm back
But, uh
Reverend Stang is here
Nice
He was on time for the show
You're a liar
Reverend Ivan Stang is not on time for the show
I wasn't making that noise
Of course not
No
Or the Devo song
I didn't do that
That wasn't my fault
Yeah, who requested Devo?
No, that was Bob
Bob asked for Devo
And while we're
Thinking Bob
Let's, uh, let's show
Uh
Stang how we're making all of our big money here
On time for the show
Let's, uh, let's read off those Patreons
Oh, man
The Patreon list
It's so extensive
First of all, we've got to give a shout out to
Uh, uh
Apostasy X Ford
APO, the well-known artist in the church
She's, uh
She's Patreon-ing us
And, uh, I actually have to
Predict her fortune
And Fid, because of the
Level, she's very high level
She's AstroTurf level
AstroTurf level
And Fid will have to read a random Bible verse
And interpret it specifically related to her
Uh, so
I'm gonna, I'm gonna have to
You can give me a second
I have to go into a trance here
I have to, I have to manifest the future
Ivan Stang will understand what I'm doing
And as will
Fid Chuli and Argus Q. Fox
As we are all indeed
Masters of time and space
We are all
We all need that
Yeah, I'm gonna project myself into the future
Okay, now I'm back
I'm back
And, uh, what I see in, uh
Fnord's future
Is within the next
Days
The Pope, Pope Francis from the Vatican
Will ask her to
Uh, commission
A portrait of him
In a kind of
Um, more Nordesque way
And this will be displayed in the
The, uh
The Vatican in the main office there
Right where the Pope sits
On the ceiling, yes, thank you
I was floundering a little bit
Thank you so much for that, like, Brian
But that's, that's my prediction
It's really not a prediction, folks
Because, like I said, it is
Her future
Fid?
Uh, yeah
I didn't set off my future
I set off my future
Fid, don't you know
I, uh, I need to
That justamente
Seems pretty
Unlikable
Help
You think
When our
End
Who
Both
Which
ife
Jason
Exactly
Flan
Ow
M
phosph
So
See
times have you read the Bible?
How many times what?
Have you read the Bible?
Oh, I've lost
count. I've read all
of the entire thing so many
times. But I know that this
is going to be about the horror of something
or the something of Babylon
one way or another.
No, it's random.
It's random. We have no way
of knowing. There's lots of parts
in the Bible.
What's your favorite part of the Bible,
Reverend Stang?
Hosea
All is vanity.
Simple as that.
That explains everything.
All is vanity.
Is that the verse?
No, that's not the one about
A.P.O. Stacey. No.
The one about her is that the horror
of Babylon shall descend down
from the clouds and spread
in the sky.
The slackedness across the
mutated until
their heads explode
and the beast with 10,000
testicles rises
from the sea to
admit that it
committed lust
in its heart
with that one other monster.
That's that New American Standard
translation.
Yeah.
New American
Dobsian.
Translation of the Bible.
That's what we need.
We need a subgenius
annotated
Bible.
Actually, you guys, there is a subgenius
who has his hands on
the ancient manuscripts
that comprise the Bible
or
should have comprised
it had they been
selected properly.
What's strange?
Dr. Onan
Kanabar is working for
some
sort of American Bible
Scientific Society
because he's a rare
book archivist. He knows how to
preserve and take care of
rare books and how to deal with them.
And there's nothing rarer
than the Dead Sea Scrolls
and the
book of James and
the book of Magdalene and all that
kind of stuff. And he gets to actually
finger those
ancient papyrus
manuscripts.
In Oklahoma City, of all places.
He is the neatest guy, too.
You can't say finger on the radio.
He's been to X Day a couple times.
So yeah, he's fingering the Bible,
the original Bible pages.
The pages written in the
blood of Jesus, god damn ya!
I'm telling you, this is where they
just took, they gathered the blood
from Jesus as he
was bleeding on the cross
and they wrote the Bible with it
and those are the pages that Onan,
has and he's scraping little bits
of the blood off so that we can
have preserved DNA
of the Lord Jesus Christ
and bring him back to life
like a Jurassic Park.
Jurassic Park? I was just going to say that. That'll be sweet.
Do you think there'll be like a G?
And here's
the other thing. We're working on
Adolf Hitler, too.
There was a subgenius
down there throttling
Adolf Hitler's neck
until blood,
spilled out of his mouth.
And who was that subgenius? It was none other than
J.R. Bob Dove!
Oh no! Not that guy!
Wouldn't it be funny if we cloned
Jesus and Hitler and the clones
became like super good friends?
They'd be like,
Hey! Adolf! Hey!
Well, here's the funny thing.
Oh! Did the Jews
do something to you, Jesus?
No, no.
It's been predicted.
It's all in subgenius doctrine.
Nenslow wrote it up.
He saw it in the vision.
Jesus
and Hitler.
Long before
the Iron Sky
producers made their movies.
Nenslow
had Jesus and Hitler
or their clones
which were the same
person, you see.
College roommates.
Who else was Hitler?
Well, he was a
than the Lord Jesus Christ.
Doesn't it all add up?
No.
Of course. It sounds absurd.
It sounds insane.
That's how you know it's true.
If it doesn't make sense.
If it doesn't make sense,
then you know it's been tampered with.
Or a little seal
has been broken.
If it doesn't,
if it doesn't make sense,
then the only reason that it can't make sense
is because it's been
tampered with
and corrupted.
So there should be like a tamper-proof
sticker on every book.
And if you break the seal,
then, you know, shit, you don't know if that book's
got good stuff in it.
Just a Mr. Yuck sticker, I think.
Mr. Yuck.
On any book. Just because books are hard.
Books are hard.
You have to like, read them.
Stay sane.
They say that we are in a digital dark age.
Hard covers, certainly.
But not soft cover paperbacks.
I'm not secure enough
in my masculinity to read
soft cover books, okay?
Reverend Stang.
Wow.
I ain't no homo, okay?
No, I think you are.
I think you are, dude.
There's nothing wrong with that.
That's fine, man.
Speaking of no homo,
uh,
we also have a shout-out for Reverend 80.
Reverend 80?
Reverend 80,
who is now a latex lover.
He's a member of,
he's a latex-level subscriber.
He is a visionary.
Indeed.
He knows everything.
That guy knows every damn thing.
And, uh,
our potassium level,
uh,
Dr. Cosmack.
Oh, Dr. Cosmack.
Has sent me a lot of music
that we'll be featuring on the show.
Right on.
So we've got that.
We've got a show.
We've got to play music on it.
No, it's funny.
These are all the kind of people
that you meet when you go to an X-Day, too.
There's all these great people
that are awesome artists
and doing crazy stuff in their own right.
And they deserve a shout-out
for supporting us
for doing what we're trying to do,
which is, uh, make radio.
Yeah, these cool people
know what we're doing.
And you know what we're doing.
You want to be cool, too?
To be cool.
And you can sign up for just $1.
If I was listening right now,
I would be like, take my...
I want to be cool.
$1 gets you algae level
with time for the show.
You get your shout-out
and you get a donor status
on the hypercom.
Only $1.
I've never heard of anybody offering
such an amazing deal for $1.
Crazy people, maybe.
Uh, but yeah.
Uh, uh...
I knew about it.
You'll get the secret show access.
With $3, you get access
to the Tap House VIP chat.
Uh, for $4,
you get access
to our high-resolution, uh,
collection of scabs.
And, uh,
of course,
our $5 AstroTurf level,
where Fit
is going to, uh,
interpret this Bible verse.
Uh, Fit, your verse was, uh...
I thought we did that.
Stang did it.
So it's a...
It's a bonus.
She got her money's worth, man.
She got...
Yeah, we're gonna circle back.
Dang bonus.
We're gonna circle back.
Rub that in.
Let them know.
Not bad for five bucks, everybody.
There you go.
Dr. Stag loves the show,
so why don't you love the show?
Come beyond the show.
And speaking of...
Speaking of Dr. Cosmack,
Reverend Stang,
guess what, buddy?
Uh, Dr. Cosmack
is, uh,
already starting the beginning works
of a subgenius video game.
All right!
Yeah, it's...
It's about time.
Is it gonna be, uh,
like on the level of Grand Theft Auto
with a huge open world
that goes on forever
in incredible detail?
I imagine the idea...
is gonna be like, uh,
press this button
and you, uh,
enter your debit card
and then you push the button
and it charges you $35
and it says you win.
And then you do that again.
Oh.
Oh, yeah!
I wonder if there's gonna be
a peas element to it.
Who gets the $35?
Uh, the app developers
are gonna have to take a,
you know, an administration fee.
Substantial cut.
Is there overhead
in research and development, boss?
Yeah.
I know, yeah.
You know, you'll get a lot
of exposure from it, though.
Uh, yeah, exposure.
That's right.
It pays off.
You've heard that before?
Come on, that's crazy talk.
You know, I thought about putting
my face on a T-shirt
and people bought it.
I've got a T-shirt
with your face on it.
You have a T-shirt
with my face on it?
Yeah.
In fact, I was wearing it yesterday.
Really?
Yeah.
And I was completely unable
to pick up any chicks at all
wearing that shirt.
I tried and tried.
You gotta wear it backwards.
And they all get my shirt
and my top.
Jesus.
You get them running
the other way
and you get a head
10 seconds on them.
It's only the hopelessly
neck-bearded
that seem to recognize
the Argus Q Fox T-shirt
for some reason.
We haven't tried it.
If only there was
an organization
for those people.
Yeah, like a church.
Yeah.
They never get adopted.
That describes me.
I've got kind of a neck beard.
Do you?
I haven't seen you
in a long time.
You're not hopelessly
neck-bearded.
I didn't shave
for the last three days.
I'm thinking more about people
whose neck
grows out so fat
that their beard
is made out of layers
of neck fat.
That's a neck beard to me.
Okay.
I can't see the difference, boss.
No, I'm the opposite.
I'm a buzzard neck.
So.
Yeah.
I'm a buzzard neck.
You usually see someone
that's in the church
of the hopelessly neck beard.
Fendora.
They call it a Fendora,
but what they're really
wearing is a triby.
They just don't know
what their hat's called.
And they're usually
complaining a lot about
the latest Star Trek
and how it wasn't
as Chewbacca should have
got a bigger park in it.
And we got it.
Actually, I should be nice
because we have a huge segment
of that population subculture
that is our fans.
And it's time for the show
here on Freethink Radio.
It's time for the show.
I'm not putting them down.
I'm letting them know
that I knew
like, so I'm identifying
with them.
Yeah, I see.
I know you're I know
your thing.
I know your thing.
Yeah.
We're total nerds.
Well, maybe not
Star Trek and Star Wars,
but Church of the Subgenius.
That's pretty nerdy.
Those are the same thing,
aren't they?
Star Trek and Star Wars
is the same thing.
Those terms are interchangeable.
Church of the Subgenius
and Star Trek
are my favorite things.
I know the most about them.
Star Trek was really good.
Star Trek is kind of,
you know,
that's like the Star Trek
is like like a Hot Wheels thing
and you would click
the track together
like little spaceships.
Bob gets me back
on Star Trek.
Oh, the show is taking
a terrible turn.
But if you're talking
viewer mail,
should we do viewer mail
while we have Stang?
I think we should do
a blind eye.
Oh, yeah.
I think we should
do the blind eye.
We have a we have a guest
on the show.
He might have a blind eye.
He wants to turn.
Well, I have
I always explain
the blind eye,
but I don't know why
I explained the blind eye
this week.
I'm up for any program.
OK, the blind eye
segment
is
why don't you explain
it to Dr. Fox?
So
each week
we all know.
Wait, let me explain it.
I want to explain it.
You guys bitched
about how I explained
it every week.
Now I said, oh,
you play.
Well, I was hoping
to throw it back to you
and it would be a funny
little joke.
But he dropped
it.
It's you can't say
explain on the radio.
Ah, that's right.
I'm sorry.
We are doing super
good, though.
This time, don't you
think, guys?
No swearing or anything.
I'm so proud of us.
Yeah.
Up until then.
So bad.
No fucking cussing.
Well, these fuckers.
There you go.
Uh huh.
So anyway, boss,
how it works is
here's the thing.
We turn a blind eye
to something.
And if during the week
between shows,
ISIS,
happens to
take out
whoever we turn
the blind eye to,
we're not going to
get upset about it.
Now, we're not saying
that ISIS should do this
or we're not telling
people to do it.
We're just saying,
hey, if it happens
this week,
we're not going to
time for this show.
People, not
everybody collectively,
maybe just the three
or four of us
will say, hey,
you guys get the blind eye.
We're not going to help
you out of that situation.
We're not going to
say anything to ISIS.
If something bad happens.
But at the end of the week,
your time's done.
And then if something
did happen,
we would all be
righteously indignant
and right.
Just right.
Righteously indigenous
like the rest of America.
Well,
like in the past,
I turned a blind eye
to Betty White
because she was kind of
saucy with me one day
in front of at bonds.
He turned a blind eye
to me.
I turned a blind eye
to Argus Figgs
because he stepped
on my heroin joke.
I stepped on your
heroin bit.
Yeah, my heroin bit.
Your heroin bit.
Well, if I really
stepped on it,
you stepped on it so hard.
It was barely even
a heroin joke.
I'd like to
because you stepped
on it so much.
I'd like to turn
my blind eye
to people
who start sentences
with the word.
So when they're
explaining something
to you and you can
tell they're like
getting off on a little
bit too much because
it makes them feel smart.
You know, you say
something like,
Oh, gee, I wonder
why this is the case.
Like, so the reason
that that is the
situation is,
you know, blah, blah,
blah.
So prefix.
So implies that
everybody else is wrong.
Hold on a second.
Let me sink that.
Let me have that
sink in for a second.
Yeah, I know.
I went with a different
one.
OK, look, I went
with a different one
that I said I was
going to do.
OK, but I just
still couldn't pull it
off.
Hey, you guys
didn't send me a script.
I'm just.
It's not a script.
It's like notes.
It's just suggestions.
It's just, you know,
lines.
The guidelines are
not so much rules
as they're, you know.
Anyway, so we're
not anyway.
Anyway, Fed.
So we've got
we've got we've got
like a notepad
like in the other
room.
It's professional
radio people.
We get together
tonight.
20 minutes before
the show and think
of stupid things
while we,
you know, put
stupid things into
our stupid loans.
Yeah.
What it turns out
is we work for
two hours on a
radio show to
come up with one
funny joke to tweet.
The whole two hours
is the production
meeting for the one.
Yeah, this isn't a
show.
This is a production.
This is a two hour
live production.
The blind eye.
That's what we're
doing.
It's the blind eye.
You're giving a blind
eye, Fed, to
everybody who's
so those guys,
right?
That's your blind
eye word with the
sentence.
So too much.
And they're smug
about it.
Those people
blind eye to you.
Have fun, ISIS.
Go nuts.
We're not telling you
to, but if something
bad happens to those
people, we're
we're not going to
get we're not going
to raise a stink.
ISIS, if you
independently decide
to do something to
those people, I
just hope that you
eat the hell out of
that hamburger.
Yeah.
All right.
Look away.
We'll blind
blind eye.
See, we're we're
we're all loosey
goosey here.
OK.
Loose is right.
So, yeah, I may
need to get to the
toilet pretty soon
myself.
Is that your
viewer mail?
Is that your viewer
mail?
Who's it from?
But when we do
viewer mail,
I need to.
And it turns out
it's a viewer mail.
It's you were just
serious.
You were just making
that you had to.
Yeah.
OK, I see.
OK, I'm following.
I'm going with
look, Argus.
I'm it's 1103
Eastern Standard
Time.
You're listening to
free.
Free.
Radio.
It's time for
the show.
The opinions
expressed on the
show are all
directly reflect
the views of
the Reverend
Ivan Stang,
who is our
guest tonight,
who, if you don't
know, is a
professional post
office employee
and the president
of the Dick Van
Dyke Dyke
Fan Club.
That's right.
Anything said
on this show
perfectly reflects
my personal
views.
Of course it does.
Do you know what else
reflects the total
character of the show?
It's Caravan Palace
by Rocket Toomey.
It's the other way
around.
Well, you got to
put it down, right?
I'm looking at the
notes here.
Here's Rocket Toomey
by Caravan Palace.
It's trying to do
something.
Free thing.
Time for the show
is brought to you
by Magnavox.
Makers of the
Baddest
Movie.
Oh,
my gosh.
Oh, my gosh.
I have some
erotic fan fiction
I can send you.
I have to go back
to my banking
and arms sales
programming.
All right.
Well, great
having you on.
Okay.
Yeah.
Thank you,
Reverend Stang
for making it
on time for the show.
If I can just
figure out how
to turn it off.
Usually the guests
stay for the
entire show,
but, you know,
that's your
celebrity.
I know.
Okay.
Dave Chappelle
stayed extra
and we had to do
he stated,
but that's okay.
We're fine.
We're fine with
the
Hey, give us
give us a shout
out on an hour
of slack.
It's your
pop in the
website dot com.
Yeah, man.
Which
what was that
dot com
time for
the website
dot com
because we're
time for the
show.
So our website's
time for the
website.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
I'm
time for the
website dot
com.
Oh, I
didn't have
the last one.
And it's
time for the
Twitter dot
com.
No, you can
reach us.
You can reach
us at sub
geniuses
dot com.
Actually, if
you go to
sub geniuses
dot com,
that will
take you to
time for the
show.
Really?
I'm really
yes.
You not.
We failed you.
I hear the
typing.
No, nothing
happened.
You lied.
I'm
buying it
right now.
I am on
GoDaddy
right now.
You probably
spelled subgenius
is wrong.
He probably
did.
Can't be
true.
Dr.
Fox,
this is
the
dot com
work.
Yeah, it
does.
Oh, it went to
Hypercube
Laboratory.
Oh, I see.
You'll be
hearing from
my lawyers,
Reverend
Fox.
Yes.
So there you go.
You can shout us
out on the hour
of slack.
Yeah, just
if we're really
easy to find
W. W. W.
W.
W. W.
Oh, oh my god.
That's
sickening.
Well, if you
if you look at
the past couple
of messages
I might have
left you on
Facebook
it looks
like when you
refer people
to subgenius
dot com
the number
one
website
for subgenius
related materials
and stuff
um
that your
phone might
be auto
correcting
it to
subgenus
or genus
dot com.
Yeah, I've noticed that.
And so I tried to buy that one,
but they want like $10,000.
Oh, God.
Subgenus.
Oh, Jesus.
But as soon as I get that one,
we're going to sweep you out.
Oh, there really is a timeforthewebsite.com.
We did all of this for you.
I can't figure it out.
You're on it right now.
We're live streaming on time for the website.
Timeforthewebsite.com.
It's just more Hypercube.
Just don't drill into it too much.
That's a Hypercube.
A Hypercube doesn't end in the third dimension.
It's just more Hypercube.
You're on it right now.
It sounds horrible.
It's time for the Time Warp.
It's time for the Time Warp?
It doesn't end in the third dimension.
It doesn't end in the third dimension?
It's just more Hypercube.
More Hypercube.
It just loops.
It loops.
You're on it right now.
It's time for the show.
I got a bill.
Her plane just got in early.
I got to take off.
Pease has to go murder people.
Pease, you have to apologize.
I've got to go there and cut the airport,
cut Black Pease.
I'm going to be at the airport before he is.
God damn it.
Darn it.
Gosh darn it.
Dude, we were doing so good.
All right.
It's great doing time for the show with you, Ivan Stang.
I'm sorry that previously my booking schedule is so heavy
with all the dilemma and crises that we have to fight down here
at Freethink Radio.
We just don't know where we get all the time to do it.
But it's wonderful to have you.
I hope to have you back very soon.
It's horrible.
Horrible.
I'm going away now.
If I can find a way to sign off.
You better go.
You better go pick up carrots before I get there, buddy.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
We can.
I forget the last time.
Maybe it was Legume.
He was stuck in.
So maybe Stang will not be able to sign out.
We'll just keep him on until the end of the show.
So just carry your connection with you wherever you go.
And Bob is here.
Bob is here, Reverend Stang.
Yeah, Bob just came into the room.
Say hi, Bob.
Hi, Bob.
Bob.
Hello.
That's Bob.
Oh, that Bob.
That Bob.
The good one.
But Bob's here.
And Bob is joining us on the second half of the time for sure tonight.
Because Reverend Pease has to go prevent the next 9-11.
I don't know.
He's headed to the airport.
Hey, 9-11.
9-11 was an honest mistake.
Okay.
It was an honest mistake.
And he figured it out.
And he's out.
But Pease is still floating.
Pease and Stang.
Finally.
All it took for me to say 9-11 was an honest mistake to get Stang out of here.
That timing.
The show, The Hour of Slack.
If you need more...
Information.
Please.
See Subjeetius.com on the internet.
That.