Ready? One, two, ready, go!
Thank you.
Like to drop by the testy pad
Well, welcome to the hour of slack
Praise Bob Gold and Connie Drag
Yes, welcome to the hour of slack
Look what you get. You get the non-stick crab basket.
You get a package of elastic chicken cakes.
And one more thing, folks.
Of course you're going to get pot.
Please return it to us.
My house smells inside.
My favorite thing is that the food comes out.
My husband hates chicken.
So I made the chicken the other night.
And he's like, chicken, chicken.
I really appreciate the fat on the meat.
Another thing that's really nice, you can have a cocktail.
My favorite thing.
Is the fact that it's my family.
You salmon is too dry, a little too soggy.
And the family kept saying,
The boss, the boss.
I like the oven.
I came home and made my husband chicken.
Such a wonderful shock.
We just love that machine.
The machine surprised me.
In the woods, it's fabulous.
I love the electricity.
Call now and order the all-purpose chicken video
and an instructional non-stick platform.
Order right now.
And you'll also get 30 gloves worth $250.
And you'll also get the $30 dual chicken ties
for only 400 easy payments of only $19.99 plus SNH.
Or send $99.99, $99.95 plus SNH to Beverly Hills, California.
Hurrah!
As soon as you're born, they make you feel small.
By giving you no time instead of it all.
Till the pain is so big you feel nothing at all.
A working class hero is something to be.
They hurt you at home and they hit you at school.
They hate you if you're clever and they despise a fool.
Till you're so fucking crazy you can't follow their rules.
A working class hero is something to be.
When they tortured and scared you for 20 odd years.
Then they expect you to pick a career.
When you can't really function, you're so full of fear.
A working class hero is something to be.
Keep you doped with religion and sex and TV.
And you think you're so clever and classless and free.
But you're still fucking peasants as far as I can see.
A working class hero is something to be.
There's room at the top, they are telling you still.
But first you must learn how to smile as you kill.
If you want to be like the folks on the hill.
A working class hero is something to be.
If you want to be a hero, well just follow me.
I am a subgenius and by that virtue I am in touch with forces greater than men
I dare you to kill me, I am not a dupe of the conspiracy, I know more than they do
I am a subgenius, that's all I need to be, fuck, I'm one of the good guys, I shall prevail
Let out the crazy man inside you, he knows what's what, smile when you call me a fanatic
Me primate, me overman, I say to the pigs, give me your money, you won't need it
The future offers you nothing but destruction
Unlike this 500 pound mouse that is inside of you, Jesus spoke of it when he said, here kitty, kitty, kitty, kitty
The United Nations would betray the purpose of its founding
Members of Congress of both political parties agree that the United Nations Security Council is a threat to peace
We agree that horrible poisons
And diseases
And gases
And atomic weapons
Since we all agree on this goal
The issue is
How best can we achieve it?
What I can't understand is why no one has seen them until now
Many Americans have raised legitimate questions
If they follow the usual pattern of their species, the nest may contain from several hundreds to several thousands
The head of more than 30,000 anthrax
Had likely produced
Two to four times that amount
If we know dangerous weapons
Does it make more dangerous weapons?
This is capable of killing at least 20 people
We produce thousands of tons of sarin nerve gas
These actions killed or injured at least 20 people
More than six people died in the attacks
And surveillance weapons
Every chemical and biological weapon of the war
The Kalas and entire以
Tur eyebrow
We have
Watch all the farce
ego
And of course, all that might be required are a small container in the United States to deliver it.
Now you're talking, talking like a man.
And that is including 12 Americans, killing an American passenger.
We know that Iraq and the United States of America go back a decade.
We know that Iraq and the United States have had high-level contacts.
These include chemical and biological attacks.
We've learned in bomb-making and poisons.
And we know that after deadly gases, we've gleefully celebrated the instruments of mass death and destruction.
May God...
Just the one he got to hit in that bottle.
And an era of new hope will begin.
The right stuff.
Gentlemen, as good, loyal Americans, I think we should take it over that the secrets of Jed Clampett's awesome experiments will never leave this room.
Yeah!
White House.
We've got this!
It's begun.
I can't look.
Oh, look, he's got, like, clothespins on his nipples.
The top of his head is shaven.
Let's just shut the hatch.
Oh, my God.
Now he wants to get in.
He's banging on the window.
No, we should just shut the hatch.
The joke's over, you know?
We just need to get out of here now.
What's that smell?
Yeah.
I don't think we...
If one of those kraut gunners get him, he's a goner.
I believe we should...
Stopped firing on the beach now because it's quiet here.
And the second batch are droning over now.
I can see them.
They're casting off the gliders as they circle around over the beach.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
That was ESO Radio.
Thanks to WCSB and Clave Moment's Professor Chaz Smith,
Lonesome Cowboy Dave, Princess Wiardo,
and your surely Reverend Ivan Stang.
We've also been hearing lots and lots of lemur.
That's right, cut-ups by Fernanda Nde Limor,
the great graphic artist of alt.binary slack,
and now the great class cut-up of our of slack.
Slack, good slack.
And speaking of slack, friends,
I was poking around on the Internet
looking at alt.binary sounds MP3 full CDs,
and I found this Brazilian band.
It had a cool name.
Ligia Urbana.
And it was doing, most of their stuff was in Portuguese,
but they were doing this one song in English
that I was familiar with.
And I downloaded it and listened to it,
and it's, friends, it falls into the category of
inadvertent bulldada.
In this case, tell me if you don't think this is
Jim Morrison beats Billy Idol.
FRANCIS
Yeah, this is just different music,
Well, it's kinda good for that.
That's good, isn't it?
That's some Pop Rock.
I like Verona dirt .
house
Lore pem
Pem
War pem
Love pem
Sister
Drugs
declare the vote
and voting on
the Mystery Girl
of the Week contest
closed and opened
the envelope.
Mystery Girl of the Week
this week goes to
North Korea
who dumped
that one.
I love the way
they dumped the news.
They like were
in a meeting
and they just sort of
looked at the Americans
and said,
of course we have
the fucking bomb,
you moron.
I think pretty much,
I think Zimbabwe's
got the bomb.
I think,
I think
Upper Mongolia
or whatever it's called,
yeah,
Outer Mongolia
might have the bomb too.
I think we've reached
the level that they
talked about.
The Tagalog Islands.
Yes.
Pongo, Pongo.
Timor has a
200 new key.
So what are you
going to do about that?
You're just going to
go plowing every place,
waving the bombs
and hoping they don't
bomb everything back?
It's kind of silly.
Well, you've got to
deliver the bomb.
I mean,
you can't just
have a bomb.
Right.
You've got to have
one of those mailers
You just have
a bomb.
You just have a bomb
and you detonate it
then you blow yourself up.
Yeah.
You have to deliver it
somehow.
Yeah, you have to make
it go somewhere else
to, you know,
whoever, whatever
you don't like
and then have it
blow up there.
And you need one
of those mailing systems
too because
I did download
a tactical nuke
video
that was amazing.
It was shot
with like a
like about a
50 or 60 foot
long cannon.
Really?
Yeah, a big recoil
thing.
One of those
track.
Yeah, they're like
back a little.
Yeah, those tubes
they use now.
The thing shot
and then about
two seconds later
the mountain range
way off in the distance
just went white
and then
the
worship
the gods of war
and then
where there once
was a mountain
Stand at the stone feet
of the red god of war.
This was just
punched with a cannon
into the hill, you know.
They call them tubes now.
There's a lot of
baby acrimony
going around
in the svelte world.
They're probably
letting a lot of
these type videos out
so that, you know.
I've also noticed
a lot of stories
that kind of talk about
how cool it is
that when America
goes to war
it goes to war
packing everything
and they start talking
about how
that some of the things
being ordered for the war
and being packed was
well, a sumo wrestler's
suit was one of them.
That's not much of a suit.
A sumo wrestler's
suit was going along
with the rest of
the guy's gear?
Yeah.
Well, jeez,
they're going to have
some entertainment there.
They call it sumo wrestler
for the news purposes
but what they really mean
is the extra costume
for the sumo wrestler.
He's a superhero.
Oh, and the belt
that he's wearing
actually that goes up
his crotch
actually propels him
over Baghdad
and drops him asunder
like some mighty sack
of flat.
All that mutant stuff.
All those movies
with Spider-Man
all these mutant power guys
and so forth
that are coming into vogue now.
Real big budget,
exciting, well done
comic book movies.
It's all based on
But the gist of the stories
are generally that
nobody goes to war
like the U.S. does.
Nobody takes as much
stuff with them.
Sheesh.
It's kind of self-facing
not self-
but you know
too overconfident.
Pretty arrogant really.
Yeah, arrogant.
That's the word.
I knew it started with an A.
They can sort of
control space.
Every blade of grass
dang.
They want to control
every blade of grass
and every molecule
on the planet.
They have
good surveillance.
That was scary
watching Dave do that one.
I'm not going to look
over there anymore.
I missed it.
I'm not looking over there.
I'm looking at
I'm going to go look at
porn on the internet
or something.
I don't want to see that again.
I could see Donald Rumsfeld
as a superhero.
Couldn't you?
Like wearing a sumo belt,
bare chested,
bare legged,
like maybe with long
like lawyer socks on.
And the power belt
between his legs
propelling him
through space.
They said he was
afraid of birds.
But wasn't he
some sort of
Pleistocene bird?
Pleistocene bird.
Bird himself?
I'm so tired.
Wasn't that beak
made for chopping
lamb chops?
Wasn't that nozzle
made for eating
human flesh?
Donald Rumsfeld.
Don't look under
your television set.
He's back.
How about
Dick Cheney?
The grandson
of Lon Chaney.
Please no.
No.
He is actually
a man of a thousand
billion dollar faces.
The man of a million
petrodollars.
Tonight in your theater.
Don't come if you've
got a heart condition
or wear sunglasses
past twelve.
Don't come if your
knees are too
to your pants.
Shepard Nazi
the engine.
I don't know what happened.
I don't know.
The Senate.
The Senate will come to order.
The chaplain will leave
the Senate in prayer.
Gracious God,
you have made grief.
As a Senate family,
we thank you for our dear
friends on timely deaths.
We are grateful for Saul
and Sheila Wellstone's
courageous deaths.
His indefatigable commitment
to help the debt of our society.
We praise you for grief
for all people, particularly police,
police officers,
those who serve to make
the Senate run smoothly.
Dear God, you have enriched
all of our lives so generously
through their untimely deaths.
Heal our grief over
maintenance personnel
and fill us with your
untimely deaths.
Amen.
The Senate prayer delivered by Fernanda Nende-Lee Murr.
So that's a sign of oppression
from the Ubermans that are keeping us down
with their ragged bags and feet.
These tagged raggedy old baggity faggity feet
smelling us.
My pups are barking, boy.
My pups is dead.
I'm a smelly friend.
You know what I mean.
Yeah, you gotta feed them.
You gotta feed those puppies.
I've just been so whooped and beaten down
by the conspiracy, I just gave up.
You know what they like, Stan?
They like when you trim your toenails,
you grind them up, you put them in a little bit
of hot sauce and you drip them back
on your self-same toes.
That's appreciation for you.
Recycling.
Yes, it's a form of internal sacrosanctivity.
Sacrosanctivity.
You know, you make yourself holier than you thou
or something every day.
At least I do.
I gave up on that, on thou, holiness and than.
Well, making yourself holier.
I just gave up.
I can see it.
Give up!
Holy and holy.
Loudspeakers spoke up and said.
It is holy and holy.
Holy and holy.
To think of the-
Christianity is stupid.
Isn't it about the-
Communism is stupid.
Communism is good.
Do you have a copy of that we could play real loud?
Common sense is stupid.
The very idea of offing yourself because of some stupid little problem like that makes
me think, well, what is a problem that's worthy of killing yourself?
So what I want you to do is imagine that you're in the car with the windshield wipers going.
It reminded me when I was a child.
And you're listening to this religious show on the radio.
Okay.
And you're wondering to yourself, who are these guys?
Gotcha.
Okay, I'm there.
I'm driving.
I'm beginning to visualize now.
Oh, what?
Don't take your eyes off the road, though.
And now I can see it.
I can see it.
I can begin to see the beginning.
The beginnings of it.
It was an old military junkyard full of trash.
Tranks and tucks and such.
Tranks and tucks and some.
Yeah, that's the kind of stuff we used to listen to on the radio back in the old days,
driving around Texas.
I understand that Texas is about the size of Iraq.
Really?
Yeah.
Is that true?
So when they say, go in and see if you can find some nukes.
My test would be, well, let's go see if we can hide a suitcase full of nukes in Texas somewhere and say, now go see if you can find it.
We only have the whole state of Texas to do it in.
You know, I think that.
That would work.
You could build an invisibility chamber if you had to and put it into the.
Hide it in Texas?
And hide it in Texas.
You could put it up by Amarillo next to Cadillac Ranch and then.
I'd take it out to the.
They just wouldn't see it.
To the Texas Triangle, which is kind of like a different version of the Bermuda Triangle, but on land in Texas.
And I would just put it out in the middle and it would disappear.
Wow.
Until.
That's like the playa out there.
I needed to find it.
That was, dear friends, puzzling evidence.
Dr. Philodrum and Dr. Howland, the Howland, a funny Dr. Howland, KPFA in Berkeley.
This genius, more than an hour, less than a show type show.
The show that dare not speak its name.
And now.
The past year resembles nothing so much as the bad alternate timeline that the hero of a cheap science fiction book or has to go back and fix.
It certainly resembles that to me.
And you, the listener, are that time traveler.
Yes, you, humble listener.
If only your memory could be restored to you.
You are the humble time traveler.
I know what you mean, though.
It does.
Yeah, that would explain a lot.
It would explain the wooden-headed people coming up to us while we're taking our sulfur baths.
It would certainly explain all the money that's now going to be flowing into arms.
And legs.
And think of how fully well laundered that money it is.
It must be very squeaky clean by now.
Just think about George the bushy-haired one himself and counting that money back in some room.
He's got to replace those behind the oval orifice.
That's not what we're talking about.
This is all about revenge. That's it.
Taking over Mars.
Yes, eventually to take back Mars.
Take over Mars. To take Mars back.
Our rightful home that we, the true Martians, were expelled from.
So that they, the oil sheiks and the oil billionaires and all the oily characters would have some...
So we're living in the Martian time slip?
Oh, I can grok to that.
In this time continuum?
I can grok to that, my water brother, but by the same token, when do we...
We were enslaved.
We've got to go back in time and kill Bob's mom.
The psychic shackles still at their feet.
After Bob was born.
Enslaved thousands and millions and bazillions of years ago.
Does this mean that there's a big bin with all the money we want near the front of our house and we can pick it up and just...
It doesn't mean anything like that.
No, man.
It just means that we were kidnapped from our home world and we're stuck here.
With you...
Twerps.
Yeah, you guys.
You just...
You guys.
Ha!
It's a space junkie cowboy just looking for a fight.
His mama's calling.
Son is dear.
He says, mama I'll be alright.
I'm fighting all the Yankees.
The sons of JFK.
The Cubans and the Mafia said man, he'll be okay.
But the cowboy in his space gun and his bitch is...
He's got to save the day
Defeat the force of evil with his worst name
SPICE BRAIN!
Well, the space junkie cowboy, he will not be denied
There's pot roasts on the table, many villains roast outside
He's fighting all the criminals who stopped him sitting low
The whiteys came from Europe to kill you, no they wouldn't
But the cowboy and his space gun have got to save the day
Defeat the force of evil with his worst name
SPICE BRAIN!
Well, the space junkie cowboy, he does not give a damn
His mama says, come on in boys, his mama's got a plan
I'm gonna fight the men in white sheets who come from the Kloot Klutz clan
They're fixing to kill a black man who grows by the name of Sam
But the cowboy and his space gun have got to save the day
Defeat the force of evil with his NITRO
SPICE BRAIN!
Well, the space junkie cowboy, he will not be coerced
His mama says, come on in sir, this is where my lab been cursed
I'm set to fight a bad man who's killing all the Jews
Making mincemeat of his continent, gotta stop him for a while
But the cowboy and his space gun have got to save the day
Defeat the force of evil with his worst name
SPICE BRAIN!
Space junkie cowboy
by Drexel
yes, that's a D-R-E-X-E-L
Drexel, from Drexel, Ohio
That's the album name is
uh, and they are at this website
www dot
Drexelent dot com
That's B-R-E-X-E-L-L-E-N-T.
And now back to, well, some Lemur-ish cut-up collages,
puzzling evidences, howling over men,
lonesome cowboys, and Chaz right here.
Well, we were through the looking glass with David Ferry and Nico.
One, two, three, four.
That's good. There we go, George.
You're looking good on camera.
Yeah, don't worry about it.
Your hair looks fine.
Boss, you want to make sure his hand stays up in the wave gesture for a long time.
We've got to go off over here.
It looks like there's about 45 of them ready.
Mr. President, 30 seconds.
Do you want to take some of the shine off the big guy's nose?
I can't get back in there again.
It smells like shit.
Commies keep talking like that.
I'll be throwing some food over the concentration camp fence to you.
How's that?
Right after the bad days, Tank.
Come on in and take a bath.
Hey, look at this special emollient they put in the bath water.
It makes you feel so good.
You don't want to think about things.
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
Knee pads truly make a world of difference.
Yep, yep.
More proof that makes knee pads possible.
Call now to order the two-piece ratchet knee pads or clamp set.
737-338-1318.
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Then, of course, there was the time when...
We're recording down there.
...they tried to fit the baseball bat in my corner.
I think you can't use that either now.
And then...
MK Ultra.
Hey, he knows about the mind control experiments.
What did they do to you?
Oh, he signed off because he's scared.
He was silent.
He was scared.
They stopped him.
Well, they stopped him mentally a long time ago in the past.
See, that's what he doesn't understand.
It was also a time control experiment, much like the Church of the Subgenius is.
And therefore...
The stars will be.
You're right.
Yeah.
That's one of the ipso-hipso's of the time biz.
But this guy wasn't hip to that fact, I think,
as he danced jolly-ly-ly-ly down there in this lane.
Well, I don't know that he was hip.
You know, if you...
He might have been.
The problem with the great conspiracy revealers...
How come they're not dead yet?
You mean like Michael Moore?
Oh, not...
But no, no.
He didn't...
Because he's not revealing...
He's not revealing great conspiracies.
I'm talking about the really great conspiracy.
Well, maybe they've lost their twang or their old epizoodle.
Why haven't the conspiracy silenced them?
Well, the silence is probably something arranged by the conspiracy.
No.
Beforehand, it's like the time control experiments.
Think of it that way, if you can.
Huh?
For example, you know, people look at an elephant and it just looks so enormous.
But...
Or someone told me earlier, you know, you eat a...
Or given enough time, they can.
Can an ant eat an elephant?
Uh, precisely.
Uh...
By eight properties, I don't think you could.
It'd be impossible.
For example...
You folks all are now unsophisticated barbarians.
And breaking news out of Bethlehem right now,
Israeli forces leaving a trail of sludge to prevent gunmen from seeking refuge in the explosive device at a checkpoint late this afternoon.
This in retaliation for a Palestinian church in Jerusalem.
The passenger apparently grabbed the sludge, killing 11 people.
Cleanup boats menace the coastline, causing an environmental hazard.
Tom Daschle and other wannabes are creating security threats to his family.
Hard Car correspondent David Schuster has the story.
The question is, has Tom Daschle gone too far, or is Tom Daschle a sore loser?
This program is known for asking you to call him.
With his majority gone and his party floundering, Tom Daschle handling defeat poorly.
But definitely...
Democrats routinely unpatriotic and un-American.
Tom Daschle shrill, nasty, and dangerous in Washington.
Foment hatred, the very essence of anger that we love.
Goodbye, Fernanda Nende.
Lee Moore.
I often want to say to a couple,
I put him down for my pizda, and then she shrieked,
We're hungry for you.
Guy back off.
Guy blown away.
Guy.
Guy in the cracks with mouths full of my cheese.
Bah, my cheese.
Bah, blown away.
As husbands and wives come together, bah creates a glow within you.
We really lost our minds and I needed to do something else.
I was struck recently by Hull and their seeking cheese, and they don't get it.
Oh, you mean that kind of bone crushing time.
That kind of bone crushing.
Guy died unexpectedly in an automobile accident this weekend.
and they don't get it.
They are normal.
Bob threatened to be ripped asunder by God.
And Jesus has been in a series of unsatisfying relationships with men
and invites him into a relationship with Bob.
And they bury the dog in the food.
But I can't say that.
And they don't get it.
Slut.
And I'm the devil.
Welcome to hell.
I am Satan.
I'll be your hostess for eternity.
You've got to be fucking kidding me.
Slut.
Heart ignition.
And now, Lemur.
Lemur.
We believe
in any inflation.
In any inflationary set of pressures that might emerge
and any negative effects
that we put in place.
Similarly, the reason
for this chronic and growing
gross P in the United States
continuously rising
or rising as much.
That means that
our short P induces P
in the United States.
And that's been going on
to prevent this from continuing.
Bob.
I have argued
that the best we can do
is to judge for decades.
Either way.
I'm having a heart attack.
Can't be the same
until I get my baby back.
She's gone and left me brokenhearted.
Came to stay but now we've parted.
Like a transcontinental island.
Burning and floating across the seven seas.
Causing the cost of formation of delicate bacteria.
Cuted in a mustard keg.
Her lemon made a beautiful sunset.
She's gone and left me.
What shall I do?
She got back to her residence
on Sunset Boulevard
where the residue of her love
is dying through.
I got bit and stoned
by a Ned fly.
Went swelled up into a baby.
And floated away up into outer space.
Like a Jules Verne hot air balloon.
Jacob Bartley took a dollax
and fled his tiny gym
with all his little friends.
Visiting from Scarsdale.
That's why I'm having
a heart attack.
Can't be the same
until I get my baby back.
She's gone and left me brokenhearted.
Came to stay but now we've parted.
Like a transcontinental island.
Burning and floating across the seven seas.
Causing the cost of formation of delicate bacteria.
Cuted in a mustard keg.
Her lemon made a beautiful sunset.
She's gone and left me.
What shall I do?
She got back to her residence
on Sunset Boulevard.
With a residue of her love
is dying through.
I got bit and stoned
by a Ned fly.
Went swelled up into a baby.
And floated away up into outer space.
Like a Jules Verne hot air balloon.
Jacob Bartley took a dollax
and fled his tiny gym.
With all his little friends.
Visiting from Scarsdale.
That's why I'm having
a heart attack.
Can't be the same
till I get my baby back.
She's gone and left me brokenhearted.
Came to stay but now we've parted.
I'm having a heart attack.
Zug's Riff, dear friends.
This is coming off of a 30th anniversary
two CD-R set
that has 175 Zug's Riff songs
from 1971 to 2001.
The great, great Zug's Riff
can be reached by you
if you have a pencil ready.
Um, at, got that pencil ready?
Now?
Zug's Riff at,
thank you Fine Lying Brothers,
at, at, subgenius heaven.
He boarded the saucers prematurely,
friends, long ago, yet long after
this show was assembled in 2002.
For this is a rerun of number 11,
number 868, a war show.
It was a different war, but hey,
many things never change.
I had to resort to a rerun
because I had to nurse my injured dog, Buddy,
who was in a war
with other dogs.
A civil war.
And now this.
This is the voice of London.
Yes, my young padlock.
Somebody's parked a bus in my butt.
Well, there's an explosive device in there.
We're talking about a code yellow.
You are not using the force,
my young padlock.
We are a code yellow right now, you guys.
I'll have you know that.
Code yellow in what?
In the air.
In Portuguese, which is
gauta jaurda.
These are not the drugs you're looking for.
No, we are at code yellow right now.
The force is not with us, you silly arses.
Come on, man.
First place cops looked was at that.
I've fallen and I can't get up.
Just lay there.
She's lying.
What are you going to say,
pack the car near Havignyad or something?
I mean, come on, boys.
Let's stop this inane game here.
Let's nail the hammer on the head.
The president is trying to...
Canadian?
Oh, yeah, right.
Okay.
Trying to attack Canada.
I can't do the president,
the prime minister of Canada.
I can't do Jean Quatien.
I can't do his voice.
And we are tired of what they are saying.
South of the border,
we have the right as a nation.
How many people showed up on the mall in D.C.
to protest the war that you didn't hear about in the news?
Bob was there.
Bob was?
Somebody sent me a picture.
A picture of Bob standing there with a couple of kids
with their faces fuzzed out in the photograph
because the kids didn't want to get caught.
Oh, wow, yeah.
But there was...
Bob often shows up at protests
and, in fact, has even been filmed by CNN and the like.
But in this case,
a friend of one of the kids
saw Bob, photographed him,
sent it in, got a rim job,
and that was the...
some totality of Bob's involvement in the...
This is more appropriate than anything.
Is this part of the success seminar thing
that he's doing down there now, or...?
No, he works for the CIA sometimes.
He was just taking notes.
So the success seminar is just like a pizza front
for the... for Black Ops, for the CIA?
No, that's Church of the Subgenius.
Is the pizza front for...?
More or less, yeah.
Okay, but, okay, which is the core of the Black Ops?
Is it the CIA or the church?
The church, the Austin office that's the church.
The Austin office or the church?
Those guys are nuts.
They get $10 for every address.
For every address?
So they can actually come around and say,
we know where you live, right?
Well, see, the thing is now,
because of the new law,
they can just get it off the internet for free.
Your computer is part of the internet,
my computer is,
and if you touch your computer,
your brain is part of the internet.
We know what you say and what you do.
And it's all recorded.
Every bit of it is on the internet.
Google.com,
which will soon be called bigbrother.com
or something like that.
But it's all going to be one big website.
I'll be able to look up your thoughts.
You'll be able to look up my thoughts.
It's a beautiful thing.
It's, well, in some ways,
it, the evildoers can no longer hide their evil,
but by the same token, you know,
it all just evens out.
There's just such a flood of endless information
about everybody's inner thoughts
that finally it just becomes a sort of a slurry,
a blank mush because it's just overload.
It's just a white static.
And when you see the sign that says,
our back is maxed free,
you'll know that you're going to finally get some work done around here.
And look at those smokestacks crackling.
Everybody gets to toggle in, man.
Yeah, when it started going down this week,
I started to,
I started sweeping up my leaves in the yard.
Did you?
That's all that's left to do.
They love shoes and,
they love shoes and pajamas.
God has gone before to,
to, to, to, to,
I'm persuaded.
God, hallelujah.
What we are engaged in is essentially a struggle for communication.
The corporate industrial complex is a heavily under-
armed fortress dictating the baloney propaganda
we are fed daily via multimedia channels.
We hear only what they want us to hear.
So long as the man prevents the message from reaching the masses,
justice is impeded.
The Unabomber used terrorism to gain publicity as an end in itself.
Notice how the press seeks to channel the public's interpretation
of the Unabomber, covering it as a serial killer story of crime and insanity,
while deliberately excluding consideration of the ideas themselves.
Imagine, if you will, mass communications not subject to corporate control.
Why, people might say anything, even things not fit to print.
Exactly.
When the ABC nightly news gets renamed Disney World,
you'll cherish the memory of your Unabomber vote.
Don't waste your vote, friends.
Unabomber in 1996.
Whoa!
And, uh, yes, that was from www.paranoia.com,
which is a fun little website.
Uh, what else?
According to my records, I've sent you 33 pages of information
plus a postcard.
Most of what I sent you proves beyond a shadow of a doubt
that much of what you've sent me is crap.
Only a person like you, with your almost total lack of...
You've be quickly
Hey, everybody!
I think it's complicated.
We can put a fool in things of this order.
Gotcha!
Watch this, people!
Lots of people venture, breast into things,
all of the pieces In a plane, boil down.
Let everybody say
Six of urgency
Like the play that they've got in May
It's only little until the last card is played
Six of one, half a dozen
Of the under-replieds of the bench
The bench is a fucker
A monster moving forward
You want to crack a heart
One monster take over
One monster pop
Play the emergency
Six of urgency
Back to the start
To the drawing board
Shake them out of business
Swing them by the side
Hop on to the bandwagon
When it's last to go
Everybody's going
Destination's at home
Well, I don't know
So don't ask me
We'll follow in each other
Like they went to the sea
Six of urgency
Six of emergency
Wow!
Without me
¶¶
himself and dishonored
the platoon.
I'm trying to help him.
I have failed.
I have failed because you
have not helped me.
You people
have not given Private Pyle
the whole of Asia.
From now on,
when your Private Pyle
fucks up, I will not
punish him.
I will punish all of you.
And the way I see it, ladies,
you owe me for one
jelly donut.
Now get on your faces.
So you get the abstract meaning of the ladies
owing them a jelly donut.
You know there have been problems with the church,
and of course there have been many problems with the armies
amongst these very stern DIs
who like to take it up
all the way up, all the way up
to the top of Jack Hill.
Well, you know, my kids are going to be learning
this stuff. For you know what,
the softer soldiers
that aren't going to make it through boot,
you know, they have to make regular
trip shit to the John.
And, well,
with one swell foop, we
laid one on our military.
We hope our brave boys out there
don't feel compelled to
jump in the shack with the first drill instructor
that she...
You know, that would be...
We hope that they carry a picture of W
in their breast pocket.
And they carry an orangutan's
breast on the top of their feet.
Because most of them won't come out.
The road goes on forever
and the party never ends.
I think that's true.
Finally the fans put
And made it work.
at sixrews ningún
con
dos
e
I did read a story that there are drone planes already flying the southern parts of Iraq, destroying anything they see.
That's what they're selling.
They've already started that.
They've been doing that for ten years, haven't they?
Have you seen the army commercials?
Well, they unleashed like a fresh batch of them, like just go terrorize everything.
Have you seen the new Air Force commercial where the kid is out with his little plane?
Hey, what is drone a euphemism for?
What?
Are they really sending out little drone robots?
Or are they dressing up little drone men as drone robots?
It's the chimpanzee clone syndrome and those crazy right-wing evangelicals behind it.
They're just drone planes.
They're unmanned planes that just fly around looking for targets.
But have you guys seriously seen those spots, those Air Force commercials that show the kid flying his little robot plane?
And then in the last scene, he's like moving one of those joysticks and you see one of those random shots over Iraq.
Really?
Oh, yeah.
This is for real.
Oh.
Yep.
Wow.
They're selling the remote robot clone planes pretty good nowadays.
Gosh, with the sun setting on our show soon.
And the sun setting on the American empire.
Or shitting them.
No, no, no.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't know.
With Anna Nicole's new show, I think we have a chance.
Well, and now that rim jobs have come back into popularity.
Really?
With Anna Nicole.
Although I, frankly, to me, I think that that's just really weird.
Specific rim jobs?
Well, there's a big, there's a...
Man, that's pretty wild.
Specific rim jobs.
Let me put it this way.
That's pretty twisted.
You can use your butt.
You can use your butt for sitting or you can use it for shitting.
And I say there is one H of a difference between sitting and shitting.
Till next week.
Keep your head on tight.
Back in the wind.
Keep your eyes focused.
Upon your solar plexus.
As the electromagnetic waves go by.
Bye-bye.
You are listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
Brought to you by the Church of the Subgenius.
You can look us up on the internet at www.subgenius.com.
You can find us on Twitter at www.subgenius.com.
Email me, stag, at subgenius.com.
Or write to us at post office box 807-GLENROSE-TEXAS-76043.
Praise the Lord.