Who dwells in here?
Who lives here?
And how long have they been here?
You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to...
The Self Genius Hour of Sight.
Hustle here and hustle there.
New York City is the place where they said,
Hey man, go take a walk on the wild side.
I said, hey Joe, go take a walk on the wild side.
Ah, honey.
Yes, dear friends, well we're back.
Yes, we're back from Cleveland where we did a show with Lonesome Cowboy Dave and Chaz Smith and Michelle and all of that hideous crew at...
ESO Radio in lovely WCSB FM in Cleveland.
And it was an ugly, ugly night.
But we survived and we bring you the skeletons, the remnants of that ugly night.
The 81 Wild House.
Hello.
Hello. My name is Chaz.
And we are Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
And that's what you were just listening to was Einstein's Secret Orchestra performing for you.
That was last week's show.
Let's put last week's show away and create a whole new show just for you.
I think we should put this guy over here on the turntable where he belongs.
And start here.
Oh, I didn't want to do that.
Okay, there he is.
Break dancing.
Now by the time you get this communique, it'll be too late.
The pigs are outside the door.
What I want to know is who speaks for Earth.
Hey, here's Moansome Cowboy Dave.
Michelle down in the other studio on that box there of hers.
I'm sitting here with a keyboard.
And Dave's got his guitar.
And Lisa Lisa is over there.
And the Reverend Ivan Stein.
Standing right behind me.
And that's a dangerous proposition, boys and girls.
Praise God.
Princess Lisa.
The KY Jelly is ready to go.
And everyone is standing around in line.
Look, they fell for it again.
They're back again.
Told you they'd do it.
And they always fall for it every time.
Always will again and again.
Thought you could get away, did you?
Look at it.
He doesn't even remember, does he?
No, no, no.
Just let him guess.
We'll just let him drift in and out of realities for a while.
Who speaks for Earth?
Who sells for Earth?
And who is the one who sells for Earth?
Who will buy Earth?
Here's one for Mother.
You are about to discover a part of yourself that you have never dared dream might exist.
This show will be a personal experience between you and the man with the pipe.
You are about to rip open a yawning chasm in what you thought was your personality.
You will stand on the brink of a hole deep within yourself.
A pit, a pit, a stinky pit, and then the very deepest, blackest part of the pit that is your mind.
You will discover a secret.
Bob.
Bob?
But first let's step back out into the real world.
The real world.
Now that you have achieved, Transstate, come with us.
Come and travel in the astral plains as we seek.
That which is dark.
But first you must pull loose from your own body.
Yes, it's easy.
Just a little tug.
Close your eyes.
Float upward and give your soul a little tug.
You see?
You're free, you're free.
You never thought you're so.
Your soul a little tug.
You never thought it would be so easy, did you?
Then let's go upwards.
Let's float.
Upwards.
To get perspective.
Higher.
Towards heaven.
But we'll stop here in space first.
Just past the Earth's atmosphere.
You see?
We can go anywhere instantly this way.
And it's...
It all was so easy.
Right within humanity's grasp all along.
And you know the secret.
Really.
You can go anywhere.
Let's try something new.
Ça n'est pas à la fois
Boutiqueball
mon
Patrie
et
sans
des
Crés unserer
Oh, it's beautiful down here.
We could just float along and watch the fish.
Or...
I can plunge you into this trench
in the middle of this blistering hell planet
and send it to you to sit in chains in this ditch forever.
Just waiting, waiting
until the ticks come again.
Yes, just waiting.
The giant ticks.
Here they come again.
Press a shooting.
Don't look.
They may look.
Keep shooting.
Shoot another one in another hour
and you'll never kill them all.
Keep shooting.
Just keep shooting
or they'll get you.
See, just like your job.
Back at home, ain't it, boy?
Yep.
You just can't get away.
You can't get away from them...
them ticks, my friends.
So join them.
The father's never answered one of my prayers.
I've made obeisance.
Well, you've paid obeisance, Dave,
but did you pay money?
Actual cash, green and gravel.
Think about it, boys.
Don't wait till everyone in your neighborhood's got the bomb.
Nuke them.
Now at Hiroshima Schwartz's Miniature Nuclear Weapons Warehouse.
Hi, friends.
I'm Hiroshima Schwartz of Hiroshima Schwartz's Miniature Nuclear Weapons Warehouse,
home of the Mini-Mag, the Pocket Thunder,
the baby neutrino that leaves their apartments intact,
and many other fine, low-range, low-rad nukes.
These teeny-tiny warheads actually fit in your wallet, purse, or pocketbook.
And what's on special this week at Hiroshima Schwartz?
It's the giant X-Day Drill Sale.
Now until the wee-wee hours of July 6, 1996.
We are literally giving away tons and tons of useless and useful weapons.
It's the Werner Von Braumeister Party Special
that blows away 50 party pinks at a time, leaving the party intact.
Disguised as a four-gallon keg, that first draft really packs a wallop.
But for paid subgenius, it's the Smart Prairie Squid Face Seeking Special.
I'm sorry, I always get that wrong.
It reads your mind and literally knows where to send the warby.
Finally, now until X-Day, bloodier than any golf pro,
it's the exploding head of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
When the pipe lights, it's armed.
When launched, it zaps up to 100.
That's 100 useless bobbies at a time.
Friends, don't wait till it's too late.
Everyone will soon have the bomb.
Nuke them now.
From now till X-Day and beyond,
we are literally blowing up the competition.
Hiroshima Schwartz's X-Day End of the World Sale.
Tell them Bob sent you and received 23% off.
Batteries not included.
Some assembly required.
You know, I've been eating alien shmigma pie for almost 50 years
since those first shawster crashes near Roswell.
My sons growed up on it. His sons too.
Here in Wilberville, it's as natural as pie.
But many folks don't know about alien shmigma pie.
Things kind of changed since we landed on the moon.
Some things we didn't even know.
Some folks believe in things called gray.
Can't sell it.
Gramps!
Gramps, Jillian.
Did you bid my fall back to events.
Please.
from alien genitalia.
It's made me sexually active again.
And it tastes great.
That's all I know.
Building a new race in this life is hard.
And nothing gets it as hard
as alien smegma pie.
Alien smegma pie.
The taste that's out of this world.
Bob loves me.
And I love Bob.
He hates you.
I love Bob.
And Bob loves me.
No, he hates you, Dave.
He hates you.
Bob hates you.
J.R. Bob Dobbs has answered
all of my questions.
He even told me
go and fling myself down the stairs.
I did it on a lark,
but now I'm glad.
Bob loves me.
And I love Bob.
He hates you.
You may love Bob,
but Bob hates you, Dave.
He makes you fling yourself down the stairs for fun.
Oh, I love Bob.
And Bob loves me.
We're sweet and slimy
just like little bricks on a tree.
And tick, tick, tick, tick, tick.
He calls me on Valentine's Day.
And I'm sending flowers and chocolate.
And he loves me anyway.
I'm sending...
Bob loves me.
And I love Bob.
He hates you, Dave.
What could be more pure?
It's the purest form of love anyone could imagine.
He answers all my letters.
He calls me up and leaves messages on my phone.
He's always with me.
The computer does all of that, Dave.
And I love Bob.
Don't be a sucker.
I may mess it up for you.
I'm sensible.
I'm modes.
my answer is whether you like me or the computer.
I can't help myself since you looked at meet you.
Maybe in Cosmody.
My answer is this.
You even send me tutte les lettuces,
peaches and frits.
To the police afore буßt với dich.
Whoa.
He turns up.
しか nichts.
Oh, my love.
Stop talking.
You don't want to.
This is what Bob meant when he said,
pull the wool over your own eyes.
I can't see anything.
Oh, I'm going blind.
I'm going blind.
But you can still see Bob in your mind's eye, can't you, Dave?
My mind.
You never stop seeing Bob in your mind's eye.
I can't stop.
Such as it is.
My mind?
What there is of it.
What?
Your mind.
Your mind is no longer your friend.
I'm a physical person.
I'm in love.
I'm in lust.
I'm in love with Bob, and I don't care what you say.
I love Bob, and Bob loves me.
Bob does love a fool.
That's true.
Bob loves the fools of this world,
and truly the king of fools is Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
now performing the greatest guitar solo in the universe.
Bob's
Rock out, baby.
Play it, Dave.
I don't hear the music, but don't make me go.
What do you mean, which one?
I thought that was all these strings.
And you see, friends, you'll see how the love of Bob has freed Dave from the ponderous
real life around him.
He pays no attention to what other people might think of him.
Sure, they think he's a fool, but he's not.
They think he's a fool, an idiot, a bad person, a half-janger.
But he's happy.
You can hear the simple happiness in his voice.
He's a form of expression.
I can't express how happy I was when I think about it.
Oh, don't think about it.
You won't be so happy if you stop and think about it.
Now, will you, Dave?
Why are my pants all wet?
What's wrong with me?
And how come I can't even breathe?
Why can't I close my mouth or open my eyes?
And why doesn't Bob ever call a writer, answer my letters, or move anything on my message
machine?
You're not losing your faith now, are you, Dave?
That would be a great sin, a grievous sin indeed.
To lose one's faith.
To lose one's faith in Bob.
I have no faith in Bob.
Bob has no faith.
He has no faith, meaning he only has a head.
He cannot have a head.
He cannot have a face and a head.
To the world's little God, John has had two faces on his head.
Neither one of them were looking at the same thing at the same time.
And Bob can see you out of each one of those dots on his face, like multifaceted eyes of
the mighty insect.
The mightiest insect.
Boing, boing, boing, what's happening to my brain?
The mightiest insect is the Dobson fly.
It's growing from its little tiny peel.
Like, hmm, into a magnificent, magnificent brain.
Yes, the sucking bugs of the amazing Northern Ohio area include, among the order Hemptera,
I said the order Hemptera.
The sucking bugs, the bugs who suck things through pipes, such as the water scorpion
and the rantrofusca.
The giant water bug. Did you ever see that movie, The Giant Water Bug?
That was great. The Giant Water Boatman was the sequel.
These are lovely and interesting insects of the Northern Ohio swamp areas.
But, aside from the pleasant, happy-go-lucky order Hemp Terra,
one also finds the order Neuroptera, which includes, in the sinister family Cory Dolly Day,
Do you hear the significance of that? Cory Dolly Day?
Like Salvador Dolly Day?
We find a creature, yes, a living, actual bug of the Northern Ohio swamp areas, called the Dobson Fly.
The Dobson Fly?
The Dobson Fly, which is a...
You know what?
You can go see a stuffed, mounted example of this hideous, vicious beast in the Cleveland Natural History Museum.
The Dobson Fly, while surrounded by lovely butterflies and not-too-alien-looking dragonflies,
you'll notice that the Dobson Fly has the head of a vicious red ant with hideous, clicking mandibles,
and the body, a body that resembles the tail of a rattlesnake.
Horrible, flapping, leathery wings.
Yes, the Dobson Fly.
This is not some biological freak that we're making up.
I'm afraid there are thousands of Dobson Fly larvae.
Now, they are in their season, their 50-year season.
As evolution lied, is evolution alive?
It was in the 40s.
In the 1940s was the last time the Dobson Fly cycle reached its peak.
And thousands died as these pincher-like beaks of billions of Dobson Flies attacked the suburbs of Cleveland.
Oh, the days of Velikovsky.
I thought it was Wassily Kandusky.
And every time you swatted a Dobson Fly, a million eggs would squirt out of its ruptured abdomen.
Each egg hatching into another million Dobson Flies.
And each time you tried to squash one of those, it would hatch another million.
Evolution has no plan.
You see, friends, man likes to think himself the grandest thing in all of God's great creation.
But indeed, no, it is the great order of the insectorii.
The great brain of all collective insect hives and tribes
is a billion times smarter than any single insect.
It has an ego-centered human brain.
Certainly, one Dobson Fly or one tick may possess a rudimentary brain,
but they can communicate by radio with each other.
And the millions of each species each forms a great brain of that species.
And those brains get together to form brains.
And let's face it, you're outsmarted, Mr. Earth Boy, Mr. Human, Mr. Two-Legged,
Mr. Two-Using Prime.
Mr. Thinks-He-Saw, Big-Time Smarty Pants.
But you know, if you took that human back into the early Devonian period,
even here in the lovely Northern Ohio area,
you would find that there was no Devo.
No Devo?
No Devo.
But because there was a slimy ocean covering the Northern Ohio plains,
a filthy, sewer-like, shallow plain.
But murky, muddy, disgusting, smelly ocean.
And in the depths of these foul, murky puddles,
there grew such creatures as the Dunkleosteus.
Yes, the Dunkleosteus.
And friends, I hate to tell you this, but there is a...
It's true that there was an ancient plant discovered, fossil of this plant,
and they named it...
Yes, the Clevelandodendron Ohioensis.
4411-O-E-S.
No, seriously, the Clevelandendor...
Clevelandendodron Ohioensis.
That was merely, however, just a tube-like plant with teeth and thousands of eyes.
From Club Moss.
Einstein's secret...
Yeah, I mean, Club Moss was a great place back then.
I saw Devo at Club Moss.
Yeah.
In the Devonian period.
Einstein's secret orchestra.
ESO Radio, boys and girls.
Ivan Stang...
in the house.
Now, as usual, speaking of the all themes of the insect kingdom,
we notice that through these over-exaggerated sense of smell,
that they also keep, in a form of ESP, extrasensory contact with each and every other member of their community.
And as we notice here, if I expose one of these insects to this molasses,
all of the rest of the insects will begin to come within the air,
even if they have been exposed, or have been held in this container,
and are incapable of actually smelling the molasses.
As soon as they're released, they all begin exploding,
because some of them have distillate charges in the back of the vacuum in.
Some of them have even approached 300 feet in length,
and some of them are already dead.
And some of them are well over 2,000 pounds.
And I see them in my dreams.
I keep on thinking that one of them was with Harry that night when they went over the edge.
Worship.
And confess to me.
In this small, dark room.
I take my corpse.
Back.
Back up.
The white zone is for immediate loading.
These phobias can be conquered.
No, but the most insects were there the night Harry went over the edge.
Oh, Jesus.
And how can we surmise that from this incident,
the head of J.R. Bob Dobbs did emerge into the lustrous as a numinous being?
I don't know, but you can find out by coming to the X-Day Drill in Brushwood, New York,
on July 5th through 7th this year and every year from now till X-Day.
That's right, Ivan, that's right.
I'll give you a call for free information about the amazing X-Day Drill.
Yes, it's like the legendary Doc Stock.
That's right, Ivan, that's right.
Oh, you'll see the most hanged preachers of the subgenius church.
You'll camp out on a lovely, fully developed campground surrounded by abandoned geeks.
You'd rather not ever spend much time with them.
But by God, you'll know more about the subgenius,
because, friends, you will have practice for that fatal day, that glorious day, X-Day.
Yes, only two years from now, in 1998, the sex goddesses,
from Planet X, shall come in their space vessels
and rupture up the news paying fully Dobbs-approved subgenius ministers.
That's right, Ivan.
All 4,000 of us, and destroy the rest of the planet.
Well, not destroy it, but turn it back into the stinking swamp that it was before the filthy humans came along and muddied everything up.
But, friends, you can come along and muddy everything up.
You can wallow in the filth.
You can dance all night.
Oh, whoa.
You can pull your clothes off and county law doesn't care,
because we are having the first X-Day drill this July 5th through 7th.
Sunday, Sunday.
Sunday!
You'll see the pill.
You'll see the bleeding head of Arnold Palmer.
It lives, it bleeds for you if you don't vomit your money back.
Friends, you will see things you wouldn't dare believe,
things you never wanted to believe,
and things you'll wish you'd never had.
Things you never saw.
That's right, Ivan.
Yetis will be copulating in the bushes.
Oh, dude.
The Loch Ness Monster will rise up from the little pond.
The crazed pagan drummers will drum all night long and keep you from sleeping.
Mosquitoes the size of dogs and flies will devour you, but you won't care.
You won't care because you spent your money and came to the X-Day drill July 5th through 7th in Brushwood, New York.
Brushwood, New York.
Only in Brushwood, New York.
Only three hours from Cleveland.
And friends, you can call for information.
216-556-0338.
I'll give that number again.
Write that number down.
It's the free information divival hotline at the Church of the Subgenius here in Cleveland.
556-0338.
That's 556-0338.
What do those numbers add up to?
Aha!
Now you know the secret.
Now you know what we're really trying to tell you.
The froth.
Yes, the froth.
There's no interest in buckets of froth.
Back tubs full of froth.
Three months tired.
That's right, I've had a froth.
An ancient Babylonian ocean full of froth.
Well, gee.
Ancient Tibetan herbs growing right up under your feet.
You won't be able to sleep.
There'll be so much froth growing at high speed underneath your sleeping bag tossing you around.
It's like a giant funhouse.
Yes, it's insane.
It's crazy.
But ain't it always been the crazy?
Crazy people that were able to party like they knew how?
Yes, sir, e-bomb.
Yes, sir, ma'am.
Sir, lady.
You will finally learn what it's like to be a subgenius.
That's right.
I've been staying in the Church of the Subgenius since...
Oh, did I say that?
Well, then pick up on it, man.
Hmm.
Oh, my God.
I wish I could make it to the top, like I always do.
It says at the end of the world, she'll come in a great flash.
I sure hope so.
Some people might go and the other ones might last.
Will you be the one who goes?
Well, you'll be on next day, brother.
Where is your where will you be on x-day brother?
Will you be on x-day brother?
Will you be in the sauce with me?
There's still lots of room
Or will you be down in the room?
You can have anything you want
Will you be burning?
Excessive
Empty sink
Will it be perfect pleasure?
Perfect pain
Which will it be?
It's up to you to choose
Bob gives you free will
But you can't feel anything
Until you sign on the dotted line
And x-day is coming so
You better move fast because
Where will you be on x-day?
I got plenty of time
To spend my thirty dollars on that Bob ministership
I got plenty of time else
Two more years for x-day
Why am I in any kind of hurry?
There couldn't possibly have been
Some kind of a misprint
In the book of the subgenius
I mean just because that first edition
From McGraw-Hill actually did say
That x-day was on July 5th 1996
Well they changed it after that
I'm sure that I mean it looked like a mistake
Probably was a mistake
I don't think I really have to spend
That thirty dollars quite yet
Because that probably was just
It's probably not that the world's gonna end
In this year 1996
Probably not I could probably afford to take that risk
I mean I've got that thirty dollars
That's not the problem
But there's this Hootie and the Blowfish
CD I wanted to get
And well you know I wanted to go to this movie
About waterspouts and
Well I just I just
You know I mean Bob will wait on me
I mean Bob's a patient man
He ain't a wrathful God now is he?
I heard Bob will love the subgeniuses
Even if they never spend any money
A patient man? A patient man?
Man he ain't no patient
Bob is the doctor
He ain't no patient man
Bob is the surgeon who will excise
The filthy rotting tumor that is America
That is modern America today
Yes my fellow rebellious citizens
And untaxed payers
And militia members
All the citizens of courts
We must come to get them quick
They're coming they're trying to stop me from speaking
All of us religious nuts
And crazy right wing maniacs
We must band together against the man
Because oh wait they're coming
I've got to get my message out
The last true hope is
5560338
Call 55603
Here they come no no
I'm gonna tell you how it's gonna be
Ba ba ba ba ba
I won't give you long to me
Ho ba ho ba ba
You'll love the lamb more than one day
Mini mini mini mini mini bow
I'm gonna tell them not that I won't
Boo ba ba boo ba ba boo ba ba
I won't tell them not that I won't
Mini mini bob mini ba ba boo
Hey!
Huh!
Ah!
Hey!
Got a cobra snake for a necktie
Got me a church by the roadside
Made out of rattlesnake hide
Bob is gonna ask you who do you love
Oh my god!
I'm gonna tell you who do you love
Oh I tried to win you but you dropped me
But
You love me
Got me around
To hell
Oh I need more
Such ropes
Just how I fell
Ha ha!
Hey!
Ohhhhh
Thud
Ah!
Wooah!
I love you.
I fade away.
Bob's love faded like one glistening dewdrop.
It's gone, man.
He hates you. He hates you, man.
Give it up. Give it up.
He don't love you, man. Bob never loved you in your whole life, man.
He don't care one
about you, dude.
You got to get it right, Brumper.
Your head screwed on the wrong man.
Bob don't love you. Hates you, man.
You understand the meaning of the word? Hates.
Ask yourself, are you worthy?
Are you really even
worthy of his hate?
To me? Am I worthy?
Of Bob's hate?
Of course I'm worthy of Bob's hate.
Everybody hates me. I'm one of the most hated
men ever to walk the earth.
There's no reason why I dare
Bob Dobbs, the old hate-meister,
wouldn't want to give me a few stabs at the old
Pogues and Eyeball.
I'm afraid you flatter yourself, Dave.
Oh, man. It's a form of love, dude.
You know, like, he beats you up
because he loves you. It's like a heavy thing.
You know, it's like a tough love.
You know what I mean?
What's so close to that?
But you know, Dobbs did love Dave.
And there have always been days.
Yes, for thousands,
millions, and millions of years,
there have been days.
Lonesome cowboy days.
Generally ignored
by science for obvious reasons.
But,
this month only in Cleveland
Natural History Museum, there is
in fact a display.
A rather large
exhibit called
Cleveland Before Bob.
In which one may
actually see fossils of the ancient
peoples. The precursors
to the modern Dave.
The Dave that we unfortunately
know now. There have
been, for instance, there's
quite a wonderful set of
artifacts that were raised up
from the P-Dog site.
There, that prove that
even the early Dave-onians
were tool using.
Not quite at the level of
primates.
They had an unusual,
there were an unusually
large number of stone
pot shards.
As well as, oddly enough,
many pot sherds
found at this dig.
Obviously pots
were used,
overused, probably.
Abused.
Yes, the abused pots. They were
broken all over the place.
Old clothes. However,
we do know that the ancient Dave's
had a sex life of some
kind. As we can see,
I see in this, a fairly
well honed
fluted
point.
Carved from stone.
And notice here, the wooden
fore shaft.
Of the ancient Dave
people.
Contained quite a wide
groove.
So you can take that wooden fore shaft.
The ancient Dave, them old Dave
men, the old Dave men
could take. They had a wooden fore shaft
with such a wide groove.
And the fluted point of it.
Nowadays, modern Dave,
it's not even made of wood.
It's just limp, like an old
wash rag. You've still got the fluted
point. But, you know,
it ain't nearly as sharp
as they used to be. Because the
ancient, strangely enough, the Neander Dave's
actually had a larger
cranial capacity than the
modern homo
Davean.
And so, the
Neander Dave,
the ancient Dave men,
were able to build nothing but
crude,
crude
pipes.
There are thousands of varieties
of pipes, shattered
pipes found in the ancient
settlement.
In which they smoked what, as far
as we can tell, wild
plant materials, including
dogwood. The bark
of the dogwood.
Which was quite strong,
quite a bit stronger than the bite of the dogwood.
Although it did have a good bite.
If he made you a dog stick,
dogwood stick, rolled you up,
run up some dogwood,
that does have a bite to it. Has a hell of a
bite to it. Man, brain too big
today. Smoke them dogwood.
Ow!
However, the ancient Dave
men had a natural enemy.
The mammothus primigenius.
Oh my god, here they come.
Or primigenius, or
which is Greek for primitive
subgenius. Ironically,
far more intelligent than the modern
subgenius. I want to play on the old record.
Proved by the fact that you're listening to this
show at all right now.
Want to smoke all the props?
Ah, here they come.
Unfortunately,
the largest display in the museum
showing the Dave men
is the items of unknown
function. Carefully
carved and intricately
decorated bone and ivory
fragments, which
the uses of which have yet
to be discovered. They seem to be senseless,
randomly created
perhaps some
scientists suspect they
may have been used to dislodge
unwanted objects from
obscure body parts.
The early Dave
men possessed more
orifices than the modern Dave
and made copious use of them.
And also thyroid wax
collector, also under
pineal nostril, also beneath
both follicles of the ear.
Ah, ah, ah, oh,
wow, wow.
In these ancient holographic films,
you can see the olden time Dave,
the primitive Dave,
chanting in their silly rituals,
yes, even then,
man had religion.
The Dave's buried their dead.
Infant Dave's fetus skeletons
have been found,
which showed signs
of having been ritually slaughtered
of a man.
The ancient Dave's
encouraged by their parents
for the delicacy,
the one item of diet that we know
that the ancient Dave men enjoyed
was fetus nads.
Don't quite know how to put that,
but certainly a serious delicacy.
Those things would go for
14.95 an ounce at least nowadays,
you know, down at the...
I want to show you...
Down at the Piggly Wiggly,
you can't hardly get fetus nads.
But the ancient Dave men were able
Time, time now.
Time to go out and harvest.
Harvest?
What was it we were harvesting?
This was during the dawn of agriculture.
And these ancient Dave men
were in fact what we call skull farmers.
Ah, there they are.
300 of them.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Just waiting to be glopped.
The women stay in the campground,
mating with the men from rival tribes
as the Daves were out in the fields
harvesting the skulls and the heads.
They tried to grow heads,
but generally they were so...
such badly skilled farmers
that they were able to only grow skulls
or else they'd forget to pluck their heads
until they had become skulls.
Ah, it's white. It is gleaming.
It is ready to lop.
And now what do we do afterwards?
We drink, we drink.
We carve out the skull and we drink.
And boy, these are big skulls
because we have such big brains.
But more to drink.
In a vain attempt to gain the intelligence
of the mighty mammoth,
the Dave would drink the brains of the mammoth.
To gain the courage of the mighty...
uh...
uh... cow.
And its craftiness and speed.
The ancient Dave men would drink the brains of the cows
or rather suck them up through crude stone pipes.
Now remember, son, when you drink cow,
you're imbued with all power of cow.
Strength, beauty, sleep, fast, quick, small, tiny, little...
Ah, shut up.
This is what is known as sympathetic magic.
Obviously, today in today's modern world,
we know better than to fall for simple, simple magic.
But there are superstitions.
I drank that genius's urine just for a taste of brilliance.
That's true.
There is the one exception.
Sympathetic magic does still work in the church of the subgenius.
If you will but drink of the fluids of Bob,
you will gain the wisdom of Bob.
His... his great intellectual acuity will be yours.
And you all know how smart Bob is.
He's from the church of the sub-gum guys at subgenius.
They're like old geniuses or something, right?
Isn't that what they're trying to say or something?
And Bob's a smart guy.
And so if you kill Bob and drink of him,
and eat of his body, then you'll be as smart...
Nay! Nay, it's a lie, friends.
Because Bob...
Bob is not smart nor intelligent, but only lucky.
So you don't drink of his brain.
You drink of his other fluids until you have gained some of his luck.
Drink his spinal fluids for good luck.
Wear it on your head.
His armpits sweat.
Wear his armpits sweat on fat.
If you can stand in front of Bob when he sneezes,
you will be able to gain the viruses of Bob.
His milk is his most precious.
Oh, yes, his milk and fluid.
If you clean up Bob's bathroom after he has finished in there,
and I think you know what I mean, Bob.
Hey, I just came to clean up.
No, no, I wouldn't want to do anything like that.
Just trying to fix the plumbing.
You will gain his sales acumen.
I will own the plumbing business around the rest of the world.
I will control the plumbing enterprise of the planet.
It's true, folks.
You, too, can be just like the modern Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
This paragon of manhood and manly beauty.
This confident and stalwart stud and cool guy.
All you have to do is to know Dave is to know Bob.
And to know Bob, you merely must call the secret number.
Yes, this is a secret.
Don't tell anybody.
Turn your radio down.
Get your pencil out.
Call this number, 5560338.
Go ahead, kids.
Give it a try.
What if you got to lose a little time, maybe?
You did sign the application.
Kids, don't forget to get your special Bob Dom's decoder ring
that explodes in your face for only $49.95.
Call now.
You don't need these for murky state.
To send me my proposal...
I told my daughter I would
It rocked me, I thought that I was like Bill Clinton.
I heard the boy dream of angels
Little darling, tell me why
I get so cold looking in your eyes
Is it you?
Baby, is it you?
I heard the boy dream of angels
My little baby
leaving this leather place
Leather and weight
take a minute to find out
Is it you?
Baby, is it you?
I heard the boy dream of angels
Is it you?
Cause you controlling me
I'm a little darling
Show me now
Somewhere, somewhere, somehow
Is it you?
Oh, baby, is it you?
I hope I dream of an angel
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Who speaks for earth?
Who smells for earth?
Who flies in the face of authority for earth?
Why is none of it in the river?
And I was staying with the church in the sub-games
Who's paying the rent on earth?
That's the question.
Who's gonna take care of this bill?
Who's paying?
It's crammed by the pretty piggy.
Well, who will stand for earth?
I don't know. Maybe me.
Maybe you.
Maybe nobody.
Oh, right.
Is that your dog?
That's really the same song.
No, uh, really, down at the Cleveland, uh,
Natural History Museum,
have you been down there lately, Dave?
I had a dream I went there.
No, no, I mean, did you know that they actually have
the jawbone of a yeti who had the jawbone of the yeti your proud city that's worth a lot of money
jawbone of a yeti a gigantic a giant they call it gigantopithecus which is of course a scientifically
inaccurate name it should be referred to as gigantanthropus it's more a primitive man than
just merely some animal gigantopithecus he's a mission and an animal an animalistic thing but
this is yes indeed the jawbone of an ancient yeti and how could you know such a thing well it says
so right there on the display is your jawbone of a ancient giant yeti yes and then it does it is
about a foot and a half long looks like it weighs about seven or eight pounds at least you lie like
dirt it's no i don't it's a it is there's a a skeleton of a gorilla not far away it's conceivable
with the skeleton even with its massive lower mandible it is merely but less than
half the size of the gigantanthropus the prehistoric yeti we call it prehistoric of
course the yetis were keeping uh records long uh 80 million years before humans uh knew how to pick
their noses well i had a dream of a yeti and it was a gigantic because it broke his mizanthropic
erectus and she was cute too well she was awful hairy she was the hairiest woman i ever saw
but she was big wasn't she yes and there was
something so fragrant about the muskies
get a whiff of that yeti
are you man enough for the she yeti are you man enough for one of her legs are you
you could ride on that leg boy you could grab you a
tight hold on that man she's got growing down that leg and ride i've tried to ride her in my dreams
i've tried to ride her off into the sunset singing my yahoo final dernier song but it seems to me
every time i begin to mount the lovely young whatever you might mean it's late i shouldn't
have asked her her name in the back room voice she said wanda wanda wanda the she yeti oh my god
she yeti
you are wanda of the jungle
wanda of the himalayas i took a walk around in the park she held my hand she crushed my wrist
i ran up running she caught me just like that man it ain't no fun when a woman can outrun you and
tackle you at the same time there was laying on the ground in central park and birds twittering
around and screaming in pain and this huge huge female yeti is she trying to have her way with me
wanda does dallas deep wanda wanda does dallas deep wanda wanda does dallas deep wanda wanda does dallas deep wanda
does deep behind the TS
real wonder behind one this green behind one like school girl beautiful yeah man if you did you see
the latest issue of yeti big yeti i think it was big yeti september by yeah i'm saying man there
was this predator i couldn't believe in fact it was one of the largest magazines i ever bought
we had to get a guy who had well he had a volvo wagon and we loaded up three or four of them and
it took half an hour just to get them in the back oh yeah the fold out in the middle is like 30
yards long yeah we just got a wallpaper that mansion over on the top of the hill there with
oh mr repercussions head lips oh those human stroke books might show some pink but you won't
be seeing no pink in big yetis no magazine it is kind of expensive they're like 8.95 it's specialty
material and if you've seen that yeti
binaries on the on the news on the internet you can get you some boy there's some pictures out
there it takes about 30 days to download
they're so big
big big yeti
harry
because the the true women of the yeti race
all of them pick on harry
and powerful
and they could pick on harry
men up by our parts and swing us around their heads and we loved it oh it hurt yes it hurt but
we loved it because we they were disciplining us you see we had discipline in those days the big
women the bigger and hairy women taught us discipline and we thanked them for it yes we
got down on our knees and we worshiped them we were polite to a woman in those days and i
language didn't like this
we exploited a woman who can do with respect for the woman
this is a big boy
when we when we
when we decimated
a race of gigantic yetis we did it out of respect
and discipline
we did it on time
not like these slackers of today
yes
the five day slackers
the old days the racking yeti women
on time always on time
the blood runs thin
they have urine in their blood
they're not like the yeti of yesteryear the yester yeti
but boy they can make a pickle when they put under the armpit
no i'm sorry i remember that sometimes from the yeti woman you could take a
whole cucumber and slap one in the each armpit and make a pickle in five
seconds
and you too can get a whip off of one of them pickles
if you come to the X-Day Drill, July 5th through 7th in Brushwood, New York.
That's Sherman, New York.
That's right.
You'll find out all about that when you call that phone number.
Call that important phone number.
Who speaks for Earth?
You can find out at 216-556-0338.
Praise Jesus.
And there ain't no Chinese fire drill, is there, Reverend Andy Stanton?
Oh, hey, did you know that Jesus is now working for the Church of the Sub-Gene?
I had heard that he was not only on the payroll,
but that also that he was having eye surgery from some crooked Medicare program he was running.
Well, this goes along with the job.
We'd like to look after our employees, but it's true.
The Lord Jesus Christ, who is now about 26 years old in this incarnation.
26 to 52, somewhere in that range.
Formerly the owner of the now-defunct Flying Lemur bookstore.
But Jesus is now, has moved to Dallas.
Jesus just left Chicago and has moved to Dallas.
And he's filling the, he's taking over the mail order of the Church of the Sub-Genius, friends.
He's the promotion, he's he who was foretold by Bob.
They said he would come wearing one sandal.
And he would buy a chariot from the Eritreans.
And they would cheat him.
And he would be screwed.
And yet it is.
Yes, it is as the prophecy said, friends.
Praise Bob.
We were saved.
The smart money guy finally showed up.
And this time he's got connections.
You know what I mean?
He's got family, if you know what I mean.
Yeah, the Church of the Sub-Genius has got some new friends.
The kind of friends that's got some muscle.
You know, the kind of friends that if you cross Bob the wrong way, you may just wake up and say,
God will have wanted this ball and this ball.
Do you have interest in the booby –
When I tell you that I'm addicted toesian energy –
You know you just get obsessed with LISA JUNG.
That handles youriah hole, that helps the power of your mind.
Be still.
Thrust her with foundation.
But he sheds. Now that it's summertime in Texas, Jesus is shedding all over the church.
I can't believe Jesus depilated all over the church of the subterra.
You mean all of his bodily hairs are laying around your area there?
Yeah, thank you. Yes, I know.