We now return control of your television set to you
until next week at this same time
when the control voice will take you to...
Bob!
From the land beyond beyond.
From the world past hope and fear.
I bid you, Bob, now appear.
Oh my gosh.
The following transcribed program is transcribed.
Friends, if you like rubbers, let's keep punching Bob till the Japs get theirs.
Tonight, as usual, Bob brings you Final Victory.
Meanwhile, don't hear Bob the greatest name in rubber.
I don't want to be no human being.
No!
Don't you call me no human being.
I ain't no human being.
Good work.
I'm a no good low down on principle crook.
We want you to know that we will interrupt this program instantly.
Bob!
This is a coordinated monthly test of the broadcast stations of your area.
Equipment that can quickly warn you during emergencies is being tested.
Bob!
If this had been an actual emergency, official messages would have followed the alert tone.
This station serves the area.
Bob!
This concludes this test of the emergency alert system.
Attention, please.
Attention, please. Attention, please. The commanding general will speak to you. Stand by.
Friends, it is imperative that you listen closely.
We're coming, but it seems they're strapped down.
Women here have been praying for God's help and guidance.
Julie's coming.
Not your kind of hypocritical praying, but the kind that comes from deep inside a man.
I'm sorry. I'll come back, Lee.
No, no, Eddie. We can't put things off till later.
Go.
We're the lucky ones.
I told you this would happen.
Now, to again emphasize our problem, most of it will be consumed,
but then, in turning completely around, every ounce will be needed to avoid crashing.
You don't know what people will do to avoid crashing.
Because in these boxes, we have placed numbered disks.
Of doom.
And so will you.
One disk.
Of doom.
I'll tell you what that mean.
Instead of d primo.
It won't событи anyone.
We'll soaked phoenix at
D bevorst Look, my nou.
That's so much lage stuff you can't put on.
Is матem永 أم ف sí irgendwo tu
It thing?
allein before date know if it works.
Bob?
Hey, the new year is coming. Hallelujah.
Well, when I was up vomiting.
Seven days a week, 24 hours a day. Amen.
Surprise, surprise.
And this ministry is love.
We love you.
A Marfa Did It Duck choice.
We like to remind the duck people to stop humping in the middle of an all-day-days choice USDA steak.
It's no time like the present.
No time.
There's no time.
Shadim Hussain, your teeth are wearing down.
Your canine incisors are those of an evil beast.
It just sounds like another plate.
Well, yes, my friends and dear prayer partners,
this hour of Slack number 1,877 is a rerun of number 877 from 2003.
And the weird thing is, once again, everything that was happening then,
almost 20 years ago, wars and fake news,
SARS and tumors from SARS, it's all repeating again now.
I'm an old man and I keep seeing everything repeat every 20 years or so.
The wars, well, they repeat every three minutes.
Wokeness.
Oh, heck, I remember correcting myself during women's lib in the 70s, for instance.
Anyway, these old shows seem so very strange.
Strangely, to resonate today, just as 1950s Dobbs prophecy is always reflected in the headlines of today,
which are all too frequently grammatically incorrect and misspelled.
Headlines with no proofreading.
Lord, my people are destroyed for lack of knowledge.
Hosea 316.
My point is, why should I stay up all night at my age editing new shows?
When the old ones from exactly 1,000 shows ago are more modern than new.
And on top of all that, we here at rural Stang Ranch have had to deal with one crisis per week,
such as wildfires over by Toler and up to Iredale.
Those came close enough to Stangville County that I actually packed my bug out bags and the cat cage
and had a big day.
I had to get them in the car ready to evacuate.
And I learned by practice there that you don't just throw the eight hard drives into a sack.
It doesn't work that way.
It was a good dress rehearsal for one apocalypse.
Then we had a different apocalypse.
The weather paranoia fear sites all telling us there was a storm coming with extreme high winds,
torrential rain, goat-sized hail, and sonic tornadoes.
And since I...
Just broken my back getting my food garden started for yet that other apocalypse,
I had to haul 16 tons of number six goat manure in pots
and batten down huge tarps over it all with tent stakes.
And then all it did was half-ass rain for one hour.
And there was the dogfight injuries to Buddy that, well,
the big ironically heart-shaped hole in his belly,
it's closing up real fast.
And it doesn't look like a heart anymore.
Buddy is okay.
And all the dogs and cats and goats and turkeys and geese and June bugs
are getting along just fine out here.
Did I mention there's a new Dollar General going up south of the river where we're near?
Man, that'll be like having a Walmart almost.
The background music is Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
Anyway, I hope this...
fills up the poorly recorded 2003 ESL radio section I'm replacing
with these exciting current events.
Praise Bob.
Okay, okay, so we got our freedom.
But management's lousing up everything.
Labor is at fault. It's ruining the country.
My constituents, as your elected representative,
I can assure you labor's right.
Management's right.
I'm strictly neutral.
Labor, management, politicians, phooey.
They can't tell corn from oats.
Work!
Drink!
Hurry, hurry, hurry, step right up, folks.
Here's the answer to your problems,
Dr. Utopia's sensational new discovery,
ism.
Ism will cure any ailment of the body politic.
It's terrific.
It's tremendous.
Once you swallow the contents of this bottle,
you'll have the bountiful benefit of higher wages,
shorter hours,
and security.
Enormous profits.
No strikes.
Remember, you're the big boss.
Government control.
No worry about votes.
Name your own salary.
Bigger crops.
Lower costs.
Why, ism even makes the weather perfect every day.
And now then, because we are introducing this amazing item
for the first time in this country,
it isn't going to cost you one cent.
All you have to do is sign this little scrap of paper,
and you're good to go.
And then you get your bottle absolutely free.
I hereby turn over to ism, Incorporated,
everything I have, including my freedom,
and the freedom of my children,
and my children's children,
in return for which said ism promises to take care of me forever.
I was there first.
I paid too much.
Get out of the way.
This is PR News from North Carolina,
offering weapons of mass destruction to most of the people
who are still in Washington.
Support for PR comes from American Dead People Foundation.
Building a dead world where dead people reject young people.
www.americandeadpeople.org
PR.
This is PR News.
UN weapons inspectors have begun examining Iraq's 12 people,
who are still without weapons of mass destruction.
Iraq submitted its opposition groups door-to-door yesterday in Venezuela.
The US and the four other pages of information on its permanent UN Security Council members
following last week's snow and ice storm on its weapons program.
From Chicago, PR Radio, opposition groups report.
Anti-government forces say they have failed to report to some unqualified leftist president,
and could cause a plot to overthrow him.
It's unclear whether the United States will support this move,
or whether the United States is crude.
Maracas.
NPR's President Bush reporting from the Iraqi capital on the East Coast.
PR.
Hundreds of people are still without weapons of mass destruction.
At least the National Guard went door-to-door yesterday,
offering weapons in Venezuela.
This is PR News, offering mass destruction.
PR.
PR is an"> military aid supplement forاء
You can't breathe.
The traffic.
You can't think.
Beep, beep, beep, beep.
Look out for that truck.
Honk, honk.
Look out for that taxi.
Boing.
Beep, beep.
Roar.
Honk, honk.
Beep, beep.
Honk.
What's that?
Look.
It's the towers.
They're falling.
Ah!
He can't stand dangerous, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous weapons.
Of course you realize this means war.
According to one conspiracy, the trade centers were faked.
That is something that will take us a long time to wrap ourselves around.
Now, whether what we were watching,
were simulation exercises being transmitted as the real event,
it's a possibility which needs to be examined.
It needs to be examined closely.
There has, in fact, been almost a media blackout,
a kind of a deliberate American policy
that's been basically there since the war in Vietnam,
and we saw it in the Falklands War and the Gulf War,
and now in the NATO war against the former Yugoslavia,
and now again in Afghanistan,
where the military do not want the media to be involved.
And the American media have been complaining bitterly
that they haven't got access to what's been going on.
They didn't destroy the two towers.
It just didn't seem real.
We thought it was something out of a movie.
Just a little while ago, one of the volunteers,
who tried to go down there and help report it back,
and said, you actually got to the scene at the World Trade Center.
What was most remarkable, what was most amazing,
what was most horrifying is that basically nothing was happening.
This is nearly a 10-acre site.
signal
Deep in the Nevada desert.
A lot of open space.
A secret film studio deep in the Nevada desert.
Two hijacked planes
were staged and filmed
before the footage was transmitted
to a gullible world.
At the World Trade Center,
what was most remarkable, what was most amazing,
The most horrifying is that basically nothing was happening.
Basically nothing was happening.
There's enough evidence there to make me doubt.
That is something that will take us a long time to wrap ourselves around.
Now whether what we were watching were simulation exercises...
They didn't destroy the two towers.
...being transmitted as the real event...
...is a possibility which needs to be examined...
They didn't destroy the two towers.
...is such a multi-layered and complex situation...
...which needs to be examined closely.
In order to retain the prestige of American industry throughout the world...
...they had to fake it.
Private.
Public.
And the rest of you guys with funny names.
Mount your pieces, lock and load.
Handle over here by the perimeter.
Stop laughing.
The IRACs could hear you and blow your mind.
Or blow your head off.
Okay.
See that over there?
That is a fully transitional lunar module capable of whisking us out of here in a matter of five seconds if we so desire.
If not, we may take that objective below.
See it?
Put on your night glasses.
There it is.
See it moving around like little blue snakes.
I can't see nothing, man.
This ain't working.
These night glasses ain't working.
Get your earmuffs off your eyes.
Where should I pull this thing?
Take his earmuffs off his eyes.
There's no reason why...
There you go.
Now see them little blue snakes moving around?
Yeah, here.
Cool.
Those are Saddam Husseins.
The evilest, vilest critter ever invented.
I hate them Saddam Husseins.
Yeah.
Each one of them's got a weapons of mass destruction.
That's right.
See that one over there?
He's got a weapons of mass destruction.
Yeah, and he just...
I got one right here.
Wanna see it?
Oh, no.
Put that thing away.
All right.
You think you're gonna get off that?
That looks like a great big giant motorized vehicle.
Yeah, I think he's overexposed himself.
He can go back from the front.
Go back home.
He needs to go back home.
Oh, he's over there, no way.
What'd you do with that dang dildo?
Is he torturing a prisoner with that dang dildo?
No, I think the prisoner enjoys being tortured in that way.
Yeah, it's not...
It's not real torture.
Well, I think that's good level...
Oh, yeah.
Tengo que decirles algunas cosas.
Ustedes están locos de todos.
Tú y tú, todos y todos.
here.
Baby.
Head-ра-... .كن, baby.
Head- мел
Oh, yes, and that last horrible, horrible noise was My Baby, My Baby by Blue Marmalade
off of the old subgenius album called Bad Doctors.
Also, of course, we heard ESO Swamp Radio from WCSB in Cleveland with host Chaz Smith,
Lonesome Cowboy Dave, Princess Wee, and yours truly Reverend Ivan Stagg.
The Great Twin Towers Hoax.
That collage about the hoax of the...
Twin Towers, and there's more of that to come, by the way, is by Reverend Buttress O'Neill.
Buttress O'Neill.
That's spelled O apostrophe K-N-E-E-L.
Buttress O'Neill, I believe from Australia or one of those under down places.
And, yes, Buttress O'Neill and Mega Conspiracies.
Friends, we've had a lot of cuts and clips in this.
And so...
And so, we've had a lot of cuts and clips in the surrounding Hour of Slack shows
from New Monet and Artemia Salina and others on alt.binaries.slack
who've contributed a lot of cuts.
But everything else on this show, I mean, all the collages on this particular show
are by Fernanda Nande-Lemur.
All those amazing cut-ups of sound.
The great Fernanda Nande-Lemur.
Well, also, I found this great old cartoon called Make Mine.
Freedom.
We heard some of that.
And because this war stuff, friends, it's gotten even me upset.
It's gotten so weird.
Like the other day when all of our watches and clocks suddenly switched over from, you know,
regular civilian time to military 0800 type time.
So, now...
Then you have them read.
You say...
Cranky and Henri, man.
Moby Dick.
Your watch went over to military?
Military.
Remember John Bush's pass?
Yeah, it's still...
And I can't get it to go back to regular 12.
And yeah, my computer clock went over to military time all of a sudden.
But they'll read it backwards.
No, it still says 2003, but it went into military, you know, 22 instead of 10 o'clock.
Well, we are all on military time now.
And time is running out.
If we'd like to quote Mr. George W. for war.
The balloon toots have dropped.
The balloon toots have hit the spatula.
And the chase is on.
The fat is...
Hit the griddle.
Sliding.
Well, actually, no.
The race is running.
Here comes heartbreak hung up behind the back stretch.
Don't say that.
There are weeks of surroundings to happen.
Weeks of smallpox inoculations for the lucky.
And weeks of procrastination for the guilty.
In front of the head of the smallpox goddess,
thousands and thousands of electees ready to be inaugurated as the president likes to call it.
Inoculate it with the smallest pox they can find.
Micro-inventesimal tiny little pox.
Tiny inoculations.
When you rub them, the liquid gel forms behind your eye cataracts and above in your modula oblongata.
Get the shot.
Be the shot.
It's good for you.
Take it.
Take your best shot.
The tiny...
Tiny nanobots in the smallpox vaccinations are there for your protection, your security.
Already I can feel the scent of a powerful missile system surrounding America.
You'll never be lost, my friend.
You may not know where you are, but the great geosynchronous satellites always will.
And the great geodesic domes, much like the random pillows in the prisoner,
will follow you and take you back, number seven.
Take you back.
I am not a...
I am not a number.
I am a teeny tiny little tiny little man.
No, the next version of that show, the guy will be running around going,
I am not a free man, I am a number.
I am number six.
The 2000...
You are number one.
I'm telling you, man, I'm a gas station attendant.
We want you to get the hell out.
You are number one.
Tell them I am...
God number one.
Mm-hmm.
It's time to dance.
No, I'm saying, no, I'm saying.
It's time to release the...
What's that aroma in the air?
Oh, I guess one of those trouser ghosts is moaning.
I think it's maybe something more bachotastylistic than that.
You know, Cleveland is a testosterone city for those wonderful inovulations our president will be offering soon.
Oh, really?
Are we one of the sample towns?
Yes, we're a sampling town.
They're taking DNA and little skull samples from the people here
and spreading them across their sandwiches and slides in Washington, D.C.
They're missing...
Or in Dietrich, Maryland.
Yes.
Oh, yes.
Brewing up a nice cocktail for all the good American boys and girls.
Now, I got my flu shot in September or so,
and then I got the flu in January,
and I wonder what else was in the shot.
I mean, because they didn't put the...
The flu inoculation was only half good.
Well, sign away my freedom.
Why, this is ridiculous.
Don't be corny, brother.
Sure, our system of free enterprise isn't perfect,
but before we throw it away for some imported double talk,
let's turn the clock back a few years to see what it's like.
Don't be for us.
The search for conspiracies is the search for explanation,
and in many cases, in many mysteries,
a conspiracy is a very plausible first hypothesis.
Two hijacked planes slamming into the World Trade Center,
and then shortly afterwards,
we had reports from Washington of an attack on the Pentagon.
A question I'd like to put to our listeners on the evening show tonight.
Do you feel that the coverage and the perspectives you're getting,
that you're receiving through the various forms of media that you receive,
that you consume,
that perhaps you pursue,
do you feel like you're getting a pluralist view?
Are you hearing different perspectives?
Do you have a prismatic view?
I guess that's another way of asking it.
Do you hear dissenting voices,
voices that are questioning orthodoxy?
Because none of these things are straightforward.
Obviously, there is no one given truth in all this.
It's a very complex and very multifaceted event originally,
and what's happened since.
I'm just wondering how you judge
what you've been able to learn through the media.
We saw them in front of our eyes being pulverized,
disintegrated in just a few seconds.
Obviously, gripping television.
But did it actually happen?
Everything seems to be wrong with everything regarding the record.
It was surreal.
As we looked at it, we thought it was something out of a movie.
Why is there a cover-up over what happened?
It's very simple, really.
There is supposed to be a cover-up.
It's official policy.
And now, of course, the towers became martyrs.
But did it actually happen, or is there a darker side?
It just didn't seem real.
They became the first skyscraper martyrs that have ever been.
It is an amazing thing to walk up and down the streets
and see vendors on the sidewalks
selling pictures of the World Trade Center,
the way they might have sold pictures of Martin Luther King
or Elvis Presley or something.
They're now selling pictures of a building of the World Trade Center.
I thought, that's what I'm watching. It must be true.
We saw them.
We saw them in front of our eyes.
And I thought, this is amazing.
And I thought, that's what I'm watching. It must be true.
Disintegrated in just a few seconds.
But did it actually happen the way we've been shown?
They didn't destroy the two towers.
Or is there a darker side?
It just didn't seem real.
Now let's see what's happening to Judy and Jimmy and the Cinnamon Bear.
We left them at the bottom of the root beer ocean
where their airplane was forced down
after the Cinnamon Bear overtook the airplane.
This made them very sad.
And they were even sadder when Cinnamon Bear told them
there was no way to get out and punch the hole in the fuel tank
and slush all the soda pop gas.
Check it out.
We found it.
It doesn't look very cute.
Great moments in oddball sports.
That's an excerpt from Saint.
Tentatively a convenience.
The material there from the bad doctors of genius type.
And this music in the background, by the way.
Is the amino acids.
You might check out theaminoacids.com.
They're in Detroit.
And we're hoping to do a revival with them soon.
Yeah.
All your wars is on TV now.
What is this?
It's all broadcasted on television.
Nobody dies.
You see what happens, sis.
You point one of them guns at the robot over there.
And you hear a loud kibble.
And if he's successful, that robot's out of action.
Now, these here weapons are so smart, they actually have an IQ.
It's a bit higher than mine.
That's not the main part of it.
The best part of it is where you can actually shoot.
As a matter of fact, I was just watching a TV special that depicted bullets that have tiny computers in them.
Bullets with hearts and souls and minds is what America needs.
Bullets with personalities and underpants.
Bullets with hearts and minds to fight the invincible.
Well, they don't have to have much of a heart.
In fact, that would probably prevent them from exploding right over the head of the guy hiding behind the wall.
Right.
Which is why they have little brains.
Seriously, bullets with microprocessors, 20-millimeter shells that are shot out of futuristic machine guns.
And the machine guns themselves are smart.
They are.
Bullets with hearts and souls.
A performing anal section.
They've got a great video camera hooked up to them so that you can see the kill in slow motion and broadcast it on Japanese TV later.
It's flying everywhere.
There's mastic mess and THM fluids and spinal fluids and brain fluids everywhere.
Oh, what a mess, what a mess.
Wow.
That was a great little rock on.
It was. We went from the beginning to the end of our military service in one quick little bite.
Go!
Huh? What? What? No!
I'm sorry for the mess.
I'm not sorry. I'm not sorry.
Yeah!
The devil!
Taking some time off into the morning air.
We've drawn in deep into you,
We've drawn in deep into you.
I'm the happy man
Photographic records hold the clues to this conspiracy.
And here we see the footage.
If you've just joined us.
It just didn't seem real.
Within spitting distance of Wall Street
and even the Statue of Liberty.
We thought it was something out of a movie.
This is the scene after the planes have slammed into the side
and you see the back tower just crumpling like cars.
But did it actually happen?
Or is there a darker side?
This is the scene...
Out of a movie.
Film in a studio.
This is the scene...
Out of a movie.
Film in a studio.
This is the scene...
Out of a movie.
Film in a studio.
Now looking at this picture of the rock over to the left of the screen
has the letter C marked on it.
Why should there be a letter of the English alphabet stamped onto a rock?
Surely we're looking at the deliberate planting of props
in a pre-designated position
in the foreground of a photographic film set.
That is something that will take us a long time.
It's time to wrap ourselves around.
It's hard to contemplate, isn't it?
Now whether what we were watching were simulation exercises
being transmitted as the real event
is a possibility which needs to be examined
needs to be examined closely.
Of course they did that and that was no secret.
It was no secret that photographs and films were taken of models.
It worked as a simulation.
Nobody knew the difference.
Well, I think they've all got the chips implanted
just like the boys at Fort Benning.
What do you think of that idea?
Do you think that our American troops or troupettes
as they like to call the ones with the wandlers
What is?
Do you think they should be chipped and stroked on their way to
Afghanistan and Iran and Iraq and North Kenya?
Or do you think they should just be dropped from the grape trestles
and maybe swept up into a pile of dung?
Why not both?
Oh, well, I see it all the way from...
Let's be flexible.
Toa Baja Puerto Rico.
Don't bend over that way. Bend over this way.
He was in the war, you know.
He was wounded in the head.
Yes.
Makes him sort of, well, rather funny at times.
Quiet. Quiet.
There's nothing so ominous as quiet.
Besides, it isn't quiet.
First, his heart is dead.
Hmm.
He's dead.
So?
What?
Goodbye.
See, that's all you gotta do.
That's all we can do.
But the thing with the paranoia, if you're getting CSB paranoia,
it's a residual kind of thing that lasts long after the listening experience, we'll say.
Because paranoia will imply...
...deploy you.
...odd dreams, strange discolorations of the knee.
Paranoia...
I get off on paranoia at this point.
Hey, if you're in the military, paranoia will deploy you.
Oh, yeah.
That's for sure.
The W stands for war.
Shaddam's got a good war bush.
Shaddam's gotta go.
Let's roll.
Let's roll a few...
...frop sticks out of this...
Let's roll the nuclear device.
...combustible, post-deal coconut device.
Donated for a while.
Donated by Friday Jones.
My God.
Not ready for war.
Yeah.
A Friday Jones sentence...
You would ingest something that Friday sent you.
I'm not ready for war.
You've got a lot of...
You should be at going to war because you've got a lot of nerve.
I'm not ready to...
...for your mom.
This is military talk.
I'm not ready to drop the bomb.
I'm not ready to chew my heart.
And that's why I want to start.
I'm not ready for...
I'm not ready for war.
I'm not...
Sorry, quick.
I got it.
What? Jessica, she was supposed to take her clothes off while she's singing?
Seek!
Hide!
That's what she was supposed to say as she disrobed.
Seek!
Hide!
Hide and seek!
Seek!
How stupid. We entertain ourselves with this.
And no one else can care about it, don't you know why?
Of course you do.
You never know why.
It hurts to care.
It hurts, doesn't it?
It helps to hate.
It's like a poo-poo that won't come out.
It's like having the armature removed.
It's painful.
It's like having the sticks in your bag of sticks all broken.
Yes, yes.
It's like trying to smoke the sticks and they become...
All your broken sticks.
...in your heart.
It's painful.
It's like being in pain and hurt.
No, I'm saying. No, I'm saying.
Yes, I...
No, you're saying. No, you're saying.
I think I know what you're saying, but I don't know if I...
No, mine. No, mine.
No, wait a minute.
You're sweating a little bit, Mr. Stang.
Your left eye is...
I told you, man, I get off on the paranoia.
No, no, I think you're lying, Mr. Stang.
It's like, bring it on, man.
It's like all your reference, Stang.
Bring it on.
No, no, no.
The coyote, because he is the paranoid animal...
Oh, yes, talk about him again.
...is the most aware animal.
Yes, yes.
The coyote, because he's paranoid, is all aware.
He never sleeps.
No, no.
He's always on the prowl.
One eye.
He's always on the hunt.
The coyote...
That's coming up.
...sees.
...lifts.
He's changing.
And he whiffs.
He whiffs it.
The change was complete.
A radical mastectomy.
An arm full of hair.
And wings the size of buzzard ears.
Even a man who is full of slack...
...and lets his farts by night.
His feet...
...like the feet of a dog.
...may become the weird bob...
His hands were like the hands of a...
...when the pea-bomb blooms.
Yes, he was the coyote.
...and the furs are full of bed.
...was the last wind.
No!
Yes, the last wind.
...and the furs are full of bed.
Well, till next week.
Keep your head undyed.
You're back to the wind.
Wait for further instructions.
And keep your babies warm.
You know the sound...
...may not tell you more.
...of this week.
You're back to the wind.
...and the furs are full of bed.
Keep your babies warm.
The awaker shall sleep.