It is a hard way, the way of being a man.
Sooner or later, we all want a thing that is bad.
To walk on all fours.
To suck up drink from a stream.
To jabber, saying the words.
To go snuffling at the earth and floor the bark of trees.
To eat flesh for fish.
To make love to more than one every which way.
These are all bad things.
These are not the things that man do.
We are men.
Are we not?
Because the Father has made us men.
Praise Bob.
Oh, Bob.
Turn on.
Tune in.
Why do you want to be normal?
The rupture is upon us, dear friends.
That fateful day, July 5th, 1998.
Next day's are coming.
And the pigs are bumming.
You are about to participate in a great adventure.
you are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to the subgenius
we don't want to hurt you no we just want to tickle you and make you laugh
we just want to show you a good time we would never dream of brainwashing you
making you kill yourself no why on earth would we do such a silly thing like that
you can't kill yourself to the next day then you may shed your meat vessels
and
but remember
do not
shed your vessels
until next day
for all that will await you
is eternal
damnation
in a fiery
hell on earth
under ordinary
circumstances I would never
deny Jesus but under
physical torture
I would never deny Jesus
afraid i would break down strapped to a table with someone sticking needles in my eyes now wait a
minute wait whoa hold the phone what kind of a false christ is supposed to be coming that loves
and saves souls now what what how many people would he to see if he took you doug and said
let's trap old doug down and poke his eyes out and save his soul my brethren
our task is nearly complete he was the last of those who brought the punishment to us
we have cleansed and purged his world now we must build built coffins that's all you'll need
and the peaks are coming
sure when the rupture hits we'll all be in our first class window seats on the pleasure saucers
watching the little pink boys fry
own alien allies bob's alien allies the exes are likened to gods their spaceships do not crash
for they do not need spaceships anymore than they are now they are the only ones that can
do anything and bob needs brains in his head soon we will be on the escape vessels yeah
each of us with our own fleet of battle planets if that's what we want they could just be shopping
malls or villages if that's what we want anything what's that need say smart witty
did he mention sacrilegious the church is not famous for its sense of humor or sense of its
uh of itself when being discussed by others uh i can understand this and it's
The issue was this new TV show called Nothing Sacred and how people were viewing that.
And in the context of that, we've gone off and talked about the church in general.
And now we have a call from Bethlehem.
Edward, I hope you are calling from Lehigh Valley and not from the Holy Land.
No, it's quite correct.
It is the Lehigh Valley.
How are you doing tonight, Clark?
Very good, Ed.
A real pleasure to talk to you.
Thank you.
My girlfriend's a big fan of yours.
I've been reading your columns and types.
Tell her I love her.
Well, you know, I've got to give it to you.
I drove an hour and a half from Reading listening to this show.
And it's probably the funniest hour and a half of radio I've heard in a long, long time.
I think so.
It's amazing when you talk about religion, the nuts that will come out of the woodwork.
Now, mind you, they're very righteous and lovable nuts, but nuts nonetheless.
I've spent a great deal of my life researching religion.
I'm myself a minister in a local church.
And it never ceases to amaze me that a church that has held so much power,
and is, what, 2,000 years old now, is afraid of a little rib, you know, a little jolt in the ribs.
And it'll poke a little fun at them, and they get all riled up.
Right.
When you get right down to it, you're talking about beliefs.
People are quoting this book and that book.
What you're really talking about is an invisible monster and who believes in which invisible monster.
Mm-hmm.
Now, you probably remember.
Well, you're not talking about the existence of God, right?
You're talking about...
Well, I'm talking about the existence of God on a person.
On a personal level, what you think God is.
Take, for example, the cult that...
What was it?
The Heaven's Gate.
Right.
Okay.
Can't be proved the existence of whatever they believe in.
Right.
Well, they followed this religion, and they killed themselves.
And all you heard about for months and months and months were people tripping over themselves on your station and every other station,
talking about, well, how weird they were, and how wrong they were, and how we're so glad that we're so absolutely normal,
because we believe in a good invisible monster that didn't make us kill ourselves.
Right.
And, well, you know, each has their own invisible monster.
If you take the idea of many of the principles and the cornerstone of the Christian belief, Catholic belief,
certainly there's a cannibalistic right there, isn't there?
That we're eating the body, literally, and blood, literally.
Quite literally.
Right.
As a matter of fact, very interesting you should mention that,
that...
Right.
With the recent development in cloning technology,
there have been factions that have actually been trying to take transformed wafers and holy wine
to actually try and clone Jesus once again.
Oh, dear.
Yes.
You know, hey, each has their own, whatever you want to do.
If that's your religion...
Hey, if your religion revolves around creating an army of Jesuses to rule the world,
hey, so be it.
Don't expect not to be made fun of, and that's the point.
Right.
You're going to believe in an invisible monster that's going to send you into a fiery pit,
into a fiery pit,
for not doing exactly what he told someone else to tell you to tell you to do.
Well, here's...
You're going to be made fun of.
But, yeah, and if we, coming through that experience,
we were willing to martyr, be martyrs,
can't we take a little ribbon?
You know what I mean?
Ah!
Sure, J.R. Bob Dobbs is my savior.
And of course I want more slack.
And I'm smoking prop nonstop.
But what I really want...
Oh yeah, that's it.
Those lovely alien-nympho mutants.
Non-stop orgies on the pleasure saucers.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I love to be naked.
More, more.
Oh, Bob.
Ah!
Oh...
We will be able to have sex and sails and mutual education with
many different species from many worlds and times
subgenius and even humans will be so few and far between amongst all these races
that when you see a person, you won't care whether they're
white or black or male or female or human or subgenius.
You'll be glad if they just have one head.
You'll say, wow, an earthling wow-ow, man.
Ah, hey, I'm from North America,
Wow, do you know Fred Schwartz?
Next day's a-comin'.
And the peaks are bumpin'.
She bumped!
She got spiked! Stop!
Ring him.
If the students know that taking LSD might bring permanent brain damage, why do they take it?
The reply the teacher gave was,
well, if a student knows that tomorrow he may lose his head in Vietnam or buy an atomic bomb,
he's not too concerned about the possibility of damaging a few brain cells with a trip on LSD.
You know how some users may have lofty ambitions and hopes
that the drug or LSD will bring them some miraculous transformation,
make them poets and artists or supermen,
and many others looking strictly for escape.
Escape from life that has become too painful for them to bear.
What are we going to answer these young people today?
The young people that are crying out, live fast, look beautiful, die young.
The bomb may drop tomorrow.
Friend, you and I must find an answer.
I don't know. Gotta nuke something.
Touche.
First we got the bomb and that was good
Cause we love peace and motherhood
Then Russia got the bomb but that's okay
Cause the balance of power's maintained that way
Who's next?
France got the bomb and that was good
We got the bomb but don't you grieve
Cause they're on our side, I believe
China got the bomb but have no fears
They can't wipe us out for at least five years
Who's next?
Josh, the only difference between peace and war
is where we place our bombs.
We know that the vehicles for this kind of human destruction
are possible because there are things known as space buses
that can carry within them literally hundreds of pods,
each pod filled with a bomb of many megatons.
By radio waves, those bombs can be released wherever they want.
So they can just simply orbit this earth and touch the button
and city after city and country after country is blasted off the face of the earth.
Sarge, I think we're picking up something on the bomb detector.
And then the heavens will pass away with a terrible noise
and the heavenly bodies will disappear in fire
and the earth and everything on it will be burned up.
I said X days are coming
And them little pigs are bummer
Those conspiracy Duke Pinkboy normals are gonna fry
They won't even know what hit them
That old Stark fist is gonna come down hard
But nothing's guaranteed dear friends
I'm a card-carrying member of the church of the subgenius
I'm the almighty king of slap
But when X day comes around
The only thing I have
is my
unshakable faith
in Bob!
Turn on
my tune-in
and turn off the lights!
That's really rude.
Really, really rude.
Now, bro, how can you get a master's degree if you keep swearing like that?
Well, you can.
I mean, Jesus had a master's degree, but he was denied ten years of worship.
For praying or cussing, which was it?
Uh, yes.
Yes.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Yes, friends!
Man, once again, I've got, just like last week, I've got so much great stuff here to play
that I don't...
There's no way I'm gonna get to all of it.
It's just too much too good to be true.
And, uh, uh, yes, what we've been listening to is what we will be listening to.
The great Bill T. Miller, king of slack, has come out with a new CD called,
Orgy of Slack, and I could easily just make this show nothing but that CD.
It is so good.
It is such a classic, pure subgenius CD.
I've also got this amazing audio collage, or media barrage as we call them in our religion,
done by the putacious sister, Susie the Floozy of Atlanta.
Congratulations to the Atlantaids.
They're a rockin' hand, and Jane and Papa Joe Mama, also, for the big Atlanta devivals
that they just had.
And, uh, friends, I've got an Einstein secret radio show that could easily carry the entire show.
And I've got the recordings from the amazing devivals in Portland and Seattle,
and I should just shut up and play that stuff, but I'm so excited.
I've got to tell you about the upcoming...
What?
Oh, they're after me, friends.
I've got to hurry.
Um, uh, uh, uh, uh, first off, in Cleveland, April 16th, Thursday, at the Euclid Tavern,
yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stank, will be preaching and, uh, and, and, whatever, with
Einstein's Secret Orchestra, Lonesome Cowboy Dave, Chaz and Michelle, and Princess Rhiar
Doe, and who knows what else.
That's, uh, April 16th at the Euclid Tavern, friends.
On Euclid Avenue in beautiful Cleveland, Ohio.
And then, uh, a week later, April 23rd in Boston, at the Middle East, the irreverent
Friday Jones brings you the final devival of all time that we know of, short of X-Day,
which will star...
Dr. Legume!
Bill T. Miller himself, the King of Slack, plus Pope David N. Meyer, Pope Sternodocs
Keycaver, possibly, and Brother Cleve Duncan and D.K. Jones.
Now, can you imagine a greater, uh, bunch of Slack bangers?
And, in fact, D.K. Jones, Brother Cleve, and, uh, Bill T. Miller, uh, together and, uh,
have become a band called the Slack Bangers.
We'll be hearing that off of Bill's amazing CD shortly.
Let me give you an address, a couple of addresses for Bill T. Miller, because when you hear
this material off this CD, um, I've been playing the old, the old, uh, X-Day, uh, I've been
playing the old X-Day as a common, uh, saw, but, uh, wait until you hear the new stuff
coming up.
And here it is.
You can, uh, uh, get this from Box, the Bill T. Miller, friends, King of Slack at Box 230-221.
That's Box 230-221, Boston, Massachusetts, 02123.
Cool bunch of numbers there, friends.
Box 230-221, Boston, my 02123.
Or you can, uh, uh, check him, uh, check out on the web BillTMiller.com.
All one word, lowercase, BillTMiller.com.
Or you can email Bill T. Miller at KingofSlack, one word, at subgenius.com.
I don't know if Bill even knows that he has that address.
But, uh, uh, he, he, he does.
And, uh, friends, oh, so I'm gonna, I'm just gonna, we're, we're gonna just dive right
into it.
Uh, uh, oh, oh.
Uh, uh, uh, uh.
Praise the .
Why?
Uh.
Oh.
Oh!
The mind is the most powerful sex organ.
You're gonna like it when you get less frightened of it, you sleazy weasel.
Listen to me, mister, it's salvation I'm talking about!
The blues isn't about feeling better, it's about making other people feel worse.
I will tell you about the fiction and the fallacy.
It's brought to you by the salesman of salvation.
That's marvelous, that is marvelous!
I'm gonna have to fire.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Easy there, bitches.
Oh, no.
I'm a slug baby, baby.
You know what I like.
A slug baby, baby.
You know what I need.
You know what I want.
Oh, yeah.
A slug baby, baby.
Now that's what I want, that's right.
Oh, ugh.
You know what I like.
A slug band, baby.
Ugh.
You know what I need.
A slug baby, baby.
You know what I want.
Ugh!
Oh, yeah.
A slug banging feels so good, yeah.
Ugh.
Slack banging with the slack bangers.
Now that's what I want. That's right.
You can always get more.
Slack bang the baby.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Slack banging with the slack bangers.
With the slack bangers.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Now that's what I want. That's right.
You want to hear some great music?
I just wanted to make money and have fun.
Hello, doctor.
How are you?
The doctor is on.
You could have a rewarding career as a subgenius doctor.
That's right. Surgeons for Connie.
Perform healing orgy-deviable surgery.
Sicken the masses.
Bombard the patient with subgenius anti-fusing noise.
I'm gonna die.
Surgeons for Connie. Standing by.
Well, I...
I...
I'm ready to operate.
Scammer.
Golf club.
Pipe.
Light the pipe full of froth and insert the golf club into the third nostril of the patient.
And the depro gaming will begin.
Stop it! Stop it!
Please, I beg you!
You will no longer believe in Connie's little puppet, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
You will now realize the truth.
That Connie is the one true slack master.
Praise Connie! Praise Connie! Praise Connie! Praise Connie!
Don't worry.
The spurting, bleeding head side effects are part of the treatment.
Now, whenever you hear the name Bob,
you will automatically substitute the name Connie.
Connie.
Praise Connie.
Hail Connie.
Love Connie.
Hate Connie.
Connie.
You are out of control.
They set me on a cold metal table.
And prodded me with humiliating probes.
Now, don't you feel better?
Warning. Danger.
This is not Bob, young. It's God.
Friends, you can actually call this unusual band,
which has an answer machine,
that they urge you to leave strange messages on.
The new number is...
617 Lick OBE.
Please make a note of it.
Disregard all rumors, no matter how entertaining.
Frankly, Mr. Miller, I don't understand this album.
The OBE album.
Could you explain it to us a little bit?
Well, it's an insane journey.
Sort of a dream flashback.
An all night TV dream flashback.
And you're looking through the mind of this insane genius.
After he's been up all night watching TV,
and he just was abducted by alien sex nymphs,
and he's on his quest for enlightenment.
Uh-huh.
And since it's a dream, it's a flashback,
it really doesn't really make sense.
And this insane genius has all these obsessions,
like he loves to eat, he watches too much TV,
he's on the phone,
he's into sex and magic and UFOs,
and he just, he tries to overindulge in all his obsessions
until his mind just blows.
This is called Out of Band Experience.
And make your dream come true.
Very sexually explicit.
Your discretion is advised.
Wait until I get my devices.
The next performer on our stage
is indeed considered to be one of the three greatest guys in the universe.
He was born of a virgin.
He was anointed and baptized by John the Baptist himself in the wilderness.
He suffered and was crucified under Pontius Pilate,
that hairy bureaucrat,
the procurator of Judea, a terrible child.
And he died for the sins of mankind,
and then after three days he rose from the dead,
and he ascended unto heaven
where he sat by the right hand of the Father.
Jehovah One,
senile and malignant space god.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the church of the subgenius of Zion,
Jesus of Nazareth!
Thank you, thank you.
I am the Lord Jesus Christ,
business manager of the subgenius.
Enough about me.
I've got a lot of people to talk to,
and I want to thank for putting this revival together.
I usually don't do this,
but I have a small parable,
a very serious parable for you.
Praise Jesus!
Thank you, thank you.
They ask me why I came back
and became the business manager of the church of the subgenius.
And it's because I like being around a bunch of non-believers,
because maybe you guys won't kill me this time.
But just in case,
I have my ticket,
and I will be on the space vessels of the sex goddesses
on July 5th, 7 a.m.
And since I'm only 28,
I don't get crucified until I'm 33.
Hell, that's plenty of time.
So here's your parable for the evening.
Every morning,
in the plains of Africa,
the gazelle gets up,
and it realizes
that if it doesn't outrun the lion,
it will be killed.
And every morning,
the lion wakes up,
and it realizes
if it doesn't run faster than the gazelle,
it will starve to death.
Friends, it doesn't matter,
it does not matter
whether you're a lion or a gazelle.
When the sun comes up,
you better be running.
And if you don't have your subgenius membership
on July 4th,
you better be running your ass off.
Thirty dollars is cheap now,
but the price is going up.
And now, let me plug some products.
The full-color poster here by, uh...
Well,
has it ever occurred to you
you might have totally lost your mind?
I mean, this is just satanic.
Judge not, Mr. Douglas,
that ye be not judged,
for by these judgments
shall ye also be judged.
And let he who hath not sinned
cast the first stone.
There is no peace,
saith the Lord,
unto the wicked.
Uh, can't we take a little ribbon?
You know what I mean?
Well, it comes down to,
what's the point of a religion
if you can't use it to say that you're right
and someone else is wrong?
Yeah, if it comes...
Yeah, exactly.
But when you get right down to it,
you know,
but a lot of people,
not all, mind you,
I mean, I don't want to condemn everyone,
but a lot of people,
they're not in it for the idea of love
and going to heaven.
No.
They like the idea of you and me
not going to heaven.
They like...
It's the inclusion.
They want to be part of that, you know...
It's a social club.
Well, yeah.
And it's also,
it gives them comfort.
Comfort to know.
You know, they get together
every Sunday morning and, you know,
play bridge with Jesus.
Hey, and that's fine.
I play bridge with Jesus.
I usually let him win
and there's nothing wrong with that.
But don't expect not to be made fun of
because you are funny.
You're funnier than George Burns.
You're funnier than Red Skelton.
You're funnier than all of them.
And what's so funny is
you don't even realize
that you're being so funny.
So...
And you know what?
You speak much truth.
I wish it wasn't quite so serious.
Well...
You know what I mean?
No, no, you're right.
And thanks for the call, Ed.
I got to make a run.
If they can't take a joke, you know?
Yeah, I hear you.
Thanks.
Ed Strangman.
The Strange, dear friends.
The amazing circus oddity,
Edward...
Reverend Edward Strange.
Bravo.
Oh.
Somewhere in sands of the desert,
the shape of a lion body
and the head of a man
is moving its slow thighs.
The darkness drops again.
But now I know
that 20 centuries of stony sleep
were vexed to a nightmare
by a rocking cradle.
And what rough beast,
its hour come round at last,
slouches towards Bethlehem
to be born.
Oh.
Well, England,
that book was just beautiful.
Thank you so much.
Very, very much.
I mean, I mean,
Jesus had a master's degree,
but he was denied tenure
and they crucified him.
You know, publish and perish.
It's industry that made this country great.
Tell it like it is, Pastor Craig.
Why, why, thank you, Princess Wee.
I mean, I've worked hard for a living.
I've worked so hard,
it's just, it's just embarrassing.
And then I get e-mail like I got yesterday
from some person who was criticizing me
for something I put on All.Slack
over a year ago.
And I'm like,
well, I'm going to go to jail.
Mm-mm-mm, how funny.
Well, what's more than that,
it's like he was thinking
he was ragging on his band or something.
Good thoughts, now I'm hanging up on you.
It was like he was thinking
I was ragging on his band or something.
He's saying,
just because we got on stage
doesn't give you the right to compliment
and critique on your parents or something.
I'm thinking, well, gee.
Looking in your bathroom window
and you don't know what to do.
Oh, yeah.
Surveillance cameras everywhere.
It's more than your dream, Pastor Craig.
They're not coming to you through the internet.
They're coming to you through your brain.
They got your brain in a jar.
Somewhere in Langley there's a clone.
Somewhere off in the D.I.A.
there's somebody who knows your real home.
Ha-ha.
Yeah, him and everybody else on the internet, but...
Oh.
But do go on. Do go on.
It's a sad song.
I like hearing my name said on the air like that.
It gives me a feeling of importance.
But it's like, it's like, geez, like...
It's like, it's like these people just keep picking on me or something.
It's like they think they're gonna...
Pastor Craig.
Yes, it is.
Really, Pastor Craig?
Yes.
Oh, Pastor Craig.
Pastor Craig.
Would you please recap the song?
Open your eyes to the Lord and share the words that won a man to go send.
We remarkably think of God as Father, but he will come to the Lord before we depart.
We respectfully think of God as the King of our eyes.
It's not easy, man, no matter who you are.
But we have received moreury all the way up until today.
What's wilder, man?
What do you got to say to Pastor Craig?
How many people do you know are looking forward to X Day
just because it will get them out of debt?
Pastor Craig
I suppose they all owe you
There's nothing else you can do, man.
You got to stop fussing, bro.
You got too many problems.
Craig
Dust stick
Oh, wow.
Stop that obscene dance.
Hey.
Can't. But I can't.
Wait just a second here.
Dancing is a part of life.
All civilizations have had dance.
Part of life is a dance.
Is it not, Pastor Craig?
Pastor Craig
That's so pretty.
I once had a band.
I once had a band, but know what happened?
It's another sad story, isn't it, Pastor Craig?
Well, it's the sort of story that people think you're making it up when you tell it.
Our keyboard player ran off to Arizona.
Pastor Craig
And you might think I'm making this up just because you guys have a song called Arizona,
but this person really did run away to Arizona.
And he ran away to Arizona because, well, his parents found him doing something that he shouldn't have been doing
and taking things that he shouldn't have been taking.
And he thought that he'd be closer to God if he gave away all his possessions.
And he was in my band.
I know.
And he was the only person in our band who actually believed he was going to be able to get with members of the opposite sex
just by being in the band.
All the other members of the band either could get it or had no illusions thereof.
Pastor Craig.
Yeah, some people talk about mean old Mr. Tooth Decay.
You talk about mean old Mr. Tooth Decay.
Yeah, for ten years the dentist was sitting on your lap.
Didn't let you go, he wouldn't let you leave.
No, he had to get closer.
He had to drill down deeper.
Had to find out what was inside.
Had to fill you up.
Had to look in your brain.
And he saw love.
You know, some people think I'm Bill Cosby, but in reality I'm Mr. Tooth Decay.
Pastor Craig.
In reality, Pastor Craig.
Yes?
Could you repeat the original question, please?
The original question.
Is this a...
Mr.
The original bleepo.
We have the original bleepo on the phone.
And the original...
Pastor Craig.
The original bleepo.
Pastor Craig's on the phone.
Here comes another one.
Hello?
Hey, what...
Oh, my God.
Here they are.
Who?
This is the original question.
We have Pastor Craig on the phone.
We have the Reverend Ivan Stang.
We have Reverend bleepo Abernathy.
We've got...
The princess we have now in the studio.
And we've got...
What the hell?
83-year-old squid falling from the sky.
83-year-old squid, man.
They make me so high.
Ooh.
Yeah.
He knows.
Well, I'm so glad to see Pastor Craig, the king of ugly.
And, oh, and lovely Reverend bleepo.
And we're going to do some healings.
The church in sub-genius, we do healings.
And sickening.
So if you have nothing wrong with you tonight,
feel free to come up and get something wrong with you.
Now, I know many of you have problems such as a job.
We can heal you of that job tonight.
I'm going to need the help of my assistant here,
someone who will be a catcher for me.
So come right up.
If you have any problems with the conspiracy,
anything you want to say, now's your chance.
Somebody out there needs to be healed.
Somebody, come up, brother.
Come up, brother.
Tell me your problem.
Tell me what's wrong.
How's the problem?
The conspiracy is holding me back.
It's holding me back because I've been working at a restaurant for four months,
and I'm still the fucking busboy.
He's still the fucking busboy.
Do you believe in water, J.R.R. Bob?
I believe.
Will you fight the conspiracy?
Shoot them.
I'm going to need your help, brother.
It can get dangerous.
He's a busboy.
Do you believe in Bob?
I believe in Bob.
Do you believe in slack?
I believe in slack.
Let me heal.
What else can we have tonight?
It's a mad too.
Come on, sit down.
We've got to do something wrong.
It's got to get something wrong with this guy.
Come on up.
Come on up, brother.
I am selling futons and futon furniture.
Futons and futon furniture.
Be healed.
Our newest brethren, just ordained tonight.
What's wrong, brother?
Got some pain in my back.
Pain in your back?
And I can feel you have a pain in your shoulder.
Is that true?
Yeah.
And you have one leg.
shorter than the other is that true? I don't know about that. And I hear you can't get it up is that true?
Alright brother be honest. Alright well we're gonna hear you. Are you ready?
Freeze Bob! Alright who else is here?
Brother stick your age person come on up. This person you got a problem brother
you got a problem. My tits aren't big enough Jesus.
Oh yes. Well this is gonna someone's gonna have to hold my mic for this one.
Jesus!
Good Lord.
Oh.
My legs are fat.
Come on.
Oh.
Dude get up.
Okay.
Oh.
This is not a game for little boys and girls.
This is your life!
Happy Meadow!
Listen to your music, man!
Words in reverse!
This is just another stupid happy meadow band!
The motherfuckers gonna eat my meadow!
You thought you were gonna get pulled in here!
You're ready for me!
I used to be a nice guy just like you!
Then I found the ticket of a soul is the truth I want!
I will eat you alive and chew you up and spit in your face!
You're ready for me!
You better be ready to face the consequences little boys and girls!
One last chance! That's all you have!
You're ready for me!
There's no escaping the eyes!
You will see them in every dream!
You're right!
You will never escape the eyes of jobs!
You're ready for me!
The eyes of jobs will follow you wherever you go!
I will wash my soul's eyes again!
You're ready for me!
You'll be right for me!
You pulled me from beyond the grave!
You better be ready to face the truth my friend!
We're here for your soul!
You will love your love!
You're ready for me!
You will eat me alive and chew you up and spit in your face!
You are my life!
Hardcore girl, you don't have to cry!
Your eyes will always be a legend!
Peoplei
Your eyes won'tler
Nine!
You can!
You haven't attended to the break of a Saturday morning conspiracy!
Praise the eyes of Bob that look into yours as you look into them.
They are looking back and you are looking into them.
You are falling into the eyes of Bob and you will never hit the bottom.
On and on and on.
Oh, please tell me, is the devil still pursuing you?
Well, perhaps you could explain to me what you mean by the devil.
You seem to be on terms with him.
Well, permit me, Mr. Douglas, to tell you something of the devil that I've come to know him.
The devil is that element in human nature that impels us to destroy and debase.
And what are you about upon this island but destruction?
Oh, well, I can tell you very plainly.
No, please don't do that.
For seventeen years I have been striving to create some measure of refinement in the human species.
And it is here on this very island that I, sir, have found the very essence of the devil.
What do you mean?
I have seen the devil in my eyes.
I have seen him in my microscope.
And I have changed him.
And I suppose you could say in a sense, metaphorically speaking, I've cut him to pieces.
The devil, Mr. Douglas, I have found is nothing more than a tiresome collection of genes.
And it is with great assurance that I can tell you that Lucifer, son of Morn,
is no more.
Well, I don't see how any of this specious nonsense justifies these monstrous disfigurements.
I have a problem with everything in my entire life.
Yes! Everything in his entire life!
It's not your world!
Do you promise to reject the conspiracy in all its evil ways?
Yes.
Be healed!
Secondary life!
Tell me, brother.
Oh.
He's evil. Everything in my life.
What's wrong with you, brother?
I work in a mortuary and I like it.
Well, I don't think you need me here. I think that's fine.
He needs a sickening. He needs a sickening.
Yes!
I'm sick of you.
Be sick of him!
Don't you wish we all had that job?
Yes, friends. The beast flesh does keep creeping back.
And we keep casting it back out and then having to clean it up.
And I must say thanks to Negative Land for providing the amazing sound effects in the background on that.
It's Portland Devival.
Recording.
And thanks to Jeremy Olson for recording the thing.
Andi.
Andi!
As all of these things culminate in these end times here, we have only 111 or 110 days, I think, left.
110.
And imagine some of the people who just cannot, who will not be accepted into this mass fold.
This big fatty thing that's going to be whipped asunder.
And then sent magnetically and magically into the sky to have every, uh, anything it wants, perhaps.
I guess it is, isn't it?
Sure. Anything.
And listeners, listeners, if you...
Listeners, radio listeners out there...
...will be crammed down its hideous fat craw.
If you don't believe us right now, listeners, go to your televisions right now and tune in NBC or ABC or CBS, any of the major networks.
You'll see it's the same thing that was on yesterday.
Yeah.
It is, every day.
It's the same.
And if the virtual world isn't enough for you, get in your car and drive north.
You'll see a Burger King.
Then you'll see a multiplex movie theater.
Then you will see a McDonald's.
And the underlying zeitgeist of the...
Right.
I can predict exactly what you will see as you drive away from downtown, no matter where you are.
That's right.
And turn on your radio.
Anybody can predict it because, uh...
You know what you're here.
It's the same from one town to another.
And basically what's going to start happening, the whole Clinton scandal is going to be hundreds and then two thousands of women are going to start recalling having been groped by Bill Clinton.
Hey, I'll tell you what, Bill is not a bad lover.
He's...
You know, I'm glad that he doesn't have a mustache because that's kind of scratchy, but I loved Bill in my own...
Uh-huh.
You know, in his...
Oh, is that when you were visiting James?
I know that I was just one of his little toys that he just...
Used during a lunch hour and threw aside, but...
That was at that lunch that Jayner took you to.
Right.
Yeah.
Sure.
Well, it's when he was governor.
Right.
Long before he was president.
This thing...
Yeah.
This marking on my genitalia...
I don't know if the listeners know about this thing.
What?
The marking on my genitalia?
I have no, uh...
It's not a 666.
I have no qualms about admitting, uh...
It's not a bad sign.
It's not a sign from Satan.
It has nothing to do with the Antichrist.
This mark on my penis is a sign that I've been in close spiritual contact with aliens.
I have, uh...
Come down numerous times and visited me in the Oval Office.
And it isn't Monica Lewinsky or...
And I resent the charges...
Take your hands off me!
In fact, it was...
Take your hands off me right now!
You know what I think it's all about?
Wow.
I think what it's all about is the Republicans resent the fact that the Democrats get it
for free.
The Republicans are used to paying for it, getting professional treatment.
Yeah.
Nobody talks.
Nobody says anything afterwards.
Yeah.
But, uh...
You know, the Democrats are used to paying for it.
And the Democrats vote with their peckers once again, as always.
It's the perennial...
It's the big problem.
You know, it's the bonobos versus the...
Well...
Bono's.
Nutless...
Nope.
Noblos versus bozos?
Yeah, I don't want to...
Yeah.
Bonobos versus the bozos.
The noblos...
Nope.
Noblos...
Yeah.
That's it.
The noblos...
Versus the no-dos.
And versus the...
Triceball.
And I just...
monitors.
Sounds like action.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Please.
Now the subtle messages are getting in there.
I had some guy...
I read a review of some genius material the other day
in some magazine called Paranoia, in fact.
Ah!
That said that it implied that we used subliminals
in our radio and video material.
P.O. Box 140306 Dallas, Texas 75214.
It implied that we lied about having subliminals in them.
There are no subliminal messages.
These are not subliminal messages.
You know, if I seem to recall correctly,
all certain various products begin with a 15-minute disclaimer
about how you can't sue a...
Bob.
Bob is whispering in your ear.
40306.
Send money to the radio station.
Support public radio.
And zip codes.
Support public radio now.
I'm going to go over you.
Bob Tilton himself.
Jack Van Imp.
Pat Robertson.
Jimmy Swagger.
And Roxanne's a babe.
Huh?
Roxanne Van Imp?
You know, actually, Pastor Craig,
I'd have to agree with you,
at least, you know, for one of those pompadude,
completely artificial, made-up, robot, bimbo-looking...
You know, for a preacher wife, you're right.
She is hot.
She's squid.
Squid.
She's...
I wouldn't mind D. Beacon and Mrs. Jack Van Imp.
No.
Squid.
In fact, I've been...
Actually, I imagine there's probably some people telling stories at parties in L.A.
about just such a thing.
That's all stories.
That is squid.
What?
Parties in L.A.?
They have squid parties in L.A.?
Well, with Mrs. Jack Van Imp.
Oh, wow.
Mr. and Mrs. Jack Holm.
I love it when she jacks my imp.
Well, the whole family comes out.
And James Swagger.
James Swagger.
And sometimes the hill comes down and scrapes the squid.
And the beauty of the squid.
Come on, baby Jack Van Imp.
And I can't really remember the...
Fallen from the sky.
And the beauty of the squid.
Gosh, Uncle Bob.
Come on, then, new people.
Get that thing going.
Hey, Uncle Bob, you know, the creator really, really took his time when he made me, you know.
Yeah, me too.
Come on, Uncle Bob.
Let me show you something.
Sit on my lap, child.
Come back here, child.
Yes, lady.
Sit down.
All right.
Here, let me preach to you the Catholic word of the catechism of the special giant rod and staff of...
Here, if you would just step aside and let me spread my Catholics here.
Ah, Father Peter Raskin.
Here into this confessional.
Father Leo Buse.
Let me take you, my little...
Leap in there, Father.
Father Leo Buse.
Let them down easy, Father.
As Father Leo Buse sings homespun toilets from the toilet.
It's...
I'm sorry.
No, it was the...
Amen's Room.
That's right.
The delightful tales of Amen's Room.
Delightful tales sung from the...
Cathedral rectum...
No, never mind.
Well, my son, I understand that you don't have a mother at home.
Let me tell you about the mother of God.
And here's a special statue that I've just unraveled here for my Catholics.
Now, just bend your head down.
Okay, Father.
Let me...
Yes, it's my...
Yes?
I've bent my head down now, Father.
Now what?
Now just pray.
And you'd better pray, good boy.
This is an old story, isn't it, Father?
Well, it's as old as the grass dance, the ancient snake dance,
which is heard in the background as the Lakota...
Holy men and shaman back at...
Cart the great buffalo skull around in a great circle around the giant campfire of...
You broke, Frank.
Yes, we...
It was good fire.
Hey, man, that's probably pretty offensive to our Native American listeners, frankly.
If you guys can't do a proper grass dance, don't try.
It's not the real grass dance.
The real grass dance involves the grabbing of the clumps of grass...
to remind us that our feet are made of clay,
and our chickens are twice as golden and rich as all the other competitors.
Twice as golden and rich as both the competitors.
It reminds us that we can win if we put our spirits to it and our buttocks down to the wheel.
Put your buttocks down to the wheel and wear Bob's new special deluxe ghost shirt.
Stop that silly...
Yes, for only $12.95, you can own a special ghost shirt,
which will make you impervious to cavalry bullets.
Or the white man's laws and taxes.
Yes, the special new subgenius brand ghost shirt.
And now do your 24-hour-a-day special subgenius brand ghost dance,
which will repel all dragons, dinosaurs, and cops.
Here's the trail of Keeler's golf course.
Uh, yes. Yes.
It still makes me cry.
I could never break it.
Even their damn mouths was getting in the way.
One day, I was out late.
It was near dusk, and I thought I heard a soft footfall.
It looked like an Indian feller walking by.
It was the little whiskey fairies.
No, it wasn't a whiskey fairy.
It was an Indian.
It was. It was us, the little whiskey fairies.
Damn it, it was.
We were tricking you.
It is the whiskey fairies.
We've been around for a long time.
Very, very long time.
We've been tricking you.
You and all the other people.
Geez, I thought you was a big medicine man coming to me in my dreams.
Yeah, me too.
I was the one who told you to beat your wife.
It wasn't the medicine man at all.
I thought I was doing Bob's will.
Man, this is a nightmare.
This is a nightmare.
Nope.
What a nightmare.
It was us, the whiskey fairies, all along.
Little whiskey fairies.
You can smell us in the morning.
I can smell the honey on your pillow.
You are my parents.
You can drink here all night.
You're so cute.
We're the ones who invented the DTs.
I love you.
Geez, you've got such soft, filmy, gossamer wings.
You ever thought there were little insects and snakes crawling all over your body?
Yeah, there was, wasn't there?
It was us, the whiskey fairies.
It wasn't so bad after all.
I guess I kind of enjoyed that soft correction.
In Mexico, they call us tequila fairies.
Tequila fairies.
I remember there was a book I never read.
Tequila Mockingbird by Herman Wook.
No, that was...
Now, wait.
Hey, who are you again?
Hey, let me have a drink of that.
Give me...
Just let me have a little drink of that.
And just like that, we'll disappear and we won't answer any more of your questions.
No, wait a minute.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Come back.
No, no, no, no, no.
We're gone.
What's happened to Dave's mind?
I don't know.
All these little voices...