A malignant cancerous growth eating at the spiritual health of the American people.
I refer to Bob.
That settles it.
We'll show this lunatic who's Bob.
Good night.
And now, let's hear what a typical housewife thinks about.
Hi out there.
And speaking of hi, I'd like to show you the...
Oh, jeez.
Hey, yes, dear friends.
Welcome to Hour of Slack number 976.
And this is a particularly unusual Hour of Slack
because we're not in our home laboratory studio
but are assembling the show in Texas at the Stang Ranch.
In fact, we're doing it all outdoors.
But, but, we're using recordings from the European Subgenius Tour
and free radio patented.
From Amsterdam.
And even some bits from Starwood Festival last year.
And yet, and yet, this is a special educational episode
on the subject of drug abuse.
Yes, we have lately seen an increase in the use
by subgenius youth
of cheap conspiracy street drugs
such as...
cigarettes, alcohol, marijuana, cocaine, LSD, television, et cetera.
And we as elder ministers in the Church of the Subgenius
are concerned.
And we intend to do something about it.
And really, I'm supposed to get off.
We're all supposed to get off, aren't we?
Earth, we must get off.
But are there any questions or anything pertinent?
That I could go...
That's always fun.
Where's all this hoo-ha?
What is all this hoo-ha?
Well, you know, that's the question that every subgenius asks itself
when it first drops that first hit of acid.
What is all this hoo-ha?
And think of all the crap that people are doing right now.
Think of all the crap that's going on in the world right at this minute.
God, I had that thought when I was a kid.
I had that thought one time.
Oh, I spent weeks writing this essay about how fragile the ecosystem was
and how we mustn't ever let nuclear weapons destroy the world and so forth.
Oh, spent weeks writing that.
Five or six people thought it was quite well written.
So, why are...
You all should have gone to see Harvey Wasserman talking about how to beat Bush.
Where is it?
Well, it's over now.
You came here instead.
You wanted slack for yourself instead of for those poor Iraqi children, you bastard.
You should feel shitty about that.
Yes, the little boy in the wig.
I'm Mel Gordo. I'm a subgenius from...
I joined in 98. I paid my $20.
I've married three couples and they're all still married.
Anyway, I got a question.
I lost a library book. It's somewhere in my basement.
Do you know where it is?
No.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Well, I was pretty quick on that one, wasn't I?
You are much better than I am on that one.
Let me tell you something, man.
I've had some real problems with people thinking I was going to be able to read their mind.
So, I'm usually the first to say,
No, I'm actually really dumb and if you have a problem, you have to tell me.
Because I can't read your mind and I don't know where your lost library book is.
I can feel you inside there, Sting. I can. I can feel you inside there.
All these kids these days, they figure, oh, I'm going to get high.
I'm going to get high and go to one of them spaced out trance-so concerts.
I'm going to get high on, you know, I'll try some of that mace mixed with DMT mixed with marijuana,
mixed with Everclear.
Man, if you want to be really cool, you'd sever the connection between your right and left brains.
Now, if you want to get buzzed on, dude,
you won't be able to tell the difference between your car and your glasses.
Reagan achieved that state without even trying.
And Bob was born that way.
If Bob actually wanted to vanquish his enemies, he'd send them a fax and they'd die from the paper cut.
Bob has, he would never kill them directly.
It was like they would end up killing themselves by some stupid error.
And die in a humiliating way without Bob's having to lift a finger.
And it would be people like, this happened to his school teachers when he was a child.
His school principal, his teacher, people, anyone who crossed him would go through this hard,
he once said, I hope you get paper cut to death.
And this teacher actually fell into the paper slicing machine at the newspaper plant
while taking the kids on a school trip through it.
That's a kind of weird effect.
When Bob was a child, he was able to do miracles, actually.
Like the baby Jesus was.
Little known fact.
He could fly.
And the infant Bob was a bank robber at the age of two.
While he was in the terrible twos, he would watch bank robbers on television.
And he flew.
And the authorities almost had to put him to death.
But, and, you know, it almost kept secret.
But you know how Bob's luck is.
Somehow, the key people all forgot the records were burned.
The courthouse burned down.
The tornado took the judge away.
This is my question, though.
Can Bob be killed?
Well, Bob has, technically Bob has been killed.
And there is a Bob corpse preserved in Lucite at the top of the old subgenius Foundation skyscraper,
which is unfortunately now owned by Sony.
We'll get that Dobbs corpse back eventually, I'm sure.
But, and, you know, I think that's a good thing.
And there is the Bob who is now out selling or fishing or whatever.
And actually all the other corpses.
There have quite a been, and the historical Bob corpses.
Mummies exist of earlier Bobs from many cultures.
There have always been salesmen, yes, of what we call snake oil.
Salesmen of faith.
Salesmen who had something.
People would pay anything for.
They sold hope.
They sold magic.
Yes.
They sold slack, essentially.
They sold the knowledge of slack.
They sold the reminder that you do have slack.
When it says the subgenius must have slack,
that doesn't mean that we don't have slack now and we misguided.
It means that to be a subgenius, you must have slack.
You must.
Little known.
Little known secret.
There's a lot of good eating on them corpse.
Mmm, gizzards.
It's good eating.
And people smoke the Bob corpses.
And the McKenna brain.
I noticed McKenna brain was going for it.
Well, I forget what it was.
Way out of my price range.
Well, there's some at one of those magic mushroom or magic whatever.
At magic smart brain shop.
McKenna brain and Bob lung.
You know, in the States,
they're now smoking dried up lung of dead heavy drug users.
It's called Lunk.
The Lunkheads are the bane of the urban.
Because, but it's actually not too bad because it's very,
you have to, it's hard to get.
You have to be in the society of Lunkheads because essentially that's the only way to get it.
You have to legally declare that your lungs are going to go to this Lunkhead society.
So that when you die, you can smoke Lunk.
Now, you know, you can get Lunk and smoke it,
but that means the next generation is going to be,
in a way, each generation gets slightly stronger Lunk.
Oh, hell, that's just too many for me.
Give me one of them drugs that's all like numbers or something.
So, friends, be careful about hard drugs.
Now, I'm a fella with a heart of gold,
the ways of a gentleman, I've been told.
The kind of a guy that wouldn't even harm a flea.
But if me and a certain character met,
the guy that invented that cigarette,
I'd murder that son of a gun in the first degree.
Now, it ain't cause I don't smoke myself,
and I don't reckon they'll harm your health.
I've smoked them all my life and ain't dead yet.
But nicotine slaves are all the same.
At a petting party or a poker party,
or a poker game, everything's gotta stop
while they smoke that cigarette.
Smoke, smoke, smoke that cigarette.
Puff, puff, puff that if you smoke yourself to death.
Tell St. Peter at the Golden Gate
that you hate to make him wait,
but you just gotta have another cigarette.
Prop is the mind killer.
That's okay, we don't need any minds.
It's a good thing, though, that prop is not a drug.
Because you'd be in terrible trouble then, surely,
if you say you have restricted drug laws.
And, you know, I think we've found some prop out here,
but it doesn't seem to be generally available.
I mean, a lot of people seem to make the mistake of thinking
that prop is the marijuana that we see
on many street corners here.
But I'm given to understand it's absolutely not the same thing.
It's a sacred herb.
If only it was, if that was prop.
But see, that would destroy the city.
It'd be like that movie 28 Days Later.
The way a normal would react to real prop
would be equivalent...
That's what the Night of the Living Dead
really is based on.
It would be like that.
So it's best that they sell...
Here in Amsterdam, they only sell
plain, ordinary, what we call dirt prop,
or, you know, the castaway.
And you can see what's happened.
There's a bowl of real prop going around,
and you can see what it's done to the city.
And you can see what's happened to the studio audience here.
Oh, damn.
Stang, stang, stang, keep it quiet.
Stang.
Stang, get...
Prop.
No, friends.
Whereas marijuana is a habit-forming, addictive drug,
prop doesn't wear off.
Never goes away.
So you only have to do it once or twice.
You can only get higher.
You can never come down.
Oh, and we should mention that it does give you a headache.
A slight headache, which will last about a year.
So just keep that in mind, kids.
As Bob said, too much is always better than not enough.
But there was actually a torn-off little section on the end
that said, but it's almost as bad.
Which doesn't sound as good, so he left it off, apparently.
It was interesting to find that life-saving.
I'll put it down here.
And find that all those alcohol overdoses by college students
excused that they thought were excused by Bob
were actually just foolishness.
Those overdoses and mental illnesses,
those were just part of the satire, Your Honor.
That was just part of the joke.
It's a religious take-off.
We're a mirror reflecting the ills in society around us.
Lenny, to quote Lenny Pierce, quoting,
what you always say to the cops,
Oh, we were making an anti-drug film, sir.
I've had to say that one several times.
Oh, and here's the one that I've had to say the most.
Well, officer, have you ever seen Mad Magazine?
That's the one I've had to say the most.
Well, officer, did you ever read Mad Magazine?
Oh, Mad, oh yeah, Alfred E. Newman, hilarious.
What do you mean?
Well, we're just comedians.
Just not as famous or as good or funny.
That's all.
Well, get out of here, you make me sick.
That's how we escape, you see.
We pretend it's all just a little joke.
We live to run away and come back,
and then he drives off with the nails in his car tires with a slow leap.
Termites set the foundation, friends.
That's what we are.
Then rats in the walls.
The rats in the walls.
The slow termites.
It's all we can do, you know.
And remember, they have poison.
So you must, they'll use to exterminate you,
so you must build up an immunity straight through disfigurement.
Go live the subgenius life and eat the subgenius industrial diet.
Get up in the morning and have some nice healthy food.
Small food, low fat toast and butter, and a big greasy sausage.
And for lunch have, eat at McDonald's and eat four rusty nails.
And drink a quart of whiskey.
Then for dinner have only the finest French restaurant food mixed with gravel.
And you can smoke a cigarette.
And drink a shot of vodka.
And go to bed.
And never ever come down and dream of Bob all night long.
I hear the tide of Bob coming in.
On and off the road to Bob
We are marching forward blind
He has gouged out both our eyes
And he's laughing close behind
He will sell us back our eyes
When we join his noble plan
For just $19.95
And a taste of our wood brand
On and off the road with Bob
He has handed us the wheel
And he cuddles up with fun
As he counts himself a field
Our eyes are on the road
But Bob forgot to say
That the steering wheel went fast
The road carries us away
On and off the road for Bob
We forgot why we came here
We have quit all of our jobs
Like a headlight frightened deer
He has lit the sacred pipe
And he's smiling at us now
On and off the road he's Bob
He's our bull dada
We are his cow
We are his sheep
We are his men
We are his bull
He's right ava
We are his sheep
search and fetch satellites
which we shot in space. They know, they're tracking
the ashes of Timothy Leary around the earth now.
They know where it is.
He's still being watched, yes.
Well, you know, he always liked the attention, I think.
I think so too, yeah. But they're actually building this
search and fetch
bots
which are going to shoot into space and fetch the ashes in order to smoke it.
They really want the ashes.
What would they do with the ashes? Snort them?
I think the easiest thing you can do with ashes is snort them.
There was a lot of other Leary brain ash
that the conspiracy had left, but the stuff apparently is really habit forming enough
that they'll send a space shuttle up to get that last few lines that were sent,
or initially just sent as a message.
It was a token gesture.
You know, a space-edness.
Uh-huh.
They should have burned, they sent his ashes up this, his brain up into space,
but they buried his heart in hell.
Actually, Princess Wee and I knew Dr. Tim.
I had to open for Dr. Tim several times when he spoke.
Yes, I had to open for him.
Well, you know, he's a big star.
He was a big star, and, and, uh, he was a big star.
And, uh, you know, we, we, uh, actually he always, he always would bum a cigarette from me.
He was always trying to quit smoking, supposedly, and would bum a cigarette.
Oh, can I get, can I get two?
And then he'd tell you about his latest new project.
And, you know, very friendly.
Actually, he was a very funny performer.
Very funny stand-up comedian.
That was what I always saw him doing.
I never read any of his books, took any of his acid.
Didn't know him.
Didn't know about that stuff until it wasn't cool anymore.
I didn't, I didn't know him until he was a stand-up comic.
Oh, that was Wavy Gravy, who's also a friend of ours.
Uh, because the Starwood Festival, see, now we can do an ad for not only X Day,
there's, uh, the Subgenius Holiday on July 5th,
which happens in Europe as well as the United States.
At this nudist campground in the U.S.
in far, in far western New York.
Far, it's not upstate.
It's far western New York.
Upstate is far north, near the, near Canada.
No.
Yeah, you've been to the wrong one.
You've been, no, there's, uh, and, uh, also there's this festival called Starwood,
which a lot of, uh, uh, hipsters, beatniks, uh, and so forth,
malcontents might be interested in,
although it's, it's partially a pagan festival,
which is heavy on the corniness.
It's also a sort of general, um, consciousness, uh, exploration festival
put on, do, put on by ACE, A-C-E,
the Association of Consciousness Exploration.
They haven't been on it for a while.
Who are they, Kraken the Poor?
I think we went to the wrong one.
Uh, www.rosencomic.com,
and that's how we met all those famous dead drug users.
We, we knew, uh, and Terence McKenna spoke out there,
and Pope Bob, Robert Anton Wilson, has been there several times.
So, this, this is how we know the ancient creaking, uh, forefathers
of, uh, heavy, heavy psychedelic use,
whose brains we now, and body parts we now try to buy smoke.
Stuff they sell on the street is not really Leary Brain or McKenna Gland or...
Oh, this stuff's awesome.
Yeah.
I promise you, the, uh, the stang, the stang-gleet that you see advertised on the internet
is not real.
That's somebody else's gleet.
I'm afraid I can prove it, too.
We have...
Oof, alright, we're going for another drink.
anyway, I那個...
Nothing good happened.
Okay.
So, Far parsley, thanks for your help OH MY GOD
Thisすごynчик
This 650S thing I really know.
Oh wow, the guy who stole the money
Great.
was from Reverend Artemia Salina.
And before that, we've been listening to some clips
from Reverend Lord Yeti's free radio patapoo in Amsterdam
with Pope Mickey Finn and Lord Yeti, Carl X, and others.
The song, On and Off the Road to Bob,
was by Reverend Bleepo Abernathy.
Smoke That Cigarette was, well, to tell the truth,
it just says hillbilly on my notes.
I don't know who that was.
And the ranting, the ranting at the very beginning
was yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang,
preaching at Starwood 24 last summer
with titles by Mr. Fernandanande Lemaire.
Now, friends, about these drugs,
there is such a thing as too much,
and we have the tapes to prove it.
The European subgenius Taurus,
or is organized by subgenius Pope David Lee Black,
a former American.
And in some of the rare recordings to come,
you'll hear examples of what happens
to even the soberest sacred scribe and space princess
when they attempt to follow one such as Pope Black.
¶¶
I'm trying to control my motor skills and I'll click in my chair without a care.
I've got this, you're standing there.
A couple of lines, lines of Akatak.
I have a ton of chronic smoke tonight.
I feel alright.
Have it or do not.
Pathetic.
Just pathetic, friends.
Well, that's the name of the band that did that piece of music.
Pathetic.
Yes, pills are bad.
Unless they're the good pills.
And luckily we had those pills in Europe.
But sometimes pills aren't enough.
But look at Kurt Cobain.
Sometimes pills, millions of dollars, fame, bimbos and heroin aren't enough.
I have to lodge a complaint now.
Since I'm with the High Subgenius Council, I want to lodge a serious complaint.
I don't know if I want to come over here and do a Deval tomorrow.
Why is that, David?
I don't want to do that.
You know why I don't want to do it?
But we like this place. Why not? Why wouldn't you?
Because Kai comes up to me and he goes,
I can only offer you guys two cases of beer and three bottles of vodka tomorrow.
And that's all I can do.
No! We won't accept those terms.
We want to accept those terms.
Ten cases of vodka.
God damn it!
God damn it! I can't bear to do a Deval in this place here with that pittance they're offering us for alcohol.
Can you imagine? Somebody has given us a place to stay and then expects us to just turn up and be paid that?
It's a dry spot to sleep.
They're taking the piss.
This is the worst, this is the worst, worst in the thousand summers in America where you can't get any weed because it's dry.
Hey, last time I was paid in London.
I was paid in London for lottery tickets.
Come on.
They were used.
Why isn't the question mark over the exclamation point?
That's what I want.
Yeah?
Ladies and gentlemen, you know what?
The most faithful of the church of the sub-genius and those who believe in Bob are still standing here now.
I have witnessed the whole damn evening people running in and out and in and out of this place.
People talking amongst themselves.
What?
People are preaching the word of Bob because they do not care about Bob.
They're still talking and they don't care about Bob.
Well, my friends, there's one thing that I would like to say to you right now.
Do not turn your back.
Do not turn your back on J.R. Bob Dobbs because this is what will happen to you.
Do I hear a praise?
Praise Bob!
Do I hear a praise Bob?
Now, without further ado, ladies and gentlemen, all the way from Zwolle, Netherlands, the Reverend Lucky Bastard.
You can clap now.
You can cheer.
Come on.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, ladies and gentlemen, I just need us to take a piss.
And when I was taking a piss, I jumped down and I smacked my head on the ground.
I mean on the floor.
It's called the ceiling.
So I smacked my head on the ceiling.
I fell down.
I'm a real jackass, but that's subgenius.
But, you know, the conspiracy's been eating my words every fucking day.
In Holland now, we have no freedom.
No!
You say something and they're gonna kill you.
They're gonna say...
They're gonna slit your throat.
When subgenius hits his head on the head on the ceiling, it means something.
It means that...
That unoriginal happens to original.
I've been brain damaged and hypnotized by the conspiracy.
I've been acting not like I used to be.
Slack, what is it?
Why this?
I don't know what it is
because Slack has been taken away from me every fucking day.
Slack is taken away.
Then I take a vauban, and everything goes back to normal.
Am I normal?
I don't think so.
I totally fuck up.
Totally because the conspiracy fucks me up.
My name's DJ Konicat. Not for nothing.
I smoke everything, because I smoke lungs every day, I take every fucking drug there is, and anyways, I'm screwed up.
Not because I'm a subgenius, but because the conspiracy wants me to be screwed up.
And Bob is the only guy who can screw my ass.
I'm a bit brain damaged from hitting the scene just now when I was taking a piss.
But that's all because the conspiracy programmed me with some kind of nanotechnology they have, which I know, and only subgenius knows.
That was Reverend Lucky Bastard from Holland at the Foundry in London, that's where he was ranting.
Ranting while with an actual concussion.
He really did bonk his head on some pipes.
And was ranting.
Ranting with a concussion.
So you see, altered consciousness can come in so many ways.
You don't have to take drugs.
Like Reverend Lucky Bastard, you can just slam your head against metal pipes.
Also, that's your other possibility.
Anyway, let's go back to the European subgenius tapes and this delightful moment from the D-Vival in Germany at the Fundbüro in Hamburg.
All I give a shit about is Bob.
All I give a shit about is being Bob and us doing one more song together.
Because you're a bunch of fucking fashion maggots and I hate all of you.
Just like Ninslo with me.
I fucking hate you.
I hate everybody in this place.
Look at you.
You're walking around and you're posturing.
Posturing.
You're fucking posturing.
Posturing trying to be somebody you're not.
Fuck you.
Fuck you and everybody else you wrote into your goddamn fabric.
Fine.
Get out of my church if you want to.
That is tremendous.
It really is.
It's Pope Black in the flowing light.
With Bob pulling his zipper down.
Praise Bob!
Is anybody getting any alcohol?
You drank it all.
What happened to that six pack of vodka?
Yeah, well that's his.
We've only been through two bottles of it now.
That's what I thought.
I think Kai is rationing the vodka to us because he knows the minute that he gets it
on him it'll be gone the next day.
Kai is brilliant.
Kai's touch is not felt.
He steers us but he steers you away.
He's the perfect host for it.
He's really into the office.
He really is.
This is his place.
He is the dream host.
He sets us on the right track but steers us away.
He gets us hookers that we don't even have to pay for.
He gets us hookers that we don't even remember fucking.
He gets us hookers that don't necessarily exist.
That's what bothers me.
Meta cyber hookers.
Ethereal hookers.
Meta ethereal hookers.
Oh yay, but we walked the valley of shame last night but we feared no evil because we
were slacker than any other motherfucker in the video series.
Actually, I have to admit I feared a little evil.
Well, we feared a tiny amount of pickpocketing but I don't know if that's the same thing.
It didn't happen though.
The octopus.
Why the fuck do we need people to pick our pockets when I can just go drop money on the
floor when I'm fucking everyone.
Hell man.
Free.
You get me drunk enough.
You've got the contents of my bank account.
I didn't drop money yet.
I think the number is.
Oh really?
It's terrible.
I'm sitting here.
I've got to smoke all this.
All this.
Drink all this.
It's just me.
Oh, it was you that drank it all.
It was you.
I thought Bob, I heard Bob was here.
I thought maybe it was him that had done this.
Hopefully we got some kind of a recording for what that's worth.
It was a recording.
Yes, it's a recording of something.
Here's to Germany Land town.
Yes, Germany Land town.
Germany Land town was cool thanks to the aforementioned Kai.
And after Germany Land town we went to Amsterdam.
And preached at the butt kite to the legal pot smokers.
The Nederlandertals we call them of Holenhepp land.
Friends, if Bob said it, then you better pick up on it.
If Bob says that traffic light is green and it looks red to you, which do you trust man?
Close your eyes and pump the gas.
You do what Bob said no matter what your mind says.
Who do you trust?
Your mind or your heart?
Your mind or your heart.
You better get that part straight first friend.
But some people fear to trust Bob and I don't blame them.
We've all been burned at one point because we trusted the conspiracy or else we wouldn't
be so screwed up today.
But really, if you can't trust Bob, who can you trust?
Anyway, surely there's a, my friends, let me, I'm so pleased to introduce, Jesus couldn't
be with us today.
Why?
Because he got a new job and had to move to Georgia.
But, Columbus, Georgia I'm afraid.
But, friends, the father of Jesus, yes, Joseph himself, the most famous cuckold of almost
perhaps of history, Joseph.
Hello, thanks for coming out, friends, brethren, uberfems, yeti, bear with me one minute, I
lost my cordless microphone, so.
This is what we're going to do.
I'm not really going to rant tonight because like Reverend Ivan Staggs said, it's no use
preaching to the enlightened.
So, thanks for coming out tonight.
You know, this is the anal frock of the Anans Band.
It is true that it is becoming tighter and tighter every day, the conspiracy, the conspiracy
putting shackles on all of us.
We can't even have frock at the frock cup.
More and more it happens, you can't even smoke frock on the streets.
You can't even roll frock on the streets at coffee shops.
You can't even smoke frock on the terraces of coffee shops.
Soon enough you can't smoke frock anywhere.
We cannot let this happen.
No!
The subgenius must have froth.
We must have froth.
But it is not Bob's pipe that is important. It's what's in the pipe.
Woo!
Hey!
I can't just sit and sing. Give me all the psychic energy.
Eat flowers and kiss babies.
L.S.B. for you and me.
There's one thing, friends, that's more powerful than human belief.
You know, when a person really believes something, they can heal illnesses they have.
You know, like faith healing.
Some people have faith in Jesus and that cures them.
I'm the kind of... I used to think, oh gosh, I'm so faithless I could never...
If I had some dreadful dream, I could never...
If I had some dreadful disease, I couldn't undergo faith healing.
And then I realized, no, I have faith.
I was taught to have faith in high doctor bills.
If I get a high enough bill from the doctor, my faith is such that it just might save me.
But there's... and that is the power of the human mind.
But there's something far more powerful than your belief or your mind.
And that is your ego!
Your ego is so good at tricking your mind.
It's so much better.
Your mind is so much better at tricking your mind.
Your mind cannot even guess how much trickier that ego is.
In fact, your ego makes your mind think that it's winning just by sweet talking it.
And the next thing you know, you're nothing but ego, telling everybody else how to run their own minds and lose their egos.
As the great rapper, Poop Bobby Bob, said one time, the pink boy's got a bob complex.
And so you see these new age gurus and philosophers,
and so forth, trying to give you ever more complicated rule books about how to run your life.
Well, friends, I'm sorry, but they just didn't give us an instruction book for this.
So we have to ask ourselves, is it all bluff?
Are there no solid answers?
Or are we all just bluffing ourselves, kidding ourselves?
Is the wise guru bluffing himself just so that he can inspire others?
The Gurdjieff said that that's the first pitfall.
But was he just saying that because it sounded wise?
So it's easy to learn the semblance of enlightenment, you know, the trappings of cool knowledge, and so forth.
And it's easy to... all you really need is impenetrably flighty jargon punctuated by pregnant pauses and flattery,
and lying by omissions and suggestions,
providing rule books as if there really was fairness in the world
for lazy thinkers who want to believe that they're actually thinkers.
And that brings me to the problem of subgenius coots.
Yes, I know it's hard to believe, but there actually occasionally are coots...
Crazy people in the Church of the Subgenius.
GREETINGS TO THE SNOW
sometimes, sometimes
is so obviously
telling kooks what they
must want to believe that
only a kook would believe it.
And plenty did, my friends.
Plenty did. Unfortunately,
none of them were really rich.
And so there's all of these
gurus and therapists
and experts trying
to tell you how to be more enlightened.
Maybe they're really
impeding your slack because
you have to figure it out
for yourself. Unless you're a dumbass
in which case you have to pay me
or Bob. But
friends, you know, the only
sign of
getting old, really, is
that after a while
you're not sure you're right.
Being more sure that you're right
is a sign of being stupid,
not getting old. But the
subgenius, my friends, is luckier
and better than that. I'll tell you
my friend, Bob Dobbs
healed me! Bob
healed me! He put his
living fist up my
butt and he healed
my ass!
Healed my ass!
That's why I say, friend,
sometimes you find that it's the path
less traveled for a reason.
Believe me, I know, because I'm
an expert on, uh,
whatchamacallit.
So, uh,
you know, the media
is constantly trying to
trick us. You know, it's
so hard to tell what's hidden
behind the headlines in the news
and what those guys are saying, those news
men are saying on TV.
War, the phrase
war in the Middle East
really means
two-for-one sale at Walmart.
And,
friends, there's a war on
drugs on Mars!
And you don't
know about it yet!
But as a
father, um, the father
of Jesus, Joseph, was
saying, we must protect our rights to
even fuck ourselves up.
Do-gooders
will be the death of us,
I'm afraid, uh,
trying to, uh,
telling us what's for
our own good.
It's funny how helpful
fascism can become.
Drugs don't
blow minds.
People blow minds!
Praise Bob!
And, uh, we, some of us
enjoy changing the channels inside
of our head every now and then.
We don't want to watch the
common hit show every night,
so to speak. Uh, Princess
Wee and I have managed to
whittle our brains down to one
brain cell, which we share.
I have one half and she has the other
half. It's, uh, we call it
his and her brains.
Uh, and, uh,
she's the one who can
understand
things, and I'm the one who remembers
them. But, uh,
as long as we're together, we're not exactly,
you know, we're still better off
than the subgenius kook.
The kook sees things
that aren't really there.
Not things that aren't there,
but we do that when we smoke too much
frog.
They don't see things that aren't there
so much as connections
that aren't there.
You know, speed freaks and religious
nuts both will see,
uh, connections between things that most of us
don't even notice because we're not
crazy. That's the reason we don't
notice. I hate to be up here
promoting sanity, but, uh,
uh, to tell the truth, I'm tired
of having to deprogram
our own zombies!
You know what I mean?
We sold these
kooks the insanity
and now we
must sell them the
cure. And with that,
I, uh, would direct you
to our sales table.
Now that we have made you completely
mad, there is a
the cure is back
there. The more
Bob shit you buy,
the sooner you will
get tired of him and be free
from his mind control.
You must free yourself
from Bob! Or come and free
the less Americans from the evil
dictator Bush!
We do a radio show.
Uh, it's syndicated to a few
stations in the U.S., about
15 college stations.
They're the only ones that are free
to say the foul
and awful things that we say.
Uh, we also find music
that people don't normally hear
or we dig, we, uh,
excavate fossilized music
that people haven't heard in a long,
long time. Great
bulldog, we call it.
The sort of thing that the pink,
the normal thinks,
crazy or trashy,
low class, ah,
that is where we sometimes find
the truth, in the label
of a wine bottle or the
ads in the back of a comic book.
And that cheesy
trash has, is still
on that table, unsold!
And it's cheap!
And yet, friends,
what worth
insanity, or a cure for the insanity
which we just infected you with,
earlier tonight, when
Joseph, the father of Jesus,
was pretending to have technical trouble
and had turned on that
random noise sound,
at that moment,
you were being programmed
with an insane, fanatical attachment
to Bob. You may not think that's
your boy, but
the only cure for it
is to go back there and
free yourself from that which
has enslaved you. You're a
slave to money! So,
you must free yourself from the money!
The chains of money!
Just as I smashed
Bob Black's watch, or
an Ultraloy Black's watch,
then, just so,
you can free yourself by smashing
that money that holds
you as a slave. Smash it!
By giving it to Bob!
You see, Bob doesn't
want you so much to
buy from him,
he wants you to
spend on him.
See what I mean when I say,
you know, it's not queer if it's Bob.
Spend on Bob!
Until you have
nothing left to spend,
until you're all dry.
And we mean spend in
every sense of the word.
So, dribble on Bob,
or spray on Bob.
If you have only a tiny little bit of money,
then the best you can do is
pop out a little
half-hearted load. That's fine!
You know, Dr. Philo Drummond,
of the Co-Sub Foundation,
founder of the church,
and other main tool of Bob,
originally, besides myself,
he said,
who does Bob love the most?
The rich man who
gives Bob $10,000,
even though he could
give him a million,
or the little old lady
who has only
one dollar left to her name,
and yet she gets it to Bob.
Who does Bob love?
The rich man!
Even though he gave a tiny fraction,
even though he's a hypocrite,
a liar, and a cheater,
he gave Bob more!
He spent on Bob!
Fuck the old lady!
Fuck goddamn Mother Teresa,
and all those saints!
Did they do anything for Bob? No!
Mother Teresa will burn in hell!
And late Princess Diana
will burn in hell!
Because they might have tried to do good things
by their silly human notions,
but they did not believe in Bob,
and they adapt you to Bob,
that which is Bob's due!
Render unto Bob
that which is Bob's!
And if it includes punishment,
remember,
I'm just his clerk.
I'm just a PR hack,
I just work here.
So, um...
Leave it to Dave.
And in fact, I'm...
It's time for me to go.
See, I still have a watch.
That's what I preach,
because I'm not the kind of man I'm preaching to.
That's what Bob said.
And it's an excuse.
That's part of the great, all-encompassing excuse
that allows us...
Well, look, let me put it this way.
I'm a holy man.
I'm a reverend in the Church of Subgenius.
That means I have magic powers.
So, by the power
invested in me by J.R. Bob Gobs,
you may now
do anything
you want, forever!
Woo!
O...
Lloyd.
Lloyd...
is...
terrified...
you...
about
prophet.
So what do you want from me now?
The compute chanting there was by Artemia Salina.
And now let's hear a subgenius devival in progress.
In this case, led by Pope Black at the Foundry in London.
Ladies and gentlemen, for the last, most sacred ritual
in our beloved Church of the Subgenius.
Not many...
Shut up!
I've got something to say.
This is the last ritual of the Church of the Subgenius for this evening.
It's the most sacred one.
And brothers and sisters, it is why I carry this golf club.
Yes, yes my friends, we are going to do what?
What are we going to do?
Launch the Head!
Launch the Head , Lensive Head
Yes my friends!
We are going to launch, not just a head, but my friends, the minute this non-arm hits
this little plush devil toy.
It doesn't turn into just a plush devil toy.
It turns into the bleeding head of the future of World Cup golfing and this is what keeps
the world imploding around you.
And it's a very, very sacred ritual in the Church of the Subjugates.
Could I have complete quiet please?
Silence!
May I have silence?
Shut up!
Are you ready?
Now before I get started there's one thing I forgot.
Shut up!
There's one thing I forgot and those who are talking won't hear this because, and this
is the most important thing I've said all evening.
The person who catches the head of the future, bleeding head of the future of World Cup golfing
gets seven.
Seven.
Seven years good sex!
Do it here, praise Bob!
Praise Bob!
May I have a drum roll please?
Drum roll!
I need a drum roll everybody!
I need a drum roll!
Come on!
Everybody!
Drum roll!
One.
Two.
Three.
Four!
One.
Two.
We have a winner!
Ladies and gentlemen, seven years, good sex,
do I hear a praise, Bob?
What's your name?
Joe Anita!
Joe Anita, praise Joe Anita!
Seven years, good sex, praise Bob!
Thank you for coming!
Hallelujah!
Goodnight!
And now it's time for me to get back to my roots.
I was feeling sick, losing my mind,
heard about this stupid from a good friend of mine,
he was always happy, smiling face,
he said he had a great time at the play, yeah!
That piece of love is here to stay,
and now I can wake up and face the day,
happy, happy, happy, overdive,
Jackson, bitch, I'm going blind!
Gimme, gimme, Jackson, give it!
I wanna, wanna, Jackson, give it!
I was feeling sick, losing my mind,
heard about this stupid from a good friend of mine,
he was always happy, smiling face,
he said he had a great time at the play, yeah!
That piece of love is here to stay,
pinning, man, that was envie,
that paper, paper, paper...
Ya, that was what it said,
No!
Gimme, gimme, Jackson, give it!
on whether chances for recovery are poor.
For TR News, I'm in densely forested areas
to prevent rebel guerrillas from seeking New Delhi.
Doctors say he has fallen two points to 10,001.
Make that 35.
This is TR News.
The U.S. Supreme Court can sniff your drugs.
Yasser Arafat caught fire on takeoff,
then dumped at about 12.15 this morning.
I'm stepping down after studies showed
that it increased the risk of TR News in Washington.
Beaver, Beaver, Beaver, Beaver, Beaver, Caraboo,
Caraboo, Beaver, Beaver, Beaver, Cara-Boo,
Beaver, Beaver, Cara-Boo, Cara-Boo.
The caraboo come to this water hole.
Caraboo, Caraboo, Cara-Boo,
Herbie may out.
Drink blog.
The Caribou and the Beaver by Imbejur.
That's how you pronounce I-M-B-J-R, by the way.
Before that, some Lemurian PR news.
And before that, Little Theodore did shock treatment.
I believe that was recorded live at 7X Day.
8X Day is coming up this July.
And now, something weird from Artemia Salida.
I-M-B-J-R.
hi
Thank you.
And that zip code is 44118.
And now some words from Popes Lillith.
Job is an alien.
As so such is this planet.
We shall have paradise.
Subgenie of the world unites.
Alien sex every night.
Subgenie of the world.
Subgenie of the world unites.
Stand hand in hand.
When the trumpet calls.
I'll make stand.
Global access to fan.
While we blow the world away.
We shall have paradise.
Subgenie of the world unites.
Alien sex every night.
Subgenie of the world.
Subgenie of the world unites.