Oh my, oh, oh, wait a minute, wait a minute, he's not dead, he's not, like that.
And now, the subgenius hour of SWAC!
I sometimes feel that I am impersonating the dark subconscious of the whole human race.
I love the smell of my cum in the morning.
You'd much rather have us happy and satisfied, believe.
Smells like...
Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
I hate you.
Oh, oh, oh renovation Sorry, REVENGE
Theultricémon
Ah, yes, dear friends, that new itchy and slacky music at the top was by Reverend Artemia Salino.
And, well, folks, I put this show together last night, April 7th.
It's made from three weeks' worth of The War shows.
And this morning I got up and they were yanking down that big statue of San Jose,
effectively making this show instantly out of date.
Luckily, thanks to time control, I had already mixed a segment on time control into this show.
See, Bob always brings an excuse.
And Fernanda Nandeli-Murr always brings the collages.
They go in between.
The ESPN.
And this time we also have a running collage by champion Jack Codini
and some mystery clips culled by Reverend Inkpay Ispay.
And, as well, we have the world premiere of excerpts from Obsessions for Oil by Halim Eldab.
Seriously, Halim Eldab.
You'll be able to tell which one is which.
Which parts, those are my friends.
Anyway, again, this show is, well, it was assembled just before the fall of Baghdad on April 8th.
So take your medicine accordingly.
From NPR News in Washington, I'm a mysterious pneumonia-like illness.
The disease has afflicted more than 150 cunts in the U.S.
A summit meeting in Washington.
President Dick Cheney's butt prefers to characterize today's meeting as a last-ditch effort at a mysterious butt illness.
NPR's Don Gagne prefers Dick Cheney's butt with deadly gas.
White butt.
They have tried to stretch it out as far as they can.
That's why the British proposed this is a butt for them to come and to come again to country.
NPR's Don Gagne reporting sores.
The German foreign ministry has issued a sore dick for all Germans comedially.
German officials also plan to close its butt once all Germans have left safely.
Saying butt inspectors should be given more cunts to do their jobs.
Israeli Prime Minister Ariel Sharon has vowed to retaliate if Iraq's butt strikes Israel.
According to Sharon, the threat of butts is low and Israel has the support of U.S. cunts.
Palestinian butt doctors say an American woman reports.
Palestinian doctors laying in front of a Palestinian house.
Dumped a large quantity of cotton on head and chest wounds.
International peace activists from Europe and America regularly attempt to strip by tunnel.
Israel says it carries out Palestinian Peter smuggled in from Egypt by butt.
The army said it was due to alerts about possible dicks against cunts.
You're listening to cunt Peter butt dick news.
You know that um, you know that, you know, you know, you know.
You know.
You're on.
Yeah, man, I know.
Uh, you know.
You know.
Come on, you know.
But, but, but, um, uh, uh, uh.
You know.
But, but.
By virtue of the way she's used her mouth.
Uh, that's so hard.
I have a message for the people of Iraq.
It is.
Go home and die.
If you talk to an individual when the flashback is occurring.
The American flag.
Actually believe.
Corporate scandals.
That it is occurring.
Recession.
Right then and right there.
If I hit ten divisions.
He's having a flashback.
I'm a businessman.
Oh.
Then our troubles here would be over.
Doc's town would be ours.
We have five nuclear weapons.
Beep.
We were witnessed.
Beep. Beep. Beep. mixed, mixed, mixed.
confirmation,
subversion,
Beep. Beep. Bible,
Beep, Beep, Bible.
umen eagle,
and lastly,
and later on,
past few hours.
This is certainly a decisive and important step in which we fly about attacking the Republicans.
A three pronged bag which has been encircled by British correspondents.
Uh, duh, um, um, uh, duh, because special biological bags they need, you know, to peanut
whirr, uh.
Well everybody's heard about the BBC in London.
Set aside a small supply of canned goods.
They're safe from radioactivity.
Have a good flashlight on hand.
Electric lights may go out.
Keep a first aid kit and learn how to stop bleeding.
Well, tell us about your adventures in London.
During the war, Dave?
Well first I was, I was captured very early.
They asked us to try and like, we were.
Dave, what platoon have you been embedded into?
Um, SAC Wing Command.
It's kind of a bird thing you wouldn't understand.
It has to do with plasma.
It has to do with plasm, the ether.
And it also has to do with reading the minds of the enemy.
Wow, that's the real, the real super cool secret, PSYOPs, right?
Yeah, I know.
PSY, PSYOPs.
Yeah, I was never understood what PSYOPs were.
PSYOPs were until I was in doctrine.
Now I'm a 33 degree, um, durd, durdmation too.
That explains the breath.
Well that's because, that's a true thing.
To become a full initiate and to learn all the handshakes, you do have to lick a foulest
animal's ass.
And it's called capitalism.
No, I'm just kidding.
I'm just kidding.
That's a joke, right, Dave?
That is way a joke, man.
That is way a complete and total freaking joke, man.
You're just making fun of those pinkos, those commies.
Those war, those.
They're a protester, peacenik, hippie, a dippy, a dippity.
She hard!
The Cold War's over.
Well, finally those capitalist pigs will pay for their crimes, eh?
Hey comrades, eh?
Austin, we won.
Oh groovy, smashing, yay capitalism.
Is there one leader that we should be most worried about?
Uh, well, uh, George Bush.
Uh, just, uh, I saw him announce with one of those, uh, mass murder cases.
So, uh, he was involved with, uh, that's why he's, uh, had, uh, serious war crimes in,
uh, Iraq.
Yeah.
Trying to, uh, create some, uh, minor laryngitis or some permanent laryngitis against my campaigns,
uh, committed by the CIA and, uh, Bill Clinton's and, uh, just our former presidents, uh, George
Washington's and, uh, Benjamin Franklin with some resurrections that were, uh, top secret,
uh, behind closed doors in Washington.
Those are, uh, quintological galaxies and, uh, alphatronic, uh, rocket vacations and,
uh, humanoid, uh, space vacations.
Some are quadrilogical, uh, uh, chemical, uh, war crimes with, uh, some are tetralogical
cosmopolitans, uh.
The U.S. imperialist aggression against oppressed peoples of the planet.
Ghosts.
Speeches and books.
Hey, Joe, the president's speech.
We will gain the inevitable triumph, so help us God.
But what about those empty beer cans?
Those who wield them are ruthless and daring.
And I should like to see this nation turn out at least 50,000.
50,000?
Yeah.
Listen, this country can turn out 4 million.
We have to.
We can turn out 14 million!
But now we have only half enough of them.
For beyond the horizon lay the British Navy to police these vast and now empty beer cans
filled with menace for French dummies and a supply of fine beer.
And what had we done with it?
First, to those empty unguarded beer cans.
We would rather see London taste.
and abjectly enslaved.
Then the unbelievable again.
And down she goes.
Well, while you're standing here
joking around, our troops are
in the most horrible, horrible environment.
What if it was all media, Stang?
Huh?
What if it was all a big media gag?
There were no casualties.
There were no even Iraqi irregulars.
Except for the ones that couldn't go
and had to take Metamucil.
So it'd be like heaven.
It'd just be like Burning Man.
It would be like heaven.
It would be exactly like Burning Man.
And just like Burning Man,
there would still be the strange
psyops creeps walking around,
taking pictures of people,
asking strange questions.
Playing the weird music.
What do you think Dr. Legume
is doing here tonight?
What are you doing here tonight?
Playing your weird music?
Am I here tonight?
Yeah, this is tonight.
Dr. Legume is ex-military.
That's right.
Very ex-military.
I remember Dave.
Dave was with the 34th R.E.M.F. Battalion.
The R.E.M.F.
The R.E.M.F. Battalion.
The Felch Battalion.
No, I was not with the Felch Battalion.
I couldn't pass basic.
It was like passing a stone.
R.E.M.F. is a rear echelon motherfucker.
That's what it is?
That's what R.E.M.F. stands for?
Yeah.
It's like...
Dr. Legume, you're lying.
You're lying.
It's my language.
I apologize.
I apologize to any mothers out there who I may have unintentionally...
Snafu.
What's snafu is?
My crudisms and my ghetto talk.
Your crudities.
That was really quite offensive.
What does snafu mean?
Military guy.
Situation normal.
All right.
Yeah.
Of course, we know Dave was with the Medical Corps specializing in personal hygiene.
I was a cop.
He was a combat proctologist.
He was expelled from the military after the hoof and mouth incident.
He was arrested in 1992.
Well, how do you think they synthesized the original anthrax strainers?
Some of them were used for spaghetti and the rest were used for our own medical corps'
luxury.
So, were you the guy that did the SSA?
R.
the oil ads. We're off to Iran
to take the rest of the oil ads.
We're off to North Korea to take whatever that is.
We're pirates of the Persian Gulf.
Pirates of the Persian Gulf.
We're going ashore to grab some
Iraqi booty and take it back
to God's country, Texas.
That kickin' camel booty and firin'
broadsides from the Gulf.
God has come to me and shown me
a vision, and he said to me that
every Iraqi should have
the right, the opportunity
in this life to have a hamburger
handed to them through their car window.
To own a brand new SUV.
To live and share
in this beautiful condominium.
To have high-definition television.
To have digital, digital
plus high-resolution
computers.
5,000 channels
over the Iraqis.
And 5,000 gallons of donkey pus
all the way to the 70s.
And wait till they see those great new
Iraqi Muslim
stroke film channels
that we're gonna give them.
Oh yeah, the repressed people
cut loose, you'll see the
finest porn.
Centuries of built-up
oozing and spunking.
They're gonna rebuild the Tower of Babel
and make it look like a big dick.
Watch the Nashville channel.
Yeah, sure they protest now, but wait till those folks
are living the life of freedom and luxury
in the state of New Texas.
That's right, New Texas.
Home of more...
More than steers and queers,
now we got candles and beard.
Come on out to Georgia's
No Pork Barbecue.
That's right, at Georgia's
No Pork Barbecue, not only is the
Saudi royal family quite welcome
at all times, but there's no pork served
ever, never, no, we don't eat no pig here.
We cut steaks from the
finest fatted calves.
That's right, Babylonian
fatted calf.
We don't eat...
Is that perfectly right?
Right.
Acres.
Parcels cheaper than you can imagine
in New Texas.
Sign up now.
And after dinner, come on down to Knockers.
We'll be using that excess oil
to oil down a couple camels
and let the girls have at them.
You'll be singing the yellow rose of
Bostra when you try on some of these
naughty, naughty ladies.
You'll be so happy you'll hurt your goat.
Oh, see?
Come on over here, all.
Knock, man.
And don't be afraid of me.
I ain't gonna cut off your head.
That's right.
Every day is barbecue day.
Hey, shove off and get your own, mate.
Thanks and shred.
Yes.
All this and more for the amazingly low
price of only, say,
what, maybe 50,000 lives this time?
50, 60?
Small price to pay for freedom.
Oh, screw those soldiers.
And 72 billion dollars.
Screw those soldiers out in the
Gulf.
hell with them.
That's what I say.
They volunteered for the shittiest
job in the world.
And by God, now they've got to do
it.
They must have known what they were
getting into.
You know, I really.
They did.
They volunteered.
I was there.
I volunteered once for the
shittiest job in the world.
But Bob was with me.
Some would say they were talking
I just happened to slide in there
during one of those short periods
when we weren't trying to kill
someone.
How come you're not still in the
military, Dr.
Lucky?
Because it's the shittiest job in
the world.
Well, Reverend Stang, aren't you listening?
And you fled, my politician.
I got smart.
Who else would just be sent out and...
Who else would volunteer for a job like that?
But the lowest of society's poor and uneducated.
But you got all those free implants and stuff.
Yeah, you got a chip in the back of your head.
We ain't got no digital angel, man.
We're all semi-normal and stuff.
Well, you know, the drugs and everything, but, you know.
Hey, what do you think old George Bush is taking, man?
He glows like a big dog when he does his speeches lately,
and he looks confused as hell.
What is that stuff?
I think it's Ibogaine.
Ibogaine?
Ibogaine, yeah.
Ibogaine, what?
Ted Muskie used to be hooked on that stuff.
What the hell is it?
Is it like, you know, a European drug?
Too much acid, man.
It's the downfall of every world leader.
They make it from chihuahua glee.
Officer, you're too late.
I've seen it all.
You have?
I can explain everything.
You don't have to.
I don't.
Don't worry.
There's nothing illegal about any of this.
Are you sure?
Of course.
This is America.
I see.
It's a free country.
Don't you know that?
I didn't know it was that free.
Secretary of State Powell will play up information to incite fear about Iraq's links to terrorist groups.
In all these efforts, however, America's purpose is more than to follow a process.
It is to achieve a result.
The end of the civilized world.
Dave, if you support the troops, is that the same as supporting the president?
I'm confused about this issue, too, because I sure as hell don't support W.
Right.
Although I don't see no reason why somebody I know from down the street should get his head shot off,
because he's in Iraq now.
Well, but here's the thing.
At one point or another, somebody's going to say, well, what does that mean?
You'd rather have them Iraqis shoot our boys than us boys shoot them Iraqis?
Oh, yeah.
I'd rather have the Iraqis invade us, because either way, it's a good idea.
You know, I mean, it's so exasperating, isn't it, Steve?
It is exasperating.
Chaz, haven't you felt kind of exasperated over the last two weeks?
I'm tired of this one.
I want to, you know, let's go down with Iran now.
I heard that.
I'm tired.
I heard Iraq's a done deal.
Let's get on with Iran.
Well, just kick Syria.
We'll step on Syria on the way to Iran.
Syria's definitely got some shit kicking coming their way.
And then North Korea, and then Canada.
Well, the ultimate dumb down now is that these right-wing jocks have got people going, China,
next step, man.
We're going to make China.
Okay.
Obsessions.
Oil.
Obsessions for oil.
Germ warfare can wipe out an entire city.
Nothing could be further from the truth.
Biological warfare?
You're wrong.
You had better find out the facts about biological warfare or BW.
BW.
chests are big enough to capture a lifetime of fish all Environments.
We're right.
Get a copy of this official booklet at the first attorney's gadget.
Do your part.
And we can successfully combat biological warfare.
Robins will wear their feathery fire
Whistling their whims on the low fence wire
And no one will know of war
Not one will care
At last, when it is done
Not one would mind
Neither bird nor tree
If mankind perished utterly
And spring herself, when she awoke at dawn
Would scarcely know that we were gone
Bye-bye, planet Earth
Bye-bye, Mother Earth
Hey, babe!
Life after man
Well, you know the best thing that we can do
Is get those little red children together
In a pile, in a sprue
In a place where we can divvy out our oriental secrets
And slam them where it needs to be slammed
The little red children?
Are you talking about the Martians
In the Chinese Martian colony of moon miners?
The ones who influence our daily behavior
With a big pulsating bio-phonic thing
That changes our thoughts
From Mars that's directed towards
Our planet Earth
And our brain
Kick it open
Those bastards!
Rotten Martian bastards!
That has to do with getting...
A spirit of national masochism prevails
Encouraged by an effete core of impudent snobs
Who characterize themselves as intellectuals
Wow, just doing my job
Did you know that the first Matrix
Was designed to be a perfect human world
Where none suffered?
Where everyone would be happy
It was a disaster
No one would accept the program
Entire crops were lost
Some believed that we lacked the programming language
To describe your perfect world
But I believe that as a species
Human beings define their reality
Through misery and suffering
The perfect world is a dream
That your primitive cerebrum kept trying to wake up from
Which is why the Matrix was redesigned to this
The peak of your civilization
The Matrix
Mommy is going to get similar
It's though you're crazy
United is how I feel
The Matrix
It's taught to the many
money fear money anger money war business
i'm afraid
the first job is to look over your own home for shelter possibilities
if you live in a private home that is well built
you can live in a private home that is well built
the cellar is the safest place to be
the lower you get the more barriers there are likely to be
against blast, heat and radioactivity
select the basement wall nearest the probable target area of your city
if the house is blown over
it will most likely fall away from this wall
you can get fired for being anti-war or pro-war
listener discretion is advised
you can be removed from the air for being anti-war
and be replaced by somebody who goes
i flaked tom dad
tom dashiell is to be shot
killed, solicited and hanged for being tom dashiell
getting out there
so what's going on somebody calling, somebody going because i, really
for some reason the real player won't work here
Somebody go out onto cbs news.com rather than
click on the bagdad cam
and let us know what's going on
on the bagdad cam
we're surfing the avenue of olives right now and it looks like
Like there are many people laying around just doing nothing, I guess.
There's a new look in the cars.
Blackened and smoking.
Yes, a no window look.
No tires and no human smells.
Oh, boy.
What have we got our show?
Well, I'm not there right now.
What the hell?
What do I care?
Well, Saddam's going to step out onto that balcony.
Gypsy woman told my mother.
I've got to get born.
Hey.
The king of the Middle East.
And you can take that in your orange bush.
Shove it up your tush.
I heard a woman on the air on one of these talk shows the other day who said all her kids were in the military.
And many of them were over there.
And she was an elderly African-American woman.
Quite wonderful.
Well spoken.
But towards the end of her conversation, she said, you can take that effing George W.
And stick that effing flag up his effing butt.
And it got on the airs.
I mean, the lilting.
She supports the troops without supporting the war.
If you can make that distinction.
Well, she's sending her kids cookies, but she's hoping they can eat them with mouths that still work.
Right.
Some people don't want you to make that distinction.
And that distinction, I believe, can be made.
In times of war.
I'll go back to blanket condemnations of my whole culture and heritage.
Carpet bombing, blanket condemnations, and carpet bombings.
I don't want you fighting.
Yes, ma'am.
I forbid you to fight.
Have it your own way.
Yeah!
Maybe you're right.
You're going to hear some ugly talk about this in school.
I did!
You're been such a big part of my life, I didn't even notice the butterflies.
If you were certain I would rot in a suit, you wouldn't dare to say anything.
I thought that wasn't too bad for most Stop entered by a mustache but did wait just to be asked
to fire.
Hello, Hassler.
Ha-ha-ha!
This is my room, boss!
core guys I surrounded.
Three or four of them, man,
they were dropping from trees and they could not
stand and they were easy to move
except for the heavier ones.
But McDonald's employees put up a fight.
They did. They defended the Golden Arches
with their lives and with
all of their hearts and minds.
Yes, they were
battle-hardened with an eight-year war with
Burger King.
Not only battle-hardened with that, they were
battle-hardened with the burger wars
of the 80s claimed thousands
of victims.
I can remember the 82nd Airborne
as they parachuted down
over the McDonald's parking lot
in my town.
And there was fearsome fighting from inside.
I'm glad the 7th Cavalry
was the lead guys
on the way to Baghdad.
Ronald's much-vaunted
berms.
Berms?
Sir, have you been waiting by the berm?
The bus is not coming.
Dropping the berm.
An enemy would like nothing better than to have us
leave our cities empty and unproductive.
If an emergency should come,
our factories will be battle stations.
Production must go on
if we are to win.
Good, Speaker.
Okay.
And again, looking at the map for our viewers,
what we have there is
the division of the various hash
districts. All tremendously
important. It is part of
what is maybe
maybe
the second largest hash field on Earth.
They would produce clouds in neighboring towns and what have you.
Set on fire.
Thank you, Tony.
I knew now that my every impulse was to kill Bob.
But I had thought of one idea.
It was worth a try.
If I tried to kill Bob, I had to act like the doll.
Anything was worth a try.
But I didn't dare.
I had to act like the doll.
Yes, yes.
And I had to kill Bob.
Yes.
I had to kill Bob.
Kill Bob.
Yes.
I had a chilling urge to get out of my clothes and get out fast.
It's true.
Yes?
It's all true.
Yes, I understand that.
I had to admit it.
Uh-huh.
And I live near San Francisco.
Yes, naturally.
Well, I guess that about does it.
Goodbye.
Ah.
Let's talk.
Let's talk about the big retired urban special surprising noteworthy religious flares in the Israeli desert.
Which I find a little bit comical.
Well, there certainly was a finding important intelligence.
Captain Bag Scope turned the lights off.
For that, I want to kick just about everything.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
And, uh, thanks.
Uh, right?
Right.
I think that's very, very cute.
Goodbye.
The British government has learned that Saddam Hussein recently had an advanced nuclear program chemical in his arse.
Even while inspectors were in his country.
Our intelligence sources tell us that he has attempted to purchase seven million hydrogen powered doctors.
And the Western Wall.
Of the Pentagon.
Like a burning man.
Or maybe a gray guy all stiff that they just prop up and take around from house to house.
You can't trust anybody.
Not even the dead.
There were government trucks going up and down the street saying, walk towards the airport.
Walk towards the airport.
Resist the...
Ah, it was nuts.
I was going, oh yeah, sure I'm going to get out my nightgown and walk towards the airport.
We come from the western shore.
But half of the neighborhood was doing it.
This is it, man.
This is George's song.
The minions of the oiligarchs.
We have come to subdue your land.
This is George's song right here, man.
To take your resources.
Edwin Starr.
Yeah, the hammer of the guards.
That's a...
That's that big bomb they made.
It's a liar.
Yeah.
Oh, the bomb of the tall.
The only goal will be the western shore.
For the olives of death.
Robert Plant predicted this war in the year 1078.
Did you know Robert Plant went to Mali and went to one of those far out in the country
things and sang Whole Lotta Love with a bunch of weird guys beating on drums?
Yeah.
And they were playing the drums and playing ooze and shit.
Of course, have you seen the kitty cat version of this on the internet?
The little viking kitty cats?
Oh, it's hilarious.
It's so...
It's like cut out character type thing.
And they're kitty cats dressed as viking.
That's inspiring in these days of turmoil.
Viking kitty cats.
You purring and you pet them on the neck and they chop off your hand.
That's just like the world...
The paradigm we're faced with.
A new crusade.
Guaranteed to wipe clean the shores of every land not touched by the red, white and
blue.
Word.
We'll all keep getting younger and younger until we suffer a fate worse than death.
Free life, then death.
Our offices and homes will also be posts of duty, not to be deserted.
With the help of the government.
With the knowledge of the first atomic explosions to guide us, our chances for survival will
be far better than those of the people of Hiroshima and Nagasaki.
Here is a certain part that you do not understand in your simple diplomacy.
Yes, my little bird, who will die.
Oh, now you laugh at birds dying.
Bombing and killing many people is going to help a little bird.
Listen to the laughter of this little bird.
You are a dope bird.
There will be civilian bird ping pong, little bird girl.
But here is a simplistic Nickelodeon that you do not understand in your certain diplomacy
is that you are guaranteed to have civilian bird pong.
So now you try again to answer my question without ping power, little civilian bird girl.
How does this girl learn ping pong?
If you just answer his question, he will be happy.
I mean, I guess a little bird is saying that it seems like you need to bomb and kill a little girl.
Okay.
Thank you.
An attack could come without warning.
The sky would suddenly light up.
If the doorway is right at hand, use it.
If the nearest shelter is more than a couple of steps away, fall to the ground immediately.
You know, take your pick.
The lesser of all swines, that's what we're looking for.
Yeah.
Whatever you do, don't throw your vote away voting your conscience.
The U.S. Army and the Marines are going to be slipping it in overnight.
Slipping it in where?
Like you got to ask.
But where will they put the disease?
Well, they're entering Baghdad from the missionary position, not from the rear.
Will they bring the disease home?
The probes have already done their job.
Now it's time for the main thrust.
We're just hoping Baghdad's well lubricated.
We've been bombing for days.
The filthy tunnels under Saddam's seat of power will be filled with the power of the American Marine as he rams home his victory.
Arby's, nasal, fluorine, nerve force, nerve, nerve force, nerve force.
Goat riper or goat roper?
That'd be cool if like the tank battalions came roaring into Baghdad with this jamming on their speakers.
He started it all way back then.
I ain't gonna lie to you.
What if the Iraqis came into Washington playing that, man?
Oh man, I'm getting scared now.
That's what I think they're planning.
Like there's all this talk that the Iraqis aren't fighting back.
No.
They're hiding in little trap doors.
Remember the saying about...
Remember that old hippie saying?
What if they held a war and no one came?
And I think that's what the Iraqis are doing.
They've got that old war movie poster.
Yeah.
What if they had a war and no one came?
None of them are coming.
They're just going, what would the U.S. Army and Marines do if they rolled into downtown Baghdad and there was a big rave party going on?
Everybody's dancing.
Yeah, big block party, man.
War is unhealthy for...
All those bombed out blocks filled with punks.
Osama bin Laden and other living things.
Smokable comestibles.
Yes.
Hummus and baba ghanoush.
Smokable little bud, you know.
Belly dancers.
Everybody's just sitting around.
Rasta dudes sitting around reading the Koran.
Discarnate feet dancing by themselves.
Burning incense and everything.
What if?
Well, back to reality now.
Yeah.
Back to raping goats.
Oh!
Ow!
Wow, Striebeck.
Oh, it's awesome.
I'm looking for a shapely communist goat.
A goat with shapely socialist curves and...
You ain't going to make an old felch in my goat.
Now let me tell you something, Strebeck.
There are two things which clearly differentiate the human species from animals.
One, we use cutlery.
Two, we're capable of controlling our sexual urges.
Now you might be an exception, but don't drag me down into your private hell.
No way.
Prince Fuzzwell and the wonderful First Lady himself.
And also, of course, the presidential chorus, which will be accompanying the leader tonight.
Tonight, there's going to be singing as well as the usual pep rally and cheering team.
We've got the girls of the 401st Armored Infantry Battalion.
They're going to be doing...
Oh, the Pleasure Battalion.
Well, well, they're employed.
Let's just say they're on the job tonight.
Nexus 7 models they've got in there now.
Oh, they're all the black-haired beauties, the Baghdad babies, they like to call them.
And they're made for confusion, and so are we.
We'll about split a zipper just watching the training video for...
The zipper is already in.
My brain, yes, it's already to be zipped up.
Things are getting much, much worse.
Much worse over there in the land of hair.
Where the people are cruel and nice and eat cheese and ice.
Somewhere where we've never been.
The world is cracking once again.
I saw the darkness grow today.
Have you seen it?
The darkness grow?
Yeah, I was just outside.
It was dark already, and all of a sudden it was like, wow, it looks a lot darker.
And I realized...
That's because they set the oil wells on fire.
That could be a shine effect from the atmospheric bubble,
because the last time I saw the darkness,
it was a scene of somewhere in the Middle East that got ho-hunk-um-dom bombed out.
And so I think it's here.
I think the darkness is here.
Could it be?
I carry my darkness deep inside.
I carry mine in a pocket in a little silver bag, baby.
They can bring on that darkness all they want,
as long as I get my pizza delivered on time.
That's right.
That's what Dr. Leigh Eames said.
As long as we get our pizza on time,
as long as we can get our pizza in 30 minutes or less,
we got no right to protest what the government's doing.
Because we all have a pretty damn good life.
And those brave soldiers are protected.
They are protecting that life.
They are protecting your right to enjoy your pizza.
And yet there's the irony that the very man who would be delivering my pizza
is over there defending my right to have that pizza
while his replacement is delivering it.
Well, he is delivering you from freedom.
And his replacement is late.
Not only pizza, he's delivering you from freedom.
And freedom, freedom, freedom, freedom.
Just another word for nothing left to buy.
I thought you were going to say bomb.
As long as the pizza's hot.
Freedom's just another word for nothing.
Nothing left to bomb.
As long as the pizza's hot.
It's a valid trade.
I'm trading my freedom as long as the pizza's hot when it gets there.
As long as there's plenty of soft slurpees
set upon you by Arabic women.
Isn't that what you're waiting for, LeGoon?
Your own 7-Eleven with your own harem?
You slut.
That's all I can think about.
That's right.
I'm a 7-Eleven harem slut.
I'm proud of it.
I'm not ashamed.
You can't insult me by calling me a 7-Eleven harem.
I'm a 7-Eleven harem slut.
You're not ashamed.
You're a shamer.
I had to come up from nothing, man.
I had to come up from nothing.
You're still not ashamed.
I was just a parking lot of the 7-Eleven slut.
He was just one of the unit guards before he became one of the sluts.
I'm more from a...
Give him credit.
I'm more from a slime unit into the full-grown bling I am today, man.
I...
Oh, wait a minute.
Either way, you're still a slut.
I'm from nothing, man.
I'm from nothing.
And back to it you shall go.
Well...
It's all gino.
What a long enough timeline.
We all do.
Well, I don't know if it's going to be so long.
Aren't you paying attention to the avenge?
I mean, not the avenge of war.
I mean, the avenge in your own bowels.
Just because we're at the end of it doesn't mean that it wasn't a long timeline.
That's true.
You confused the hell out of me, man.
And that's what we call a baggy daddy.
When you do something like that...
Time control!
That's why Bob wants you to have time control!
Time control, an indispensable framework for freedom.
Time, to the pink, is only what oozes through his watch.
He sees not its total pervasiveness.
The subgenius knows that time is what we beads are strung on.
It makes possibility possible.
It kindly allows us to feel we are continuous and mercifully hides from us that we are instantaneous.
Time control is what we've wanted all along.
It makes pain hurry and slack slow.
All the moral and emotional work to continue and to eventually fall down.
We perceive the lack of it clearly when, for instance, we are in a crowded room and must withhold a tremendous fart.
In those hor Elliottless moments before the gas ball seeps back in, we consciously wish we could ignore it, and we could had we true time control.
Any form of postponement or procrastination is a subtle bite of time control, and so slightly sacred.
Even pinks strive for time control without knowing it.
It is the reason they love stories, movies, jokes, songs, what are these, if not time control.
Unlike mundane live experience, these media seem to compress time.
They make events happen with more clarity than normality would allow.
All the following are time control, language, writing, photography, recording, shortcuts,
matter transmitters, stimulant drugs, fossils, pyramids, TV dinners, torture,
daylight savings time, and prophecy.
And so the subgenius pays attention to the strange rates and paces at which our lives are projected.
He rewinds back to whatever memory frame he desires and lets it stand frozen for his inspection.
He manipulates his own moods by splicing together the appropriate thoughts.
For even hallowed time may be compressed, preserved, extended, traversed, frozen,
twisted, reversed, knotted, circled, recycled, looped, and even erased.
Time control is possible.
Preserved.
The past.
Boil it down.
Extract its patterns.
And wield it without mercy.
Cry havoc!
And let's slit the dogs of war!
A miscellaneous religion has declared war on the Christian business class of this land of the free!
And if they are as dumb as we are stupid, you better start digging your shelter now!
What do you know about the prophet above all?
Authoritarian commerce machine careers grinding bones as they turn vain from a human!
No!
You know nothing!
And what you do know is from the dead look in your father's eye!
From the way the bank teller rubs the money!
From how cops pose like action figures with hands on their guns!
No matter what the truth is, they think their job is to make some superheroes!
No matter what, the news anchors will sit there, smirk, and lie in your face!
These people are no longer human!
They do not blink, except when they need to breathe.
So when the normal Duke tries to breathe, they don't blink!
And they convince you that no, they're not all bad!
They'll come out straight in their pink face and say,
Nay! Nay! Capitalism has mutated to a disease!
And has infiltrated our masses with their Walmarts, their Starbucks, their oil, and their greed!
Rotten Republic, uh, did that rant.
New subgeni apparently, mysterious.
They posted that to all binary slack.
The time control lecture is a lie!
The time control lecture is something I wrote 23 years ago that was almost used in Revelation X but cut,
uh, now rendered in Machinespeak by Dr. Philo Drummond.
Before that, Halim El-Dab, uh, did Obsession for Oil.
And almost everything else on this particular next to the last of the war shows, uh, we hope,
is by Fernanda Nandi-Libmer and ESO Swamp Radio of WCSB Cleveland, which is, uh, Professor Chaz Smith.
And, uh, the host, uh, Lonesome Cowboy Dave, the longtime, uh, sort of, uh, creature that goes with that show.
Princess Wiardo, yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang, and in this case, guests, Reverend Ed Strange and Dr. Katahdin Legume.
The background music, uh, right now is by The Cosmix.
Uh, spelled C-O-S-M-I-K-S.
And you can check out www.thecosmix.com.
Uh, just remember that it's spelled The Cosmix as, uh, C-O-S-M-I-K-S.com.
We'll start playing the other submissions, uh, in future shows now that the war is slowed down.
And you are listening to, uh, the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
For more information, see www.subgenius.com.
Subgenius is spelled without an O.
Church of the Subgenius.
Friends, see our website for information and a catalog.
And I should mention, uh, just heard that they have let Revelation X, our last book, go out of print.
Uh, so the last copies are soon to be gone.
Praise Bob. Check the catalog.
Uh, our first book, uh, Book of the Subgenius, is still in print at better bookstores everywhere.
Let there be slack.
Uh, yes.
My boy.
We're pilgrims in an unholy land.
How does that make sense, though?
I really like how convicted felon, Olly North, is a...
Me too.
...is a correspondent.
I thought I was hallucinating for the first week.
I did too.
We all did.
But convicted felon, Olly North, is a correspondent.
Hey, that's Fox.
Is it Fox?
That's Fox.
The same network that brought you Geraldo.
The same network?
And canceled Futurama.
The same network where the guy who's in charge goes to Bush's residence, or the Oroville Orifice, frequently and says,
Hey, I want this, I want that.
And he says, Well, what do you want?
And he goes back and forth.
He's George W.'s buddy.
Hey.
Roger Ailes and all those other squimbags.
You could be like that, too, if you would play the game.
But you don't play the game, do you, Dick?
Oh, I would have assets of over five million dollars if I played the game.
Where's your stick?
You could do that any minute.
Where's the hockey stick?
I'll play it.
I can walk out.
I can walk out at this college radio station and play it.
I can play the game and be a millionaire.
He could straighten his ass guard and pull up his long, slender socks up around his knees
and walk, stride, yes, stride with his head held high, out of the door, into the stock market, and pull down his moon band.
Tonight I have a message for the people of Iraq.
Go home and die.
The American flag stands for corporate scandals, recession, stock market declines, blackmail,
burning with hot irons, mutilation with electric drills, cutting out tongues.
Thanks, brother.
Dr. Holt is reporting for WXXI.
Thanks, doctor.
Wrong, Mr. Chekov.
There are casualties.
My wits are as enfrightened out of Captain, sir.
You are my brothers.
You are my sister.
Across the sea.
And my name is Peace.
Peace.
Look in the mirror.
You're fired.
Hidden deep, hidden deep, your enemy hidden deep in your heart.
Your enemy hidden deep in your heart.
guitar solo
One night, one night
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah
Ooh, loo, loo, loo, yeah, yeah
Ooh, loo, loo, yeah, yeah
Oh, oh, oh
You, oh, yeah, yeah
Ahh, yeah, yeah, yeah
Well, the paroxysms have begun again.
This time, the vegetable matter is cringing,
and most of the humans here in the sack,
the sack elevated nearly 3,000 miles above the city of Braggdad,
5 million people below us,
some of them still standing, other ones wearing their correct harpoons,
cursing skyward and hoping somehow, someway,
that the machinery fails.
This machinery, this is God's free machinery.
Machinery, free and full of liberty,
and made for, uh...
What was this made for?
Holy mother of...
Okay, all right, we're back now.
Please, for four hours.
Hey!
Hey now!
Trusting in the sanity and restraint of the United States
is not a strategy, and it is not an option.
Well, things sound blinkier than they ever did before on this radio station.
And blinkier, too.
Man, I'm telling you.
How much did you pay for that MP3, Chad?
I taste only neoliberalism.
the bitter rank waters of nihilism
coming from this radio show.
I can only say...
Oh, here we go, this one.
I hear no truth and no positive.
Everything's all right.
No love.
Oh, now I hear some.
A little small...
What are they?
They look kind of human,
dancing in the grass.
Oh, look, they got balloons.
No, wait a minute, those are...
Oh, man, those are exploding
vests full of sutures.
Oh, my...
Those are the last of the Martians.
Those are the nearly extinct Martians.
They're frolicking in the little Martian field.
Look, look, part of their brains are exposed.
You could even have a night, little droogie.
Let the world do without you tonight.
It was me and my three drinks.
I just decided...
Those ancient Martians are partying
on top of our very nuclear beer, Ram.
Are you going to let them do that?
Are we going to go in there
and get our nuclear beer?
For a new...
Nuclear day tomorrow.
The sun.
Yes.
The thousand suns
of a nuclear holocaust
are shining.
I'm going to sell real estate, Sting.
I'm going to sell those, um,
those, you know, sandy things
that have been turned to glass
by the explosions.
I'm going to send the great wastelands.
I'm going to sell, uh,
everything I can find.
What's left?
Oh, you're going to have to be
in competition with J.R. Bob Dobbs,
my friend.
But what will we use for money
as a change, you know,
for exchange and stuff?
Souls.
I thought, you know,
like maybe pemmican
or pieces of butter.
Human souls.
And little liters of anguish
and horror.
Bottles of anguish and horror.
Enthusiast form.
You've been selling the same
foul elixir for,
since day six.
It's a medium of exchange.
Snake oil.
And the exchange that creates
the power of a thousand mediums
How many stangs of pain
does it leave the past?
No!
Martian blood
for the sake of life.
Did you see that?
No.
Did you see that new
paid-for-view show
called
Harnford's Airborne Gone Wild?
Yep.
Yeah, pretty cool stuff.
They put them on an island
somewhere near
the Gulf of Arabia.
Give them all the tequila
they want.
And all the pemmican
and saltwater corn.
They get speed, too, right?
Yeah.
Harnford's Airborne Gone Wild
We love speed.
A parrot to wear
on their shoulders.
Each one has their own
private, you know,
they wear on their shoulders.
Somebody follows them
around with a camera.
Well, the guy with the
pet leg follows them
with the camera.
The guy with the one good eye.
follows them with the
The guy with the peg eye.
The aluminum.
That peg eye
is really a camera.
The sky is as a peg.
But it really works
as an eye.
I've seen plenty
of peg eyes lately.
I've seen people with
actually with stakes
driven into their foreheads.
I'm having bad dreams today.
I think the end is nigh.
You think the
collective unconscious
is creeping into your
It's balking.
It's stopping at the
terrible step it's ready
to take into the latrine.
I think it's
It's a full moon
and you're just, you know,
kind of teetering on
Well, how can we attack
with a full moon
in our eyes?
We need a stellar thing
We need a full moon
A full moon
to guide our stars.
We need a full moon?
Yeah.
Well, I guess we got one.
That's like broad daylight
if you got those
night vision things.
Easier to shoot at, too,
if you think of it that way.
Yeah.
Oh, well.
Oh, yeah, the other guys.
Depends.
Well, what if we start
shooting at each other
like we usually do?
It's hell.
What, shooting at yourself?
Here we are trivializing
this hellish thing.
That we don't really
know anything about.
We're trying to get
a handle on each other.
our nature running.
We're trying to understand it.
Keep your head on tight.
You're back to the wind
and you're sacking the saddle.
Bums me out, dude.
Yeah.
Bums you out.
It's going to bum you out
pretty soon.
It's going to be a bummer, man.
Bob said so.
He said,
it's going to be a bummer, man.
Your eyeballs are hanging
from your socket.
It's going to be really beautiful.
He said that in 1980.
Yeah.
It's going to be fine.
It's all right.
Wash the exposed areas.
Pay particular attention
to your hair. Get all the dirt from under your fingernails. If the people of Hiroshima and Nagasaki
had known what we know about civil defense, thousands of lives would have been saved.
Yes, the knowledge is ours, and preparation can mean survival for you. So act now.
Someday your life may depend on it.
Emergency alert.
Orange alert.
This is an actual emergency.
This station serves 50 equipment.
If the time comes when you actually have to take shelter, lie under the table.
I think you hurt my head real bad.
I'm dizzy.
I need a doctor.