Bob?
Ah, yes, dear friends.
It's rerun time again.
Susie the Floozies.
Bob's Slack Time Funhouse number 51 from 1994.
Praise Susie the Floozy and W-R-E-K in Atlanta.
Praise Bob.
B-O-B-B-O.
Let the joy jump in the good times roll.
Let the pleasure pop.
Now let's take a stroll.
Light up.
Let's all get mellow.
Get smoke in your eyes.
Light up.
Get hip, I say, fellas.
Say, what is this job?
Light up.
Let's all get ready.
I know how you feel.
Light up.
Now don't be afraid of me.
You'll find what I mean in any old field.
Pop.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Blow.
Eight, nine, ten, and then eleven.
Light up.
Now get your day going.
Lays up.
I'll say that's the thing.
Light up.
Don't let that man get you.
Just pop on your cig and blow the smoke out.
I may not change my underwear, but I'm changing my ways.
Oh, there hasn't been a whole lot of Bob in the Slacktime Funhouse lately.
But now it's battle stations and full speed ahead slack.
Ooh, with the size tension in the air.
Whew.
God, it's the reek of future death.
Zooming down on us.
This isn't the time to be lulled into warm complacency.
Oh, the end times have checked in and they've left an early wake-up call.
What does it take to convince you of the signs of the end times anyway?
Oh.
The Republican Party and the zombie Jesus slaves of the Christian radical right
have seized power in a bloody coup, which you did little or nothing to prevent.
Oh, think you'll be able to hang on to your precious slack now?
You don't have enough slack to go around now.
And they're going to take even that little bit away.
Good luck.
Name me one friend you've got left, he said.
Bob, I said.
This was the only lifer in the prison,
the only American to have been convicted of treason during the Korean War.
He was the chief clerk in the supply room where I would soon be given my civilian clothes.
He was a science fiction writer of some note,
publishing many stories a year under various pseudonyms,
including Frank X. Barlow and Kilgore Trout.
Somebody said, oh, Mr. 666 is way off in the future.
No, my dear friend, he's been around a while.
And he's here tonight.
He's here tonight on the face of this earth.
And all the world is wondering after him.
And that's why this subject is so important.
The deceptions are all around us.
Deceptions are saying it's off in the future, it's off in the future.
Don't worry about it.
Friends, we better start worrying about it.
And friends, there are some things taking place around us
that's going to come down very, very soon.
Friends, are you ready for it?
Are you ready for it?
I tell you, we're living in serious time.
Look at the signs!
Before basic food groups have been replaced with a pyramid.
Isn't that enough to tip you off?
Look at the signs!
The new Blue Star ointment commercial no longer mentions tether.
I don't even know what tether is.
They took it away from me.
Look at the signs.
We think we're okay in our little shells, minding our own business.
Standing on the corner of walk and don't walk.
But Seekers, it's time to run!
Quick!
It's not too late.
We gotta get some Bob into us.
Bad!
Oh, even if it hurts.
Oh, it will.
It will.
Oh, it's time to read some beads until it bleeds.
The only sensitivity I care about is nerve endings.
Are you serious?
Are you yeti enough to attest yours?
So welcome, friends, to Reverend Commandant Susie Der Flusie's Boot Camp for Bob.
Today is the first day of your last hurrah.
Hey, you, pink boy!
Drop and give me 20, mister.
The rest of you, you'll have to suffer through these Bob songs.
And don't think you're getting off easy.
The hell is just beginning.
She says things I would not dare to articulate.
Well, I'll simply say this.
If that is true, why so many of them get injured in the very act?
Why are some of them killed in the act?
And why do so many of them have to have colostomies?
Good times.
You!
You're one of us!
Maybe you're one.
Something to be outright laughed at.
I heard someone over here say who's been the most effective evangelist the last 20 years.
His name is Bob.
And why, listen, listen, wait, listen, look at me.
Listen, wait, wait, wait.
While he entertains you, he indoctrinates you.
While he entertains you, he gets through to you.
While you laugh, you begin to lose automatically.
I met Bob when he came in the door, when I came in the door to service today.
And Bob was formerly bound by the powers of darkness to a terrible degree.
Oh, whatever.
He says he gets a funny feeling down inside when he sees the Boy Scouts and the YMCA.
Thank you very much.
And they were doing these crazy things.
Of course, that's just the start.
Thank goodness that, you know, nobody I knew was there because I thought,
Bobby, I'm never going to another one of these as long as I live.
I mean, you know, and he was a little nervous, too, when they grabbed his hand.
You know, it was like, this is not what we're used to.
What we learned a long time ago is that you become what the people you associate with.
And so he started associating with people in this business.
And I began to see the changes.
You know, Bobby was a good person and a good guy.
But I started seeing the change of staying away from the people that he was hanging around with
and looking forward to the future.
And so I started getting a glimpse of what this business had to offer.
So will all you goonie birds answering this description please stand up.
You misfits in this brave new age.
You dismally disorganized, improperly apologetic ghosts of the past.
Stand up. Stand up and be counted.
To healthcare experts his near-death experience
You
And now it's time to bring up the headliner of the evening, a very special gentleman.
Please welcome to the stage, Bob.
Bob!
Last night my baby wanted to talk to me about art.
But I said no, no, let's just close our eyes and watch.
Bob!
Hi, Bob.
I like to get mail, of course, but for some reason I get the strangest kind of mail,
and these are all real letters I'm reading you.
Every one, I assure you, has come in in the mail from someone I don't know.
To give you an idea of what the people think of the show and what they like to say in their communications.
Dear Bob, before I tuned in your program,
I could never get through to you.
I had to get my husband out of bed in the morning.
Now he can't get out of the house fast enough.
Why don't you give up?
Why can't you act like normal people?
Why don't you stop whistling?
Why don't you stop acting like a moron?
Or maybe you aren't acting.
Yes!
That's all I'm taking from you.
Get back here, you devil!
He's gone!
Find him!
Oh, yeah.
That old slack man.
I wanted to know this thing,
And are you?
And look!
back up now!
It's so freezing, Bob!
What's wrong, Bob?
Hey!
Oh!
I've got it!
Johnny,
God
Hey,
what's up there?
people have a show called Bob's Slacktime Funhouse. They often say, who's Bob? Well,
that certainly separates a wheat from the chaff now, doesn't it? Oh, I like to think that you
all know Bob, at least those of you who matter. But don't fool yourself into thinking that that
puts you any higher up in the food web because of it. Oh yeah, here at the funhouse, it seems like
we've lost our grip on Bob. We gotta latch onto his pipe and pull him down off the ceiling and
bump his stomach and get him into fight and trim because he's our only hope.
I want you to get to know Bob personally. If you don't already, those of you who don't know Bob,
my heart sings like the prairie squid in rutting season for you at the joy you're about to
experience.
Oh, and those of you who have forgotten Bob,
by, by upon thee, wake up. It's time to cover your ass, kids. Don't be a pink boy.
Pinks are like sponges that don't work. You, you subgenius tides, yeah. You, on the other hand,
soak in this. I want to give you a close encounter with Bob and his amazing life.
His precocious youth, his early careers in sports and salesmanship, and his hot, hot linkage with
Connie, his first and primary wife. And all through the wonders of our patented sub-g-liminal
hypnognostic brain ventilating system. I want you to take the fronts off of your speaker seekers.
There. Yeah, now, now, put your head in the speaker cone. No, no, no, not, not that way.
The big one. Yeah. Okay, reach over. Yeah, you can still barely reach now. Turn that dial up to 11.
Or lethal, if you have it. And I want you to feel the slack pouring over you like drug tapping,
saturating you with pure Bob land. Meanwhile, I'll just notch up your pain meters a little bit.
Ha ha ha!
Once upon a time, there was Bobby. Bobby was a boy who drank milk. He drank milk in the morning,
he drank milk at noon, he drank milk before he went to bed. And where do you think all that
milk came from? Well, that milk had a long journey. For once upon a time, there was Bobby,
and once upon a time, there also was...
Do you hear them?
Yes, there also were five cows, five cows, five cows. They didn't like to wait, but came and moved
at the farmer's gate. Five big cows. The farmer came when he heard them call and led each one into
her stall. Now I must milk them one and all to get the milk for Bobby.
The five cows were Daisy and Squirrel and Queen and Lady and Buttercup. When they were in the barn,
the farmer took his stool and big pail and sat down to milk. Squirt, squirt, the milk poured into the
pail. And when the five cows had given all their milk, the farmer let the cows wander out of the
barn and into the pasture again. There they ate the green grass and forgot all about the milk.
But the milk had only just begun its journey. For once upon a time, there was Bobby,
and once upon a time, there also was...
Do you hear it?
Yes, there also was a wagon, a wagon with a horse,
whose rubber shoes clipped off each time he started, each time he stopped.
A milk wagon! And the milkman said, my work is done before most other works begun.
From house to house, I hurry on to bring the milk to Bobby.
The milk wagon came down the street until it stopped at Bobby's house. The driver jumped out
and put down the bottles Bobby's mother had ordered. Then he drove away and forgot all about
the milk. But the milk still went on with its journey. For after the milkman went away, Johnny's
mother ran downstairs and...
All right, that's the milk that jumped the Romanian cow, Naomi.
And when he opened the door, there stood the milk bottles.
The milk from the cows who couldn't wait, But said moo moo at the farmer's gate.
The milk in the trucks that couldn't stand still, But went a-hawking down the hill.
The milk on the train that carried the freight, And clickety-clackety, couldn't be late.
The milk where the factory whistle blew And said now, there is work to do.
The milk that went where the horse could flop, Each time he started, each time he stopped.
The milk from the bottle that opened up, And mother poured into Bobby's cup.
Don't call me Bobby.
The milk slipped and slid down Bobby's throat,
and so turned into Bobby.
And so at last, the milk ended its long, long journey.
Your commentator was privileged to visit Space Platform 7 last week.
And before Cadet Bobby and Cadet Betty went into pre-lunar medical quarantine,
I interviewed them.
These telememory tapes will introduce you to these two exceptional youngsters.
Cadet Bobby.
Don't call me Bobby.
Bob, are you and Betty worried at all about your lunar adventure?
Not really, Doctor.
We've been thoroughly checked out on our space shuttle craft,
and of course, adults have made thousands of such trips.
After all the years of...
training, I suppose it's really a great thrill.
It certainly is.
Bob, of course, studied 18 months longer than I.
Bob, where have you trained?
Well, I had calculus and logarithms in elementary school in Washington, USA.
Then I spent one year in the Space Flight Center at Houston, USA.
Another year in Moscow on advanced power and propulsion systems.
Six months in England at the Academy of Celestial Navigation,
and then back to Houston.
I went to the University of Michigan for advanced computer technology.
I had just about the same program, except for the fuels and propulsion.
The girls just don't seem to take to the engineering courses.
Well, you kids have spent six months here,
50,000 miles from Earth on Space Station number 7,
and now you are ready for the final 200,000 mile voyage to the Moon.
Goodbye.
And thanks to all of you.
Release Flight!
LOL
I think it was just a matter of time.
After all when we were growing up, Bob had a huge supply of Playboys underneath his bed.
His dad had a subscription.
Bob dearly loved those Playboys, if I recall.
klob circle
O
B
He said, do you know the story about Bob?
And I said, well, Coach, the only thing I can tell you, he looks like Mr. Clean.
I mean, he's the largest thing I've ever seen since a Big Mac truck.
He is about 225, 230 pounds, packs arms the size of my thighs.
A huge, huge man.
This is my friend and colleague, Texan.
Howdy there.
I didn't catch your name, mister.
I'm Mr. Clean.
He interviews in his letters.
No, he's, you know, not retarded.
I mean, I've talked to the man, and he's pretty quick.
But for some reason, you kind of get that impression sometimes.
I don't know, maybe he just like, you know, when he goes into create,
it's like somebody playing a musical instrument or driving a car.
They kind of go into that zen state of retardedness
where if they were neurotically trying to,
you know, do something, specifically,
you can't drive a car if you're totally concentrating on it.
You'll go nuts.
It's like being, you know, that's the way you are when you're learning to drive.
At the same time, he's kind of nuts.
I mean, he's kind of a nutty guy and eccentric.
I mean, he's not Hugh Beaumont.
He's definitely not Mr. Normal.
Then neither am I.
BEEPING
Your secrets belong to him
You're at his beck and call
You feel his hot breath down your neck
Your skin begins to crawl
He knows your life
The things you think no one knows
BEEPING
He has a lot of secrets
He has the files
But you know he won't show
The eyes are everywhere
It's the electric stare
No one's there but the face in the window
And when you think he's gone
Read your curtains draw
His red eyes on the face in the window
BEEPING
He never steps out of line
He can't cheers this tone
He won't run out of time
BEEPING
Ever forever
A true friend through thick and thin
BEEPING
You can't keep him out
But you won't let him in
BEEPING
The eyes are everywhere
where it's the electric stand no one's there but the face in the window and when you think it's gone
leave your curtains down his red eyes on the face in the window
we've been throwing out some real good hotels in america
ride those three wheelers down the lobby of hyatt and miami
i gotta tell you you know some things change about well let's just take bobby brinkley don't
call me bobby bobby
a lot he's changed a lot in a lot of ways he's become very refined but there are things about
him that will never change is that clear to you the brain is not a container to be filled
it is something to be activated to be excited i'm trying to find a young man here's one i'll
bet he's less than 26 how old are you 26 i got him
what's your first name
bob
ah it it appears to me that you don't need much motivation but i'm going to use it anyway
i think probably this is true bob isn't it true then unless you have found your field
in life the thing that you want to do isn't it true that you frequently think of what
you are best suited for and if you can only find out what he's best suited for he would
work 18 hours a day i assure you he would study he would self-discipline himself he's
stopped fooling around enough things to worry about too and i got to tell you that bob and
that you are. I'm just using that as an example. I'll tell you what you're best fitted for.
How do you like that? Now, Bob, if you could ever believe this, you'd just jump out of
your skin. I guess you're jumping now, aren't you? Bob, you are best fitted for anything
you want to do. Anything. I don't care about your past education. I don't care a thing
of your past. You're best fitted for anything. You know this theory that's been known since
the beginning of time, that we are what we think. I'm Bob, and this year is my place.
Excellent. Christ.
Ooh, you want to kill me?
I don't think that's a wise thing, not a wise thing to do. Do you really think that
you can't even see him? You will feel him, and if you're dreaming that you can take him,
I don't think that's a very wise thing to do.
Ooh, ooh.
Ooh.
Uh-oh.
You know who that is?
That's right. It's your pal, Bobo the Clown. Yay!
Hey, Bobo. Want to play a game?
Okay. Look up. Look down. Now look at Mr. Frying Pan.
Uh-oh. Bobo, fall down. Go boom.
Ooh.
Wake up.
Oh, Bob. Wake up.
Boo!
it's on every station get a trace on that signal now
the other officers quickly take up the slack
that's how big it was it could be seen for miles and miles around now here's the king's command
i'm going to command all these musicians to start playing their musical instruments and as soon as
they start playing the music you are to fall down and bow down in front of that great image 90 feet
high and pray to it i'm not giving in to a smile or a grin on a face i might never see again
i'm not gonna fly in some big phony sky
on a
yes bob you rang am i a lousy picker whatever i analyze it and assess it thoroughly and then
i make my prediction on the air and i pick the opposite me too i stand on my record
but one thing i shared with you this afternoon is that bobby didn't listen to me and i'm
thankful for you and i'm thankful for you and i'm thankful for you and i'm thankful for you
and i'm thankful for you and i'm thankful for you and i'm thankful for you and i'm thankful for you
now that he didn't and hopefully if you've got a negative spouse you're not listening to them
either because he didn't listen to me and he went about and built the business because he saw
something in it a friend of his or acquaintance of his had shown him the plan and i won't bust
his bubble that's his part of the story well mr stang it was an almost foolproof plan but let us
look to the next paragraph of prophecy which says dateline for dominance 1991 first paragraph and i
quote
world war three church of the subgenius shifts into operation removal end quote
now admittedly dear friends that leaves open some room for interpretation and just what is
operation removal designated to remove when knowing bob he'd want to remove the very concept
of removal i suppose i'm not sure if i'm going to be able to do that i'm not sure if i'm going to be able to do that
i suppose bob told you that his plan has been approved and recruiting is about to open you once
offered to help us find the right sort of recruits how many men do you need i thought you'd say that
we'll need 1100 men to begin with i'm in this thing any way you can use me looking forward to it mr stang
hi i'm bob hi are you famous
yeah
see i saw this program that i'm talking
about tonight some seven years ago seven years ago when i saw this program i folded my arms across
my chest i crossed my legs and then i looked at that guy that was talking about this program
and i said no way whoever this joker is whoever's up there he's always grinning i thought why was he
always grinning it never dawned on me because he is so doggone rich being broke is not a good deal
but he looked at me he says
ow whatever you do you're gonna like area three
he says as a matter of fact judging from the first two areas you'll probably want to be involved in
area three and i was committed and convinced that area three looked good and then he spelled it out
to me d e a d dead fantastic i'll talk like this bubs your uncle mate that really doesn't help bob
um
you're getting the slack
and all you get the back slim
well that would have to have been last fourth of july was very hot out oh so hot it was just
blazing and i was at the youth group picnic minister bob was there in his bermuda pants
they cover more legs than his bermuda shorts you see and they're just a little bit tighter in the
back they just don't fit in the back of the shorts they just don't fit in the back of the shorts
so i'll get buns in the cutest way but anyway
i was slicing some rice crispy squares i had made and minister bob was filling cups of the punch bowl
with his ladle it was the biggest ladle i'd ever seen
i wanted to touch it but i was afraid to because it was so abnormally large
as i watched him with that ladle he kept dipping it into the bowl and pouring punch
and dipping and pouring and dipping and pouring
and dipping until all the cups were filled.
It didn't take long because that was some big ladle.
And then suddenly, violently, there was a shudder.
My buttocks were tingling.
I was alone, lost in space.
I saw him toss that ladle aside, his arm exhausted.
I must have passed out because that's all I remember.
You may call me Connie.
You did what was doing the storm, remember?
You said, all right, Connie, we might as well go down together.
I like the way you said Connie.
Connie, it was like a punch in the door.
Now, what's going to happen?
Do you know that's breaking the second commandment?
Because Babylon was the head of witchcraft, sorcery, fortune tellers.
Notice that.
When the music starts playing, you're to bow down and worship the great image.
Night and day, you are the one.
Only you beneath the moon and under the sun.
Whether near to me or far.
It's no matter where you are.
I think of you.
Night and day.
And I won't tell you, I jumped in with both feet and started listening to tapes and reading books because I didn't.
I had to read lots of books, lots and lots of books.
And sometimes you're going to pick up a book in the beginning and you're going to read it and you're going to think,
I can't finish this.
This book is too heavy.
And you're going to put it down and a couple of years later, a couple of months later,
you're going to pick up that book and all of a sudden it's going to slap you in the face.
Hello, Connie.
Bob, I'm so glad.
You're glad.
How do you think I feel?
You're just as good as new again.
Stop kidding.
Why are you kidding?
In high society, I just ain't the type.
Folks all look so surprised when I light my pipe.
Oh, yeah.
Do you smoke a pipe, too?
No.
Don't be coy.
I like it, too.
What's it going to get you, Connie?
All this business of filling my pipe, pouring my drinks, corned beef and cabbage?
I suppose I should pretend that I don't know what you mean by that.
But I won't.
Connie, look, for the past few days, all you've done is...
All I've done is what?
Well, is to tell a man in a thousand little ways.
To tell what man in a thousand little ways?
Well, not with words, maybe, but with looks, actions and...
Aren't you ashamed?
All right.
Maybe you should say, I'm not.
A partner in sin?
There was an influence there.
Sometimes there is a mood that just...
We don't know why.
You wouldn't get a pal, would you, Connie?
Or yourself, maybe?
I don't know yet, Bob.
Hello, children.
Oh, here we are, Doc.
The two lovebirds.
I'm all ready for the wedding.
Sit down.
Are we healthy enough to get married?
Yeah, both as solid as a new dollar.
That first baby didn't hurt you a bit.
You can have a dozen more if you want to.
And, Bob, you'll be pleased to know that there's no trace of your old V.D.
One hundred percent sure.
What did you say about a first baby?
You've been married before?
Doctor, what did you call it?
V.D.?
You mean to say that Bob has actually had one of those horrible diseases?
That isn't true, Doctor.
Is that true, Bob?
All right, if you must know, I did have it.
But it's no worse than having an illegitimate child.
I think it is.
Why, I'd sooner marry a leper.
Thank you for letting me know about this in time, Dr. West.
And now I'm going out into the clean, fresh air.
Well, there went my happy wedding right out the door.
I'm terribly sorry, Bob.
Okay, let's get going.
You'll be a double.
Just grab it by the scalp shaker up and down a bit and chop off the slack.
Come on.
Damn, this streaking out pit.
We'll finally blame it on God.
And there'll be some kind of church started called the Streaker's Church.
And, Bob, they'll just, they'll follow, try to make it religious.
But I want to tell you it's abominable and it's filthy and it's rotten.
And then I'll stand up against it and say amen.
more show
the pipes
we need a
jolly life
we're free
from every
garren's stripe
we drink the
best
no's wrong
I'm glad that
this gay life
is mine
fear the name
of fingers
waters
dirty birdie
holland
no sterling
beef
or chemistry
fear the name
of mystic
myron
tucker
tolan
badass
soaring
in
oh georgie
three
oh smiling
no neck
bob
cobalt
bar
mcnulty
oh golden
throated
john ad
if you understand
that we
have all had
a partner
in sin
you really
didn't do it
by yourself
there was an
influence there
now we shop
at neiman marcus
instead of
k martin sears
we go on
neiman marcus
and as soon as
they spotted us
and I was there
last year
they said
hi bob
and bonnie
how are you
they remembered
us
and so on
the back
they take you
in the back
and they have
drinks for you
whatever
it is
scotch
whiskey
whatever you
want
and I ask
for the usual
if you drink
five gallons
of gatorade
you're gonna
expend five
gallons of
gatorade
somewhere
in one of
these restaurants
you buy that
right
frankly
either way
it's
something
that's
a lot
of
time
to
drink
it
it's
not just
a drink
it's a lot
have to be
careful
and you always
think about
you know
getting poop
on the finger
you know
and I remember
the first time
it happened
I couldn't
believe it
I mean
it's like
oh my
god
I've got
poop
on my
finger
and then
I started
thinking
to myself
it could
be worse
I could
have a job
I don't
think
I can't
I just
can't
do it
and I said
Bobby
please
don't ever
make me
do that
again
don't
call me
Bobby
no
Connie
call me
dear
don't
ever
go
you're
my
guiding
light
each
and
all
oh my
god
no
Connie
night
and day
under the
height
of me
there's
oh such
a hungry
yearning
burning
inside
of me
and the
storm
and won't
be through
do you
let me
spend
my life
making
love
to you
night
and day
oh
day
and night
night
and day
they won't
believe that
they will
when they hear
the things
you and Bob
said to each
other the
other night
in Irene's
apartment
you were
there
and there
were probably
a thousand
people there
but I thought
there were
7,000 people
there because
there was so
much excitement
and for once
in my life
I found a place
where I could
be accepted
for being
me
and that
people loved
you unconditionally
no matter
who you were
what you
looked like
and everybody
was going
towards a
common goal
everybody
was excited
for everybody
else
and all of a
sudden I felt
like I was a
big lover
I just
all of a
sudden found
a place
that I felt
like maybe
I could
grow into
and of course
that wasn't
the beginning
either
it's a long
stretch
it's a journey
it's something
you do every
day that helps
you get closer
to your dream
well Bill
I'm an admirer
of Bob
does it worry
you Bob
you can't
let this
thing taste
I think they
could take it
a step beyond
them
to the bizarre
the grotesque
to an intentionally
mean-spirited
injury of other
innocent people
it had Bob's
fingerprints all
over it
and he and I
both would agree
that Bob's
not a nice
person
I saw him
shoot Bob
he chose what
you get with
a little
liberal agenda
you pump people
full of drugs
and pipe dreams
and what happens
they come gunning
for people like Bob
but those folks
don't realize something
you can't
kill the truth
Bob is not
going to be
stopped by any
bullet
he'll be back
and man you
better watch out
because he's
headed straight
for Washington
and that's all
I've got to say
excuse me
I have to go pray
yeah right
his new album
entitled Bob
on Bob
is released
and debuts
with a bullet
at number two
on the charts
boy let's
never heard
no scene again
officially
presumed
is dead
but the words
he left behind
still echo
through my mind
I'm the only
man who'll
ever get to
and come back
alive
he's the only
man who'll
ever get to
and come back
alive
so
this is no joke
now
not building up
to a joke
it was hot
and I knew it was
going to stay hot
terribly hot
exactly as I had
predicted
this is beautiful
ain't it
yeah but it's hot
oh we'll have a
swell time here
yeah a hot time
just like the movies
yeah just like
the movies
soon me and
Natasha
will be right
under them palm
trees
soon you and
Natasha
will be knocking
down them palm
trees
soon you and
I thought
they would
see this
brilliant
automatically
to save
this
sample
he's
there
watching
it
need
to
are
alone
over
will we've rented a porcupine to chaperone so um there are a couple of little canvas chairs there
and they're cooking somebody's skull you know or something and um the scene is an american
and a britisher and they've been discussing all afternoon a little juice and all the vodka
and um the britisher says i know you've hunted in many many sections of the world
and i know that you've killed an innumerous amount of animals of all types birds reptiles
things of that nature but you have never hunted bob in that he's the great white hunter and i
think as far as i'm concerned greatest white hunter of all times yeah i'm looking forward
to meeting him he better be pretty damn good i'll clue you
as i've spent a hundred thousand dollars coming over this godforsaken territory
and i'm looking forward to meeting him
story. True, I've made some foolish investments. I've married three or four times. One was
a teenager. I was really drunk down in Big D one night. Married a child. Married a child.
God, she was heaven, oh heaven, heaven. I'm looking forward to this guy. I hope to God
you say he's as good as he is. Believe me, he is. In fact, he's coming up right now.
Striking blue eyes and carrying a .22 short rifle. What the hell's he expect to kill with that?
I've only known him to be always a crack shot. Strange, I must say, going out after elephant today.
He'll have to be good all right, won't he?
We have a friend that we don't talk about. Wears a black leather jacket. Sort of I'm the brand of time.
Oh, what a friend.
A friend that we don't like to talk about.
Has black hair and a set of teeth to match.
We're just having cocktails right out here in the sun, jungle, listening to a little hi-fi.
Pictures of home waiting for you, Texan.
This is my friend and colleague.
Out of there. God almighty.
Oh, what a friend that we don't like to talk about.
Ah, I guess this doesn't seem strange to you.
But you should see what our friends can do.
He lets Satan tempt you. He just lets Satan wet up his knives.
He lets him get the filthiest, rottenest, degradating rot of hell and hit you right smack with it.
And then he says, use my word. Use my name. Use my power.
Yes.
Get yourself a couple of pints and a chicken tikka masala takeaway.
Bob's your uncle and f***ing is a rude word.
I haven't heard it from your mouth. Yours and Bob's.
Yeah, you heard it from him.
I did not hear it. He slept with you.
On July 4th, this weekend.
Don't you want to sleep? I'll give you a snack.
Look at that in your pipe and smoke, good whore.
I feel bad. I know. I feel bad about the way things happen.
But I don't regret it because I love Bob and I'm happy.
I think it was just a matter of time before Bob came up with a song.
I want to be Bob.
Sit and smile all the time.
Think everything is just fine.
Don't want to be Jesus.
Always look so sad.
Ha ha. He must have had an awful dad.
I want to be Bob.
Tell everyone about slack.
Let the pigs kiss my crack.
Don't want to be Jesus.
Don't want to be no slave.
He should have stayed in his grave.
I want to be Bob.
Never have to work a day.
All eternity's a play.
Don't want to be Jesus.
Don't want to carry no cross.
Don't want to speak for no ha ha boss.
I want to be Bob.
See everything all so clear.
This sh** is in your ear to ear.
I want to be Bob.
Don't want to be Jesus.
Always trying to figure things out.
Who needs all the f**king
apostate doubts.
I want to be Bob.
Yeah, I want to be Bob.
I'd even like an In-N-Out jersey.
Yahoo!
I wanted you to know what radio announcers
are up against. Feel sorry for them.
Send in a little something, whatever you can afford.
And now friends, we have a time check.
And would you just fill in your own time, please?
Well, my freedom was so precious.
I took my noxious alarm clock.
I took my sludge hammer and I painted it
red, white, and blue.
Because in America, if you can afford it,
you can do it.
And I smashed it.
And it was so fun.
What an experience.
It is really fun. I like that.
You know what time we're going to wake up Monday?
See, we don't either.
Let's be Bob! Let's be Bob!
Thanks to Bob, our eternal hope.
And praise me to Erwin, New Jersey's Pope.
We're fickle and free and we don't make no fuss
At the Church of the Subgenius.
Bob, hear our plea.
We beseech thee.
Help us be free from normalcy.
We're done devoted and done devoted.
So back, please give us an hour of slack.
J.R. Bob Dobbs never fails.
He's the living slack master of mystic sales.
All you conspiracy doofs, just you wait
till July the 5th, 1998.
Invaders will come from Planet X
bringing gifts of money, time control and great sex.
A new age will dawn and we'll never look back.
We'll be busy enjoying our slack.
Everybody now.
Bob here I'm Lee.
We be seized free.
Help us be free from normalcy.
We're dumb, devoted and dumb.
Talk back.
Please give us an hour of slack.
Hour of slack.
He's the bridge between heaven and earth and hell.
He's the patron saint of sales.
Yeah, he's doing well.
Media, retins and novels and memes.
Beware.
The slack master sells everywhere.
Give thanks to Bob.
Our eternal hope.
Praise me to Owen.
New Jersey.
We're fickle and free.
And we don't make no fuss at the Church of the Subgenius.
Everybody now.
Give thanks to Bob.
Our eternal hope.
And praise me to Owen.
New Jersey.
We're fickle and free.
And we don't make no fuss at the Church of the Subgenius.
Dear Bob, I must give you credit for playing some good music, but why spoil it with your
stupid asinine whistling?
Why?
Lock yourself in a broom closet while the music is on.
I'm disgusted and from now on I'll do my own whistling in the morning.
This is from Springfield.
Is there any lower form of life?
Let the record show that the witness made a drinky, drinky motion.
A bottle.
Who has it?
Stupid mailman, squealing me.
I still enjoy your program even though you've been back two or three weeks now.
Isn't that nice?
Here's one.
It says, Dear Bob, please don't pick any more winners.
I'm going broke.
And you bull thrower, how are you going to crawl out of this?
That's a nice one.
I like the short one.
At least you're not going to be the only one to get a little bit of a break.
I think you should get him over with in a hurry.
Dear Bob, I had heard so much about you I was prepared to like you immediately.
I tuned in your show and you talked me out of it.
Here's another one from Springfield.
Could you please give me the exact address in Washington, D.C. of the Bureau of Indian
Affairs?
I've always wanted to have an affair with an Indian.
This from Springfield also.
Dear Bob, this morning you advertised boys' suits for youngsters aged three to seven.
You said they were trimmed with piping.
Piping in a boy's suit?
Wouldn't you think they'd be housebroken at that age?
Hang in there, Robert.
Yours truly.
This letter from New Britain says, Dear Bob, I was standing in the kitchen in front of
my radio this morning pulling my two-way stretch over my hips when you said, Are you a little
on the fat side?
What I want to know is, can you see out here?
If so, I must dress somewhere else.
It's a joke, Dobbsy.
Aren't you going to let me in on it?
In on it?
Sure I will.
Sure.
Ah!
Oh, my God.
Isn't it great swimming in a sea of slack?
Let's just immerse ourselves in the luck plane's surfy, surfy waves and waft along.
Dr. Philo Drummond once said, If slack was water, Bob would be surfing and you'd be drowning.
Hey, I'm willing to settle for death by drowning in slack any day, Doctor.
I'm going to get you a drink.
Oh, this is the soundtrack to Mr. Lucky, which is one of Bob's nine billion middle
names.
And you know, he's taught me that it's better to be lucky than good any day.
And what an example he sets.
I rejoice in the failings of Bob.
I exult in the slip-ups of Bob.
Hey, Bob, show us how you make a mistake and make a million dollars.
Yes, make me a failure, too, Bob.
I'm going to get you a drink.
Oh, Bob, show me the witching ways of surfing the luck plane.
Look, Bob, I can hang, too.
Oh, and when Bob forgets to screw up.
Oh, when he screws up by not screwing up.
It's like breaking the bank at Monte Carlo.
It's such blinding, radiant luck that you can't believe it.
You appreciate the good things in life if you don't waste your time counting on them to happen.
But if you expect the bad things, every day can be like Christmas.
Just forget yourself and go with a path of least resistance.
Sharpen your abnormality focus.
You might do only one weird thing exceptionally well.
Well, take that weird thing and turn it around and milk it dry.
Milk it for Bobby.
Tap it.
Strip mine it.
There's strip mining your slack away.
Leaving toxic slacks.
And toxic poisons to leach into your psychic water table.
Fight the conspiracy.
Give up for Bob.
On and off the road to Bob.
We are marching forward blind.
He has gouged out both our eyes.
And he's laughing close.
Behind.
He will sell us back our eyes.
When we join his noble plan.
For just $19.95.
And a taste of our woodland.
On and off the road with Bob.
He has handed us the wheel.
And he cuddles up with mine.
As he counts himself a fiel.
Our eyes are on the road.
And we're on the road.
But Bob forgot to say.
That the steering wheel went bust.
The road carries us away.
On and off the road for Bob.
We forgot why we came here.
We have quit all of our jobs.
Like a headlight frightened deer.
He has lit the sacred pipe.
And he's smiling at us.
And he's smiling at us now.
On and off the road.
He's Bob.
He's our bull god.
We are his town.
That hurt Bob.
Bob where are you?
Who are you?
A friend of Bob's.
They found my fingerprints on my ashtray.
And not yours.
It had Bob's fingerprints all over it.
And he and I both would agree that Bob's not a nice person.
That was enough for them.
It's funny because it's true.
And hey.
Admit the truth to yourself now.
You know you'll be clawing your way to the head of the line to buy a membership.
When the atomic heat rays are so close they're welding your butt cheeks together.
Oh but don't come crying to me.
I can't wait for X day.
I love the taste of human flesh.
I just haven't had it cooked yet.
We get down and dirty in this church because religion happens to be a dirty, dirty business.
This church is a lot like an old car sometimes.
In that it's the dirt that's the only thing that's holding it all together.
And Bob.
Bob is the bondo that keeps our sagging bumpers up.
Bob.
Isn't that the one thing that we're here for after all, sneakers?
The dirt.
So let's dig in and dish it up.
It's crammed packed with minerals too.
So don't settle for the poop du jour.
Excremeditate your troubles away with the armor-piercing slack of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
I'm mighty, I'm full of it.
But I'm going to let it go.
And you've got to let it go dear friend.
Just as sure as you can bet it, one of those two greatest guys up there is going to let go just as you is letting go.
Bob, what's Ms. Preskey's heat so far?
Right Jack.
Ah.
Yes.
Well, how do you feel Ms. Preskey?
Sick.
Ah well, you can afford it now love.
But like the good book says, there are bigger deals to come.
Oh Christ.
Right Jack.
Uh oh.
Let me keep the do littlehammer.
Snatch on the next opportunity.
Don't know much.
I can't say go.
I hope things work out the way you want them to.
Thanks, bud.
I'm hoping too.
Oh, crap! It's on fire!
The Hour of Slack
From the Church of the Subgenius
For more information on the Church of the Subgenius,
write for free information from P.O. Box 204-206 Austin, Texas 78720
Or you can send tapes and things, CDs, whatever, to me, stang, at subgenius.com
by email or to Post Office Box 181417
Click on the link.
Leafland Heights, Ohio 44118
And friends, this music in the background is the amino acid.
Uh-oh!
Bob will fall down, go boom!