We don't have no time for that
All we want is an hour of slack
Do you know where it's at?
All you need is an hour of slack
Everyone needs a strained jacket
Pull it tight, let's all slack it
Hold on tight, let's all slack it
The Steaming Sack of Slack Part 8
So give me B.O.B. or kill me B.O.B.
Slack ain't free, you gotta pay your fee B.O.B.
How is it I'm so happy? How is it I'm so free?
How is it that I shun the stench of mediocrity?
I'll let you know the secret to slack and kill your job
Dig deep into your pockets and praise the face of Bob
So give me B.O.B.
B.O.B.
Or kill me B.O.B.
Slack ain't free, you gotta pay your fee B.O.B.
For more information visit subgenius.com
Now the world don't move to the beat of just one drum
But my bear up for you, my bear up for some
A man is bolder, yes a man of means
Been along come two, they got nothing but the genes
But they got different strokes it takes
Different strokes it takes
Different strokes to move the world
Well everybody's got their special kind of story
Everybody finds a way to shine
Little matter what you got, not a lot
So what they'll admit, you'll have yours and I'll have mine
And together we'll be fine
Cause it takes different strokes to move the world
Yes it does, it takes different strokes to move the world
So what they'll admit, you'll have yours and I'll have mine
Everything we know is right
We're not leaving without a fight
No matter how they insist
It's time we all resist
Be an exception to the law
Let's beat the irritating flaw
Wise men go against the wisdom
Time for a kink in the system
Wanna be a disappointment
Gonna be the fly in the ointment
We don't need an advance directive
Backwards through is the right perspective
The kink is up, we won't be fooled
Time for us to change the rules
We don't need a protective sack
Time to get them off our back
Give the man a big surprise
Bend them over, cranialize
Wanna be a disappointment
Gonna be the fly in the ointment
The stage is set for the unexpected
You can be the deciding factor
Back and forth like a bunch of jerks
Throw a monkey wrench in the works
When it all becomes a drag
It's not too late to be the snag
Mediocrity is like an infection
Stand up and make an objection
Wanna be a disappointment
Gonna be the fly in the ointment
Wanna be the fly in the ointment
Make your own specialty
You and I don't have the discipline
Sew rib Bank
Creep argue
Make your own specialty
Thank you.
Stop it on your sensible comrade Trump
Your big American oil bill took a dump
When they ask you what you know
You just say nichimo, nichimo, nichimo, nichimo
Howdy doody, howdy doody, comrade Putin
Your American mineral rights deal took a poopin'
When they ask you what you know
You just say nichimo, nichimo, nichimo, nichimo
In Russian, nichimo means nothing
In English, it means even less
All of the world's leaders
Are leading the world into a mess
It can't happen here
I'm telling you, my dear
That it can't happen here
Because I've been checking it out, baby
I checked it out a couple of times
And I'm telling you it can't happen here
Oh, darling, I'm telling you it can't happen here
Darling, it's important that you believe me
Bop, bop, bop, bop
That it can't happen here
Who could imagine
That they would freak out
Somewhere in Kansas
Kansas, Kansas, Kansas
Who could imagine
That they would freak out
In Minnesota
Minnesota, Minnesota
Central Virginia
Los Angeles, Maldives
Stormwater, Arkansas
Few of those in the lab
МУЗЫКА
Hey everyone, thank you for watching
See all the bottles on the board
Diplomas
час
Thank you.
Susie,
you just got to town
and we've been
very interested in your development.
Forget it.
It can't happen
here.
Organic
head.
Dear friends, the mothers of invention there.
That's a real oldie from one of the earliest albums from good old Frank Zappa.
Before that, yeah, that was Lonesome Cowboy Dave's new song,
Dasvidanya, Comrade Trump.
It's amazing, but true.
Before that, there was an instrumental called Comrade, We Have Cabbage,
or something like that, from the Rudy Schwartz Project, relatively new album.
And the song before that, that sounded kind of Devo-like,
was Exposed Foreheads doing Fly in the Ointment.
Exposed Foreheads is spelled with a big X and a big numeral.
And at the very beginning, we had an opening collage,
the steaming sack of slack number eight,
from Reverend Dew-8, or Dwight, or however you pronounce that.
That involves numerals, too.
And Reverend Burn Bridges did that strange version of the song,
Different Folks.
Now, Dave and Princess We are going to call in in a minute,
but I have to read a rant real quick.
By the good Reverend Roger.
Dear humans,
just look at yourself.
Just look.
Sitting there drinking crappy beer,
stuffing your face with processed lard,
and worshiping the wrong Jesus.
How do you people do it?
How do you get through one single day without blowing your own heads off?
Hemingway was way smarter than you, and he couldn't do it.
So how the hell do you?
Not only do you not put your head on the ground,
but you also have to get yourselves out of your misery.
You breed like fruit flies.
At the time of this writing, there are seven and a half billion of you,
and there's a net gain of 200 more primates per minute.
That's New York, all five boroughs added every 14 days.
Stop.
Buy a condom already.
I mean, I don't care what happens to you,
but when you drown in your own crap, you're going to drag us down, too.
I find that to be very rude.
It's worth mentioning, at this point in my job,
what I get paid for,
is to measure the pace at which you fail
and to make guesses at what those failures will entail.
In many ways, it's a dream job,
watching monkeys ignore things like the shrinking availability of potable water,
power and communications infrastructure rot,
and the complete failure of Western nation states to shield their infrastructure from cyber attack.
Don't even get me started on your sewers,
but I can almost guarantee that someone hearing this will be killed by their toilet.
At this point, most primates will show me their inflamed red arse
and start screeching that climate change is a libtard myth.
It's almost understandable,
given that many supposedly educated people build massive models of climate change
based on incomplete data, which always turn out to be wrong.
It happens so consistently that a paranoid person might suspect
that they're being paid to be wrong.
A sane person might point out that paranoid people are just more aware of their surroundings.
And this is why the Church of the Subgenius keeps Reverend G. Gordon Gordon on retainer
with his signature baseball bat.
It's got three nails driven through it.
The first nail?
Is truth.
The second nail?
Is the facts.
The third nail is PAY ATTENTION!
And then there's generally a lot of running around and screaming
and the boys in the boardroom get a new, if final, view
on the nature of a market correction.
Or kill me.
So says the good Reverend Roger.
And it looks like the bad Dr. Sinister wandered in while I was on the mic there.
I guess you didn't know I was going to be here.
I saw the new i-van.
Yep.
There's a lot of things new this time.
This is my first time in seven months I've done a show in the actual studio.
We've missed you.
Well, thanks for not changing everything.
Except for that over there.
Oh, well, I'm not going to look at that.
And I don't think the listeners should either.
Just don't look at it.
It's easier than it looks at first.
I'll show you later.
It's my first time I've done a show without Princess Wee here.
Yeah, where's she at?
She's watching the new old hound dog.
Damn it.
This is his first.
We have a dog now.
Okay.
I inherited my father's dog.
He's a big dog.
A big tree, treeing walker coon hound is the actual coon hound.
Yeah, that is the.
That sounds racist.
He is bred to hunt raccoons.
Okay.
And he does.
He trees them.
He's a treeing walker coon hound.
He's not a walker.
He was bred by somebody named Walker or his ancestors were.
Anyway, he freaks out in the bad weather.
And so does that poor old lonesome cowboy Dave.
If that's him.
What's wrong here?
Hello?
Well, hello.
A big tree.
What?
Treeing walker coon hound is the actual.
It's Princess Wee.
I'm waiting to get on the air.
You're on the air.
And I can tell because.
You didn't turn your radio down.
Well, I have a complicated situation here with this dog.
Turn.
Please, listener, turn your radio off.
Dammit.
See what I mean?
Because it's stormy tonight in Cleveland, we dast not leave the dog alone.
It is a dark and stormy night.
Yeah.
He's huge.
But he doesn't like thunder.
The gods of thunder make him quiver and pee.
And so we could have brought him to the station.
I wonder if that's something that wolves have.
Like, you know, how many other canine species out there that are less domesticated have a fear of thunder?
Because, I mean, for a wild animal, that would be a real disadvantage.
I mean, like, you know, when I was a little kid, I didn't like thunder.
You know, I remember going to my first Fourth of July fireworks.
I nearly jumped out of my skin.
It was so horribly loud.
But you'd think that an adult animal would have eventually gotten used to that kind of stimulus.
And I wonder if it's the domestication that makes dogs afraid of thunder.
I figure chances are he was out in the woods one day and got almost struck by lightning.
And that just put the fear of the thunder god Wotan in him.
He quivers like that even when he's safe in the mighty Stang Ranch house.
But now he's in Cleveland Heights at the Slacker Mansion.
And we were afraid to leave him alone.
This would be his first time alone.
We didn't want to do it during a thunderstorm.
That's all.
You're just being a responsible doggy, Danny.
Yeah.
So, Princess Wee, are you there?
And yes, you wouldn't believe, but when you were speaking on the radio, your canine friend was staring at the speaker.
He heard your voice and he recognized it.
Yeah.
Oh, well.
Next RCA mascot.
I could hear it too with a seven-second delay.
So this is the first time I've done the show with hearing aids.
The first time without Princess Wee.
The first time that I won't have my eardrums blown out by the headphones when I take over after the show?
Maybe.
Yeah.
They're turned up all the way.
The first time I've done a show with a bionic stent in my heart.
And the first time I've ever done a show weighing only 158 pounds.
So I had a heart attack while I was in Texas.
And they made me stop eating bacon and ranch-style beans and anything canned.
And they made me walk on treadmills while they monitored me.
And now I'm this old skinny little sacred scribe.
You have led a much more ascetic life.
No, actually, more athletic was more what it was partly.
I wonder where Dave is.
I was expecting Dave to call in.
That old cowboy.
You know, oh, I've got a copy of his book here.
Dave's book?
Yeah, this is a proof copy.
Wow.
We haven't released it yet because we're still fixing little technical things in it.
If you need editing help, I can do that.
Oh, well, we've actually done most of that, I think.
Okay.
I'm not going to change.
Let me tell you, before he calls in, it's really good.
It takes some work getting started, like many good books do.
It's written a little bit like a clockwork orange in that it's partly in future slang invented by the lonesome cowboy.
And I had, of course, read it before I decided to publish it.
But I hadn't read it as a book.
I read it on a screen.
It's just not the same.
When I was able to peruse it at my leisure in my extra meditation chamber, it turned out to be quite a page turner.
As I was saying, I got towards the ending.
I was like, is our hero, Standard Mosek, going to be a happy ending or a terrible ending or what?
And I won't spoil anything.
But Jimmy and Guitar and Tina on vocals, that band was quite a page turner.
Yeah.
Jimmy Page Turner?
Remember Tina Turner and Jimmy Page when they had that one band for a while?
And Bob Keesham, of all people, Captain Kangaroo, was the lead singer.
That was a short-lived band.
It was great, though.
Tina Turner didn't even sing.
She just played tambourines and oranges.
And she was singing along.
And I was like, what's that?
And where's Dave?
That's very strange.
You know what it is?
I bet he doesn't know what time it is.
Or he fell asleep.
He exists outside of time.
Dr. Sinister, when I was doing the show at Stang Ranch, we had to call Dave.
He couldn't call in.
I had to call him.
And a couple of times I had to wake him up.
Oh, I see.
Sometimes when No Money Mark calls in, I have to wake him up during the show.
Our friend Dr. Hal has been known to fall asleep with his head leaning against a microphone.
It may sound like a joke, but it's not.
The smoking loon once passed out drunk on the air here.
Puzzling evidence show takes place in the middle of the night, though.
Well, of course.
It would have to.
But it's not going to happen.
That kind of thing isn't allowed during the daytime.
The Puzzling Evidence Show, friends.
That's actually the first subgenius radio show.
It started in 1982.
Hour of Slack didn't start until 1985.
And by the way, this would be episode number 1,624.
Pretty good.
My heart beats still.
Oh, my God.
1,600 hours of slack.
1,600 hours of Slack, and only about a hundred of them were reruns.
By the way, thank you for playing those shows and babysitting every week, Dr. Sinister.
Well, I mean, the babysitting, it's been a good supplement to my allowance.
And your diet, since you've always enjoyed the flesh of human immensely.
Dignified plants.
spawn well of course doesn't everybody well no no not on the air anyway come on
you don't know what you're missing yeah the man could be listening you know i i or even worse the
woman might be listening no man see i uh even better i mean you know i i don't believe in in
waste you know when it comes to uh using uh the resources because you know it's expensive to raise
animals and especially human animals um so we you know i follow that ancient tradition of using all
parts of the animal and uh you know i like to uh render the fat of these babies and i have to make
sure they haven't been baptized and then i can um make an ointment out of that rendered fat which
will give me the power of flight at least that's what the malleus maleficarum said but then those
mormons came along and invented baptism of the dead so one time i was flying along with my
unbaptized baby ointment um in effect and then i guess some mormon baptized that dead baby
oh no no so retroactively i fell from the sky well you know you would hate to be a troll hunter
wearing what you thought was non-christian baby fat oil only to have it post saved by some
nosy pesky mormon suddenly the trolls would smell you you smell just like a christian baby
or a mormon baby like no controls smell the blood of a mormon
man that's a question i don't know by the way don't get close to me not that i'm worried that
you would but i've got that cold that cold yep i got that cold off that plane no it's not it's uh
it was from i i had to fly to la and back last week as soon as we got back from driving back
from texas i had to get the yard ready to put a fence up to keep the dog in then i had to jump
on a plane fly to la and party with roger
and superstars and fly back and now i have the cold and i'm sure all the rock stars and superstars
do too i know you want to know which rock stars i was part of i am a little curious well the only
one was jerry casale of the devos okay um and we'll be seeing him and his wife reverend galaxyna
who's also a subject of the show and i'm sure all the rock stars and superstars do too i know you want to know
jerry casale of the devos okay um and we'll be seeing him and his wife reverend galaxyna
um at the devotional in august but he was kind enough to be in the documentary movie that these
conneyites are making out of austin do you know anything about that what movie well um
a few months back i was approached by a team of experienced filmmakers in austin
who happen to be mostly dames
and they wanted to start work on a subgenius documentary if i had the archives in the
interest and i said yeah i've been kind of trying to start something like that for 35 years
whatever happened to those people that uh at wisteria a few years ago again i never have
been able to they did they vanished all the only reason they did it was just to get nude pictures
of subgenia at the baptism
no in 3d yeah it was in 3d but that would make it even worse i mean yeah they go the only thing
you make it worse than that would be smell a vision oh no is that dave trying to call in
finally hello hello dave oh hello dave oh god i got interrupted for a while but you haven't picked
up for a long time well yeah yeah i yeah you called 10 minutes late princess we is on the
other line i think or did i just have to call you i don't know i don't know i don't know i don't know
i don't know okay alright i're gonna always see if i can call you and give you all a reminder
of the look and Alexa was to you raw girls so i thought i had to ask you random time
you kind of nice picture of yeah well it's me i'm getting showyDj
alright was it me i think i felt safe would it be me or would it be the line in that was
you and i was whispering my questions to you that day oh when somebody asked me to tell
else to crisis is a big one well i really want to put out that it was confined just
fresh mind you had a stupid question like i know i wanted to just lock all these little
bol structure and to broadcast and it was ridiculous i only had like voters should be
Turn to enter your number or code and try again.
Well, here's another first for this show.
This is the first time we've ever had anyone besides Lonesome Cowboy Dave call in simultaneously.
And I just learned how to do that.
He's a man who dresses, who likes to wear ladies' clothes, and has a huge proboscis in the middle of his forehead, and he's got, like, elf ears.
No, that's Dammit, the dog.
No, that's, that's, it is?
Yeah, Princess, we, Princess, Dave, Princess, we had to stay home with the dog because it would be his first night at the radio station.
We didn't want to do it during a thunderstorm.
So she's on the phone, and you're on the phone, and that's another first.
Yeah, it's delightful.
It really is to have this roundtable conversation about absolutely freaking nothing.
Did you play Doris Bedania von Tomeret Hump?
Yeah, I sure did.
Oh, I missed that.
I think it sucked, but I like it anyway somehow because it's kind of strange.
Well, Dave, I improved it.
Oh, that's great.
There were three places in the sound file that were 100% volume.
They were just little smack noises like that.
And when I lowered them, I could bring the rest of the volume up, and lo and behold, you could actually understand the words once it had been processed.
I'm sorry, I missed that.
I was in a turlid.
I was in a turlid when that happened, and I felt kind of funny for a little while.
I got reorganized and came down as quickly as I got the message from it.
I knew you were in the toilet when I played it.
I knew you were in the bathroom when I played it.
And that must have also been while I was trying to connect my speakers to my computer.
It's because my guts are out of radency.
And that's the same thing about your CD player, or at least whatever, homongifier.
What is it, an iDoc?
It's a homongifier.
Homongifier.
They had those in the South where Stan was raised, right?
We used hollow logs where I grew up, man.
Homongifier.
We used big logs to listen through.
I used to have a kookamongifier.
We used to take grapevines and smoke them like cigarettes.
Did you ever do that?
Anybody from North Dakota?
Oh, you?
You had grapes.
Oh, you're one of those rich kids that had grapevines.
No, these are wild grapes.
We had to smoke old tires.
We had to wear these old sandals and things.
And shoes.
That's all we had to smoke.
I smoked shoes before, man.
What are you, imputing my...
Hell yeah, I smoked shoes and hats for me.
And I smoked the whole trailer park just because I had to keep my nose out of trouble.
What about banana peels?
Didn't you guys ever smoke them?
No.
How about corn silk?
Corn silk, we did try.
I read about that as a kid.
What?
You can smoke that and get cancer just like with cigarettes?
Oh, boy, I want to be like my parents.
Yeah, get cancer like my parents.
Yeah.
See, we called them, the grapevines, wild grapevines, we called them stogies.
Because they resemble the cigar.
If you got them close enough to the big branch things there.
Oh, and they lost.
Oh, so it is a strange taste.
Oh, the grapevines are pretty old, huh?
Why would you smoke grapevines when you could be smoking trailer quarts?
I just don't get it.
Or salvia divinorum.
I said I was smoking...
It was funny, as a kid, they didn't know about salvia back then.
But it was still legal back then.
Right, but it hadn't been invented.
Oh, yes, it had not been invented.
Oh, it's elaborate.
You know, not really.
It was kind of reconstructed from an age-old myth.
Is that St. Pancreas and the hot dog people?
Do you remember his many, many, many, many, many, many works?
St. Pancreas?
A lot of his state development, but you know what I'm saying?
No, I usually don't know what you're saying.
He's the patron saint of diabetics.
Go ahead and mock me down, dude.
Did you know somebody named St. Clair is the patron saint?
Of television?
I did not know that.
Yeah, why would there even be one?
Well, hey, you know, I pray to the patron saint of sales.
Yeah, that's Bob.
And a lot of sales are done over TV.
I don't know that I would advise praying to Bob Dobbs.
Well, you know what I mean by praying to him.
You know, it's not a traditional prayer in that sense.
Right.
When you just shriek out,
something like, Bob, darn it!
That's about as close as it gets.
I mean, every, every, you know,
and every orgasmic scream is a prayer to Connie.
Yeah.
Well, that's a nice way of looking at it.
The problem with praying is,
you never know who else is going to be listening.
Besides the one you're praying to,
probably some other entity might be tuning in
just to find out who's going to be listening.
So, you know, you're going to have to ask God
to do something about what it is you're most afraid of
or what you most want so that they can do the opposite.
What, who you, they are crazy?
Well, I've ascended to a certain level of sainthood
and divinity myself, so I'm not really afraid of them.
Well, that's because you stink like marmalade now.
Back in the old days,
we'd have our caffeine crying out at the bar.
They'd grow huge.
Look who's talking.
More like stink like Marmite.
Huge growth would come out of their foreheads.
And then the people would ask them,
what are you thinking about?
Can't you see?
You just put your hand on my forehead.
Man, those were the days.
Those were the daves.
Those were the daves of our lives.
Back when there was more than one.
Yep.
But one by one.
These are the daves I know, I know.
These are the daves I know.
Not a monochromatic ooze.
One by one, the daves were carved off of the church body.
Sold to the highest bidder.
Each of them grew off into its own church.
Much the lesser was the church once the deans were trained.
There were a lot of daves that had to be shelved.
You know, Jayner was a dave.
I'm an original.
I'm not parenthetical either.
I speak for a whole generation of sandwich heads and freaks
and buzz babies.
And anything...
Anything...
They think...
You think...
Oh, never mind.
It's just too hard to describe.
Bob told us not to think.
Not the way you're thinking.
We're supposed to, at best, do break thinking.
Although that's kind of old-fashioned now.
And you can get hurt that way.
Yeah.
Non-think was another approach.
I love that one.
That was my favorite.
Non-think.
Well, that's real easy for most people.
It just comes naturally.
For most people, it's really difficult, though,
when you think of the answer.
The hypothetical parts of it,
of having no...
holding no thought in your brain
for longer than 20...
You know, like a piece of bologna
can speak to you in many...
You know, it's...
It's the same.
Buddhists pay extra not to think.
Buddhists work hard to get to the point
where they don't have to keep desiring and fretting.
Maybe that's smart.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Why not just hit yourself in the head real good
with a big rubber mallet every time you wake up?
I don't know.
Like so many subgeniuses do.
Go home and bury that mallet
so that at any time,
when you feel disruptions occur,
you can just beat the hell out of yourself.
Well, not everybody uses a mallet.
Some of them use dope,
or beer,
or TV,
or pornography,
or a porcupine,
or a ball-peen hammer,
which has a very, very different type of consciousness
explanation than the rubber mallet does.
The rubber mallet just kind of knocks it out
all across the board,
whereas the ball-peen hammer,
if it's applied by a doctor,
can take out just specific things,
like your...
Like balls and your peen.
Right.
Or your math, for instance,
or your emotions,
or, well, your higher emotions, anyway.
It depends on where they whack you,
you know,
and where they hit you.
They poke the pen up your nose,
or up your eye socket.
That's why the Dosh Bedaniah Trump song
was done at Tim Dorman's place,
because he's like one of those few people
that knows how to keep his scrotum
from the rest of it.
You know, keep those ideas separate.
At least that's what I've been told.
Okay.
Sure.
Yeah.
So what's wrong?
It's not like I invented the concept
of scrotal disembodiment.
It's like I know how to read, man, you know?
It's pinky in the suffragette.
They're hiding in the customized cool bars
and up above in the furniture.
You know, this is the first time
I've been in the station
since the new president was enacted
and enunciated in.
And if you're the prime minister...
Because I've been gone.
...of Montenegro...
It feels like he's always been president.
Really.
I just, I got used to him so fast.
That was the whole idea, I think.
That's what they were banking on.
Yeah, I've spent a good chunk of my life,
you know, having a president to hate.
And the last eight years,
you know, I had some disagreements with the guy,
but I didn't hate him.
Well, now it's back to normal.
Okay, yes, of course, we hate the president.
Like, that's the way things have always been.
So it's almost like a return to normalcy.
Yeah, it is.
I guess when you think about it that way,
I mean, yeah.
Bush-like.
You know, it's so easy to hate.
You have so many manners.
Well, actually, you know, by comparison,
W was downright likable.
Second term W.
Right.
And George H. was just a sweet old...
Geysar?
Geysar, yeah.
And Reagan and Nixon were like...
They're like brilliant super football players
that could also do brain surgery
and high calculus relatively.
I mean, this is all just relative.
The Bushes are compared to Trumpskins?
Anybody compared to Trumpskin
is like a beautiful, athletic, super genius.
Well, you know, I mean,
you can't have him...
You can't have Trump working out
because the body only has so much energy
and he can't use that energy.
Right.
It's like sperm.
Trump said he does not exercise
because he believes that every human
is like a battery
and there's enough juice in there
and you can't recharge it.
Right, can't recharge it.
You know, exercise doesn't recharge the battery.
What the hell?
We don't need a president like that.
That's going to make the kids get fat again.
Said...
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, it could...
It's like the limited sperm thing.
It's to get kids to quit
jacking off and exercise.
I think Trump might be the fattest president
we've had since Taft.
I mean, even when Bill Clinton was at his chubbiest,
I don't think he was quite as full-bodied
as the Trumpster.
For people who don't know,
of course, he didn't use furosemide
or for ointment.
One thing I can say for Trump,
he does represent his support team
as his voters.
He represents them.
He looks like a large percentage of them.
He talks and writes
like many of them.
I don't know that he looks like many of them.
Every time he...
Every time he does...
Well, Bush spent most of his life in Texas,
not...
He was born in Connecticut,
but he did spend most of his life in Texas.
No, he moved to Texas
when he was in his 30s.
By then, you definitely have your own...
No, he went to SMU for college.
Okay.
Well, SMU, where's that?
In Dallas.
He lived in Midland for a long time, too.
Yeah.
Yeah, and remember...
Of course, Poppy Bush adopted
kind of a Southern accent,
and he was definitely a Yankee.
All right, so you'll say...
It's an infectious accent.
That's the thing.
So that you'll sound like the Republican voters.
Now they all do.
They say nuclear and...
If I moved to the South,
I'd probably start speaking
with a Southern accent very quickly.
My wife says y'all now.
She was in...
That's a useful word.
Texas for two winters.
Every other European language
has a plural second-person pronoun.
I think y'all is a useful word.
Or yins.
Yins.
In Pittsburgh, they say yun.
Yeah.
Yuns is Midland speech.
Yus is Northern speech.
And y'all is Southern speech, Pata.
Oh, yeah.
Y'all.
All y'all.
Southern anywhere.
It's Southern New York,
Southern Michigan,
Southern Ohio,
and it's Southern Cleveland.
Like Parma.
You knew what I was trying to say.
Yeah.
Well, you know, I got...
Princess, we and I,
after seven months,
you get...
Well, a lot quicker than that.
You get used to being
in a neighborhood
that's the exact opposite
of the one you've lived in
for the last 20 years.
You must be going...
In every possible way.
You must be going crazy.
That's true.
No, it makes for a good contrast.
Yeah.
I get to know that the people
who think the inner cities
are just hotbeds of crime,
I get to know they're wrong.
And the people who think
the small towns
are all hotbeds of crime,
stupidity,
well, they're wrong too.
Although,
there's plenty of both.
In both.
I have to say...
Both of them are hotbeds
of stupidity and crime.
Yes.
I heard that every time
a lovable Clevelander
moves to Texas
or another Southern state,
an angel loses its wings.
Oh, wings are way...
I'm just...
I'm sorry.
The fact that you're...
The fact that you're trying
to move down there
permanently kind of hurts.
It's like I lost my sister
to North Carolina.
And now I'm losing you
and Princess Weeda, Texas.
It's rough.
Well, no.
We're still going to be doing
X-Day up here
and Starwood up here,
assuming we have to keep doing
anything after this July 5th.
Which, by the way,
people who do wander
into the X-Day campground
this year
really do stand a chance
of being in a major
motion picture...
Well, documentary.
But they're all brown shirts
staying next to problem.
They're all members
of the private mockery
of the Mango Mussolini himself.
Who?
People at X-Day?
They don't even have shirts.
What are you talking about?
Of course not.
Much less brown ones.
They're sky-clad,
bare-naked brown shirts.
And the brown shirts
are only brown
because they, you know,
kind of soil themselves
a little bit.
That's all.
Yeah, they're saving
on toilet paper.
It's just not a big deal.
Oh, look at the brown pantos.
Brown pantos.
A lot of subgenius doctors
used to do that.
Soil their...
What?
It's a shower curtain
related thing.
You wouldn't understand.
Let's change the subject.
In fact, in about...
In about three minutes,
I'm going to change
the subject to some music.
And I'm sure the listeners
will be happy about that.
What have I got?
I had something coming.
Oh, the Psychoskeletons
have a new tune.
I left my list at home.
It has a title like...
Something like Psychodrums
or Schizophrenic Drums.
Why don't you just make up
the names of the bands
and the lyrics yourself?
You know, just make them up.
You don't need to go
all the way home right now
to get ready to...
No, that's what we do at X Day.
I'm not going to do that
all the time.
We make up the bands
then and there.
Anyway, yeah,
there's going to be...
What was the new slogan?
Bob Needs Women.
Nasty women
to be in the...
in the subgenius documentary
filmed by a bunch of nasty women.
Although you wouldn't think it
to look at them.
They look pretty...
pretty...
not nasty.
But looks are not important
in the Church of the Subgenius.
Just look at our grades.
They're terrible.
Yeah, and we can all be like
going to fetal positions
really quickly
and quite easily
and snap right back
into normal...
normal...
almost.
So, uh, okay.
Dr. Sinister has gone to go
look for something
to play on his show.
That's his way.
He doesn't really think about it
until he gets here.
I'm the opposite.
I start fretting about it
two hours before
it's time to go on the air.
I thought there was...
you were a colonialist
and that your grandpappy,
I think it was
Elmo P. Fordard,
and was the emperor
and transpector.
No, you're thinking of
Senator Cotton Ed Smith.
That was another ancestor.
Right, right, right.
Poon Pappy.
Or Dune Pappy.
Okay.
Okay, friends,
you're listening to
The Hour of Slack.
This is around
the 1600th episode.
We've been doing it
for over 35 years now.
And you probably know
all you want to know,
but just in case,
you could look
at subgenius.com.
And see about
this X-Day event
that happens on July,
early July,
and the Starwood event,
which happens
a couple weeks later
in the same place
in Southern Ohio,
and the devotional,
which is in August
in Cleveland.
And then we go back
to our fossil hunting.
And Dave,
I'm going to have to fade
you and Princess We out
because it's time
to put this music on.
I think.
If it were only
could be really
considered music,
and so be it.
Psychoskeletons are ooga.
Ooga.
Unfortunately,
we're not yellow swans.
I do wonder
why not yellow swans.
That's not sure at all.
I've been living
they're not gentlemanly
and not perfectly
hunting,
color or animal wenig.
as if they're
Thank you.