1, 3, 0, 1, 3, 1, 3, 0, 1, 3, 1, 3, 0, 1, 3.
1, 3, 0, 1, 3, 0, 1, 3, 0.
Imagine there's no garbage
It's easy if you
Don't have no one
Above us only
Imagine all the people
Living for
Bob
Peter Lorre
Careful now
Don't be so sure of yourself
Because
You are listening to Peter Lorre
You don't believe it?
Neither do I
They gone?
Yeah
They're gone
Huh?
Hmm?
Oh, no
Trapped
In a living nightmare
Don't shut up
Put me through to Dickson Bainbridge
I don't know how to dial
Thank you
Hello, my Bainbridge
It's Bobby Bob Bob
Bob
I'm outrageous
How dare he say such blasphemy
I've got to do something
Bob
There's nothing you can do.
I like.
Guess I'll just have to develop a sense of humor.
My baby was talking in her sleep.
She said, bye.
I said, what?
I said, I'm bye.
She said, no.
I mean a different bye.
So I asked her the next day.
I said, Jane.
She said, what?
I said, who's bye?
She said, you're bye.
I said, no.
I mean a different bye.
She said, go.
Frig.
Jig.
My baby was run over by a truck
It was a dodge
As she lay dying
She called for Bob
I touched her hand and said I'm here
She said no
I mean a different Bob
My baby was dark and in a sleep
A different Bob
Their friends
And their friends
That was by
The Colorblind James Experience
That's the actual name
Of that actual band
That did that actual song
A different Bob
By the Colorblind James Experience
Before that collage is
Thanks to
Lemur mostly
Fernand and Andy Lemur
The very beginning Stangolini ad
Was from I Dr. Mr. Sistar
And
Tom
Holm
And Throwback Soul
Contributed little tiny bits
Of the bits and pieces there
And probably any other bits and pieces
You hear later on will be from
Lemur
And where's my
Background
There's some background noise
Yeah there is
A little bit
Frozen
Am I hearing
Am I hearing things?
Yeah okay
I'm hearing things
Friends
We have
We're all in the actual studio
Station right now
And there
We have a special guest
Tonight
Can I say that?
Is that a
Special
An excellent guest
A very differently
Ability guest
That being
Friends
The great
Bishop Joey
From the first
Church of the Last Laugh
He's right here
Among us
Today
What a
There we go
We must note
The complete differences
Between the one known as Bob
And the one known to my people
As his son
These two have been at each other's
Throats for a long time
And it is time not only to bury the hatchet
In each other's heads
But also to forget
Why we came here
Well I don't know about that man
Cause I mean
No no no
Let me take it from here
Okay the first church
The last laugh
Is pretty funny
And yeah they're gonna get
The last laugh
That's right
We're gonna have the last laugh
Cause we came all the way out
From the left coast
To help convert you people
Who don't know that
You already are
Members of the first church
Of the last laugh
For the fastest growing snack religion
150% less dogma
To light religion
One whole new day a year
And today is not it though
So April 1st is
So you gotta get ready for the parade
So what are you gonna do
You guys think you're so stupid
Oh yeah
You guys think
We're gonna show you stupid
We're throwing down stupid pal
Come on out
Real stupid anchors
In the streets of San Francisco
In the financial district
J.R. Bob Dobbs is so much dumber
Than Saint Stupid
I can't even
He's like a hundred thousand
Million times dumber
I don't think so
Oh no he's a hundred thousand
Million plus one dumber
I don't think so
Bob is godzillion times dumber
Than Saint Stupid
Oh no
Bob's a baby Godzilla
Saint Stupid is the Godzilla
The Godzilla
No godzillion
No oh gazillion
Plus one
Godzillion
No there is no
Godzillion is the last number
There is no godzillion
Get off the table
Stay
Okay
Oh
Well look
It's true that there has been
Long been
In fact since
What did we decide
79 both church started
I started at Saint Stupid
In 1979
You started the
Whatever you do
No
I went to work
For J.R. Bob Dobbs
In 1979
You call that work
Bob started the church
Of the subgenius
In 1953
I'll have you know
Oh 53
Oh really
You got some documentation
On that
Show it
Put it up on the wall
Now
Put it up buddy
Put the docus on the wall
I really want me to do that
Put it up
That would be like
Me showing off my tattoos
I don't think you want to see
Where my tattoos
I don't want to see
Where your tattoos are
I want to show
East 9th
And Euclid
I don't think we want to see
Either one of your tattoos
Friends
Bishop Joe
Yes it says here
That was a slip
He actually did a show
Earlier today
He's an actual
It's a one man show
And get this
This is the actual title
Of the show
Subhuman
It was a one man show
At the Lake Erie College
A benefit for extended housing
True tales from beneath the sea
A salty tale
Of danger
Discovery
And destiny
Now with extra salt
Ed is a
I mean a
Bigger than a
Bishop Joey
Is a local boy
And a graduate
Of Shaw High School
He's been performing
And teaching
In the San Francisco
Bay area
For 33 years
And that'll probably
Explain a lot
Way Bay
He is a member
Of the Tony Award winning
San Francisco
Mime Troop
No not that kind of mime
SFMT.org
They just
What was that?
SFMT
When you say the word
SF Mime Troop
You have to say
The thing
The tag
Right
SF Mime Troop
No it's
It's parenthetical
No not that kind of mime
And then the website
SFMT.org
That's true
Close parenthesis
That's a parenthetical
Mime Troop
And has performed
With these
Minor two bit
Bunches
The San Francisco Opera
Oakland Symphony
The Antenna Theater
Four bit
The Berkley
Mime Troop
Six bits
Which probably is
That kind of mime
Movie credits include
The Right Stuff
Big deal
Tucker
One of the greatest
Movies ever made
Howard the Duck
Duck
How many people
Do you know
Who were in
Howard the Duck?
Yes
Cleveland
I blew away
From your shores
And bore fruit
On the far left
Of course
Right
It was Howard the Duck
I'm sorry
I have to apologize
For everybody
I was a duck hunter
On the TV screen
When Howard
Is up against
He hits the streets
And he's running
Down the street
And he's freaked out
And he turns around
And looks in this TV window
That was you?
There was a TV
A cook taking
A casserole dish
Off some duck
And scooping up
And then there's
Another shot of a TV
With me being interviewed
As a duck hunter
And I'm going
I'm going to blast
Them feathered
Beep from the sky
That was me
I remember that part
I know
I felt it
Were you in the comic book?
No
I was not in the comic book
I take exception
To that movie
Because they actually
Shot that in Sacto
In Sacramento
I know
And in Lake Erie
Which is supposed
To be like this
I know
It was like
Lake Sacramento
Which you could actually
See across
And it's like
A huge pond
You know
So everybody
Was supposed to get it
But not
Teeters
So that's
That's why I argued
With the producer
And that's why
They shot me later
In a leg
And that's what
This wound is all about
It's a tough business
It's a tough
You're messing with
Hollywood
The families
And you mess with
You're going to
Pay the price
You know what I mean?
But why do they
Put an antenna
In here like this?
Tracking
Just tracking
It's just
You know
Tracking
Couldn't they
Just you know
Let's move on
To the next segment
Of the show
Shall we?
Okay now
The first church
To last last
Sponsors the
St. Stupid's Day
Parade in San Francisco
That'll be this
April 1st
Noon in the
Embarcadero Plaza
It'll be the
Weekday route
Through the
Financial district
On the sidewalk
With the
Proverbial stations
Of Stupid
The Federal Reserve
Bank where we
Thank them for
Turning our economy
Into a casino economy
The leap of faith
The tomb of stupid
The sock exchange
And tossing pennies
At the banker's heart
So come prepared
Come dressed for it
Noon
Embarcadero Plaza
San Francisco
Now back to you
Be there for the stations
Those are better
Like when Jesus
Falls down
And can't get up
And then the crippled
Guy comes
Comes over and
Shoots him
And then the
Roman centurion
Asks him if he
Wants another
Drink of water
That's the second
That's been going on
For how many
Thousands of years
Now the St. Stupid's
Day Parade
It'll be the
31st this year
Man
And I thought
I was tired of
X days
You can't even
Walk upstairs
And every year
He makes the
Point
Embarcadero
Biker
How many you
Got
How many you're
We've drilled
For X day
For
13 times
We are going
To strike
Greece
This year
I have faith
That this
This year
X day
Will be X day
Although technically
There were two
Drills
That we considered
Before
What we thought
Was July 5th
Church business
Is very complicated
Isn't it
Tomorrow might be
July 5th
For all we know
Listener
Really
And that doesn't
Matter where you're
Listening from
Or what day
Or time it is
Because
We are lost
In time
Yeah that was
A very important
Part of our
Doctrine at the time
Was that
X day
Had actually
Happened
And
Everybody was
Confused about it
And we're all now
On the ships
Speeding our way
Into wherever the hell
We're going and stuff
Planet X
Having everything
We want along the way
But we don't know it
We think
It didn't happen
So we think
We're still here
Doing this radio show
I know
Yeah it's complicated
You create your own reality
And unfortunately
The reality most people create
Is their cheesy apartment
Yeah
You know
Their crappy old
Comic book collection
And so forth
Bishop Joey was in town
To
To tell manly stories
About his adventures
As a mechanic
Aboard a diesel submarine
In the Pacific Ocean
Thousands of years ago
So this is a sub
Submarine
Subgenius show
That's right
And there have been
A lot of subs in the news
Genius
Piloted by geniuses
Yeah the FBMers
Are bumping into each other
In the ocean
The other ones
Are bumping into
The other surface vessels
And then the space junk
Is bumping into each other
It's getting very
Very crowded out there
Wait until the space junk
Bumps into the submarine
Then we'll have come
Full circle
Man
Are the poor voices
Made angry by the
FBJ
Suffering
We're working on
We gotta
Yeah we're looking at that
Right now
We have somebody
Who's thinking
They're tuna fish
Yes tuna fish
Yeah we have a tuna fish
Research council
That is
Hopefully will have
A reading for us tomorrow
So there's no problem
With the fish
The fish are happy
And what we do here
Content
First church of the last left
Submariner
Exposition
The fish have gone
Where the fish
Are supposed to go
Staying
Been relocated
So to speak
But they'll enjoy
Their new homes
In another
Terraformed environment
Well we had
The ocean
Is a whole
Another planet
That's twice as big
As the one we're used to
There's smokestack cities
Down under there
And big big titties
And everything
Just like it is up here
Only it isn't up here
Come on let's get wet
Let's get wet
We were watching that movie
Mysterious Island
Last night
That was based on
Jules Verne
Yeah
And you were showing
On your show today
You were showing that
Who's the guy who does that
Yeah
Who is that guy
Who's that guy
It wasn't George
Yeah
You know that guy
But it was a second
Another French dude
That did
Yeah
Amazing Jules Verne movie
Which I've seen on YouTube
And never elsewhere
Until your show
Bishop Joey really was
A sub
A bubble head
Genius
Bubble head
And I was a smoke boat
As well as being
A tea kettle
Bubble head
Smoke boat
Was the old diesel boat
And the tea kettle
Were the nuclear powered
Steam boat
So you have to differentiate
Or I'll kill you
Right right
No I got that impression
During the show
It's tradition
And you know
We had to
To stick with it
So you was
You was a bubble head
I was a bubble head
Yeah I was in the Navy
For seven years
That's right
And I told my little play here
Subhuman
Which I did
Is the story of how you
Choose going into
Why you know
And then what you choose to do
While you're in there
And what happens
And I had a little sea story
About my one cruise
And you know
It's slapstick
Philosophizing basically
With some sea jokes
And tattoo jokes
Thrown in
And toys
Toys
I got toys
He's got a
More toy
Little model
Submarines
Than anybody I ever saw
And he had a
A fish tank
In front of a television
The television was showing
Submarine movie clips
Of all ages
From the very beginning of time
To now
Every submarine movie
Carving the first submarine
Out of Iraq
Yeah
And then he would
Occasionally demonstrate
Submarine failures
By dropping models
Into the tank
Where they would just
Sink straight to the bottom
Oh those baking powder ones
Are the coolest things
I've ever seen
That's right
We were shown
The magic submarine
And yeah
I demonstrated them
And I asked the audience
And I hold up
And I said
Remember these
And I go
What is it powered by
And somebody goes
Baking soda
No no no
You blow up
If it's baking soda
It's baking powder
But one show
I go
Oh yeah
So when I ask
For the seven C's
There's also
I think
I'll buy a drink
For anybody
Who can name
The seven C's
So I asked
The crowd
I think it was in
Berkeley or something
Maybe San Francisco
And he says
Can you name
The seven C's
And somebody says
Yes
Salad dressing
High C
And he won
So it's
So it doesn't work
All the time
I mean you try
I mean I know
But I'm honing it
And I think I can get
This show up to speed
By next year
If I just get a grant
Ed St. Joey
What are the
Who and what
Are the seven C's
The North Pacific
The South Pacific
The North Atlantic
The South Atlantic
The Antarctic
The Arctic
And the Indian
Indian I mean
By Indian Ocean
I mean dots
Not feathers
Well and then there's
The sea at the center
Of the so called
Center of the earth
The internal
Underground sea
Which Jules Verne
Also talked about
The Spondyland
Did you know
That if you were
Actually to drop
A large object
Through the earth
It would go
Speed
Because of gravity
All the way
All the way down
To the core
Of the earth
And as it
Approaches the earth
The core
Would start to slow down
Because the
Gravitational activity
Would catch up
So by the time
It would get to the other side
It would actually break
Through the surface
Of the other side
And then the
Gravitational pull
Would go the other way
And it would go
All the way back
Like a pendulum forever
That's why I keep seeing
These Chinese coins
Pop up out of my backyard
And then fall
Straight back down
And the gold doubloons
Little kids
Little kids in China
Would drop them off
The Chinese Empire
State Building
And they'd bore through
And come up in my backyard
Go up about six feet
And then fall right back
Down the hole
That they burned
So bizarre
You know they heat up
Quite a bit
Going through the core
That's because of
The baking powder
No soda
Don't use the soda
That'll blow your ass off
Exploder
Yeah
Remember the exploder
Powders
And only use
Clabber girl
Baking powder
When you just need
To have that submarine
Go right to the bottom
Clabber
Is that what they're
Calling them now
Clabber girls
Yeah
Yeah go ahead
Check your prostitutes
Clabber girls
Well that was
Yeah
The insinuation
But it was nudge nudge
A wink
But at least I found
We're only trying to help
His friends
This station is here
To help
Yeah right
Yeah
Somebody was saying
The other day
On alt.slack
The only thing worse
Than an internet kook
Is an internet hero
But who is
Who's trying to help
Everybody else
Are there many of these now
Oh that's
That's all it is
That's what the internet is
It's just
It's like
I know
It's real big out there
It's the kook soap
Soapbox
But they all want to be heroes
But the thing is
Where the money to be made is
Is with their sidekicks
Cause side
Every hero has to have a sidekick
And there's a lot of people
Who can't be heroes
So the
Berkeley
Sidekick Institute
Well and the same is true
Of minions
For villains
You know
Berkeley sidekick
Well that's how you start
You start out
You start out as a minion
And then you graduate
Or henchman
Well go to henchman maybe
And then you go to
Sidekick
And then that's it
That's the top of the line
Cause only
Only people who are
In touch with their
Inner number two
Get to be sidekicks
Oh well I've been in touch
With my inner number two
For a long time
There's no compatriots
No colleagues
No
Well it starts out
With getting a hat
You have to find your
Character hat first
That's the first
My inner number two
Was wiped away
Yeah and then
You need to get to your
Your buzz phrase
You know like
You know
Gosh darn it
Or
Gee willikers
Mine was corn sarnit
Corn sarnit
So that's patented
You can't use that
You have to come up
With your own
Jeepers
So if I was like
Your sidekick or something
I could make a million bucks
I was just like
Screw you Joey
Joey
Buzz phrase
Each buzz phrase
Is guaranteed
Guaranteed six figure
Income for life
Wow
Mine was
Was Jeepers
When I was working
Under Bob
J.R. Bob Dobbs
He would
Make some
Pronounce
Announcements
You know
Look the volcano
Is exploding
And my line would be
Jeepers
And that was it
Yeah well
That's what I was there for
To say Jeepers Bob
Holy smokes
Cuts through the drama
And delivers a little
You know
Oh Philo was the one
Who always got to say
Holy smokes
That was the good one
Because Bob had the pipe
You know
So everybody remembered
Oh holy smokes
Nobody remembered Jeepers
How about this one
As cripes as my witness
Cripes
That'll work
Yeah that'll work
But you know
St. Stupid said
I know I know
But you know you never know
He said so far so what
He said if it's the truth
It's funny
He said the closer you get
The nearer you are
But more importantly
St. Stupid said
Remember
Don't forget
No no no
He said don't forget
Remember
I said remember don't forget
Or don't forget
Remember
No no
It's not
I don't think it was
Even either of the two
Those who nay
Cannot sow
We'll
We'll get back to you on that
It's one of them
Close
Close enough
Forget you not
Those who nay
Cannot sow
Which had something to do
With the horses
And Amish sewing machines
And something
Something
Aren't we supposed to do
Our puzzling evidence
Homage right now
Or something
Puzzling evidence
Homage
Are you
You're gonna
Who's puzzling evidence
He'll hear that
He'll know
He'll know who
Friends actually
Bishop
He'll know who's
A regular
Special
Oh there I went
I said it again
He's a regular
Guest
On
The puzzling evidence show
You don't hear him there
Every time
But he
Yeah I dropped an
Obama
So yeah
Sometimes on the hour of slack
You will
You have heard
Bishop Joey
But it's hard to hear him
Over Philo
But that's kind of true
Of everything
Yeah
He's inquisitive
Yes
Philo is
No
Philo is declarative
Ah
And extremist
Yeah
And loud
It's Philo
And
Hal
Doug Wellman
Yeah cause Doug Wellman's got
Like about five tape machines
Four
You know
Record players
Six CD players
You know
And five microphones
Open to the outside world
All on his side
Which he pots up and down
To slather
Everybody else
Across the asonics
Of Warfield
Well he usually waits
Until somebody is about
To get to a really good punchline
And that's when he
Jacks them all up
At once
Yeah
Or Philo jumps in
Over everything
But it's worth
Tracking him down online
There's people who catalog
All these
Puzzling evidence shows
And you can go there
And download them
To your iPod
And yeah
And walk through the streets
With a smile on your face
The easiest way
To find him
Is through
What about us
Philo's website
Quibble
Quiveringbrain.com
Oh yeah
Must see
Quiveringbrain.com
Leads to links
To the puzzling evidence show
So does subgenius.com
Leads to
If you look for the radio part
You click on the big button
On the first page
That says radio
I've actually had people go
I never can find
Where your show is
On your website
It's like the fourth word
Down from the top
The one that says radio
HOS
For our slack
Anyway
Yes they're all there
And Reverend Susie
The Philly
Lousy's show
On WREK in Atlanta
And the
The Ministry of Slack
Which is now
A podcast
And Bob's Golden Stream
That's another podcast
Oh nice
These are ones
That have never been mentioned
On this show before
Let's get them out
And I won't
I don't make any
I can advertise
These other subgenius shows
Because I don't make
Any money off of them
See the way
These stations
Are set up
You're not allowed
To talk about things
That would make
Money off of them
Money like X-Day
July 5th
Extermination
Or Dragon Con
Coming up
We're going to be
At Dragon Con
Apparently in Atlanta
Not apparently
We're definitely
There's going to be
A big subgenius show
At Dragon Con
With Tesla Coil
Concert
There's this group
What are they called
Arc something
They make music
Using Tesla coils
Have you ever seen
The YouTube effect
Yeah
It's the one I saw
They did the
Super Mario Brothers
Thing
And it's
There's no speech
Speakers involved
But they can tune
The
Of a Tesla coil
To a high
So run by a computer
You can actually
Do the Darth Vader theme
Make your Tesla sing
And they trust
Those Tesla coils
So that's going to be
The band
Interspersed
With the subgenius
Devival
At Dragon Con
In Atlanta
In September
Sounds like a tasteful night
As a man
You can imagine
The comic book conventions
Are very very tasty
And very graceful
When we first
Bumped into
Gwar there
In an elevator
Hey man
I'm Nikolai Tesla
I invented a lot of things
A long time ago
But nobody paid me no mind
In fact that guy
Edison
Well yeah
You know what happened
I was going to free
The people with free energy
I was going to bring it down
Like rain
Yeah
There was going to be
No more trouble
And no more trouble
No more pain
But that time
Good dish
Was really
I'm sorry
Yeah
It was the first time
We were playing
With real anti-magnetics
Who knew a whole forest
Was going to blow
Perhaps thousands
Of Eskimos were lost
But I didn't care
At the time
Maybe a weapon would sell
Because you know
She left me
And I
Been wandering around
Romania
Or was it
Yugoslavia
Man where was I from
I
Oh wait
I'm an American
No I
Oh baby
Why'd you do this
Yeah I keep seeing her
In my mind
And free energy too
The Nikola Tesla Blues
And he could
Make magicians
Duplicate themselves
Strange
Post-modernist
Horror movies
Yeah well
I don't know
That's what it takes
Nikola Tesla
Played by David Bowie
He was played by David Bowie
Yes
In The Prestige
Oh I thought it was
The man who fell
From the earth up
Yeah that was
The man who threw up
On the earth
Yeah the man who
Threw up on the earth
Yeah so we can turn down
The porno music background
You know that's the only
Dependable background music
For this show
Always works for everything
The 70s porno music
Porno movie music
Yeah yeah
Can't beat the classics
Yeah
Always works
And everybody remembers it
You know
They've heard it a million times
And sort of in the background
Of their lives
Well
You could even have
Dinosaur narratives
Over the top of it
It just works
It's that kind of stuff
But that's not what
You two are about
Illuminating
Elucidating
And then lubricating
The minds of the
I hate that man
Who the hell are you trying to
I thought
I always thought
You two
Here's my
My two word review of you two
Them two
How's that?
Them are two
That's what I think of you two
And it's
It's not
It is personal
It's personal
They
They squashed
Negative land
Like a bug
That's right
They should be
They really should be
They proved they couldn't
Take a joke
Yeah
They didn't listen
To their lawyers
Or no they did listen
They did
They didn't care
What their lawyers were doing
Like that's what they did
That's what it amounted to
They were too busy
Saving the world
Oh yes
From people making fun
Of you two
That may be kind of
An inside joke
For some people
Who don't remember
A thousand years ago
When you two
Sued our friends
At negative land
For making an album
That made fun of them
Just because the album
Looked exactly like
It was the new you two album
Which was also scheduled
I can see why
The record companies
Got stirred up
But still
Now you can download it
You can go and download
That new
That negative land album
You can download it online
And listen in the privacy
Don't let Bono
Know that you're listening
Right
Because Bono knows everything
Bono cannot take a joke man
And it's church scripture
That you must be fornicating
If you can't take one
I have trouble
Getting a Bono anymore
But he won't answer
Our phone calls
We've tried to get him
On the show
But
He's changed
Yeah
Lost his edge
You know
The funny thing is
I probably would not recognize
A you two song
That's how
How removed I am
From pop culture
There's a
Oh the ones that
The negative land made fun of
It's like
That's how I know
That's all the pop culture I know
It's from cartoons
Mad magazine
And nowadays
The Onion
The only way I keep up
With what people are watching
On TV is
By The Onion
That's how you get your news
And take offs
Those idiotic comments
You were making earlier
About the economy
Proves that
All you'd read
Are satire magazines
There's not
Like what was the one thing
That was in The Onion
You would go completely nuts
If you
That's not real
What?
The headline of The Onion
That you were reading
Earlier about the economy
That's
It's like a joke thing
That's what I'm trying to tell you
It's
They're making a joke
No it's a newspaper
Yeah it is a newspaper
It folds and everything
And it has words on it
But that is not a real newspaper
It's not a real newspaper
In that
It transmits
Some degree of truth
Or what really happened
How can they print it
If it's not true?
Because
It's printed
The machine that prints
Works all the time
Whether it's the truth or not
Just like the church
Of the subgenius
I don't get it
I don't understand
What you're trying to get at
I'm
I'm saying
There's something here
That I do not understand
It's like Bob
It's not real
There's a pain
Between my ears
It's fake
It's phony
Oh that
Oh oh oh
Oh okay
I understand that
I understand that part
Sure
Okay moving on
The con
The big con
Yeah
Yeah pledge allegiance
To the illusion
And to the pyramid scheme
For which it stands
One nation
In denial
One species in denial
With error and excess
By all
Thank you
Well
I guess we're all
In the same stew
Thinking about
Where America's heading
And the global
Globalism is too
Is of it
It's getting
It's getting globular
Globular
It's globular man
Yeah
It's like
It's like if your eye
Act loco
Think globular
Whatever that was
Act globular
And think
Loco
Yeah
Act globular
Think loco
No think globular
Act loco
That's what it was
I think
Or am I just acting
God
Stop
It gets so confusing
You must think
We'll rewind it later
Listen to it
And figure it out
Just keep moving
How'd that turtle
Get on top of that post
Get in my pants man
What is that turtle
Doing to that tennis shoe
The turtle on the post
Go ahead
You finish that one
Okay
No there was
Princess Weebs
Recently
Found on the internet
There's an amusing
Video of a
Turtle attempting
To have sex
With a tennis shoe
Many of the
Of them
Many
What
Many videos
So it's a real common
So the
Masturbating chimpanzees
Are out
This decade
Yes
That's so
So last year
Yeah
So 2001
I've waited so long
To be able to say that
That is so 2001
I mean
You know
I
2001 came out
The movie
Came out in
Or 68
Imagine
Imagine the mind
Blown
By a
Yeah
And my mom
Took me
And my brother
To go see
We got scared
When the monkeys
Started banging
On the bones
And stuff
And there was
That big scary thing
That was like
We were real scared
And we thought
It was on the moon
And so were the monkeys
Man we were confused
At those days
And now that music
Is just instantly
A laugh generator
Yep
What used to be
The most moving
Powerful
Stretch of music
Thus spake
Zarathustra
Is now a comedy
King
Thanks to that
Thus spake
20th century's
PR department
Or did we already
Talk about this
Last week
I think it was
Three weeks ago
I saw another
Medium
Platform or
Different medium
An actual medium
It was another
Vehicle
A vesicle
This is like
Deja news
A tube
It was another tube
We got sucked
Into it then
Yeah
And we're coming
Out the other end
What if the tube
You tube
Then there's red tube
That's all porno
Free porno
Amateur porno stuff
I couldn't understand
The name
Why would they call it
Red tube
I just don't get it
I've thought about that
Over and over again
What would that have to do
With porno
Gosh
They're giving away
Free porno now
Why don't I hear about this
No it's true
There's free porno
On the internet
You don't have to
Give them your credit cards
I just gave
I just advertised them
Red tube
Wow
Okay well
Who's got a computer
You know
There's a whole string
Of them in front of me
I never use them
In this station
They don't need
The real DJs
Like Dr. Sinister
He'll come in here
And he can
Actually look at
All the listeners
Through the different
Monitors and so forth
You guys can do that
At KPFA too
Yeah
But I just
I'm pure
You know
I'm old school
Yeah a lot of people
Talk about you
I'm from the days
When radio was just noise
Just sound
Right
Yeah
And it was like
Pedal powered too
Yeah
When you go
Looking for porn
We used
We took turns
We'd
Like if it was
The old days
Dave would pedal
For a while
And I'd talk
And then Dave would talk
While I pedaled
Because otherwise
You were like
And then
Bob said
It just didn't work
I don't want to be
The gerbil in a cage tonight
If you listen to
Some of those
Old Bob and Ray routines
You can tell
They're having to trade off
Oh yeah
You got goon shows
The old goon show
Yes
They all trade off
And we all rip them off
They sweat
They swap spit
They swap perspiration
They collaborate more
Than you can imagine
In different special events
In outer space
Equality
Eternity
Liquidity
Yeah
They're very lucrative
In outer space
They've gone on
To the other side
But the other side
Has some things going for it
Big butts
Plenty of
Dough
That's right
You can make a lot of money
Being dead
Just think of it
Hendrix sure did
Man he did so much better
After he died
A lot of those
Rock stars
They wouldn't even be
In the rock and roll
Hall of fame
If they hadn't died
No taxes
They get their own room
Now since they're dead
No rent
No utility bills
No production costs
Everything you did before
Is mixed a thousand
Different ways
Just think of it
You're immortal
But you're not
You're a mortal
You're a lump of slime
But you're immortal
You look the way you did
When you were 24 man
Those dimples are sticking out
You know what's really sad
Is that everything we say
On these dumb shows
Is immortal too
Somebody will have a copy
There'll be some copy
Floating around on the internet
And every day
I thank the fates
That the internet
Wasn't invented
When I was a young man
Because then every stupid thing
I ever said
Would have been recorded
It's bad enough
You know
When I'm 70
I'm going to have to listen
Back to myself
At age 55
Involuntarily
Going
God
How could I have been
So immature
There's no end to it
Apparently
No
Foolishness
Just changes
Its character
And color
A little bit
As the years go on
It begets more
But you'll always
Be doing something
You'll be embarrassed
About later
Kids
You hear that?
Think you're cool now?
Wait until you're 40
And play back a tape
Of last night's party
Wait until you're 80
In the hospice there
And you're walking
Down the steps
And you break your pelvis
With your colostomy bag
In at the same time
And you'll be laughing
Your socks off
But those are those
Little ridgy blue socks
They make you wear
And you'll be laughing
Oh, that's all right
We're just
We're all reincarnated again
So it doesn't matter
We just
I don't believe
In reincarnation
Oh, you don't have to
They just reincarnate you anyway
I believe in reincarnality
That's doctrinal
You get to have
The second helping of meat
Yeah
Going for more?
Well, Pappy
What was it
Pappy would say
My father
Loves to get into
Religious arguments
With anybody
And he'll
He'll fight for any side
Jesus or the devil
Or Mohammed
Or whatever
He knows
He knows them all
And I don't even know
What it was
He was talking about
I remembered
What Pappy said
That was so cosmic
He said
I know what
The afterlife is like
It's just exactly like
Before I was born
Remember when
Before you were born?
Staying on the mountain
It was
Staying was on the mountaintop
He was
And he
But no
No, no
Stang never made it
He made
Stang made it to where
He could peak over the mountaintop
But he never got any
And everybody else
Got to ski down the slope
Others were peaking
And Stang was just peeing
Down the mountain
What was it
The cosmic
Well, one cosmic thing
My father said was
I believe whatever I want
Whatever I need to believe
That was it
I believe whatever
I need to believe
I thought
My God
That sums up
All human nature
In one sentence
That's right
Yep
Survive
Believe whatever I need to believe
The utilitarian beliefs of Pappy's
Yeah
Yep
Just enough Jesus
To keep a smile on my face
And just enough Satan
To keep an erection
Pappy
Teaches a Bible class
That's when he teaches
To little girls
In Stangville, Texas
And he
Specializes in Bible class
In teaching them
The contradictory parts
Of the Bible
Or the nightmarishly
Fiendish and sadistic parts
You know, like
The smite and smote chapters
Yeah, yeah
When the school children
Made fun of the bald pate
Of the prophet
And so
And she-bear came
And tore the children
And rended
Rent them
Well, it's only fair, isn't it?
Come on
For making
Well, it was
It was okay to make fun
Of some bald-headed people
Yeah
But not prophets
Not a guy with a bear
Not a guy with a
Yeah, with an she-bear
Or two
Hidden in the woods
Hmm
Well, that's why
The First Church
And the Last Lap
World's fastest-growing
Snag religion
100% less dogma
To light religion
One holy day a year
Today is not it
Is there for you
That's right
The First Church
And the Last Lap
Offers you
A two-dimensional
Spiritual scapegoat
So next time
You slam your
Dog's tail
In the refrigerator
You lock your
Sports car keys
Inside your
Sports car
Don't blame yourself
Just go to
SaintStupid.com
That's S-A-I-N-T-S-T-U-P-I
Whatever
Dot com
And you can
Gaze upon his visage
The two-dimensional
Spiritual scapegoat
Will relieve you
Of your stupidity
That's right
And then
Only one holy day a year
And it's April 1st
Noon
The Embarcadero Plaza
San Francisco
For the 31st Annual Parade
So if you can't be there
Be somewhere else
Now, the First Church
Of the Last Lap
Has
Saint Stupid
And just as the church
Of the subgenius
Has Bob
Or really vice versa
But
Now Bob
Is a fully
Half-toned
Fleshed out
Deity of
Luck
And brainlessness
Whereas Saint Stupid
As a logo head
Is a rather
Crudely rendered
Line drawing
Looks like a
Five-year-old
Drew him
He kind of looks like
A KKK member
With a silly grin
Well, the original
Saint Stupid
In 1979
Was an engraving
Out of a German
Medical text
Of a hydrocephalic child
About this high
And it was
An old-time engraving
Turn of the century
The other century kids
I've got one
Two hearts
And it had a pointy head
And a beatific smile
So that was
The original Saint Stupid
Because I was reading
About the Feast of Fools
And there's this history
About deformities
Back there
And so this head
Would have been
Looked upon as holy
And also I was reading
Jane Roberts
Seth Speaks
Remember those books?
Oh yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah
And she was describing
You know
The alternate reality
Through this Seth guy
But occasionally
She would go into
A higher trance
In a being
Several levels up
In consciousness
Higher than Seth?
Higher than Seth
That's pretty high, dude
So high
That all the energy
That manifests
Our reality
Is but a thought
In that being's mind
And when that being
Talks through Jane Roberts
And Jane Roberts' husband
Is writing it down
A cone of light
Forms above her head
And she speaks
In a monotone
Not unlike
The Saturday Night Live
Convergence
Which was going on
At the same time
Destiny?
I don't think so
So that was the first one
But then the next year
I couldn't find it
So I sat down
With a brush pen
And went
It looks like this
I drew about seven of them
On a piece of paper
Threw them away
Went no, that's not it
Then I had to send out
The flyer
So I went to the garbage
Pulled it up
And says this'll do
And so the brush pen
Version of St. Stupid
Then became the logo
And it really
Maximized our profit margins
Quite considerably
Well, I can tell you
It takes a lot more ink
To do those
Half-tone dots
On Bob's face
I know
It's like
You know, we can't do it
And there's no shading
On St. Stupid
He's like a
Haiku
Of a face
That's right
It's a suggestion
It is
It's a relationship
To the Holy Fool
It's got Zen elements to it
It's got Feast of Fools
European elements
It's got the
Indian dots
Not feathers
Holy Festival
You know that
The Holy Festival
In India?
No, what is that?
It's a very special thing
Where they
Spritch the colored inks
Over everybody
Everybody
But it was white
For a couple of days
And they run around
Spritching colors
On each other
Oh, and you said
The Holy Festival
I assumed you meant
The people who worship
The whole
The big nothing
The zero
The whole nest
That's whole nest
The whole nest festival
Yes
Which is in trouble
Financially
You know
You've never
You should someday
I would love to
Introduce you to
Reverend Dennis Murphy
Who is the head
Of the Church
Of the Living Bull
Oh, wonderful
Another local
Ohio
False
Satanic cult
Which
Room for more
Worships a little
Mechanical
Wind-up
Bull
Toy
And they are also
Cannibals
Yeah
There are still
A few left
I've been initiated
Into the church
The cult of the
Living bull
You
Scream
The word
Bull
With the other
Bullists
At dawn
After
A certain time
I love traditions
And rituals
That's what I'm all about
Traditions
The emergence
I noticed
That you were able
To repeat
Those ritualistic
Statements
Off the top
Of your head
That's amazing
First church
And the last
Laugh world's
Best growing snack
Related to 150%
Less dogments
A light religion
One holy day
A year
And today
Isn't it
You mean
That one
Yeah
That's amazing
Boy
You know
If we can
We never were able
To sum up
The church
Of the subgenius
In one incomprehensible
That says it
That's it
It's power packed
I know it is power
You take out the spaces
And punctuation
You get a lot more
Information per unit
Of
My
Talkability
How can you
Breathe now
Is just
There's
That a
Faisal
Device
That it's
Kind of like
I got one
Nostril trained
Again
And one
Nostril trained
Out
It's kind
Of a
Circular
Nasal
Like the
Yoga
Thing
That's
Very yoga
It's like
What's
The little
Device
By the
Well
That's
Just a
Little
C-clamp
That helps
Me
Channel
Better
It's
Just
Orchard
Hardware
Membrane
Yes
But you
Get it
Down
Just
Right
At the
Edge
Of your
nose there, and you can tune your nasal
frequencies to wherever you want.
And if you forgot the words, like say for instance
that last passage that you've memorized so
well, would you call them right
to your cell phone right away? I mean
immediately. Your phone will ring, you look at it, and there will be the
lyrics. That's great.
See, you don't have anything like that, Stan. No.
If I did, I would have been able to remember that
line that my pappy did that I'm still
trying to remember. I'll probably
come back and cut it in
to the other versions
of the show. I know what
the afterlife is like.
It's just exactly like before I
was born. See,
WCSB listeners here in Cleveland
get a unique chance
to hear this show
before I remove my own
mistakes. Oh, man.
See, that's defogged.
So these become like extra
special, like a trader, you know, like
a collector's items. This show,
this whole show that we're doing tonight,
this is a blooper show. This is one
giant blooper collection because
when I get back home tomorrow,
I'll re-edit it for the other
beloved stations.
I can understand that.
And I'll remove everything stupid.
So it'll mostly be
music and
other material. Pretty much everything
except what we've been saying.
That helps that way.
But we'll sell this one as the bloopers.
Yeah.
And that's what people really want anyway.
They don't want the scripted show.
We'll put it online. We'll put it on bloop.
Doob.
One time on a
methamphetamine rampage,
he took all of the bloop
words, I'm sorry, and re-edited
them back in so that it just sounded
like somebody was just saying beep, beep, beep,
beep, beep, beep, beep, beep. That wasn't me that did that.
That was hilarious.
That was dial tone or something?
That was a hippie in Chicago.
He recorded
a vicious argument between
two roommates.
A heartfelt, serious end of
our friendship forever screaming
fight between two roommates.
And they made two versions. One with all
the cuss words cut out and one
with just the cuss words.
Which was a little longer
than the one with the cuss words cut out.
So it was the kind of thing
that we'll never be able to play
on this
fine, tasteful
radio station.
We'll have to save it for the special
hour of Slack. X-rated versions
which are heard only on the internet.
At subgenius.com
Yeah.
Well the music
faintly hurts.
That's not a professional all the way up to the point where
Dot com.
I stand in front of the mirror
and practice that dot com.
It's weird to see the
twitching eye thing and everything.
It doesn't work with dot com.
It's a video really.
No, org is different macularly.
It makes your mouth different
when you say org.
Okay, so it's
stupid.com
and subgenius.com
and what's
the lonesomecowboydave.com
Oh, that's right. We're still trying to get your computer
to figure out how to
get it out of the PC
somehow.
I'm missing it.
Think of it though. Someday there will be a
lonesomecowboydave.com.
Probably after he's dead.
Right. We'll call it the abattoir dot com.
Honesty, my life's blood.
Here it is. For real.
No, I'm sorry.
I'm sick.
Rhyme of the ancient mariner.
I was thinking about the submariner.
I was thinking about Popeye.
I was thinking about everything.
There's a submarine in every show.
You just can't see him.
Every movie there's a submarine.
That's right.
You just can't see him.
All the time.
Well, of course, because they're underwater.
Duh.
That's the whole idea behind the submarine.
Sub part.
People don't understand that.
Submarines are with you everywhere.
Everywhere you go, there's a submarine looking at you.
Now, wait a minute.
What about Stang County, Texas,
where there is no water for 500 miles
in any direction?
It's underground submarines.
Underground submarines.
Those are so boring.
With that drill in the front
that moves through the ground.
No, no, no.
More like the Buckaroo Bonsai version,
you know, with the phased molecular structure
delimitator in the front of the car.
Or they don't have to have a drill to bore.
No, no, no, no.
So they can be boring without a drill.
A molecular phaser, basically.
You tune it to the different frequencies,
and that's whatever the rock is, you know.
And then you have it on.
You got computers.
You know, computers make it all the more easier now.
You can go right through the mountain if you want to.
I guess I need to reread Buckaroo Bonsai.
You know, you gotta get caught up
with what's going on now, man.
Even though that's like 20 years ago.
You still gotta get caught up.
I know, I'm still behind.
With the repercussions, man.
That's what we have to, you know, the waves, man.
You know, the waves go on forever.
And so we must grasp the waves whenever we can.
And like, you know, go for the substance of the waves.
And there's no future and no pasture.
And there's no...
No waves, Dave.
Bishop Joey had an epiphany on the waves.
Peak. I had a peak experience.
Yeah, that was a great description.
That was a true one.
Our listeners will never hear of it.
Yeah, you ever have one of those?
You ever have one of those peak experiences?
A non-drug state?
Are you taking this from Ohio State?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ohio State.
I definitely have.
I've had quite a few of them.
And I've had just their very opposites as well.
Yeah.
Probably a few more of those.
What do you call the opposite of a peak?
A ditch experience?
A ditch experience.
Yeah, I've had a lot of ditch experiences, too.
Well, you have to have both.
You can't have one without the other.
That's true, yeah.
But I think that's a good thing.
Yeah, yeah.
Because otherwise, if life's nothing but one big peak experience, then it's just dull.
None of it's a peak.
We've all attained entropy, the final static state of entropy where there's no ups,
no downs, and no in-betweens even.
They're all irregular movements.
There was a pretty girl that lived across the street named Diane, and that was my first
peak experience.
I'd sneak out and peak in her, and then later I developed the mirror on the shoes, and I
had no more peak experiences.
Yeah, technology.
You got the X-ray specs and thought they really worked.
But if you squinted.
You can make them work if you squint.
Then I got one of those see-through-your-neighbor's-wall special screw-in periscopes.
I had another peak experience.
Then I got the sea monkeys thinking, well, at least I could watch them have sex, and
if I could never have it with Donna or Janet next door.
That was more like a leak experience for me.
Well, you had an old fish tank, so yeah.
Well, your fish tank's old.
Yeah.
It leaked.
It used to really shoot, but it just dribbles now.
Well, maybe you could get one of those pumps, those new pumps, those new hydrostatic pumps.
Oh, yeah.
And you can get boosters for those, too.
You can get 1,600 PSI animals.
Yeah, there's new blue organic food.
If your PSI lasts more than four hours, alert your physician.
Or your hydrolithist.
Have someone alert your physician for you.
What time is it?
Oh, my gosh.
It's time.
We're lost in time.
It is the time.
The star of the interlacs.
But luckily, the next show is coming up.
And we must go.
And our special ... God, there I go.
I said it again.
Our excellent guest was the King of Tyroo.
Yeah.
Bishop Joey ...
His noblest.
Holy Ghost.
I have the first church to last lap.
He's our homie.
April 1st is the 31st annual St. Stupid's Day.
We're going to celebrate.
St. Stupid's Day Parade.
See you there in San Francisco at noon at the Embarcadero Plaza.
And if we don't actually see it live, Puzzling Evidence TV on YouTube will almost certainly
be carrying it.
It'll have the video of the parade.
So, yeah.
Puzzling Evidence.
Yes, Puzzling Evidence TV on YouTube.
That's yet another one of those.
And then there's Puzzling Evidence TV on RedTube, which I don't even want to think about, okay?
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
All right.
We'll turn on the background, whatever it's.
I think it's some ...
Oh, no.
It's a little bit more of a humor coming up.
If it actually gets as far as the version of Purple Haze, that's by the Kleptons.
But we probably won't get that far.
Thank you.
Cattle's my name.
And there's no man west of the Rio Grande big enough to take it from me.
Man of vision.
Man of legend.
He's going to be a legend.
Well, yes.
Yes.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, I suppose so.
Yeah.
Come in.
I've heard of you before.
You're Holmes, the meddler.
That is my name, sir.
But look here, Holmes.
I still don't quite understand.
It's all quite simple, my dear Watson.
Amazingly simple.
A good doctor may tip his root out rather than use her.
When she in the fight, I couldn't be made to become.
How did he succeed?
I mean, by what method?
He thrust the slimy fool, not caffeine,
through Nixon's brain, late into the fruit track.
I see.
That was why the blood in the labenters taps the full bell down.
Exactly.
And that was why the vacuum came up with just no check on the deviance, sir.
Mark Watson.
Oh, the feisty big butt.
Quite, my dear Watson.
Goodbye.
It may merely have been the effect of delirium.
I'll find myself when they pry me out of my cold, dead fingers.
And my cold, dead fingers.
I'll find my dead fingers out of my other cold, dead fingers.
Bob was an advocate of freedom from speech,
and yet he still has all these quotes.
Is something sacred, he once asked.
Is something sacred?
I see you shiver with anticipation.
Patient.
The blades are on my brain.
We can't clean the things that don't seem the same.
I've got the money, but I don't know why.
Excuse me while I kiss the sky.
Purple ink all around.
Don't know if I'm going up or down.
Never happy.
I can't listen to you
Whatever it is that there is
What does family mean?
Help me, help me
Yeah, I'm in heaven
I'm never gonna die
No doubt
If it's day or night
You got me broke
No, my mind
Is it tomorrow
Or just the end of time?