The phone you are using does not allow...
The Self Genius Power of Swagging!
This device requires recall passes. Please hear a clinical note early, then reach in card.
Sitting on his pedestal and reaching for a roll of paper, Mr. Satan Butterwolf began to plan his fiendish caper.
With a grin and with a look that reminisced of butter books, he wiped the residue from neath his tail,
buckled his perfect trousers right, and to himself we hear him pray.
Or do we?
Or say.
Or whatever.
My body's full of shit and bones. My body's full of angel light.
My legs get very sweaty when I sleep alone at night.
My body's full of angel light. My body's full of shit and bones.
My legs get very sweaty at night when I sleep alone.
And when Mr. Satan Butterwolf came up, all the bunnies gathered round.
And when Mr. Satan Butterwolf came up,
he saw the fiendish caper.
He saw the fuzzy bunnies for miles and miles.
And when Mr. Satan Butterwolf came up, all the bunnies asked his name.
He answered them with vicious lies.
Their laughter made them all fair game.
Now sitting on his pedestal and reaching for a roll of paper,
Mr. Satan Butterwolf found humor in his recent caper.
Peering in the water cool, he saw the faces in his stools
of Bunny Bob, Clark and Carl, Bunny Biff, and Baby Bunny Sue.
They appeared to have fun out laughing in the sun in their carefree bunny gardens.
Vegetation everywhere, life without a care in a carefree bunny, bunny garden.
Everything was happy there, bunny crap left everywhere to sit in the sun and harden.
But Mr. Satan Butterwolf had plans for tomorrow.
Their cheap facade of innocence would lead the bunnies all the way to the sun.
But Mr. Satan Butterwolf would hide his face behind the shadow sheet.
And Bunny Greed brought bunnies to believe it best to just pretend
not to see the cloven hoofs that butterwolves are forced to wear for feet.
For a fair weathered cherub is a butterwolf's meat.
As they come hopping, as they come hopping to hell,
as they come nonstop hop, hop, hopping to the sound of devil bells,
all pride-eyed and bushy-tailed, the bunnies found it well for them to cheat.
And to tell lies behind your backs so vulgar that a gentleman like Mr. Satan Butterwolf
could never find fit to repeat.
Gracious indeed.
Alright, that's all I have against the Billy Dare Show.
Thank you very much for having us here.
Thank you for bringing us.
Quite welcome, quite welcome.
That was the Billy Nayer Show, live at 9X Day.
BillyNayer.com is where you can learn more about them
as well as their great movie, The American Astronaut.
This is Hour of Slack number 1058,
a fourth of the specials recorded entirely at the 9X Day subgenius festival of July 5th week,
or at radio stations WCSB Cleveland and KPFA Berkeley,
right afterwards.
This episode features some great ranting and music,
especially from the Billy Nayer Show soundboard recordings
made by Reverend Maynard Graynard.
These soundboard tapes don't do justice to the way the band really sounds,
and yet they're still better than most bands' best recordings,
just because of the extremely high bull-dada content.
You'll see what I mean.
Also, this show will feature and play,
and document the ongoing travails of Reverend Magdalene,
whose child, Con Bow, is still in the custody of Peaks
because of a judicial system so dumb that it thinks the church of the subgenius,
since it's obviously not Christian,
must therefore be the work of Satan!
Is it?
Let's find out, along with this caller, to the Puzzling Evidence Show
with Dr. Philodrum and Dr. Hal Puzzling Evidence and some little girl.
The church of the subgenius?
Yes, this is subgenius. Can I help you?
Hi, Colleen.
I have a question, please.
A subgenius-type question?
We have an answer. They may not match, but go ahead.
I've been considering joining your religion.
Well, that's right, Hanson.
Demanding our religion?
You can see it behind us here.
Joining.
At the wrists and elbows.
I think I may want to be a subgenius.
Well, here you are.
You say you want to know where to send me.
Is this a monotheism that you have here?
No, it is most definitely not.
It has to do with the consideration of the bewildering number of deities.
And now I know of something I can say that will be of interest to other people.
I was searching among the odd fragments that I heard
when I was out there at that great festival called X-Day,
and here is the scoop.
That you're just gonna love.
Yeah, yeah.
Vanilla, chocolate, quartz.
All this is very real. That's the sad part.
People don't understand that.
No, it is.
The event he's describing was just held, the end of the world.
All right, well.
And here we are.
What we heard more about was the presiding child custody trial involving Magdalene.
Well, it turns out.
All of a sudden we get dragged down to real.
Well, it turns out that the prosecution really tried to make a big thing out of this.
And it was a subgenius and how it was really a Satanic cult.
So there was testimony with the court recorder taking it down.
All right, could you describe the meaning of Gabor Fram, please?
Yes!
Narnini and Narnunu.
Where is this?
This is public record.
Yes, let's watch it.
Court recorder is just going like this.
Oh, that'd be great.
Because she's seen pictures of Gary coming up on her computer.
It sounds like this.
Meanwhile, Judge Punch stormed out of the courtroom.
And came back without his robes on.
It's like Iraqistan.
And called them over for a conference and then recused himself.
And he was quite angry about all the bad things he got on the internet.
People calling him bad names.
That's what he gets when he messes with all the techno.
And he gave Magdalene a tongue lashing in court.
Ever seen that?
The Russian tank in Afghanistan?
I don't remember.
I don't have any idea what people write in Boing Boing or on the internet.
Yeah, Laughing Squid.
Yeah, she didn't get a movie.
So it was all very interesting.
Yeah, man.
It's a sinister plot against a…
Oh, we should mention, what schedule is there?
One thing that definitely will happen at a time tonight.
And that is the burning of the sacred icon.
And the book burning.
The Judge Punch Memorial book burning.
Oh, and I've got to remember, we've got to remember to put together the Judge Punch Memorial
punching bag.
We're going to be punching and bitch slapping Judge Punch by proxy.
We're going to be burning Bob's head, burning our parents' divorce papers, burning
whatever kind of hated documents or things we've got on us.
I wouldn't recommend membership cards.
That's an old joke.
And it was…
Sending onerous, uh, books.
Paperwork to bureaucratic shiel.
Right.
And, uh, and also the Judge working out aggressions.
Unfortunately, Jesus isn't here.
I've noticed that when the Lord is at X day, at some point or another, he gets the crap
beat out of him just because people have such powerful feelings about him.
Even though they know it's not his fault.
He didn't mean to put the Y-0-K bug.
He just wanted to put the Y-0-K bug into effect and cause the Dark Ages.
Uh, that was all his fan club.
But nonetheless, people, God, they always just tear him to shreds.
Maybe that's why he's not here.
It could be.
Last time we saw him at X day, he was carrying a cross formed into a dollar sign
of pool noodles down the road.
And half the people here were hitting him, striking him, and squirting fake blood at
him through silly squirt guns to humiliate him.
Aw.
Thanks again east of A災.
Don't mention siitä, writs е!
That was literally his first comment.
Just seeing Brian DePaulus are not blind.
So, uh…
It gets me.
It's been interesting.
I don't even want to talk about it pal.
Ladies.
Him who shall come is Bob.
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Yes.
And he also has not been seen at an ex-day or drill in a long time or any revival
because every time he did, somebody would take him up on that advice to kill him.
Young punks.
Yeah.
So he got tired of having to wear bulletproof clothing at shows.
He had to go up against every young whippersnapper who came along
and tried to take old Dobbs down.
Now they use me instead.
It's like, oh, I'll show that I'm not a Bobby by making fun of Reverend Stang constantly.
But tonight you can all take a whack at Judge Punch,
the Judge Punch by proxy punching bag punch out,
and later on dance dementedly around the fire.
Well, maybe we should describe what happened at the bonfire, or do you think not?
Sure, why not?
The bonfire?
The bonfire.
First off, the Brushwood Woodbusters, which are the fire experts there,
built us a wonderful copy of the Dobbs head icon,
sort of a stripped down Bob head that looks almost like a cross,
but with more cross bars on it and a pipe.
Yeah.
And that thing was set on fire, and I ranted interminably over the bullhorn as always.
And so now.
Judge Punch thought we were satanic because of the goat head.
And now we're burning crosses, so he's going to think we're affiliated with the Ku Klux Klan.
Well, but we tried to bring it all together in a symbolic moment.
During this particular burning of the icon, the little pipe part fell off in one piece.
It's actually two pieces of wood, but it fell off of the face part onto the ground,
and the whole of that wooden pipe was smoking.
It was an all-smoking pipe.
Right.
The pipe up to the satanic goat head that, well, actually it was a cute goat head.
Yeah, really, that's not satanic at all.
That Judge Punch had complained about.
And so the goat head came together with the all-smoking pipe.
Later on, there was like a bigger log pipe, which was smoked by the big fire itself.
I'm still trying to figure out the logic of that one and what it means.
Basically what it all means, all right, is that you can burn Bob to death,
you can burn him alive, but his pipe will keep on burning and burning.
His pipe will smoke forever.
That's right.
And sometimes it will smoke itself.
It's got froth in it.
What do you expect?
Well, it's got more than that.
No, actually, Bob mostly smokes Borkham Riff.
Did he come back from the ashes like a phoenix?
But I was very surprised because we were burning hated books like American History Text.
Now we're burning books, too.
There was also a full-sized Judge Punch punching bag,
which I had actually purchased at one of those stores that has toys.
It was really hard to find a punching bag.
Anyway, that was the Judge Punch punching bag.
And I expected the subgeniuses to be lining up to abuse that thing.
But oddly enough, the most famous...
Nobody wanted to touch them.
The most vicious Punch Puncher was a little five-year-old girl.
She was five.
Wow.
Named Haley, who was the...
Daughter of the wood dealer.
Yeah, she was the daughter of one of the wood busters.
Haley, a little PC pagan child, was just furiously angry at Judge Punch
and tore into him with all her heart.
Her mom later came up and knifed him, although she knifed him in the air part.
His bottom part was full of water.
And I gutted that part.
Just like the real Judge.
It got kind of violent.
And then, of course, we had to...
Eventually, there was a sacrifice.
And as usual, who had to drag the burned-up guy out of the fire?
Me, Reverend Stang.
Everybody else had gone off to party.
Well, me and Reverend Nicky.
Nicky had his experience with that.
Well, I mean, you kind of broke Haley's heart when you tore apart the Judge Punch doll.
Oh, she knew that was going to happen.
She was really having fun torturing him.
Actually, her dad told me that he was going to find her another one.
And I was able to...
Luckily, I was able to tell him all about every kind of punch bag available.
Wait a second.
Having just shone for him.
You know, it's weird the things you end up doing just before the end of the world.
Oh, my God, I've got to find this punching bag.
Well, it's a pity that you couldn't be there.
Fly high over the lawn sprinklers.
Okay, I've got some bubble gum.
I'm going to patch that hole.
It's dawn in that forest that you were just in.
Causing the reverse pressure leak.
It's more pressure in here now.
Cooking chicken and ale ate there in the forest.
Ah, yes.
That's what they do.
They get this soda pop from Kentucky and they cook chicken in it.
It comes out with a very strange taste.
The taste of X-Day.
So, how many...
How many...
This tastes like X-Day.
The ashes and smell.
It's not bad, no.
It's just...
You could ask how many weirdos and occult poops were there.
I don't know.
How many weirdos and poops were there this year?
More than you could shake a stick at.
Yeah, the Wonder Bread logo.
For the most part, you didn't, but you wanted to go to Doc Frop's camp and vape out every hour, every day.
I saw somebody...
I saw the little over-weight go face down in the vape-o.
Oh, yeah.
He had to go to the hospital.
And almost get me arrested just to take a picture of him.
A certain vape entity said he...
He had to go to the hospital.
So, did anybody have to go to the hospital this year?
No one went to the hospital.
See, that's the measure of a good stock of any kind, like Doc Stock.
But one thing is...
Somebody has to go to the hospital.
Nikki Deathchick is actually a medical technician of some sort.
So, she is essentially the medical person on the spot.
She's like the general, the secretary general.
The...
What do they call them?
The Joyce elders of the...
Joyce Day.
Of the subgenius church.
Magdalene Sister Zeus is also studying nursing.
The surgeon general.
She's like the surgeon general of the church, Nikki Deathchick.
Officially, whether or not the church is satanic.
Well, that...
It all depends on what...
What happened is with the new trial, they said we refuse to admit this subgenius thing as evidence.
It has nothing to do with anything.
It was...
You know...
Yay!
But...
But then the court said...
Don't fall over.
Stand up there.
The court said we're going to allow it anyway because it shows the state of mind of the defendant.
Wait, yay!
But...
State of mind?
Subgenius shows state of mind?
But the lawyer tried to get it completely thrown out on the grounds that it had...
It was not composed at the same time.
It was not about the defendant.
It...
You know, it was...
It's really being brought in in there.
They're...
They're having all this testimony about Gabofam.
And...
Yeah.
And who can define Gabofam?
We've tried it a lot of times here on the show.
Yeah.
To define...
Define it now.
Do it.
Or Bohongas.
The...
The Gafine...
Gabofam.
Yeah.
Some people would say divine, but we say Gafine for Gabofam.
Gafine...
Gabofam.
Mighty fine.
Stammy fine.
Gabofam.
That's a real...
That's like nailing Jell-O to a wall.
Or stuffing it into a parking meter.
Jell-O?
But why?
And...
I like to take Jell-O and put it into a parking meter.
Or trying to clean the windshield of the same vehicle with it.
Yeah.
Trying to clean the windshield with Jell-O.
If you have enough of it, it's okay, because you just spray it on.
Oh, okay.
The Puzzling Evidence Show there with Dr. Hal...
Dr. Philodrumon and Callers and K. Rob's girlfriend.
Friends...
Reverend...
Magdalene...
Magdalene needs help.
Seriously needs help.
Her lawyer bills are huge.
In fact, she needs $10,000 yesterday.
As you can hear, the subgeniuses are frantic about this.
Friends, I'm going to pull that music down because this is important enough.
If you want to get more information about the Bevilacqua case and how to donate...
I'm going to give you some...
Well, first, the PayPal address for...
Moms4Bob, if you just want to PayPal it.
MagdaleneatSubgenius.com
Magdalene is spelled M-A-G-D-A-L-E-N.
Or, her blog...
Well, her name is Rachel Bevilacqua and she's on blogspot.com at rbevilacqua.blogspot.com.
I'm going to spell rbevilacqua.
That's R-B...
E-V-I-L-A-C-Q-U-A.
R-B-E-V-I-L-A-C-Q-U-A.blogspot.com.
Or, modemac.com.wiki.com.reverend.magdalene.
Praise Bob.
I think that's all the questions.
We do have one more. Can we do one more question?
All right. Certainly.
And this is... I don't know why this one wasn't asked before.
The question is, why a goat?
Well, you see, Bucky...
I should have brought that goat head down here. I have it.
Well, we have it. We have it nearby.
In a sense, it is always hovering nearby.
An ethereal presence to remind us that we are, after all,
dealing with religion here, with numinous powers.
Not only a cleverly constructed goat skull,
but also a goatish presence who no one knew would have the power
to reach ahead through time and affect and manipulate future events.
But why choose a goat anyway?
The fact is that in all previous cultures, sacrifices were made to the gods,
because these older gods had a taste for blood.
Yes, the blood was poured on the smoking altars.
And even the Christian gods, so goody-goody and namby-pamby,
enjoyed torn flesh and blood when it was offered up by Abel,
and not the completely vegan and politically correct repast offered up by Cain.
Thus, Cain, in utter frustration,
slew Abel and was discharged from the Garden of Eden
with the disfiguring mark of the bobby on his brow.
So, why a goat?
Because the Judas goat, the sacrificial goat,
the one who goes before,
the goat is the symbol of the entity, the being,
that the hammer of injustice will come to.
And the goat is a beast that will come down upon,
right between the horns,
in order so that the same thing doesn't happen to us.
Let it happen to something,
and let that something be a goat.
The goat.
Dr. Howell, there's another answer to that question.
There usually is.
I think Reverend Magdalen was a little too flustered
by being asked the question by the judge,
but there was a very simple answer to why a goat.
Well, of course, there's the...
When young Conbo asked her once,
Mom, why does the moon get bigger and smaller?
So sometimes there was a full moon,
and then it would become a crescent moon.
He said, why does that happen?
She didn't want to go into the whole complicated explanation
about the sun and moon and everything,
and she said, well, that's the sky goat comes
and eats a little out of the moon every night.
That's a real neat joke.
And it grows back.
And Reverend Magdalene, during the deity ball that year,
dressed herself as the sky goat.
There you go.
This charming, self-created myth that she told her little boy
so that he would...
She quit asking questions about scientific,
astronomical, geophysics, and so forth.
And that the...
I'm sorry I didn't bring it down here.
We should bring it down.
Certainly for the ceremonies at the fire tonight.
We have the original sky goat mask.
We had no idea how important that would be to Judge Punch.
It wasn't that important to us.
She almost threw it away.
But it turns out that that was the key
to the hidden Satanism of the subgeniuses.
Speaking of Satanism, you know, at Starwood,
they have 1,500 pagans here.
And I've stood here, and I usually...
I don't get all 1,500.
Come to my thing, because they have a nude body painting opposite.
But I've many times asked the assembled pagans in front of me,
200 or 300 people,
how many people here believe in Satan?
And one year, one guy held up his hand,
and he was a heavy metal band member.
Well, it's a Christian sect.
You have to be a Christian if Satan is a member.
That's what I used to say.
But Nenslow corrected me very insultingly and said,
My God, do I have to explain everything to you?
Satan has been around for 3,000 or 4,000 years.
He was Shaitan.
Under the name Shaitan, he was a sand devil or demon
of a pathetic little wandering tribe
whose rep just got bigger and bigger and bigger.
You know how that happens with some gods and demons.
They don't do anything that big,
but they become celebrities nonetheless.
And so for 2,000 years, we have to follow laws
made up by their dipshit.
Paul M
A
philosophy. You can't
contradict it. It's the ultimate
kook vehicle.
And as a result, we've got a lot of
kooks hanging off the rear bumper
of our fine vehicle.
Yes, it's too much for them.
The seething eddies
of our passage have
disturbed them from their trance-like
sleep.
Hi, I believe
you should check out The Legend of Atlantis.
As Bob said, it's going to be
a bummer, man. The prophecy will
ring through. Check it out.
I better hear something on the next
hour or so. And peace out.
Ivan Stang.
Peace out.
You know, Bob
did
say over and over again
the kind of things that
schizophrenics and
crackpots most want to hear.
And
they have flocked to hear
him say that.
Now, we probably don't have to
deprogram many
of you, but
you know, there's people in the basement
of the Dobstown University
Science Clinic that we just can't
tell the conspiracy news media
about. We've never been
able to deprogram them. They're
still down there going, Bob Slack,
Bob Slack. Nothing wrong with that.
I did that for my first five years, too,
just as I'm sure most of you did.
But there is
such a thing as you going overboard.
They do work for us at airports and
bus stations and things. They really
need supervision.
Right. So we find these people who
believe all the
jokes and
get the lies and then
call everybody else Bobbies.
So
I was the first Bobby.
If anybody calls another
subgenius a Bobby, you've got to call me
a Bobby first. I was the first Bobby
and I'm the most slavish
and corny Bobby.
I'm not going to let anybody else
out Bobby me.
Nor shall we let
the Jehovah's Witnesses out
kook us. That's right. How many times
have they waited for the end of the world?
Not more than six or seven.
We've waited for the end of the world. This will be my
eleventh time.
Well, the ninth time.
Yeah, maybe this will be
it, though. There have been omens
that this could be the
X-Day. The angel turds that
have been left all over the campground.
Verily, a great marvel.
A great marvel. The collision
of the two great storms on Jupiter
that's due to start tomorrow.
We have no idea what kind of result
that could be. Yes, between the
great spot and the not so great
spot. Yeah, Red
Junior, they call the smaller
red spot.
But it's still going 350 miles an hour.
Before the eyes of the astronomers of Earth.
Oh, that's right. And the other,
thank you very much, Reverend Scalpod.
During this X-Day,
friends, this is the most important one of all.
See the X-designed
electrostimulo wristbands?
We ran
out of them this
weekend. And since that time,
people have been wearing the
Dayglo orange electrostimulo
wristbands. By this, we know
the time is nigh
for their arisal.
And it's possible that some may be
divvied up into the
X-wristband
kind and the... Well,
you mean that the writing
and they shall have two bands.
I thought that was the amino acids
in the Billy Nair show. I didn't realize
that it referred to two wristbands.
But this shows how
difficult it is
to understand these prophecies until
one gets right on the cusp
of them. Right. Sometimes you don't know what
it meant until after the miracle
happened.
Well, that's a possibility. It could also
mean that you're more like part of the
refreshments that will be served
during the trip.
But we just don't know.
As you board those great ships,
some will be led, in fact,
to those first class seats. And no doubt
some will be led through the
slaughterhouse doors.
They may be pink. Their money is
green. I sold
a membership last week to somebody
that I would
judge to be the dumbest,
just the pinkest
fuckwad.
And yet, he sent his 30 bucks.
So how pink could he be? I grappled.
I really, really thought
I didn't cash that
I didn't punch in those credit card
numbers for a whole week.
Because I had to
But finally, in the end, I thought, what would Bob
do? Bob would take the fucking
money, tell the guy, yeah,
you're a subgenius. Now chant this.
Oh, wah, tagus, I am.
And, you know, 500 times
a night, everything's cool.
And, by the way, don't you need
this new, improved Arise
video?
Reverend Stang, may I take a minute for a very
brief commercial announcement?
Sure, sure.
Everything set up here is a commercial
announcement. Praise Bob.
Praise Bob.
But, of course, I do want to
just give one more mention to the
lovely person who won the most stoic
award, and that would, again, be Reverend
Magdalene. And since
we have all of you here, now is a good time
to make a plug for a very,
important fundraiser for
Reverend Magdalene's legal fund
that is going on at this time.
The noble folks of IRC
Taphouse have
produced a series of
t-shirts that state
Why a Goat?
Also, they have one special
shirt that they are going to auction
off that has been autographed
by Reverend Magdalene.
100% of the proceeds of this shirt
will go to her legal fund.
Thank you very much.
Obviously, it's autographed.
I don't know how many of you are doing the online thing.
It says Why a Goat in the front. I'll read you the back
and then show it to you.
We are dedicated to our art.
I'm sorry that you don't understand it, sir.
Signed, Rachel Bevilacqua,
Reverend Magdalene.
Stop talking. Obviously, there's nothing
funny in those pictures.
Honorable James P.
Punch, Family Court Judge.
Woo!
And so we auction this shirt
in memory of
a time when subgenius
could run freely through the country
without being persecuted
for their heads.
Alright. So, it has to start
at $20. That's what they cost
on the internet. If you get one for $15 that's
autographed, that's just stupid.
It's a bargain.
...
Sold!
$220!
That's not loud enough, ladies and gentlemen.
I wish there was someone responsible
to give this money to.
That is all.
Anyone else?
...
Nick Abbey of The Billy Nair Show.
All right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right.
On this day, we became newly ordained ministers on this very day.
And someone requested certain topics, certain subject matters on this day,
on this very day when we became newly ordained ministers.
So I think we'll start off by telling a story with a little conceptual dance I once learned.
I was there the day that Christ was born.
I heard Gabriel blow his happy horn.
Three men came to the manger.
They whispered, howdy, stranger.
And I could tell right then the child's life would be in danger.
I heard him talking on the hilltop high.
And I remember thinking, what a guy.
He didn't look too tough, but he said some real cool stuff.
And he quit talking after everyone had heard enough.
And I was there the night he had his trial.
I took a seat because it took a while.
It got pretty intense, though.
He had no real defense, though.
But everyone I know's been talking about it ever since, though.
And I was there when he was crucified.
I hung around and watched him as he died.
I packed a simple lunch, just something I could munch on.
I couldn't hear what he was saying, but I had a hunch.
And I was there the night he rose from the dead.
He had a light that went around his head.
He drove around all night.
And he was quite a man.
He was quite a sight.
And when I talk about this part, people get real uptight.
But I was there the night he rolled his truck.
And I remember thinking, what the fuck, man?
He was a real good driver.
He was a real survivor.
He had the driving skills Americans should really strive for.
His truck bursted into a flaming heat.
That's what you get when you buy trucks that cheap.
But all his deeds were simple.
One time he got a pimple.
He waved his hand and it was gone.
And it was just that simple.
I watched him walk out of the burning pile.
He blew the crowd a kiss and flashed his smile.
You should have heard them clapping.
He act like nothing happened.
And then he sang a song that said, everyone's toes are tapping.
And it went a little something like this.
I saw Santa and I saw Satan.
And I said, it looks like they're about to begin it.
No, you're wrong.
A voice said, the boys in red will be back in a minute.
I saw Lazarus sitting on the sidewalk.
I sat down by his side.
I said, he died.
What's it like to be dead?
He just looked me in the eyes and shook his head.
Though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death,
I will fear no evil, hear no evil, see no evil,
speak no evil, I just keep walking.
I saw Lazarus walking through the valley of the shadow of death.
He was out of breath.
I said, you've always been a hero to me.
He said, if I'd known that, I'd have done things differently.
I saw Santa and I saw Satan.
And I said, it looks like they're about to begin it.
No, you're wrong, said the boys in red.
They said, you're soaking in it.
There is a world
that's so hard to find between reality and your mind.
There is a part of you that works like a spy
between your conscience and your eye.
And each time you swallow, it photographs your thoughts.
These are the only moments God will ever see.
Believe it or not,
ready to die.
Fear not, you've been recorded for posterity.
And if you don't believe in God,
it's because he never gave you a soul.
then it really shouldn't bother you to know this fact.
And if you don't have a soul,
then you're never going to get one.
If you don't have a soul, then it doesn't really matter,
so you might as well just have fun.
If you seek inner peace,
in a world of strife and struggle,
and if you can achieve some personal relief,
well, don't let God's face burst your bubble.
A battle that's well chosen
is a battle that's already won.
So pick your fights,
focus on yourself,
and above all, just have fun.
Make this world a better place
by living a good life
with your wife and your kids and your cars and your house
and your houses and your cars and your wife.
Set a good example,
not like the unfortunate ones
who struggle and suffer and starve and die
because they don't know how to have fun.
And then also we had the Billy Nair show up here.
How was that?
That was ultra cool and groovadelic,
and it drove the females into a tizzy
as his lanky cowboy hat had formed,
danced on the stage.
Then his film, The Reluctant,
I mean, The American Astronaut was shown.
Yay! That's my favorite movie ever!
Yes. The Reluctant Astronaut, of course,
is the Don Knotts classic.
Not the same.
What a classic.
Not the same, and yet in a class by itself.
And of course, we also had other films shown there,
including Island of Lost Souls,
Five Thousand Fingers of Dr. T,
The Tingler,
House on Haunted Hill,
Sky Cap Tink,
and The World of Tomorrow,
and the King Kong remake,
with special focus on giant insect scenes
and other felicity.
So speaking of Don Knotts...
Yes, you could tie yourself in knots laughing at...
He has a boulevard named after him
in Morgantown, West Virginia,
where he hails from, as do I.
You have a boulevard named after you?
No.
I just hailed from Morgantown.
Oh, well.
Yeah, there's Don Knotts Boulevard.
Where music like this plays in the bank.
Well, sure makes the line go faster.
Yep. While you're waiting in line,
you can read the supermarket tabloids
on Coogee and Joogee's new baby,
and the stretch marks that appeared on San's hand.
I am gonna take out my favorites
Don't think that you have to take it
home
Hitch it, hitch it, hitch it,ім
Get it, get it,交
Get it, get it,àcies 획
Don't think that you have to take it
Home
I fell in love in the usual way
I said things that lovers say
Lovers say, lovers say
I went to work on the wrong highway
I fell in love in the usual way
I set my back on the ground
I sat down and she sat down
What's that sound, what's that sound
What's that sound that's calling me
In a most familiar way
Could it be the wrong highway
Twinkle, twinkle, little heart
Where you are is what you aren't
What you are is what you are
There's a lover holding me
Holding me to make me stay
Holding me to the wrong highway
There's a star up in the sky
Scenery there when I die
It will always shine for you
Loving you the way I do
Till the sun comes shining through
And it's time to go away
And there's nothing you can do
And there's nothing you can say
You're the star of where you are
Shining on the wrong highway
There's a star up in the sky
And there's nothing you can do
Thank you.
In terrible color, but we had nothing to do with the contraption that's projecting it.
What we have to do with is the result which has been achieved.
Yes, one can be proud and stand tall as a subgenius.
Tall as a brachiosaurus, indeed.
Tall as the extended neck of the Atlantosaurus or the giants of the Mesozoic Age.
What is the largest dinosaur now known?
Well, it's difficult to say because the Seismosaurus was the longest dinosaur.
Though Seismosaurus shook the earth with gentle steps from day to day,
she sought the uplands of her birth, devouring forests on the way.
But larger than the Seismosaurus was the Argentinosaurus.
The old-style Brontosaurus could walk under the legs of the Argentinosaurus
and not touch its pendulous, rumbling abdomen.
Vomit Argentinosaurus was not welcome at parties.
No, but there was an entire category of busy insects which welcomed the vomiting behemoth.
Think of how much that could feed, friends.
Think if you were there with the dinosaurs as they vomited fast gouts,
enough to feed a small man.
I've been a mammal for weeks.
Those small mammals were there.
But they didn't have weeks to dine on nature's bounty.
They had to snatch and grab what they could to do a dine and dash and eat alfresco
in the jungles of the prehistoric world.
And you know what, folks?
Our own kind was represented even then.
The primate order.
Oh, it was there.
It didn't look like King Kong that much,
but you can't blame the animals.
You can't blame the humies for a little bit of glamour in their productions.
No, if you look back into the labyrinth of ancestral memory,
you'll see a little fuzzy fellow squatting there
as Allosaurus and Ceratosaurus do bloody battle
under the quivering fronds of Arboraceous palms.
Man, you're turning me on now.
The Brontosaurus, a living mountain of flesh and bone.
All right, all right.
Well, we'll get into that later.
What did they tell you?
They were too heavy to support their own weight
unless they floated around in swamps of blood.
Well, if they let themselves go.
I mean, aerobic exercise was important for all beings
and particularly for large sauropods
because if they fell down, they could injure themselves severely.
So every step really had to be skillfully done.
It makes me sick how these Johnny-come-lately humans
who have only been around a few million years
go on and on about a legend.
It's not just about the rigid dinosaur clumsiness.
It's humans who are always falling over.
And why not?
They can get back up again.
Unlike the ponderous dinosaurs
who would have to be aerobically successful and clever
beyond the agility of stumpy, bumpy humans.
And even the primitive humans were in many ways
the superior of the modern man
because they had to be to exist in their strange, wild world.
We think of a caveman as some belching slob.
Nay, not so.
The modern TV-watching pink
is the belching, stubbled, scratching, farting slob.
Our intelligence has devolved.
The caveman
It can't help but devolve.
or cavewoman
Until next day!
like all so-called savages,
intensely ritualized every portion of life.
You were talking about the fact that
It's something about dumb versus stupid.
I got that.
Dumb versus stupid.
And dumb wins when it comes down to it.
But there's two kinds of monkeys.
Dumb monkeys and stupid monkeys.
And praise Bob, I'm a dumb monkey.
But I ain't a stupid monkey.
Now, of those monkeys there are other variations
of which one might perhaps account
the situation of the mean monkey
and the stupid monkey.
More often than not, the mean monkey is a stupid monkey.
But there are occasions where the mean monkey is a dumb monkey.
In which case we have problems.
Severe problems.
Because the dumb monkey,
although dumb, is not stupid.
And when mean, can commit acts of egregious
and unreasonable verisimilitude.
And the monkeys,
well, I have heard speak of monkeys
with a nature that is neither dumb nor stupid.
One might call them perhaps smart monkeys.
But I myself have not had the glory or honor
of interaction with such monkeys.
Such monkeys are, to my own experience,
strictly hypothetical.
And not in any way legitimately real or referenceable.
But the hypothetical possibility exists
for the smart monkey.
And towards this end,
I think it is not inappropriate
for us to aspire in such a direction
as to perhaps consider ourselves as potentially smart monkeys.
Although I would say, in that regard,
it is perhaps overly ambitious
for us to consider ourselves presently smart monkeys,
but only hypothetically...
Yahtzee!
...future smart monkeys,
in a Yahtzee sort of a sense.
Right.
Well, some might agree,
and some might not.
And I would say to those that do not,
that they are incorrect.
And those that agree,
they probably just misunderstood.
Frankly, with the issue of the dumb versus the stupid,
there are also other varieties of monkeys.
Drunken monkeys.
And the drunken factor can augment
and magentify the...
Magentify.
It's a color!
It's, yes, it makes them...
It has a really nice flavor, magenta.
I don't know if you've had any lately.
They can magentify and augment
in particular directions and spectrums
so as to manifest various other quantities and qualities.
The dumb monkeys may or may not be mean monkeys,
and the stupid monkeys are often inadvertently mean monkeys.
But you know what?
If you keep poking the retarded dog with a stick,
don't be surprised if he bites your ass.
Dogs and monkeys are much similar in that manner.
Poke a monkey with a stick, he'll bite your ass too.
Whether or not he's retarded.
But
please repent if you use your smart hands at this time.
Some of you missed the first half of the set
so we'll start it all over again.
We're the Billionaire Show, ladies and gentlemen.
This will be our last song for the night.
Thank you so much for having us up here.
This is a blast, and it's so nice to see all of you.
We have our movie playing tomorrow night,
The American National.
We wrote it, directed it, acted in it,
did the music for it, and so on and so on.
It'll be playing tomorrow night.
Oh, I envy you the experience of watching it,
even though I have seen it myself.
You must find...
What's that?
Our contract?
We signed the contract,
and we are ordained ministers on this evening.
Thank you very much.
So again, we're the Billionaire Show.
If you don't come up and say hi,
do please stay in touch.
We've got a new film we're working on right now
called Werewolf Hunters of the Midwest,
and hopefully that'll be out at some point soon
or by next year,
and we'll let you know when that is.
Again, thank you very much.
I'll finish all my lunch
And I'll eat all my fries
And I'll prove to you
That my stomach's as big as my eyes
I'll spring for the check
And walk you to my home
That's where I spend all my days
All alone
I'll show you my chair
And I'll show you my chair
And show you my bed
And I'll show you movies
That I've taped
And all the books I've read
I'll show you pictures of me
When I had lots of hair
And I'll tell you all the things
I think of when I sit and stare
I'll tell you some of my plans
And some of my schemes
And I'll tell you all about
Some of my dreamy little dreams
And I'll tell you all about some of my dreams
I'll tell you that my apartment
Is the center of the universe
It gets hot there
It's hot there now
But it's been known to get a lot worse
I'll show you paintings that I painted
And tell you all about my lamp
I'll show you water damage
In the corner where it gets damp
I'll put my chair in front of your chair
And my feet against your feet
Then later on I'll show you my lamp
And maybe we'll want to
Go and get a bite to eat
I'll finish all my dinner
And I'll eat all my fries
And I'll prove to you
That my stomach's as big as my eyes
And after I have shown you
All there is to see
I will ask you
Will you marry me?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I'll just better cool off
Thank you very much!
And in addition to the Billy Mayer show,
we also had the amino acids,
and the amino acids,
and some other bands.
Professional bands.
Some other...
Making all the subgenius bands look all the more stupid.
Was there much jamming by the subgenius bands?
There was a little.
Even it wasn't too terrible.
You know, I think we had it a little wrong.
It seems...
There will be bar and damnation.
But it's not like there's some.
The end is nigh.
Time to die.
Friends, you have been listening to
the subgenius hour of Slack.
The background music here is,
and before, is by
Reverend Angry Larry with Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
Reverend Carter LeBlanc,
Reverend Two Beans, Reverend Phil, and Princess Wee,
altogether known as Five-Fisted Tales for Connie that one night.
For more information about the Church of the Subgenius Friends
and everything we've covered here, check out subgenius.com,
if that gives you slack.
Subgenius, by the way, does not have an O in it.
However, Bob does, and praise Bob.
Subgenius Friends