Now, ladies and gentlemen, soon you're going to hear the voice of Ivan Stang himself, the sacred scribe.
We also have Papa Joe Mama, an extraordinary ranter and theologist,
who has helped us refine our doctrine down to the purity of bedrock,
and acts as a check upon the wild and fanciful flights of the rest of us.
And it's possible that we may entice Priestess Pisces to the podium.
And, in fact, there could be an agreeable smorgasbord in all ways.
Once we get going, which is imminent, we are making the final technical adjustments.
All systems are go.
We are prepared for launch and are holding.
Our announced time to PM is theoretical,
but we will hew to it.
As closely as possible.
He gave me his phone number and we said goodbye.
It was two months later that old Bob died.
Needle in his arm.
In some hotel room.
With a needle in his arm.
My name's Bobby.
He said I'm Bobby too.
He said I'm...
Self-genius.
Our own self.
We are Bob Dobs!
They are Bob Dobs!
We're still preparing for the main sequence of our broadcast,
and now it is my privilege to introduce to this stream
the redoubtable Papa Joe Mama,
deacon of the Church of the Subgenius.
Could you pot up Papa Joe, please, on the far microphone? Thank you.
We have to be plugged into the matrix here.
We have to turn the magic switch.
Now I'm feeling potted.
Actually, that started the moment I got close to the campgrounds.
The...
The air.
The camp air.
And speaking of air,
the idea is that this will be live via tape.
Is that the idea?
Oh, it's as live as can be.
It's as live as a wriggling snake.
Oh, live versus via tape worm.
Yeah, exactly.
And...
It gets into your gut.
Not only that, but... It gets into your gut.
Not only that, but it will be resurrected and live again.
And again and again and again.
You know, a tape worm is one of the unique animals in the animal kingdom, Dr. Howell,
because you can slice it and dice it into a million pieces,
and it just keeps growing and growing,
much like the word of Bob.
You can break it up, sever it, chop off its head, cut off its tail,
and it just resurrects and grows even more.
It's like the sorcerer's apprentice.
Yes, it will grow an extra head if you tease it properly.
But what it will never be is an amphisbema,
a being with a head at each end.
One end must always be anterior.
And we of the Church of the Subgenius,
whether or not we be a parasitic organism in the bowels of the conspiracy,
must move ahead or face choking ourselves in the labyrinth of our own coils.
Indeed, the subgenius motto is,
You never get enough head.
And you know, lately we've been studying parasites and microbiology in the Church of the Subgenius.
Soon Ivan Stang will be able to pronounce on the water sample he took yesterday from the swimming pond,
and tell us what jointed horrors are swimming in it now.
Some microscopic, some terrestrial, and some from origins unknown.
Well, that's all relative, you know, a matter of size,
but sometimes the little guys can sting you the most.
There's all sorts of different orifices that climb into that pool,
and what they emit is almost as scary as what enters those orifices.
But there's somebody there.
And the orifices enter other orifices,
and then there's orifices that enter other orifices,
and then slot A, tab B, and I think that makes sex hurt.
Other combinations make sex hurt.
Slot B, tab B.
Instead of slot A, tab B.
And then there's tab B, tab C, and slot A.
Slot A.
But the little critters in the puddle are so finely organized
that there are special delegations of them organized to take advantage even of the mistakes.
But you know, I think the pond organisms will find that the yeti chemistry,
the body chemistry and the makeup of mutants,
may not work exactly with their body chemistries as nature intended.
Producing gigantic mutants,
huge diving beetles,
blood-sucking sand fleas.
But it's not always about reproduction.
Sometimes it's just the act of reproduction.
If there's one thing that there's never a shortage of at these events,
it's lots of yeti and lots of their cohabitating slots.
Of course, the yeti lives in happy harmony with nature,
and acknowledges the many fellow travelers which abide in his shaggy pelt.
And even we, the etiolated descendants of the yet and sin,
have special organisms that live in the eyelash
as different from the other arthropods that live in the eyebrow,
and so forth and so on.
Your body requires this maintenance staff.
But the mighty yeti had a whole army of critters
scampering through his fur.
And please be kind to your maintenance staff
and these anima-cules, as they've been known.
Yeah, you don't want to singe them with chemicals and all this crap that conspiracy gives you.
All they want to do is get their groove on,
have a little anima-cule sex hurt.
Don't stop them.
That would be so cruel.
Be kind.
Let these organisms reproduce.
Provide your sex.
Your ancestors may be one of them.
As the lusty, cheap motel for microorganisms
to have their exciting, though momentary, trysts.
You wouldn't be able to have a normal bowel movement
without your large group of intestinal flora,
who are always on the job, helping you out.
And if you ever disturb their world of equilibrium,
you can eat yogurt and things like that.
And help them out.
But what one should not do is be at an antagonistic remove
from one's churning insides.
From any part of the body.
We must work in sync with it
so that we are better able to achieve our goal.
When it comes down to the battlefield
and the war against the conspiracy.
In a similar manner, such is the subgenius to the conspiracy.
They think of us as parasites,
but what they don't realize is that we are not.
We are the salvation of their existence.
Without us, the conspiracy cannot survive.
But we, fellow subgeni,
we can survive without the conspiracy.
And that is what we are about to discover.
And just to load these three days away.
Papa, Joe, Mama, as usual, you'll get right to the point.
I was taking too long to make it.
Which is that we are not the parasite on the conspiracy.
The conspiracy is the parasite on us.
Though vastly larger and bloated,
mostly with our juices,
all their ideas come from us.
And for good or ill,
we direct them on their reproductive,
mimicry-dominated pattern.
We're sort of the intellectual energy
which they sap their battery packs from,
much in the same way that the Matrix might live off of humans.
We are, in essence, the intellectual firepower
of all humanity.
If not civilization in general.
Not to take too much on ourselves,
but the stimulus which creates the tropism.
And keep in mind,
it's not unlike, if you remember the concept of that
sort of ectoplasm.
How the ectoplasm gets its,
going back to a good, great subgenius movie, Ghostbusters.
And the ectoplasm sort of absorbs the energy that's put out.
The conspiracy is also that ectoplasm.
And they can pick up our energy.
So it is a possibility to,
I don't want to say use this for good per se,
because we're not about good or evil or such,
you know, binary terms as that.
But it is possible that you can take your yeti energy
and take, and sort of push it into,
and let that conspiracy ectoplasm absorb it.
And what's great about that is then,
one of the greatest things about it,
one of the great examples that I've always heard,
is that yeti sex hurt, for example,
can often spawn future yetis.
For example, if you and your yeti mate are getting it on,
and your neighbors upstairs are at the same time,
that yeti energy actually goes into the fetus of your neighbor.
These completely, utterly pink conspiracy slaves
will then give birth
to a mutant yeti.
But that wouldn't be parasitism,
that would be synchronicity,
an organic, orgasmic vortex,
in which nobody suffers and all benefit.
It would be symbiosis, right?
Yes, symbiosis, that's what I was thinking of.
And yet they always try to make you feel guilty
for inspiring this act of creation.
They might take their broomstick and hammer it on the top of their ceiling
and complain that you're disturbing them.
Such mindless primitives.
And yet if we hadn't made that noise,
they never would have even been inspired to have sex in the first place.
They would not even be alert,
but snoozing and dozing on in their own blocked-off, mind-forged manacles.
Once again, they try to make you feel bad for what you are.
They say that your ectoplasm is nothing more than snot
that they blow out of their third nostril,
and yet it is...
You can't survive without mucus.
You need that ectoplasm.
It's a spiritual ectoplasm.
It's more than just some sort of bodily fluid.
So they may think of it as something that's just
not even worthy of picking from their nostrils
and smearing underneath the underbelly of the dining room table,
but it is an essential ingredient to their survival.
This whole thing of the reprimand which they give,
which seems so hurtful to us, the sensitive individuals,
means very little to them in truth,
and it's actually just a trick, a device,
to give them time to catch up with us,
because they don't think as fast as we do,
and they want some breathing room,
and so they try to make you feel guilty.
And while you stammer, blush, stumble, and flush,
they can come to the next slow plan
of how they can trick you out of your last simoleon.
And the problem you have is that they are so limited.
They can't see beyond that which is just in front of them.
And you, in your very existence,
are inserting this X, this unknown variable,
and they don't know how to do the math.
Their brains just can't handle another variable
into the equation of their lives.
But they might be able to.
They might be teachable, do you think?
Well, unfortunately, yes, but they'll take something like math,
the pure science that does not discriminate,
and they turn it into a tool of discrimination
by using something like the law of averages.
We know just from our mathematical studies
that for every conspiracy dupe,
there's only one one-thousandth of a subgenius.
So in essence, there's a thousand pings
for every subgenius that's out there.
So they'll turn that around on its head,
and they'll say, well, there's more of us
than there's more of you.
Therefore, you are the abnormal one.
You are the aborition.
You are the mutant.
Well, it's true that we are the mutant,
but is that a bad thing? No.
Just as to humanity,
the Neanderthals were unique
when it first dawned on this planet
amongst the fields of Neanderthals.
They turned and said,
look at the ones with the extended foreheads.
They are ugly.
They are stupid.
They cannot even throw a spear as far as we can.
And they made them feel abnormal.
And yet, where are they now?
I have to...
They're still here.
The Neanderthals are actually still here.
They are folded into our own genetic...
...genetic...
...structure. It's interesting.
The only true humans left on the planet
are Africans.
Black Africans.
Every other type of race,
so-called, on the planet's surface
migrated out of Africa
and encountered other forms of hominids.
Those who were sexually incompatible
bred mules,
offspring which were sterile themselves.
But the Neanderthals,
from whom we get fair skin,
blue eyes,
light, easily sunburned,
skin, and so forth,
intermarried with
the dear Africans and produced
the contemporary races.
First, the races which
developed into Asia, and then
finally, the races that
inhabited Europe.
This brings up an interesting point, though.
That would sort of
lead me to make a logical jump
to assume that not only
are
every peak
has a small portion of us,
but
we have a small
portion of pink.
Yes, and our lives have a small portion
of death. It's important
to keep a little bit
of the opposite matter
incubating, just to be on
the right track. There's really no way to
remove the pinkness, but there is a way
to replace the pinkness. And the idea
is to simply
push it out with new DNA
from a new life force.
That life force of which we're hoping to
encounter in just a mere three days.
So, new genetic
material is on its way from a distant
star system, but
we'll want to still encapsulate
some of those pink genes and put them
in deep seed storage, much
like some of the seed stores
in Antarctica, just for
museum purposes. Well, and the
thing that bothers me about that thought is
that, you know, as
much as we look forward to
the saucers coming, and as
much as we look forward to the sex goddesses and
the eternal bliss that's guaranteed,
I worry because
how does one know slack
without knowing not slack?
What will happen to us
when we forget
what not slack
is? Sister Pisces, you
bring up a very controversial but important
part of the whole Holocaustal
theology, which is the necessary
perhaps the
setting aside of
pink reservations for the future. Should
we save not just some of the genetic... We could call them
camps. Yes.
So people can concentrate on those
pinks. Concentration camps for
the pinks. Yes, right. They could be concentrated
into these camps. Now, at the
present time, here we are in a camp,
but after our revolution,
they will be in the camps
like this while we inhabit
the catbird seat.
When we put up the
barbed wire fences and
electrified fences, it will be... It's really
to keep us out from messing with
them and their poor, feeble
nature. It is for their own safety,
I would imagine. I mean, once everything
comes into place and we have the alien technology
to make us reach our fullest potential,
it's... We would...
I mean, the decimation
that we could rack upon...
I'm not saying they're
innocent. Please don't
think that. They are innocent of some things.
We should pity them.
It's that little gene of pinkness that you're
talking about that is responsible for
those less desirable
traits and subgeniousness.
The feelings of wanting revenge,
the feelings of contempt for them, that is
the pinkness of coming through. So,
again, the electrified fences and the barbed wire
fences, right now it's to protect
them from us going out and
ravaging them, but when they're inside
the camps, it will be to protect them from
us coming back. Absolutely. Because we're going to outnumber
them. The guard towers
with the machine gun carrying
guards... Protection. They're
psychological protection for them. They
have to believe that it's not their
choice to be inside
these compounds because their
egos wouldn't stand
the knowledge of the real truth.
And keep in mind, we will have to
train very special, very
hardy subgeniuses
to manage these.
A special staff. A special staff.
Maybe we could give them their own uniforms
or something like that. It needs to be...
I honestly believe that it will have
to be some sort of
rare...
A true holocaustal would
have to manage that system.
All these scare tactics,
these rumors that people have been passing around
about... Deplorable.
There's going to be millions that are going to be killed
as they try to escape. They don't understand the
economy of fear.
The fact of the matter is, is that after
your first attempted escape,
say six
people, maybe twelve people gunned down,
no one else is going to attempt after that.
I mean, you only need to demonstrate
once. This is a concept that we
learned from training elephants.
Well, now you're talking about directing traffic.
I mean, we can take care of that after the...
You put the chain on there only for the first
time until they hurt their ankle, and then
after that you just have a little rope and eventually
you can replace it with a thread.
But sadly, even today
we have to ask ourselves, how has that
been twisted and used on us?
How have we been held
at bay with these psychological
threads that are chains
in our own minds? They represent no
real physical boundaries
and yet they hold us back.
That's your elephant. This is a really big
concern that has been, you know,
and especially, and I know there are
some uberfems in the audience,
uberfems are subjected by the
conspiracies to some really,
really horrible programming
that is sort of deep-seated in
us that we have to fight on a daily basis.
I mean, the conspir...
It's the same thing with the fear tactics.
As uberfems, we are told we
are too fat,
we are ugly, we should
shut up, we should sit down.
Carping cause of jealousy.
And what that does is
we...
There are beautiful women here, and the truth
of the matter is you won't see as many
titties as there should be.
Because they have that conspiracy
programming in their head that says that
they are ugly, they are worthless,
they have been treated this way.
They should be ashamed.
Exactly. That you should be ashamed
of how you are, you should be ashamed of
your wonderful mutant beauty.
And that
goes back to what you discussed with the
fear tactics. It's being used
on us, but we can learn from that.
And we can adapt that, and we can not
only break our own programming
that has been embedded in
us by the media, by our
parents, by the conspiracy,
by television, by radio, by
the stores everywhere.
Will you dare to wear your underwear
on the outside of your clothing?
If not, why not? Because someone
tells you that it has to be on the inside?
It's more comfortable on the outside, especially
after you've soiled it. You don't want to be that
trash. But no,
we continue to follow what they tell us to do.
This is outrageous.
But remember, they are not
always only in an official guise.
Your peers can
be silent simps and
fellow travelers of the conspiracy.
They will enforce
these meaningless memes
upon you if you don't
examine each and every one of them.
Now I know this could cause a
skull-buster of a headache,
but it's worth to fall into the habit
and ultimately more
easeful in the long run.
More producing of slack.
Conventional wisdom, the dirtiest
conspiracy word ever
developed.
Because if wisdom is anything, it's not
conventional. No, no.
And if common sense is anything, it's not
common. Also, there's quite
a difference between wisdom
and intelligence. They are
not the same thing. Being
smart is being able to figure things out
and take care of yourself. Wisdom
is simply to be able to
incorporate extra-somatic
knowledge and remember it.
Knowledge by writ
instead of knowledge by intellect.
Repetitio est mater
studiorum. And this is another thing the conspiracy
is so good at doing.
I mean, we, we, they are
good at having us wrote,
memorize. We get
taught again and again and again
reinforcement, reinforcement,
reinforcement of these
horrible ideas.
That we are then stuck.
They're programmed in our brain before
we even know it.
But fortunately, we being subgeniuses can
invert them,
speckle them, turn them inside
out and otherwise
arrange them for our own
convenience and pleasure. We don't
just accept what they
spoon out, but we spice
and season it according to our own
dictates. Perhaps the most
insidious thing that the conspiracy ever
developed was the ability to erase our
racial memory. There was at one
time when we were born with the ability
of language and
all the experiences of our forebears.
But they realized that if we continued
this trait, we would know that
we were better than them.
This is true. So they had to erase
all the history that we might otherwise
know. And we are born now, but
essentially without any instinct other than the
bear instinct of that to suckle.
And thank God for that. Well, without any
conscious instinct, but as
Plato proved,
actually we already know
all that stuff. We just need it to be
teased out of us.
Get that little slave boy the proper
pencil and a little bit of guidance.
There's no telling what he may innately
know. He may be an
astronomer equal to Aristarchus
and a philosopher equal to
Heraclitus. And this he can
demonstrate to the Athenian Solons.
Then he can go back and clean the toilets.
But why is it that the animals have
more instinct than us? I mean, they're supposed
to be lesser beings. Because they don't have
the conscious
governor, the system
which sits on top of the limbic
system which only yet in sin
and humans have.
That and the fact that there
are not animals telling other
animals that they're wrong. And yet
it only takes one generation often to
forget some of those
instincts. You take the simple rabbit, for example.
Take that rabbit,
take it out of the wild, put it in a cage,
breed one generation,
and that new generation loses the ability
to burrow. And thus,
the ability to survive in the wild. They've been
domesticated. Dear friends,
this is the essential problem of the
subgenus. We've allowed ourselves
to become domesticated.
Not only
domesticated, but completely
inculcated with false
principles. Like false
slack. This is why coming to
a camp like this is so essential
to our salvation. We are going back
to the pre-civilization, the
pre-domestication days.
We were all born with original slack.
But the conspiracy
wants to suck that away
from us, to use it for its own purposes,
and then to sell us
false slack, which
it manufactures.
And to pay for the
false slack, to spend
endless hours of meaningless toil,
only to buy
meaningless tchotchkes.
But every iPod or
iPad or whatever that you're jonesing
for that you think is going to
be the thing which completes
you and will make you happy thereafter
turns out simply to be
an ignis facius.
A mirage.
Because the moment you get it, you want
the next thing and you forget that other
thing. And you were never truly happy
because your attention is not
where it belongs.
They should be wanting your stuff.
You shouldn't be wanting their stuff.
And they do want your stuff.
But they just don't let you
know about it.
They turn you into servants.
Servitude. They want you to
work for them all your
lives. They want you to punch a time
clock. And now they want to look at your
pee. They want to look at your body
fluids. They want to control what
you do when you're off site.
They want a complete
lattice of control.
Perhaps another one of the
conspiracies most, greatest
accomplishments in rewriting history was
the so called emancipation
proclamation where they quote,
did away with slavery.
Unquote.
Well anybody in their right mind knows that the only
difference between old time slavery and
present day slavery is that
present day slavery is timeshare
slavery. And you know back
in the old days, the old form of slavery
was actually more expensive. You had to
pay for that slave. You had to provide
that slave healthcare. You had to provide
that slave food. You had to provide
that slave clothing. And yet
what do they have now?
Slaves who go and work for them at least
eight hours a day, often times more.
And those slaves buy their own
food. They buy their own
clothing. And they even have to pay for
their own healthcare. This is
outrageous. And the
moment that you're no longer an efficient
slave, and you're no longer
capable of producing
the necessary quotas,
then you're let go.
And replaced with a new
slave who jumps in the line
looking forward for the opportunity to
serve them. I might also
add that you're let go into an
abyss of economic uncertainty.
But still with the basic
needs that have to be met.
And your recreational needs,
your recreational drugs, or what have you.
So you end up being criminalized.
You fall into the extensive
prison system, larger
than the population of many countries.
And there you are a slave again.
Only now you're not
being paid. Or you're paid such
a small, contemptible amount that
might as well be nothing.
It's just as much a kick in the slats
to your self-esteem. So of course
you want to stay out of the prison system.
You want to stay out of the medical system.
You want to stay out of the legal system.
You want to stay out of any
system. And the conspiracy
is the greatest system
of all. The greatest time
waster and the greatest
ball breaker that you'll ever
encounter toddling down the pike.
Never fight the
system. That's what they say.
We say the only good system
is a non-system.
A system that's been systematically
destroyed from the
inside out. And that is why many
subgeniuses have their so-called
con job. We're in positions
usually having to do with computer networks,
nerds, people who are right
at the epicenter of the control centers.
And when it hits the fan,
who do you think is going to be throwing the switches?
This is true.
You'll notice many
subgeniuses have jobs in
things that seem not
very subgenius at all.
Food service. In the government.
In legal.
School crossing guards.
Healthcare. Garbage
collecting. Things that seem
not so slackful,
but yet they keep going.
Mechanics. But how
many of them are lawyers? Well,
that's not a position of, that's a
prestigious position of subgenius.
Why? Would they want to be a lawyer?
Go look in your phone book. The typical
phone book, let's say it has, oh,
200 pages.
I'll bet you 60 of those pages are filled
with lawyers. 60 pages
for lawyers. And yet
if you turn to the section on mechanics
or garbage collectors...
One page.
Fewer pages than
the lawyers. You are so preaching to the choir.
And yet how long can society last
without garbage collecting?
How long can society last without
food preparation? How long can society
last without mechanics to keep the cars
running? And then we have to ask ourselves,
how long can we last without the
lawyers? Forever!
At the moment, the conspiracy is
trying to destroy these civil
bonds of society and
place all against all, because
it's found that desperate people
are even better customers than
the self-satisfied
cud-chewers that used to be their
prime source of revenue.
And this is the thing, the one thing,
the reason the conspiracy wants
your slack, and you touched on
it, is that slack cannot
be bought or sold. True slack
has no monetary
value. Unfortunately, it
is a motivator, and the conspiracy
also knows this. And that's
why they present their false version.
They try to actually badmouth
slack. They try to make you afraid of
slack. I mean, ten years ago
we were saying real slack
meant quit your job. And yet now
they've turned that around on their heads. They want you to
feel the worst thing in the world that could
possibly happen to you in today's modern
age is for you to lose
your job. And I do believe
it was Ivan Stang who said that
the worst thing that can happen
if you quit your job is that
you'll find a better one. That's him.
He's right over there.
And yet even within these conspiracy
times, we've managed to get our little worm
holes within their little systems.
The very first, the moment that it becomes
hard to get a job, we've managed to extend
unemployment insurance
for another, what was it, 13 months?
They can't get rid of us.
They keep trying. They take
one step forward, but they go two steps
back. Because, let's face it,
there is no aspect
of life, no phase more rewarding
than that involved with
being the highest
example of evolution, an
art bum.
Ah, the art bum.
I love subgenius
art. I've seen such great
things. I have right here
a
Bob-marked
pinball machine.
A pinball machine with
planets and saucers and
a nice message on the back
that says, if you see this
man, kill him.
Subgeniuses
have a special kind of art.
An art that is completely
incomparable to what
the conspiracy would call art.
Subgeniuses often
will be walking works of art.
Walking a pure
slack in an artistic form
their very appearance and
movements and voice
are art itself.
But the conspiracy will never
see that because they can't
package it. They can't
market it. They can't figure
out how to control
that which is mutant art.
This conspiracy
shuns the bull dada.
They laugh at it.
It is ridiculed unless they can make
a trend out of it and the hipsters will buy it.
The conspiracy doesn't like
real art because it shines
a little light and shows
just a portion of the fraud
of the conspiracy. But let's
be real. Genuine
art comes from pain.
It does not come from a desire to
decorate your living room
with a Thomas Kinkade painting
which comforts and cheers
until the next
few seconds when you forget about it for the rest
of your life.
The being of art is therapeutic.
You do it because you know
you need in some subconscious
way to right the wrongs
that have been done to you.
And ironically
enough it's often the conspiracy which is
producing, at a remove,
this pain.
So in a way you could even
thank the conspiracy for
being the
fountainhead of art
just as
the Jews could thank Hitler
for preserving the Polish
the synagogue
in, where was it,
that he wanted
for a museum of
Jewishness so it was saved.
It's like with friends like that
who needs enemies? It was in
Prague actually and still is.
Well once again the essential
difference between art and entertainment
is that art spires
off some of the synapses in your mind
that actually engage in think.
Thinking art. Whereas
entertainment is just sort of stimulation
for stimulation's sake. But the
conspiracy knows that if you don't
use it you will lose it.
And that is why their entertainment
has so little real art.
They don't want you to fire off the synapses.
They don't want you to think. They want you to lose
that ability to think. They want you to lose
and snooze. They want you to
be just enough awake
to order
the special order that
you can order at this time only.
Can I get you to move ever so slightly?
And while
we're pontificating about art
I'm going to advance the controversial
view that good art
entertains. Yes I know
this is blasphemy because art exists
for the artist and so forth.
Well as Gertrude Stein said
the bad artist suffers
just as much anguish and agony
as the good artist.
And then at the end is still a
bad artist. No
you should unbend a little bit
as an artist and try to make your work
appeal to somebody
not to everybody.
Not everything's for children and not
everything's for everybody as
R. Crumb said. But it should be directed
towards somebody. It shouldn't
be masturbation
like bad art. But
it should have some
recipient in mind. There's going to be
someone out there who appreciates it.
I would believe that sometimes
even if you design
or imagine your art just for yourself
that someone
must appreciate
some reference of the same thing
that you appreciate. And like that
mental masturbation you don't want it all to just
be wasted. I mean that's almost like
mass murder. You want there to at least be a
chance that one of those little modules
of your satisfaction
might lead to greater satisfaction for future
generations. Ah Papa Joe
Mama's Jesuitical training
always shows through.
Yes in principle I agree with
that as well.
We must keep these sorts of principles
deeply embedded in our subconscious
and we must not
extended vacation type events like this.
Well it's important not to let it just
wander away at the end of its tether.
And this might be the appropriate time
to promote the latest addition
to the subgenius
merchandise branch which is
the Connie and Dobbshead condoms.
I'm sure everyone's seen those
or have they?
Oh my gosh
I'm on. Yes
the Dobbs and Connie condoms are over there.
Oddly enough there are more Connie-doms
than Dobbsdoms.
Why wouldn't you want...
They're only two dollars a piece.
We're selling these at a tremendous loss.
We do this as a
head of health concern.
These are not disposable condoms though
Reverend Stang. That's why they have to be
two dollars each because if they were less than
two dollars each you might throw them away after
using them. But with the
subgenius condoms they're actually
suitable for freezing.
I'm really disappointed that the con...that the
Connie condoms have sold less because
I hear all the time
the males in this church talking
about how much they want Connie
on their schlong.
Well they're not just for men too. I mean these
female condoms. They're just trying to be
politically correct.
You may want to use these for
all sorts of appliances. I hate to say it
but Connie's face
on a Dobbs product is the
kiss of death.
Sales wise. I'm not sure
why that is. It's because Connie... I guess
people walk...they like Playboy better or something.
It depends on what way that...which direction
the face is facing.
It really comes down to this. This is something
that I...is sort of ingrained
in our minds and not
on a conscious level but
there is no one face for Connie.
Connie is every
woman. And by
every woman I do unfortunately mean
every woman.
Connie is the
angelic sort of
cherubic beauty such as
a woman like Pantiera.
Connie is the buxom loud
mouthed crazy woman such as
myself. Connie
is the space goddess
princess like we.
Connie is
any number
of the women you see here. We are all
facets of Connie. And
trying to nail down just
one side of Connie on any
just an item.
That is...it doesn't do it justice.
Yes the side is not
the same.
Ironically there is a little bit of Connie in
everyone and everything except for
conspiracy.
No no.
That is the opposite.
It's almost like the anti-Dobbs
has Dobbs name in it. You
can't go off of just simply the name.
There is more to it than the name.
Connie is...I...I...I
Connie has her
place in the conspiracy.
Connie does have her place.
I tend to believe there is sort of a difference
in the machinations and the movements and how
Bob and Connie work.
Connie has the gift
of...let's put it this
way. I recently had a discussion
with a fellow sub-genius
who said...we were
discussing it and I said you know honestly I think
I'm more evil than you.
And he said...why?
And I said...
because I'm a woman.
Females have an ability
a manipulative power and Connie
has to be part of the conspiracy because
that's where she can use
that manipulative power.
It's not a bad thing per se.
Just as nothing as I said before is good
or evil in itself.
It's how those powers are used.
Well like most animals, female humans
are the more lethal of the species.
Exactly.
They have to be to protect the future
of the race.
Speaking of the future of
the race,
I believe that we can now
say truly that the hour of
slack number
or something
like that has begun.
Now that I've finished my
janitorial duties
and we've got
the music soundtrack from the
time machine running, the George
Powell time machine. Ah yes!
Welcome to the sub-genius
radio ministry hour of slack.
And we hope you enjoy
the next hour of
broadcast as much as we enjoy
bringing it to you.
So we were yak yak
yakking about Bob and
Connie and the conspiracy.
As we know, Bob embraces
Connie and
no one, let's be quite
real about this, is pure
enough to be untainted by
the conspiracy. All
religions present an ideal
which you try to live up to.
Trying to divest one's self
from the conspiracy is an ideal.
But you know, many
Muslims who consider themselves
quite devout still go to strip
clubs and bars. They
give themselves a pass for falling
short of their severity. But
they still consider themselves good
Muslims, just as Christians
who also fall into
sin know smugly
and confidently
that they will be forgiven
if they simply perform the proper
rigamarole. But you see how
Bob isn't about
forgiving your sins. Not at all.
Bob is about watching your sins.
And Bob likes to videotape
your sins. And Bob
likes to sell those videotapes
on RedTube later.
Most of you have already bought
the excuse for your sins that he
sells. That divine excuse.
And if there's any
unsaved listening
now, this could be your
last chance to go over there to that sales
table. That's right. There's the swag.
Right there. It emanates.
It radiates darshan.
Holiness. Just a touch
that stuff puts you a leg up.
It radiates an excuse.
That's right. You show it to the cops
and they'll go, oh, sure, of course,
Bob, fine. Go ahead and finish
what you're doing.
That hasn't ever worked for me.
It works for a buzzly hand.
Bob sold it, I smoked it,
that settles it. Praise Bob.
And how many times have we heard
people outside the church say derogatory
things like, oh, that subgenius church.
There's too much resentment.
There's too much hatred in that religion.
I'm not interested in that. Boy, if they
only knew. We've got more love
than all those other religions put together.
How many of those Christians will say things like
love the sinner but
hate the sin. In the church of the subgenius
we love the sinner and
we love the sin. We've got
double the love that they have, brothers and sisters.
And Bob doesn't care diddly
about sins, honestly.
That is such a wrong idea. Bob
doesn't give a frog fart for sins.
Maybe Bob,
if he had the thought, would wish people
didn't have them, but in general
they're not going to scratch his
veneer. What Bob has
and has all of
is luck. And the
closer you can come to the nature
of Bob, the more you can
surf the luck plane
and avoid these conspiracy
monsters that we've been talking about.
You just have to keep surfing.
Of course, like anyone who surfs,
eventually you're going to wipe out.
But don't concentrate on the wipeouts.
They happen. Get back on the
board and continue to
surf the luck plane.
That's all Bob would ever advise.
Sins indeed.
And the quicker you get back on that board,
the quicker you can catch the next
big luck plane wave.
You don't want to wallow in your sand and bruises
and splinters and shark bites. You want to
get back on there and
recreate the glorious moments of
slack. And it is then that you
evince the Bob-like nature the most.
But please, correct me if I'm wrong,
Reverend Stang.
Well, actually, it's the whole
lack of luck that's the tell-tale sign
of the conspiracy. You go into the casino,
all ties go to the house.
You drive down the highway, making some good
time. Well, there's that conspiracy
highway patrolman there waiting for you.
It's infuriating. Who are we
to have to obey society's primitive
laws and morals of stop signs,
yield signs, and so forth?
But with slack,
comes luck. And with luck, comes slack.
But which comes first?
Speaking of coming,
sinning and the
sinless, I have noticed that
for many
subgeniuses, there's this
odd, perverse
desire that increases
for a person with the
innocence of that person.
For instance, some
subgeniuses, if they see a
woman walking
along all dressed up, you know,
slutty style,
Las Vegas hooker look,
they're not that interested.
But when they see that prim and
proper Amish girl,
that Hasidic high school
girl walking along the front
street, that flow of innocence
and sinlessness,
for some reason,
I don't know about the rest of you guys,
but for some of us, there's
this odd desire
to
taint them, to take the clean
and the pure.
What was that line in Shakespeare?
Dost thou
love her most foully
for that which makes her
good?
That was Antonius, I think,
talking about a nun that he had a crush on.
That is true.
How many of y'all had a crush on a nun?
What it comes down to, Stang, is it's a blank
I know Princess Wee did at one point.
She was raised by nuns.
Stang, it's a blank canvas.
Our sins and our dirty thoughts
are in some ways our art.
And we see the
innocent, beautiful,
pure
being and we think,
I would love to spread
my art all
over that canvas.
I hate to repeat myself,
but I've always said that
the truest, most honest
artist, is it not the
jack-off artist?
Or the rub-off artist? Because
that is the artist who's
doing it for the audience.
They're not doing it for an audience.
They don't care what the critics think.
They're doing it for their own
pure self-expression.
That's what I call real art.
It's the most real art.
And as such, I am the Van Gogh
of the subgenius world.
That type of art.
Or an impressionist, or pointillist, maybe.
But the idea is
that that may be pure art,
but it's not necessarily
good art. It's simply the most
original art.
I'm not trying to sell it
to anybody. I'm just
saying that in terms of, well, you could
probably get paid for it.
No, I'm just saying, Wankers for Bob
absolutely supports wanking in every shape
and form. One of the discussions
that Wankers for Bob have had is,
why do the saucers keep not showing up?
And someone proposed
that maybe the problem was
we weren't letting off the right energy.
And it's been suggested that
I understand that
you don't always have time
to get it on with another
fellow Yeti.
But you can always get it on
with yourself.
You can take a few minutes and
run into the bathroom on your coffee
break at work, or you can
do it while you're driving down the road.
It'll stop you from falling asleep at the wheel.
How did Bob put it?
Fornicate as if your very life
depends upon it, even if you
have to do it with someone else.
Or somebody else, I should say.
Or something else.
Or something, yeah.
But the point is, is that this
jilling, or jacking, or wanking,
or whatever term you want to use,
if we could encourage
more of this amongst subgeniuses,
I truly believe that
it would send the message.
Those
energies that are released when you
get that point and you reach the top of that hill.
A Ruben Funny name. She doesn't mean
you have to do that right now in front of us.
That's a private thing. You go
somewhere else. So we should all make a point of
reaching out to those people that aren't
doing this enough, and reaching out and
shaking their hand, after
washing it, and making sure that they join
us in this self-satisfaction.
This great circle of
jerks, or subgeniuses,
as we prefer to be called. Right. And jerkettes.
Yes, and I'm amazed
that, you know, that there's
some of you boys seem to think
that us
uberfans don't do that, and
God, you're stupid.
I mean...
Only because they revere you,
you see. I revere
myself quite a bit. But, as my
father said, there's such a thing
as too much. He didn't say how
much. When I was about twelve,
Pappy, the great Pappy,
he said to me,
Ivan, I'm sure you probably
do that thing that
all boys do.
And I kind of sheepishly went,
well, we never
know. I didn't throw in
eight times a day.
But he said,
just
don't do it too
much.
As if he had some experience with that.
But I never was told
what too much was.
And, as I
became a father,
I said to my
daughter when she got of age, I said,
I know that
you're going to be bad
sometimes. I just
didn't think about it in general.
She was a teenager, a fairly normal
teenager. And I said, I know you're going to be
bad. Just try to
use some common sense and
don't be too bad.
And she looked at me sideways,
the same way I probably looked at my dad
when he made that vague warning.
You know, it's like, well, how much
is too bad? How much
is too much? Too much,
we know this much, is
always better than not enough.
Or at least that sounds
good. But sometimes it's
just as bad. The original line was that too much
is always better than not enough, but it's almost
as bad. And our
publicity people suggested we cut
that last half of the sentence because it
didn't appeal to the kids as much.
And if you do too much, there are creams.
Bag balm seems to work in certain cases.
And the first aid
trailer is right over there
if you happen to do it too much.
Well, that's why Dobbs created blisters, so
you know when there's too much.
The other warning I would make
would be don't take the other
half.
If it's given
to you by a subgenius pope,
don't take the other half.
I hate
to leave you people wondering
what I mean by that,
but when the time comes,
I think you'll know.
In the fullness of time, all shall be made apparent.
You'll notice that
the wisdom of Dobbs and his great
sound bites have a
certain ambiguity.
We leave a lot up to the common
sense, or lack of it, of
the subgenius.
We don't have that many
rules where we're going to tell
you exactly how
many
sins of whatever
kind or cans of
root beer you're allowed to drink.
You have to decide
that for yourself.
Exactly. You may be a subgenius, but that doesn't mean
you're not smart enough to figure this out.
The problem is when you're too stupid
to be a subgenius.
You know, and that's what kills me.
I mean, here we are. Let's face it.
I mean, it's not Church of the Genius, it's Church of the Subgenius.
It took me 45 minutes
just to set up a backup
recording deal and to be able to get
the music running on here, and that was with the
help of four other subgeniuses.
And yet,
if it was Pink's, it would have taken
five times as long and fifty
times more of them, and they still
never would have gotten it right. And they would have
charged you for it.
Yeah, they charged twice as much.
It's irony sometimes,
I think, of what drives a person
to become an idol,
to realize their unsubgenius.
It's an evolving church
for the evolving being.
It's not so much what's said in the Church
of the Subgenius, but that which is unsaid.
What you yourself must put in,
the parentheses that are implied.
It's like when you read a comic book. You're looking at
a series of static pictures.
The action in the comic book
occurs between the pictures,
in the gutters between
the panels. All of life
happens when you're not looking.
When you're not paying attention.
It's what's happening between the lines,
or in Dobbs' pictures case, between
the dots. Sleight of hand.
That's how magic works. Real
magic.
Magic without a K.
Sleight of mind. The kind I believe in.
Out of sleight, out of mind?
Yeah.
The other kind is not worth
messing with.
Well, actually, we have many of our pagan brethren
are here, and pagan
subgeniuses, and some of them
are practitioners of magic.
But they go into it
so blithely and
cast spells and so on.
Well, they brag a lot about it, but the funny
thing I've noticed is that
the ones who
talk the most about it seem to
benefit from it the least.
Yeah, well, the more you talk about it, the least you
benefit from it.
The ones who say it the most do it the least.
The sleight of hand job.
Magic right here on this poster.
Why don't you point those out?
You know, a poorly cast spell,
and it will be poor if you don't know what you're doing,
it's going to come back and
continually strike you.
So, why even bother?
Oh, we have visual aids.
Here we go. Can everyone see this diagram?
There is such a thing as magic.
This is the Slack Pyramid.
King Bob's keys to magic.
They were inspired by
Solomon's keys to magic, but his
report is hard to understand.
The first
key to magic, friends,
so simple, get off
your ass. I think we all understand
that's how it starts.
If you're, if you
want a girlfriend,
don't pray for
a girlfriend. Talk
to a girl.
Second one, bust your
ass, which is merely an amplification
of get off your ass.
But, when you get really good at
busting your ass, you learn how to
get others to bust their asses
for you. As you can see
for the first 45 minutes of this
recording, I have not yet mastered
that myself.
More impor- a very important
rule of Bob's rule of magic,
watch or cover
your ass. That can be
taken both ways.
You know, watch out for the conspiracy
sneaking up behind you, and
also, just to do the right thing,
best of us favor, keep your pants
on until the Bob test. A robot must
protect himself, except where it
conflicts with the first or second law.
Red Fox actually taught this one
to Bob. Wash your
ass. More important than
watching, and those of you who
are talking about, hell, I can't get a girlfriend,
I need to talk to a girl,
maybe you ought to wash your ass first.
You'd be amazed,
as I think Pisces has said
before at X-Days,
how much difference a little person
of personal hygiene could make.
I have extra soap.
I do, I bring extra soap
every year.
The slack, the
high point of the pyramid.
If you
need to wash your ass,
talk to me, I collect
throughout the year hotel
soaps and save them, and
I can ensure you that you'll have your own
soap and you can wash your own ass.
Yes, your bombosity will
smell like a Motel 6.
Actually, I have a word to add
to, just as a general announcement
to folks, they like you to use
Dr. Bronner's soap here,
and they supply it at the shower house,
so avail yourself
from the free dispensers
in the shower house. You'll also enjoy
reading the bottle. Not only do you get this excellent soap, but you get
some of the best reading material
outside of the book of the subgenius.
It's almost like the book of the
subgenius, as you read the outside of
this incredibly
highly lettered soap bottle.
Okay, okay, slack, slack.
In fact, certain key
subgenius, uh,
well, not doctrine, but ways of stating
it were lifted directly
from Dr. Bronner's
essays on his soap
bottles. Now, once again. I'm sure most of you are familiar
with these, and if you're not,
hide thee up to that shower house
now and read them.
And while you're at it, take a
refreshing shower.
Please. But, uh, you know,
we do not so much steal,
as synthesize this material
which we get from all
points of the compass. Because
we don't present it as our own,
but we mix it up with a lot of stuff.
And that's what makes it our own.
It's a little bit like the mama bird
who chews up the worm
and then spits it back out again
for the baby birds. Because those
little conspiracy, uh, chicks
have not yet developed a
horny beak to
slash through their fodder.
It is this tendency to assimilate
that makes it impossible, it makes it
virtually impossible, to resist
Bob, for resistance
is futile. Well, Bob's
power is like the warmth of the sun
rather than the blowing
of the wind. Bob beams
and radiates and ultimately
must be accepted and cannot be
avoided. But at the same time,
does Bob also, not unlike
the sun, burn
and scorch? And then there are those
troublesome sunspots. He will burn
away all that which will not
be assimilated. He will
burn everything down to the quick
and what's left will be pure.
Will he burn you, my
friend? Well,
some people would say, hey, he burned
me the day I spent thirty dollars.
And of course... They lack vision.
The day that X-Day
does arrive, it might be this, uh,
7 a.m., uh,
July 5th, it might be
tomorrow! It might be in five minutes.
Now, wouldn't that be...
That'd throw everything out of order. Now, there is this little problem.
Of, uh, panicking
when you see your fellow
subgeniuses and yourself
suddenly burst, screaming
into flames.
Don't worry, you're simply
casting off the old shell.
That's right. You'll gain a new body
or at least a brain in a
tank aboard the escape saucers.
It will seem like your own panic.
Your dreams come true.
And, uh, so
it's like casting off
an old shoe. So if you find yourself...
You don't need that body anymore. You're gonna have
a new, improved version
of everything. So if you find yourself reaching a
high temperature in the upward, uh,
area of 1300 degrees Fahrenheit,
uh, and your, uh, skin,
uh, burning off into ashes,
do not panic. This is completely normal.
It's
not necessarily going to be a
cakewalk, a walk in the park.
It might hurt. So what? Boo-hoo-hoo.
It's worth it for
transitioning to your
new and better
existence.
Right. I don't like haircuts, but I get one
every 15 or 20 years.
Post Office Box
181-417
Cleveland Heights, Ohio
subgenius.com
But, you know, he can
work his way up at the 7-Eleven.