This is not a rerun.
You can tell because this episode will have way more girl voices than usual.
Bob, would you help me please?
Bob!
Bob, what do you mean Bob?
The thing wasn't weird.
Well, you pulled it too hard.
Well, it's a good thing I don't believe in ghosts.
Neither do I, but let's get out of here anyway.
Bob, who attended a party in the country last night and on the way home, took a detour.
Most of us on waking in the morning know exactly where we are.
The rooster or the alarm clock brings us out of sleep into the familiar sights,
sound,
aromas of home and the comfort of a routine day ahead.
Not so with our young friends.
This will be a day like none they've ever spent.
And they'll spend it in the
Self-Genius Power Rolls
Work.
Is this a test?
They're trying to find out how much of this we can take before we turn into blabbering idiots?
Honey, look at this.
This is bound to be an explanation.
What?
Grass.
Come on.
Grass?
Just calm down.
Here.
Grass?
Come on, get up now.
Come on.
Oh.
Well, I knew you were swacked, but really.
Oh, boy.
I didn't have that much.
Oh.
Hoo-hoo.
Where are we, Bob?
Where are we?
Where'd everybody go?
There isn't anybody.
Just us.
Oh, come on.
There isn't a person or a thing alive in this town.
And yet?
What?
We're being watched.
No.
Now you're getting delusions.
Nothing in this town is real.
The house we slept in.
His child was gone.
we can't find.
That squirrel
stuffed with sawdust.
Show me one thing
that's real.
Bob is real.
That's where they must be.
They're in church.
Maybe they're praying.
Was that a delusion?
Here's the church.
There's the steeple.
Open the door.
Open.
Is this some kind of a joke?
Church?
I don't get it.
Bob, where are we?
I had hoped we were in
the self-genius
power of
the squad.
Well, we're not.
I don't know what it is.
A trick, a joke.
I don't get it.
Nothing moving.
Nothing real.
How did we get back there?
Why?
Well, this...
This isn't grass.
This is a...
It's a prop.
Maybe we're dead, Bob.
Maybe this place is hell.
Did you ever hear of a railroad in hell?
Huh.
What a nutty little tongue.
And how.
I still wonder how we got there.
Well, somewhere along the line,
your drinks caught up with you.
And you got lost.
And we ended up here in
Centerville.
I suppose it's the kind of screwball thing that I would do.
How do you put up with me?
I don't know.
I guess I just have a weakness for screwballs.
Well, you certainly have a good one.
Well, well.
No.
Well, uh...
Maybe it's not the same Centerville.
Centerville.
A real nice place to raise your kids up.
It's really neat.
Churches.
Churches!
And liquor stores!
Yes!
Be careful with your pets, dear. Daddy brought them all away from Earth.
Oh, can I play with them, Mommy?
After lunch, dear. Right now, put them back.
Oh.
Go on.
The moral of what you've just seen is clear.
If you drink, don't drive.
And if your wife has had a couple, she shouldn't drive either.
You might both just wake up with a whale of a headache in a deserted village.
The Self-Genius Power of Self.
Bob, please don't try to find out anything more.
Let's just keep going.
Well, I used to be a sinner, cause I truly did believe
That the Virgin Mary, Jesus, and me were together
And I used to give my daughter televangelistic nods
But then the light, it showed me that I was wrong
And I found J.R. Bob Dobbs
And now my wallet belongs to Bob
Yes, my wallet belongs to Bob
Well, my heart is for my honey
And my brain is for my job
But my wallet belongs to Bob
And my wallet belongs to Bob
And I was just saying
Well, Bobby goes to profit
Every day of my life
And I'm just saying
Every chance that he can get
He can outperform the biggest
Without even breaking sweat
So I gave him all my money
Reverend thanks that it was right
And for only twenty dollars
He just saved my soul tonight
And now my wallet belongs to Bob
Yes, my wallet belongs to Bob
No more can the conspiracy
My lonely wages rob
And my wallet belongs to Bob
Well, Bobby's got a sweetie
And Connie is her name
And her ways could put the sacred whore of Babylon to shame
She reaches in Bob's pocket
Feels around for something hard
Then pulls her hand out holding on to his mighty credit card
And now my wallet belongs to Bob
And my wallet belongs to Bob
Yes, my wallet belongs to Bob
And I never have to fear
Cause I know Connie's on the job
And my wallet belongs to Bob
Well, you may have your lady
And your horny green man too
Their existential energy may be what's right for you
But someday you'll grow weary of those paganistic cunts
And give away your money to the one that gets results
And then your wallet will be for Bob
Yes, your wallet will be for Bob
And you will be subgenius
Not another stupid slob
And your wallet will be for Bob
Well, I believe I am much calmer
Got the bleeding head of Arnold Palmer
Sitting on the dashboard of my car
Praise Bob!
My wallet belongs to Bob
Friends, by the, as of last night, late Reverend Melodious Chops
Late to us, early to board the saucers
It was sudden and not fully expected
You know, if you live long enough
Watching your contemporaries drop like flies
is enough to make you want to drop acid and become like the fly, the Jeff Goldblum version.
Princess Wee and I are pushing 70, and it seems like some old friends and some not that old
dies every month or week.
Rock stars and billionaires younger than me are kicking the bucket right and left.
I'm not surprised.
I've watched my parents and my mother-in-law go through that period
where your friends vanish into the saucers or heaven or the crematorium or wherever
until they're the only one left.
Bummer, man.
Bob predicted it, and he was spot on.
He said, it's going to be a bummer, man.
Quote, unquote, it's going to be a bummer, man.
Boy, was he ever right.
All this is building up to this episode's obituary.
Because after a short struggle with everything imaginable,
Sister Melodious Chops boarded the saucers.
She was known in subgenius world for several clever and well-recorded songs about Bob and Connie,
but she did a whole lot more than that as Victoria Ganger and Revelry.
My wife, Princess Wee, was one of the other two singers in that folk trio,
Four.
For 30 years, along with our friend, M.A., who is okay.
The songs were almost all originals by Vicky.
Vicky Ganger, like so many of these artistic types, was a complex person.
I mean, she could be a bit of a challenge to get along with.
She was mercilessly sharp-eyed and a razor-tongued,
critic and a control freak.
And she partied pretty hard.
You know all that stuff Mom tells you not to do?
She did all that.
She was also one of the most talented, funny people I ever knew.
And Princess Wee and I are sure going to miss her.
So tonight, we'll be hearing the Bob works of Sister Melodious Chops,
also known as Vicky Ganger,
and also some non-Bob songs.
So,
let's now hear her classic,
The Marriage of Bob and Connie.
The Marriage of Bob and Connie
by Bob and Connie
In the world of mating,
in the world of mating habits,
I have seen it all the more.
I see the 98-year-old couple lock their walkers right on this floor.
I've seen communal carnal relations nearly turn into a mob.
But for a truly unique sensation,
you get to turn to Connie and Bob.
Oh,
it's the miracle of the 90s,
it's the talk of all the abyss,
it's the manhood of the 90s,
it's the marriage of Bob and Connie,
in the church of subgenius.
I've seen the mating of the iguana,
on the rocks is what they prefer.
While the sloths just like to hang around,
hoping something will occur.
And though the rabbit is most unsteady,
he is always ready once more.
But when it comes to Bob and Connie,
there's no way of keeping score.
Oh,
it's the miracle of the 90s,
it's the talk of all the abyss,
it's the marriage of Bob and Connie,
in the church of subgenius.
La la la la la la.
Ay!
A dragon's lie has balance,
a black widow has panache,
but Bob and Connie got their hands
on each other's personal stash.
An anaconda has got constriction,
and a crocodile has her grin,
but Bob and Connie are the one true origin of sin.
Oh,
it's the miracle of the 90s,
it's the talk of all the abyss,
it's the marriage of Bob and Connie,
in the church of subgenius.
La la la la la la.
Ay!
An anaconda has balance,
a black widow has constriction,
but Bob and Connie has a grin,
and a crocodile has a stature.
Oh,
La la la la la la.
Ay!
la la la la dear Bob.
La la la la la.
Ay!
La la la la la la.
La la la la la la dear Bob.
Brown-eyed Bob!
The ostrich do it in circles,
with her head stuck in de ground,
while the lemmings like to get it done
with lots of folk around.
So many combinations!
The results are always
is the same
You're prepared to get it on
In Bob and Connie's name
Oh
It's the
miracle of the 90s
It's the talk of all the
of this It's the marriage
of Bob and Connie
In the churches of
GDL
It's the miracle of the 90s
It's the talk of all the
of this It's the marriage
of Bob and Connie
In the churches of GDL
It's the miracle of the 90s
It's the talk of all the
of this
Don't just
live it in the hell
It's the miracle
of the 90s
It's the talk of all
of this
Don't just live it in the
church of GDL
La la la la
Oh
And Connie
I'm sorry
La la la la la la
And Connie
La
Bob made his radio debut on the new DVD Bob the Ultimate Collection.
Bob made his debut on radio.
For more information about Bob, please visit bob.com.
Bob on the radio.
It's a Bob show.
How do you do ladies and gentlemen, this is Bob.
Thank you Bob.
Say Connie, you get around quite a bit don't you?
I'm going to ball girls.
Yes Bob, girls cunt.
So many plugs in there, Tommy.
Bob, one more cuck like that.
Did they ball girls too?
Yeah, I had a lot of fun.
Isn't that wonderful guys?
Butch.
Bob, you're a good boy.
I'm a good boy.
Philo, you're a genius in a moronic sort of way.
Say, where's Philo?
He's in the back room listening to gang bangsters.
Gang bangsters.
Get that Philo.
Hello.
Shut up.
Down Philo.
Say Connie, why are there three girls going around and around without stopping?
Look Bob.
What?
There's a woman.
Let's go right over there.
Let's ball girls Connie.
Okay Bob, but leave the nipples.
That like what?
Quiet Philo.
Bob.
Yeah, well I'll buy the tickets.
I got the right tickets.
No, no, no Bob.
Bob, I'll get them.
I've got some money.
Yeah, what have we got for 20 cents?
Bob, what?
That woman.
Say Connie, who's that blonde down her face?
Who is that?
Oh, that's the brunette who taught me how to move my lips.
A little torture on a loose lip.
Yeah, sing the torture song Philo.
Well, that song's here again, but this time we get Bob's own version of it.
My yellow mommy.
A woke up son in one.
Oh, Bob.
Yeah.
Couldn't find my soul.
When I woke up Sunday morning.
Well my toilet seat was freezing.
And my bagel didn't have no hole in it.
I went down to the river.
I didn't have any money.
I saw Bob say goodbye
I went by the river
A pipe clashed between his molars
And a twinkle in his eye
I said, Bob, you're coming
Bob, you're coming
BOB, YOU'RE COMING…!
You said I can give salvation
And I can show you a real good time
I said, won't you set your card in
So you're just a friend of mine for tonight
Well, that's all
I said, won't you set your card in
Well, she plays them and she finds them
She don't stack the deck no more
You better save your contribution
Or she'll kick your bling
And head right out the door
I said, I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming
I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming
I'm coming to you
Come inside my room
Come inside your room
Where you're off, every Hph
Lose yourenen
Then you can get your ticks
Pulling your awnings
There's no turning back
All of your fucking life
So stop the beating
Say it's opposite to law
Say it's opposite to discourse
Cause it ain't no use in denying
She's the one that gives you the slack
One more time
Bobby Connie
Oh, so right
If you want to go to marriage
Well, then you've got to tie the knot
Well, you've got to tie the knot
Well, are you in or out of the program?
Are you on or off?
On or off?
O.K.
One, two three
This is my life
Aw, you can't believe it
with the ladies.
You got fools.
You should see them.
Mine are bigger.
Penetrate my body.
Gentlemen, I drink.
Not polite cocktails.
I mean, I drink.
Connie said she was gonna ream us
with 20-inch cattle prods
and I'm still waiting.
Mom, you can play with your pecker
for all I care,
just as long as you don't do it
in my control room.
Dismissed.
But then why?
Because Bob is inside each one of us.
Bob and Connie really enjoy life.
That band,
Victoria, Ganger, and Revelry,
well, to me, that was Vicky and M.A.
and Princess Wee.
They played out a lot.
They were regulars at the legendary
and beautifully named Cleveland Bar,
The Barking Spider,
and subgenius devivals
at the Beachland Ballroom
and lots of other places,
but their real audience
was the folks at pagan festivals,
especially Starwood and Winterstar,
of which she was one of the first organizers.
Now, some of you subgeniuses
might be all like,
ooh, pagan festivals,
all those New Age love burgers.
How can you stand it, Stag?
Well, let me tell you a thing or two
about pagans,
the ones up north anyway.
They know how to party.
And what you may have heard
about the temperature of a witch's breast,
that's not true.
I can't speak for gravediggers' butts,
but I mean, they probably are pretty cold.
Only about half of the pagans
are humorless, fundamentalist New Agers.
The other half are mischievous weirdos
who love to tick off the fundy pagans,
which is why I, the mascot skeptic,
was hired for almost every festival
until I married the Starwood Festival
and the former Princess Wee,
after which I worked for free, mostly.
Anyway, being married to one of Vicki's
trio, I saw many, many revelry performances indeed.
And another thing I'll tell you
is that Vicki Ganger was funny.
Her onstage banter between songs was really fun.
And what I'll play next was recorded live at Starwood,
the song Tool Time,
a very funny and naughty song
about sex and magic.
Basically, it's about doing,
doing a ritual to get the perfect boyfriend
with a great big tool set, let's say.
See if you can recognize all the male gods
she rattles off in this.
One dark and stormy night
I thought I'd do me some magic
And work me a spell that was cool
Not to be a fool, not to be a fool
Not to summon up a pixie
Or think something tragic
Just get me a magical tool
I had cups and wands and cauldrons
Even an altar with daddies carved out of stone
But I was feeling all frustrated
Cause I was lacking a magical tool of my own
One with the heart of a god
And the mind of a druid
And built like the bull of Queen Maeve too
But I spent too much time
In the arms of Bacchus
So I'll probably settle for you
Be careful what you wish for
Now that's a lesson
And I've tried a long time to learn
So I knew that it was risky
But I was frisky
And I had some power to burn
So I did some meditating
And gazed at some crystals
And splashed in my vision
And I was in a visionary pool
I threw caution to the winds
And then I started to spin
And called for a magical tool
That had the heart of a god
Oh please don't make him dizzy
Built like the bull of Queen Maeve too
But Osiris is unwilling
And Odin's busy
So I'll probably settle for you
With my higher power
Yo yo can you hear me
I'm praying with all of my might
For the planets to align
With every magic sign
And you'll bring my tool here tonight
Now I know you don't like whining
So here's some candy
And maybe I'll pour you a beer
And if it's not too much trouble
It would be handy
If you'd manifest him right here
And with the heart of a god
And the mind of a druid
And built like the bull of Queen Maeve too
But Cthulhu is outrageous
And Krishna's contagious
So I'll probably settle for you
And up and down and in and out
Cause that's what magic's all about
I really want me a magical tool
And round and round and round we go
With me above and you below
I really need me a magic tool
That has the heart of a god
And the mind of a druid
And built like the bull of Queen Maeve too
But Poseidon is suspicious
Thor can be vicious
So I'll probably settle for you
Dearest higher power
Now don't you tease me
I'm not asking much of you here
Just to sing your song
My name's not a single magic tool
That will try to please me
And help me to be of good cheer
I have practiced long and hard
So you will reward me
The way that you know that you should
And I swear I won't abuse him
I'll never lose him
And I'll only use him for good
Give him the heart of a god
Oh, please don't make him lazy
And built like the bull of Queen Maeve too
But Apollo's such a player
And a god like me
And Loki's crazy, so I'll probably settle for you.
I want some magic, I want some magic.
I want some magical tool.
Oh, I want some magic, I want some magic.
I want some magic.
I want some magic, I want some magical tools
I want some magic, I want some magic
I want some magical tools
I don't want to be depressed
I demand the best
So I'll probably settle for you
Do you?
It's all her fault. Don't blame us.
For some reason, people my age are referred to as boom operators or something like that.
Many of us had love-hate relationships with computers and the internet when those things hit the home and office.
Not me, I had love only.
was more of a typical early computer user. On her day job, she was a professional freelance
copywriter, someone who writes ads. So she had to learn the new technology, and this resulted in a
whimsical song called Comp U Blues, probably from the early 90s. Later, however, after computing
moved from desktops in the home to phones on the subway, she wrote a still funny but also somewhat
darker song, Technologized, which addressed the weird isolation in a crowd brought on by smartphones.
Now, I'll play the lighter, earlier, more innocent type song first.
? Blues news,!. spies!
Must 그렇게 alles onde você come seguir?
Well, everybody got one, I wanted one too For many things, and then there was theおお
My very own computer, all brand new, of my very own computer, all brand new
? I was dreaming! ? I was dreaming!
A multi-task dream, irradiumanknight Boulder
Making other things I could do, doing other things I could do
on the screen. I read articles, surveys, and asked by the score. Then I screwed up my courage and I
went to the store. It was homeless. I wish I was dead. I called to the salesman and here's what I
said. Gigabyte, megabyte, ram, ram. Gigabyte, megabyte, ram, ram. There's too much to see.
I can't possibly choose. I got the drag and drop screen, save a Pentium Blues. I got the blues,
blues, blues, Pentium Blues. I took my baby home from the computer store.
She sat on the couch about a week or two more. It was a monster. A sight to behold, about 15 tons,
and it cost a load. Then late one night, I gave in to the call. Put it together,
plugged it into the wall. I might just get sat. Looking so pretty, then it blew every fuse in the
goddamn city. Gigabyte, megabyte, ram, ram. Gigabyte, megabyte, ram, ram. Everything I save,
I eventually use. I got the drag and drop screen, save a Pentium Blues. I got the blues, blues,
blues, Pentium Blues. Blues, blues, Pentium Blues. Blues, blues, Pentium Blues. Blues,
blues, Pentium Blues.
I got books to peruse. I got articles to read. I got everything I could possibly need. I'm not stupid,
but I'm telling you, to figure it out, I need a higher IQ. What's a Windows? A manager? And what
is a PIF? I think my mouse just died. His tail is getting stiff. The application, I wanted today.
I double clicked twice and it went away.
Gigabyte, megabyte, ram, ram. Gigabyte, megabyte, ram, ram. Everything I save, I eventually use.
I got the drag and drop screen, save a Pentium Blues. I got the blues, blues, blues, Pentium
& stable-play-boost, pentium-balse. I need your disciples fond of Jebus blues,
my mentor's shoes, Mic それ以勇者服,
make yourimport takes all. Now, one of the things I wanted to do. Which studio? Let's go!onyata,
I'll be surfing in a minute or two.
Oh, yeah, right.
Caught in the net, been pointing and clicking,
and I ain't there yet.
Still, I managed to find America online.
Got in the chats, and I was doing fine.
I got an upgrade.
It was such a thrill till I got the $123 bill.
Gigabyte, megabyte, ram, ram.
Everything I save, I eventually lose.
I got the drag and drop screen, save up heavy, I'm loose.
Gigabyte, megabyte, ram, ram.
Everything I save, I eventually lose.
I got the drag and drop screen, save up heavy, I'm loose.
First it was 386.
SX.
Then it was 486.
DX.
Then it was 33, 60, 75, 90, 101.
Pentium fun.
I got the Pentium Blues.
Everything I save, I eventually lose.
I got the drag and drop screen, save up Pentium.
Lose.
Two, three, go.
And those technologies, oh.
Everybody's on a cell phone.
Got an iPod in their ear.
Text messaging and pointing cameras.
And nobody's left to hear.
So I got a phone.
Everything is on a charger
Chargers plugged into a wall
Cordless battery convenience
Means no outlets left at all
And I make my way through darkened rooms now
By the light of the LEDs
Oh, those technologies
I've been technologies
Oh no
Those technologies
I've been technologies
Oh no
Got no I.O.
upon the road now got no hands upon the wheel everybody's multitasking like a fool
got a buzzing in the brain now got a ring tone in the ear it's the vacant plugged in look that makes
you cool did she say something oh yeah and a cell phone
seems like every life is running on a tiny little screen everyone is off the wire every place
wonder if this is the future living in a world where no one sees
those technologies oh i've been technologies oh i've been technologies
those technologies
oh
no
everybody's on ourself
can you hear me now
that was victoria ganger and revelry live at starwood festival and i'll never get to see
that band again bummer i have to admit putting the show together has made me weepy
at times we just heard the news of vicky's passing last night and you know how it is it takes a while
to sink in and seem real that's another thing i wish i wasn't getting used to on the other hand
at least i'm still around to get bummed out it beats the alternative as old folks say and say
and say anyway vicky liked to pick apart the little paradoxes and big contradictions of daily life
she was kind of like a hippie pagan irma bombeck actually i guess she was a little more like tom
wearer she came up with clever lyrics that lightened up the things that can ruin your day
so
monday morning and i go to my employment to discover that the fax machine is jammed
that the copier's completely out of paper and the printer cover now needs to be slammed
so i look it up in my employee handbook to find the proper places where i now must go
but when i find the designated person they proceed to shrug and say hell i don't know i'm not sure i'm
everyone's mystified everyone's mystified everyone's mystified and it sure beats the hell out of me
i take my car in cause it's making noises like a cross between a buffalo and cat
some mechanics give professional opinions then conclude that they don't know imagine that
at the store i asked the clerk whatever happened to the service and the products on the shelf
but she shakes her head at me like i am crazy said you'll have to solve that mystery yourself
you're sort of mystified
everyone's mystified
they are so mystified and it still beats the hell out of me
last night i saw a sort of celebration where the druids and the techno heads combined
they dance around a fire in a disco
then they put on these machines to blow it off
and they blow their minds
oh this smile of me with faces so beatific
and the music that they made was so serene
that i couldn't help but think that i was missing
something cosmic in the make up of my jeans
they were so mystified
they were so myst
hadn't a clue
they were so mystified
and it still beats the hell out of me
now if you're on the horns of a dilemma and you haven't got a clue where you should go
you might as well just hang it up completely
oh man
you're gonna make your own solutions as you go
cause there ain't nobody gonna give you answers
nobody's got the means to set you free
and if you're asking for the hidden meaning
why i even wrote this song
don't ask me
you can be mystified
and it'll still beat the hell out of me
everyone's mystified
for sure
so mystified
no clue
and it sure beats the hell
you never can tell
it still beats the hell
out of
me
I don't know how people do that
I should also mention that while I'm playing mostly her funny songs
her CD albums have more sensitive and mystical type songs of love and magic and the moon
and all that nice stuff
but no, I don't really have a clue
but this is a subgenius show.
I wish I could tell you where you could get her recordings,
but you can't.
Maybe look for concert videos on YouTube.
Okay, all right, okay, all right.
Change of pace.
How about some Zappa compositions
performed by the Empire Jazz Orchestra,
conducted by our buddy, Reverend P...
I don't know how to pronounce his subgenius name.
Bill Meckley.
He's a subgenius we got to know
on the mostly online Diaspora Zoom meetings,
and we had him as a house guest last week.
Praise Bob.
And he didn't die of old age during his visit,
despite being almost my age.
In fact, he was rocking out and having fun with us,
within reasons.
We have to be careful how we rock out
if we want to keep rocking.
Now see if you can recognize the songs
in this instrumental medley.
Here we go.
Let's do this thing a bit faster.
guitar solo
applause
Frank Zappa's
Who Are The Brain Police and Holiday
in Berlin performed
by the Empire Jazz
Orchestra. Also
heard in the background.
Too cool.
Thank you Empire Jazz Orchestra
and our pal Reverend Billy
for more information and worse
see subgenius.com
I'm going to let our departed
pal Victoria Ganger end the
show with her crowd favorite at the
Pagan Festivals because it's
about the Pagan Festivals and a certain
type of person one meets at
those. Pagan Fest
Barbie by Victoria
Ganger and Revelry.
Most of you
probably won't cry like I did.
Pagan Festivals
You came to my festival
all pretty and pink
You brought your own
mirror and your dream
house and your sink
I tried to resist
falling under your
spell but when I
saw you Barbie
spiritual
spirituality went
to hell
doo doo-doo-do
Whoo Bree-doo
Whoa
Any
Deeds
Whoa
Bye.
Dip, dip, dip, dip.
Whoa.
Oh, Pagan Fest Barbie.
You walk on your toes.
Must be the heel.
Your nails are all polished.
A gem in your nose.
Genuine pearl.
I see true magic when I look at you.
Pagan Fest Barbie, I love you.
Never dresses in leather.
Leather of feathers or fur.
Politically perfect.
You're polyester.
Pagan angel.
That's her.
She's polyamorous.
With anyone.
True.
But Pagan Fest Barbie, I love you.
You came and you danced by the firelight.
With your sweet smile fixed on your face.
It's so plastic.
And you're so pretty.
And all of the gods of the day and the night.
No, no one can ever take your place.
You're unique, Barb.
A starry blue running deer.
Deep crystal in flame.
Wait, there's more.
Yeah, you love Jim McKenzie.
Well, that is her legal name.
I hate to admit it.
But what can I do?
Pagan Fest Barbie, I love you.
She likes to take showers.
Anytime, anywhere.
On and off.
She may stay there for hours.
With her razor and her nails.
Water's gone.
You can talk conservation.
And she won't have a clue.
Pagan Fest Barbie, I love you.
You came and you stole my heart away.
Take it, baby.
With your sweet smile.
Yeah.
You have my big style.
And your charm.
And you put a spell on me.
And if we should do the great and right tonight.
I know.
It'll do me no harm.
And it harm none.
Oh, Pagan Fest Barbie, you are the best.
Good for me.
By each god and goddess.
You're triple blessed.
Blessed by me.
So you get your hair done.
I'll get it done.
Tattoo.
Pagan Fest Barbie, I love you.
Whoop dee doo.
Whoah.
Doop dee doo.