Uh, yes, dear friends, this is Hour of Slack number 888.
An auspiciously named show, don't you agree?
So auspicious that I'm going to celebrate and slack off by rerunning a show from WREK Atlanta.
Bob's Slacktime Funhouse with the Lymphnode Institute.
In this case, their wonderful, salacious springtime sex.
Spectacular.
I really enjoyed pre-screening it.
I patted it down real good.
And, well, their choice of music is perfect.
And their in-between banter dada is even better.
So, now.
Mommy, I want to ask you something.
What is it, dear?
What I wonder is, how did the baby get started in this?
Let me tell you how it is.
There's a special opening just in front of the place where you have your BM.
It's very, very tiny in a little girl, but as you grow, it grows too, right along with the rest of you.
Until when you're grown up, it gets to be just about this size.
The special opening that little girls have.
The special opening that little girls have has a name, the penis.
Now, you know that little boys like our Johnny have a vagina.
When a boy grows up and is ready to be a father, he is able to put his vagina into the penis.
That special opening that mothers have.
Do you understand?
Yes, I think so.
But if I forget it, you can always tell me again.
You're listening to Bob's Slacktime Funhouse.
Whee!
The Lymphnode Institute Edition.
Edition.
Black Time Funhouse.
The Lymphnode Institute Edition.
Presents.
Our salacious spring sex spectacular.
What?
Accidents happen.
Accidents do happen.
And on the subject of sex, that's how babies are made.
Babies are made with accidents.
Mm-hmm.
Often.
I spilled my seed.
I blasted my photon torpedo into her nebula.
Yeah, so in the 70s, they stopped being so puritanical about sex and did a lot of blow and got kind of naked dancing.
The pill.
Yeah, the pill facilitated that.
And then AIDS came in.
And it shut it down.
Your mother was a whore in the 70s.
Wow.
Really?
I don't know your mother.
It's just a general statement.
Casual sex, though.
Isn't that like, isn't all sex pretty much casual?
Unless you're Catholic.
I guess casual sex really just means...
Don't want to know your name.
Exactly.
Just give me the hole or the rod or whatever it is you're after.
Hey, you look like the gender I prefer.
Come on back.
Exactly.
If you multiple times you're always cartoons.
Too fucking exaggerated.
You know, I love her.
You love her.
I miss her.
One, two, three
By the duty of a Nick Roy
Don't
Come spread your tail on me
Wild wonder of a midnight
Forrest
Toss down your glossy
Wham
She's got me by the level
Sticking it out, sticking it out
Insinuating leather
I think she broke my terror
Come on, come on
Keep on coming on now
The ladies on the television, I know they like sex
And if I just buy the product they associate with
You'll have sex
Apparently
With them or a woman much like them
Much like these beers you should be drinking
Hi there, what can I get you?
I would really like a water right about now
Oh, are you sure you would like a refreshing adult beverage?
Well, you've piqued my curiosity with your challenge to my order
What would you suggest?
How about a vertical smile beer?
Vertical smile beer?
Mmm, yes
A cold vertical smile beer
Yes
Satisfies when I'm hot
Yeah?
Oh yeah
And after two or three I begin to lose my inhibitions
Wow
Mmm
I love it when vertical smile hits the back of my throat
I'm overcome
I'll drink it all
Uh
A cold refreshing vertical smile satisfies me deep inside
You want one?
Are you implying that vertical smile will allow me to have sex with you and by extension all women?
Mmm
Are you getting thirsty for vertical smile?
You're really hot
So?
Do you want it?
I've lost my capacity for rational thought
I want it
You, I...
I want...
Smile, sex, beer
You got it, sure
Vertical smile, raise one to your lips
Meanwhile, at a popular bar
What can I get you, buddy?
I don't know
Something bothering you, pal?
Yeah, my girlfriend dumped me
Mmm
Now that's a shame
Say, friend
How'd you like to have two chicks at the same time?
What?
That's right, two chicks at the same time
The new adult beverage from the makers of Vertical Smile
What?
Vertical Smile, you say?
Well...
Here, chum
On the house
Aw, gee, thanks
Wow
It tastes like a hot redhead with big...
And a hot blonde with even bigger...
While I take her from...
All over those huge...
Like a...
Fire hose
Sure does, partner
You see, the brewers of two chicks at the same time
Use only the finest hops and barley
Cold, double-filtered
And aged in real oak barrels
For that hot girl-on-girl flavor
You can only get one other way
How likely is that?
Uh...
Not very?
Damn right
A guy like you?
Hey, I don't...
And the new wide-mouth bottle
Allows more of that adolescent fantasy-drenched flavor
To flow right into your insatiable face
Right, buckaroo?
Well, I...
You bet
Get out of your plain, ordinary beer
And get into two chicks at the same time
Can I take this bottle home?
Sure thing, amigo
You've earned it
So you see, Mr. Bungle
Film's spunging up your whole campaign
He's totally incompetent
Sleeper X commercials will be laughed off of television
If you approve his campaign
Well, that's very interesting
I never thought too much of film, now that you mention it
And I'm starting to think that's a good thing
I'm starting my own agency, Mr. Bungle
I could do a hundred percent better job than that turkey
I'll bet you could
What you say is very interesting
In fact, you are very interesting
Oh, Mr. Bungle, I didn't know you were interested
And you will give me your account for my new agency?
Later
We'll talk business later
Right now I want to make a love to a beautiful
Beautiful body
I heard everybody get a set host ding-dong
Grab an egg while I run my walk
Don't let my sister see you dip in my pong
Give me a kiss, I'm an average French
And I'll tell you about the good, the good, the smart, and the less
Keep blowing my gong, cause here I come
Gonna get you all the secrets of my boy, yeah
Yeah
Nick-Nock Party Watch
I'll give you a dog a bone, baby
I'm a man, I'm a queen
Just a little friend, friend
With a fork and a spoon
I'm a friend of mine
I'll give you a friend, friend
And my phone alone
And a bob and a face
With a fork and a spoon
I got yogurt meat, loaves, middle of my ass
Smoked in the interbars and a gift of the gas
Top of cream from the steaks and the Levi's cheese
Turn the boss's seat with a ring of beans
I'll give you a dog a bone, baby
Just a little friend, friend
I'm a zoo skaboos
Gonna give her a boost
Like a chicken project
Super goop, poop, goop, loop, loop
Cheeky goop, shorty boop
Drop the floor, low, broke the groin
Top of the hippie jeans, please, please
Do a skimpy, please
Woah!
Nick-Nock Party Watch
I'll give you a dog a bone, baby
Woah!
I'll rip off your...
Your... your... your muscles
Your muscles
Aw, yeah!
Fführ одной funded beer
Fearless waves, look forward
Like you're gonna head all the pa deployed
And fuck your hoes
Its a long road
Searching the
Obstruction
Like aebe
We'll be right back.
and then you have a really big sneeze
and the mucus goes all over the back of the girl's head.
It's a little like that.
At the same time, a spurt of quite thick, sticky stuff
comes from the end of the man's penis.
And this goes into the woman's vagina.
Or whatever.
Well, believe it or not,
this sticky stuff is how you and I all started.
It's called semen.
And in the semen are sperm.
And they make babies. The end.
And that's why your mother's a slut.
The End
I'm calling you
One, two, three
By the beauty of the necronom
Come spread your tail on me
For a wonder of a midnight forest
Toss down your glossy web
She's got me by the leather
Sticking it out, sticking it out
In simulated leather
I think she broke my tether
Come on now, come on now
Keep on coming on now
And that brings us to your mother.
I'll tell you about my mother.
That zish, swilling whore.
Oh my.
Your mom talks like a bitch at least once.
Almost guaranteed.
Your mom and dad, I know you don't want to think about it,
but think about it.
They fop, nek-hop, nek-hop
like there's no tomorrow.
The happiest day of their lives
was when, when you left the house
so they could fop anywhere they wanted to.
Your parents are ingy-hop in your bed right now.
And their wife's swapping too, man.
Your dad's flying on wits and cuffs his mom.
And she's zis-flying on wits and cuffs dad.
Don't put me on, cause I'm on fire
And I can't quench my desire
Don't you know that I'm burning up for your love
You ain't convinced that dad is enough
I put myself in this position
And I presume he in position
But you know I'm alive
And there's something in my heart
It won't die
I'm burning up
Ooh, you're always closing the door
But that only makes me want you more
Day and night I hope for your love
You're unconfirmed that dad is enough
To justify my wanting you
Tell me what you want me to do
I'm not lying, and I know
That you don't want to want me
But you can't let go
I'm burning up
You're a super-elmo-mese
But you know that's not a word you please
But like me, you're a super-elmo-mese
But you know there's nothing way to thank
I hate to say it, but I'm on fire
I'm burning up
I want my gold
When you want to see me
Care all my needs
When you don't
The back is down
When you please
I'd like to hear
This after any day
I ain't the same
See I got no shame
I'm on fire
I'm burning up
Fire
You'll notice that
we haven't made really
any mention of homosexuality.
So for the
purposes of our
homosexual listeners
man means top
and woman means bottom.
You know what's funny?
Is you can
sexualize anything
if you focus
on one thing
like Peggy Hill's
big sexy feet.
She's a cartoon character.
Yes she is.
That would be a fetish as well.
Oh yeah.
Cartoon characters.
Ask the Japanese
all about fetishizing.
Is that even a word?
It is now
cartoon character.
Lactating lasses.
Lactating lasses
and gob on me knobs.
Gob on me knobs.
Spring is here.
Of course
you know
variety is the
spice of squirt.
But I mean damn
if you spend all your time
in your house
watching videotapes
of whatever it is.
But you gotta go out
and get you some
or you will wind up
trying to draw
a happy face
with pipe bombs
on the map of the United States.
And that's not gonna
get you any
unless you're into
federal prisoners.
But yeah you can
get off on anything.
Golf balls.
Planes flying into buildings.
Ooh now.
I don't know if anybody
popped a chubby on that.
Well.
Not in this country.
With this next song.
Who what?
Is this filking?
Uh friends
and the only thing
sicker
than what the
networks
did
with it
is this
very very
strange
homage
or whatever
by
Chris
Corden.
I put my hand in my pocket.
What do I feel?
110 stories
of concrete and steel.
I like too much.
That plane shaped pole
really gets me high.
But the big ball of fire
is the money shot.
I like too much.
The plane going in.
The plane shooting out.
People dive into the street.
While I play with my meat.
My steel melted and my tower is coming down.
I'll be right back.
You're listening to Cronin.
The New York skyline.
Will never be the same.
But the guys who flew those planes.
Have an amazing aim.
I like too much.
There must have been a reason.
But I don't understand.
Why they hit the pentagon.
Instead of Disneyland.
I like too much.
The plane going in.
The flame shooting out.
It's raining broken glass.
While I sit on my ass.
I like too much.
My steel melted and my tower is coming down.
I almost had enough.
Of watching planes explode.
Until they showed it in reverse.
And I had too much.
I like too much.
Now my hands all sticky.
And I cannot find a rag.
I guess I'll have to use a rag.
The American flag.
I like too much.
The plane going in.
The flame shooting out.
People died into the street.
While I play with my.
My steel melted.
And my tower is coming down.
I like too much.
The somewhere in《Date of the World》
The most famous book about you.
The 같n dinner.
and steamer where you take a poo on someone's
chest. Yes, yes. There's all kinds of
dirty Sanchez. It's the dirty Sanchez.
Which where you smear the
fecal matter covered finger on the
girl's upper lip and give her the Sanchez
mustache.
And then there's where you plug the wrong hole
and she turns around to get mad at you and you deck
her and that's called a donkey punch.
The donkey punch, yes, yes. Not many
repeat customers after the donkey punch.
Well, if you're paying for it, who cares?
Pick a different model next time.
Then you're liable to get...
Pick a different what? I said model, but I didn't
mean that in like a beauty model. I meant that like a
model of car. I thought you said mom.
So who's got the problem now?
A lot of moms,
especially in the spring, because they know
the winter's coming and they need to start hoarding
food for the babies.
Storing semen for the babies.
Oh, we
never not gonna go home.
We won't go, we won't
go, oh, we never not gonna go
phone, cause mother
is
, isn't home. Oh, Sugar
Bush, I love you so.
I
will never let you go.
So don't
you let your mother know.
Sugar
Bush, I love
you so.
Sugar Bush, what
can I do?
Mother's not
so pleased with you.
Promise me
you will be true.
And I'll
come along with you.
Oh, we never not gonna
go home. We won't go,
we won't go, we never not
gonna go phone, cause mother
isn't home.
Sugar Bush, come dance with
me. And
let the other fellas
be. Just
dance the polka
merrily.
Sugar Bush, come
dance with me.
Oh, we never not gonna go
home. We won't go, we
won't go, oh, we never not gonna
go phone, cause mother
isn't home. Oh, chocolate,
you are so sweet.
Yes,
yes, you I'd like to eat.
If
I do, oh, what a treat.
Chocolate,
you are so
sweet. Oh,
Sugar Bush, I love
you so.
And I will never
let you go.
Now don't you let
my mother know.
Sugar Bush,
I love
you so.
Sugar Bush, I love you so.
If your
parents did it in the springtime, which this
is our salacious spring
sex spectacular. If they were doing it in the
early spring, which is the beginning of April, the end of March,
that means the resultant
baby by the bad,
planning committee, would probably
be coming around about late December
or early January.
Which means that's when Jesus' parents knocked
boots. If in fact Jesus' birthday
was in December, which we know it wasn't, so
totally disregard what I just said.
Well, you can't totally disregard that because they
say it's when they say it is now
because they're trying to get all those pagans
involved. Saturnalia, yes.
And the pagans knew how to bust nut.
Oh, did they? Seven day orgy?
That's what Christmas used to be. I know we've discussed
this before, but Christmas used to be a day.
It used to be a seven day orgy.
They could not get the pagans to give up
the nut busting, so they said, well,
you can still bust the nuts, but
you must bust them for Jesus.
Eat of my flesh.
That was in December, so it doesn't fit our
spring sex spectacular.
That's the best time to
have an orgy with a woman in her third
trimester, is during the Saturnalia
orgies. Well, as Sid Barrett said, I'll do
my loving in the winter time.
I think. Because of the third
trimester and the free breast milk.
The old baby kick from the inside.
Normal couple after 35 years of marriage, trying to make
their sex life interesting. Don't be such an
ass face. Come on, all I want to do is get close
to you.
I heard they built this city on rock and roll on the radio
today, and that's our song, and it kind of made me think that
maybe we've gotten old and terrible like Jefferson
Airplane when they became Starship.
I kind of have a headache. Alright, I'm going
to the titty bar.
Oh, we're sitting next to you.
We're sitting next to you.
And I close
my eyes, and I'm
in orgasm
way.
It's a street
around the corner,
it's called orgasm
Baby, I've been working at the termite farm for 40 cycles, Mama.
I gots to have it.
I'm tired.
But if we don't reproduce, we get recycled into food for the cyworm, baby.
You know that!
I just can't, Gary.
Why don't you try the ass mule?
Oh, that gort couldn't get off a bicycle.
How many times has this happened to you?
Looking for love in the mutual exchange of pleasurable juices only to end up squeezing
your essence into the waste chute.
Well, do it the way the free men did it, with roofies.
General Pharmaceuticals.
Brand roofies provide hours of unfettered access to all of your partner's Orify without
that bothersome rigor mortis or embarrassing necrosis.
Let's see how Gary does with a couple of General Pharmaceutical brand roofies.
How's that drink I fixed you, baby?
That's good, baby.
So you want to get to the humping?
Well, all right then.
General Pharmaceutical brand roofies.
Ask for them by name.
General Pharmaceuticals.
Now in new seizure-free formula.
General Pharmaceuticals is a division of Glorp Co.
So you spent a lot of money on your date.
Took her out to a lot of fancy restaurants, hoping to get into her pants.
Springtime rolls around.
She becomes amorous and is interested in the pheromones you've been extruding.
Waft.
They put pheromones in perfume.
They put pheromones in McDonald's hamburgers.
Wait, those are hormones.
Whoop whoop.
Hey, make a hormone.
Put sand in the hamburger.
Oh, a moan in pain, right.
Ugh.
Oh, baby there's something inside me That wants to be inside me
Oh, baby there's something besides me that I just can't resist
Oh, baby there's a soul in me that wants to be inside me
song in my heart
and the words just won't go away
Oh baby there's
so much more that
I pray
for
Oh
Break it
Wait baby there's a chip in my neck
that tells me where
I'm going
little
Oh baby, there's a spring in my step
Cause I'm here, and I'll be with you
Oh baby, don't you know
The words I say just must be true
Oh baby, what I'm trying to say is
I can't spell you out
Why would they do that?
Why wouldn't they just have the dad work for the daughter?
I have no idea
They couldn't get that hedonist, but they'll take a turkey baster and do it?
Well, you know, it's all fun until the inbreeding starts
They said recently there's a study that determined that first cousins could do it in relative safety
Man, I wish I'd known that
I got first cousins all over the place
But no, was I touching them?
No, not on this coast
Hell, I'd move
Metamist, not for her
I'm gonna have you be in this world
Hey, little Miss Snowball
Well, now there's so much you and me can discover
And I think we should start
I think we should start
Wandering through a big plant orgy
A big vegetable gangbang
Stamen
Pistols
Plug the stamen
Plug the pistol
I wonder if plants have fetishes
Just Venus Fly
I don't know
Venus Flytrap from WKRP in Cincinnati
Was a man and not a plant
Yeah, those things aren't really teeth
They feel good
I like those afrocombs
That's my fetish
Afrocombs?
No
Hi, this is Casey Kasem
And welcome young loveers to the show
Please subscribe to our channel
And do what you love
Take advantage of all our posts
Click the little bell
To like our video
Don't leave us
In love
With therefore
Think already
Think
Things
Don't stop doing it!
Sex, sex, sex, sex, sex, sex, sex, sex, dirt isn't that sweet?
Sex, sex, sex, sex, sex, sex, sex, sex, sex, dirt isn't that sweet?
Sex, sex, sex, dirt!
Baby, baby, baby, baby.
Sex, sex, sex, non-stop sex dirt.
Don't stop doing it, don't stop doing it!
Non-stop sex dirt.
non- non- non-stop sex
dur!!
DON'T STOP doin' it!!
DON'T, DON'T, DON'T
STOP ash removing viral behind the scenes
Bape Bape Ba-BAPE
hpdahfldaihhi
dphewbjfks Washington- D-fufeflthard mutcher
misunderstanding
hm pied
C.B. Sage
As you've probably well noticed,
many of the major control outfits of this world
use sex as their primary weapon against you,
making these ridiculous demands of you
to not have sex,
or wait many years between sex,
or only have sex when you want a baby.
That's insanity.
Wait till you're married,
but then these same people,
or the same agents of this organization,
or those organizations,
will assault little boys in confessionaries.
I think that's a valuable lesson
on what happens when you can't get off.
You gotta squirt.
I mean, it's just,
you gotta poop, you gotta pee, you gotta squirt.
That's just how it is, folks.
Yeah, what's the Maslow's hierarchy needs?
You need a treehouse,
and a big red fire engine.
And then something to park your Maserati in,
as Ted Nugent would say.
That's exactly what the Nuge would say.
Yes.
What would the Nuge do?
And the Barbie doll to ride a straddle your big stallion.
Yeah!
From the director, Daddy Digny,
and the production team that brought you
Full Cervix Sting!
and auto-erotic ass fixation
comes a ball-buster of a summer vid feature.
It's Humpbot's Mexican Vacation,
starring J.J. Coolsie as Ghetto Geppetto,
the robot mechanic who keeps Humpbot
equipped with all the latest erotic attachments
designed to make you at least one load lighter.
That's Humpbot's Mexican Vacation,
on paper vid now!
Humpbot's Mexican Vacation
From the makers of Clitorox
The Booty Band-Aid comes
Hydro Lube
Industrial strength lubrication from concentrate.
Just add water and dive on in.
Available in 10-ounce and 20-ounce sizes.
And for those special occasions,
there's even a jumbo-sized economy two-gallon party pack.
Hydro Lube
For when he can't get enough of your love,
babe,
can't get enough of your love, babe.
Oh, babe.
Girl, I don't know how...
But a beauty of an egg boy,
oh,
come spread your glossy,
shallow heart,
for you.
Boy, a wonder of a midnight,
for this
lost town,
your way.
For the devil it상을.
Oh, baby.
Torgue, come out of me.
Ar Victio
Oh, you like that, don't you?
Yeah, take it. Take it.
He's back in the army.
Oh, yeah.
That's the stuff.
Okay, I'm getting my second wind here.
All right.
Damn good for a monkey.
Oh, me like. Me like a lot.
Oh, you can't get love like that back in the States.
Yes!
Cut it out.
Come on.
Cut it.
You've been listening to Bob's Slack Time Funhouse,
the Lentone Institute edition on 91.1 FM,
WRIK Atlanta, the voice of the students of Georgia Tech.
It is now that time.
The Church of the Subgenius has a new P.O. box.
No, it does not.
Yes, it does.
They moved the whole damn thing to Austin.
And I can't tell you what the damn P.O. box is because...
Is that where Jesus is?
Yeah.
They can't forward the address?
They're keeping the box.
In case.
They'd better.
Because the only P.O. box I know is 14030.
406 Dallas, Texas 75214.
Couldn't begin to tell you what the P.O. box in Austin is.
I wrote it on a Post-it note.
I put it in my wallet.
I took it out of my wallet.
I have no idea where it is.
So go to www.subgenius.com if you really need the new Subgenius P.O. box in Austin.
And be sure to visit us online again at www.lymphnodeinstitute.com.
That's L-Y-M-P-H-N-O-D-E.
E-I-N-S-T-I-T-U-T-E.
Another fine Lympnode production.
Contact us at P.O. box 670-541 Marietta, Georgia 30066-0126.
Or www.lymphnodeinstitute.com.
Listen to Bob's Slack Time Funhouse at WREK.org.
91.1 FM WREK Atlanta.
No, we don't talk about Bob a lot.
But we're more of the advanced Subgenius show.
We're entertainment.
We're entertainment for the Yetis.
I'm personally not interested in recruiting another single person.
Since X-Day could basically happen at any second or in a thousand years.
Just don't know.
So, I mean, there's only so many seats in those escape vessels.
And I'm not in the mood to be sitting next to some little Bobby who's, you know, just joined on six months ago.
Waving his card around.
Spewing the goddamn buzzwords.
I don't have time for it.
They won't make the escape vessels.
I don't think it's the card carrying that necessarily.
It dictates you'll get on the ship.
It's the DNA.
Hmm?
Yeah.
If you got it, you got it.
There we go.
It's very, what is that, the Calvinist view?
Calvin and Hobbes?
Those who will be on the escape vessel, their names are already written in the book of the Exist.
So there's no need to really do anything different.
You're either going or you're not.
Well, we're not witnessing.
But I just think that if you can make a couple of close-minded people open up their perception a little bit.
Ah.
Maybe open up those legs a little bit.
Let us get some springtime sex action.
Sex action?
Who sings sex action?
L.A. Guns.
We should play sex action.
Sex action.
Have another tequila, baby.
Just chill out.
That's good.
Sex action.
Oh.
Say that you
Baby knows
Wherever she goes
She's like
Say that you
How's it baby
I got the potion
You're a cool operator
Got the first in the potion
Now we're all alone
Doing all the talking
She's got me on the back
Let her figure through the walls
We can talk about love
Talk about love
Here she comes
Never get enough of her
Sensations
Baby knows
Wherever she goes
She's got
Sensations
Talk about love
Here she comes
Never get enough of her
Sensations
Ask me that
Who's next
They say
Sensations
And it all
Always fails
Some
Girl
Girl she got a star
Boy she got a fleece
She's knocking them dead
She got me down on my knees
Now listen
I'm a sex gun lover
In the heat of the night
Star of a cover
I got you in my sight
Talk about love
And here she comes
But never get another fat
Sensations
The baby knows
Wherever she goes
To be
Sensations
S-E-X
I know whose next door
Sensations
The baby knows
Wherever she goes
T'know what it gets
Sensations!
S-E-X
You've heard the following songs in the following order.
Negative Land with A Special Opening.
Devo performing Buttered Beauties, Part 1.
LNI doing the Vertical Smile ad and the Two Chicks ad.
Mr. Bungle with Squeeze My Macaroni.
Negative Land performing Penis and Sperm.
Devo with Buttered Beauties, Part 2.
Mike Watts covering Madonna's Burnin' Up.
Chris Korda with I Like to Watch.
Doris Day performing Sugar Bush.
LNI with the Normal Couple skit.
Stump performing Orgasm Way.
LNI doing the Roofies ad.
Throbbing Member performing Shantae.
Jimi Hendrix with Little Miss Lover.
Negative Land performing Don't Stop Doin' It.
LNI doing the Humpfbot ad and the Hydro Lube ad.
Again, Devo performing Buttered Beauties, Part 3.
Dr. Bugbladder all on his own with Monkey Madness.
And of course, L.A. Guns with Sex Action.
Now the leading...
I thought that was delicious.
I like the part where the sex happens.
In the springtime, there's nothing I like more than hot.
gooey sucks.