and sex well sex is great but it's always right after sex when the crash comes and things go sour
the petite mort the little death that follows orgasm the dark side of sexual pleasure when
sensation evaporates and leaves you right back where you're at with a lot more empty time in
your hands and there's really no one to talk to no one to go to without embarrassment and besides
what would you say you really aren't sure what it is that's actually bothering you just that
something's always bothering you and that's something changes every day maybe you've got
a job or what I'm not trying to leave the one that has you or maybe you've been to school and
are now out of school floundering or maybe you're still in school and asking yourself
am I doing this for anyway and you're sick of teachers and people who Lord their authority
over you
parents doctor lawyer business big shot and they're empty encouraging be all that you can
be career you can't bear to hear another word of their crap every word of it makes you
sick because deep down you know you can't be anything you choose you know there's only so
many winners and your track record is nothing but failures and besides there's really nothing that
interests you enough to dedicate yourself to be all that you can be that's crap and you know it be what
happened chopsticks
leave
me
if good
걱정
taking
meeting with you
right
symptoms
worthbor машина
Subtle, making shapes that my throat cannot tell.
A friend of mine sent me a tape that's every James Brown scream edited together in one tape.
What you gonna play now?
Bobby?
I don't know.
The Subgenius Hour of Slack.
I believe Reverend Erwin Chusid provided us with that.
Before that, a tiny clip of the incredible string band
and the brand new guitarist,
up front was from Thought Alchemy.
As you may have gathered, this hour of Slack number 1303
is in fact a rerun of the classic episode number 553 from October 1996,
the first half of which was from Chaz Smith's ESO Swamp Radio on WCSB Cleveland,
except for this song by My Life with the Thrill Kill Cult.
The Subgenius Hour of Slack
is a brand new
series of clips.
The Subgenius Hour of Slack
is a rocky road
The Lama is a rocky road
And then it hit me
And it felt like a cheers
The Lama is a rocky road
And then it hit me
And it felt like a cheers
Skin flicks
Lipstick
Baby scribbles in the mirror
Drama overdoses
Night shift
Mind twist
She's got her finger on the trigger
Drama overdoses
Skin flicks
Lipstick
Baby scribbles in the mirror
Drama overdoses
She drinks
For kids
Nasty little bling
The Lama is a rocky road
And then it hit me
And it felt like a cheers
The Lama is a rocky road
And then it hit me
And it felt like a cheers
The Lama is a rocky road
The Labyrinth is a Rocky Road
And then it hit me
And it felt like a kiss
The Labyrinth is a Rocky Road
And then it hit me
And it felt like a kiss
She's got a finger on the trigger
Chicken by Eve has gone off the deep end
The Labyrinth is a Rocky Road
She's got a finger on the trigger
Chicken by Eve has gone off the deep end
The Labyrinth is a Rocky Road
She's got a finger on the trigger
Chicken by Eve has gone off the deep end
B-L-N-D-N-P-G
That spells blind pig, don't you see?
Teacher said with some surprise,
Son, you left out both the I's.
Now I said, teacher dear,
Won't you please and listen here?
Blind pigs have no I's, you see.
You're right, the teacher said to me.
Root for that acorn.
Hey, I got some dirty pictures here.
Ever see any bug porno?
Are you talking to me?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You look like the kind of gentleman that can appreciate
a special, uh,
special interest photography,
we like to call it here.
What do you have?
Yeah, look at this.
Are you selling something?
Yeah, these are for sale.
Like, check this out.
When was the last time you saw
an 8x10 color picture of a female praying mantis
chewing off the head of her mate?
Come on, George, that's a bad man.
Let's get away.
Oh, come on, take a look.
Look, we got little movies here, too.
Look, this one.
It's a spider chewing on a fly.
We can't do this for a living.
Spider to fly!
Come on, these pictures are taken with an electron microscope.
I want to look, I want to look, I want to look!
Yeah, check it out, check it out.
Oh, come on, lady.
Look, this is a free country.
Okay.
Hey, you into cockroaches?
Here's a cockroach being enabled by a wolf spider wasp.
Look at that, he's chewing away.
You like it?
Let's go right now.
Hey, look at this.
This is one of the things.
These things live.
Inside your eyelashes.
Can you believe it?
This most hideous looking thing ever.
So yeah.
Yeah.
Check it out.
It's nude, man.
It's all nude.
You can see my eyebrows are nude.
Check it out.
This bug.
Man, it's bug porn.
It's a bug?
Oh, yeah.
Bug porno.
It's a dirty, bug's a dirty.
Hey, honey, it's all relative.
What are you doing?
Oh, no, no, no.
Don't you get it wrong.
No.
We don't have any new.
It's all.
Oh, Jesus.
We just developed the film and he's the processor tattoo.
And then they do some with it after that.
I got nothing to do with the bug porn or anything.
.
Ow.
Hey.
.
I had a cellular phone, and the woman, what's the woman's name?
Princess Weardo.
Princess Weardo was screaming something about bug pornography.
Death of a fly.
So we'll have an officer come out and talk to you.
Can an officer come and visit you perhaps tomorrow around 2 o'clock?
Well, look, Your Honor, we really, I mean, look, yes,
we publish the bug erotic photography shots,
but we have a constitutional right.
This is an artistic study of the lovely structure of the insect body.
Some, I admit that there may be some trade in this sort of thing illegally on the Internet
or something like that, but we have nothing to do with that.
These are expensive art books.
We're not interested in investigating the investigation entirely.
We're only concerned.
Dobbs approved art books.
Well, we're only concerned with the disappearance of these two people,
and we're not interested in investigating the pornography ring right now on any level that I know of.
Anyway, I just want to know if an officer can come around your house around 2 o'clock tomorrow.
Well, those people didn't, those people probably got whatever they, I mean, we didn't have anything to do with that.
You can't pin that on us.
Show me a witness.
What was the question?
Something about, no, no, they can't come around.
I'm going to be gone.
I'm out of town.
Got to preach a show in Columbus.
Yeah, that's it.
Columbus, Saturday night, Sunday night.
Ike.
Is that you, man?
Ike Sting.
That's Ivan.
Hey, man, I knew you when you were Ike.
Yeah.
You do all that Bob stuff, man.
Look, hey, man.
Dead of a fly.
You're doing pretty good with that stuff, you know, all that Bob stuff.
You got any money?
You can do anything.
Dead of a fly.
My baby.
I went to school today, you know.
Um, sorry, I don't carry cash anymore.
I do everything with this chip in my forehead and my hand.
Well, could you, like, you know, take it over to some place and get me a hamburger or something?
Uh, yeah, I'll tell you what.
I'll be back in about ten minutes.
Hey, look, no, Ike, man.
I'll see you later.
Hey, man, I remember when...
Hey, Sting, you suck, man.
Hey.
I remember the little people.
I detest them.
Sting.
I ignore them.
Sting, you've forgotten the little people.
I don't notice them.
Even you have an inner voice, Sting.
Even Sting has an inner voice.
I wish that inner voice would leave me alone and leave me in peace.
Drive back.
Drive back, Ivan.
Jeez, that guy probably dead.
There's pizza huts all over that neighborhood with help wanted signs out that...
He's hungry.
Bum.
He can get a job just like I had to do back that one time a long time ago.
I hate those bums.
I feel kind of bad for him, though.
I mean, it would be so easy for me.
It wouldn't...
I mean, what's five bucks?
That's like nothing for me.
I could hand him a fiver, but that would just be encouraging.
Your heart is shrinking, man.
I'd just be encouraging.
You like those pinks and all those unpassionate, though.
It's people you despise.
I guess it does.
It does.
It's kind of pink of me not to give those lazy bums a buck.
Stop making it up, man.
Lazy bums.
It's not like you to do something like that.
Just go ahead, man, on a whim, on a lark.
That's the point.
Wait a minute.
Now I'm getting an idea.
I could go back there and promise him five bucks, lure him into the car, gas him...
See now you're thinking right, man.
...and put him in the vats.
Yeah.
See, your inner voice will direct you.
Yeah, we can turn him into dirt for a special vat.
Yeah, man.
You're all right.
Yeah, I guess I'll do a...
You haven't lost it.
Here.
You haven't.
I'll just...
I feel good now.
I think I feel like I've listened to my inner spoiled brat.
It's always...
Just, you know, doing whatever the hell I feel like doing.
It seems like such a rewarding way to...
Speed up, man.
Yeah, I'll just...
I'm gonna head out...
Drive faster, Ivan.
Man, I'm cool.
I can drive fast like a he-man.
I think I'm gonna have a swig of this here...
Yeah.
...cord of beer here.
Oh, damn, it's empty.
Keep drinking.
I'll just throw it out the window here into this yard.
Hey, hey.
Oh, I hit a little kid.
Let's go, man.
There's a drive-thru beverage store.
Knock it over, man.
Steal some beer.
Beer.
Oh, let's...
Impulse, man.
You're a subgenius.
Yeah, natural-born killers.
All right, everybody in here.
This is a stick-up.
Give me all your beer.
Wait a minute.
What am I doing?
This is wrong, but I've already started into it.
Now I'm gonna be in trouble if I don't kill these bastards.
Hey, man.
Blam!
What are you...
Don't...
Stop pointing your finger at me.
Do you want something?
Now that I've started this...
Into this criminal act,
I guess I better find...
Holla through all the way.
See, I've killed three convenience store clerks.
Who's that guy?
And...
I...
What else?
I guess I could rob a bank,
and then I'd be rich.
Then I could run for president.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll be the ultimate arch-criminal.
I'll run for president.
I'll become friends with the CIA.
I know everything they're up to anyway,
and I'll just let them know,
hey, look, you guys do your business.
I'll do my business.
Let me get re-elected fair and square,
and I'll keep my mouth shut.
I'm sure you guys have stuff on me.
You keep your mouth shut,
everything'll be fine.
I got those ne'er-do-wells
and have-nots to vote for me,
because they thought I cared.
But I'm with you guys.
I know the way the world really works.
I know how it makes the world turn.
You understand.
I am so glad that you masons
and Disney CEOs and people
let me into the circle of ten.
Yes, and we're proud.
I'm glad to have you, too.
I'm also, well, I'm glad that Mr. Rockefeller died
and left, made a place for me, but...
Oh, that's a nice chair you're occupying, too.
Don't remember, there's a lot of tradition
in that chair, Mr. Stagg.
Oh, believe me, I know it.
I've done my homework, and you can bet
that the Church of the Subgenius
will happily work with the conspiracy from now on.
Of course, we're gonna make a lot more money
if we can maintain our anti-conspiracy,
conspiracy image.
You know, I mean, I assume that's why you brought us in.
Just a minute, Mr. Stagg.
Could you please just sit down?
You're making some of the members of the table
a little uncomfortable.
We certainly appreciate your attitude.
We're not much of a sort of behavior around here, boys.
We certainly...
Sorry, Colonel North.
Just relax.
We'd like to talk to you about some of your other activities.
You see, Mr. Pipe Mill and Mr. Crack Tuber,
they feel that some of your activities
are encroaching on...
Well, how would a gangster say it?
Encroaching on their...
turf, so to speak.
Uh, could you clarify that?
I, uh, don't...
Wally, just sit down.
Now, please put it away.
I'm sure we can work things out.
Well, we're definitely going to work things out now,
Reverend Stagg.
You see, uh, according to our figures,
you owe the conspiracy a lot of money.
What?
But I owe the conspiracy...
I would think that...
I thought you guys were gonna be paying me.
For a lot of airports, yes.
I gave you our mailing list.
Ha, mailing list.
The mailing list doesn't pay our bills, Mr. Stagg.
You know what kind of company you're sitting with.
Look at the men next to you.
These are men of power and wealth.
Now, you've dared to join our fraternity.
We've learned the idea,
and we've accepted you in our midst.
You're going to have to make amends.
You're going to have to do something
about all this money you owe us.
What?
Now, wait a minute.
What kind of...
You've got three weeks, Mr. Stagg.
How have I encroached on the turf
of any large conspiracy conglomerate?
Wally, stop that.
The church is...
The church had its own market.
It was completely different.
I'm sorry, Mr. Stagg.
You're going to have to come up with the money.
We paid our taxes.
Wally, please just...
The same way you guys do.
Now, come on.
Hey, we're in the circle again.
You can't kick us.
Come on.
You can't...
Come along.
Come along, Reverend Stagg.
Looking for fun and feeling groovy.
Hey, hey, Rev.
Hey, Rev.
How come you look so forlorn, man?
Hey, what you doing walking out of that alley anyway?
Oh, I'm feeling real groovy there, Dave.
Yeah, you don't look so good, buddy.
Oh, everything's okay, I guess.
You look like the world's on your shoulders, man.
Like a whole mess of trouble or something.
You look like the weight of the world on your shoulders.
Yeah, well, you know when they talk about the man?
Yeah.
Well, I met the man just now.
What?
You know.
The man?
Yeah, the man.
And he's...
He said we, uh, owed him a whole lot of money, Dave.
What do you mean, we, Kim Sabe?
Well, the church.
The church?
Yeah.
Owes the man?
Jeez.
Everything we've got.
So, uh, let me see your wallet, Dave.
I was just going to try and hit you up for a cup of soup, buddy.
Well, we don't...
Come on, we're walking right by some cadets.
I gave him the office.
Come on, you...
Now, fork it over.
Hey, look, if you're in Dutch with a man, you know my 25 cents ain't gonna help you out none, pal.
Well, you've probably got a point.
But I'll tell you what.
Do some more panhandling and whatever you come up with about tonight, we'll...
We'll let you live if you give it all to us.
Yeah.
It should be five or six bucks.
That'll be a start.
Damn.
Yeah, sure.
That sounds great.
Let me live.
He's got to give me this broken down...
This bill is broken down, let's see, for mind control.
Seven and a half billion dollars for sabotage of computers worldwide.
Let's see.
Eight and a half billion dollars.
How are we gonna...
All the lonesome cowboy days in the world wouldn't be able to pay off this debt.
Wonder if they'll take it in souls.
But even then, we probably don't have more than about seven or eight bills.
Maybe it's time to use one of those four little Ukrainian nuclear weapons.
One of the federal bills.
No, that...
But they did that already.
Damn.
This is your stop, sir.
Jim.
Sir, everyone is off the bus, please.
Get up, Jim.
I don't have anywhere to go.
I used to be world overlord.
I was president for five minutes.
I was in the circle of tens of air vaults.
I knowed the seven demons for what they was.
And I knowed J.R. Bobbitts.
I'll tell your story for 50 cents.
No, please.
Listen to him.
He's crazy.
I'll hold this sign for liquor.
Come on.
I think he's been hiding out from the conspiracy for the last 40 years.
I remember.
I was on the escape vessels for the crash.
You gotta listen to him.
I was on...
I was given a special...
I wrote Zodinimus Pamphlet number one in 1979.
Yeah, you did.
Old time.
I seen it.
I was there when J.R. Bobbitts was shot.
Shot in the San Francisco Theater.
That is a weird thing, though.
I have seen them pamphlets.
Just listen to them go on.
I was there when J.R. Hypercleats first launched the bleep.
I thought he was a world overlord or Bob or something.
I was elected president in 1996.
Been lost at all.
Been gambling on drugs.
I was...
Never did make it to television.
But now it's cover the conspiracy.
He's on the line taking a nap.
He starts a wave in his mind.
Believe me, son.
I fought the conspiracy just like you.
I fought harder than anybody.
I want to show you this withered up old card.
Of course, first chance...
See, 30 bucks is, and 30 bucks is.
First chance I got, I joined them, of course.
Thought I didn't feel treated.
Make Bob world overlord.
Just a bit off more than I can chew.
That'd be a lesson to you.
Now, can you...
Hey, can you loan me?
I just got to get to the bus, get the bus back to my house.
I just loaned some old bum the last 50 cents.
You can loan me like 50, maybe a dollar or something.
You don't have to have five, do you?
Because I'll pay you back.
Sit down, old son.
Let me stroke your gray head.
You haven't washed your hair in a long time.
And my hands are up.
I will give you your money.
And I will drive you down to the edge of the old graveyard and leave you off.
And whatever sort of way you can make on your own, then you can do.
You ain't going to cart me off to the glue factory yet?
No, no, not the glue factory, just the cemetery.
It's a fine deal.
Take it, son.
You know, this ain't fair.
Nothing's fair.
You trudged through life doing the best you can.
What's it all for?
You're getting the car.
Yeah.
Stars up there twinkling, shining away in the void.
Oh.
So this is what happened.
I should have believed in Jesus when I had the chance.
I asked him into my heart once.
He never showed up.
I broke the date.
Just shut up, old man.
We got four more hours to drive before we get to Philly.
I don't want to hear nothing more about the church of the subgenius.
I need to use the bathroom.
Pull over next stop.
Yeah.
That's the last time we're going to pull over for you.
The next time I'm going to pistol whip your head.
Now shut up, old timer.
Oh, my God.
There's no respect for a holy man no more.
You actually believe all that stuff about Bob he's talking?
Well, don't you talk bad on Bob.
Hey, listen.
I told you to pipe down that thing.
What he was.
Oh.
There's my teeth.
Where's my teeth?
He knows my teeth.
I can't see nothing.
What are we going to do with him?
Man, I can't stand all this blitting all the way to Kansas City.
We're going backwards.
Now let him off at a rest stop or something.
Buy him a hamburger.
Do anything.
Get rid of him.
It's no kind of a world for an old man no more.
Yeah, old man.
Men flying around the moon.
Yeah.
Paying no attention to the troubles down here on Earth.
You'll find it one day, old guy.
Just keep going.
Don't come out there.
Thinks people are flying around the moon.
Shut up, will you?
You've only been on 14 planets.
I'm just an old.
I once owned 14 planets.
Then I lost them.
Then I lost it all.
Lost my faith in Bob.
You lost your teeth.
You lost your watch.
Let me tell you about the time.
You don't shut up.
You're going to lose a lot more than that.
You're standing down at 44.
Now shut up.
There's probably more planets than there are atoms in the universe.
You've only been on one.
I met Colin Powell and shook his hand.
I knowed all the world leaders briefly back then.
Give him a colon warmer.
He used to live at the mall.
Pass him the colon warmer, will you, please, before he expires in the backseat.
I used to live at the mall, too.
Oh, man.
Life 101.
You flunk.
Can't you do anything better on the radio than that weird buzzing sound?
Yes, these inspirational parables have been brought to you by ESO Radio and the Church of the Subgenius
and the endless...
Tribes of all the UFOs and the conspiracy.
In hopes that you will learn a lesson.
Young man or young woman out there driving down Euclid, lost, hopeless, looking for something,
seeking something.
Tried Scientology.
It was too stupid.
I want fun.
Tried TV.
It was too stupid.
Tried real life.
It was too hard.
Well, you can escape from all of those things into your own fantasy world, your own delusions.
You don't need a life.
Join the Church of the Subgenius.
Thank you.
Thank you, Reverend.
I've been staying for those wonderful, inspirational messages.
Now, during the cocktail here, cocktail hour here aboard the Exeter,
the vessels of the space...
I'm sorry, this is my first night here.
Tonight, performing, we're going to be having the...
Oh, jeez, I can't read these cards.
The hairy women are going to be crucified.
Was that your request, Reverend Stang?
Oh, no, no, no.
Not crucified.
I just want to see a live sex show.
I don't want to...
No, I don't enjoy the violence.
I thought you wanted to see a hairy monkey woman crucified.
I've been watching that stuff all day on the view screens.
Okay.
It is not her suit to be crucified.
No, no.
I hate the hairy...
She's a yeti.
Would you like to pretend like there are more people in the audience
so we can have more interactive
and you can think of maybe something else you might want to do?
No, I'm tired.
I think I'll just sit here and listen to Elvis and drink.
Would you like to drink real booze
or would you like to drink some of the exacerbated boozy?
Or would you like to perhaps drop again?
No, no, I'll just have this off and statters.
Double-edged rope?
House standard.
Primo triples, Rob.
No, no, no.
Just sit here.
Would you like your toes shined?
This isn't all I expected it to be.
I'm tired.
My first day on the escape vessels, I'm already...
Bored.
Bored with pleasure and...
Is this what it's going to be like?
One day of having everything you want
and by the end of the day, you've had enough.
You're bored.
You're ready for...
You're ready for bed.
You don't know what you're going to do the next day.
You've had everything.
Reverend, excuse me.
The queen of the Nubians would like to do you again.
I'm just...
I don't care.
I don't really go on hearing your lies.
Let me just listen.
Leave me alone.
Go away.
Drone.
Clone.
The stage is bare.
Not Sergio?
No, just go away.
Shut the planet down.
Shut off the sun.
That's your pleasure, Reverend.
I'm going to go.
Close down all the malls.
Tell the hookers to go home.
Or we're back to the factory, wherever they're made.
If only Elvis would come back.
Hey, Reverend, baby.
Hey, I have a head of this.
You'll love it, man.
Oh.
Oh, thanks, Elvis.
Maybe that'll make me feel better.
Go.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
We'll see you next time.
Bye.
violence to run rampant in our streets. What are we going to do about it?
I don't go looking in a garbage can for fresh food.
All right? And when you're looking in something that's essentially a garbage can and you're
trying to pick out the applicable positive morsels, it's futile. Futile.
I will be there. You be there and expect the unexpected. This is Bob.
I believe we should pray that any vehicles transporting illegal drugs and attempting
to enter our neighborhoods shall simply quit running or that they shall be detoured in some
way so that they cannot enter our neighborhoods.
or that they shall meet with some accident along the way,
and that the drugs shall be completely destroyed in this accident.
At the same time, we should pray that no innocent person shall be hurt in these accidents.
God is able to protect the lives of people,
while at the same time allowing the drugs and the vehicles transporting them to be totally destroyed.
One way or another, let's agree that all such vehicles shall be prevented from entering our neighborhoods.
After we have prayed for our own neighborhood, where we have the greatest authority,
then pray similarly concerning any vehicle entering the city,
or any vessel entering the port of Philadelphia, or Camden, or Wilmington,
or any planes heading toward our airports.
Then let us pray for our country, that the same thing may happen to any vessel or vehicle
that is entering our neighborhoods.
This is why I don't understand why the Christians hate us so much.
I believe the great Dr. Legume once said,
there's not that much difference between the Christians and the subgenius.
They have a savior that they nail to a stick, and we have a savior we beat with a stick.
It's all the same, and I think I could bring up now short-duration personal saviors.
Once you have a savior, you have a savior that you beat with a stick.
Once you make Bob your personal savior, you realize that you don't need Bob as your personal savior.
What you really need is a short-duration personal savior.
We push this in the Church of the Subgenius.
Really, anything can be your savior.
Any of your favorite bands, or rock stars, or Blade of Grass.
Your cat could be your personal savior.
Because really, in this fast-paced, hectic world, that's what we really need, isn't it?
A short-duration personal savior.
It could be Zeus. It could be Jesus.
It could be Buddha.
Whatever you want.
For this week.
Next week, pick another one.
But really, in your heart, you know that you love Bob.
S. Send your $30 to Bob.
L. Launch the head.
A. Acknowledge your superiority.
C. The conspiracy.
K. Kill Bob.
S-L-A-C-K.
Slack.
And this is what you need in your life.
Point number three.
Call down blindness and confusion on the smugglers and pushers,
so that they will not be able to find the drugs to sell.
In Acts we read,
Then Saul, who was also called Paul, filled with the Holy Spirit,
looked straight at Elimas the sorcerer and said,
You are a child of the devil, and an enemy of God.
You know, the faith of God is
If Jesus Christ
was a man
as he put the son of case
Hey of God in the oil
And he sent the plan
he had not told you
how come he doesn't know
all the truths
All the subject
And all this
their heads instead. God sent confusion into the camps of Israel's enemies and caused them to kill
each other. Let's pray that the smugglers may become so confused that they will not remember
where they hid the drugs which they are attempting to smuggle into our neighborhoods, our city, and
our country. Most Christians should be able to agree with us on that. Do not attempt to pray for
anything with which you cannot agree. Some Christians would rather pray for the salvation
of the smugglers and pushers. Fine. By all means, pray that God will send laborers across their path,
someone to whom they will listen, and pray that the Holy Spirit will move upon their hearts.
The main thing we are trying to achieve here is to prevent the smugglers and pushers from finding the drugs to sell. We want to put them out of business, and in the name of Jesus, we can do it.
Amen.
Point number four, which the Lord gave us.
Ask the angels to hide the drugs that are already in your neighborhood, your city, and your country, so that the dealers and pushers cannot locate them.
What would the angels do without us?
Ask the angels to hide their drugs.
Pray that God will drag this down.
Pray that the G Color would bring about a new generation of have woken up today.
Thanks.
Thank you very much children, and now, my compatriot, my companion, traveling partner,
and colleague, Reverend Steve Slack would like to express himself to you.
What happened to me?
I think the Holy Spirit just spoke to me.
What do you mean by that?
The Holy Spirit...
I haven't had this happen in many, many years, ever since I was suckered by a Christian cult.
And this time the Holy Spirit had a different thing to say to me.
He said that the money changers are...
They're back in the temple.
We must chase them out.
These people who call themselves Christians, who praise the name of the Lord and supplicate for him,
like Tony, useless little fanboys, they tag along behind the Lord like a pesky kid brother who he can't shake off,
trying to impress the Lord, they commit acts of cruelty in his name and call it piousness.
They make him look pretty damn lame and silly.
They don't even know his name, the Lord.
Don't even know what it is.
Don't even know what to call him.
Jehovah One is what we call him, but that's just one...
That's just the god of the local galaxy parish.
They use his name to scour the planet of passion and imagination,
and in its stead they place conformity and sterility and an unferal and diminished cloning of ideas.
And these behaviors are increasing exponentially,
and the planet will consume itself and mankind will cease to be anything but a mass of robots,
and all timid and in one accord, and punishing those who break from their herd.
And these Christians, or so they call themselves, these zombies, these sons of snakes,
these plastic little robots are ruining everything!
They're claiming the creators of ideas, real ideas, they're claiming them as their pasties and their fall guys.
Now, when Jesus Shanghai Shuka Gruber got him nailed to that rock,
he didn't know how much of a big deal those funny guys meant, or what Mark would have meant of it.
You know, Christ was so tired of those twelve toadies that the, you know,
they couldn't even tell a joke right, let alone get a story straight!
I don't even know how to tell a joke!
You know, Christ just wanted to, you know, pull some kind of stunt so he could grab Mary Magdalene
and get away to a little love nest in Galilee.
Whoo!
Oh yeah!
Oh, the Christians are great!
They're gonna bring a whole new world of love and peace and universal oneness and harmony
that is after we kill off the weirdos with their weirdo ideas!
Like, maybe one weirdo idea providing a release valve for repressed glands, drives, and emotions
to prevent them from driving its possessor over the brink into some hideously destructive action!
Like, when people come and go and say,
What's wrong with you?
You're weird!
And, and...
You...
You're kind of young and sensitive and...
You cry a little bit about it, but after a while, after you get run through the gauntlet of hate,
and all the hate that I have witnessed, the hate that I have experienced, the hate that I have seen,
nowadays when they come up to you,
up to you,
and you're aware in this life,
Thank you!
Whoo!
Thank you for calling me weird!
That is a compliment!
Whoo! All right? Now,
I take it.
Aww...
Normality is everything it's cracked up to be!
Yeah!
I... Now,
my acquaintances,
several partying buddies, say that's a face of
Dots!
Just Dots!
He's not real.
They believe what they see on X-Files.
They... They...
sit over beers and discuss the truly tangible and possible elements of warp travel and matter-energy conversion, but...
Oh!
Dogs can't possibly be a corporeal being!
And, you know,
so, we really don't ask for much now, in trade for, um,
what some people might call entertainment.
Thirty dollars?
Well,
I mean, thirty dollars, you can blow thirty dollars on a... on a date!
Some horrible...
mismatch that might end in disaster!
Well,
thirty dollars wasted down the tube.
Why not spend that on something that's going to last...
far longer?
Maybe to the end of your life!
Well, I mean, if you pay your thirty bucks, you might... life might not end.
We might keep and continue you all... all your life.
All the way into some far-off planet, or... or...
or... or...
or maybe the end of your life will just be...
skinning everything from your body except your brain,
which they'll hook up to a machine and...
and... and keep you alive so you can...
feel nothing but pain!
You think that Bob Dobbs cares about money?
When he sleeps on a mattress stuffed with dollar bills?
He's more interested in the psychic stench from the butt sweat...
that seeps into your thirty dollars!
That scent is important!
That scent is important because...
they can... they can snuff you out...
in a room full of people...
and if they can snuff you out...
then the Exosaucers can snuff your house out...
among the whole neighborhood...
so that your house is still standing when the other ones get torched!
And you'd better be ready to take up the slack that Bob left off in that...
that secret little mail drawer!
You'd better be ready, you know why?
Because he's dead, that's why!
So we keep bringing him back...
to kill him again!
Because that's the whole point, you know?
If... if... if Bob were around...
I mean, if Bob were around...
you'd just take him for granted...
and when you leave here tonight...
and you might go tomorrow morning...
you'll go back to your job and you'll... you'll...
sit there at your desk looking at the clock...
and you'll think about...
what you saw here tonight...
and you'll think, well, that was nice entertainment...
and then you'll go on and continue with your job...
and things will go pretty much back to normal...
and soon you'll forget about Bob...
soon you'll forget about what you saw...
and soon everything you heard here tonight...
will go out of your mind...
and you'll come back home...
and you'll watch your TV...
and you'll get your silly drugs or whatever...
and you'll forget about Bob...
and you'll just quietly go back...
to the life you once knew...
before you came here tonight.
Get locked into some empty career...
for 50 years until you're dead...
or...
what's the use of struggling all your life...
to build something when down there...
anything can come and take it away...
like that.
Nah, you want something more...
you demand something more...
but you really don't know what that more is...
and yet you don't care...
you still want more...
and you'd really rather not have to...
work too hard to get it.
The only thing you want to be is you...
and you have no idea who the hell you even is...
but that's not gonna stop you from at least trying...
to make something out of your life.
Gotta be more than just working and saving and slaving away
like every other frustrated idiot
hovering over his possessions
and moaning proudly about his bills.
And, dear friends, there is indeed more.
And the answer to your questions is so simple.
If you'll just take up that pen, that pencil,
and that piece of paper
and write down the sacred post office box number
I'm about to give you.
Because, friends, you can just throw all that baggage away
and write to Bob.
And just send Bob a self-addressed stamped envelope if you want.
Just send that request, that humble request.
It doesn't even have to be very humble.
A lot of them aren't.
Send that to Bob at post office box.
1-8-1-4-1-7
Cleveland Heights, Ohio
4-4-1-1-8
www.subgenius.com
So, we're waiting to hear from you.
Oh, and what we've been listening to,
well, a little bit of thought alchemy there at the very end.
Before that, the long rant was, of course,
by Reverend Steve Slack,
recorded at the Columbus, the Bible,
a couple of weeks ago
at Stash's Club.
And Dr. Dinosaur with Steve Slack and Princess Wiardo
doing a version of For What It's Worth.
The war on drugs tape was sent by Dr. Katadn Leyoum.
And we heard a little clip of music
from a band called Ewing Oil.
Used to be called Chewing Foil.
Earlier on in there,
yes, yes, yes, friends.
So, and so we leave you, sort of,
for in a few minutes here.
We'll see what comes up next.
Apprise that man, Bob.
Or, or kill me.
Or kill me.
Believers, let us all agree
and ask our angels to frustrate the dealers and pushers
by hiding the drugs which are already in our neighborhood,
our city,
and our country.
They can hide them so well
that the dealers and pushers
will never be able to find them again.
You may either pray to our Heavenly Father,
asking Him to send the angels on this assignment,
or you may command them directly,
speaking the faith command in the name of Jesus.
Hmm?
Yeah, it's evil to have glands,
drives, emotions,
say the Christians.
You want to corral them in a pen?
No.
Until they boil over into doing something stupid,
like driving your car into a tree.
Whoo!
You think that life or a church is a spectator sport?
You think this is TV?
You think that you can just sit back here and watch this,
like, you know, for some TV?
You're just going to sit there?
Stare at us like this?
Friend, if you want that kind of church,
the kind where you can sit on your butt
and do nothing but listen to some preacher drone,
and smile and shake hands,
and...
Well, you know, next Sunday,
you know, any old church around here
will serve your purposes.
And, uh, you got faith?
You got faith?
Mm-hmm.
They talk about faith,
like you've got faith that your college degree
will get you some kind of job that's lucrative enough
to pay off your loans,
or you've got faith that some significant other
will be around forever.
You've got faith that Social Security will be there
and you won't run out by the time you retire,
if you even have faith that your job will last that long.
So, really, is it such a stretch
to have some kind of faith
in a duck-faced, pipe-smoking dumbass
that just might be the thing
that will save you?
Think about it.
And help out the mission,
the continuing, nameless mission,
that we have here tonight.
And we hope that you will
give something of yourself to us
and take something back with you.
And tell all your friends
that there's just a little bit,
something more,
than the narcosis
that the conspiracy is compelling you to accept.
Thank you.
Whoo!
They play around with words.
Don't you see how the cults just play around with words?
It sounds good, warm, fuzzy, forgiveness, love, acceptance...
But it's all lies.
Hey, when you're getting a book dictated by demons,
what do you expect?