What's the name of this place?
The Salt Genius!
Watch!
Now!
I have absolutely heard of that place.
Sounds like a school for Neanderthals.
No, it's actually considered the Harvard of kindergartens.
We found a sweet haven of sunshine at last
The exes are biting above
They'll scoop us with tentacles luridly cast
And smoothly they'll sell us some love
The tempest is our relief evermore
What slackness, what rupture is not
The danger will pass
We're rescued at last
The Indies are here by and by
He sees us endangered and sends out his men
To pilot our ping-baiting soul
The Inclans have teased us again and again
But this one's the true Rufus Toll
The tempest is our relief evermore
What slackness, what rupture is not
The danger will pass
We're rescued at last
The Indies are here by and by
Scrant's jail control made through lightning death
On Bob all my money all speddened
All praise him each hour of my last fleeting breath
Repentance slack off to the end
The tempest is our relief evermore
We're rescued at last
What slackness, what rupture is not
The danger will pass
We're rescued at last
The Indies are here by and by
The tempest is off
We're safe evermore
What slackness, what rupture is not
The danger will pass
The tempest is our relief evermore
We're rescued at last
The Indies are here by and by
We start with nothing
Nothing, nothing
Nothing, nothing, nothing
With a rainy day in mind
The sun will rise in the morning
Sure as every night it sets
Maybe there'll be no warning
From the men from Planet X
Who knows who might be next?
Who knows you might be next?
Who knows anyone's guess?
Who knows?
Hated all of it
It might soon be you
Who knows?
It could be me too
When your time is time
Who knows?
If heaven is here
It's been one hell of a ride
We start with nothing
And leave everything behind
No point in waiting
In saving
With a rainy day in mind
The sun will rise in the morning
Sure as every night it sets
Maybe there'll be no warning
From the men from Planet X
Who knows who might be next?
Who knows you might be next?
Who knows?
You might be next?
Hated all of it
Who knows?
It might soon be you
It could be me too
Who knows?
When your time is time
If heaven is here
It's been one hell of a ride
Leave everything behind
Behind
Who knows?
Hey, you want to see a magical type trick?
You want to see it here?
Watch it.
I'm going to do it.
Behold!
Just show me a trick.
You want to do a step?
Yeah, not everybody can do that, huh?
Show trick.
Impressed, eh?
Sure, okay, I'm impressed.
Can you teach me magic, man?
Can you show me how you did that trick?
Oh, well, you know.
The magician doesn't like to reveal how he does his tricks.
I mean, that takes all the glamour away.
It's rather simple when you find out what it is.
To see the magic makes the magic go away.
Well, to see the behind the scenes, yes.
Then certainly whatever you get for being an insider,
you lose in your guileless appreciation of some magician's.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
You know, you can fire some cliches and...
Something's not right.
Something is just not right.
The magic land of Alakazam.
It's because you're missing the A's.
Oh, Betty, Betty.
These things.
These things?
Have you got some more of them B's things?
These tings, man.
Oh, it gives you a tingle, yeah.
Tings, yeah, tings.
But this is different.
All these tings.
This is something different.
These B tings.
These tings.
It hurts.
Honey badgers don't care.
Honey badgers have a tough little skin.
Well, imagine the tremendous danger a Kryptonian honey badger would represent.
They're masters of mayhem, too.
I don't think they had those on Krypton.
They had all sorts of weird, bizarre creatures, but no honey badgers.
But, of course, they'd all be horrendously strong here.
Uh-huh.
Including the miniaturized ones in the bottle city of Kandor, though they were only about
as big as a...
Miniature honey badgers.
...a flea's foot.
They would still be strong enough, in theory, to move the Earth.
What do you think they did about animal control in the bottle city of Kandor?
They must have had some way of controlling, keeping those creatures in the Kryptonian zoo
in the bottle.
Well, not just that.
What about rats and mice and things like that?
Oh, they're in a good, thick glass bottle.
No rats and mice.
No, but I'm talking about the tiny little mini rats and mice that came...
The vermin that came along with the city.
But, again, I don't know if Krypton had creatures like rats and mice.
Are you saying that it was...
That Krypton couldn't support a full ecological biodiversity that would have included even
vermin and scavengers?
Well, the thing is, I remember what was in the Krypton Zoo, and all those creatures were
so weird that they didn't seem to be broken down into the divisions that we have on Earth.
Right.
All the exotic creatures.
I'm really just talking about the common creatures.
Sure.
They're not going to put rabbits in the zoo.
They're going to put some exotic creatures.
Or even possums.
You know, the possums are hanging around the sewer in Krypton.
They're not...
Or in, you know, whatever the...
What was the main city that they lived in?
I can't remember the city's name.
Well, Kandor itself was a city, but...
Well, the city on Krypton...
Hey, you've got a mosquito on your head.
There you go.
You got it.
How dare they?
How did that happen?
It's probably a disease-ridden one.
Yes, he's probably...
Is it experimental?
He injected me with...
He probably broke out of an experiment.
I haven't been feeling too well lately anyway, so I'm assuming...
And now you don't...
Was he biting me?
I don't think he'd actually sunk his proboscis into your face yet.
That little bastard, if I catch him again, I...
Oh, is this on?
Yeah, that's on, but...
Well, I suppose since this is KPV, I should speak of my reverence for all living things.
You're listening to KFV.
Yes, I was involved on part of the same...
You, the listener.
...lake pilgrimage through life.
And so...
Some of you on KPFB, do you think people actually listen to KPFB in Berkeley?
Oh, I know they do, my dear friend.
Because they have KPFA.
Why would they choose B if they have A?
Because that is the nature of people, to wish to differentiate their choices.
I think one of them is for when you're behind a tree and the reception's better, you know?
And then, of course, if you're in Fresno, you have to be at 88.1 on KFC.
You know how all this works.
I guess you sound very knowledgeable about...
Oh, yeah, I know that you have to have four letters and at least two numbers.
Although I never hear about, like, you know, 100 FM.
It's always 101 or 101.
That's your special buzzword, I mean, your password that you use to unlock the mystery.
Mm-hmm.
They never say 90 FM or, you know...
It's never a round number.
It's always, you know, goes to some point.
Some fractional point on the dial.
Yeah, you should know why.
There's a very good reason.
The same reason gas is always 399.
Because the government has to put some points on the end.
That's why.
No, it's a sales trick.
Come on.
89.3?
You mean it's not just because that's where they cut the frequency range?
Nope.
And the megahertz are measured that way?
No.
The megahertz is to sell the numbers.
But what about the gigahertz and the terahertz?
It all hurts.
The bigahertz.
There's no differentiation.
Unless you're Honey Badger.
Nothing hurts.
No, if you've got a good, tough, pachydermatous skin like a little Honey Badger,
and the unpleasant disposition of a Honey Badger to go with it...
I'm kidding.
They have got...
They're fierce little guys.
I don't know if their disposition is that unpleasant.
They're just not that cuddly, and so that's resented by humans who...
Humans hate ugly animals, don't they, Dr. Howell?
Well, they like little fuzzy animals.
They like the fuzzy ones to be fellow travelers and to get in line and not act out of, you know...
But they won't invest in the preservation of the mosquito.
Why they do.
Because, once again, as I was saying before,
agriculture makes it possible for the mosquitoes to live,
and malaria comes after agriculture.
Rice has to be grown in standing water.
They can't think beyond their own...
The perfect place for these insects.
...to develop.
Are you familiar with the appearance of a mosquito larva?
As a child, I always observed these things with wonder.
For one thing, it's larger than the adult mosquito, right?
And it's all jointed with all these...
I mean, it's a hideous, horrible thing.
It's a hideous, horrible thing.
It is.
Well...
So are maggots, though.
Maggots, maggots, maggots.
But maggots have...
Those sort of intermediate stages of a lot of animals.
Maggots have great use in treating...
They have open wounds.
If you just pour maggots into the wound,
they eat all the necrotic flesh and leave the healthy flesh alone,
so you are...
That's generally what I do when I have a big necrotic wound that needs...
Just dump maggots in it.
...needs cleaning.
I dump maggots in it.
Right.
That's the thing.
I've always done that to every necrotic wound I've ever had.
Really?
Even, like, a sucking chest wound?
Well, I've got to hand it to you.
And here it is.
No.
Okay, thanks.
All sticky.
Now, what do I do with it?
You can put it in the disposable chute over there.
Okay.
I won't need it anymore.
It's kind of been used.
It's got some dirt on it over here.
Don't toss and turn all night with spiders in your hair.
On the pseudo-carpet.
I wish that thing that we did earlier was about five times bigger.
We did a big thing, huh?
Yeah.
Well, that was...
I did a big thing, but only about one-fifth as big as what it should have been.
Well, there must have been expenses involved, you know.
Dr. Hal, I've got to get something off my chest, and I think I can let you know about it because you're a know-it-all.
Well, it's something...
Don't you hate it when people say,
that object is five times smaller than what it was, than the other object?
And why should I be particularly...
Why don't you hate it when they...
When they're talking about something that is a fraction of the other thing, that they use the word times to describe it.
Oh.
It's fractional proportion rather than the proportion itself.
That drives me nuts.
That just aggravates a lot.
That body in space is five...
There's only...
Instead of one-fifth as large, they say it's five times as small.
It's like a ridiculous series of words that mean nothing to me.
When I hear a scientist or some supposed person with a reputation say that,
it makes me want to reach through the radio and choke them to death.
Now, Philo, please, remember your blood pressure.
I'm sorry, but this is just...
Some people have pet peeves.
This is my pet peeve.
When someone refers to a body that's a smaller proportion than the other one,
they refer to it as some number of times smaller.
Oh.
You can't make something number of times smaller.
A times is a multiple.
Unless you're multiplying negatives, I guess you could.
Well, but that would be pointless.
It would be pointless.
Yes, multiplying negatives has no future.
So, I've got that off my chest and I feel remarkably better.
Well, I am afraid that there are even a large number of subgeniuses who use that expression.
Well, there's...
There's something around chewing the fat at X day.
Yeah, they say that and they say I'm like...
Speaking of pointless, here I am.
Pointless?
Pointless, you say?
I'm eminently an expert in the pointlessness.
The finer points of pointlessness.
Well, sometimes...
Well, don't you agree with my assessment of the previous statement and agree with me 100%?
Isn't a rounded version just as accessible as a pointed version?
Just minimum, at least.
107%.
Yes.
I'm glad.
I'm really...
Subliminally, minimally.
Not only do you agree with me, you agree with me more than I even agree with myself.
Yes, that's tricky, isn't it?
It is tricky and it's awesome.
I appreciate that.
I want that ahead of you.
I appreciate that because...
Harmony in nature.
Someday I'm going to appreciate me as much as you do.
Is expressed through privileges.
Now, I have a question though.
But chaos and destruction are expressed through points and angles.
I'm just nabobbing about a thank you to the listener.
How do you know you have a listener?
And how do you know if they're actually listening?
They are theological.
We do make a leap of faith at the point where we...
The second...
We know sometimes that we have a person that has engaged their computer with a stream on the internet.
We know that.
There's software that tells us that...
It shouldn't be on their computer.
I don't know why you're encouraging that.
The computer and its browser has engaged with the stream of the show.
Oh, the dog was...
The dog was your neighbor.
Anybody that's just out there in the ether and they're listening to their radio...
No, I think I understand.
I have no idea what that is.
You said the dog was urinating on it.
The dog was urinating on it.
The browser was doing...
How's still thinking about McNamara's electronic fence?
I'm not browsing your browser, okay?
The browser, we know...
So, we do get an indication of that.
Bad dog.
We like to extrapolate that and say that...
Are you vindicated or cylindricated?
Which exactly is it?
It's bifurcated.
No, we appreciate it.
Uh-oh.
I'm not Twitterpated.
He's a...
Adelpated, more like it.
He's a banana split personality, apparently.
He's got a paint, a shiny paint.
He's got bananas, I tell you.
Is there another mosquito on me?
And now it's on Puzzling Evidence.
No, it's flying around.
This is utterly unacceptable.
I think you guys, in all fairness,
developed some sort of Turing-type test
to determine whether a listener is actually a listener.
If it's a real human listener or a robot listener.
Whether they're actually listening.
The listeners have to take care of themselves.
We have all sorts of problems.
We need a feedback system
where we can broadcast a certain number of repeated messages
and the listener would have to repeat them back to us.
And we need a mosquito-free environment
in order to do our show.
That would be a good start.
We're starting on Mars, I guess.
Too many mosquitoes in the control room.
There's a mosquito in here
and we're actually under attack.
I'm telling the listeners,
all of you people out there in the ether zone,
we're under attack by giant mosquitoes.
Get away.
Get them away.
These are Anopheles.
Get them off.
Weather one haywire.
These mosquitoes are deadly.
I'm pretty sure Mars is going to be our salvation.
I'll just give them a good smack.
Sure.
Sure, why not?
That's my blood in there.
That's good blood.
I bet you there's no dang tooting mosquitoes on Mars.
Maybe something a lot worse,
but at least we won't know what we're doing.
No, he's absolutely right.
There are no mosquitoes on Mars that toot gangs.
Well, you're thinking of that movie
where they did have mosquitoes on Mars.
There could be a darn toot mosquito on Mars.
There could be darn toot
and there could be two mosquitoes on Mars.
There could be college-educated mosquitoes,
but probably none that,
pretty much we're sure,
none toot gangs.
Well, we don't know.
But you don't know which college.
He's doing Pedro.
The only thing worse than a mosquito
is a Harvard-educated one.
Yeah.
That would be a bad thing.
Landing on your cerebellum.
A mosquito with a budget.
Sarah Palin or something.
Yeah.
Hey, props to the protesters at Harvard right now.
They're trying to get them to divest
from fossil foolishness.
And they can take up extracting sunbeams from cucumbers.
I think they should run on magic unicorn juice.
They got like trillions of dollars in investments or something.
They're the biggest,
most heavily invested university in the world
and most of it's in fossil fuels,
probably half of it.
I don't know.
Yeah, that's where the old money came from.
I don't know why you would be investing in fossils,
fuels when you've got unicorn juice.
What fuels we morsels be?
All you need is one unicorn
and you can power a whole country for a year.
One unicorn.
That's not a good use of it, though.
Well, we don't use all of the horn at once.
We try to just whittle off pieces of it at a time
so as it grows back,
we can continue to keep the unicorn trapped
in their small cage
and just milk, more or less,
milk the horn over time.
You say it's sustainably harvested.
Who am I to question you?
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know.
Oh, who are you?
Take a break here for a minute
so we can question something else, man.
You're an active caller.
A caller that...
A caller ID.
My name is ID.
And being a caller,
I'll tell you that we'll be right back.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm taking Yazidi women as sex slaves.
The Centers for Disease is ramping up its efforts
to protect the U.S. from West Africa.
The World Health Organization warns
that West Africa could start every week by December.
WHO's assistance says West Africa is already killed,
more than 4,400 people in recent months.
The numbers we need to get behind are 70% of 60
and 76% of October.
Dow is 27, 16, 46, 61, 20, 42, 34.
I am doing well and want to thank PR News.
The prosecution says this is PR News.
Control, control.
Mind controlled by Bob by Slack T
is playing in the background.
We heard some PR news from Fernanda Nantes,
the ladyly mer.
And we heard about 15 minutes
of the puzzling evidence show from KPFA Berkeley.
That particular episode,
Philo titled,
The Massive Frop Show.
We'll probably be playing more of that next week
because they continue to have trouble
with those mosquitoes and callers
if they aren't the same.
Before that, that song,
You Might Be Next,
that was by Max Slack from a few years ago.
And the very first song we heard was,
the bluegrass song was
The Mutant Mountain Boys,
recorded live at X Day Drill
of the conspiracy named year 2014.
In a little while,
we'll be talking with Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
But before that, we'll listen,
well, I'm going to,
make you listen to the
Monster Hunter 4 Ultimate Rap Song.
But in the meantime,
back to Slack T.
Slepti.
Sleep.
Thank you.
My voice would have sounded better singing the backup on the Monster Hunter song.
I can hear you, but it sounded like you were on the other side of the room.
Aw, well.
I didn't really realize that that mic there isn't working.
I didn't realize that either.
The other mics are, but...
Yes, this one is apparently working.
Plankets are important.
Give me something.
Rubber blankets?
Yeah, I'll take a rubber blanket.
I'll take a number of them.
As many as you've got.
And even prosthetic, oh, like wooden prosthetic devices from the Crimean War.
Stuff like that, you know, where the originals, I mean, not the aborigines, but the generals.
Well, you know, Princess Wee was quoting a famous aphorism from the Book of the Subgenius
that was originally uttered by the late Dr. X.
It went like this.
I can't decipher anything.
Put me where you want me.
Give me rubber blankets.
I called it the drunkard's lament.
Because that was something he actually said.
Yes.
I was like, you know, come on, Dr. X, you gotta go.
I mean, it's time for bed.
People are already marking you up with markers because you're passed out at this party.
And he goes, I can't decipher anything.
Put me where you want me.
Give me rubber blankets.
Well, he was already familiar with rubber blankets.
And, you know, he went to New Jersey.
He went to the hometown institute for quite a few years.
He was also drummed out of the courts.
Oh, those are all rumors.
Yeah, but it was a regular rate.
So, you know, it didn't jar him too hard.
The fact that he wanted to join the Merleville's later and become a civilian autocrat after that
makes me wonder if he's from planet Earth.
Well, I got to get off this planet's kick.
I have a deep desire to jump ship tonight.
Get to some place where everything's...
There's glue and ego and...
Speaking of jumping ship or spaceship Earth,
actually, I have several things I could read from about that.
Remember last week we got this book of this dissertation by Reverend Lee Seifer
that was about the rhetorical ripples, Church of the Subgenius,
Kenneth Burke and comic symbolic tinkering?
I read...
Here's some more fancy talk.
Here's some more fancy talk and it involves the end of the world too.
Burke concludes that the result of this quantified rational order, that is civilization,
has been a crop of, quote,
new material and moral resources that after nearly half a millennium
seem to have been exploited to the point where they in turn are nearing their Malthusian limits, unquote.
Now...
Now, subgenius teaching in Revelation X acknowledges our impact on the environment
and urges us to imagine being exploited by satirically...
I gotta look up that word.
Satirically casting humanity as little more than toxin generators for exploitive intergalactic alien industry.
And then it's a quote from Revelation X that I probably read.
Oh, that guy was probably...
Probably artichoke back in 1978 when the project...
Over the aeons, aliens...
No, oh, this should be in my voice.
Over the aeons, aliens have been sending planets across the universe...
Let me start that again.
Take two.
Yeah, yeah.
Get in character.
Over the aeons, aliens have been seeding planets across the universe with humans.
There is tremendous intergalactic demand for planets having atmospheres ripe,
with deadly hydrocarbons, pollution, and heavy metal contaminants.
It was long ago and far away discovered that if one takes a nice virgin carbon-oxygen planet
of the right specifications, puts a few thousand humans on it,
and leaves it alone for a couple of hundred thousand years,
upon return, it will be a wonderfully contaminated hell planet,
a veritable cornucopia of synthetic poison.
The aliens then transfer the few surviving humans, the most ruthless ones,
to a fresh planet to begin the process anew.
Oh, yes.
Well, so the bad-doers, the evil-doers are kind of semi, like, immortal or something?
And also, I forgot what a Malthusian argument was.
Well, human intelligence and technological progress is such that we have an international space station
continually orbiting the Earth, and we have a spacecraft exploring beyond our solar system,
yet we continue to struggle with basic solvable problems, like environmental degradation.
Human intelligence has yet to keep our hubris in check
and prevent us from unnecessarily contaminating our only source of life.
Oh, well, we knew that, as Philo had the answer earlier in the show.
Unicorn juice.
Unicorn juice will run...
...run everything forever, peacefully, and without polluting.
That's right.
...safe for kids.
It's a beautiful substance, a milky kind of blue-green.
It's wonderful stuff.
Yes.
Unicorn juice.
Oh, yes.
Oh.
I find the juice machines to be quite reprehensible, though, and I was gonna call PETA or somebody.
Don't.
Don't call PETA.
No.
PETA is a very unhospitable kind of tyrannical and subterfuge in its tube.
Can you imagine stuffing a whole baby unicorn into its tube?
No, no, no, no.
The unicorn juice is an extract that is made from the urine of the unicorn.
What?
Yes.
Unicorn juice is an extract of the urine of the juice.
Of the...
I thought you milked the horn.
No.
No, no.
I thought you put one in your squisher and then, you know, just drain off the material
stuff and add the juice.
It's a distillation.
Anybody have a napkin or a glass of water?
A distillation.
I've got coffee in the other room.
Well, couldn't they conceivably, with nanotechnology, take that unicorn uterus and place it into
another much further and further away than the one that they already were talking to?
Because those guys get confused, especially when they're in those, like, sample groups,
you know, like at the mall.
Did you enjoy product so and so?
It's very wonderful.
Here, put, you know...
Is it like that?
Yes.
Try my tincture of unicorn horn juice.
Well, it would be like, did you find the unicorn...
Tincture of unicorn juice.
Lovable, smarmy, sweet.
You know, you check these different boxes.
And then you jump up and you start smashing the pen against the pad.
And you run out and you scream epithets.
And you say, I'm going to get a new one.
And you scream epithets as you leave.
Well, that's all beside the point because we're not going to get any unicorn juice.
All we're going to get is more Bab.
There's always more Bab out there.
Bab.
I have a little poem about Bab.
Poem?
Yeah, it was...
Are you mocking the northeastern Ohio accent, specifically the Buffalo...
No.
Buffalo...
I'm mocking all civilization.
This lady...
Bab.
This person, name of Ann Glenn, if that really is its name.
Boy, it could be Ann Glenn for all we know.
Now they're speaking of another headless wonder.
The book of the subgenius and decided to write a poem based on the book.
Now, so this is partly her...
This is her additions to the Bob chapter in Book of the Subgenius, okay?
And this is real cute.
I think y'all will like this.
Bob.
Okay.
Bob is the money a sucker spends.
He can be your toilet paper when you wipe your rear end.
Bob is war.
Bob is peace.
Bob is the president.
He's the Indian chief.
The key to the gateway is Bob's pipe.
He's the fool of the universe, a tomato that's overripe.
He's the laxative of the world.
He's victory without a battle.
Bob is the money.
Bob is a baby's rattle.
He is the great work that sleeps.
He's silence in the noise.
Bob is Santa Claus who brings good kids their toys.
Bob is the phoenix rising.
He's the black goat of the woods.
He's heaven's perfect policeman, a policeman in heaven's hoods.
He's the sucker born every minute.
He's the bank in which money is locked.
Bob is your neighborhood.
Bob lives on everyone's block.
He's companionship when no one is there.
He won't laugh when he sees you in your underwear.
Bob is the friend who will never let you down.
Bob is the circus.
Bob is a clown.
Bob is your dad.
Bob is your brother.
In a weird way, Bob is even your mother.
Bob is a rock.
Bob is a tree.
Bob is you.
And Bob is me.
Says Anne Glenn, quoting the Book of the Subgenius.
Book of the Subgenius.
Bob's your uncle.
Bob is your...
Oh, yeah, yeah.
She left that one out.
But that was, see, that wasn't, we didn't know about Bob's, Bob's uncle.
Bob's your uncle.
When we did the Book of the Subgenius.
Ah, I see.
That was because of the putrescence at the time.
You said you had a mole with a split hair on the end of it or something like that.
And that the, the Garbanians, or not the Armenians, but the real Garbanians had been making threatening
phone calls in your direction to try to get you to stop what you're doing in the Ministry
of Bob.
Yeah, well, they...
That's some serious stuff right there, especially if you're from Illinois.
Yeah.
Putrescence.
A putrescence, meaning it was not just putrescent, that it was an oozing thing itself of putrescence.
Yeah.
Dave, I had a quote from the news I wanted to run by you and run over you with it.
Okay, I'll slam.
Well, it was, I'm kind of paraphrasing a little bit.
But Paul Ryan, who's good at...
He's going to be running for president.
He was saying that basically that poor cities like Baltimore are stuck that way because
welfare pays too well.
In other words, the poor are so rich that they have no incentive to become...
Well, the whole thing, I'm just lost when I...
So am I.
It's too lucrative to be on welfare for them to get off welfare.
Now, I've heard...
I've heard that.
And so I always go, well, why don't you get on welfare?
And they go, well, because I don't want to live in a box.
But all I know is every time I see them buying fancy foods using food stamps and I can't
afford them fancy foods.
Well, it's like, why don't you get on welfare?
I don't want to live in a box.
But they're too rich.
It's like, well, look, they decided to spend their food on, I mean, spend their money on
sushi instead of a roof for their box.
Yeah.
And so, you know, it's one or the other.
I don't know.
All of life is a choice.
All I know is the poor are rich and the poor rich get blamed for it.
Those poor rich people.
I know.
It's really sad the way they treat rich people in this country.
The 1% are really, really caring, loving...
The 1%, you mean the subgeniuses?
No, not the subgeni.
Yeah.
Because subgeniuses are also only 1% of America.
And you know, America is 5% of the whole world's population.
And you know what makes us the greatest?
We've got one quarter of the entire world's jail population.
And that's what I like about it.
You and the Texans.
Have crazy people like, you know, come around and rattle their cages all the time, make
them do stuff, beat them up.
Of course, some of them are genuinely bad people, should be treated genuinely badly,
perhaps.
I don't know.
I'm not a sport when it comes to ethics and violations of morality.
But I do think one thing, if you accept Bob as...
What should we accept him as?
Bab?
Bab.
If you accept Bob as Bab...
Is that the way it goes?
Yeah, Bab.
You accept Bob into your mind.
Into your heart.
Into your heart and mind and soul.
Into your very being.
Down to your toes, where your feet can...
Any place you can find, like maybe in your hair, in the dendrites...
Oh, did I already talk about the dendrites in your head?
The spinal fluids.
Everywhere.
He's in our spinal fluid.
And that's all I got to say.
I'll bet you're lying about that, aren't you, Dave?
No, but I've been drinking a lot of spinal fluid lately, and I knew it would taste like.
If you know what I mean.
Well, I knew it wasn't all about spinal fluid.
It wasn't all you had to say, is what I'm saying.
Well, I know, but all those words didn't amount to a hell of anything.
That's what makes me want to cry.
But I don't know.
You were talking about subgenius soul, and that is in your foot.
So, what's the complication?
I don't get it.
No, there's no complication with that part whatsoever.
The soles of the feet is a wonderful place to hang the soul, so to speak.
But I think people who've actually hanged up some of their religious lives, they're
religious leaders in the future, in the past, to pay heed to where the soul is truly found.
I'll just make it short, you know, truly found.
That's just the bees keep at it every day.
I can dig that.
Princess, we went to one of them smoke-ins last Saturday.
Uh-huh.
She went to the...
I went to the normal rally.
She went over to the normal.
Yes, she went.
We went normal.
Princess, we went normal.
Yes.
You know, Mr. Sister, when he started reading my report on you going to the normal march,
he went, oh, no, it's gay and lesbian transgender stuff.
You're kidding.
No.
And then I explained at the end of it, by the way, normal means National Organization
for Reform of Marijuana Laws.
Good.
He can't even remember the acronyms.
When you take your finger and shove it in your ear canal...
Now, that hard, that's what happens to you.
And I hope nothing...
Well, no, he said, oh, it's marijuana.
Well, that's okay.
But see, let me clarify.
Well, it is okay, at least.
Princess, we don't care about marijuana.
We're froppers.
So we really...
Why would we mess with street drugs like that?
But, Princess, we did understand that the people at that festival would be part of the
audience that would be interested in the Starweed...
I mean, Starwood Festival.
The Starwood Festival, which happens to happen right after the world ends every year at the
same place where we gather for the end of the world at Wisteria Campground.
And in their case, it's the second week of July.
And it'll be held aboard my escape saucer, Dobbs Willing.
But if we got our dates wrong again, it'll be at the same campground as X Day, only they're
more hippies there.
Yeesh.
And that's why we weren't handing out X Day postcards at the free weed rally.
Not free weed.
Free the weed.
Yeah, free the weed.
But I understand.
I mean, there were people just smoking right out there on the street, weren't there?
Well, yes.
Did you see it?
That does happen.
I did see it.
Yes, I did.
That's where you're bailing, Mr. Hillman.
And you once again...
I tried to win the contest, the oregano rolling contest, and only this time.
Last year, she got second place.
But this year, she only got third place.
Oh, because the winner was so pretty.
That's what it was.
Well, she came in second.
Her sticks that she rolled were terrible.
They were really loose.
They were unusable.
Unusable.
But she was...
She was cute and young.
Right, and so, well, there you go.
So, I came in third instead of second.
Doggone it.
So rather than the speed of the rolling technique,
they were judging for the extreme beauty and the physical body marks and stuff like that?
No, not in theory, but in practice, that's what happens.
It would have to be both.
You have to be fast, and they have to be a usable, workable cigarette when you're done.
So you could produce neither because you have no experience with that.
You smoke frap out of one of those real long Tibetan monk pipes.
We pack it up our exit wounds.
The wounds that Bob gave us.
The blueness of the wound will not cleanse away the evil.
Don't you see?
No, smoking is bad for you.
We don't smoke.
Now, in Dallas, I read they had a march.
It ended up being peaceful by some miracle,
because listen to who all showed up for the Dallas protest.
Four different groups.
We're all ears.
One was Mothers Against.
That's police brutality.
Or MAPBABA.
MAPBABA.
Yeah, Mothers Against Police, you know, because there's a lot of that going around.
Well, the Immigration Reform Group, this is mostly Mexican-Americans, I think,
and their friends showed up, too, to protest for immigration reform the kind they like.
Now, I saw pictures of this rally,
and most of those people were on one side.
And they were all kind of skinny.
Now, also, there was the Back the Blue, a pro-police group,
you know, who have some sympathy for the tough life of a tough cop.
But also, because this is Texas,
the Open Carry activists showed up.
So you had a bunch of guys in combat outfits
with huge rifles and ammo packs slung across their backs,
parading back and forth across the street
from the street.
And the anti-police brutality.
Now, of course, they were part of that Operation Jive Mind or Jade Helm or whatever.
Jade Helm.
They were ready, as soon as the police showed up,
to herd everybody at gunpoint into the Walmart detention centers
and then run them through tunnels underground to the slave camps on the moon.
These guys were going to stop the cops
and anybody else who was an evildoer
because they're good doers carrying big, big guns.
Like they say, everyone should.
If kids in schools were packing,
you wouldn't have these school massacres.
I don't quite understand the logic.
It seems to me like you'd have one every recess.
But maybe kids are much more disciplined than I ever remembered.
Maybe. I don't know.
Yeah, maybe.
Reverend Fid Chooley had an answer for this.
I read about it.
About two minutes before we left, by the way.
Reverend Fid Chooley said,
less terrorism, more care-or-ism.
And he said, I'm going to hashtag that stuff
and put it on the internet and save the world
and make some money and maybe everybody will like me finally.
Less terrorism, more care-or-ism.
That should be a bumper sticker with a peace sign on one side
and a heart.
And a cute little Scotty dog in the middle.
What a drizzle bit.
You're allowed to say that, too, on the air.
Drizzle bit?
Yeah.
Actually, Reverend Fid Chooley had a whole rant
that I saw just before I left it.
I printed it out and I'm not going to read it
because we don't have time.
Well, we know the reason what we need,
what we need, what we need is for the aliens
to come and get us the hell out of here.
We don't need terror.
It's not even a real word.
It's a perfunctory item that's put into the language to make...
Well, you are...
Oh, perfunctory.
Listen, he's using big words now.
Perfunctory.
Now?
He always uses big words.
What are you talking about, Reverend Stang?
But it's perfunctory.
That's even...
That is kind of perfunctory, I guess, I suppose.
This is our Dave.
Oh, hey, here's a bad thing in that book, Dave.
Here's a bad thing in that giant book
about the Church of the Subgenius,
which, by the way,
you can find online.
Yes?
Well, sort of.
It starts talking about this radio show,
The Hour of Slack.
And it says,
named after Reverend Bucknaked's
1984 Naked Church newsletter,
The Hour of Slack is the most prolific
of subgenius productions.
That's actually not true.
With over 1,500 live broadcasts
beginning in October 1985
on KNON Dallas.
And continuing today,
I've got to wipe the book off,
on Cleveland on WCSB.
Yay!
Cleveland State Student Run.
Ooh, don't spit on this book.
It's inkjet.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
It's running on the word run.
Cleveland State Student Run radio station.
That word ran.
Reverend Ivan Stang is usually
the central host of the show,
along with Dr. Howell or Princess We,
Stang's wife.
Notice anything missing?
Notice anything missing there,
Lonesome Cowboy Dave?
Yeah, of course.
So, yeah.
We did.
Actually, the guy who wrote this book
asked me at one point, he says,
now, Philo Drummond,
is he the guy that's on the show
with you all the time?
And at that point, I thought,
this guy doesn't really listen to the show,
or he didn't then.
He probably is right now,
aren't you, Reverend Lee Seifer?
Anyway,
I wrote,
realized, no,
how could you think?
Of course, Philo was on the show tonight,
and Dr. Howell was on the show.
Yes.
And sometimes Dr. Howell is on the show
in this room.
Yes.
Around X days.
Sure.
For about 10 shows in a row.
But,
Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
let it now be stated
that since the year of 1991 or so,
when I first stumbled into this radio station,
led by Princess We,
and suggested,
suggested by the late Jeff Rosenbaum,
and I met the late,
God, everybody's dead,
the late Reverend Professor Chaz Smith,
Lonesome Cowboy Dave
was on his first hour of Slack.
And that was 1991.
How many years?
25 years.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave is the only person
who is even allowed to call the station
during the show minutes
of 9 to 10.
That is correct.
No one,
even if people even pick up their phone
and try to call the show,
their phone will explode
and blow them to smithereens.
Don't even try it, kids.
So, just so,
that's the first thing I'm getting straight.
He also seemed to think that Philo
had created the Puzzling Evidence Show.
Whereas actually the Puzzling Evidence Show
was created in 1982,
before the hour of Slack,
by who?
Who?
Puzzling Evidence.
Philo became a guest on Puzzling Evidence.
A co-host now, I suppose you could say,
after 25 years.
And Dr. Howell is another of those guests.
But the very first people
on what we would call the Puzzling Evidence Show
were neither of those worthies
but Puzzling himself,
yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang,
the great artist Palmer Vredes,
and maybe Gary Gabroga.
Gary Gabroga.
Who later became a major co-host
until he moved to Santa Cruz.
And Bob Nelson,
whose show it originally was,
which Puzzling Evidence
gradually eased into his own possession.
And yes, Princess Wee,
I know we are approaching the end times
of this end show.
The time everyone's been waiting for.
Well, I say that because I know that.
I said that last week,
and then I heard Puzzling Evidence said it.
Puzzling Evidence said it months earlier,
but I haven't seen it at the same time.
The moment everybody's been waiting for.
The end of this show.
This show, The Hour of Slack.
If you need more information,
please see subgenius.com on the internet.
And you can write to
PO Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Praise Bob.
I'm hoping now I can give out your phone number
and your own phone numbers.
And now we'll copy the Fire Sign Theater again
for those of you on drugs.
Yes.
Well, I guess Chris,
Chris, Cool Hand Chris's music ended
just as the show itself came to an end.
It was the perfection of timing.
That weird rumbling sound,
but I couldn't hear anything.
That weird rumbling sound ended.
Let's just put it that way.
And the weird rumbling sound was not a borborygmi.
But speaking of borborygmis,
it's showtime.
Borborygmi?
It's showtime.
Following show host has just entered the room.
Abandon hope all ye who enter here.
And you're listening to radio station
in the city of...
And...
What they're going to get into
when they start genetically modifying people from Cleveland
already full aware that it's DNA level C spelled backwards.
I know that's an old joke.
But just imagine,
it's just that's in the...
You know, they're going to try to do that
within 18 years.
I don't know why they get such a ridiculous spirit.
And this is because it's under 20,
but it's not over 25.
Hi, hi, hi, hi, hi, hi, hi, hi.
Hi, hi, hi, hi, hi, hi, hi, hi, hi.
Insane show.
And now we're signing off
for bigger and better things.
Oh, come on.
Don't try and butter me up.
Bigger and better things.
Come on.
Oh, you're moving on.
You're moving on for better things.
taller and louder things are on the way.
Much taller and slightly louder and much...
Your night's about to get better.
Mine's about to go in the toilet.
Far more intelligent.
Less deaf.
I'm still a subgenius.
Barely.
Okay, there goes Dave.
Barely qualified.
Dave, start talking while I fade you out.
I admit I missed the last two X days.
I just wanted to make sure that everybody was aware.
I'm here to get you.