Are you ready, eager young space cadet?
I'm a-a-a-a-a-a-all set, your hero ship, sir.
And now here comes the blind commissioner
Where the cannon in a stress
One hand is tied to the tightrope walker
The other's in his pants
And the riot squad, they're restless
They need somewhere to go
As the lady and I look out tonight from
DESOLATION
SUBSCRIBE
The Self Genius
Make sacrifice!
Look!
Look into the red eye
of your God!
Bob
Michele Agnolo
di Ludovico di Leonardo
di Buonarroti
Simone
Michelangelo
That was him
We forgive him because he is a genius
Whatever that means
Teabagging day
for the right wing
and they are going nuts
for it
Thousands of them whipped out
toothless
The teabaggers are full strong tongue lashing
and lick Bush and Reagan
under Reagan
That's teabagging in a nutshell
In a nutshell
Teabagging is a spontaneous uprising
uprising
The people who came up with it
are a familiar circle of Republicans
including former House Speaker Newt Gingrich
and former House Majority Leader Dick Armey
both of whom have firm support
from right wing financiers and lobbyists
as well as Washington prostitute patron
Senator David Vitter
Teabagging
Dick Armey
tight tight tight
back in Sean Hannity
Both are looking forward to an up close and personal
taste of teabagging themselves
back in Sean Hannity
Teabagging
got them confused with
Dick Armey
Teabagging all around the country
you're gonna need a
Dick Armey
Do you guys really
do you think about the multiple homicides
I mean
Honestly I don't
Do you think that maybe we're kinda weird
America's getting a little weird
I think America's always been weird
Well they've been having multiple homicides
all over the civilized world
America's too damn normal
Healthy people have a need for
Hookers for Jesus
Prostitute, stripper, what have you
I went to Sunday school
I went to the gym
I had a lot of issues going on
MTV
and pop culture
I was living the life I had a pimp
and I OD'd on cocaine
I had a blast it was really fun
I can't even count
and now I reach out to prostitutes
Hairy, horny in my imagination
writhing on the floor
all over the world
my mom and dad manifested horny, freaky, scary
the psychosis, the pathological fear
People, people canceled history
very good
God, he wants automatons
Automatons, he wants
Bang, bang
totally
How come we have these ideas
that are so mythical
that are so primitive
Why don't you
um
I have to dance
Drink beer
Him, or her or it
and Hitler
who also believed in Jesus
and thought he was doing God's will
I went to Sunday school
Fem lui mes nas
It seems like if Jesus was going to show up somewhere, it wouldn't be an ice cream.
But maybe he's everywhere.
He'd show up anywhere.
Sweet Jesus.
I don't see her.
I don't either, but it's still a good story.
It's a good story.
I see it on the toast.
I see it on the cat.
I saw it on Cheetos.
Butter.
Trees.
Potato chip.
A mint.
Remember the mint and squirrel?
Oh, yeah.
Maybe that was Jesus.
I forget.
Yeah, we see it at ice cream, grilled cheese, on trees, roadways.
Awesome.
You can see it in the sunrise and the sunset.
In Emmy's eyes, you can see it in that way.
But what a feeling.
In your heart.
In storms.
When you're storm chasing, you're out there.
God's control.
You treat Jesus like a box lunch.
Go ahead, say it.
Holy fuck.
Look, if you don't turn your face away,
I'm the looking glass you see like you see yourself in.
Uh-Uhhh, Ahhhhh!
Mama's raging.
Nobody can kick the butt of Jesus Christ.
He's the King of Kings and the Lord of Lords.
That's gone over the line.
My life is just one big joke.
I don't think your life is a joke.
Yeah, well...
I'm sorry if I don't trust your sense of humor.
You få' schedule miubaò su Regыт!
便nas
Thank you.
That's gone over the line.
Well, that tender moment.
Adopts, adopts, adopts, adopts.
Pleasure.
We started talking.
And we talked.
Keeping the most important thing, the most important thing.
You was precious to me.
Yeah.
Stay at home.
You have.
Well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well.
I didn't know why I was crying.
And it's just crazy.
If you don't know what's going on, it's not comfortable.
Rubbing her.
Her bi mommy.
What, what, what, what?
That feeling.
Balls.
I have no value.
Axe.
Hey, well, let's talk about the other problem.
I'm so happy.
I think it's one of the best things that could have happened to this country.
Yes.
I think of women.
Women.
Women who ache to do.
To do.
Prophylactic.
Yes.
Those mothers.
I always suggest when they're in these situations to swallow.
To remedy the situation.
And things.
Shock.
Ball.
Being greedy.
It is.
I was finishing up my patient.
Subgirl.
And you know what?
Boy, I got a lot of hate.
Got a lot of hate.
And then I got.
Put a lot of money in the bank.
Money in the bank.
In the bank.
People.
Meaning and fulfillment.
Don't make babies.
Babies.
Come.
Every.
You're right.
You're absolutely nuts.
It's true.
People.
Squash it.
Rip it up.
Scribble on it.
Throw it away.
Experience it.
You know, I love being a mother.
Oh.
Boys need.
Women can get a little piece.
Ooh.
Evidently came in the pool.
The mothers.
Yeah.
I.
Hmm.
We're all doing it.
A couple of times.
You know, maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe I'm wrong.
Ha ha.
The mummy.
Mummy.
And there's a lot of resentment and anger.
And.
Uh.
Ha ha ha.
I.
We had to come.
S.
Got it.
Well.
My.
Butt.
Touched.
You feel sexy.
Having sex.
Want women to be sex slaves.
Sex time.
So.
Really.
Feel like a man.
And frankly.
And Frank.
He will eat out of your.
So when women are.
Ha ha ha.
App.
That's nutty.
Yeah.
Isn't that nutty?
Don't you think that's nutty?
Nutty.
I like being told.
I like.
Very open.
I didn't have a relationship.
Cult woman.
Uh.
Very narcissistic.
Very hard.
I feel bad.
Rob yourself.
Hmm.
Yes.
Ha ha ha.
And as we rep.
Rep.
Now sex is nothing simple such as smoking or lie.
I see a lot of goodness in a teasing glance of thine.
I think I'll reevaluate lascivious behavior and declare this incarnation a new pro-sex
kind of savior.
Libido is a freaky thing.
I find it fairly vexing.
And sure it's true it's cooler when you love the gal you're sexing.
But horny pairs who wish to share in hopping in the sack-o are twice as blessed as them
still dressed in holy ipso facto.
Guys and gals and guys and guys and gals and gals.
Amen.
One at a time or two or nine.
I'm thinking.
One at a time.
The birds, the bees, the dogs, the fleas, the meek ones like the rabbit.
All like their fun.
So what's up, nun?
How about you drop that habit?
Now you do think I'm mischievous and lack erotic powers.
But I've had a few direction and it kept me nailed for hours.
The point I make and what to take.
You have a chance.
Don't lose it.
matured於
G todo uma médio
Luigui
demó
Pum was lost.
E avemos morido?
Cantuamos.
Rápido!
otz serious.
Poor dinosaurs lost their jobs, but we do have dinosaurs here as members of the panel.
So I want to start with, well I curse the ground because of man.
I'll destroy all living members of the clergy.
I believe that's the infallible word of 24, and that's the way it's going to be.
This time to be over.
Destroy the theological, religious beliefs.
Perfect.
And I do appreciate that.
What is there about frozen water that makes you think one religion is more true than another?
What's it going to be, eh?
Is it going to be in and out of institutions like this?
Or are you going to attend to the divine word?
The subgenius.
Power of the subgenius.
This is some new form of torture.
Say it, brother sir.
I hope to God it'll torture you to madness.
And how's that working out?
I hope it's working out for you, listener.
Thanks for that intro, and for the first intro, Mr. Leemur, for this hour of Slack number 1201,
which is on the theme of Jesus and X-Day coming.
Because they are.
Our biggest subgenius annual gathering at Brushwood Folklore Center near Sherman, New York,
on July 5th weekend and the prior week, which happens also to coincide with the end of the planet Earth.
More about that soon, but first, credits.
Going back in time, the bluegrassy song about the pro-sex savior is from a movie called Ultra Christ.
Look it up.
There were some clips from the 2007 movie Cthulhu.
The collages that mostly didn't have music were by the great Nor El Pref of norelpref.com,
while the more musical collages were by Phineas Narco and National Cynical Radio.
Available at nationalcynical.com.
Those would include the mashup of My Life with the Thrill Kill Cult with Phil Hendry, called Cooler Than Hendry,
and the one about the black and white Jesus, which was Phil Hendry versus Michael Jackson.
From nationalcynical.com.
As is this next piece, My Watts, smushing Gary Neumann into Alan Watts.
Starring the famous
Oh, use me, Jesus. Use me.
Now, you see, if you were brought up in the Bible Belt,
you came out of Arkansas somewhere and that's all the religion you knew,
and you had a mystical experience of the type where you suddenly discover that you are one with God.
then you're liable to get up and say, I'm Jesus Christ.
And lots of people do.
Well, the culture that we live in just can't allow that.
There's only one Jesus Christ.
And sort of you don't look like you were Jesus Christ coming back again
because it's said in the scriptures that when he comes back,
there'll be no doubt about it.
He'll appear in the heavens with legions of angels,
and you're not doing that.
You're just old Joe Doakes that we knew years ago,
and now you say you're Jesus Christ.
Well, he says that when Jesus Christ said he was God,
nobody believed him, and you don't believe again.
You know, you can't answer that argument.
But you see, he says it that way
because he is trying to express what happened to him
in terms of a religious language which is circumscribed by the Holy Bible.
He's never read the Upanishads.
He's never read the Diamond Sutra.
He's never read the Tibetan Book of the Dead or the I Ching or the Lao Tzu.
And therefore, there is no other way in which he can say this.
But if he had read the Upanishads,
he would have had no difficulty,
and nor would the culture, the society in which he was talking,
have any difficulty.
Because it says in the Upanishads,
we are all incarnations of God.
Only they don't mean by the word.
In fact, they don't use that word.
They use Brahman.
They don't mean the same thing that a Hebrew meant by God.
Absolutely not.
The Brahman is not personal.
Brahman is, we would say, suprapersonal.
Not impersonal, because that is a negation.
But I would say suprapersonal.
Brahman is not he or she.
Has no sex.
Brahman is not the creator of the world.
As something underneath and subject to Brahman.
But the actor of the world.
The player of all the parts.
So that everyone is a mask.
Which is the meaning of the word person.
In which the Brahman plays a role.
And like an absorbed actor,
the divine spirit gets so absorbed in playing the role,
as to become it.
And to be bewitched.
And this is all part of the game.
The mission at hand.
The mission as part of the game.
This game is released, that is to go with,
Pokemon.
For Viola.
For
I'm ready
This
The
Game
This
So
Is it?
All my life, I have believed in nothing.
VapRDude, thank you so much.
She is not, she is not at her office.
So if she is not here and she is not there.
Use everything, leave nothing.
Use everything.
Leave nothing.
Why did those things happen?
Howard Amos, The Howard Amos Show.
Is that them?
Is it?
Good afternoon. Thank you so much.
The devil.
Welcome to hell.
He goes by many names.
Satan, Lucifer, Mephistopheles, Beelzebub, Old Nick.
Let's not forget Ryan Seacrest.
I wish I could.
Hello, you're on the air.
I think the idea of the IBM people,
that is, if you can call them people.
The irritable bowel movement?
See, I was going to say that,
and you knew I was going to say that,
so I didn't say that.
I was waiting until a time when it would be,
well, I actually forgot for a brief moment,
but I was thinking maybe incalculable,
impacted, innocuous,
incubus is the one I settled on
because I thought it would show the otherworldliness of it.
Or an international bowel movement.
That's what happens when you're on an airplane crossing the ocean
or perhaps if you're taking a tour of the UN
and have to use the facilities.
Hey, Senator, I just realized you got a line.
Did you know that?
I'm sorry, Rockner, what?
You've got all your lines tied up.
Stan's trying to call back.
I want to free up a line.
All right, well, thank you for calling.
All right, talk to you later.
Thanks, Rockner.
Here's the sad thing about what's happening.
I hit the wrong button.
All right, well, Buddha, sorry I hung up on you, too.
You hung up on the actual compassionate one himself?
Buddha's not that compassionate.
He doesn't care.
He'll keep calling you back and calling you back
and hoping you get it.
Hey, I actually saw a video of a cow
eating a baby duck the other day.
Was it a zombie cow?
No, this was a real cow.
It's on that YouTube website there.
And it made me think a lot about Buddhism.
Well, it does make you think of Buddhism,
but at the same time, you can't really, you know,
in your mind's eye, see the compassionate one as a zombie, can you?
If you came back to life.
If you came back, well, there you go.
That's all beyond religion, for sure.
That's the thing.
We're all kind of, like, covered in this zombie glaze right now.
So it's hard to really tell who's illuminated from without
and who's illuminated from within because we're all shiny from it.
I, for one, welcome our new zombie overlords.
I do believe that zombies are our morals.
We're all superiors in every way.
I also carry a flashlight, so illumination's easy.
Did you hold it under your chin and go,
I want to eat your brain?
Stuff like that?
Sure, why not?
Well, it looks cool.
Well, that's about all it does, though, unfortunately.
It just scares some children and causes some weird little nervous pomeranians
to bark real loud and stuff.
I can think of no higher calling.
Fear can be a path to illumination.
Well.
Was Rocknard talking about the defecation of our economic system?
I think it was pre-defecated.
It was pre-defecated?
Just like that cow regurgitating that duck.
That's what you didn't see.
That's what you YouTube guys never see,
is when the duck is actually back in the cow's mouth and it's...
Never mind.
Maybe the duck was trying to eat the cow.
How does a cow digest a duck, you know what I mean?
Do they have to, like, you know, chew its cud on a duck?
Yeah.
I wonder.
And besides, since they don't really digest things in their stomach,
that duck, I mean, they don't...
Probably got puked up later.
Yeah.
That duck wanted a burger.
He had a plan.
The duck probably had a little bit of burger while it was down there waiting
because they have two stomachs.
Not ducks.
I mean, ducks only have one that I know of.
But cows have two stomachs, and one is, like, where the cud goes
and waits until it's something else, and then it goes to something else.
Only two?
I thought it was, like, four.
Really?
I don't know.
I'm not sure how many stomachs.
I don't want to say.
They're multi-bowled and multi-stomached.
Just like the multinationals that are moving.
Like, IBM is actually moving to China, or they want to.
The, uh...
Oh, gosh, what's that?
Lenovo.
Lenovo, that's the new spin-off.
That's the spin-off company that makes the computers now that IBM used to make.
It's a Chinese company.
Yeah.
So the, um...
But as far as digestive tract comparing mammals to birds,
I'm glad we don't have cloacas.
I'm glad it has made...
Heaven happy that the emperor will also be happy.
Yes.
Father, son, holy cow!
Well, well
Moses went up to the mountain high
To find out from God why did you make us?
Why?
Secret words in a secret room
He said, wop, bop, a-loo, bop, a-lop, bam, boom
I did not put you here to suffer
I did not put you here to whine
I put you here to love one another
And to get out and have a good time now, now, now
Let my people go, go, go
You gotta let my people go, go, go
You gotta let my people go
Yeah
Josh and Victor battle in Jericho
He tell the boys with the horns
Get down and blow
They rear back, aim their bells at the stars
He said, wop, bop, a-loo, bop, a-lop, bam, boom
I did not put you here to suffer
I did not put you here to whine
I put you here to love one another
And to get out and have a good time now, now, now
Let my people go, go, go
You gotta let my people go, go, go
You gotta let my people go
What'd I say?
Now, when Jesus went out for a walk with his mother
The scribes and the Pharisees
Plotting hugger-mugger
They locked him up and they threw away the key
He said, why is everybody always picking on me?
I did not put you here to suffer
No, I did not put you here to whine
I put you here to love one another
Yeah, I said, now, get out and have a good time now, now, now
Let my people go, go, go, go
You gotta let my people go, go, go
Let my people go, go, go
Sing in time...
The Bible does.
Bugs Bunny, Roadrunner, it's fairytale, and I don't believe that is the case.
Everything is one.
And that gives me great joy because...
What? What?
That is irrational, that is primitive.
Uncreative, fuck, fuck, up and down, hot, hot, fuck you.
Actually, yes.
As best as man, as best as man.
Totally irrelevant to me, I'm just being honest with you because I experienced my life.
And, and, um, dumb, dumb, no one boy, you know, it's not going to work for you.
It's, it's not the truth.
And making things up, upside down.
Let's create a religion.
Eating chicken wings.
Belief is a cover-up for insecurity.
All belief is a cover-up.
For insecurity.
And the most fervent believers in the world are the cause of all the problems in the world right now.
You know?
You know, who causes their own mess?
Ignorance.
Some boogeyman out there.
Choose evolution or entropy.
And our boogeyman is Bob.
Friends, thanks to Noral Pref for that cut as well as the next two to come.
And the song before that, Let My People Go, was the one song by The Rain.
And it was a hit.
It was the first hit of the kind that ever became an actual, what you would call, hit.
One hundred years ago is when that happened.
Prior to that and more coming up was and is from Radio Synesthesia on WCSB Cleveland.
Hosted by Dr. Sinister with call-in guests Lonesome Cowboy Dave, Dr. Aganfly, and yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang.
The music in the background is by The Amino Acids, who will be at next day.
But now, I must ask you.
Oh!
Oh, many of you out there by radio truly believe in that man J.R. Bob Dobbs as your short-nuration personal savior.
Ten percent of us believe that there is, believe that there is a God.
We seem to be pushed around.
Don't believe in God.
Worship a broom.
I could really worship a broom.
Remove God from, from America entirely and, uh, you can't even now use the, use the word.
I ain't forcing it down your throat.
I don't care what you believe in.
Religion.
Warp their minds.
Here's Dobbs.
Hello, Dobbs.
Dobbs.
Goofy.
I like Dobbs.
That's crazy.
Sit and think.
Game, game, game, game, game, game, game.
Eliminate.
You know, Dobbs, Dobbs, Dobbs, Dobbs.
Oh, I'm traumatized.
Our rights come from Dobbs if you eliminate Dobbs.
Uh, it, and, uh.
Everything is rap, rap, rap.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, humanity.
Dobbs, Dobbs, Dobbs, Dobbs.
Ted Bundy.
I remember being a kid with Ted Bundy.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Well, I did.
Ted Bundy.
Pornography.
He wanted me to come.
Got a dick.
Dick.
Pornography.
Pornography continues.
Dobbs, Dobbs.
Thank you very much.
Goofy.
I like Dobbs.
Hey, why don't you guys come have lunch with Bob and me?
We'll take all afternoon.
Michael is terrified of Bob.
What do you think?
I have a lot of work to do this afternoon.
Those minds aren't going to sweep themselves.
We're in.
I have sent for you, Dodgers, because we are facing a crisis.
The world's supply of Illudium Fosdex, the shaving cream atom,
is alarmingly low.
Now, we have reason to believe that the only remaining source is on Planet X.
The old world is dying and we are giving birth to the new.
Look!
They come!
But I really need you to tell me what's going on here.
I'm not allowed.
These people are freaks, man.
They're friggin' cuckoo.
Vic, look.
You need to relax, all right?
I'm sorry.
Can you tell me what the mission is?
The teacher says we were chosen.
Chosen?
What does that mean?
When the sun comes up in the morning, the teacher is going to take us to the new world.
He says we can live there forever.
And where is this place?
On the other side of the universe.
Did you hear that, man?
This is some kind of...
Frickin'...
Hail Bob or Bob or some kind of Heaven's Gate kind of suicide cult, man.
Freaks!
Vic!
Please!
Libby.
Libby, did the teacher tell you how he was going to take you there?
We will come to X-Day!
Shut up, pink boy.
That was actually the fr-
I don't mean you.
The listener.
Those were the first-
First transmissions we received from Planet X.
Tuned into a CB car radio in Dr. Drummond's Bobmobile.
At random.
Randomly scanning the channels, we heard those fateful words.
Shut up, pink boy.
And so they shall shut up.
On July 5th, 1998.
Which could be any second now.
Although it's convenient for us.
To just name July 5th of every year.
To remind us to ask ourselves.
Am I ready?
Or did I just come to X-Day because I thought it was a funny joke?
Oh yeah.
Bob's take off on other crackpot religions.
Yeah.
He was just making fun of the Jehovah's Witnesses.
Heaven's Gate.
Uh huh.
Or Jim Jones.
Speaking of which.
Children.
Take the Kool-Aid.
On 7 AM.
So many of you come to X-Day.
You come so far.
From many distant climes.
And yet.
At 7 AM.
There are so few who've been able to withstand the hangovers.
And the travails of the night before.
So few professional X-Day goers.
Who've actually dragged their asses.
Out at 6 30 in the morning.
Every X-Day.
On the other hand.
Some of you drag your asses out of bed at 6 30 in the morning.
Every god damn day.
I am not one of those.
Anymore.
And so.
When I get up at 6 30 on X-Day morn.
To come down here to the pavilion at 7 AM.
And await the saucers in faith.
And I keep up the FIB.
The faith in Bob.
I feel that I'm.
You know how Jesus died for the sins.
And Bob wears polyester for the sins of the pinks.
I get up at 7 AM.
Or 6 30 AM.
Once a year.
Because I'm thinking of you poor suckers.
That have day jobs.
And when we talk about the excess friends.
We're not talking about your.
Flying saucers.
Made of metal.
That crash in New Mexico.
And get reverse engineered.
By the Z-Rocks corporation or what not.
No sir.
We're not talking about.
We love to talk about the saucers arriving.
But the excess are so advanced.
They don't even need bodies.
They're so advanced.
They don't even need money.
And yet.
They take it anyway.
Like Bob.
Bob doesn't need money.
He only needs your belief.
And how can he.
How can that belief be proved.
Until you are willing.
To give up.
The thing that's most important to you.
More important than your parents.
Your children.
Your brothers and sisters.
Your money.
Well that's wonderful.
That means we can get off.
No you can't.
Why have you stayed hidden from us all this time?
Because contact with my own species has always disappointed me.
Solitude gives me freedom of mind.
And independence of action.
Why have you picked this particular town.
And time to interrupt this solitude.
I'll tell you.
I don't believe personally in aliens.
I mean.
Do you?
I don't think it's a question of whether or not you believe in aliens.
I think if you believe in aliens or.
I think it's obvious that there's other life forms out there.
I don't think it's a belief system really.
It's not really obvious that there are other.
It's not a planet that can support life.
It's not obvious that there are other life forms out there.
It's obvious that the possibility is very real.
And that the universe is vast.
And you know.
What is life?
How do we define life?
There's definitely no zero.
Self replicating molecules that.
There's definitely no zero probability of it.
It has to exist somewhere.
But the vastness of space is just so vast.
That it makes it very theoretically challenging.
It's one of those questions that we are not equipped to answer right now.
Oh no.
I can answer their question.
They will come on July 5th 1998.
Whenever you want.
Whenever that is.
It's that simple.
I think once in a while you just rip in and just laying out exactly where them X's come
from.
And what their real, real, real, real agenda is.
Which you so well espoused throughout these years.
What year is it in the year?
But we rarely hear this in an ectoplasmic of spirit.
I mean an auditorium.
You know on the public platform.
Like that.
I tell you if you can get arrested for doing that on a public platform.
That's been a problem at various X days.
People wanting to commingle with various.
That only happened once.
The infamous floating object in the hot tub.
That was a one time thing.
I can tell you this though.
Turned out to be a Baby Ruth candy bar.
If you know a band.
If you hear about a band called the Date Rapists.
Don't invite them to your party.
Oh my God.
I think everybody who remembers getting invited to a pool party.
When they were younger and stuff.
Did have a sudden urge to go.
Just as soon as you hit the water.
Just as if it was something that you were meant not to do.
That you had to suddenly do.
You know some existential angst had taken you over.
And you're just like.
I'm going to put a Tootsie Roll in this pool.
Just because I'm not supposed to.
It's like the big red button that says do not press this button.
Yep.
The shiny candy bar.
You can't press the big red button.
Do not press.
The history erase button.
Right here.
Yeah.
Doug is here to see you.
Yeah I'll be right out.
Okay.
That'll be just one minute.
Doug.
Bob.
Good to see you.
Come on in.
It's through here.
Now help me out here Doug.
You were interested in a memory of.
Yeah.
Mars.
To be perfectly honest with you Doug.
If outer space is your thing.
I think you would be much happier with one of our Saturn cruises.
Everybody raves about them.
Okay.
You're the boss.
Mars it is.
Now let me see.
Basic Mars package will run you 899 credits.
Now that's for two full weeks of memories.
Complete in every detail.
If you want a longer trip that'll cost you a little more because it's a deeper implant.
Well first of all Doug let me tell you when you go recall you get nothing but first class
memories.
Private cabin on the shuttle.
Deluxe suite at the Hilton plus all the major sites.
Mount Pyramid.
The Grand Canal.
And of course.
Venusville.
As real as any memory in your head.
No I'm telling you Doug.
Your brain will not know the difference.
And that's guaranteed.
Or your money back.
I claim this planet in the name of Mars.
Isn't that lovely?
It's great to talk to you Sang.
It's been a while.
I was actually working.
Oh you must be the guy with the bob shark.
I'm Dr. Agonfly.
I think you're the guy with the bob shark.
I think you might remember me.
Oh oh oh oh oh okay yeah.
No I didn't recognize your voice over the phone but uh.
I think we had a cup of coffee at uh some sort of uh subgenius festival one time.
Some sort of coffee?
Yeah yeah sure.
I bet you haven't made it to Cali yet.
I don't know I remember how you uh.
Some sort of.
You're in San Angelo now huh?
Yeah I'm on my way to Ex Day actually.
I've already begun my trip.
I will be doing the subgenius couch crashing tour on the way.
Oh my god.
That's a long trip.
That's a long way.
Well well at least somebody's coming to Ex Day.
Yep.
This is going to be a quiet one I think.
Everybody's broke.
Maybe you'll get one of the multiple homicide guys.
Everybody heard I was coming too.
You know the the going postal guys will come to Ex Day and expect to find more than three
people there sleeping in the sun while somebody's ranting.
I keep expecting a going postal guy you know I mean and I suspect we're not I'm not the
only one who kind of has that.
I expect a going postal guy but by definition those guys always kill all the wrong people.
Well yeah.
So I know I'd survive.
Yeah well maybe you should offer that as some kind of commercial you know PR thing come
to Ex Day there's no chance that one of those guys you're gonna well no wait maybe.
You know the very first Ex Day somebody uh right at the end of the festival I was up
there blathering away thanking people for being there and somebody got tired of it and
walked up on stage pulled out a handgun.
Pointed at me.
Pointed it at me and shot.
And of course it was merely a starter pistol and it was Dr. Legume.
But I fell down and the funny thing is nobody did a thing the musicians didn't stop playing
or anything.
The show must go on.
It was a perfectly realistic death scene and then and then everybody just stood there it's
like man.
When Bob got shot it was a huge uproar.
Oh no Bob shot.
Everybody was screaming and yelling and gnashing their hair and pulling their teeth out.
For one thing you're not Bob.
But second of all.
I knew Bob and you're no Bob.
But second of all why would anybody be disturbed by Bob getting shot.
Gosh he'll be fine.
He'll be just fine.
Well I mean it was yeah sure he was asking for it but um but you don't know what it's
like when you know when you actually see somebody get shot that's a pretty traumatic event.
Stan you gotta remember you at that time you were in the ages of squibs and uh and uh
center flies and all kinds of like uh you know acoustical ceilings that's not a real
gunshot sound there you know that's that's a cap gun or something.
No look man I was at Dealey Plaza I know what a real shooting looks like.
But there were no there were no blood bags no squibs you know there were no no shooting
out any any uh plasma on the floor of the place.
I was in the basement of the Dallas jail when Lee Harvey got shot man.
I know what it's like I know what physical violence is like and you just don't.
You were what all of 10 years old then?
You don't just lay there and well I guess you know at X Day I can see how they'd just
they'd be so full of flack they'd go oh look somebody just got killed oh well.
Oh well who cares X Days are coming the future looks grin as Reverend Sodi said on
allthoughtslack.
What we just heard was of course radio synesthesia.
From WCSB Cleveland before that many clips and uh Clutters.
From Noro Pref, Mr. Sister, Neuromancin, uh the movies Believers, Mysterious Island, Total
Recall and Cthulhu or pronounced Cluloo.
Which we also have to thank along with Sweetness McGee for this preview of the upcoming X Day
12.
I implore you not to turn away.
The most wonderful thing in the world.
The most wonderful thing you could ever imagine.
Eternal life.
And in the hall of Cthulhu we shall dwell forever.
I trust we've managed to plumb an heir out of you.
I cared for your mother a great deal.
But what's two years on a life or 10 or even a hundred when it's not going to last anyway.
I'm sorry.
Our bodies will last a hundred thousand years in the sea.
They drive and drive the highways we built even though it's destroying their world.
Great Cthulhu carries us.
They keep moving, searching.
They look into his eye for it.
All they have is the moment and they can't bear it.
They can't bear our death.
the loneliness of it.
When the waters rise into their cities,
everything shall be ours with you to lead us, my glorious son.
Oh, the sick room.
Oh, the air. The air is almost unbreathable.
No clothes on.
Gaunt.
Vacant eyes.
Oh, rose.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Betrayed.
More than they do.
They're gonna bring them to the factory
with a heart attack machine.
It's strapped across their shoulders
and in the car seat.
It's brought down from the castles
by the insurance men who go
just to see that no one is escaping
to desolation row.
Joe.
I'm talking to you. You're listening to me.
What's the answer?
Ten little words for my name.
You're giving up quicker than usual, Tony.
Just tell me the goddamn word.
Palindrome.
Your name's a palindrome.
What's that? Huh?
You making fun of me?
Is that something bad?
Spelled the same way forwards and back.
It's like the phrase,
Madam and Eden, I met him.
It's a palindrome.
And it's the same way it begins.
Oh, I get it.
So it's like the name Bob.
That's one too, right?
Is this the ghost milk hotline?
You're listening to the emergency broadcast system.
Please be advised, this is not a test.
Violence is taking place in post-heteronormative...
There's a lady buying a stairway.
What's the matter with you? Come on!
I'm sorry.
Joe!
Oh.
When you fall asleep before the end of the day
You start to worry
Like when a taxi comes to take you away
When you're in nowhere
Up at high into the sky
All the stars still shine so bright
Above
At least
It's not on the other world
It's not the end of the world
We can live in a barge
Because there's one way out at once
Let's make a difference
Turn all the hate in the world
Into a walking bird
Make it fly away
As the light turns grey
Everything is far from
A-A-A-OK
At least
It's not on the other world
Not the end of the world
Nothing
Never
A-A-A-O
At least
It's not on the other world
Not the end of the world
Way, way, way, way
This is nothing
When people fraud
The participation
Till the night
The world is a fine place and worth fighting for.
I agree with the second part.
Good morning! Are you injured?
The Lord knows why, but it seems not.
A miracle. I expect you'd like to use my phone.
Thanks, I would.
Well, it's right in there.
All right, all right.
So, what are you babbling about?
The world's an imperfect place.
What? Over?
Did you say over?
Uh, yes, friends, Hour of Slack is almost over for this week.
The world itself ends July 5th, 1998,
but salvation is available through the Church of the Subgenius and J.R. Bob Dobbs.
The song mix we just heard,
Imagine the End of Time,
The world was by The Kleptones.
That's Kleptones with a K, as in K-L-E-P-Tones.com.
Before that, Lemur, Cthulhu, The Large,
and the Desolation Row clip was by My Chemical Romance.
You can learn more about Bob and X-Day from subgenius.com,
or you can write for free information from a post office box,
1-8-1-4-1.
7 Cleveland Heights, Ohio, 44118.
Once again, that's box 1-8-1-4-1-7,
Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
The zip code is 44118.
The background music is The Amino Acids
from their incredible, horrifying album,
Humanity Will Fall Like Pins.
Praise Bob.
In a moment, Lemur.
In a moment, The Planet Man.
The Planet Man.
This is the fascinating story of The Planet Man.
The Planet Man, victim of his own evil,
was himself poisoned by FEMA,
but though badly wounded, he is alive, planning revenge.
US zoomed in on the
horrifying ещё film.
The Planet Man named,
The End
Well, I have to go in now. Goodbye.
31110, 13, 13, 13, 130, 13, 13, 13, 13, 13, 1110, 10, 10, 130, 13.