You could just see there were a lot of things going wrong in the world
and nobody was saying anything about it.
You know, Bob had long since faded from the present memory.
Iron Man is a great story, you know, revenge.
And when I heard that story, I'm like, yeah.
Khan, coming up in just a couple of days.
Yes.
All right.
And I know I've already been told that I'm to refer to it as the Khan.
You call it the Khan.
I mean, you can call it Khan.
You can call it the Khan.
No, I had a nerdy guy say, don't call it Khan.
You must call it the Khan.
He called it the Khan.
He's going to call it the Khan for now on.
You think they're playing a joke on me?
Because I'm going to the Khan in a couple of days.
I'm going to make a little appearance there.
And I thought maybe you could.
Tell me what to expect because I've never been.
Everybody talks about it.
And I know that this is your thing.
This is your wheelhouse.
I like Khan.
There's a lot of things there that I like.
And most of the shows that I make or have gotten involved with.
The Self-Genius Power of Squash.
Goodbye, Bobby.
Oh, great.
It's the Bob Twins.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It hasn't been a good day.
If I don't get to the top of the mountain real soon, I could get fired.
Friends, Dr. Howland Owl,
the toast of,
of stage, screen, and radio in San Francisco and New York City,
many other places.
We are so gifted to be,
to have him here with us.
Welcome, dear friends.
Because we truly can answer any question.
But I believe while,
while you try to attempt to come up with something to stump Dr. Howell,
I believe he will be doing a recitation of some kind.
That's correct, Ivan.
We begin and end,
with a recitation at this show.
And others often crop up in the middle.
But being not the middle, but the beginning,
the best way to proceed toward the end
is to start what we are going to do.
Leviathan.
This is the black sea brute,
bulling through wave rack,
ancient as oceans shifting hills,
who in sea toils traveling,
who, furrowing,
the salt acres heavily,
shoulders spouting,
the fist of his forehead,
over wastes gray-green crashing,
among horses unbroken,
from bellowing fields,
past bone wreck of vessels,
tide ruin,
wash of lost bodies,
bobbing,
no longer sought for,
and islands of ice gleaming,
who ravening the rank sea flood,
wave marshalling,
overmastering the dark sea marches,
finds home and harvest.
Frightening to foolhardiest mariners,
his size were difficult to describe.
The hulk of him is like hills heaving,
dark yet as crags of drift ice,
crowns cracking in thunder,
like land's self by night black looming,
surf churning and trailing along his way,
his shores rushing,
shoal water boding,
about the dark of his jaws.
And who would moor at his edge,
and fare on a foot,
would find gates of no gardens,
but the hill of dark,
underfoot diving,
and closing overhead,
the cold deep and drowning.
He is called Leviathan,
and named for rolling.
First created he was of all creatures,
he has held Jonah three days and nights.
He is that curling serpent that in ocean is,
sea-fright he is,
and the shadow under the earth.
Days there are, nonetheless,
when he lies like an angel,
although a lost angel,
on the wastes unease,
no eye of man moving,
bird hovering,
fish flashing,
creature, whatever,
who after him came to herit earth's emptiness.
Froth that flanks seething,
soothes to stillness, waits.
With one eye he watches dark of night,
sinking last.
With one eye day rise,
as at first over foaming pastures.
He makes no cry,
though that light is a breath,
the sea curling,
star climbed,
wind combed,
cumbered with itself.
Still as at first it was,
is the hand,
not yet created of the creator.
And he waits for the world to begin.
See you soon.
Okay.
I don't have context for this more than two and a half months
Look at what I do.
Here we go.
How hard and gloomy the world is.
transmitting an entire É Stars is.
Tell us your question?
With Orville she was just sitting there,
Oh I don't have if.
I thought,
and that's always a question of where one must individually negotiate.
And besides, how much of a dance would it be?
I mean, just a gesture or something more?
Anyway, this may have to be put aside for subsequent negotiation.
But I am no stickler for a low price.
I will pay for value offered because that is the only fair and honorable thing to do.
I'll give you a free pamphlet number one if you do a lap dance for me.
Free pamphlet number one.
Let's continue.
Okay.
This question, although the name Bob is misspelled,
the question is, what will Bob do when the Mayan calendar ends?
Well, I guess he'll...
There was no money with that.
He'll put...
He'll put that big heavy stone thing in the garage
and probably not throw it away.
Maybe keep it for a garage sale.
I saw the Mayan calendar at the New York Museum.
Very impressive piece of carving, wouldn't you say?
Yeah.
It was...
Yeah, big...
A little too large for a paper weight.
You could crack walnuts with it, but it'd still be more trouble than it's worth.
All right.
Thank you.
in the newspaper
Performing clown
available
for your next
children's party
Pancho
spent his
last ten dollars
on a rubber nose
and face paint
and some funny
floppy shoes
The children
all ignored him
They thought
he wasn't funny
Their parents
wouldn't pay him
So he had
no food that week
No food
Nobody
cares
about
Pancho
Nobody
cares
at all
,
nobody cares
about him
He's a
good boy
and a
Pancho
fell in love
with a beautiful
trapeze artist
He showered
her with flowers,
gifts and candy
He was
a good boy
Hero!
He was a flower
and lazy
butweet
won't fly over his again.
New on the regain
His courage is bloomed
Nobody cares about Poncho
guitar solo
Poncho
Heartbroken and lonely
Jump off a bridge
Into
the icy
water
They found
his rubber nose
Smashed on
the pier
They found
him with his
face paint streaked
with tears
They buried
Poncho
in an
unmarked grave
Nobody
cared
about Poncho
Nobody
cared
about Poncho
Nobody
cared
Poncho
Don't you
caution
for a man
with a bloke
blood
Once at the
flowering
osair
Nobody
cared
about Poncho
in a
real
ت
Thank you.
Thanks to the Rudy Schwartz Project for that song,
Puncho the Clown from the new CD, The Year They Switched to Cornmeal.
If you need to know more about Rudy Schwartz Project,
Schwartz is spelled S-C-H-W-A-R-T-Z.
The Rudy Schwartz Project.
And now back to Dr. Howe.
Here's one.
One with a dollar bill.
If a Viking baby dies on a battlefield, does he go to Valhalla?
Trademark.
Isn't that an interesting question?
You know, if a Viking dies, a Viking has to die with a sword in his hand.
So this baby could go to Valhalla if it only had a sword in its little pudgy fist
when it died on the battlefield.
Then the choosers of the slain, the Valkyries,
would come diving down and they would seize that tiny toddler warrior's soul
in their long, slender fingers and fly up with him over the rainbow bridge
past Jotunheim, the frozen lands of the giants,
to Valhalla, the Hall of Heroes.
There, while all the Vikings drink enormous vessels of beer and fight all night
and then are miraculously healed of their wounds,
the next day when they start the whole thing,
this baby would be way out of place.
Sitting at the end of one of those long tables,
they wouldn't have much baby food for it in Valhalla, would they?
They'd have to start it on beer really early.
This may seem barbaric, but it's an honor.
It's an honor to be there.
What this reminds me of is that picture that was in the newspaper a few weeks ago
of this Filipino two-year-old who was smoking cigarettes
because they encourage kids to smoke.
He smoked cigarettes in the Philippines.
This smiling little naked baby with a smile on his lips
was expertly holding and puffing a cigarette in this photo.
Well, when that appeared in the paper,
the goo-goos of San Francisco almost had a cornea.
I mean a hernia.
I mean, you know, whatever.
A coronary.
They wrote endless letters to the paper.
They're still pouring in.
I'm sure that kid over in the Philippines is still puffing away.
This is from a relatively rich subgenius.
We can tell because it's a $5 bill.
A rich relative, eh?
Maybe it's from Richie Rich.
And the lettering is very, very clear.
It's rich lettering.
It has shading.
All right.
I have a throbbing sensation all over my body.
You too.
What is it?
It is knowledge that soon your chrysalis will crash.
And the new gleaming subgenius self will emerge
and flex and pump its atrophied muscles into fullness and hardness.
And then, reborn as a warrior for Bob,
you can reclaim your former domain,
which those who undervalued you kept from you.
And now, against them,
you can exert the full and glorious revenge.
Of ultimate success.
This July 5th, friends,
if you can stick around until Tuesday morning.
And even if you can't stick around,
they'll find you.
A long time ago in the 60s,
this reminds me of a TV show back on CBS,
back when there were only three networks.
They interviewed all these people,
including flying saucer cult contactees.
And they asked this one dumpy old lady,
well, Mrs. Yuka Brockowitz,
could you tell us a little bit about your trip to Venus?
And she said,
well, it started with a tingling sensation
all over my whole body.
Maybe a trip to Venus is in your future.
The planet Venus.
Anyway, let's go on.
¶¶
the olive branch
observes the sky began to blanch
without a cry
without a prayer
with no betrayal
of despair
sometime when light obscures
the tree the zenith
of that life must be
past
done forever
and from thence a second
history will commence
a chronicle
no longer gold
of bargaining with mist
and mold and finally
the broken stem
the plummeting to earth
and then
an intercourse not
well designed for beings
of a golden kind
whose native green
must arch above the earth's
obscene
corrupting love
and still
the ripe fruit and the
branch observe the sky
began to blanch without a cry
without a prayer
with no betrayal
of despair
oh courage
could you not as well select some
other place to dwell
not only in that golden
tree
but in the frightened
heart of me
applause
años
wikij
of
wind
courtyard
Are there any animals besides subgeni allowed on the saucers?
And if so, which ones and at what price?
Well, you know, it's a picturesque picture of leading the elephant and the kangaroo two by two aboard the saucer.
But all the time it takes and the feed bags and the vets and so on,
I think far more likely it is that the template for each species has been preserved by excess science.
Hence, the seeds saved, as Papa Joe Mama pointed out the other day in the redoubt in Antarctica against the oncoming disaster.
They'll be whirled away with the saucers and there shall be a new heaven and a new earth like nothing yet seen.
Yea, like nothing ever seen.
There the tamarisk tree shall grow.
The lion shall lie down with the lamb.
And.
The titmouse will shiver in the tumtum tree.
But it may take some time to set these things up and I'm not leaving my stateroom until I feel like coming out.
I plan to.
We don't have plesiosaur seeds, but maybe they do.
Right.
I plan to beam up our pet newt when the time comes.
$16.99
Thanks for playing the next
Get your things, set them in a tent, a little bit faster.
Search, get what you find.
Can't you see we're in a tent, a little bit faster.
Get your things, set them in a tent, a little bit faster.
Search, get what you find.
That was Study in D, draft by the Psychoskeletons.
You can look at the log of this show on subgenius.com
and find the links for the Psychoskeletons.
Praise Bob.
And now back to Ask Dr. Howell live at 14X Day.
Here's a question related to an earlier one.
It's a logical question.
A Viking.
We get a lot of Viking questions here.
If a pregnant Viking woman is lanced with a sword
and the baby hand grabs the sword before self-aborting,
does it go to Valhalla, trademark?
Well, that is one for the judges, not for Dr. Howell.
The judges, you may remember, are three old ladies,
or actually one of them is quite fetching,
but they are the Norns who determine the fate of gods and men.
And this is such a narrow one that it would have to be called on one side or the other.
The baby hand has grabbed the sword.
He is a Viking baby.
He is dying.
He's dying with a sword in his hand.
But is he dying on a battlefield or in the comfort of his mother's womb?
There's a great difference.
You have to be in battle slain to go to the Hall of Heroes.
And they might have to put this fetus for all its valiantness
on the same end of the table with that other baby who died on the battlefield.
And now the gods are even more uncomfortable.
But they'll get used to it over eternity
until Ragnarok, the end, when flames devour Valhalla
and Midgard is destroyed only to be reformed.
Which should be the day after tomorrow.
That's right.
Jormungandr, the giant serpent, will rise from the sea
and, well, let's just say it won't be pretty.
Here's another question.
How many licks does it take to get to the center of a Tootsie Pop?
That's a very good one.
And remember the slowpokes, the all-day suckers they used to say
as part of their advertising that it would take an entire day
to lick to the center of one of these.
Gluey, sugary, hypoglycemic concoctions.
They were made by the Welch's Candy Company
which supported the John Birch Society and Robert Welch.
Too bad if you were a fan of sugar babies, sugar daddies,
or any of the caramelized concoctions of this Midwestern candy company.
How many licks does it take if you're a mouse
and your tongue is three-fifths of an inch long?
How many licks does it take
if you're a camel and your tongue is a foot and a half long?
You know, who are you to lick a Tootsie Pop?
But I would have to say it takes as many licks
to get to the center of a Tootsie Pop as you care to give it.
Because if you're like me, after a while,
your tongue gets tired of the licking
and you just gnaw the thing between your teeth
and grind it up and have a large ball of caramel, sugar, and saliva in your mouth.
Whose aftereffects you will feel, perhaps even for years.
Ah!
No.
No!
rooted muốn
I know sound effects are...
also from the movie Troll Hunter, a Norwegian movie that I would recommend if you love monsters.
And I'm not just a monster hugger.
Praise Bob.
And now back to Ask Dr. Howell.
Why does every day end in the letter Y?
Why slash why?
Why does every day end in the letter Y slash why?
Because this is the freedom-loving, red-blooded United States of America and not godless Russia,
where everyone looks at the sun when it goes down and shrugs and nods and says,
Duh.
But with us, it's day.
Glad, beautiful day.
Coming to its end.
Coming to the glorious end as the glorious lamp of heaven descends.
The heavens declare the glory of God and the firmament showeth his handiwork.
Day unto day uttereth speech and night unto night showeth knowledge.
There is no speech nor language where his voice is not heard.
His line has gone out through all the earth and his words unto the end of the world.
In them hath he set a tabernacle for the sun, which is at us a bridegroom coming out of his chamber
and rejoiceth as a strong man to run a race.
His going forth is from the end of the heavens and his circuit unto the ends of it
and nothing is...
hid from the heat thereof.
Thank you for your question.
That was pretty good for an unpaid question.
Speaking of the end...
If you could ask Bunny Day, she'd be Bunny Duh.
That wouldn't be good.
Welcome to my secret lair on Skullcrusher Mountain.
I hope that you've enjoyed your stay so far.
I see you've met my assistant, Scarface.
His appearance is quite disturbing, but I assure you he's harmless enough.
He's a sweetheart, calls me master, and he has a way of finding pretty things
and bringing them to me.
Oh, and I'm so into you, but I'm way too smart for you.
Even my henchmen think I'm crazy.
I'm not surprised that you agree.
If you could find some way to be a little bit less afraid of me,
you'd see the voices that control me from inside my head
and say I shouldn't care.
Oh, yeah.
I made this half pony, half monkey monster to please you.
But I get the feeling that you don't like it.
What's with all the screaming?
You like monkeys, you like ponies.
Maybe you don't like monsters so much.
Maybe I use too many monkeys.
Isn't it enough?
You know that I ruined a pony making a gift for you.
Oh, and I'm so into you, but I'm way too smart for you.
Even my henchmen think I'm crazy.
I'm not surprised that you agree.
If you could find some way to be a little bit less afraid of me,
you'd see the voices that control me.
You'd see me grill when my head is so black
and I get in trouble around you then
Shim Industrialぶみたい to kill you!
But I'm not surprised that you agree.
You look like an elk when you do something funny.
My lover is a monster, my lover.
token. And forever.
And the last one.
Fools who lead their foolish lives may find it quite explosive
Well, it won't mean half as much to me if I don't have you here
I know it isn't easy living here on Skull Crusher Mountain
So maybe you could cut me just a little slack
Would it kill you to be civil?
I've been patient, I've been gracious
And this mountain is covered with wolves
Hear them howling, my hungry children
Maybe you should stay and have another drink
And think about me and you
And I'm so into you, but I'm way too smart for you
Even my henchmen think I'm crazy
I'm not surprised that you're not
Can you agree?
If you could find some way to be a little bit less afraid of me
You'd see the voices that control me
From inside my head
Say I shouldn't kill you yet
I shouldn't kill you yet
Bobby!
You also do this character Bobby
And you made an audition tape
Or Bobby made an audition tape
And I think you brought that
Let's take a look
Thanks a lot
Now it's stuck on that haunted house
I heard a witch lives there
I heard a Frankenstein lives there
You guys are way off
It's a secret lab where they take the brains out of zombies
And put them in the heads of other zombies
To create a race of super zombies
That's the house?
Ivan has to take to heart that he has control of his life
He's got all the tools to do whatever he wants
What you've done is so great
That I don't know how to even reciprocate
Ivan, can you be a good boy for me?
I want to be a good boy for you
Alright
I will tell you that you learned a lot
Bye Ivan
Bye
I think that the things that Ivan saw
Couldn't give us hope for change
But will Ivan change his ways?
I know myself better than anybody
Ivan please don't speak to your mother like that
Hey Ivan
How's it going?
Good
Got a few minutes?
I told Ivan I got a surprise for you.
It's a letter from Bub.
Mom, this is Amy.
Amy? Hi.
So you're the older woman Jay Arndt's been telling us about.
You are just as cute as a button.
And I can see what Jay Arndt meant when he said you have the curves of a video vixen.
What? No, I've never said that.
Oh, no, that was me.
Mm.
Hi.
How you doing? You can call me Bub.
Okay.
Mm, okay.
Have a seat.
Then bought a few bottles of the good stuff to go with it.
And Jay Arndt, if it's okay with your mama, you and Amy can drink as much as you want.
Yeah, a few sips.
Let's pretend we're French for the evening.
And Julio's gotta be a 착 on the cake?
But it's a little bit of a struggle.
Am I an ole animal club?
Maybe can she make it out with capt?
When it comes to music, Jamaica is all about Bob.
In fact, the late, great musical legend Bob is from right here, y'all.
Ladies, flash if you love Bob.
Bob's memory and music are kept alive at the Ocho Rios Reggae Museum.
In case you wanted to know what that Jamaican ganja was good for.
Captain Bob was in command of our sturdy little vessel,
and you could tell he really hated his job.
Well, like I always say, work is for people that don't know how to fish,
especially when you're out here off the Mexican coast,
catching 25, 30 sailfish a day on a good day,
and a good buzz and a bunch of naked ladies on a bad day.
Listen, I know a lot of you thought,
your world was going to end on Saturday.
Some of you even quit your jobs and sold your possessions.
What a bunch of idiots.
Bob it.
Salado, Texas.
Bob just turned 75, and he's having second thoughts about his birthday wish.
Bob, first and last jump.
I'm not going to be parking last.
You want a word?
I'm going to get up and drive.
Before Bob can back out, they're at 13,000 feet.
But this trip will turn to trouble as he called in Bob.
The instructor forgets to release his safety belt.
Bob hangs helplessly two miles above the ground.
In less than 60 seconds, they'll be beyond the drop zone.
If they don't sever the belt quickly, there'll be no hope for a safe landing.
Just in time, the Tangling Duo is cut loose.
Oh, my God!
Now that they're finally free falling, Bob can enjoy the ride.
Safe on solid ground, he wonders what went wrong.
That's weird. Good job, Bob.
I couldn't see. I couldn't hear anything.
I didn't know what was happening. I was just dangling.
Bob waited 75 years for his first skydive and celebrated his birthday with the ride of his life.
Who's that, George?
That's me with Charlton Heston. He was...
Ah, see, you know him. That's Bob.
Recognize this?
Yeah, it's Don't Stop Believing by Journey.
Great song. Great song.
Yeah, but there's a few more. Listen.
My life is brilliant.
My love is pure.
I saw an angel.
Of this I'm sure.
Wherever you go, whatever you do, I will be right here waiting for you.
No one, no one, no one can get in the way of what I'm feeling.
Since the way you left me, I'm not pretending.
No love, no hope, no glory.
No happy ending.
Thanks, you were fuel for thought.
Now I'm all lonely than before.
But that's okay.
People killing, people dying.
Children hurt, women crying.
If you practice what you preach, you can turn the other cheek.
Cause you were amazing.
And we did amazing things.
If I could, then I would.
Oh girl, wherever you will go.
Don't let the days go by.
So tell me why should I let you go?
Cause we are gonna be forever you and me.
And where I go, I just don't know.
I gotta, gotta, gotta take it slow.
Say you're gonna stay.
Now I need to know it.
And I want a TV embrace.
And she will be loved.
Yeah, she will be loved.
Oh I can't live with or without you.
Whenever I fall at your feet, you let your tears.
Am I not pretty enough?
Is my heart too broke?
Hm.
When I find myself in times of fear.
When I find myself in times of trouble.
Mother Mary comes to me.
Sometimes I feel like I don't have a partner.
I'm starting with the man in the mirror.
Can you feel the love tonight?
I come from a land down under.
Once a jolly swagman can't buy a billabong.
Do I cry too much?
Am I too outspoken?
Take on me.
Take me on.
I'll be gone in a year or two.
Save tonight.
And find the break of dawn.
Come tomorrow.
Tomorrow I'll be gone.
Gonna take a lot to drag me away from you.
There's nothing that a hundred men or more could ever do.
I know she's playing with me.
Well that's okay cause I got no self-esteem.
Away, oh yeah.
It's alright to tell me what you think about me.
I won't try to argue or hold it against you.
It's too late to apologize.
It's too late.
Take your canvas bags.
Take your canvas bags to the supermarket.
Nothing's right, I'm torn.
I'm all out of faith.
This is how I feel.
I'm cold and I am shamed.
Lying naked on the floor.
Illusion never changed.
Into something real.
I'm wide awake and I can see.
I'm more than a bird.
I'm more than a plane.
I'm a bird plane.
A motherfucking bird plane.
Doesn't that sound familiar?
Doesn't that hit too close to home?
Doesn't that make you shiver?
The way that things have gone.
Doesn't that seem peculiar?
Cause everyone wants a little more.
And something I do remember.
To never go this far.
That's all it takes to be a star.
And that's what I'm going to ask Dr. Howell.
Here, we keep getting questions.
And this one has an IOU of ten dollars.
From Reverend Fox over there.
Excellent. Ten dollars.
If all the dinosaurs came back for 24 hours,
how would you schedule that day?
I'd want to high tail it for the mountains.
Because as far as we know,
there weren't too many mountainous dinosaurs.
Actually, all the fossils that we have
come from the lowlands.
From the swamps.
The watery areas.
We have no idea what existed.
What lived up in the mountains.
At any time in the history of life.
Fossils just don't form up there.
Now you may know, or may not know,
that as a cartoonist,
I've worked on trading card sets before.
Of the non-sports group.
And I worked on the dinosaur's attack cards.
The thing about the dinosaur's attack cards,
is this was the scenario.
All the dinosaurs come back.
They pop into existence.
Sometimes they form into existence
around people who are entombed.
Partly sticking out of a dinosaur.
Wiggling their arms in vain.
And all sorts of thoughtful atrocities
are in these cards.
I would schedule this day with a nice trip to the mountains.
And that's where I'd stay.
Watch the whole thing on TV.
Come down when it was all over.
Although I wouldn't mind the dinosaurs coming back.
They wouldn't like it here.
Because there's not enough food for them.
In order for enormous monsters to exist,
there has to be lots and lots of food available.
And we have used almost everything up.
Soon there will not be enough for us.
Now hopefully this is the last question.
By the way, these...
You'll get it.
We're starting to get questions written on these
anonymous subgenius orgy invitations.
You're going to have to close us down.
That's what we do.
We can't go on forever.
And so at a certain point you say this session is closed.
But how long are we supposed to run anyway?
It's now 5.10.
Bulldada auction would be the next thing.
Okay, it's 5.10.
We'll do the last question, closing poem,
and start the bulldada auction.
What do you say?
That's fine.
And this is pretty...
So here's our final question, folks.
Yeah.
Take a look at the handwriting on this, Dr. Howell.
When is the anal prolapse for distance competition...
Competition.
Dot, dot, dot, dot, dot, dot.
Or is that taking it, quote, too far, non-end quote?
I wonder if the writer of this question
has been at earlier X days
where people played some of these games
and played them a little too hard
and had to have, was it helicopters coming in, ambulances?
Whatever.
People had to be hauled out of here screaming in pain.
Is that what you need to complete your X day?
Perhaps you should be the volunteer.
But, you know, the anal sphincter is fairly elastic.
You'd have to work really hard to create a prolapse like this,
like the one you mentioned.
You should probably get busy.
So that concludes our question and answer session.
And in keeping with the Viking theme early,
I will conclude with a Viking poem,
The Skeleton in Armor.
Speak, speak, ye fearful guest,
Who with thy hollow breast,
Still in rude armor dressed,
Comest to daunt me,
Wrapped not in eastern balms,
But with thy fleshless palms,
Stretched as if asking alms,
Why dost thou haunt me?
Then from those cavernous eyes
Pale flashes seemed to rise,
As when the northern skies gleam in December,
And as the waters flow under December's snow,
Came a dull voice of woe from the heart's chamber.
I was a Viking old,
My deeds though manifold,
No skald in song has told,
No saga taught thee.
Take heed that in thy verse,
Thou dost the tale rehearse,
Else fear a dead man's curse,
For this I sought thee.
Far in the northern land,
By the wild Baltic's strand,
I with my childish hand,
Tamed the girfalcon,
And with my skates fast bound,
Skimmed the half-frozen sound,
That the poor whimpering hound,
Trembled to walk on.
Oft from his frozen lair,
Tracked I the grizzly bear,
Oft from my path the hare,
Fled like a shadow,
Oft through the forest dark,
Followed the werewolf's bark,
Until the soaring lark sang in the meadow.
But when I older grew,
Joining a corsair's crew,
Over the sea I flew with the marauders,
Wild was the life we led,
Many the souls that sped,
Many the hearts that bled,
By our firm orders.
Oft the wild wassail bout,
Wore the long winter out,
Often our midnight shouts,
At the cocks crowing,
When we the berserk's tail,
Measured in pots of ale,
Draining the oak tree,
The oaken pail filled to o'erflowing.
Once as I told in glee,
Tales of the stormy sea,
Soft eyes there gazed on me,
Burning yet tender,
And as the white stars shine,
On the dark Norway pine,
On that dark heart of mine,
Fell their soft splendor.
I wooed the blue-eyed maid,
Yielding yet half afraid,
And in the forest shade,
Our vows were plighted,
Under her loosened vests,
Grasped I her trembling breasts,
Like birds within their nests,
By the hawk frighted.
Bright in her father's hall,
Shields gleamed upon the wall,
Loudly the minstrels all chanted his glory,
When of old Hildebrand,
I asked his daughter's hand,
Mute did the minstrels stand,
To hear my story.
As the brown ale he quaffed,
Loud then the champion laughed,
And as the winds that waft
The sea foam brightly,
So the loud laugh of scorn,
Out from those lips unshorn,
From the deep drinking horn,
Blew the foam lightly.
She was a prince's child,
I but a Viking wild,
And though she blushed and smiled,
I was discarded.
Should not the sea-mew's flight
Follow the dove so bright?
Why did they leave,
That night her nest unguarded?
Scarce had I put to sea,
Bearing the maid with me,
Fairest by far was she among the Norsemen,
When on the bright sea-sand,
Waving his armoured hand,
Saw we old Hildebrand with twenty horsemen,
Launched they against the blast,
Bent like a reed each mast,
Yet we were gaining fast,
When the wind failed us,
And in the dusky scaw came round
The windy flaw,
So that the foe we saw laugh
As he hailed us.
And as the flapping sail
Veered round to catch the gale,
Death was the helmsman's hail,
Death without quarter.
Mid-ship with iron keel
Struck we her ribs of steel,
Down her black hulk did reel,
Through the black water.
As with his wings aslant,
Sails the fierce cormorant,
Seeking some rocky haunt
With his prey laden,
There towards the open main,
Beating to sea again,
Through the wild hurricane,
Bore I the maiden.
Three weeks we westward bore,
And when the storm was o'er,
Cloud-like we saw the shore
Stretching to leeward,
There for many years,
Through my lady's bower,
Built I the lofty tower,
Which to this very hour
Stands looking seaward.
There we lived many years.
Time dried the maiden's tears,
She had forgot her fears,
She was a mother.
Death closed her pale blue eyes,
Under that tower she lies,
Never shall sun arise
On such another.
Still grew my bosom then,
Still as a stagnant fen,
Hateful to me were men,
The sunlight hateful.
In the vast forest here,
Clad in my warlike gear,
Fell I upon my spear.
Oh, death was grateful.
Thus, seamed with many scars,
Bursting these prison bars,
Up to its native stars,
My soul ascended.
There, from the flowing bowl,
Drinks deep the warrior's soul.
Skull to the Northland!
Skull!
Yai, yai, yai, yai, yai, yai!
Thus, the tale ended.
Thank you.
Thank you, Dr. Howell,
for answering so many difficult
and impossible questions.
Oh, by the way,
why is a turtle mound,
why do they call those turtle mounds?
Well, Ivan, they called it a turtle mound,
because to the Native Americans
who inhabited this area,
the turtle represented the great seat
of the cosmos and the earth itself,
was conceived as on the shell of a turtle,
which is to say, more properly,
a tortoise, not a turtle,
the land-dwelling tortoise.
And as you know, in some cosmoses,
the earth and its seas
are on the back of a giant tortoise,
and beneath that, there's another giant tortoise,
and some people say it's tortoises
all the way down.
Time will tell, when we take
off, we may get a good view.
Thank you.
I had to ask Dr. Howell that question,
because, and I've got this on tape,
there's a turtle mound down the road,
and I idly said,
why the hell do they call that turtle mound?
And I have a recording of Dr. Howell
saying the phrase, I don't know.
And I said, I'm going to ask you,
now I know the question to ask you,
and he said, I'll answer it.
So, friends, thank you very much.
I guess the Bulldada auction now begins.
I need a break.
Yes, let's get that going.
Okay, you take a break,
and we'll come back,
and we'll start the auction.
Yeah, and friends,
these Jenkum Huffing Chamber things,
anyone who wants to grab some Scotch tape
from the registration box,
and these anonymous, mysterious,
subgenius orgy invitations,
they're meant to be just left in mystery,
mysterious places around here.
The Jenkum Huffing Chamber, of course,
goes in the chem toilets.
And they always get taken down within a day,
but it always does my heart good to see them.
So anyone with the red minion bracelet
should take on that chore at some point.
Thank you.
Don't let us deter you
from doing business with us again.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
You're listening to
the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
For free information on Bob Dobbs
and the Church of the Subgenius,
send a self-addressed stamped envelope to...
Got your pencil ready?
Bob, Post Office Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights,
Ohio 44118 www.subgenius.com
That's Bob, P.O. Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights,
Stay tuned and praise Bob.
Now this whole world has no clue what they're doing
Got enough money in the bank for the tools
So I gotta keep enough lettuce to support the shoe
Fetish lifestyle so rich and famous
Robin Leach will get jealous
Half a million views
But it's gold
Take a trip from here to Rome
So if you ain't got no money
Take your broke and moaned
There was a boy
And he said,
I need a brand new ball
And I don't wanna buy it
There was a boy
And he said,
I need a brand new ball
And he broke and moaned
There were no teeth teaming him on
How to support cool sports
I can make you broke and lonely.
No one knows what I'd be with.
Yo, DJ Pussy Party!
Pussycat went to sea in a beautiful pea green boat.
They took some money and plenty of honey
wrapped up in a five-pound note.
The owl looked up to the stars above
as he sang to a small guitar,
Oh, Pussy, Oh, Pussy, Oh, Pussy, my love,
what a beautiful pussy you are.
You are? What a beautiful pussy you are.
Pussy said to the owl,
You elegant fowl, how charmingly sweet you sing.
Come, let us be married.
Too long we have tarried.
But what shall we do for a ring?
So they sailed away for a year and a day
to the land where the bong tree grows.
And there in the wood a piggy wig stood
with a ring at the end of his nose,
his nose, with a ring at the end of his nose.
Dear Pig,
are you willing to sell for a shilling
your ring?
said the piggy, I will.
So they took it away and were married next day
by the turkey who lives on the hill.
They dined upon mints and on slices of quince,
which they ate with a runcible spoon.
And hand in hand on the edge of the sand
they danced by the light of the moon,
the moon, they danced by the light of the moon.
Oh, sire,
no more money?
We gotta get some money.
That dirty purgish harker backflagging
Wharton, Philip Bunker Burton,
Perkaluma Burton,
doesn't wash the night away.
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show
and we're even more glad that some listeners
have donated enough to help us keep on going
for another couple of months.
And not just this show,
but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob,
and want some of that slack back to rebound to you,
you should go to subgenius.com front page
or especially the radio page
or the catalog store pages
and help out financially as best you can.
Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty
and we don't want any subgeniuses
to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference,
even if it's only,
only once a month from enough of you.
50 bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that
blow jobs could go the way of Steve jobs
if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to
Subgenius Foundation.
P.O. Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44.
First ListenquaO checked in last night
It hole never has snow dry
I don't know how to believe
You've beenddenned
for watching If you're aĝ captain
be sure to thumbs up
See you next week
Wrongke0
Great R pillar
Go Buzzard
Daddy Italy
The subliminal hypo-corporation.
Sex, money, Bob.
Free pills.
Kill me.
Sex, money, Bob.