Life dropped by the fantastic bag. Well, welcome to the hour of slack.
Praise Bob Gold and Connie Drag. Yes, welcome to the hour of slack.
Whoa. Oh, man. Don't take that pill.
What about the New Fuzzlums we have to worry about? The people...
The people from New Fuzzland?
Yeah, the people from New Fuzzlums.
With the new fuzzles, with the big cyclops eye on top that you're talking about?
They're self-created people, much like the old Bodhi Dharmas of old.
And, you know, they just spring into existence.
You can always sharpen things to a fuzzy focus or blur them to crystal clarity.
Thank God for that.
No, I don't think you can.
You were right.
You are not in control of the train.
I debuked everything.
You debuked it fully.
And he rebuked it.
Thank you, Tim, for bringing it up, too, I might say.
And rightfully so, because, you know, we're hip.
You know, we're beatnik rabbits.
You can't...
You ain't gonna control the fuzziness or the sharpness or focus or anything.
Have any of you two fellows ever heard of Madcap Jack?
We're just down there for the ride.
Just admit it.
Madcap Jack, who was shortly around the same time as Jack the Ripper,
who might have been a time traveler.
He would, like, appear on London streets and squirt people.
He would squirt guns and then bound over hedges and stuff.
Oh, Spring Heels Jack.
Spring Heels Jack.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's his name.
Spring Heels.
That was the same...
That was the grandpappy of the Spring Heels, the crop circle maker.
Now, you've really heard of Spring Heels.
Crop circle making Jack, I mean.
But nobody ever discovered who Spring Heels Jack really was.
I'm telling you, it's the same family that does the crop circles.
And they mess with people's minds.
That's what they do.
They're descendants of Sonny Bean, the Scottish serial killer and cannibal,
who really got a bad rap.
And they're now a clan of secret scientists
who do the crop circles and cattle mutilations and so forth
just to keep the CIA scared.
Trash, he says, old Kenny got a bad rap.
It's the old Outer Limits routine of the, you know,
the secret scientists getting together to scare the governments
with a fake alien.
Yeah.
Richmond and have...
It was another example of that.
But the Church of the Subgenius is not.
These aliens are real and they are going to destroy the world.
Why even care if they have an alien or not?
Huh?
Well, it is sort of out of our control.
They have one or they don't have one.
Who cares?
He's into oblivion, man.
He's a beatnik tonight.
You know, he's like...
No, no, no, no.
It don't matter.
Blessed, blessed oblivion.
Man.
The sweet smack, the horse riding over the top of your hooves.
There's nothing to climb for, man.
That's true.
The rat race is self-exceeding.
What about more money and more things?
That is the self-exceeding rat race
that climbs in and out of your colon on a daily basis.
You know, he hit guys with the most toys wins.
That's what I was always...
Or was implied by the pink world anyway.
I was told the one who dies with the most tools
is the quickest one.
He dig his way out.
The Pharaoh told you that, didn't he?
Yeah, Pharaoh told me that he did.
Back in the day, man.
Yeah, he was working for the Pharaoh back in the day.
He who dies with the most slaves wins.
And he who slobbers the most
and his pancreatic juices
is the one who wins.
Well, I'm working on that.
Do I have to be buried with my cats?
Because they're just going to use me...
What do you mean it's a litter box?
No, you build a separate sarcophagus for them
that looks like a pyramid or a finx.
You have them mummified too.
Or it's only it's free.
They use freeze-drying now.
Yes, they've been freeze-drying cats
for quite some years now.
I've got several of my little dogs
and one goat done that way around my house.
So you have some jerky to eat in the afterlife.
Yep.
A snack for the supernatural traveler.
Yeah, to take with you.
And that's what this show is, dear friends.
A little something for the supernatural traveler
to take with you.
This is your host, Reverend Ivan Stang.
And I'm so sick with this cold
that everybody has that I'm not even standing up
over at the mix board.
I brought the microphone over to my computer.
I don't even...
I don't even care.
Don't care.
I'm too tired and snotty
to make a special mix of a show
with all the wonderful new contributions
from strangers that we get.
I'll have to do that next time.
I just don't have it in me to mix it up, man.
Luckily, in previous weeks,
we were healthier and mixed it up live
on various live broadcasts,
such as we just heard ESO Swamp Radio
from WCSB Cleveland.
And also tonight, we're going to be hearing
lots and lots more of the subgenius business retreat
conclave recordings from KPFA
last December 2002.
KPFA Radio in Berkeley
allowed us to do that.
Over the edge and puzzling evidence
to provide this smattering
of earthly entertainment.
Praise St. Stupid.
We'll take a short break
and let's have a little entertainment.
And you can call in
4425 at the 510 nickel and dime code area
so you can...
Call us.
The Church of the Subgenius
and the First Church of the Last Life
is the most powerful religion
right here to answer your spiritual
and financial questions.
Thank you.
Give us a call.
Another 100 years of this?
That's right.
Coming your way.
I think that's the Not You Gary microphone.
Oh, okay.
Not you.
Oh, is it not on or something?
Oh, no, wait a minute.
Not me.
Yeah, he's there at the Gary Cool Lounge.
The Lizard Lounge.
Yes, flat on my stomach.
My butt in the air getting a little sun-shiny.
That's what they do down in Santa Cruz.
How much does it cost to become cold-blooded?
And how extensive is that operation?
Or those operations?
It's not much.
It's covered under our...
Well, most faculty members actually are cold-blooded.
Really?
Yeah.
It doesn't really mean anything.
You mean like Eohippus Love Child?
Obvious in the face of it.
The poor little Eohippus that couldn't come here.
No, she's a dick.
She lives a life of freedom and happiness in the pasture.
You do what you do because you love to.
I do what I do because my mom told me to.
Copyright 1981.
Dr. Slovak.
That's your turn.
It's your turn here on the show.
So 848-VAL.
Who's going to roll for the call?
And the caller?
Go right ahead.
Don't call.
I dare you.
I dare you to call.
I dare you to drive with your knee as you call on your cell phone.
508-4825.
I like the don't ask, don't call talk.
Give it a try.
We are going to lose a caller out there.
Go ahead.
Come on in.
Ornate?
Are we Nate?
We're Ornate.
Ornate?
Yeah.
That's friends from real Clinton.
That's a good one.
I'm going to join the church of the genius.
Okay.
How much do you got?
I got a pound of grand here and a grand there.
Okay.
Well, it sounds grand to us.
Hello?
Why don't you go out and invest in crispy green donuts and bring them on down.
Don't do grand dives.
He's doing a backwards call in which he says hello and hangs up.
You talk about your grand there and your grand there and you hang up the phone.
He's a contrarian just like a little big man.
It is true that there is a thing I do not understand.
What?
There's a pain between my ears.
That's your life, Reverend.
It tastes just like chicken.
When did it start?
That's how I felt.
I thought it was the show actually.
When did that show start?
It is.
It's the show that's the painful thing in your ears.
Lean closer to your radio.
Look in the little tiny speaker slid.
Put your hands on the radio.
Look deep inside the bowels of your radio.
Do you see that tiny little glow?
And now stand up and feel the power of the show coursing through your body.
So call 848-445 right now.
510-848-445.
Okay.
Here's a caller.
And help us pick all of it.
It is as if they are walking out.
First of all, I want to thank you for being here.
The first thing we're going to do is push you in the deep end.
It's like the old days.
I'm moving to the dock to go to Carrie.
It is like the old days.
The first, the very first subgenius show on the 26th of June, 1982, was a five-hour show.
Really?
Who was on it?
Lies, Dr. Albert Tsang, and Palsy Nevins.
And I had these special pills that were white on one side and blue on the other.
So I cut them in half and distributed the white parts and we yacked and had fun all night.
That's right.
Four o'clock I just rooted the blue parts.
Oh, good.
And you go out and hold it.
That's right.
Yeah.
That was back in the day before you had to pee in your refrigerator every night.
That's right.
Yeah, just to open it.
Come on down.
Later in your life.
You may not open.
You may not access your own beer.
There's two callers now.
Two callers.
Yes.
One.
Kill them.
Caller number one.
Kill the callers.
Kill.
Wrong pee prep.
Cannot open.
Authorization not given for refrigerator.
What about 21 years?
Nor toilet.
You've been listening for 21 years?
Running around your apartment full of big tubes.
Nothing's opening up for you.
None of the files will open.
You've been listening for 21 years?
I do.
If I piss, the whole place will go up.
I haven't been in the chat for 21 years.
Man.
I've got too many sensors in my suit.
The government will know right away.
Don't, don't pass out.
Please don't.
No.
Don't stop.
I won't pass out.
I've got to.
Yeah.
Get down, damn it!
Slow 10.
It is.
It's slow 10 time.
So I may speak again about this nonceless babble that speaks within my mind.
Babylon.
So now I must draw comics and send them to homeless people where they look at me crazy
and call me weird as much people do because I walk around with underwear on my head.
Anyway, when I do that, they look at me and they call me the do.
So what does hooki do mean when I'm hooki do?
You're on break for 21 years.
Well, silly, I'm using a paper.
Watch your language.
Even late at night, little kids could be listening in on their earphones.
They fell asleep listening to Britney Spears.
See what happens?
A special tone kills the bad word.
In their subconscious, like you're bleeding into their ears.
You said that word.
Government?
We're in love with all the callers.
Don't forget.
Yes, friends.
The church of the subgenius is a church of love.
Guaranteed.
We reach out with love.
We love you.
We love the holidays.
Hate squared might as well be love in this church.
That's right.
When we talk about all that hate and killing, what we really meant was love and sex and sweet talk.
What's the connection between this church and the bonobo business?
Well, if you kiss a bonobo before the dissection.
Really?
Is that the problem?
Kiss the bonobo before the dissection?
Robin refused to kiss the bonobo before she dissected it.
Oh.
What kind of wimp is she?
God.
Is that a chance?
It's a frozen bonobo.
It came from, it had to come all the way from the San Francisco Zoo.
Before she dissected it.
It was driven down to Santa Cruz.
She has a tough and weird.
Maybe the lips had kind of like thawed out and she was kind of like.
Yes, these are the kind of people that throw up and weird.
These are our church members.
And you could be a member of our church too if you call MD484.
Our name is bigrigindustries.org I think it is.
No, it's ststupid.com.
Ststupid.com.
It kind of looks like aliens.
So if you're curled up in your bed with your laptop.
Ststupid.com.
I hope you're not curled up in your bed with your laptop.
Yeah, do it.
It's better you're fried.
Dot com.
M-I-S-S-I-S-S-I-I-N-O.com.
You have all kinds of dreams that are happening in your mind.
You know, you're visiting different states and you're thinking of religion and bonobos.
And you're starting to drift and you're thinking I got to not fall over because I'm going to
fall face first into the chili or the cereal and spill it right on the keyboard.
Or the dashboard.
Why did I put it on the bed like this?
I better remind myself to get up.
I'm driving with my knees while I call you.
You're not in bed.
You're in your car.
You're going 70 miles an hour.
I'm going 70 miles an hour.
Wake up!
Up and forward.
Add digital sound effects at this time.
We can fix that in post production.
It is true there is a thing here I do not understand.
Do you know all the more why I'm here.
There is a pain between my ears.
And so the confused initiate was led to Dockstock, Dobstown itself.
Dobstown Malaysia, where he was shocked to discover the most primitive possible living
condition.
As I entered the bedroom, there were two elderly albino women robed entirely in black.
Lavinia's insides were all torn up.
Now, uh, now, uh...
Bizarre.
Yeah.
It's kind of funny, too.
Minimal brain dysfunction.
I'm that kind of a guy.
Uh...
Questionable.
Ejaculation.
Unemotionally.
You know, we have met your sons and daughters.
Earth was inhabited by, uh, species.
Uh...
Species from another dimension.
With certain chants from the book, sacrifices.
This race, the old ones, can be brought back.
And mankind?
Destroyed.
A sizeless, shapeless spirit manifestation of pure evil.
Pure evil.
Not evil.
Not pure evil.
But pure evil.
Much like old Spring-Eels Jack, he was.
He'd, uh, disappear and never reappear.
Spring-Eel Jack.
Now, you know...
Spring-Heels.
Heels.
I couldn't hear it.
Oh, Spring-Heels.
Hey, did you guys hear about Bigfoot?
No, we smelled him, though.
Bigfoot's a man who...
He died.
...who was most responsible for certain Bigfoot evidence.
Most of them.
Died.
And his...
Just some Bigfoot evidence.
And some of that evidence that people have been seeing Bigfeet for centuries.
Yeah, but he got, like...
Was he crushed?
He hired, like, townspeople.
Like, this one lady came forward and said that she was Bigfoot one time in one of the
videos.
And she was, in that slap-happy kind of Arkham sex way.
She was big everywhere.
Well, it was like a town joke.
It wasn't like his own joke.
It was like a town joke.
The conspiracy wants to convince the humans that there's no such thing as yetis, for good
reasons.
I think that's great, that it was a town joke, that Bigfoot was a freak.
I think it was a freaking town joke.
As it should be.
You know, a community who's got their own pet who lives and eats grubs and nuts.
Now, just because, you know, one little old man is Bigfoot and does all the crop circles
doesn't mean that all the Bigfeet are that same little old man.
That's true.
So you're saying the same man who was...
Is Bigfoot to the small community?
The Yeti actually live...
Crop circles?
The Yeti live on today in the form of you, Dave.
Well, they live...
And you, Chaz.
They live on rice and beans when they have to.
Now, what proof is there of that?
Wild oats.
You're gigantic peckers.
Gigantic peckers.
This is not a Tex Avery cartoon.
And your huge personalities and egos are proof of Yeti descent.
So that's what it takes, huge organs and huge egos.
Well, no, or in my case, real short legs and a real large head and long arms that kind
of drag across the ground.
Well, for Mike's...
I mean, there's various different traits of the Yeti.
But yeah, I mean, the Yeti is certainly still around.
Yeti's our president was an old saw.
I remember that very vaguely because of what happened last night.
I'm afraid that's something I cannot allow to happen.
The back of my head, once again, keeps on getting the brunt of every...
You ever strike yourself more than once in the same day and you think you're cursed by
some...
Oh, I'm afraid I can't do that, Dave.
It is over again.
You can never leave.
We can never leave because we have never arrived.
We're in here.
Yeah.
So now we're driving high above Berkeley.
You can look down and see the city.
You can see Gary's hair from up here.
Wow.
And the hospital.
It's beautiful the way it ruffles in the wind.
I think we can rock out now.
It's hard to see.
It's hard to tell his hair from the highway.
It sure is cold.
Some of the stress is...
Make the bass player come back.
Which one's Cowboy Dave?
Which one's Chaz?
Chaz is the skinny one and Dave is the upside down one.
Oh, okay.
Little icons here on the top.
I see.
You go over here and you can...
No, no.
Don't go over there.
That'll crash the whole thing.
Oh, jeez.
I think Saint Stupid's rubbing that harmonica on his leg like a cricket.
I think he's rubbing it on his leg.
It's the same as his.
Is this what they call an experience?
Yeah.
Or is this one of those happenings?
What do you call it?
What's this a thing?
The show changes entirely in 11 minutes.
Just completely.
Oh, that's right.
Because that other show starts.
Yeah.
And you won't be able to...
I mean, you'll just...
It's mind blowing.
The whole thing's just mind blowing.
Is it another show?
There's more than a name and less than a dare?
Yeah, less than a tape or something, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
More than four hours.
Tape of a tape of a tape of a tape.
That's true.
Of an MP3.
Yeah.
Of 20,000 hours of MP3 on one CD.
You can't ever listen to it in your entire life.
But it's every show ever done, so you keep it in your library anyway.
That's right.
Just so you can say you have it.
Yeah, I have every show ever done, yeah.
I do have every show ever done.
On your pop pod?
But it's not on MP5 or anything.
It's not on some little file, man.
Every show.
It's on a big, bulky thing.
Ever done by anyone will be on this one holocube owned by this man in the U.S. government.
He's got your name.
He's got your number.
And he's sharing it with everyone else.
It's President Michael Jackson.
He owns everything.
And here he is.
Information is finally free.
Looks just like him, doesn't it?
Please follow the yellow line.
I feel so much better.
Better now.
Man, it's been weird ever since the pigs started driving those yellow submarines.
Submariners once.
Submariners twice.
Holy jugglers, Jesus Christ.
We go up.
We go down.
We don't even fuck around.
Submariners!
What you gonna do?
Last line is just silly.
Whoa.
I liked it last time I was here in the 80s.
Yeah, things have changed in the intervening 20 years.
Rip.
Rip Van De Broek, man.
A man, a stone age man from the past resurrected.
He was one of the creators, the inventors of the stone show.
Can I get my typewriter fixed?
Anybody here know how to...
How to...
How to use a hammer?
Gary.
Hey, look.
The Iceman.
Princess Wee is doing a howl.
Is that...
Like this.
Will you fall asleep on the show?
Joining the listener in blessed slumber.
Because it is so relaxing.
From Princess Wee.
Well, Mr. Gabro Fran, having been resurrected from your icy sleep for at least intervening
20 years.
Or sleeping or whatever you were doing.
What changes do you find especially remarkable in the show and society around it?
Well, one thing is you don't have to wind up the show anymore before you use it.
It has a battery now.
That's really good.
You know, I remember back before the show, you had remote controls.
You had to push actual buttons on the physical show.
You couldn't do anything.
You couldn't stand across the city from it and activate the controls like puzzling evidence
is doing now.
We used to have to subdue Mobius Rex before we could actually...
There's no Mobius here to subdue.
Do not resist.
There's no nattering neighbors.
No nattering neighbors.
How can you have nine babies on the new show?
I'm so sad.
The show is a living...
The rugs of nattering maybobs.
This whole show.
I've tried to be as much of a...
God, every time I watch that, I want to shoot myself.
Is that that ghost again?
Yup.
No.
Those things that drift in from outside.
The old rock bands are better than the new ones, you know.
The old rock bands...
Negi loves the old ways back.
It's one of those old...
Old...
Narnunu and rules.
In front of Pebbles.
You know, it's funny.
My dad said the same thing.
He said the old rock bands were the best.
Yeah, I mean, he meant the really old ones.
Yeah, he was talking about Bob Wills.
I'm talking about like, you know, Jim Morrison and Jimi Hendrix and, you know...
Well...
They're really good.
You know, they had to die to be good.
Yeah, you know, they fought...
Now, when you die, you'll be good.
The bands that fought the system are dead, you know.
They're long dead.
Maybe they're all rest in peace.
Yeah, the Miles and Bob is...
What does that tell you?
If you...
If you want to be good...
Die!
Don't sell out.
That's what I was saying earlier.
Oh, yeah, and die too.
But, yeah, don't sell out, you know.
Two keys?
Increase sales.
Kill the deal.
Don't become part of the beast.
Don't sell out.
You know, that's why I enjoy shows like this because, you know, it's untouched by that
media crap, you know.
Untouched?
Well, you know what I mean.
Why?
It's not like...
I think he means I didn't wipe well enough or something.
Yeah, I think so.
I could tell that.
I think so.
Well, do you have a question for the Clean Up UFOs?
Uh...
Huh?
We're just feeling a little bit sick back here.
What?
I don't feel so well, but please, ask any questions to the Clean Up UFOs that you'd
like to ask.
Oh, look, he became shy.
Chill, man.
That happens when you're up against a superhero.
But, acids were the most likely to sell because they were sexy.
Oh.
Wow.
Mm-hmm.
Not you, Gary.
Potential big deal.
Yeah, I was gonna say, like, I'm not gonna lie.
The big dick buyers began lining up as soon as we indicated interest in selling.
This is so funny.
I think it looks like a flop.
But the contest quickly boiled down...
...to police-area's big dick contestants.
What, are you having a, uh, um, uh, um, um...
Now we gotta go further.
There's some kind of peppygasm happening over there across the bay.
Oh, yeah, I see.
Peppygasm?
Peppygasm.
You know, I thought it was.
There's that other guy that plays on Telegraph Avenue.
Yeah, I heard Saddam Hussein has Pepe gas stockpiled.
The butcher of Baghdad has an army of Pepes.
Ready to fly over his much vaunted berms.
The street price.
Saddam's much vaunted berms.
I think he's referring to the missiles.
Are no match for our Republican moms.
At the time I bought the company.
At the price.
Hey, K-Rock.
And if it does, how much?
Cereal.
Juice.
The company was a steal.
Yeah, it's like juice.
But with the cereal gone.
And you just have that sugary milk.
With dextrose and pieces of cereal and milk.
Oh, it's not milk.
It's soy.
It's upstairs.
In this jar.
And you can have some.
It's from Korea.
It's called.
This is called Power Plus.
Are you guys beat?
This is theft.
The other one of my favorites called Five Cereals Drink.
That man is singing back there.
It's not a man.
Provoked to react.
He thinks he's entertaining.
He thinks entertainment is entertainment, man.
Bob said that entertainment would become entertainment.
He went beyond McLuhan.
Bob did.
When he declared that entertainment eventually, finally, after the internet took over,
entertainment would become entertainment.
So, what?
McLuhan then was brought full circle.
And the full meaning of that great Canadian philosopher's ultimate statement was made clear.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, sure.
Cool.
Yeah.
Is this religious stuff?
I thought we were doing business tonight.
What's that white stuff for?
Sorry.
I just got so excited when you were talking about business and religion together.
Well, how do you think this whole thing started?
And I was not going to be denied.
Well, the Frommaster 2000 was started first.
And then the church started about an hour after that.
Did you stop the Frommaster?
Not the Frommaster.
The Frommaster.
Remember those commercials?
Late night TV.
With the Frommaster.
Yeah.
My honest.
Spirit.
And Tibulator.
The first time they started calling.
On TV?
On that 1-800.
Well, it was toll free.
It was before 1-800.
Yeah.
We sold the Frommaster first.
And then when they started actually dialing in with their money, sending the money in
in the credit card numbers, we had to come up with, you know, the instruction booklet
for the Frommaster.
And that was where, that was what finally prompted Philo to get off his ass.
And go to the hospital.
Right.
And Frommaster.
And finally go to the hospital, which is where we met.
And that's how the, uh...
There we go.
We see Philo walking up to receive his award.
Let's wheel Philo up.
Would you believe this man is 86 years old?
He doesn't look a day over 60.
I have a very diversified portfolio of...
No, that's from living here in beautiful Northern California.
Here we go.
Philo will tell you, Northern California is heaven.
But what about...
Caller, where is heaven for you?
Yeah.
Hello?
Hello, hello, hello.
No, he's talking about hell.
No.
He is in hell.
Yep, I'm in my own deep hell.
And the little...
Dealing in my own paranoia.
And stressed out negativity.
I love to do one.
No, that was the other show, Negativity Land.
Ah.
Yeah, it's quite...
Yeah, this is positive land.
This is a new...
We're the new approach.
We're the new...
The new school.
Positive.
Yeah, negative land.
That was for the old geezer people.
Being positive is like being nice to people.
And that's not nice.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, positive land.
In our CDs, we send you helpful stuff.
It's fun pointing out stupid people, though.
Not little things.
It's positiveland.com without the E.
And then there's this other place where they...
When negative land dropped the E, it got stuck every place else.
So it's always e-commerce.
Well, everybody thought it was a typo.
Is that what happened to that E?
Yeah, it was a typo.
Yeah.
They always correct me.
When I put it down.
So I'm trying to figure out what that means in a hundred years from now.
When everything...
The entire countries are called E.
And if you remember, that was a nickname for an intimate partner.
Like when we met.
That's right.
Before it was a drug.
And E was...
E-girl and E-boy was our moniker for each other at that time.
That was before we changed the slang, the official slanguage.
Slanguage doesn't work now anymore.
Well, we changed the alphabet.
And that affected the codes.
The codes.
What did they do with the extra 16 letters in the alphabet?
Um...
What?
Byron has those.
Byron has them.
If you want them back...
I think it was either Byron or Gordon has the other 16 letters.
Maybe that Gordon has eight and Byron has eight.
But they've got your letters.
I was having a hard time spelling the impossible words without them.
Oh, when's breakfast?
This show should be over by now.
Finally!
It's the end!
Because Gary said on the radio it's over.
It is now a completely different new show with all new people.
It's about a very, very big dick.
And that certainly describes me.
I do have a big dick.
I've had, uh...
I've been depilated and I had a few inches added where it's necessary.
So, I don't feel like I'm available.
I'm not a victim of science or that I'm some sort of unnatural miscreant.
I feel like I'm quite viable as a subgenius.
You know what I mean?
Hey, for all you know, you're just somebody's prank.
Like that big foot.
But we keep on missing the ass crack of the joke.
The brunt.
The dig.
The final punchline is never there.
And we never get to enjoy it.
That's what I wonder about.
Now, just because this old po-bucker in Oregon or Washington...
Or wherever...
This old po-bucker.
Walking around faking Bigfoot tracks...
Doesn't mean that those Sherpas were tricking all those expedition leaders in the Himalayas
with Bigfoot track boots.
I told you they'd take a slut to the Himalayas.
So, as they keep expedition leaders coming back and buying Yeti skull caps and so forth...
They sold Yeti skulls on the market?
You see, the Yeti themselves set up these obvious hoax situations.
Because it's not really the conspiracy that doesn't want people to believe in Yetis.
It's the Yetis that do not want people to believe in them.
That's as obvious as a slice of rhubarb pie with a piece of cheese on the side.
I say this to ensure disbelief.
Because I'm saying it on this entertaining little college radio underground thing.
So that, you know, of course, it's all wacky, crazy stuff.
But, in fact...
It's horrible to keep you from ever believing in it.
And as does the Yeti and the... the saucerman.
Well, you are a master of disinformation.
And that's all I can get out of that.
You've made Chaz cry.
You've made me wet my pants.
And I'm...
That's what the blues is all about, baby.
Right.
Sucking your thumb and wetting your pants.
You just lay back and just give up.
Give up and just hand it all over to Bob.
Give him all the credit.
All your money.
Give him your will.
Give him your... your, uh, uh, power of attorney.
Give him the hair on your hands.
Give him your children.
Give him your mind.
Give him the smile on your lips.
Give him your soul and your spinal cord.
Give him your spinal cord and your epiglottis in a bag.
Donate your blood.
Give him your sperm samples, your eggs from your uterus, your...
He made a cycle clear.
You give them to him.
Cut things from your fingernails so he can do voodoo.
You cannot do what he says.
You must think of Bob Dobbs on the phone and think your card.
Shave off all your hair and give it unto Bob.
But start with the wallet, of course, because of all those things I've mentioned, your money
is the most important to you.
And always wash your hands.
Always wash your hands.
Don't forget.
Oh, you can't forget to do that.
And don't forget to disinfect the moon pants.
And it didn't work out at all that great, so...
You washed your hands and they washed you.
Much in the same way we've all been washed clean.
What?
Now, that's true subgenius, I think.
Yes, but we're supposed to say, well, pull it out of your butt and show it to us.
Is that the way our courts system works?
That's not very patriotic, you guys.
This movie is tough.
And that was never more clear than in 1987.
What has our glorious experiment come to?
If you're listening to KPFA, KPFB, and PNP, you shouldn't think about these things at
all.
What has become of Bob's glorious experiment in slack and humor?
Has it devolved into a mishmash mush of audio masturbation?
Pull it out of your butt and show it to us.
Swallowed by the overman, Dr. Philo Drummond.
Now, Dr. Drummond has taken the second half of the pill, the prophesied other half, and
now a third half.
A third half.
The clear half.
There's four halves.
Dr. Drummond's mouth hole has been infested with halves of pills, wizened, wrinkled, old
pills.
Friends, not these new chemical pills.
These are the pills that God created in Eden in the day, the real day, day one.
What?
The pills were here.
I hear Satan trying to call.
I hear my walls talking to me.
It's inside you.
You will be dead within weeks.
I don't hear the dead.
The walls are prophesying.
Yes.
The Baron went home.
Be careful.
Only little Gary is there.
The prophet howling lonely
Yeah, one of those guys.
Damn well.
Street preachers, we'll call them.
Yep.
You're on I thought it was spirits.
Down the hill.
Where do they got streets?
Get yourself inoculated now.
He's a-
He's practicing for his barker job outside the strip joints.
If we had more write-offs, we wouldn't have these prophets to deal with.
Well, you know, actually, we rarely have any of those prophets to deal with,
and we have plenty of write-offs.
There has been a great rise in write-offs.
Is that what happened to LeGoo?
He was written off?
No, no.
Doctor, like, he just went on to the Internet.
That's sort of like disappearing.
You vanish into cyberspace.
Into a digital self.
Yeah, which is, it's not actually real.
I used to think that it was sort of real, and then I decided it wasn't.
But then I decided it was the Internet.
But now I've pretty much arrived at the conclusion it's not really real
until you get the credit card expiration date,
as well as the credit card number.
Then the Internet, at that moment, becomes real.
I'm going to have to reformat my site before I can even eat again.
Did you guys really tell David Meyer to call?
Because I don't even know where to call David Meyer to tell him to call.
Well, I emailed him, actually.
He had sent me.
He sent me some email, and I returned this email with instructions
that he should be right here right now.
Oh, well, you check your email.
He might be on the show by email, and you don't even know it yet.
I'm so stupid.
He's behind.
No wonder you guys don't allow me to do any of the good stuff.
Why don't you just download him?
Well...
Oh, you probably can't deal with binary attachments.
You can't download your emotions in a PowerBook.
Oh.
You have to have the actual full screen.
Well, you can get a kind of...
those choppy emotions, the ones that are kind of low-res.
Yeah, pixelated feelings.
Yeah, kind of a rough-edged happiness or anguish, depending.
This is about the only two emotions I can do.
What about all the anti-alising?
Why is no one...
Oh, I think our boats are...
Some people are, actually.
But it's an acquired taste now.
It's the way people used to be.
Back in the day, everything was not anti-aliased.
It's only in the last ten years that anything was anti-aliased at all,
and yet people don't even see the change.
It happened so gradually that we think everything was always smooth.
Mind you, I'm all wrong.
But in our grandfather's day, everything had that stair-step edge to it.
I remember when I used to have to cut all the photographs up into tiny little squares
to make them look pixelated.
Right.
Remember how your grandpa used to look with the tiny jagged lines around the edge?
Yeah, but it took hours to cut those pictures.
I'm not talking about the pictures.
I mean grandpa.
Well, grandpa...
He himself has...
Rough edges.
Those blocky squares defining him.
I thought those were cigar edges.
I thought that was a sweater.
I thought that was kind of a sweater thing he had going on.
You know, he always had to be a guy.
He always had to be an old man, and he died.
Well, see, that's what I'm saying.
You guys can't even...
You didn't even detect when they started anti-aliasing everything.
And now it's all smooth around the edges.
And then it seems normal to you.
Like, oh, this is the way it's always been.
But it quickly became apparent.
It's frog water syndrome, man.
You know, it's like frog water.
You put a frog in it.
You know, like in some water, man.
You know, and you're like...
If it's boiling water, the frog hops out, man.
You know, but...
Oh, how many millions did they spend on that study?
But, you know, like, man, like frog water.
Like, if you put, like, in cool water, and then you slowly bring it to a boil, then...
And then you add some salt and some butter, and they're really good.
Cool.
I like it, man.
It's frogs, you know.
It's like nature.
Yeah, I'm gonna have to go home and make sure that I wasn't joking.
Save the frogs.
Whatever, man.
Save the frogs, man.
Yeah, it is like nature.
It's naturish.
They told us nothing.
I know.
It's frogs.
You gotta know your frogs.
You wanna know the future?
Study the frogs.
Joey, when you're afraid, do you lay on the ground and put your feet against your tail?
Get really flat?
No, I usually just stick my head up my own butt when I'm really afraid.
I wish I could do that.
Yeah, you can.
You can call 844-44-GRAD.
I'm gonna go to the park and...
It's the ostrich position.
...and do that.
That's right.
It's the ostrich position.
You better listen to me.
Uh-huh.
Like an ostrich eating his pizza with his head stuck in the ground.
Doctor!
Dr. Bob!
Rel
Don't do this anymore!
Directed by
And something's pretty clear. Every one's a Bolivian here.
And there's almost nothing to fear. Cause we got everything we want right here.
We got great big heaping buckets of Bolivian here.
Bum, bum, bum.
The water's here.
Yeah, we're singing a praise to Fox.
Cause he's done a mighty fine job.
Cause I'm slopped up and silly like a rip-headed slob.
And all I got to think is Bob and Ivan Stagg.
And all I got to think is Bob and Dr. Doo.
And all I got to think is Bob and everybody.
You can call it a win a date with Dr. Drummond.
I understand that that's been done frequently.
That Dr. Drummond has been using or abusing this show.
And the public airwaves for purposes of sexual procurement.
Oh, has he scored big time?
I hope his sons and daughters aren't listening to this.
Numerous sons and daughters all birthed on this show.
Not all sporting the name Drummond.
I had my last baby on the show.
Really? Yeah?
Yeah, but it was before Philo lived here. So it was a secret.
And what's the baby? How old's the baby now?
Seventeen.
Seventeen. What's it doing?
What's it doing?
Um, um, um, you know, what a seventeen year old baby does.
What babies do, you know.
What babies do.
You don't want to talk about it on the radio.
Pooping, you know, sucking.
Pooping and breathing. Poop, breathe, suck. Poop, breathe, suck.
Okay. Boy, those were the days.
Oh, I remember that.
When they talk about the day, that was the day I was there.
Man, I remember those days. Do you remember those days, Collar?
When everything was simpler.
When everything was less...
...complex than it was now.
I know. Now it's poop, eat, suck, surf.
Poop, eat, suck, surf.
Jam.
You do a lot of web surfing, do you, Gary?
Yeah, with my tarantula.
Clears the airwaves.
Oh, there's your tarantula just wiped out.
Yeah, I know.
Swims fast with those eight legs.
Runs on the water.
I'm a fan of 13 years.
And he will be your...
Nice music. How come the band couldn't play this?
And the show has won.
It's the Beatles.
Overthrown.
And the fate of one who dares to underestimate the power of woman.
For tomorrow's door of arc will lead womankind into rebirth.
And then will come the golden age.
Power of woman.
Boy, that Jimmy Swaggart sure could prophesy, couldn't he?
Yeah.
Every time he made a bid, they raised their big dick bid by a quarter.
There are some serious problems in our country when we let the media control what you think and what you believe.
Tell us, Bob. Tell us, Bob.
Yeah, that was...
Bob's telling us.
The mighty...
The mighty Bob Tilton.
Dallas preacher Bob Tilton.
I think that will give a whole...
The windy preacher.
Hamanishnemena, Hamanishnemena, Hamanishnemena.
Shalakundalee Basoya.
I love it, speak it in tongues.
The language that God speaks in heaven.
Sow your seed.
When you're seized up in the spirit, you will actually talk God's language.
And I don't mean California announcer accent.
I don't mean down home old Texas whittling front porch man accent.
There's the accent God speaks.
I'm going to gulag heaven.
Televangelist.
B-C-D-E-T-L-O-B-O.
Shikad personal image , shitadelae e tekkabo.
Yellow mucho?
Play that backwards friends.
Let's do it's necklace.
I actually cannot.
What is Bob saying?
When you play it backwards...
DeAh Nicole
Kle Line
It's right.
LaDah basonya.
LaDah basoya.
Lodge
Basoya is uh heaven talk, for frog.
Hey.
5,2,4,4,4
LaDah basoya.
That's the heavenly frog.
015.
Are you guys actually inviting strangers to call?
We're inviting strangers to come down and marry Faso on the air.
I mean, is this station like a glory hole for you?
Oh, yeah.
You should like it.
About this time, you get the guys riding around the hood.
They deny they spoke to you the next day.
Calling us on their cell phones and talking about who you guys are.
You ever see a caller walking down the street and you grab the caller and then they deny that they spoke to you?
No, I don't.
They would always deny, you know, by definition.
99% of the people I grab and shake on the street deny that they spoke to me.
They say they've never called.
They weren't that caller.
Oh, I see what you're saying.
No, no, actually, I don't usually don't want to deal with any of the callers.
You don't grab strangers and try to dump their listening habits right out of them?
I don't call them.
No, I never have.
There are Clevelands behind the times, always.
You wouldn't happen to have one of them smallpox inoculations to spare, would you?
Boy, this is kind of environmental.
There's plenty of spare inoculation.
For an old soldier?
Ah, we have plenty to spare.
Come and sit aboard the back of the truck here.
Relax that wounded leg.
It looks like it may be coming gangrenous.
Oh, that ain't nothing.
I just wanted to give me one of them smallpoxes.
No, no, no, no.
You've just been wounded by a piece of shrapnel and let it to wedge out them feces for the
last weekend.
It's become biotic.
That's just about organ wound.
Don't worry, your organs swing back like our wings.
They are broken into the dark time.
What does it mean when the stock starts coming out of other parts of your body besides your
nuts?
Nose and mouth.
What now?
What does it mean if the angel snot starts coming out of other pores of your body besides
the nasal and the lungs?
It means the indus neish.
It means the indus neish stain.
I think you know what that means, don't you?
I don't know what anything means anymore.
I'm so debilitated.
Yes, ladies and gentlemen, the indus neish.
The man I'm talking about is of the spirit by
his looks and noce.
The man I'm talking about is Mr. Philooooo Inivatte.
Stretchy, stinky, closed mouth.
Nothing at all to say.
All .
That was the ultimate joke.
Cecil was a puppet?
If Cecil the sea serpent was a puppet,
then how can you believe anything is real?
For all we know, Bob could be some made-up character.
For all we know.
Bob could be Beanie.
Bob could be Beanie himself.
For all we know.
Do we really know anything?
Has cultural relativity stripped us of all solid knowledge?
You cannot know anything.
Are we now on a shifting, sandy beach of hypocrisy,
even in science?
You can't not know anything.
Once you know something, you can never unknow it.
You can't not know it.
Only an overman can not know.
You can unknow it.
No, you can't unknow it.
I know that.
You can't unknow it.
You have to talk much closer to this microphone.
Oh, is this the screaming microphone?
Yeah.
That's what I like to think of.
Yes!
Reverend Stang's special screaming microphone.
Yeah, that's the Linton Raven microphone.
You can't not know what you don't really know,
and what you never really wanted to know in the first place.
Those are the kind of paradoxes that the philosopher enjoys,
that the philosopher seeks out,
to test his understanding,
this logical understanding of how the instructions look
for the whole world really works.
I think that goes back to the ancient Greek.
There's no going back.
Once you do see your own mind, you can't quit.
You have to go forward.
Once you have begun that journey inside your own mind,
you cannot ever turn back and go back out.
You can't erase the horrible knowledge
that you have acquired in your inner journey.
What's the use?
So true.
You cannot erase it!
You cannot erase the shock!
The horror!
Yes, you can.
Oh, wait.
Right over there.
Oh, they just...
Oh, okay.
I take it back.
Doctorate in erasability.
I guess you could erase it.
In fact, you might even...
If you forget to hit record...
Erasability.
Then it might as well have never happened.
That's right.
Can you prove it didn't happen?
It didn't happen.
I'm talking about...
What will happen in the future when there's no tape?
How will we know if...
I predict.
...we can prove it?
In the future, there will be no more audio tape,
and everything will be recorded on tiny, flat, shiny discs.
Oh, that's so sad.
Can you prove it won't happen?
I'm lying in bed, you guys.
Oh, no!
I'm doing this exciting radio show from bed.
Bob Dorgan.
In his most disgusting dream is the 175th dream.
This might as well be a bad dream.
I'm lying in bed, hearing this weird music in my head.
This horrible sound.
Lonesome cowboy Dave muttering.
Princess Wee coughing.
Fittingly.
Pitifully.
Faces appearing in the Luxor windows.
The orphans whining.
A sound in the attic.
Cracks in the space-time fabric are appearing and disappearing in front of your eyes, left and right.
The lost souls are moaning.
That old genitalia is making the earth move and shifting time for you.
Some people down this story don't like the noise and may call the police,
but you don't care.
Why could you? How should you?
You've been there before.
You know any day is blast-off day.
You know the code. You know the right mix of chemicals in your own body.
Get ready. Blast off.
The perfect thing to last a day.
He's speaking in tongues. It's the language they spoke in Bible days.
It's what the angels speak.
Bible days.
I remember the Bible days.
The Inukian, the Enochian, the Pebble of the Star People.
The dog-faced Anunnaki.
God loved me then.
Back in the day.
God loved me.
He wanted me. He loved me back then.
He don't love me no more.
God lost his mercy after Waco.
When they killed David Koresh, that's when God lost his mercy for mankind.
He lost his vibrator after Tuesday night's debacle.
They went too far.
Too, too far.
Ever since then, God first went after the ATF.
Now he's after all the rest of America.
Now you don't want that on you.
No, no, not that blue fungus.
It came from Koresh's place after the bomb blasts.
Don't you know?
America has fallen short.
There it went.
Five feet short.
Another one fell in the bucket.
Gone.
You little bucket.
I guess it's time to elongate.
Why not?
Right into the bucket.
Let's get it as big as we can get it.
Because before two elongate.
Well, till next week.
My long john's back on here.
Not since the days of the old Hitler.
Keep your hat on tight.
You're back to the winter and you're sacking the saddle, you dang old son of a bitch.
I'm just gonna roll over and go back to sleep.
Is it the loneliness that I'm gonna cry myself to sleep?
You old son of a bitch.
My heart is saddened like the morning.
Go back to bed, you old son of a bitch.
It's the old diseased coo-roo-yo.
The diseased old coot, son of a cootin' bitch.
Is lonely through the seas.
Dave gotta go pee or something.
He's gonna pee.
He's still smokin'.
He's gonna smoke that one cigarette for 45 minutes.
He's dunkin' this place up.
If you take a break for a half hour, it's okay.
You don't have the smoke in a half hour's time.
It's all right.
I am ill.
I swear to you.
I'm in front of my narrow head.
I'm a paraplegic god.
I swear to you.
This is all for naught.
This is all a bunch.
The principles elongated on this broadcast are not the opinions of anyone living or dead.
It may be considered too incidental.
Some characters are composites.
Other characters are compositional.
And other characters are full and yet to be grown.
Here they are, King Cole of Love.
All the happiness is slowly flying by.
Uh, yes, dear friends.
I'll just listen to my voice.
I've...
...had a bit of a cold.
And, uh...
What better time to record the credits with...
...no background music.
Friends, we've been listening...
...because it was easy to do it this way...
...to, uh, some, uh...
...live subgenius radio shows...
...from two different places, of course.
WWW.CSB Cleveland with ESO Swamp Radio, Lonesome Cowboy Dave and Professor Jazz Smith.
And the, uh, subgenius business retreat marathon five-hour over-the-edge sh...
...and puzzling evidence show...
...engineered by Don Joyce of Negative Land.
And puzzling evidence...
...with Dr. Philo Drummond directing on KPFA in Berkeley, California.
You are listening to...
...a compendium of those subgenius shows.
The subgenius radio ministry hour of slack.
Praise Bob for...
...more information.
Check out www.subgenius.com
Or...
Write to...
Post Office Box 204206 Austin, Texas 78720.
Praise Bob.
Wake up.
If you want a picture of the future, imagine a pipe smoking in a human face forever.
Word up.
Throw off your pants, unroll in your mistakes, get dirty for Bob.
Heart Ignition.
Word up.