You are about to participate in a great adventure.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to...
The Subgenius Hour of Squash!
Yes, we're back, back, back, back, back, back, dear friends.
Where am I? Where am I?
Oh, what a day, what a night, what a week, what a month.
Let me adjust my little levels here, you know, we're, uh...
Working in a void, a void, dear friends.
It's such a delightful void.
Listen to that, that's, um, the Flying Ryan Brothers in the background.
Well, that's cheery music, that's good, I need some cheery music.
Don't worry, I'm not about to complain, although...
Well, I can't, because my mouth is full of Novocaine, dear friends.
It's true, I busted a tooth last night, and I just thought two hours ago had the dentist give me a new tooth,
and that required pumping my jawbone full of Novocaine, and on my left side, I don't know if I'm drooling or not.
And I feel like I must look like the Elephant Man on that side.
Uh...
Uh, yes, yes, it's been a...
Hey, well, wait, before we go on, let's just go on here.
Oh, girls, they're flashing lights in all of the...
Let's see what the boys in the other town do.
Uh, let me ask you...
There's a minotaur who lights his face on fire constantly.
Yeah, I saw that minotaur.
Oh, did you ever see a movie called Jack the Giant Killer?
Yeah.
John, I've seen that.
Oh, I just watched that.
When I was a kid, I loved it.
What did you think of it?
Well, I'll ask you this, was it a musical?
No.
No?
Then you've seen an unpolluted version of it, because that movie was bought by a character
named Moose Charlap.
And Moose changed it into a musical by pixelating the characters, making them jerk back and
forth, and apparently sing songs that he wrote and sang.
It is one of the most bizarre things you ever saw in your life.
Friends, I have to cut in, in the midst of my Novocaine-induced mumbling.
Dr. Howell there on the KPFA show is in fact expound...
Talking whatever, about...
A movie called Jack the Giant Killer.
I doubt if most of you have even seen it.
If you ever get a chance to, it is so, so brain damaged.
It's unbelievable.
Bouncy, boingy-boingy style.
Yes.
So that's the most interesting contemporary thing about Jack the Giant Killer.
Well, this was Ray Harryhausen's first movie.
It has nothing to do with Ray Harryhausen.
Oh, really?
How could that be?
Well, when Ray Harryhausen was making the seventh voyage of Sinbad toward the end of
the 1950s, he took the idea to producer Edward Small and offered the entire concept to Edward
I think the Purins made that movie at some point.
But Small turned it down, and so Harryhausen went back to Charles Schneer, who produced
the seventh voyage of Sinbad, which grossed highly at the box office.
So Edward Small decided to make Jack the Giant Killer a blatant rip-off of the seventh voyage
of Sinbad.
They even measured the Cyclops' steps, the walk cycle, and made their giant Cormoran walk
exactly the same way.
Well, I'm very surprised to find out that Harryhausen wasn't involved in that.
Not at all.
It's a imitation of Harryhausen.
Wow.
The best answer.
The geekiness of the subgeniuses.
I actually know, not only do I know every detail of that obscure movie story that they're
talking about.
But I've handled it.
I've done it.
I've handled the Cormoran model, the original stop-motion model.
A tattered up, beat up, horrible looking little thing made by the young Jim Danforth.
It ended up in Dallas, that model did.
I used to be a stop-motion animator myself, inspired by the great Ray Harryhausen.
Up until recently when I heard Ray, right after Jurassic Park came out at a sci-fi convention,
my hero, my erstwhile hero, Ray Harryhausen, was heard to say,
Well, those dinosaurs in Jurassic Park are just not as good as what we used to do back
in the days of King Kong and the Lost World.
Anyone can push buttons on a computer.
Well, friends, guess what?
I would much rather be working on my computer animation projects and 3D animation right
now than I would doing this show.
And if you knew what, could see what was inside my computer, you'd agree with me.
But, but, but we will nonetheless continue, friends.
A mouthful of mush and all.
Friends, we have been, you know, you would think I would have tons and tons of tape to play.
We have been traveling.
I'm sorry that we had to do reruns last week.
I wish I would love to do a rerun this week, actually.
We went to Rutgers University, did a D Bible there.
We went to Atlanta.
And it had the most amazing, it was a wonderful D Bible starring Sister Susie the floozy and
Dr. Legume and Papa Joe Mama and a really cool band and myself.
And you know what, friends?
I don't have a bit of tape of any of those shows.
Other people do, but not old Reverend Stang, no sir.
No sir.
Atlanta has always been a challenge.
For some reason in that city, it is very hard to record a program.
I didn't know much about it.
I's Б, you know, guide told me it is C but bad enough.
So, what can you do to the doctor businesses around town, and I just try not to have much
I really love Maslow's Voicing letterbox.
your health to find information.
I don't know what they're worries.
I have this.
This year, I was thinking over it, and they weren't very happy with it, dieses mobile
channel.
I love that, theони.
They re-lins TEDacement.
Is somebody like you possible, call me Cron?
The only place that has restraints big enough to hold him.
He's a very, very large dog.
And he gets very riled up if anybody messes with his hideous, diseased, lupus-ridden nose.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
But what else was I going to bitch and gripe about?
I don't know.
A couple of shows back, I was bitching and griping, wasn't I?
About the bobbies and such like.
I was griping about the endless.
No problems.
But you know what?
My friends, I've solved all of my problems with the bobby squabbling and all of that.
You know what I did?
I forgave them.
Just forgave them, friends.
Just decided to forgive everybody.
Forgave myself.
Forgave Jane Dobbs.
Forgave, that's Bob's mom.
I forgave, I forgave everybody.
I forgave John Benet Ramsey.
I did not forgive her parents, though.
Friends, I've...
I'm not going to tell you a bad thing that we did.
When in Atlanta, Sister Susie the floozy, well, she happened to know where the unmarked grave
of the little murdered child, John Benet Ramsey, was there in Atlanta.
And we went there, friends.
Jesus and Susie and I went to the grave of the murdered child.
And there were toys and letters there.
And we did a real bad thing, folks.
We did a real bad thing.
And when I get the tape of the Atlanta revival, then I can reveal to you the bad, bad thing
that we did at the grave of John Benet Ramsey.
I'm not proud.
I'm not proud of what I did.
And I'm not happy at all with the way the sound is on this setup.
But my headphones, if I loaned my headphones to somebody and they got wrecked and now I'm
on bad headphones.
One of my mixing devices just died.
And the volunteers that said so much stopped at that point.
And I should stop at that point and see if I can move on to find some other piece of tape.
When somebody else's show...
Okay, enough.
Enough.
Friends, I'm sorry.
I'm really losing it.
I'm having to...
I need help.
I need...
I need physical help.
You know, maybe I ought to just do a Gene Scott.
What would Gene Scott do at a time like this?
He'd say, well, I guess you Bob believers just ain't believing in Bob like you used to, huh?
I guess you're just going to let me sit here.
I ain't hearing that phone ring.
And actually, it's true, friends.
We ain't been hearing the phone ring.
We haven't heard anybody call 1-888-669-2323.
We haven't...
You all haven't been emailing slack at subgenius.com or staying at subgenius.com, for that matter, to order.
Y'all just...
I don't know.
I'm just going to...
I give up.
I'm just going to go back in time and let an...
I am going to just do reruns.
Hell, I've had it.
I've had it.
What do y'all care anyway?
There's no sense of possessiveness...
There will be a better world.
...in that...
...no zone of the saucers.
Time ceases to exist.
Or at least it feels that way.
And you don't need to be grasping anymore like you did on Earth.
The overwhelming feeling that you get on the escape vessels is like,
wow, the best part is it lasts as long as I want it to,
and I can take forever.
I'm immortal for now.
And I don't have the urge to grab this and keep it
so I can run somewhere else to grab some other thing.
I don't have to kill or defeat another monster.
I don't have to be a monkey man to hang on to these big round soft things.
I'll have plenty of time to get to those other big soft round things.
More than I could ever use.
My pipe overfloweth,
and the big round soft things shall follow me through the land of Dobbs,
and I will dwell in the cleft in between forever.
It's like, oh, how are your multiple partners today, dear?
Oh?
Big and random?
Round and soft?
Ah, yes.
And there's, but people ask so many questions.
I say, well, Reverend Stang, is there just one giant saucer,
or is it a bunch of regional saucers, you know,
like an East Coast saucer and a West Coast saucer?
No, there's a million kinds of saucers, friends,
but it's like virtual reality.
So once you're inside one of them, you might as well be in all of them.
You might as well be on Planet X.
You're not in normal space.
You can sort of phase to the other side.
You can go to other saucers or find your friends telepathically.
And go, oh, I think I'll go to the Chinese saucer today,
or I'll go to the gay and lesbian saucer.
Gee, I always wanted to try being a lesbian female.
But meanwhile, those who are left behind,
which is 99% of the population and probably 90% of the subgeniuses,
all those who didn't sin, they're $20.
They'll miss out on X Day.
You know, come to think of it, I never sinned.
Technically, I mean, I've spent a lot of my own money on the church,
but I never sent my $20 in for a membership.
Dr. Drummond never did.
Palmer Vredes never did.
Puzzling Evidence never did.
Sterno never did.
And, you know, friends, it won't matter what you did for Bob.
What'll matter is whether you sent that for that membership card.
I guess I'm going to have to get around to that.
Well, I got plenty of time, plenty of time till X Day.
Oh, hell, that's 1998.
We got all the time in the world.
There will be one big escape vessel just for the doctors, for the hierarchy.
And I can just see Byron and Gordon and some of those other people up there going,
hey, you know, we ought to go down and save Ivan and Philo
and all those who never got around to sending the $20.
And then they'll go, well, we'll get around to it.
Heh, heh, heh.
We're not sure where the escape vessels of the sex goddesses go,
dear friends.
As far as I can tell, they probably just fly around.
But I'm going to go, I'm going to get off of this for right now.
We'll go to an old hymn.
This is a lovely old subgen...
And I do mean old.
This is like from 1981.
Old subgenius hymn by someone we only know as Doug No. 4.
Oh, yes.
Young will die for caw.
I want to die in a holy hole and thrive.
The bank boys and the normals.
If we have to, if we have to, probably make them die,
and we'll all come back older men, we'll all come back older men,
and we'll all come back older men,
old older men.
The reason why.
See, we've got another key.
Praise Bob.
Kill me, Bob.
I want to buy from Bob.
I want to buy and ask the holy war fulfilled.
The pink boys and the corn boys.
They went, they went.
We can make them buy.
And we'll all come back home.
And we'll all come out over men.
If we don't come out over men, there ain't no reason why.
All times, gizms, they will fall beneath our laser blades.
And we'll all come back home.
But we'll all come back home.
But, well, he's not going to lack for royalties, dear friends.
Because he'll be on those saucers.
And I hope, I hope that you will, too.
I hope you'll join us there on that lovely day.
And to make sure that, let's go through some of these things to double check just before X Day.
There'll be more of this in our upcoming book, Revelation X.
This is where a lot of these notes are coming from, by the way, friends.
From a research session between myself and my wife.
And Dr. G. Gordon Gordon in conference with that man, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Yes, sort of a teleconference that we were on.
Praise this modern day technology.
That way we didn't have to be in the same room with Bob.
Don't you see?
But anyway, I mean, you don't want to miss your chance to be on the escape vessels of the sex goddesses on X Day.
You don't want to end up down on Earth being fried.
You don't want to be on the same planet as the other sex goddesses.
Now, you never know.
X Day might come early.
So keep it with you.
Subgeniuses often lose those in the wash.
We get a lot of mail from people saying that.
I washed my membership card.
Can I have another one?
And you don't want that to happen just before X Day, friends.
So if you're members who have lost their cards, but who are paid up and on the master disk of souls,
because we can tell.
You can't fool us.
We'll give you a free replacement card from the Dallas headquarters anytime, free of charge,
just by sending your self-addressed stamped envelope.
This is members only.
To Bob.
And we'll be giving that post office box number soon in the broadcast.
P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214 is what I'll be telling you.
But, ah, X Day.
You know, on X Day, for those down below on Earth,
you know, it'll be a little different than it would be up in the escape.
Vessels of the sex goddesses.
They'll look up trying to put while they're trying to put their clothes out.
There'll be this huge eyeball in the sky, this giant pyramid shaped light form with a big eye that just covers the whole sky.
And it's filming for the escape vessel screens.
Oh, yes.
When we can watch what's going on down there, we can watch any part of it we want.
And we can also leave messages because it.
The big eye projects sort of billboards, holographic billboards from horizon to horizon that say things like.
Smile.
You know, welcome to your stupid life.
You're being seen live on the escape vessels of the sex goddess screens where the subgeniuses are now partying.
You dumb idiots.
I mean, a big billboard stretching all across the planet in all languages saying fools.
We're having a great time.
And the subgeniuses can take turns broadcasting personal statements.
So, you know, this horrible pink evil person will be down there fighting the Robeast.
And suddenly there's this voice will ring out.
Hey, Mrs. Darden, I was in your 1959 fifth grade class.
Remember me?
Steve Wilcox.
Ha ha.
I'm up here.
You're down there.
Or like pain radio coming to you, Mr. Shaughnessy, the principal.
Remember when you expelled?
How do you like the pain?
And, you know, you get back at anybody.
Oh, you laughed at me in junior high, Max.
You put me upside down into a trash can.
You and your jock friends.
You aren't laughing quite so hard now, are you?
And there'll be little holographic ghost-like things.
Green slime type ghost sort of things.
Millions of little 3D Janers flying around taunting and saying you should have spent your $20.
You should have spent.
You're $20.
Oh, friends.
Friends.
Oh, praise Bob.
Praise Bob.
It's going to be so.
But, you know, and so we find that the world isn't really to be destroyed.
It's that the humans, what happens is the humans are given all this alien technology
and they screw everything up.
They've got a miracle machine there, this mom thing that could do anything they want,
but nobody pays any attention to it at first because they don't know what its capabilities are.
And it's real cautious about revealing itself too fast.
And they don't know that this fungus that's growing around them could fulfill their wildest desires
because they don't believe it can, because they don't have any wild desires,
because they didn't think to ask.
And people will be down there in the ruins begging us with their last potato to preach and deliver unto them the word of Dobbs
because it's the only thing that'll save them.
And subgenius artifacts like old copies of the book of the subgenius or illegal bootleg tapes of this radio show,
original pamphlet number ones, even an old Dobbs head, it'll be worth a boxcar full of canned peaches, friends,
because the luck shell, the luck shell that we've always claimed was around our various products
that you thought we were only kidding about, and that's real.
And it will become visible on X day, a glow that's visible even in daylight.
Any day.
Any given page of the printed word of Bob will be not only of practical use as lamps in the dark,
but more importantly, they'll be unthinkably valuable religious treasures, dear friends,
the most valuable things on the whole planet.
Because you're safer if you have that, if you've got a copy of the show with you.
It tips your luck playing.
It helps a whole lot against radiation and landslides and brain worms and noise demons and nerve runners
and all that.
It isn't nearly like having a membership card, but it's a lot better than having nothing.
Because friends, your faith, your faith in Bob will be all you have left on that day.
And he'll know whether you believed in him.
Wotan will know.
And he will come.
He will come to judge.
The X in the room.
Have landed, Earth's under their control.
Dobbs vision, sky's proven.
The city's radioactive holes.
We don't know what they're gaming.
But their name is unpronounceable.
We don't know what they came for.
But what they aim for is impossible.
But despair not, we beings.
In the second year before the millennium of the day of God,
come Wednesday, as in the twinkling,
of night, they will come among the Yarkatism,
which are like unto thy great white brothers.
They come as men, as grave and impetuous,
as a whirlwind and as a cloud,
and they are now the heavens, let it go.
The extras have landed, their machines,
following our tracks.
Yes.
Then we're on the moon,
and thewrite,
glaring.
Everyone,
birds幡
a single light습니까
según
The Thuoken
LIzos
O O
20th
27th
Destruction! Nuclear Armageddon! All-out war!
Now, most beings, they're afraid of what they see.
Oh, no, we might get hurt, they say.
Damn right! And that's the beauty of it.
Not only are they going to get hurt, they're going to get killed.
Each and every one of them.
They're going to be slimming in their own blood.
Now, what about the subgenies, you say?
Well, we're all in this together now, you say.
Right? Wrong!
We've got a lifeguard, someone to toss us a lifesaver.
That life preserver is none other than J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And the rope that connects us to his salvation is slack.
The only way you're going to be able to reach Bob Dobbs and stay afloat
is to have enough slack on your lifeline.
Now, friends, what does it take to have enough slack?
For one thing, you should always remember who you are working for.
Now, the pinks, they think they're going to retire for the conspiracy,
and the conspiracy is going to protect them.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Oh, they have a rude awakening in store for them now, don't they?
Yes.
It will begin as a small conflict, a police action, if you will.
Then it will expand and grow and engulf the Persian Gulf.
Next you'll know they'll be knocking at your door and ringing on your telephone.
Guess who gets an all-expense-paid trip to the Mediterranean?
They don't call it Club Med for nothing.
The Med stands for medical, because that's where you're going to wind up.
But the real fun doesn't even start until the bombs start going off in your very own neighborhood.
Oh, sure, at first it'll only be a local terrorist or two,
so it won't be as if you're being blown to bits by strangers.
But then again, what difference does it make when you're flying through air with the greatest of ease, eh?
Besides, it's only a matter of time before it begins to rain bombs from the heavens.
You won't be able to step outside without getting an instant flash burn.
What's that you say?
Everyone is on our side?
The world is united so no one would want to attack us?
Who said the bombs would be coming from anywhere on this world?
Friends, they'll be dropped from sub-orbits.
From intergalactic sanitation and sterilization ships dispatched from our good old friends up yonder on Planet 10.
They'll watch until the pinks are pretty well pooped from killing each other.
And then they'll come on down and mop up.
The killdozers and amphibious land shark ships will sweep across the countryside with typical efficiency.
They'll round up the pinks like cattle.
Death will take a holiday.
The lucky ones will die quick.
The unlucky ones will die slow.
And the moron majority won't die at all.
They'll be put in plastic bags and freeze-dried for convenient interplanetary self-surgery.
Oh, don't you believe the conspiracy lies that pinks don't taste good?
They may not have good taste, but they damn sure taste good!
This is just a plain and simple fact you must take on faith.
For even Bob Dobbs does not suggest that you eat pinks before X-Day.
Lick pinks, now that's alright, but eat them taboo!
They're a dessert to be savored, to be saved.
I only think that a pink can't be freeze-dried.
And then thaw back to life.
But you're wrong.
Her talking about a conspiracy technology there folks.
but we're talking about the same brains
but we're talking about the same brains that can go traveling through light years
and instantaneous folding of space!
Do you think the minds that contain the wisdom of the universe
Would allow the pinks to escape life with nothing more
Having nothing more than a FREEZE BURN?
Why, That only measures 265 candles on the agony scale.
Getting sliced to death by paper cuts earns less candles than that.
done to you, you're willing to send them off with a mere million paper cuts? Have you no human
dignity? Have you at long last surrendered all semblance of common decency? Bob said, do unto
them as they have done unto you. So anything short of the glass rod ramming routine is fair game.
Then again, nah. Don't let anybody say the subgenius don't have a little compassion here
and there. So where does this leave us today, dear friends? It radiates new hope amongst the dark and
dreary horizon, while some whine and whimper about the possible loss of a few million lives,
hither tither and yon. We celebrate, for bubblical prophecy is coming to fruition.
At long last, the exes will come forth to wreak Bob's revenge. For lo, these many years of yearning,
burning, and churning amongst the pseudo-syllable substance some say sucks. Let my people go.
Swing low, sweet chariots of fire. They're coming to take us away, huh?
Yea, the indus nigh. So eat, drink, and be merry, for tomorrow they die. Praise Bob, amen.
Oh, praise Bob. Praise Bob. What a beautiful, beautiful thing. That was Father Joe Mama,
also known as Papa Joe Mama. We call him that sometimes. And before that, of course,
the redoubtable Pastor Butt Naked, Butt Naked and the Jaybirds, doing that classic
subgenius song, The Way It Should Be Done.
The exes have landed. Ah, yes. And while I'm thinking about show,
if anybody out there got a copy, a good stereo copy of this show,
particularly somebody who lives, like, in Arlington, give us a call up here at the station.
And, uh, because we'll probably, there's probably two or three people in there.
I guess we must have gotten a good stereo copy of that show somehow or another.
Friends, sorry to have to do reruns like this.
Number one, this stuff is really classic. That was a great rant by Father Joe Mama.
The other, the other thing is, friends, it's true that I do have hundreds of new tapes,
hundreds of new tapes that you haven't heard and I haven't heard, because they're all 90 minutes long.
And I have tried to listen to some of them while I was, you know, in between all the menial crap I have to do.
But, man, it's like there's, if there's 10 minutes of crud at the end of the show, it's like,
I can't, I can't, I just don't have time to edit this stuff anymore.
I don't have time to listen to all of your tune-ups, friends.
And I don't have time to listen to your pledge drive stuff for your local station.
I really want to be playing more hour, more original material on Hour of Slack,
but you aren't making it easy on me, man.
Um, and, and, and, oh, oh.
But, but I'm going to do, the side two of show will just be, I'm just going to start grabbing tapes.
I do have a hundred new tapes. I'm just going to start grabbing them.
I'm going to stick them in.
Paranoid yet? No?
Well, let me ask you this.
What do the American Communist Party, the Ku Klux Klan, and the Universal Church of the Subgenius have in common?
Government funding again, Dr. Void?
Hell no, stupid.
The conspiracy has learned its lesson about the funding part, and they don't waste any money on the church.
The informers.
The Church of the Subgenius.
The Church of the Subgenius is packed to the gills with government informers.
Think about it for a minute.
Hell, think about it for an hour.
Most so-called subgeniuses are loners.
Rebellious, maladjusted, antisocial, subversive, loners.
They do not join organizations because of their basic antisocial orientation.
No organization that is, except the Universal Church of the Subgenius.
All of us who would have fallen through the cracks of the conspiracy,
monitoring apparatus, all of you anti-American way, anti-conspiracy, rebel loners,
have been found and put on the list.
Hell, you put yourselves on the list when you first rode into Dallas for the free information about the church.
Ha! You thought then that you'd found something free,
even though you know damn good and well that this country is ruled by the conspiracy,
and under the conspiracy's rule, nothing, and I mean nothing, is for free.
You have paid and are still paying the price for your free information.
If you paid your $30 for a membership, then you're on the A-list, alright,
but not the A-list for any stupid pleasure ships or sex goddesses,
but the smaller list, the boiled down list of hardcore malcontents
who will be watched all the more for having become ministers.
What does the conspiracy value above all else? Money!
By sacrificing some of your money, you can get your money back.
By sacrificing your hard-earned money, you have proven to the conspiracy
that you are a greater threat than even those who merely rode in to ask about the church.
In this way, the conspiracy even gets you to identify yourself as the enemy they must identify,
categorize, and destroy.
The beauty of this is that you even help finance their infiltration efforts
instead of them supporting the church and its informers.
It's a self-financing operation.
But wait.
Am I accusing Reverend Stang of being a traitor?
Of being a government conspiracy agent?
A lying rat for the normal human forces of evil?
Of course not. He's not that smart.
But who is that smart?
Who's behind it?
Philo Drummond. Overman, first degree.
Why do you think Dr. Philo never rants,
never appears at devivals as a speaker,
but instead pretends to front a rock band called the Swinging Love Corpses
even though he can't sing, or even sing?
Or play an instrument worth a bucket of warm spit?
It's the perfect cover.
This way he can always be hanging around without incurring suspicion,
with Stang as his lightning rod frontman to attract all the attention.
Reverend Stang is actually FBI Special Agent Philo Drummond's dupe,
with the mission of locating and registering all you individualist rebels,
while Drummond looks over his shoulder at that ever-growing list.
Think about it.
It was Drummond who talked Stang into going on the internet in the first place,
even though Stang didn't want to in the beginning.
Drummond wants us all on the net,
so we can all be watched more effectively and easily.
He's even got Stang saying stupid things like,
the internet is the last lawless frontier of communication.
What a laugh. What a dirty, ironic laugh.
On the cover of USA Today just last week,
the conspiracy boasted that they busted over 40 child porno buyers,
by doing what?
Monitoring the net!
There are conspiracy law enforcement creeps crawling all over the internet,
watching everything you post there.
They maintain the illusion of freedom on it,
in order to encourage you to reveal yourself and your activities and plans.
They couldn't have found you by conventional investigation,
so they've gotten you to register yourself for it.
Why do you think I'm not on the net?
Because I know the free speech on the net crap is a lie.
A lie that Reverend Stang has been foolish enough to fall for.
Who knows, the poor sap probably has a Frankenstein computer god control microchip
planted right in his cerebrum and doesn't even know it himself.
And Philo, good old overman first degree Philo,
sits quietly in the shadows and chuckles at your blind stupidity.
He's got Stang urging you all to get on the internet and write to the church
and talk about what kind of anti-conspiracy scams you're cooking up
right there in the open for all to see and hear.
Tell you what, try posting something truly illegal on the internet,
like those kiddie porn people did, and see how fast they bust your ass.
The Church of the Subgenius is a conspiracy front,
and I for one am not afraid to say so.
If you're underground now and want to stay that way,
you'd better tear up all that church literature, change your name,
move with no forwarding address, and pay cash for everything you buy.
Even if you do all that, they are likely to find you, but maybe they won't.
Meanwhile, I am now announcing the formation of a new church,
a new religion for the unhappy, the unruly, and the untamed.
I'm calling it the Universal Church of the Not-Quite-So-Damn-Stupid.
But how can you know that you can trust me?
How can you be sure that I'm not an agent of the conspiracy
seeking to undermine your precious church of rebellion and sin of sarcasm?
I'll tell you how.
I don't want your freakin' name.
There's nothing to write in for, no place to write to to contact me,
and get your name, made-up church name or your real one, on any list.
I don't want to know who you are,
because I don't want the conspiracy to find out from me somehow
who you are or where you live.
I'd probably hate you if I knew you anyway,
if you're just another subgenius dumbass.
All I ask is that you tune into this show and get the truth,
the real, unvarnished, untraceable to you truth
about the conspiracy and their army of informers.
This show is the last real voice of freedom in this country,
and you can trust me.
Because I don't want to know who you are,
and the agents of the conspiracy will never know who you are.
What the hell? What are you idiots doing in here?
Can't you see I'm doing my show?
Get the hell out of my damn studio, you piece of crap!
Oh my God! No! No!
Turn off that microphone.
You really... Oh, God.
Eh, Reverend Dr. Nolan Void.
Uh...
Oh, man.
Oh, what a...
What a...
Really, man?
Who you gonna trust?
Well, one thing you...
One thing that you know we're serious about here at the Church of the Subgenius,
at least the Dallas headquarters,
we're not lying about this.
We really do want your money.
Now, let's see how Jehovah Hates Fred's new album sounds.
So far, it seems to be completely blank.
Is there any slack out there?
Is there any slack...
Out there
Well, okay.
We know how the first song goes.
Oh, good.
They faded it out just in time, I think.
I hope.
Well, let's see.
Friends, you see why it is actually rather time-consuming
to put together a radio show.
And because I would have to listen to all of this noodling
in order to know that it was, in fact, noodling.
It's probably pretty good noodling for a bunch of amateurs.
It's St. Andrew and Pope Fred.
Andrew is the cute one, and Pope Fred is the one that everyone likes.
There's supposed to be a song about Connie on this.
Well, there's...
Connie, do you think that Bob is dead?
Connie, do you think that X-Day will come?
Ooh, ah
What's up, genius? Just be dumb
Hush now, Bobby, Bobby, don't you fear
The X's will come and they soon will be here
Bob Dobbs is coming
I promised you they would be here
You'll be up on the saucers at day
Bakes will all fry, but you will be safe
Just so long that you've proved that you've paid
Ooh, Bob
Of course we will help find the car
Connie, do you think I'm good enough?
Ooh, Bob
Connie, do you think I should quit?
Conny, do you think I'm good enough?
Ooh,Spider, who's there to get me?
Who's there to get me when I'm gone?
Ooh, Bob
Oh, Bob, come at all
Hush now, Bobby, Bobby, don't you fear
The exes will come and they soon will be here
Bob Dobbs has promised you they would be here
You'll be upon the saucers at day
Things will all die but you will be saved
For so long that you've proved that you've paid
Oh, Bob, oh, Bob, oh, Bob
Of course there will be an ex day
Connie, did they have to break the pipe?
Oh, isn't that sweet?
Well, I'm glad I checked some of the new tapes that came in
Yeah, Jehovah hates Fred
They're St. Andrew making, like, Sting or Bono or somebody
Uh, well, hold it
Where's that feedback coming from?
Hold it, hold it, hold it
On we go, we're the wild and young
Crying high into the storm
Hamaker Schlemmer is selling a shelter
Worthy of Kublai Khan's Xanadu Dome
Hushy and swanky with poshanky-panky
That affluent jankies can really call home
Hamaker Schlemmer is selling a shelter
A push-button palace, fluorescent repose
Electric devices for facing a crisis
With frozen fruit ices and cinema shows
Hamaker Schlemmer is selling a shelter
Our chromium kitchens and rubber-tiled dorms
With waterproof portals to echo the chortles
Of weatherproof mortals in hydrogen storms
What a great come to glory in Portland
To enjoy a deluxe moratorium
Where nuclear heat can beguile the elite
In a creme de la creme crematorium
I've been to Nagasaki, Hiroshima too
The same I did to them, baby, I can do to you
Cause I'm a fujiyama mama
And I'm just about to blow my top
Fujiyama, yama, fujiyama
And when I start erupting
Ain't nobody gonna make me stop
I drink a quarter sacky
Smoke dynamite
I chase it with the backy
And then shoot out the light
Cause I'm a fujiyama mama
And I'm just about to blow my top
Fujiyama, yama, fujiyama
And when I start erupting
Ain't nobody gonna make me stop
Well, you can talk about me
Say that I'm mean
I'll blow your head off, baby
With nitro glycerin
Cause I'm a fujiyama mama
And I'm just about to blow my top
Fujiyama, yama, fujiyama
And when I start erupting
Ain't nobody gonna make me stop
Well, you can say I'm crazy
But I'm not crazy at all
So deaf and dumb
But I can cause destruction
Just like the atom bomb
Cause I'm a fujiyama mama
And I'm just about to blow my top
Fujiyama, yama, fujiyama
And when I start erupting
Ain't nobody gonna make me stop
I drink a quarter sacky
Smoke dynamite
I chase it with the backy
And then shoot out the light
Cause I'm a fujiyama mama
And I'm just about to blow my top
Fujiyama, yama, fujiyama
And when I start erupting
Ain't nobody gonna make me stop
The planet is pulling loose from its moorings
Careening into space
Spilling cities and mountains and seas
Into the void
Spinning faster and faster
Days and nights
Flash by like subway stations
Iron penis chimneys
Ejaculate blue sparks
In a reek of ozone
Tunnels crunch down
Teeth of concrete and steel
Platining cars like beer cans
Graffiti through glass and steel
Like acid races across the sky
And tornadoes of flaming
Repent
Quit your job
Slack off
Friends
The old pooperoo
The old fart was smart
The old Bill Burrows there
So much of that rant of his got played in the last few shows
I honestly can't remember what got played and what didn't
Running a little bit of this music and stuff
Has been from Suzy the Floozy's Apocalypse show
And I was just sitting here listening to that
And I thought that maybe I should say something about that
I know you may know me
And I think that I know that I'm not on the show
This is a very long time ago
You may have noticed that lately I haven't been
Preparing special rants for the show
And ranting them
And you get the impression that I'm like
Throwing this show together in two hours
At the last minute before we have to start dubbing them
And sending them out
And that's exactly right
And the truth of the matter is
Folks, I'm trying to learn how to delegate
I've been babysitting
subgeniuses for the last almost 20 years and it's just about driven me nuts so I decided
among other things that I was just gonna quit gonna start delegate just if when people offer
to do things I would say okay and when they don't do them it's not my fault you know it's like I
delegated it if it ain't getting done well too bad and and actually I have been a very hard-working
preacher on but it's in an area that nobody is gonna it's like everything else I've ever tried
to do my whole life I was working for Bob nobody's gonna understand it until it's all done and then
when it's all done you'll all go oh man I was gonna do that but I watched TV instead so I
we are working on something but friends are so damn much stuff we're trying to do around here
we got X days coming up in what 412 days and our as of as of the day I'm talking from and there's
just I mean we've got the the internet stuff we've just mailed out a stark fist y'all should have
that by now any dues paying members we you know we're doing the mail order stuff we're doing the
we're working on a game with Steve Jackson
we're working on a whole lot of men I've got these well it's it's the 3d Bob man it's the
Antichrist we he we have the technology we're getting closer I merged him with a naked woman
last night last night I created a form I've been making a lot of little about every night I make
a couple of new homunculus Dobbs is I'm not the only one working on him I get the image like the
Prophet Jim sent has sent a couple of his attempts at the world's greatest and the world's greatest
the image map texture mapping it's tricky it's real hard but if we can get if we can master a false
Dobbs in virtual space I mean that's it we what we can if we give him enough personality we can
just release him he'll be the virus we can I'll be able to retire I'll actually be able to retire
I'll be able to watch that show the X-Files I've never watched that show because on Sunday night I
preach on the IRC actually on the internet hey hear that that's a phone call so you're asking
yourself of course Reverend Stang what can I do to help and besides support my local station that
plays this weird radio and well I I'm not split this is non-profit radio so I'm not going to state
the obvious but
when when y'all send tapes in don't send a not unless your sister Susie the floozy or a pretty girl don't send a 90 minute tape and it's and and and expect me to to weigh down to the very last song that has the cool part in it you know just have some mercy friends we've just you've got a I forget I forgive you I forgive you in advance for it
Unexpectedly
me Reverend Stang not Bob but me a just some dumb hippy redneck in Texas to make you rich and
famous like I am I forgive you for inviting me to do that that's not a problem
but you know just keep in mind that's all just fight tough
manners folks just remember your manners it politeness is so important and it's a forgotten
school in today's modern world with all this
hustle and bustle? Why, when was the last time you held the door open for a little old lady and
walked her across the street? When was the last time you called up your old ma and said, ma,
I love you? Friends, remember your manners. It's a message of love. Don't you run away.
A vast souvenir postcard of Grand Canyon. Repent. Quit your job. Slag off. Water trucks
slosh out paint. Outlaw painters armed with paint pistols paint everything and everyone in reach.
Survival artists paint cans strapped to their backs, grenades at their belts.
Paint anything and anybody within range.
Sky riders dogfight collide and explode.
Blood, fire, and pillars of smoke. The exact effects of a nuclear blast.
Zephaniah 118, the whole land shall be devoured by the fire of his jealousy.
Malachi 4, on the day cometh that shall burn as an oven. Revelation 8, 7, a third part of the
trees was burned. All green grass was burned. And I want to pause there for a moment because it says
a third part of the earth was burned.
What is this?
You go for a lick of salamis!
You go for a lick, you salamis!
Oh, welcome back, Seekers.
It's just me again, your Spiritual wet-nap, Reverend Susie the Floozy.
Ooh, I'm feeling cooler since my hair fell out.
Can't tell if I'm getting much of a tan yet. These theta rays are real hard on the old peepers.
But hey, if crispness is any indication, I'll be looking fine and foxy by the end of this show.
But that's if we can survive, Seekers, because there are constantly forces at work striving to
bring about the end of the world as we or anyone or anything.
be looking fine and foxy by the end of this show. But that's if we can survive, Seekers, because there are constantly forces at work striving to bring about the end of the world as we or anyone or anything.
knows it. Even now, independent of each other, countless conspiracies are plotting just how
and when to imminentize the eschaton. And hey, when you get down to it, I'm all for
it any way it can happen. Because whether fried by the X's or the pinks, it would be
the greater planetary mercy. Because only global incineration can sterilize this reeking,
stinking cat box earth. Oh, sometimes, Seekers, I swear I don't think I can make it till
X-Day. Oh, but stop me before I pick up a hope habit like some people. Micro-phallus,
intellectual vermin like those L5 society losers are banking on technology to save their
larded asses. Ha! Who are they kidding? Oh, because of technology, they can't get out
of their Barca loungers to walk to the TV.
They can't even be to change channels anymore. They sure as hell won't be dragging their
flabby pink butts off the planet before our Armageddon shows up. Oh, but as for me, there
yet glimmers hope in my bosom. Oh wait, it's just a crusty old sequin. Oh, but still, I'm
feverishly scanning the horizon for the three stooges of the apocalypse. And there they
are, with a fourth stooge, Bob!
Oh hey, I'm back!
Hopping a walk big time! For I shall ascend up into the heavens in the glory of Bob, while
the pinks are too busy frying in their own rancid fat to look up my skirt. Oh, I shall
be ruptured up into the escape vessels of the sex goddesses, and smothered with mounds
of warm, squishy slack. Yay, though I walk through the valley of duh, I shall fear no
weasels, because Bob is with me, and I can tell by the lump in his pants.
Oh, I've got protection. Protection that money CAN buy!
Oh yes, the Church of the Subgenius dispenses better protective devices than Schmidt Laboratories,
kids. You can get that crucial, life-saving information from the source itself, the radiation-proof
subterranean bunkers of the Church of the Subgenius compound, way down in Dallas. Just
write to Bob, P.O. Box 140.
0306 Dallas, Texas 75214. And hey, lead shielding can't protect you from the X's death rays,
but a tiny pasteboard membership card can provide full-body protection from the Yakke-tizma
itself. Yes! Oh, my other car is an X's escape vessel, and you're not on it!
Will be added on text.
Atomic flesh du-luke!
Atomic flesh du-
Atomic flesh du-luke! Atomic flesh du-luke!
Atomic flesh too! Atomic flesh too! Atomic flesh too! Atomic flesh too! Atomic flesh too! I feel I have to từknick it up a fast.
Atomic Flash Deux
The Assassin
The Mannequin
The Diabolo
The Gigo
The Pure Roman
It's up to you
The cocaine
In beautiful Vienna
The Futurist
The Extremist
He just said, beautiful
Atomic Flash Deux
Kalahari
Harahara
Kiri Kiri
Kirihara
Harahara
Harakiri
Atomic Flash Deux