🎵
Bye!
Ah, yes, dear friends, it is rerun time again.
But you'll be glad to know that we're not going to just do the same old three Christmas Hour of Slack show reruns in a row.
No, I'm going to compress it all into just this one intensive total rerun show.
Except that actually it's not the whole first half will be largely peppered.
A new Christmas sickness for the holidays and holy days and the hole-in-head days, as it is for some people.
Actually, I have to work double time because it's the season of selling.
Selling, yes! Oh, you wouldn't believe what the elves have done over at the subgenius catalogs.
But anyway, happy whatever you do.
Thank you.
Ah, yes, this music in the background is somebody named Kenny Wayne Shepard.
Yeah, there's an album called Merry Axmus and Guitar Axmus.
It's cool, man, cool!
And praise Bob and...
Ho, ho, ho!
I'd like to find the guy who done me wrong
And stuck my butt up on this Christmas tree
Ho, ho, ho!
Ho, ho!
Boo!
Who pooped the stump in my romp-a-pomp-a-pomp?
Who tuck and jammed it in my ramb-a-lam-a ding-dong?
Who stubbed the wood where I poop-she-poop-she-poop?
Who pooped the stick up my hip-day-dip-de-dip?
Who was that man?
He shoved it up my can
And left me stranded on this Christmas tree?
Mr. Spock, ou!
Will you stop it?
When this angel heard
Chop-a-pop-a-chop-a-pop-a-chop
A dreadful fear went right into my heart
Those pine tree needles sting me
Ram-a-jam-a-ram-a-jam-a-nam-a-ding-dong
You'll never know how much that smarts
So who put the stump in my romp-a-bomp-a-bomp
Who took and jammed it in my ram-a-lam-a-ding-dong
Who stood the wood where I boop-sheep-boop-sheep-boop
Who put the stick up my hip-a-dip-a-dip
Who took that bush and crammed it in my tush
He made this angel beg for mercy, please
I might squeeze him too tight
It's that psychedelic time of the year
The year of the beast
You know where your brain cells are
It's already 9 p.m.
Don't go looking out in the backyard to dog-aid him
Don't go walking down to the bar
Cause old Frankie died last night in the backyard
I mean, in the apartment store
Oh, can I borrow the brain cells tonight?
Yeah, he brought back the chainsaw
Yeah, and I ain't gonna let you use the brain cells
Till I get the damn chainsaw fixed
And back in my arm the way it was Tuesday
And I'm gonna give my boss a him
Now you boys be good and I'll give you something to see
Apple mango pie
It ain't no good of a child
The dog's runin' off with him brain cells
Can you do something about that, boy?
I'm gonna have to, I'm gonna have to
I'm gonna have to
Could be his head wasn't screwed on just right.
What?
Eric Crespo!
What wing is manufactured with Sally is fun.
The fate of a child.
Spend all the money you've got.
The Christmas truck.
I've lost my freaking mind.
Dave's dressed like Santa Claus.
He's like a cowboy.
Santa.
How jolly.
Oh, Jazz is giving, gives Dave the show pills.
Boy, I really need one of those.
What am I going to do about laundromat in this suit though?
I need the show bath.
The show de-lousing.
Oh, Dave doesn't even have headphones yet.
That's enough of that.
Oh, he's got headphones.
I also have the part of my pancreas that I'd like to show you now.
It's been increased in size to...
Oh, your pancreas?
This looks lovely, Dave.
Look at swelling!
I actually have the capability of a man of 190 IQ's brain power.
I'll put more pills out for everybody.
Yum.
Oh, those pills.
They make my mouth feel like it's on fire.
Ah, more pills.
And my brain feel like it's a puddle of liquefied crystals.
I'm shocked by...
I'm sorry.
The red pills are really good.
I like to take the red one and the blue one.
The red one and the blue one.
At the same time.
That way you go in and out.
The warp mix is easy.
It's so high, you can't go over it.
Angels we have heard on high
Singing about mountains new
And those mountains in reply
Saying we wish we had some too
Oh, oh, oh, oh, warriors
In excelsis Deo
Barbie dolls.
Women rape and memorialize their lives by role-playing with Barbie.
We have devised a marketing scheme for children's toys.
It will empower us to resist us.
You will use your church as a vehicle to bring these toys before the public.
It will be a bomb for kids.
But how will the battle of good against evil be represented in your marketing schemes?
Kids, humans.
Good as love and muscle.
Good.
Good!
The primitive earth societies should accept this value judgment.
Good will have great physical attributes according to human desires, sexual desires, latent in
children brought out through the vehicle of this.
So-called farmer told these boys at church,
Better is not good.
She's new, from Kenner.
Where illusion is the ultimate weapon.
We must buy our toys!
Yes.
The old subgenius toy marketing scheme,
recorded there at Dockstock 1984,
and me and Palmer Freedies.
Angels We Have Heard on High,
it was by the Philistines.
The collage called All the Money You've Got
is from the great Obtuse Christmas collage album,
which you can get for free.
Check out this website,
obtuse.iuma.com
That's Obtuse...
Excuse me!
Ah yes, and next up,
The Real Story of Christmas,
by...
Michael Shelley.
Once upon a time,
there was the baby Jesus,
and he had two eyes made out of coal,
and he was stuck up a partridge in a pear tree,
and he wanted his two front teeth,
and he got McDonald's gift certificates,
and he had a dog named Santa's little help,
and he took all the presents from Whoville,
and his friend Yukon Cornelius came with the three wise guys,
and he wanted to play the drums and be the little drummer boy,
but he couldn't.
He wanted 10s and 20s, 10s and 20s,
and he got McDonald's gift certificates,
and he got Zuzu's pedals,
and that's the real story of Christmas.
The Real Story of Christmas
Shut up, pink boy!
No way, I'll never sell out for the conspiracy.
Taste a little of my rocket pipe, alien fool.
Bob Dobbs comes with rocket pipe,
head launcher, janger device,
fighting Jesus and other action figures sold separately,
some assembly required,
Our battery's not included.
This toy falls apart every day.
He-Bob!
And the bastards of the universe.
Too much is always better than not enough.
The creatures in Queen Barbara,
when I can't douse all separately.
Gorgeous.
Seagulls can blow from head to toe.
Drama.
Everything you see here,
can't douse all separately.
He-Bob and the bastards of the universe
will be back after this message.
Santa Claus.
Well, Tommy knew exactly what he wanted for Christmas.
He wanted an electric train.
He had the whole thing in his mind,
even to the table where it was going to set it up.
He had a picture of the whole thing,
and he would dream so hard
that the whole thing would come to life
right before his eyes.
Of course, Tommy was a pretty strong wisher.
And what he started wishing for
was a pretty fancy-looking train set
with locomotives and freight cars,
and a station and a gateman,
the water tower,
and all the kinds of wonderful equipment
and accessories.
So grand that you might think
Tommy was waiting for something
that just didn't exist.
But Tommy knew what he was wishing for.
It is turnover.
The time of the year when all things sell.
The end of the year sale.
Oh, yeah.
So come and get it, everyone,
and just buy our products.
Now, are we...
I'm a little confused about what Christmas is all about.
Are we...
Are we celebrating the birth of Santa Claus
or his death when they nailed him?
Well, that's the ancient, ancient subgenie.
But the present subgenie
tried to make sure that
we have our inventories cleared by now
and sell everything to the pigs.
Oh, yes.
Once a pagan holiday,
and now a shopping season.
And it was something else in between there.
Before it was...
After it was a pagan holiday
and before it was a shopping season,
it was something else.
But I think they started a war over it.
Yeah.
Like the soap opera,
but now Santa won't really do it.
And we probably won't need to follow theaged angels
and I she went too far.
So,
I still don't understand
why Santa's left letter perché
he wants to pay this money.
Friends, try to imagine
somewhere in the snowy north,
the Santibob trudging mindlessly
through the Himalayan snows,
driven by strange forces
to complete his nameless errand,
and he may show up at your house,
my friend, if you've been a bad subgenius
or a halfway subgenius,
or if we keep getting tangled up
in these other shows
and having strange microphones.
How did that paternity suit ever turn out
between Dobbs and Santa?
And who?
His dad.
Santa dog.
I don't know.
I don't think it was...
Yes, but St. Nicholas, this is fact,
St. Nicholas punched another bishop
in the nose and bloodied his,
in the 4th century over us,
over a dispute over the trinity of God.
The original St. Nicholas in Turkey?
I swear upon Bob and the house of God.
The heart of the country is the more part of the country.
I can tell you shit, God.
Who the hell is God?
Ask Dobbs one day.
That's the question we should be asking.
Suddenly, a lightning bolt struck from nowhere.
On that bright, sunny day,
Bob did a backflip,
and from that day on,
he too was a believer.
And from the snow,
a little child bearing flowers emerged.
Chip, what else is on the table?
Each one a dirty flower.
This is St. Nicholas.
Sip, sicken.
The historical Santa Claus
is originally lived,
as the caller knows,
as a bishop in,
was it Constantinople?
Yeah, like...
Or it was an ancient Byzantium.
Yeah, Asia Minor in general, yeah.
Yes, he was, and he was, uh,
he was known for
sneaking into the rooms of young women
and leaving,
ahem, ahem, gifts.
Life-sized lumps of coal,
complete with a fake beard
and a CIA Wall Street credit card.
complete with a fake beard and a CIA Wall Street credit card.
A saint he was, the girl said.
Well, that's to say that he had St. Nicholas invented the CIA.
You got it, brother.
He moved all those houses through the chimney.
He knew they were sleeping.
They knew when, he knew when they were awake.
You got it, brother.
But like the CIA, he was protecting them.
Foucault knew that St. Nick was a creepin', stinkin' spy.
What?
He knows when you've been sleeping.
He knows what you've been eating.
Hey, man, my kids still believe in St. Nicholas.
And who keeps that belief alive in their
fevered, sick little brain?
Madison Avenue, of course.
No, the surveillance community.
And Disney.
Under your direction.
Reynolds Tobacco Company.
Miller Bear.
If you're bad, he punishes you.
If you're good, he rewards you.
He's probably the closest thing to Jesus walking the earth.
He's the closest thing to Big Brother there is.
He rewards those who knows when they are smiling when they're awake.
I think really if you want to make a deal, you have to do it with, you know.
Could Dr. Claus in fact be the wandering, quote, milkman rumored to have fathered our savior J.R. Bob Dobbs?
Well, we find it a very likely possibility from the falsified documents we have here.
And also the fluffy beard that often grew on Bob's feet.
You better watch out.
You better not.
I'm telling you why.
Santa Claus is coming to town.
He knows when you're away
He knows when you're in bad or good
So be good in this goodness sake
Oh, you better watch out
You better watch out
I'm telling you why
Santa Claus is coming today
You think I'm psycho, Mama?
I seen my ex last night
Oh, I'm sorry.
We all saw X-Mas last night.
A vision of Christmas that was dancing in Stank's head.
It would not leave for the little shickle plums and berries dropping toxic tears.
Oh, this little shickle plums are the reason that plums are the poison in the plums.
Material plums?
Biological agents?
Who only take...
15%?
It came with our fantastic boxes of bags.
And now...
Oh, my God.
Now check this.
Oh, my God...
A big news.
COM Drax!
I'm not the best mechanic I've ever been.
I cleanup many figures and Earthlings arefallen.
A beautiful church...
First I could possible anybody prayerancy...
And going to the ICBM...
And over millions are paying for my égal holy witnessing toeting activity.
Because you left me, too!
accommodate and...
You will not
That's two days old Christmas, a million things to do
Clean the house, put on tea, company is due
Where are my relatives, why haven't they showed up?
I met her at the airport, I forgot to pick them up
Christmas, almost here
Sometimes I think all that Santa crap's just bull
Santa Claus is real
Who's the hitman?
Santa Claus
He was a huge, beastly, bulging man
He was so real, how come we didn't get squat last year?
Yes, the birth of the baby Satan
On July 4th
And now you can have it all pure 100% vinyl chloride CID
The birth of our baby Satan
As told by various authors and acquaintances
And eclectic scholars from around the globular unit
Including that announcer
This announcement has not been a perfunctory announcement
But an announcement of the blessed anointment and birthday of our Lord
Zin
Crazy
For
One
Bright Christmas morning
Zin
Was born in a cradle
To a rich man's family
The Rave Jesus
Oh, I know the Rave Jesus
I'm partying with the Rave Jesus
Have yourself a merry little Christmas
Let your side be light
From the all-out fire of the sky
Let your troubles with the outer sky
And have yourself a merry little Christmas
From now on a few miles away
Once again
As in old times, I'll be back in time
And the world will see me
Happy golden
I'll have a sight
The Jackholms following
Happy golden
Merry Christmas
And a go surprising gift
From Mutated Christmas, friends,
have yourself a merry little Christmas by No-L.
No-L.
Before that, some year-old ESO and Michael Shelley did that real story of Christmas
from the Tarkin Records All-Star Holiday Extravaganza.
I'm playing a lot from that.
So check out www.triage.com for that one also.
The Tarkin Records is also on www.triage.com.
And now, the Jethro's.
The Tarkin Records.
Oh, yeah.
Wow.
The Weirbobs and Ima, those who have the psychosis that convinces them that they are the Santa Bob.
Or that they're Santa Bob by night.
And they go shuffling through the snow on their nameless hitchhikers.
Hideous errands.
The grin of Bob and the beard of Santa Claus and the pipe of the Lord stuck on their face.
They stop using the locks of their doors and they just kind of float into the keyhole.
Oh, friends, it's tough.
And, you know, just going to church ain't enough.
You gotta send your money to the Santa Bob.
As a matter of fact, the people across the street from me told their kids that,
that,
Santa Claus bills them for the toys he brings.
Can you believe that?
They asked, the kids were asking if their parents, if, if, maybe Santa Claus will bring us two He-Man erector sets.
And the mom said, no, no, he won't because he bills us.
We can't afford that.
Santa Claus sends us a bill after Christmas.
Yeah, but at least he totes the note.
.
I have no kids.
That's fair to give our kids a rub-a-bum-bum.
Rub-a-bum-bum.
.
And, uh, amazing.
More from Corporal Blossom.
I am really impressed by their editing work.
And that's on Corporal Blossom and the mutated,
uh,
Christmas is, uh, on the illegal art label.
That's www.detritus.net
slash illegal art.
www.detritus.net slash illegal art.
And now, more Jethro's.
.
5 nessa executive réfl unjustia
dm
Emma
and
Ros cervo
r
mor
Corvo
halten
vog
lpin
lim limits
Now you're blaming Jesus.
You're blaming our Lord.
I sort of understand because I understood the way any old fool would understand.
There was no Jesus, no flatulent old woman waving her panties on the hill.
It's not that you don't want to, it's that they won't let you.
No, they're ashamed.
Just a cry in the wilderness.
They're ashamed.
In the hot pursuit of wolves everywhere in the background.
I'm ashamed of them.
It's cold.
I'm leaving that city life behind and radio people are crazy.
I can't get my noodle back in the pan, Jan.
Come on, cowboy.
No, man.
I was.
I'm trying to hear a can against this here tree and it started whispering to me, man.
Oh, you've been drinking.
There's the face of Madonna right up there.
There's the face of Virgin Mary.
I swear to God, look at it.
Isn't it?
What?
It's her Christmas.
It's your Christmas witch coming true.
Wow.
A Christmas witch?
I'll be whole and snuggled.
She's beautiful.
Oh my God, yeah, I guess it does look a little bit more witchy than angelic.
I know she must be a true witch.
I guess you could call her that if that's what she's packing down for real.
She's running by hovering Christmas.
Christmas ornaments.
It looks like a radar device.
What?
Yo.
Yo?
It's her.
What up?
Nothing.
Shut up.
What's up?
What house?
What a deep voice.
What's up?
First Christmas witch.
Today is definitely a Christmas since Rider Rider.
Oh, see her face?
Aetzel ho.
officers.
Any student B dictionary will just drop in.
Wait, is this Timothy Mi'kmaq?
No, no.
We should ask Timothy.
Let's see who made this, expect our advertising device?
Say hello to Texteria Sport.
Thank you.
When your little brother
fell through a hole
and you went and saved
You didn't laugh at him and huff some more glue.
It was a wonderful life back then.
But today, Christmas is lost its meaning.
Scott, you made your choice.
When you rejected my word, you rejected me.
And to your eternal soul, you have found that I only could you afford to give to God that which was his.
But you could not afford to do otherwise.
The Senate still stands.
In the outer darkness, where there is wailing and gnashing of teeth.
Sir, please give me just one more chance, sir.
I don't want to go to hell, sir.
Sir, no.
I don't want to go to hell.
I don't want to go to hell!
No!
And the children say you could laugh and play just the same.
You and me.
The tail bearer will be at the judgment.
Thank you.
The tube marks certainty in the fuzzy place called the Twilight Zone.
Everywhere you'll find pieces of Cupid and Comet.
And he tied up his helpers and he held the elves hostage.
And he ground up poor Rudolph into reindeer sausage.
He got dancer and prancer with an old German luger.
And he slashed up Dasher just like Freddy Krueger.
And he picked up a flamethrower and a barbecue blitzer.
And he took a big bite and said it tastes just like chicken.
The Nonsense.
Santa went crazy.
The nitrous crinkle went nuts.
Now you can hardly walk around the North Pole without stepping in reindeer guts.
There's a National Guard and the FBI.
There's a van from the Iowa News.
And helicopters circling around in the sky.
And the bullets are flying.
The bodyguards rising.
And everyone's dying to know.
Santa, why?
My, my, my, my, my, my.
You used to be such a jolly guy.
He knows when you're sleeping.
He knows when you're awake.
He knows when you're down.
You're good.
So be good, for goodness sake.
You better watch out.
You better not cry.
You better not pout.
I'm telling you why.
Santa Claus is coming to town.
Have yourself an advanced Dogmatic Christmas song thing called Santa is Coming by F. Gillespie and F. J. Coote.
ElectricElf at loop.com can tell you more about that.
But now...
Who gave the Lord the Claptrap?
Who made him talk in funny riddles so that we cannot understand?
Who made him so succinct and blind that he is actually blind?
My one good little...
Well, officially in the Jesus season.
The time of the Lord, of the fact that...
How many before you reach your limit?
Jesuses?
Yeah, how many can you bag?
How many messiahs can you bag?
If you're doing it in season...
If you're doing it out of season, you need a special permit.
Oh, you never do that.
And you can only take one.
You never bag the Lord in C. You bag the Lord in B-flat so you get that kind of rough sound.
But when they're in season, it's every god for himself.
This is the season for the fighting Jesus.
Obviously.
We are between a rock and a hard place.
Did you know the Lord walked through Chaldea in the old age and he got a very, very hard foot?
And he got elphantiasis of the rectum.
You know, it's not something well known by many Christian scholars.
But I think the phrase in Hebrew was...
Well, I like the story...
I kind of like those stories where the Lord dies and then comes here to America and settles, you know...
Tames the West.
I like when he moves into a trailer park and cowboys walk with his dog.
Jesus fought for the Confederate Army!
The Ranger. I like the...
The Texas Ranger. Jesus, Texas Ranger.
Johnny Rebel was a Jesus!
I could see Jesus for the Navajo police, for maybe the Hopi police force.
Billy Jack was the Indian Jesus.
Man.
The white brother who came to instruct the Indians how to be liberal.
Well, what about old Peacemaker?
The...
Jesus of the Iroquois who was actually a Huron.
A Huron.
You didn't know that, did you?
I got you!
Thin Ron.
Jesus!
El Ron.
I got a Jesus like no other Jesus you've ever seen.
Oh, it tastes like butter.
A new Jesus. A different Jesus.
It tastes like crappy pie, children.
A pot smoking Jesus!
Hey, Dave, you know where it is. Go kick that window open.
I already kicked it. I'll kick it again, though.
Kick it good this time.
We don't mean nothing by this Jesus and God.
We hope that...
Slappy.
We thank you for all the nice things that you've done for us this Thanksgiving.
Clapping.
We appreciate all that.
And we're just trying to insult your fan club.
That's all.
That's why we do this blasphemous stuff.
But we knew that you knew that because you're in all things and everything, right, Jesus?
Right.
I could hear him say that.
Praise God and Bob and Jesus and...
And Bob.
And Jesus and Tony and...
Next topic.
And the devil and...
Could you see Jesus as a terrorist?
And science and...
Well, that's the life of Brian, isn't it? That was...
And Greek mythology and Norse mythology.
Listen to the sounds of hell.
Jingle, jangle, jingle, we're on a sleigh ride to heck.
Santa and his reindeer are really wicked.
Wrapped in wrapping paper.
We're gonna break our necks.
Got a rocket in my pocket on a sleigh ride to heck.
Sleigh ride to heck.
The elves are full of cheer.
The kids are in hibernation.
are tucked in bed
Santa ain't
coming we're on a
sleigh ride to
heck
their dreams are filled with toys
but they're
out of luck
cause Satan's taking
Santa on a
sleigh ride to
sleigh ride
to heck
to
heck
the greatest
scary Christmas song
ever friends from his new album
Don't Trust Whitey
James Kochalka
Superstar
you know see a subgenius
has so much faith
that he
he not only can accept
somebody making fun of Bob
stomping on a picture of Bob
he'll do it himself
he has so much
trust and faith in Bob
Bob is such a good friend
that he can insult Bob
now we subgeni
I hate to get on my soapbox
in the middle of a bunch of entertaining tapes
but we subgeni may be bad
but our way of bad is holy
is holy compared to the evil
of so not all
at all by any means
but so many American fundamentalist,
charismatic evangelicals,
et cetera in general
of course
they and their corresponding types
in Iran, Russia, Libya, South Africa, et cetera
if you ask me
are actually the ace up the devil's sleeve
wolves in sheep's clothing friends
just like Jesus warned about
I'm
we're
Jesus and Bob
like we say
our old drinking buddies
got nothing against Jesus
it's just his fan club
and now we aren't saying that Bob is the ace up God's sleeve
he's more like the smear on God's handkerchief
just like you or me
but the uptight rival cults
they don't think God has a handkerchief
uh-uh no
because God's perfect
he doesn't even sneeze
we're made in his image
except that we have all these nasty parts attached to us
we have to go in the secret room
the bathroom
to do awful things
but God, oh he's clean and pure
according to them
oh and he's male
but he doesn't excrete juices and sweat and smelly stuff out of him like we do
because we sin
oh yeah we all sin
we're bad
we're worthless
we're no good to God
unless we sign a contract with his agent
we interrupt this program for a special promotional announcement
we turn
E-Bob and the bastards of the universe will be back after this message
Santa Claus is coming
Wanna join a fad?
Don't forget to like this video and subscribe if it helped
good bye
cogenic
other nós
Oh
Hey
Why
Oh
the angel voices
Oh night
divine
when Christ was born
Oh night
divine
O
Mithras won his fight.
Ho, ho, ho.
Come on, come on.
It's He-Bomb.
Hey, kids, you can help the mighty Satinus Rice overthrow the evil normals
with new Bob-Dob's action figure with Rockin' Pie.
What I wouldn't do from Bob-Dob.
Get new more chocolatey pebbles from you, no?
I'm a chocolate spice cadet.
Life support system down to zero cocoa.
Feeling face-free.
Have some of my new cocoa pebbles.
Now so trumpety.
Mmm, smells cocoa.
This cocoa.
Blow.
Well, friends, what do you think?
Is it the nativity of Santa Claus that we're trying to celebrate here?
Or is it the horrible death of the Santa Bob, the Santai Bob,
as he's been referred to in some early films?
Pre-scriptures?
We're getting so separate.
The Jethro's, friends, you need to know where to write to the Jethro's.
They're at, they did that Wreck the Halls and so many other versions we've been playing.
The Jethro's are at 212 and a half Miller Avenue.
That's 212 and a half Miller Avenue.
Portsmouth, New Hampshire.
H-O-3-8-O-1.
Santa Claus is Coming to Town was by Corporal Blossom.
Information on that mutant Christmas is available from www.triagemusic.com
or www.detritus.net slash illegalart.
I'm Reverend Ivan Stang, friends.
You can reach me, send me tapes or whatnot at Post Office Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
And friends, as always, the Hour of Slack is brought to you by the Church of the Subgenius.
www.subgenius.com
It's all Christmassy right now.
There's a bright green bob in the window.
There's a little bell in the window.
And a...
Is there a light out there?
And Christmassy lights.
Is there a DJA?
Is DJA out there?
And devilish artwork that's Christmassy.
No, that's something just left for DJA.
It's all Christmassy.
It's all wrapped up in a perfumed ribbon-wrapped present.
Under the tree.
Smell that cinnamon.
Open the door all the way so we can see if he comes in.
And those sugar plums.
Something's up the chimney hole in Satan's, isn't it?
Yeah.
Of Santa, I mean.
Otherwise.
Gosh.
I guess we have to wait till Santa comes, Dave.
Oh, beloved Santa.
I have wanted to...
Put your bag down for a minute.
It's always so ready to let him be.
What?
For so long.
Hi, Bob and Mary X-mas!
Bye, Bob and Mary X-mas!
extra
pro
It's another day on Peter Pan, Tampa, specifically,
Just said to him on the top left.
Why?
To tell him that Antoine really is trying to sell,
More decir-
Emergency police emergency.
Yes.
zem cicle, there's a noise.
Lone cow Dave, don't you know what they're doing to yourself?
Don't despair just because it's Christmas
Children there are so gay at Christmas
All the children on the street
Hope they get something good to eat
But for me it's not so great
Fuck Christmas!
What a night!
Right before Christmas and all through the house
Not a creature was stirring, not even a mouse
The stockings were hung by the tree
Merry fucking Christmas
To you!
Thank you.