Yes sir, I'm the guy that has my legal notices in the paper to explore base.
I have the one by the sheriff and he mentions I have problems with a clemency policeman
and permission to exchange those seeds, a seed source.
I have my case in the Indo-Chinese one.
I'm allowed to put in one from North American Indian.
I'm allowed to explore base.
I'm allowed to smoke out in the open if I wish.
It's not my wish that I have a privacy case.
I have an oxygen case.
I had another legal notice.
The whole reason I called, I forgot.
Wasn't it a really big, long message?
What the hell was it?
I'll call back to you in a minute.
Jesus.
Bob, what button did you push?
The Subgenius Hour of Swag.
I think they're learning how to fly.
To fly?
Yeah, fly.
Yeah, no, we're learning how to crawl, dear friends.
We're crawling through these cassettes.
Yes, crawling through these cassettes
and cigarette butts and spilled coffee.
But I'll tell you what, my friend,
we've come to a new fork in the road.
Yes, here at the Church of the Subgenius.
I bet you can't hardly believe
we actually got a new show out
only one week after the last show.
But it's because Jesus got here.
Jesus got here.
He's been healing and sickening everything
except his own equipment.
And friends, it's making a difference.
And I'll tell you something.
I'll tell you.
You know, we've done some artistic projects
in this old church of ours.
We've done all kinds of terrible crimes
in the name of Bob and so forth.
We've worked hard and we've saved a few mutants
from suicide.
Even a few that we should have saved from suicide.
And, you know, now we're ready to get down
to a new phase, a new artistic approach.
Yes, our new goal, our new way
shall be to make money.
Money.
Hand over fist.
Yes, that is the new...
Actually, that was always a goal
of the Church of the Subgenius.
But now that we've...
I mean, heck, X-Day is only two years away.
And we'll be giving you detailed information
about the X-Day drill coming up in New York later.
But, friends, I mean, at this point,
you know, as we've said so many times before,
in order to completely and utterly destroy
the concept of money,
it's going to take money.
It's going to take a lot of money, my friend.
And, by God, before this show is out,
we shall be millionaires.
I swear it.
And, Bob, that's a much bigger transaction
than what we puny human beings want to get involved in.
What about those millionaires, eh?
What are we going to do with the millionaires?
As the money comes pouring in,
we'll realize our potential
by creating great obstacles
in the way of hospitals and libraries.
We'll keep these things from being spread
and destroyed.
First, so that the populace can wallow in ignorance
in the new world which is to come.
Thank you.
You've got it. You've got the part.
I told you he could do it.
Sure, I could.
What?
Not only that, it's on the television station
that you could be watching right now
instead of this show.
And he's happy about it.
He knows how to celebrate.
They stay happy in their tiny mud huts
with the dirt floors and the bugs
dropping from the little palm frond roof
watching their color TV.
Instant or not, all pseudo-slack or false highs,
every bit as fulfilling as a real thing
are quickly reached through repetitive monotonous
and phantomatic.
And healthful competition.
It's shown here.
Here's what happens when one worshiper
gets his prayer wheel just a little out of control
and has it wallowing too fast.
Remember what I said?
Yes, sir.
I'm the guy that has my legal notice
in the paper in advance.
Also, I mentioned I'm having trouble
with a clemency policeman or two.
I sued them in the 70s
in the front hall of Euclid High School
and they won't get off.
They want to disturb my privacy.
And then I believe I have a story.
I'm large.
And I am allowed
for the reintroduction message,
crap, I'm allowed 9 leaf
and 11 and lucky 13
and 15 and bad news 17
and 19 and 21 leaf.
I'm entitled to scientific
and entertainer's roles
and music industry,
entertainment industry,
where it's going.
Scientific.
I'm allowed to carry a sizable amount
because I'm supposed to be
international status
and this is my privacy case.
And a large amount for bail
and bond and severance silver,
Ms. Sparry's I'm entitled
to liquid blue,
blue mid Spirits,
sacred Indian Blue,
blue Mesa, blue corn.
pretty much
clemency is mês
Mr. Sparry,
Thank you, Mr. Sparry,
And now it seems like we've been waiting for ages
Consciousness has walked through states and stages
Shaking it up, spreading around
Making up religions and filling up pages of history
It's a mystery to me who wrote that story
What do you believe? It's an Illuminati party
A space dog's dream, you watch yourself
Cause they could be mean
Illuminati, Illuminati, Illuminati, Illuminati, Illuminati, Illuminati
Illuminati, Illuminati, Illuminati, Illuminati, Illuminati, Illumination
They be scheming like demons, sucking your brain
Making you feel like a new age when it's blackmail
Wholesale, anybody's game, you don't know you're in the club
Till it's too late
Look real close, read between the lines
World leaders and coots with kooky canines
Gonna make you wanna laugh, make you wanna scream
It's an Illuminati party, a space dog's dream
Illuminati
Illuminati, Illuminati, Illuminati, Illuminati, Illuminati, Illumin junto
Lyrics 송이랑
루
Illuminati, Illuminati, Illuminati, Illuminati, Illumination!
Eat it up, think boys, swallow it whole
Swallow in stupidity, smoke it in your bowl
Swallow...
Swallow it whole
Swallow in!
Oh, it's更,更 hell appearing now on screen
I am name Jena
I just got the random Chinese word
guitar solo
Now everybody thinks dog's man's best friend
Waggy tail, lick your hand and all that kind of shit
But I don't buy the domesticated crap
What the hell, hounds talking, shitting in your lap
Breathing down your neck with their dirty doggy breath
I see them trotting down the street
You know they scare me hot to death
It's an Illuminati party, a space dog's dream
You watch yourself, cause they could be mean
Illuminati, Illuminati
Illuminati, Illuminate
Illuminate
Shun!
While inoculate, mercury umbilical clear
Umbilical clear
Mercury and atmospheric light gone
All recorders to fast D-18
D-18
Oh, the recorder's fine
Because Bob is watching
Bob is listening, dear friends
Bob, yeah
Because, you know, friends
Since that mess with the
Branch Davidians
Many small religious sects
Have been the recipients of some
Negative dogmas
This has long been the case
Among the church of the subgenius followers
The so-called pinks
Or normals
Have been critical of the idea
That salvation is guaranteed
For the reasonable price
Of thirty dollars
Some believe an upright life
Lacking in sin
Is the key to a good life
And the only way to eternal happiness
But through the timeless teachings
Of J.R. Bob Dobbs
I have finally learned
How to slack off
Bob's optimism
His valuable teachings
And contagious enthusiasm
Are just a few of the traits
That led him to lead
The subgenite
Millions and millions
Of people are depressed
Right now as you're hearing me
Give this introduction
Someone, somewhere is planning
Their suicide
They are cleaning the gun
Or writing the note
Because nobody cares
They know greed
Has overtaken society
They know that people would be afraid
To give them mouth-to-mouth resuscitation
For fear of disease
And lawsuits
What these unfortunate souls lack
Is J.R. Bob Dobbs
Optimism
He sees our greed
And accepts it
He has put a price
On your salvation
And you're only worth thirty dollars
And that is no problem
There's no prob
With Bob
Bob has glimpsed our collective future
And is still able to smile
His famous smile
Above all else
Bob is a teacher
He unselfishly tells the universe
What it wants to hear
Slack off
Quit your job
Pull the wool
Over your own eyes
Bob knows what is true
And allows his message
To be broadcast on radio waves
And other various waves
Throughout the cosmos
Anyway
Bob also teaches of the coming
Of X-Day
July 5th, 1998
He ensures the end is coming
And gives his followers an option
Of salvation
Thirty dollars, dear friends
That is all it will cost you
The Book of the Subgenius asks
Are you abnormal?
Then you are probably better
Than most people, it responds
This kind of enthusiasm
Is contagious among the subgeniuses
As children
They felt misunderstood
Alienated by their peers
Because they were different
Bob's contagious enthusiasm
Abets the self-conceit
confidence of his followers by convincing him they are not the freaks they once thought
they were. In fact, they were far greater freaks than they ever dared dream, and gives
them a feeling of connection.
Ah, yes. J.R. Bob Dobbs has an enthralling optimism, strong teaching skills, and an extremely
contagious enthusiasm that shows his followers for years how important it is to slack off.
Ah, yes, dear friends. That lovely little essay there was actually written by Reverend
Rachel Simon, a Plano High School student here in North Texas.
Oh, yes. Thank you, Rachel.
Thank you, Rachel, and how truly smarmy it is. Sort of like this music in the background,
which by the way is Brother Cleve Duncan, Cleve Donut Duncan from his new tape, Dreamsville,
which is mostly music by Henry Mancini redone by Brother Cleve. And friends, tonight we're
going to take young Rachel at her word and we're going to go slack off. We're going to
go see Brother Cleve perform tonight in Dallas with the combustible Edison. No, with cum
the.
combustible Edison. That's like saying the Devo's. And oh, it shall be spacey, dear friends.
You know, space age bachelor pad music as it is. So let us be off.
Now, let's not go off. Let's, uh, let's, oh, hey, old man, let's have a damn party. That's
what I say. We'll have this damn party because friends.
There is a damn party coming up. Wait a minute.
You kids keep it down back there. It's hard to get work done. You know, as much as we
have to party constantly here at the subgenius foundation, but friends, I wanted to share
with you before we get going on to more incredible music, uh, and amazing rants. I wanted to
share with you some news about upcoming deed Bibles. Yes. Um, there are some coming up.
Uh, here and there we've got actually almost all of these are up north around the Cleveland
and New York area on May 25th. Uh, music star, uh, yours truly will make that's just a small,
uh, pagan folky. I don't know what it is actually to tell the truth, but, but, but, but heck,
you know, we're going to be there May 25th for information on that. And on starwood,
the giant pagan, uh, camp out event, the infamous thing.
That happens every year. That one is, I think the, the last weekend in July. And for information
on those, you may call, uh, ACE in Cleveland. I'm about to give that 1-800 number and here
it is dear friends. It's a 1-800-446-4962. Once again, that's 800-446-4962. And, uh,
ah, but that, yes, as much fun as that is.
Those may be friends. What's really, really gonna peel your hide right off of you is the
X day end of the world drill. Number one, coming up at brushwood folklore center, Sherman,
New York X day, 1996, July 5th through 7th. It friends, it's going to be a little taste
of Dobbs town. Oh yes. Because you know, there's only two years left, two more July 5th before
we kiss all calendars. Goodbye.
And that gives us barely enough time to get to the end of the world.
I'm going to give you a little bit of time to prepare by gathering together all the tribes
and files of sub genius them for a fast yearly doc stock, like free for all outdoor slack
best at the coolest campground in these new United States. And, uh, well now everybody's
talking at the same time in the background, but friends, here's that number to call, uh,
the call the slack crusade hotline. I'm going to give this one again for free information.
2 1 6.
That's 2 1 6 5 5 6 0 3 3 8 because, and friends at brushwood. Yeah, sure. You, most of you
are going to have to travel a long, long way to make it to X day, but dang it. Um, it's
in southwestern New York state about an hour from area and about two hours from Cleveland.
And it's a it's a hand zone, it's going wait a minute.
That's better.
Yes, friends. It's true. I didn't know the Interstate was about to decode this. Whoa.
out on this amazing campground.
It's a nicely equipped campground, too, by the way.
They've got a giant tent for holding tents, show devivals,
a swimming pool, a hot tub area,
and enough electrical power to keep 10,000 doctor vans
cranking out the hits, using all their equipment,
while breathing church air and performing nasal sex,
start naked right there in front of everybody all night long.
Yes, that's right.
You can finally really let your Yeti nose hair down
at this little event.
It'll probably scare the crap out of the norm worms
and us as well.
But this isn't the sort of sleazy little...
Excuse me, friends.
This radio station's falling down around our ears.
These are the end times.
But, you know, this is a secure situation, friends.
We will own the cops at this particular setup.
It is the perfect place to practice and drill
for the utterly mouth-watering slack
that we'll have to undergo come 1998.
None may stop us.
None may escape once the gate closes.
And, friends, it will be an unforgettable,
insane, nervous system-raping experience
that should freak out the normals
as well as the stuffed shirts of Geni
until they too join the orgy.
And, yes, friends, saucers will scream overhead.
Greys will skulk in the butches.
There's an actual live Yeti.
Bees will materialize by your campfire.
You'll finally meet your true Yeti mate
and play with prairie squids in the bushes all day.
You'll become your own heroes and meet friends for life
who will get you rich without working
and, uh, it may even permanently traumatize or scar you.
We certainly hope so.
That's okay.
That's all part of Bob Dob's great underplan.
It's a subgenius X-Day drill party, friends.
You bring the self-ignorance...
You bring the exciting bobbies...
And I'll bring the binoculars.
You bring the candy warheads...
And I'll bring the real ones.
You bring the pipe cleaners...
And I'll bring the cornstarch.
You bring the great big wooden cross...
And I'll bring the hell of skulls.
You bring the messiah...
And I'll bring the nails.
You bring the pit bulls...
And we'll supply the pit, friends.
So, um, well, there's gonna be so much to see there.
Sideshow marvels, tubs and tubs of purple Kool-Aid,
Spongebob, and the other stuff.
Spontaneous doctor band combustion,
trained prairie squid gigging parties,
um, free de-beaking tools for the first five gig-ees,
uh, sports figure body part launching,
nude chainsaw juggling,
bull fights,
frop enhancement workshops,
acubating psychic surgery cockfights,
live freaks of nature and acid casualties,
uh, bobby roping,
private adult sex-hurt seminars,
bonobo chimpanzee goblin contest,
dog fights,
self-mutilating preachers,
oddly normal seeming people,
and insane irritating bobbies who won't shut up.
Free crucifixions in front of lobotomies,
live casner heads,
live aliens and their walk-in dupes,
and body painting, friends.
Well, there's so much more we could tell you about that.
All the greats will be there.
Uh, Dr. Katahdin Lagoon, Papa Joe Mama,
Circus Apocalypse, Reverend Nikki Death Chick,
um, uh, Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
the Lord Jesus Christ of the Dead,
Son of God, King of Slack Bill T. Miller,
yours truly, uh, j- and, uh,
everybody, everybody cool, man,
everybody cool will be at, uh, the X Day Drill.
It's your chance this decade, until next year,
to do a Doc Stock, if you know what I mean.
And, hey, where's my left channel?
Oh, it's there, okay.
Um, and once again, that number to call is
216-556-0338.
I think you may be able to hear the, uh, enthusiasm in my voice.
That man Bob has given me that contagious enthusiasm
that we need so badly in this church,
and now we're going to get rich, rich, rich beyond, um,
even my wildest nightmares.
So call the Free Dobs Hotline,
D-Vival Hotline, 216-556-0338,
or write to us here at the post office.
That's the P-O box for that free information.
And that address, of course, is Bob at 140,
Box 140306.
That's Box 140306, Dallas, Texas, 75214.
And, uh, I'm sure we will be giving that number again.
I should now, uh, tell you that the music we were listening to earlier
was, of course, uh, that song Illuminati Party
is by, uh, the Klingons in Germany,
in Berlin, in fact.
That's Captain Nancy Darnier,
and her, uh, side captain, Rocking Wanky.
I love to say that guy's name.
Rocking Wanky.
And, uh, yes, yes, yes.
And, oh, God, there's so much, so much here.
What shall be next? I don't know.
I'd love to be able to go to a party where I can yell out,
I want to hear some pervert music!
So what I mean by pervert music, it doesn't have to be, uh,
overtly pervert music,
but it does have to, for no particular reason,
psyche up to want to do sexually perverted things
to women and or girls.
Like that song by the Monkees, I Saw Her Face.
Now, I'm a believer.
When I hear the beginning of it,
it, uh, psychs me up to want to do kinky sexual things.
I almost forgot. Here's the How Dare You song.
How dare you?
You made me ejaculate in my pants.
For I was only in junior high school.
I was too young to fall in love and have sex.
Here's an imitation of an angry transvestite.
How dare you?
You made me ejaculate in my skirt.
For I was only in junior high school.
I was too young to fall in love and have sex.
And today, we are still, if they still had animal sacrifices,
and Bob, before the Lord comes back,
or in that period of time,
that temple's going to be rebuilt,
and they're going to be reinitiating the sacrificial system.
And I can just see a bunch of these Christians
that are more preoccupied with Israel than they are Jesus
just flocking over there to get involved.
Just thinking that's the neatest thing ever going.
Well, there's a...
My daughter has become involved in something that I think is a cult.
I think it might be a satanic cult.
Um...
I saw an astral star on some of their literature.
Okay.
Well, let's just do an abbreviation of what's going on in here, okay?
She's a member of this group,
this organization,
the First Church of Cute Young Girls Who Are Sex Wives to Jane of Iberclades.
Okay, because this is the card of the devil.
It's reversed.
Yes, ma'am.
And this couple have a chain around their necks.
Is that bad, ma'am?
Well, yeah, because I'm saying that there's some kind of illusion there.
There are chains, whatever it is, you know?
And between now and six months,
you're gonna be in a better frame of mind about this,
because I'm saying that there's a way out.
They're chained to Bob.
Yes, ma'am.
I don't understand why she would want to be a sex slave.
I mean, we tried to raise her, you know, in a Christian manner.
It had nothing to do with what you raised her.
It's the company that she keeps.
Yes, ma'am.
That had pulled her away from her upbringing.
Hanging out with subgeniuses again.
Jane, what you gotta do is you gotta hire a deprogrammer.
And the only kind of deprogrammer that can deprogram your daughter
is another subgenius.
You know, it takes one to know one.
That's Jane of Iberclades doing a prank call on the psychic network
or something like that.
Jane has got a show in Little Rock,
and I guess they're hearing it right now.
And I'm very glad of that.
Finally, the church has a chance of taking over the entire universe
now that Jane of Iberclades is on the radio.
Yes, yes, it's absolutely true.
Hey, another show to them.
Hey, bro.
I'm getting a strong reading over here on this meter here.
Uh-oh, I've got a funny reading too, sir.
It's something big, and it's coming this way.
Now, this is a 40-foot mosquito you're seeing here.
They would...
They would coax the giant 40-foot mosquitoes to come towards them
and run behind one of the ancient hardwood trees
that go all through the jungle.
And as the mosquito hit into the hardwood tree,
they would grab the...
The musketeer would grab the mosquito beak with his pliers
and hit with a sledgehammer,
bend over the beak on the backside of the tree,
thus trapping him.
Here we go.
Here you go.
You can see him.
There's the musketeer.
Hey, you got a musketeer?
And you can see the musketeer chasing down the mosquitoes.
The doctors are chasing the insects around Green Hill now.
They've gone completely out of sight.
I didn't know.
But of course, when that insect...
Actually, they kill...
Ah, yes.
When you can finally trap him
and bend his beak over into that hardwood tree,
you can then sap his bodily fluids
and make that ancient liquid that you're talking about, girlfriend.
He's got a giant weather balloon there.
He's looking for two or three of the cats.
I don't say I can get the whole bird.
Yes, yes.
Yes.
Oh, look out.
Ah.
You can hear the squeaking.
That's it.
He's got a body and he's now trapped.
You can see his giant body withering and limp hanging from the trunk
as the musketeer comes around with his tiny...
Limp hanging from the trunk.
...spittle bucket and puts it beneath...
Listen, you can hear it dripping out now.
Yes, there it is.
I can hear bubbles coming out.
You can see that.
There's the liquid.
There's the liquid coming out of that giant 40-pound mosquito.
There it is.
Listen.
Oh, look at...
Give me another glass of that, would you?
Here.
Here's more.
Look.
There's more.
Yeah, you're going to be able to expect...
This isn't bad at all.
You can expect at least 20 gallons of this stuff to come out of this one 40-pound mosquito,
and the mosquitoes are such a popular cult.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
A lovely classic little stretch from the old KPFA subgenius show in Berkeley, this time
with Glass Madness, Dr. Hal Palmer Vreides, Puzzling Evidence, and Gary Gebrogfran, an
all-star lineup.
And, friends, don't you forget to go to that X-Day party, that X-Day drill.
That is...
It's going to be your big chance to face the spike.
You'll love it.
Yeah?
Well, you know, the last time I partied like that, I woke up in the morning, and I was
like, I'm going to get married.
How's that?
I woke up married.
Hey, Jack, you forgot your muffin.
Have a good one, Bob.
Thanks, Jack.
Take care, huh?
Yes, sir.
I'm the man that has my legal notice in the newspaper in advance.
I figured I'd give you a chance to practice your business and trust you with my privacy.
You have permission to serve me in the newspaper.
I need to talk to somebody that knows what they're talking about.
I have my story in the paper.
I'm missing my degrees, and I'm the big shoe on campus.
Man, I'm going to have to go to the office.
I'm the man that can't remember where he went to college.
There's an explanation about it, the Dr. Galakowicz incident.
Anyway, I'm entitled to black.
I'm allowed to grove, and I need to talk to somebody who knows what they're talking about,
a seed source, and I need to know about soil and pH and the right environment.
I'm allowed pink.
I'm allowed to have pink.
I'm allowed to have black and blue and yellow or gold, green and red.
I'm allowed to have purple or yellow.
I'm allowed to have pink, getting a little purple.
They call purple space grass, or scientific.
And rules outer space.
Purple space grass.
Purple Polly.
If I was a subgenius, I could drive a Cadillac with class,
my pockets stuffed with bad checks, and I could sit on my fat ass.
Now you take a subgenius, he ain't nobody's fool
He doesn't buy any gasoline to drive his kids to school
Damn, I wish I was a subgenius
Our government has gone crazy, I'd change things if I could
If only I was a subgenius, I could afford to live in a good neighborhood
All the things I could do if I was yeti and hellbent
I could send my kids to college, and it wouldn't cost me one damn cent
Damn, I wish I was a subgenius
My wife and I, we're down on our luck, we're really starting to sink
They sent my local subgenius slack helpline
You ain't white, you are pink
Oh, how I tried to get a job, and a diploma I had with pride
The post office man laughed and said
You're not yeti enough to even qualify
Damn, I wish I was a subgenius
I took a civil service exam and passed it without shame
A subgenius took one next to me
And couldn't even write his own name
The subgenius got the job, now he's government top brass
He couldn't qualify for a trash truck
And I'm out in the street, on my ass
Damn, I wish I was a subgenius
If I was Reverend Ivan Stang, I'd be nobody's slob
Buying $5,000 computers
That subgenius hasn't even got a job
If I was G. Gordon Gordon, then I wouldn't have to think
I could run for president and paint the White House pink
Damn, I wish I was a subgenius
If I was of yeti genes, then I could trace my kin
To a pair of horny snow beasts and a dozen prairie squid
If I was only a subgenius, I could stand proud in this life
I could eat high off the hog, just me and my yeti wife
Damn, I wish I was a subgenius
Things are supposed to be segregated, but things are a little off key
Hell, I can't even find a normal job, and I'm not even a subgenius
I can't even find a normal who's not too shy to pee
It ain't that I don't like a subgenius
If I rubbed you wrong by chance
Then take a look at that mistletoe hanging on the seat of my pants
Damn, I wish I was a subgenius
If I was some weirdo freak, I could be just like Sterno
And burn down the whole damn pink earth
In a terrible, blazing inferno
I could have me a hate march on the streets of Dallas, Texas
I could tear up the whole damn city
And make love with the exests
Damn, I wish I was a subgenius
A lot of things in life I know
One thing's not too clear, though
Like why a weirdo can call me a pink
But I can't call a subgenius a weirdo
If I was a big ugly subgenius, I could ring a bell
I could be sphinx drumming, and party, in subgenius hell
Damn, I wish I was a subgenius
If I was a yetikin, and I could be some other finger- они
eno
seven feet tall and lean, maybe I'd be Reverend Snavely, rich beyond my dreams. If I was only
yeti skinned, I could have my prairie squid in bed and on the weekends, launch Arnold Palmer's head.
Damn, I wish I was a subgenius.
Reverend Lagoon was buried in Philadelphia with class,
face down in his box so the bobbies could kiss his ass. If I was only a subgenius,
I'd live high up on a hill, selling frop and prostitutes, popping all kinds of pills.
Now take the church of the subgenius, they can hold the bibles and raise all kinds of hell.
Let the normal start to talk and they'll all wind up in jail. Damn, I wish I was a subgenius.
I dreamed my life was over. I heard Jehovah One say,
today we're taking only subgeniuses. You gotta go the other way.
Then I heard the devil,
he said I heard what Jehovah One had to say. But I'm sorry to tell you son, today in hell is subgenius day.
Damn, don't you wish you were a subgenius?
Johnny Rip, and all that you believe.
You fought all the way, Johnny Rip, Johnny Rip. Yeah, you fought all the way, Johnny Rip.
You fought all the way, Johnny Rip, Johnny Rip. You fought all the way, Johnny Rip.
Oh, yeah.
Yes, I wished I was a subgenius by Jesus. Yes, that's our first little tape piece there by
Reverend Jesus H. Christ de Valaqua, the new business manager here at the church of the subgenius.
Let's have a hand for, a big hand for Jesus. Praise the Lord. Praise the Lord.
Oh, and friends now, DK Jones.
Hello, Joe.
Reverend DK Jones is not a preaching man by nature.
Reverend DK Jones is a musical artist.
He's a great anti-musical man.
But I want to testify tonight to the power of that man, Bob.
Sixteen years ago, dear friends, I was in Texas, and a man named the Reverend Stevie Hambone showed me that face, that grin and face of Bob.
And it caught my eye, and it caught me by the back of the head.
And I copied down that P.O. Box number, P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
And dear friends, up to that time, I thought I had plenty for me.
I had that conspiracy money.
I had that conspiracy job working nine to five.
I had that sports car, friends, that made it an American sports car.
But did that do it?
It didn't mean shit, dear friends.
It didn't mean shit to me. You know why?
Because I was missing something in my life.
You know what I was missing?
Bob!
That's right.
It was Bob!
You know what Bob is?
Bob is the original band, mother fucker, children.
Samuel L. Jackson ain't got nothing on Bob!
Bob was the man that gave the Jones to D.K. Jones.
He made huge voodoo huge!
He gave a grand to Bruce Grant over here.
He made wetlands wet, dear friends.
You know why?
Because Bob's a sex gun!
Bob is a sex gun!
Not just that, but Bob is sex.
Bob's all encompassing sex.
Bob's got more wives than anybody in the country and he still makes it on the fuck honey every night!
That's Bob!
What's his name?
Bob!
Fucking right!
Who is Bob?
I said it!
Bob!
Huh!
hu hu!
Bob!
Yes, friends, D.K. Jones, rats.
It's true, D.K. Jones, not...
Oh, wait a minute.
It's been a long time since I've seen that face up big and close like that.
River and Stan will tell you.
He's going to tell you later.
He's scared of Bob.
Do you think Bob's your friend?
Do you think Bob's your savior?
Bob don't give a fuck about your sins, girls and boys.
Bob has come to justify your sins.
And he's going to come again and again and again to justify your sins.
That's because he's Bob.
What is it?
Damn right.
It's Bob.
Tell him, River.
Who you got talking?
Talk it.
Yes, friends, it's D.K. Jones and Huge Voodoo at the Wetlands nightclub there in New York City
a couple of months ago in February.
An amazing revival.
They're performing in front of one of the prettiest big rear view video projection screens
that I've ever had the pleasure of dealing with.
And, yes, friends, it was a righteous and holy, holy revival.
One of these days I'll have to read from the negative review that was in New York Magazine.
That was just ridiculous.
And what did we have coming up next?
Ah, b-b-b-b-b...
I-a want to join Islamic jihad
I-a just want to kill for God
Praising Allah is the law for me
All you spy coms, what the fuck?
What?
Killing a Hebrew brings good luck
Gotta make the old man proud of me
Load a car with dynamite
And drive into a synagogue without any brakes
Nothing could be better than
Impaling your intestines on a big rusty stake
And grenades and cattle prods
Let's go out and kill for Bob
I can hear Mohamed calling me
A subgenius tape
But we'll have the real thing soon enough
So, uh, you know, wait until you hear
The version of Shock for Livin'
Geatomy combined with Mission Impossible
On next week's show
Oh, the Koran seems quite odd
I still want to kill
For Bob
Praising Jesus is the lie for me
A fuck of them pagans
They're such cynics
Let's bomb the abortion clinic
Jesse Helms, hey, is my cup of tea
Never thought I'd make it big myself
And got two idiots on cable TV
What the fuck, it's not cheap
But still a better way to use my business degree
Use the rifle, spare the rod
Let's go out and butt-butt Bob
Baby Jesus, hand that gun to me
I'm a slut, that's just the way it is
I like it
Oh, I love the world
It's all a joke and I've got a sense of humor
You know when Wavy says
If you lose your sense of humor, it's not funny
I'm a slut, that's just the way it is
Here's an example
I like rock and roll
I like jazz
I like country and western
I like the blues and tribal chants and choirs
I like fast music
I like slow music
Holy fuck, I'll listen to disco
I'm a slut, I'll listen to anything
Right here, in this world
Right here in the midst of this
I'll just enjoy myself
I'm just a slut, that's just the way it is
I never had any favorites
I like Jesus
I like Moses
I like the force
I like the Buddha
I like Atlantis
I like the great spirit
I like the higher mind
I like spirit guides
I'm a slut, I'll pray to anything
I'm a slut, that's just the way it is
I'm not saving myself for anything
Okay?
I'm gonna use it all up
All those stops go nowhere
Until I'm my alma mater
I'll stay at my soul´s마 2020
I like rock and I like jazz
I get all the ballad I love
I love my Philippines
I love the atmosphere
I love everyร♡
We'll see you next time.
and the alien sex workers.
Oh, I love to be naked.
That's what they all really want.
But the Gilly Bobs, they've got their hands up.
They want something for nothing.
They think Bob has something to do with slackers or something.
And they're non-members.
We might be able to get a few of them to empty their wallets and join up,
but most of them have no clue.
But we need them anyway,
because on that fateful day, X-Day,
when the normals are all, like,
striding pink boy hell,
we need somebody to pick on,
so the Bobbies will come in handy for that.
Because X-Days are coming,
and the pinks are bombing.
Ah!
Blaze Bob! Blaze Bob! Blaze Bob!
Yeah!
Of course, here comes my favorite sort of Bob.
It's the Buy Me Bobs.
They've got product to sell,
but they're also willing to buy product.
Most of you hopefully fall into this category.
And that's why you're going to be interested in the amazing section coming up now,
the section where we give you the post office boxes to write to
to get information on copies of these amazing tapes
by these amazing subgenius artists.
Going backwards in time,
rewinding in our brains,
as one might say,
that was...
what we last heard was Bill T. Miller,
the King of Slack,
preaching about used Slack and Gimme Bobs
live at the Slack Crusade Devival in Boston
at the Middle East Club.
And friends,
the easy way to get the information
on Kings of Feedback,
Out of Band Experience,
and Bill T. Miller's material
is just call.
This is a phone number.
Call 617-LICK.
O-B-E.
That's 617-LICK.
Ah, yes, and friends,
before that we heard a little bit of preaching.
And we'll hear some more from Reverend Velveteen Sly
and the mighty Heidi and Spring Herbage
at the Slack Crusade Tour of the Bible
in Madison, Wisconsin.
Yes, hello to our listeners there at W-O-R-T.
The slaves of the devilish Reverend Velveteen Sly.
And before that, friends,
that song called I'm a Slut.
Now that's something else, now ain't it?
That was by R. Moon
and the new Improved Night Nurses.
A brand new tape from them.
And you can get that information
from Holy Funk.
That's Holy Funk Records.
Just write to Holy Funk
at P.O. Box 2329.
That's it.
P.O. Box 2329.
San Anselmo, California.
9-4-9-7-9.
And between that,
we heard Dr. Bizarro.
Yes, you thought it was Frank Zappa,
but it's Dr. Bizarro
from his rock opera,
The Big Machine.
And he's got tons of tapes.
And you can get those from iBob.
That's iBob.
At Post Office Box 3405.
Skokie, Illinois.
3405.
6-00-76.
And we heard some bootleg
Joe Newman
and Rudy Schwartz Project
combined with Colonel Sphinx,
Drummond, and the Swinging Love Corpses.
Wait until you hear what more of that we shall have.
And you can always get Joe Newman's CDs
by referring to
Box 4542.
And it's fortuitous
that it is in Austin, Texas.
Where we just returned
from a great crusade ourselves.
78765.
For Joe Newman there.
And, oh,
yeah.
Yes, and this is Doctors for Bob in the background.
We have also heard some cosmic triad
from Reverend Emot Zipol
in our backgrounds.
And, oh, I think I forgot
one other little P.O. box.
Now, didn't I?
You got a pencil?
Who's got a pencil?
Write it down, children.
Bob!
Post Office Box 140306.
Dallas, Texas.
75214.
That's where you gotta send
that dollar.
All right.
So, we can help you.
Stop thinking so much.
Stop trying to be a genius.
Just kick back and be a sub-genius.
Sub-genius.
Yeah.
Doesn't that sound good?
I like the way that sounds.
Oh, yeah.
But how does somebody turn into a,
from a genius
into a genius?
Into a sub-genius.
Well, we have a special cure
that comes from Bob.
What we do is we take
a little bit of these elements here
and look into all the stuff
that's bugging you every day.
You can put it together,
mix it all up.
Bob will help transform it
and you'll have the substance you need
that will make you immune
to those conspiracy.
All those components together
are gonna sort of neutralize each other,
you mean?
Kind of like one of them there.
Homeopathic remedies?
Oh, yeah.
It's a homeopath.
It's a homeopathic remedy.
Right here in Madison, Wisconsin.
We can mix up the homeopathic remedy.
You know what it's called?
Tell me, sister.
Tell me, Reverend.
I need to know.
If I block that brain thinking too much,
it's brain-o.
Brain-o.
Good Lord, man.
Yes, sir.
I'm the guy that has my legal notices in advance
and permission to contact.
You have permission to serve me
after you practice your business.
So I'm Dr. Golankowicz's incident.
And I'm the guy that a center for,
let's see,
Dr. Vendicronology
that produced my evidence.
I was having trouble
with the center for Clemency Police.
They got spattered.
The big shoe on campus.
They had orders to give me the keys to the zoo
and accept my position
and liaison to law enforcement.
The guy I can't remember
what college he went to.
Then I'm entitled to free base,
explorer base.
I got the $150,000.
I was on 32nd Street.
Poleste Ball.
That, before I moved in here,
had the keys to my property in the early 80s.
And they had my bail and bond
and my right to explore base.
And they stole it.
And enough for my friends.
And what this address was about.
I had my bail and bond here.
And I had to pay for the property myself eventually.
Again.
Um...
And now the climax of our show.
The Pope of Berea, Ohio.
Lou Ducey.
And his friend, I'm not sure who it is,
doing their, um,
uh,
sympho-flatulation suite.
Uh, yeah.
Uh, thank you.
And good night.
Or good morning.