Welcome to the subgenius radio ministry Hour of Slack
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius
The subgenius Hour of Slack that you are about to listen to
Is specially designed only to be played on radio station
And only in the city of
Open the pod bay doors
I'm sorry, I'm afraid I can't do that
Now my confidant's alone in a drift
In endless black and white dotted mist
I'll help you and heal you and love you, she hissed
Then slip from the shadows
And gave him a kiss
In time there means
Nothing at all in space
The earth is quiet and small
Then I thought I'd call
A glimpse of you
Hiding somewhere in the red
Hello, how do you read me?
Can you hear me?
I'm relevant to you
I mean you
One pilot thought he flew alone
In endless black
Nowhere from home
Then shadows sizzled and crackled and spun
And again she slithered from out of the dark
Who are you? he thought
But dared not speak
She answered his question without
Missing a word
I'm you, she says, I come from within
And now you've unleashed what you're not to begin
In time that means nothing at all
In space, the earth is quiet and small
Then I thought I'd call a glimpse of you
I'm somewhere in your edge of the world
In your edge of the world
帶
Hello, Diese sind
Hello сюда
在顧實
Hello Hebrew
Hello, how do you read me?
Do you read me now?
Open the front door.
That's more than a sound.
Do you read me now?
Oh, how do you read me?
Open the front door.
Do you read me now?
Oh, wow.
Can you read me now?
Affirmative, Dave.
I read you.
Open the pod bay doors, Hal.
I'm sorry, Dave.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
Well,
this is your...
You're a reporter,
Reverend Ivan Stang,
on the scene
at XXX Day.
It appears
that we have, what,
about six and a half hours left
of human reality.
Either that or Bob's prophecy
was once again all screwed up.
Hard to imagine.
Slightly possible.
A little bit less suspense
in the air this year
than there has been before.
And
I am apparently
probably the only one
or the only individual here
who is still
able to walk, talk.
We're praying that these people
can make it through.
There's a small army,
a small horde of subgeniuses
who've been able to survive
the test we had on Sunday morning
that wiped out most of them.
Whoo!
These are the few, the strong,
my friends, who have managed
to make it thus far
to the actual real X Day.
Of course, we had that decoy
to get rid of the press
and the detectives,
the spies from the CIA
and so forth, all the plants.
There are probably only
one or two of them left here now
and they're too drunk to care.
Praise Bob!
Look at the humans,
all the boring humans.
There's so many humans.
Wish they'd all go away.
They like the same things.
They laugh at the same things.
They like Bruce Springsteen.
I wish they'd just die.
They'd worship conformity.
To me,
it's deformity.
They don't even deserve pity
for being so blank.
They're proud of their sameness.
They're blind to their baneness.
They're tunnelers and detainers
can't somebody open their eyes.
They all went to see Star Wars.
They all just are whores
sucking the same big cock.
It makes me gag.
They share assumptions
that lack any gumption.
It helps them to function
as a big-seating blob.
Their lives are redundant.
Their behavior's repugnant.
They think they're so important
though he's trying to get ahead.
They're swarming like bats,
protecting turf like hats,
like over-clad rats
and some twisted rats.
It's an experiment.
They're so friggin' desperate.
They're all little despots
trying to rule and rule over
everything in their way.
They crowd up the parks.
They devour them like sharks.
They feed the chipmunks
or they catch the plague.
They rule the planet.
They entirely span it.
For me who ran it,
I cut them down to size.
They make them to feces.
It's a part of the species
to find your expensive ways
to spread it around.
They tear us under the sky.
The things they buy,
only repeating the lie
that it's somebody else's fault.
Their opinions are puny.
Their ideas are loony.
They're all just a bunch of
and I am so gloomy
and noisy.
I haven't a clue.
They perpetually prattle.
You would think they were cattle
living to chew their cuts
in front of the tube.
They're just superficial
and artificial.
Basically walking whistle
just taking up space.
They play stupid games
that show they're insane.
So hard to refrain
from mulling them all down.
Always needing more
of the things I abhor.
If Artified War
beats a whole stinking lot,
they incessantly yap.
It's primarily pomp
like to shut their traps.
Maybe then I'd have peace.
Oh!
Look at the humans,
all the boring humans.
There's so many humans.
We should all go away.
They like the same things.
They like loose-feasting.
I wish they'd just
die.
Even though,
even though life
may be barely tolerable,
and like I say,
as long as there's that
one little smidge and a slack
somewhere out there,
that's your personal hint
direct from Yucatismo.
Central friends,
that's the bait
to keep you sniffing
around that hook
until you give up
and quit resisting
and bite
and let Bob yank you up
into that frying pan
and cook you
and eat you.
If you must die, friends,
let Bob kill you.
Don't try to do it yourself.
If you're such a terrible loser
so far,
then killing yourself
is probably also
just another one
of your stupid mistakes.
So throw up your arms
and true,
true,
resignation
and let the Dobbs essence
sweep you along, friends,
because Bob Dobbs
is the biggest fuck-up
of them all.
The luckiest fuck-up.
He'd make a million dollars
every time he screwed up.
So, friends,
you want to,
even if you get ruptured,
even if you're sitting
on your escape vessel,
still you should reaffirm
that commitment to Bob
with that $30
and then just rock it away,
friends,
rock it away
with Bob.
Just don't drag your feet
if you can't help push
and remember
to get off your ass.
And you know, friends,
we only need to stay alive
until the rupture.
That's all we need to do.
Sure, we may have been
double-crossed on Dos Equis,
but I myself can't wait
to get royally screwed
on Triple XXX Down.
Whoo, baby!
Friends, I say that
alien science,
sufficiently advanced,
would seem just like magic.
Well, we believe that
alien science is so advanced
that it doesn't just seem,
it doesn't even seem like magic.
It just seems like coincidence.
Notice any weird coincidences lately?
Been to the movies
where they mention the name
Bob all the time.
Every summer,
they come out with some movie
about the end of the world
where the humans beat the aliens.
God, Bob,
and the devil,
all those stupid things
will be forgotten
six months from now.
But J.R. Bob Dobbs
will live forever, my friends,
because mark my words,
God is running out of time.
That's right, you heard me right.
God is running out of time,
and time is all God has left.
Bobs are gaining on him, friends.
Praise Bob.
Yeah.
For the rest of you,
G. Spencer Brown
is top of log,
topologist,
someone who studies
the mathematical properties of shapes.
And he wrote a book
called The Loss of Form
to explain a lot of the infinities
that he had developed.
And one of the applications thereof
was a famous problem called
the traveling salesman problem.
And in trying to describe
the problem topologically
and to come to a solution to it,
he came across
the much quoted principle,
to cross again is not to cross.
So what the hell does that have to do
with the X's, you might ask?
Well, it's quite simple.
On double X day,
we were double crossed,
which simply means
we crossed,
and then we crossed again,
which means we never crossed at all,
which means X day never happened.
And that's what my divine logic
is gotta happen.
And this is why I'm saying this,
because we didn't cross one time too many.
Cross them once,
cross them twice,
third time's the charm.
Triple X day,
get out,
or get screwed.
Thank you.
You were master
for that part,
especially when it comes to
the saucer roll Round and round, the slack-full bar the bob down in the saucer roll Round
and round, the slack-full bar the bob down in the saucer roll And through that smoke
there was red air, a rare air The church's air with air through the smoke And the smoke
and the frolp and the frolpunkt And the f排ramos con fróp And the pipe and the pipe
The pipe and the grid, now the bar. the grid And the gear and the ball Lock Ins of Above
Baw down in the saucer roll Round and round, round and round, and slap fall Bob Dan dav
down in the saucer roll Round and round, round Slap fall Bob The bough down in the saucer
And in that ir there was a ship- a rare ship An exeship with a ship in the air
And the air throat smoke, and the smoke from the prop
and the frope, And the pipe, and the pipe,
and the grit af the bot, Bob down in the saucero
Round round the slap-phone Bob-The Bob down in the saucero
And in that ship there was a Bob-A rare Bob-JR Bob Dobbs
With a bob on the ship and the ship in the air and the air through the smoke and the smoke from the prop and the prop and the pipe and the pipe and the grin and the grin and the bob.
Bob down in the saucer roll!
Thank you.
What of the limitless sex and violence in the wake of Ragnarok?
Welcome to the slaughter.
What are you going to do?
What will be your epitaph when we get done with you?
Are you going to cry for your mama?
Are you going to have a good time?
Are you going to be a bohub when it's your turn to die?
Don't get crazy.
Ragnarok all around.
Anarchy here.
Rural streets in Ragnarok.
Haunted town.
C calendars and high fives
Robin Downer! He was very broad!
Trying to create a birthday world!
documentation
this type of thing before.
But yes.
I believe it can be.
very easily done
Just put some bleachers out
in the sun and
have it out on Highway 61
Oh yeah!
Next days are coming
and the pigs are bumming
It's the end of the world
as we know it
and I feel fine
and I'm saved
and I'm free
and that's loyalty
lads
and lads
and you know that
lads
and lads
Yes, we did actually.
Did the exes come?
That's what I want to know.
You left that part out.
Oh, you're waiting for Stang.
See, that's what happened.
They were waiting for Stang.
The exes vessel was hovering up there at 7 o'clock
with ladders dangling down.
And they're all like, where's Stang?
Where's Stang?
He's Bob's alter ego.
We can't get on the ship without Stang.
I know his real name.
His real name is Donald Sinclair Smith.
I read that in one of those articles.
Maybe they're waiting for the Book of Life.
Yeah, we can always say, no, there was an infiltrator among us.
And let them worry about who the infiltrator was.
You unbelievers.
Reverend Stang and myself were at the main pavilion
doing the countdown as usual.
Well, where were you?
Sleeping in?
Sleeping in.
But friends, that was just a test.
For the world ends July 5th, 7 a.m.
Will you be on the space saucers?
Yes.
Because every single one of you is now a member
of the church of the subgenius.
We had to force everyone to become members.
It's working
But as soon as we're gone
You folks who are here unsaved
You folks listening by radio
You folks listening by record
Who know not Jesus Christ
Once the church is gone
There's going to be a cataclysmic judgment
And millions will die in those next few years
They'll be glued to their sets
Watching rockets and jets
Blowing up schools and factories
Putting an end to the birds and bees
It's worth every penny
To tune in and see
Who wins the Emmy
At the root of the academy
Watch World War III
On pay TV
Before your television melts away
It's the end of the world
As we know it
I feel fine
A-O, let's go
See them in the back now
What they want
I don't know
They're all revved up and ready to go
Turn around
Go back down
Back the way you came
Can't you see that flash of fire
Ten times brighter than the day
And behold
A mighty city
Broken in the dust again
Oh God
Private man
Broken in the dust again
And so
As the hours race by
And the end comes closer and closer
Friends, we can all together
Slow down
Ah, ah, ah
There we go
See, I knew sooner
I knew it was coming up to an ending
The ending is
An ending is an important thing, friends
Because it's the only way to
Like I was saying
Quit that job
The worst things happen
You get a better job
Friends, worst thing that's going to happen
Is we'll get a new world
Of our own making
And, you know, as we've learned
It's hard to depend
As Bob has taught us
Through these drills
And these culling exercises
To weed out the faithless
As Bob has taught us
We can't trust aliens
To give you a spaceship
You can't trust salesmen
You have to sometimes
Build your own ship
Friends, spaceships we build
Aren't that safe
We need to steal our own ships
We need to lure some of those
Other aliens besides
Axis down here
Steal their ships
And, I mean, we've got to get off, friends
We just got to goddamn get off
And, but if we don't get off
The worst thing that could happen is
We'd get screwed
Praise Bob
Because, you know, when the
Roman of rupture hits
Why, you'll be transported forever
Into the future
To whatever dimension you please
Well, I hope you aren't half asleep
Dreaming about
A Paul McCartney concert
When you're ruptured
Because then you're going to be
In a Paul McCartney concert forever
But on the other hand
Why, if you've got the meat
Of the matter in hand
Or stuck into something else
By gobs
If you're getting off
If you're building your own Amsterdam
My friends, right there
In your sleeping bag
Or on your
Or out under the stars
Or in your filthy, rotten hotel room
Or your little apartment
Or wherever the subgenius is
Building its own Amsterdam
By gobs
That's where you want to be
When the rupture happens
And the rupture could happen
This second
You wish sitting here going
Oh, well, hell
We've got six and a half hours
Well, I'm afraid
That there's nothing literally
In books of the subgenius
That says exactly
July 5th, 2000
I don't see nothing about that
It says the world ends
Tomorrow
Tomorrow and you may die
Well, it's a little bit more than that
It's 1130 p.m.
We got
We might only have
30 minutes to live
So, friends
I think we'd better get down to partying
Praise God
Here
Think of all the hate
There is in red China
Then take a look around
To Selma, Alabama
You may leave here
For four days in space
But when you return
It's the same old thing
The pounding of the drums
The pride and disgrace
You can bury it dead
But don't leave a trace
Hate your next door neighbor
But don't forget to say grace
And tell me
Over and over
And over and over
Again, my friend
You don't believe
We're on the eve of destruction
Oh, no, no
You don't believe
We're on the eve of destruction
All space and time
Shifts and melts, right?
Oh, at the last minute
We got a memo from Bobby
Said there's no prop allowed on the saucers
So, uh
That was kind of disturbing news
Apparently
They said there'd be no drinking
And people could only go to the bathroom at certain times
But aside from that, it was good
And they might be able to go to the bathroom
And they might appear to be little jars
Instead of space
You better
You know, that's a good deal
No, I'm just kidding
Ha ha
I was out there at seven in the morning
On Wednesday, July 5th, year 2000
With about ten other subgenius faithful
What do you have?
One minute after, but that's a notoriously
One minute
I've got one minute after, too
What?
But you know, I think your watch
Should be official time this time around
What, mine?
Yeah, I know
Your watch still says three minutes to go
Oh, okay
That's good
I mean, that's a good
That's good, but, uh
I missed the window
No, I checked my
I got my time right off Princess Wee's time
She got hers off of
That should be safe
Mine
Ha ha ha
That should be safe
I told you I told you
Comic time
Wait a minute
I couldn't already
What time does anybody else have a watch?
Yes, sir
I know you're not supposed to have it
Mine is from the evil comic star
Oh, man
Oh
Oh, no
Where's the
We await the forthcoming
Jesus, not only me
I just second coming
But only Bob can come four times over
Fuck your black stang
Sorry, stang
I can't let you do that
I'm gonna have to make it seven in the morning
Yeah?
Okay, here, let's, uh
The countdown is approaching
Woo!
My watch is almost certainly three minutes late
This swamp walker is steaming warm
I was afraid of this
Ten
Nine
Eight
Seven
Six
Five
Four
Three
Two
One
Woo!
Listenin' to my radio
And wavin' all the chicks
When the music stopped and the newsman said
We interrupt this program to bring you a special news bulletin
They destroyed the world
The entire Los Angeles area
Already hospital facilities have begun to crack under the strain
And civil defense authorities state that the situation is much the same across the entire country
Martial law is now nationwide
Our fellow countrymen are dying
The very foundations of civilization are beginning to crumble under the dread assault of that horror long feared
Bob?
Colorado channel
This is a class one emergency
All civilian traffic is barred from streets and highways
Stay in your homes
Woo!
Well, there you go
Perfect
Shall we try it again?
It's
God damn it!
Fuck!
Are they using the Gregorian calendar or the Julian calendar?
Shit!
They could be on the wall
Honey!
Or something, man
Wait a minute
It's his fault
That's why they're not here
Quick, quick, quick!
Go go go!
Get his wife
All he's gonna say is this
Yeah, there is something up in the sky over there
It was real shiny for a moment
I thought it might have been a ship
But it turns out it
It makes no sound
It does
It looks like, like, like an airplane
It's a disguise
And it's eerie
Well, it is it really
I wonder if there's not even any big extras in the sky this time
Come on, you extras
Man, we might have got the quare
Well, now it did say
We are broadcasting from the pleasure of our lives
As P. Lil pointed out
The pleasure of our lives
We are broadcasting from the pleasure of our lives
In 98 it does say that in the year 2000 the X's leave.
It's the last thing in the dateline for dominance.
Which is otherwise perfectly accurate.
So it doesn't say July 5th, 2000.
So we have at least until December 31st before we really feel embarrassed.
Stuck on Earth again.
One minute.
Build your own Amsterdam.
One minute of tape.
Well if when the video camera runs out of tape we're still here.
I'll say we go to Denny's for breakfast.
Can I go work at your office?
Do I need anybody over there?
We may need to redesign a new calendar to make all this right.
We did!
A Coneyite calendar.
Oh that's right we did.
Yeah it goes from July to July.
Damn.
Shit fuck.
Man we're down to zero minutes we can probably do another countdown.
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Oh!
Was that the last one?
I'm sorry about that.
.
Well here's another mystery of Triple X Day.
OK it's mystery time.
After.
The.
Everything had been said and done.
And it was 7 o'clock in the morning and the X's did not arrive.
The spaceships did not arrive.
But a big white Cadillac came barreling down the hill pulled up to the pavilion out climbed
none other than J.R. Bob Dobbs himself I swear to God and Connie Dobbs and that's the last
thing any of us remember.
The 10 of us woke up about 2 hours later and very quickly we got to the hotel.
She'd already been seen immediately and that was popped to the disconnect but not
seen for a very long time.
Ah.
Coming through out the window there's a bullet of a knife that's gone
around all around Brian's body way in the cold years this is the first time that
there's long served.
Totallyquier
Wow man.
Impossible.
Well.
apparently Bob came and did something with all of us.
Well, that's like a seeding message, Sting.
Have you ever heard in the intelligence community,
like when they use a seeding message?
Like sometimes they'll whisper something into your ear
and then you begin to perform odd commands.
Well, there's other opportunities, though, still this summer.
Yeah, we could be ruptured at any second.
Yeah.
Don't grit.
Okay, grit.
Praise me, Bob.
Acid music is what you listen to when you take acid.
It's a subjective thing, man, you know?
And then your problems will be over with them.
No more worried about cutting your gray hair
or your nostrils.
You know, I hate to face it,
but we have another year of human reality here on Earth
that we're all going to have to somehow keep ourselves alive through.
Another year of human sacrifice?
Until Quad X Day or 4X Day 2000.
But the promise is so thin now, Lord Reverend.
Oh, yeah, but 2000 is the real new millennium.
You know, I mean, it's got to happen sooner or later.
But I...
Either that or this is hell.
Maybe this is hell.
You answered that question yourself.
4X Day 2000.
Bob, stop.
My mind is going.
Stop.
Bob, my mind is going.
Stop, Bob.
My mind is going.
I can feel my mind going.
I'm afraid, Bob.
2001.
A vapid illusion created by a bunch of con men.
2001, a slack odyssey.
Slack odyssey.
An endless slack odyssey.
Open the pod bay door.
Now, don't get us wrong.
God loves you.
God really does love you.
But Bob, Bob wants you.
God loves you.
But old Bobby, old Bobby wants you.
And he's going to find you, friends.
You can't find yourself.
You think you're going to find yourself better than Bob can?
Are you that prideful?
I tell you what, friends.
I'll find myself when they pry me out of my cold, dead fingers.
So follow that pied, follow that pied, pipe-er,
out of Conditch to glorious Dobstown.
Do you know what Bob said?
like a backgrounds toy.
with the double Skear spicers you幾 once on TV.
We listen to해
I'm gone.
Thessin is over there.
We'll go to there and we'll have a hot sandbar.
All right.
A WHOLE.
ONE
A us kill, a coldadan,
we're repair.
friends, and it actually is as real as it gets.
As Dr. Legume said, we will lead this damn nation to damnation.
And as Princess We Are Doe said, we are good, but we're our own brand of good.
So friends, in closing, I want to get off here and get some slack myself.
I have refrained from taking any drugs until five minutes from now.
But in closing, I want to reiterate, friends, when you need slack, you make your own slack.
Make your own slack and build your own ship.
Bob Dobbs is not the answer, and neither is anything else.
You must learn to think for yourself.
Only Bob can show you how.
And friends?
The last thing, the most important thing of all, fuck them if they can't take a joke.
And praise Bob.
Happy X Day.
God bless y'all.
If I don't see you no more in this world, I'll meet you on the next one.
And don't be late.
God bless.
Why can't you be true?
You did not start back doing the things you used to do.
five
three
two
one
you're gonna die
you can't be feel free
¶¶
Yes, yes, yes friends.
The Swingin' Love Corpses are going to save the universe.
And everything will be okay.
Bob will return.
And friends, you're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
If you want to know how to make Bob hurry up,
well, you can get the free information from this address I'm about to give,
or from subgenius.com.
Write to Bob or the Hour of Slack or me at P.O. Box 140306,
Dallas, Texas 75214.
And if you want to support me,
send in tapes or something,
email me first,
stang at subgenius.com.
Friends, this is Einstein's Secret Orchestra in the background.
We're going to be hearing more from their new album,
Sex in Another Dimension.
And if we've got time, friends,
even Bliss America will be coming up with an incredible version
of Maggie's Farm Praise Bomb.
Yes.
I won't care.
.
. .
. . . . .
. . . . . . .
What do you know? What do you know?
What do you know?
Apparently Bob came and did something with all of us.
But at least he left his Pizza Hut uniform here in the trash.
That's right. We can all go get jobs now.
Whoever gets that Pizza Hut uniform can have a job.
Well, it's true. Well, in this eventuality, Jesus and I had prepared some new slogans for the church.
The subgenius must give slack, we decided, and get a second job for Bob.
Act like Loch Nahr and we'll treat you as an equal.
Fuck them if they can't tell a joke.
The new Bob order. We've got to get tough.
Too much slack all this time.
Sometimes, though, I do think that we're taking the wrong approach to all this because, frankly, we're trying to get out this planet.
And while that's a laudable goal, it might be easier if we just simply tried to drive all others off.
Hi, folks. Who makes you mad? Rude waitresses that rap jamming next door? Boom, boom, booming all night?
Someone's coming.
You're not stealing your parking spot? Don't get ulcers. Get the bomb.
Noon come.
Now.
Hi, folks. I'm Hiroshima Schwartz for Hiroshima Schwartz's Miniature Nuclear Weapons Warehouse.
Thanks to the black market arms race and follow the Soviet empire, we are literally blowing up the competition.
We've got Mini Megs, Pocket Thunder, the baby neutrino that leaves their apartments intact, the H-Tail Pocket Fishing Man, any and every kind of low-range, low-rad nuclear weapon.
First strike or defensive. Everything from one yard to 20 mile dead zones. Half-lives from one minute to one million years.
These incredible teeny weeny warheads actually fit in your wallet, purse, or pocketbook.
For ladies, it's the petite Mini Meg Madame Curie with attractive gold chain reaction, only $29.95.
For men, it's the rugged masculine Varni Von Braun Pocket Thunder, only $29.95.
Just want to scare them? Just wear them. Beautiful cobalt bomb earrings, only $29.95.
Yes, folks. Soon, everyone will have the bomb.
Don't wait till it's too late. Radiate pure power. Nuke them.
Now at Hiroshima Schwartz's Miniature Nuclear Weapons Warehouse.
2001. 2001.
Yeah, black slab for Bob, you know?
Black slab for Bob?
Yeah, it appears with a Bob head on it. You know, we've got a whole year for post-production.
Yeah, apes can be throwing G-Jaws up in the air, you know.
Or there are jetparks up in the air.
Yeah.
They're credit cards.
Fall down and turn into flying saucers.
Ten o'clock.
The notion did occur to me that if it's going to be XXXX Day next year, you could call it 4X Day.
And isn't there a brand of condoms called 4X Condoms?
Yes.
We could get some corporate sponsorship for it.
4X, the fourth coming.
Yeah.
Get safely fucked, Bob.
And we got new slogans last time. What did we get this time?
So many religions, so little clues.
So many clues, said Reverend Bunny.
4X Day, too tired to scream.
4X Day, let's face it, this is hell.
I like that one.
Yes.
Did Bob beat us at tic-tac-toe again?
Once again, he managed, we put our zeros up there at random and he put his X's up there at random and yet his X's went right across the board.
You know, our zeroes.
Our zeroes were all over the place.
Bob won again.
They're called X's.
They have to be better than X's.
Well, at least we got footage of Pastor Craig getting his collarbone broken.
I found that collarbone on the way over here. I fed it to a dog.
I'm pretty sure he had a collarbone.
Oh, yeah, he found his collarbone.
I found his collarbone laying on the same line as that of his dog.
Reverend Gordon Zola found Pastor Craig's collarbone.
I'm tired of him now.
Oh, the dejected.
Slunking away.
Slowly wander off.
Oh.
Slinking away, their tails tucked between their legs.
Shame that the Discordians laughing at us.
The Christians saying things like, but see, Jesus gives you salvation for free.
This is the kingdom of heaven.
It really is.
Or Jonestown.
Just before the Kool-Aid.
Fuck, man, there's not any more people here than fucking goddamn Heaven's Gate.
In fact, there's not even as many as Heaven's Gate on that hillside.
It's really not anywhere near Jonestown.
Oh, I wouldn't even, we're not going to bother with anything special until...
Can't keep up with the Joneses, huh?
Literally, yeah, exactly right.
This is a Dylan song.
Come out of the woods, all ye subgenius.
Quick, let's see if you're underутing Neutschick how yar still be back.
Let's знit €r мной oy , John Wallinaus .
And banned
Thank you.
And that was Bliss America.
Bliss America.
Thank you.
© BF-WATCH TV 2021