Congratulations! You've made a firm decision, a strong commitment to unwind, to relax, and enjoy the slack you need.
Now, in a few moments, I'm going to give you a series of suggestions that will help you to reinforce this commitment that you've made to create this positive and permanent change in your life.
Brothers and sisters, the self-genius, our own spark!
We're back!
Oh, that's right, everybody's been here for three hours drinking.
The book club, I hope you enjoyed your literary discussions.
But now, as part of an X-Day tradition, and also it's a weekly show in San Francisco, we're about to do the Ask Dr. Howell show.
You'll have to wait.
You'll have to pay to have that question answered.
And obviously, at least one subgenius sent us one penny.
That statement won't mean a lot to the folks who listen to Hour of Slack only on broadcast radio from their local college or independent station,
because you people don't even hear certain episodes, the X-rated internet-only ones.
For the internet listeners, this episode's very interesting.
It's a great way to help people understand how the internet works.
And it's a great way to help people understand how the internet works.
For the previous episode, the one only heard on the internet, number 1327.5XXX, marked a critical turning point.
It was almost the last Hour of Slack.
But I can't explain why on this broadcast PG-rated episode.
And here's why I can't explain it.
Some of you may not know this, but by law, on non-commercial public college or community stations,
I can't raise money for myself or the Church of the Subgenius.
I can't raise money for anybody except the station.
I can't even say, you've got to go see this band.
The most I can say is, you might be interested in this band that's playing at such-and-such next Saturday.
Or for more information, see subgenius.com.
That's what they mean by non-commercial.
And the subgenius thing isn't just this show.
For one thing, it's my actual real job, because the church also does a whole lot of other media,
like books and even events.
Now, if you go to subgenius.com and click the radio button at the top, you can hear
not only last week's X-Rated Internet Only show, but all the previous ones.
In fact, all previous hours of Slack, almost all of them, in uncensored form.
Also, hundreds of previous episodes of the Puzzling Evidence show,
Susie the Flusie's Bob's Slacktime Funhouse from WREK Atlanta,
Phineas Narco's National Cynical podcast, and the Ministry of Slack podcast.
If you do listen to last week's show, it's more than an hour.
It has cuss words like crazy.
And at the end is a 14-minute rant by me that calmly explains a very dire situation.
A situation that threatened the show's existence, even the whole church.
But it's the kind of situation I can't talk about on this station.
You know, I edit a few cuss words out of all broadcast hours of Slack.
The internet version, which has been free, but won't be forever.
At least not quite the same way.
Has the cuss words.
Now there's some songs or rants or whatnots that would simply be totally wrecked if I
cut the naughty words.
And when enough of those clips build up, I do those X-Rated non-broadcast shows, generally
about two a year.
That last X-Rated show was really funny until the end when it got really serious.
That's the thing.
The bottom line is, there's been some news in subgenius land that we can't talk about
on the non-commercial radio.
And because advertisers and executives are, by definition, such total chicken shits, I
long ago quit even trying to sell it to commercial stations.
It's like trying to get a vampire to go to church.
Ain't gonna happen.
Anyway, if you like this show, be glad you're hearing it at all, and next time your local
station has a pledge drive, pay attention and do something besides listen.
Give the station money.
The more perceptive of my listeners can see what I'm getting at, and the less perceptive
are free to download the X-Rated show from subgenius.com.
The true children of Bob, the people who helped us out in our time of need, I cannot thank
you enough, except by continuing to make this darn old show.
And, uh, so let's get back to it.
Oh, by the way, the titles in this show were by Pope Zarka of Radio Eschaton on WCNI, Connecticut.
It's one of our newest stations.
And the music in the background right now is Reverend DJ Two Beans.
Oh, yeah.
Uh, Two Beans live at the X Day non-rave.
And now back to Ask Dr. Howell at X Day.
Drill number 14.
Price bomb.
Dear friends, I, Dr. Howell and Dowell, am now here to answer your questions.
Your questions must be written in orthographic form.
Use the pencils and pens which have been provided for you.
And then write them down with the kindliness and charity of Ivan Stang.
Use them to write on the slips of paper, which have also been charitably donated and distributed.
And if you feel the impulse of charity, which distinguishes the noble from the bestial,
you will include a small premium for me, Dr. Howell and Dowell.
The equivalent of asking the withered crone who tells your fortune if she would prefer
that you cross her claw-like palm with silver
because nothing has value
like something which is sponsored with value
and nothing has more value
than that which we invest with value.
Monetary units and paper notes
have no intrinsic value in themselves
but we all agree that we do.
Therefore, send them unto me.
Of course, even if you don't
send a solitary cent up here
I will answer the question
but my answer may be terse, succinct, laconic, brief.
If, on the other hand,
you feel motivated to generosity
my answer may be provided
with the flowery elaborations
which are so often a product of this program.
And, indeed, if we like the question inordinately
I will come forth with a bardic recitation
which is the most important.
And I forgot to mention
you're supposed to give him a shot of liquor
if we like the question
but I guess we're going to pass on that tradition too?
Not going to give him a shot?
We just did give him a free beer party.
That's right.
They had a free beer party.
And to go to my show in San Francisco
costs ten bucks
but it's free to you
because it's included
with your admission
to this wonderful event.
And so, my golfing and prayer partner
Ivan Stang
is going to read
the questions that you write to me.
At that point, I will answer them.
And as long as that lasts
we will do this
our version here at X-Day
of the Ask Dr. Hal show.
Then it will be time to continue
the bulldada auction from yesterday
for many wondrous treasures
have in the interval come to light.
All through the show, by the way
you may continue to write down questions
as they occur to you
and send them up.
Until Ivan Stang declares
the session officially closed.
The very first question that we were handed
it came with a one dollar bill
by the way Dr. Hal
but you'll see that
this is
the question
hold on
don't answer this yet
because it's followed by a statement.
The question is
whatever happened to James
Doohan's dick?
And then in parentheses it says
give your answer
then read mine
on the other side.
So he's actually giving you both your answers
So we have dueling answers here?
You have to answer it first
and then read his answer.
Whatever happened to James Doohan's dick?
Alright, well James Doohan
as I'm sure
each and every one of you knew
played the beloved Officer Martin
Montgomery Scott on the original Star Trek
television program that debuted in 1966
and he was in trim fighting form
then when he would defend his ship
from scurvy inter-seller sailors
and their bad mouthing
of his beloved craft
and not one to shy from a brawl
but success
has a debilitating effect
if you get what you want
you tend to lose your fighting trim
you tend in fact to stop trying so hard
and you get comfortable
and with good cape on lined
and this certainly happened to James Doohan
and he grew wider and rounder
more like those planets that he used to orbit
on the show
in his mighty starship
eventually this condition continued
as it will
until James Doohan's dick became invisible
from his vantage point
like an unknown stellar phenomenon
obscured by a pulsating cloud of dark matter
or nebulous material
there was a knowledge
a vague knowledge
though with the passage of time
less and less a certainty
that it was still there
but as I said
you can look at this as a cautionary term
about success
don't be so sure that you want to gain
everything that you aspire to
of course if James Doohan is being used in this question
as short for Scotty
one can assume that his dick
and all his junk
received far too many rads
through involuntary exposure
to the cores of the ship
which you probably remember
were always overheating
malfunctioning
sparking
and fritzing
now at this point I'm going to turn it over
and read the answer provided
and it's in poetic form
the prick of engineer Scott
fell off from Saturnian rot
so he went to the basement
and made a replacement
out of tungsten
and lambskin
and snot
very good very good
very good
and thank you for your dollar
you are here for a special return
Lord God
Fanny and his buddy bundled up a box of baby birds
Brought the baby birds to the blueberry bush
When the bumblebee folded, bit Bobby on the ball sack
Thank you.
Friends, that was the first cut on the new album
from the Rudy Schwartz,
Project.
The title of the album is...
How could I not...
How could I forget this?
Reach across the office and grab
the CD. The Year They Switched to
Cornmeal by the Rudy Schwartz
Project on
Dr... Is it really
Dr. Jam Records? No,
DC Jam Records.
Yes, Bagpipe
Benny by the
Rudy Schwartz Project.
And now, back to Ask Dr. Howell, live
at 14XX. Here's a
$5 question.
How can we prove
to the pinks that
Bob is real
and Jesus is pretend?
Well, you know,
Jesus used to be
portrayed as knocking on your door.
You know, coming to your door
and knock. And yet, how likely
is this? In
an infinite universe of infinite
possibilities, almost anything could happen.
And yet, this has got to rank
near the bottom. Like
Santa Claus paying a personal
visit. But, on the
other hand, Bob
was known for going
from door to door and knocking
on the door and selling
the vacuum cleaner after dumping dirt
on the floor and all that stuff.
All those traveling salesman jokes,
but perhaps no one today remembers them
or has heard of them or tells them,
but they used to exist and they were
all about
Bob. Bob was the
traveling salesman. Sometimes they even gave
his name as Bob in those
stories. So,
although there aren't too many
vacuum cleaner salesmen prowling
the suburbs today because
people are so fearful.
Oh, well, there's one right here.
I'm delighted to be...
What is the vacuum of choice
that you sell?
Hoover and Dirt Devil.
Is that a Mighty Might?
Does it take style C vacuum
bags?
We have SDXY.
SDXY.
Yeah, very exciting.
Those are good machines.
But do you go from door to door
selling these vacuum cleaners?
That's too classic. I'm
overwhelmed. I'm touched. Moved.
I'm moved!
Large big glass for the large big glass.
Ah, that's it. You see, now there is
a mediator between the traveling salesman's
and the customer. And it's the giant
big box store where you have
to buy 90 rolls of toilet
paper at a time. But in
older times,
J.R. Bob Dobbs wore out
his shoe leather
plodding from door
to door. And it wasn't collecting for UNICEF
either.
So, Jesus lived
2,000 odd
years ago. Bob
is likely always to be
still living. Who is
more likely to knock
on your door?
We've got photographs of J.R. Bob
Dobbs. I'd love to see a photo
of Jesus.
Simple as that.
I think you'll like this question,
Dr. Howell. It came with $2.
Good. The question is,
how did you become a member
of the Church of the Subgenius?
Well, I
was going home one night.
I actually had an accident.
I fell
through a sewer grating, which should have been
fastened.
Whenever I passed those things, I always thought,
what if it was loose? And I fell. But of course,
it never happens. I thought, oh, you're neurotic.
Just step on it. And this time,
it fell. And I met a
group of old people in the
sewer. The Nostotuti,
they called themselves, who
conferred upon me. No, none of that is
true.
That would be the sort of story that you'd
want to tell.
But in fact, how did many
people get honed
onto the magnetic lines of force
emanating from the Church of the Subgenius
through one
special chosen
medium? Three words
here. Pamphlet number
one.
In this case, pamphlet number one had
traveled to the underground comic book
factory where I was working
at that time in San Francisco.
Where it arrived on the desk of the
publisher, Fred
Todd, who took one
look at it and
pitched it into the trash
where Paul Mavridis
and I found it. And we thought
it was hilarious. And much to
Fred's irritation, we kept
going on and on about Bob
and Paul
got in touch with Ivan. And yes,
indeed, there was more to be
said on the subject of
this interesting fellow, Bob.
And so began
an association
which over the years has proved
more than mutually beneficial.
Praise Bob.
Praise Ripoff Press.
Praise Mavridis
and Fred Todd.
Ripoff Press no longer exists.
Really?
I was told
by Doug
Wellman of puzzling evidence that
when Paul looked
at the pamphlet, he said,
Oh my God, these guys hate Jesus
as much as I do.
Which is actually not true.
We don't hate Jesus.
We've never met the fellow.
Some of us aren't sure that he ever
even existed.
Some of us aren't certain we're livres.
Some of us aren't sure that it really
is the intentionally
thank you,
Mr.
That odd piece of music was by Fabrizio Fulvio Fiale.
I don't know much about it.
Reverend Titor sent me a link to it,
and I downloaded it and played it.
That's all we know.
The last name is spelled F-I-A-L-E.
Fiale.
Fabrizio Fulvio Fiale.
And now, back to Ask Dr. Howell, live at 14X Day Drill.
Now, here's one that came without an envelope or any money,
and it's almost completely unreadable.
Can you...
To me, it says,
Can to bus butthurt?
Can...
I'm able to...
How do you interpret that better?
It says, can to bus butthurt?
Can...
Well, what is this?
I don't know.
Is there any...
Fast?
The last?
Did the questioner...
Can the questioner clarify the question, the handwriting?
Can to bus or hobus...
Hobus.
Or perhaps it says,
Ian hobus butthurt?
Question mark?
No, that's not an E.
There's a...
It's a...
It's funny, though.
There's a curly Q at the top.
I don't recognize the problem.
Can to bus butthurt?
Over a consonant?
Apparently, the questioner has already left.
Can has.
Maybe...
If this were an H, H-A-S...
Can has butthurt?
That would be that funny cat talk they use on the internet.
Has met?
Like, can has cheeseburger?
Can has butthurt?
Well, it does have a question mark at the end,
which makes it a question interrogative.
Thus, it deserves a response.
The presence of questions suggests the existence of answers.
Both are constructs which we fling at the implacable silence of the universe.
So, let's just ask...
Let's just act as if this is a question.
And since it is, my answer is...
E-B-S...
Or...
Thalass...
Has...
Or...
House...
Can experience butthurt.
Why not?
Who can't?
Fortunately, there are a series of nerves there, though not the greatest concentration
of nerves.
But sure, no one is immune.
I'm sorry if I disappoint anyone with that particular answer.
Dr. Legume brought up something regarding butthurt.
When both cheeks are so very, very butthurt, a third butt cheek will sometimes evolve.
And where?
Where does it appear?
I don't...
He didn't say.
But I would assume that somewhere maybe between the original two hurt butt cheeks, a third
butt cheek will evolve.
Although that might close off and negate the purpose of the butt.
The main purpose.
In my opinion.
Some people may find other reasons for butts to exist.
Perhaps under an increased gravitational load on a heavy gravity planet, more butthucks
would be necessary.
This is a good one.
It came with one dollar and one cent.
Very good.
And a monster skeleton.
A screaming skull sticker.
Oh, boy.
It's a dick, Alex.
And a well done graphic of Bob changing into the Hulk that's an ad for the great We Slack
Radio, Reverend Slander Bob's 24-7 streaming copies of all subgenius radio shows, plus
the new ones.
And the question is, if...
I think this is.
If you...
If you stopped being so stubborn, would you rather be free, sad and happy new Rick?
not a hardly human without 인'Syth.
translation loss Highly Princeton University at selonda.co. Studies as l Chair.
feel, always makes one see an image of little sperms
wriggling through space. Did these
primordial seeds carry with them the taint
of primordial evil, of primordial disease?
It is not necessary for that
to happen, but it's certainly an interesting poetic
idea that wrapped up in the seed bundle, which
contains everything, is also the element of its downfall.
After all, death was an invention which came
long after the invention of life in order to
manage the number of living things acting
on the resource base, and it was necessary
to counter the invention of sex,
of sexual reproduction, as opposed to budding and
unicellular reproduction.
So maybe it did. Maybe some of Satan's
jisms sizzled down through the various atmospheric
layers onto the earth, and just maybe
evil is older than the beard of the ancient
of days. But those of us who have a greater faith, a faith in evolution,
know that a simple, advantageous
struggling between types is sufficient
to
be a
信念
Jungle
jungle
Apple
cares
g
To
as animated by Bob Clampett.
Could be.
Once upon a swinging time
Frank Sinatra looked around
And he said, I'm lonely for some
Cats and kitties
So he built himself a man
Out of clay the story goes
Then he made him a groovy chick
So they could mingle
The cat surveyed the lady fair
He purred, I'd know you anywhere
He entroved, madam
My name is Adam
And she said, buddy
You're all covered in mud
Head to toe
And Frank said, now you'll be
Man and wife
But they said, what are we after
And they lived happily
Ever after
I'll be back in a week
To dig the falls
Then they made the polka nose
Every room a heart-shaped haven
Ooh, them bubbles
Next the recess ding-a-ling
Turned that Chevy to the left
Victor moaned at the frontier room
And there's no cover
This chair is a mess
The chick adored her shining night
They cuckooed till the morning light
She said, good lovey
My turtle dovey
And he said, sister
Let's us savor this bliss evermore
And Frank looked around
And he saw it was good
A dug of the kicks and the laughter
And they lived happily
Ever after
рей
My giant heart
It seemed secure
The canceled encouraged
At the pool one afternoon
Chicky met that record man
He said, check my apple pie
I think you'll dig it
Those kids took a little bite
Reaching for their darkest shades
And before you could say Jack Robin
They were swinging
That chick turned into Peggy Lee
Thus Bobby Darin came to be
They sang out blue eyes
Here comes us new guys
And they said Frankie
We'd just like to thank everyone here
And Frank said I always knew you'd be stars
Here and in the hereafter
Let's all live happily
Make that swing and leave
Ever after
EHS
I learned that love
In the whoa
Cannibalism
The sense of something
S穴
I was never
wears a light cloth or artificial fabric outfits that are very small and short,
but then that's the way I see it.
And second part of the question.
Second question, how is justice best served?
How is justice best served?
I would assume differently than revenge.
Revenge is served best cold, but justice is served hot
and must be consumed while hot.
Otherwise, it fades away and disappears into the vanished heraldry of history,
into a confusing blur of shields and banners.
You've got to enjoy justice while it lasts because it is a transient phenomenon.
If you're too far away from it, you won't get the best blame.
You'll get the bays of its benefit, its warmth.
But revenge is best served cold, as the apothegm says.
I believe it was Jonathan Swift who said that princes never managed to eat their meat served hot.
This was a dig, of course, at Louis XIV, who made such a ceremony out of being served his meal
that it had to be passed down an enormous line of lords before it would come to his table.
So he said,
He, the emperor of everything and the Sun King, didn't get to enjoy the meat that the cook in the kitchen could eat when it was hot and savory and piping.
My name's not Bob.
Not a prop, Bob.
Good drugs?
Hey, Bob.
Where are you?
I'm not in a cell.
Maybe.
What do you mean, maybe? What's that supposed to mean?
Means maybe.
Maybe I'm in the next cell.
Another volunteer like you.
Or maybe I'm in the central office, spying on you for all those science bozos.
Maybe I'm not even here.
Maybe I'm just in your...
Self-genius.
Powerful.
Swag.
Ah!
Bob!
Bob doesn't believe I have one.
Hey, Bob, can you move your...
Oil de Bob.
Oh!
Look out, Tim!
Here's an important message from your Uncle Bill.
Don't buy drugs.
Oh!
Get it, got it.
Bob.
Bob here.
Yeah, Bob spelled backwards. It's still Bob.
Hey, for every stank, I got a new joke for you.
It's just Bob is what it is.
It's just...
It's literally Bob.
Big Bob.
Dude, what?
Big Bob, what?
What?
What is he doing?
What gets you up?
Is he fucking with Big Bob right now?
Why are you fucking with Big Bob right now?
You're fucking with Big Bob, dude!
He would do something!
Why you talk on Big Bob?
Big Bob will eat you up!
Big Bob?
It's like a weird dream.
Oh, year.
We'll never talk shit about Bob.
Big Bob will smack you up so hard.
Big Bob's the truth.
Okay.
That's Big Bob.
That would be my bad, Big Bob.
That's a big bar.
That would be my bad big bar.
What do you call that?
Uh, bottle.
Bottle.
What about this?
Uh, straw.
Straw.
What about this?
Uh, the salty sour of suck it.
Did you say you are ready to have my thang in your mouth?
Yes, sir.
What do you mean by that?
Big bar.
You smell like rubber and you're really sketchy right now.
Look at me!
What is that?
I'm in some hot soup here, Bob.
Some teenagers are hanging out in front of the store.
I think they could start slacking at any moment.
But I need time to cool down.
Bob, Bob, Bob!
Anything you want, you gotta fill.
Anything you need, you gotta fill.
Anything at all, you gotta fill.
Anything you need.
Cooling, cooling, cooling by day and then at night, working up a sweat.
I don't need no pay.
Step, step, step.
One, two, three.
Boom.
Cooling, cooling, cooling by day and night.
Working up a sweat.
Pushing up a tear and wearing a fit.
One, two, two, pushing it.
Cooling by day and night.
Working up a sweat.
Come on, girl, let's go show the God that we know.
How to control number one in a high-supply show.
Now push it.
The Large did that collage.
My name.
My name is not Bob, which also had in it, let me see.
Oh, Girl Talk doing In Step.
Thanks to The Large and Girl Talk.
And now, back to Dr. Howell.
This decorated one, this could go on forever.
It's got curly Q's and thingamabobs.
Yeah, it looks like a paramecium.
What does Dr. Howell recommend?
Read for more insight.
The other day, the film crew that's here was asking me my opinion of who prototypical subgeniuses are.
And it was difficult for me to give the proper answer as to where subgenius thought formulates.
But there are names that come to mind.
Mark Twain, for example.
Or go back earlier.
Thomas Paine.
Jean-Jacques Rousseau in his more...
Bearable interludes.
Or how about Restif de la Bretonne, the revolutionary French writer and pornographer
who wrote that loathsome 18th century work, The Perverted Peasant.
He was a free thinker who, in some ways, anticipated subgenius thought.
And he even used the French equivalent of the word slack.
H.G. Wells, I promoted the other day.
Jonathan Swift wrote the first great comprehensive science fiction novel.
Gulliver's Travels.
Clark Ashton Smith, besides being named Smith, with his friend H.P. Lovecraft,
largely helped to construct the foundations of our mythology.
But, as the old saying goes, if you wish to see a monument, look about you.
I am in the presence of people who are creating subgenius doctrine and thought.
I can speak of those progenitors who have died, who have gone before.
But we...
Are all moving forward into a glorious new realization of these things.
And it will take someone far beyond even this place to have the final, arbitrative word.
Thank you, Dr. Howell.
Three hours after the rapture happened...
Dr. Three hours after the rapture...
Dr. ...happened, buddy.
congratulations everybody
To the Although I었습니다
direction
Everybody
You will appreciate
the partnership
we gave to the film
Bob
Congratulations
Bye.
That was the Ministry of Slack and the Evolution Control Committee
late at night at the
14X Day Drill.
I don't really know the title of that song
but
you can
look them up
both Ministry of Slack and Evolution Control
Committee at
subgenius.com if you click the radio
button and then click the
title of this show.
Now back to Dr. Howell.
We still have questions coming up.
Define
why? Question
mark, question mark, question mark.
Define why.
That's not the same as just asking
why.
But why
is the operative part of the
interrogative
proposition. You must
ask a why in order
to get a because.
So why is
that which needs to be submitted
before achieving a because.
And the presence of a why suggests
the answer of a because.
So they are two
mighty twins who go forth
hand in hand.
You have been
listening to the Hour of Slack
number 1328
from the Church of the Subgenius.
For more information about the
church and or
all of the stuff we play
you can look at subgenius.com
and click the
radio button.
Dr. Howell
can be found at ask
drhowell.com
Howell is spelled
H-A-L because
he's also the
well known illustrator
Dr. Howell Robbins
with one B by the
way. So we'll
see you at subgenius.com
Thank you very much
everyone who helped us out.
And that includes the artists such as
DJ 2Beams heard here in the
background.
Praise Bob.
.