We're holding this public meeting in the Civic Auditorium tonight because of the story.
Good afternoon.
The subgenius, our old son.
For juvenile delinquents?
I'm happy to hear that.
Well, that's very interesting.
Yeah?
Mr. Dobbs purchased another radio station.
Oh, okay.
Assuming that radio would be in his future, Dobbs adds yet another laurel to his long list of achievements.
You do take medicine for schizophrenia.
Hopefully.
I'm sure you're not having an episode.
I haven't heard this before.
In the last 20 years of his life, the most dynamic industrial individual,
with 41 hours of tape, as much as 41 hours of tape,
secret conversations recorded.
Therefore, simple mathematics dictated that in less than one minute of each hour,
actually, the show could penetrate the record population with little effort.
And so, there were the first 20 years.
Hey, calm down, Jack.
Oh, my head's too big.
Wait.
I've been piping.
Here, let me pull you back in.
Oh, here we go.
Ah, yes.
The year 2000.
The distant future.
Oh, that's better.
That was a long way back, Jack.
Smaller now.
There's no show in there.
Yeah, I didn't think so.
I can remember.
Show's over here, Doug.
Y2K.
Here I am.
We are robots.
Okay, good.
The world is quite different.
We're the robot versions of ourselves.
That's the really cool thing.
I love it.
I was trying to tell you earlier.
Yeah, we're the automatons that just keep going, even though our bodies have already
left for X.
You know, for the outer world.
Yeah.
For the outer world.
We already left a long time ago.
That's why we keep going about this myth of X-Day.
But still, it's good.
Everything is so automated now.
We actually did leave.
Still, it's good, right, X-Day?
Yeah, we actually, our real, our earthly selves actually did leave in 1998.
It's just our robot selves that continue.
It's just our robots that continue on this illusion.
And here we are.
And this planet is Mars.
The humans are dead.
The humans are dead and we're still here.
But we're just robots.
Michael Jackson was a human.
It's too soon, sorry.
Yeah, they talked about Ali, about Michael Jackson, but what about Aliak Mark-Connor?
They look like they're dead.
They're a boss and girl.
I'll just confirm that they're dead.
Okay.
So that we could have fun.
The bubbles is not dead.
We stopped at the end of the world.
We're not with nothing.
Okay.
Nothing, nothing, nothing, nothing, nothing.
We start with nothing and leave everything behind.
No point in saving with a rainy day in mind.
The sun will rise in the morning, sure as every night it sets.
Maybe there'll be no warning from the men from Planet X.
Who knows who might be next?
Who knows you might be next?
Who knows it's anyone's guess?
Who knows hate it, all of it?
Who knows it might soon be you?
Who knows it could be me too?
Who knows when your time is time?
Who knows heaven is here?
It's been one hell of a ride.
We start with nothing and leave everything behind.
No point in saving with a rainy day in mind.
The sun will rise in the morning, sure as every night it sets.
Maybe there'll be no warning from the men from Planet X.
No point in saving with a rainy day in mind.
If heaven is here, it's been one hell of a ride
Leave everything behind
Behind, behind, behind
Who knows?
unbesmirched.
The salsas are coming.
Yes, the salsa
dancers are indeed coming.
They're going to bring their frantic
rhythms into
everyone's lives. But once again,
a strange phenomenon
has occurred that a sleeping
planet knew nothing about.
That the Earth was
saved from the fate of
ultimate destruction
one more time
at a lonely, secluded
campground in
remote western
New York State.
For X Day 12
dawned and
set, with all of us
still here,
with still a little bit
more time given
to us by the grace of fate
to clean up
our mess and do
our laundry.
I've got a lot of laundry left to do, actually.
Yes, I know. Nobody prepared.
And so it will be on
that great day when the sea
gives up its dead
and monsters walk the Earth
that nobody will be prepared
and will have even bothered
to destroy
his pornography collection to
keep from influencing whatever
posterity may remain.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is our special guest in the studio
this evening, Dr. Howell.
Oh, thank you. And of course, I'm
here with my co-conspirators
and fellow travelers,
Reverend Dr. Ivan
Steng and
his consort, Princess
We Are Doe, Queen of
All the Rebels. Yeah, we gotta do that laundry, because in case
there might be any earwigs
still in there. Oh, that is a distressing
episode she refers to, folks.
I have to put in a correction.
She's the princess.
I'm the princess.
I'm the consort.
Well, that's, uh...
However, I am the sacred scribe of the Church of the
Subgenius, which is a...
You see such becoming humility, friends.
Surely this must be the genuine
article. Not some
flim-flammer, but
one actually
riddled with
holy effuvium, or darsham,
as it is called.
Yes, the
emanation that radiates
from holy men is very
strong in this room, as I sit across
the table from Ivan
Steng and shapely
Princess We Are Doe, here
in the center of the
belly of the beast.
I thought I felt something crawling up my spine.
Oh, wait a second. That's Rocknar.
Hello, you're on the air.
Good evening, Dr. Sinister.
Well, if it isn't Governor Rocknar.
Price Rocknar, it's good to hear
your voice. We missed you the next
day. We really did. We missed you, but
you received a special Bobby Award.
During the coveted Bobby Awards
ceremony. Well, thank you.
I'm honored. I
just wish I could have been there in person to receive
it, but... We've got
the award for you, so don't worry.
You will get it.
Yeah, handmade
by Susie the Flusie and
Pantiera,
Reverend Pantiera.
No doubt they used their hands,
yes.
At least that much, yes.
And when the
award
were displayed,
they were displayed by those two
who hung them on themselves
as if they were living
Christmas trees.
Nice.
It's true.
I'm not making it up. That's the
honest-to-God gospel truth
about what happened out there.
It was a great X-Day. My baptizing
hands are still glowing with the
holy power from
dunking those sinners
into the pool and washing
their sins off. Actually, what we try
to wash away is the concept of
sin. We don't care about their
sins. It's the idea that they might
feel guilty about something at all
that we're washing away.
That and the filth on their
bodies.
It's only real filthy
sinners need to worry about that. Certainly
no one who associates with us
at the secluded Brushwood
campground.
A lot of people are still
out there tonight.
We rushed back to make it to
this show. Barbaric punishments
being administered.
This show
important. You may be the first person in
the history of the world to have said that. Thank you.
I think he meant
important. Yes.
Um.
Important.
That too.
Why not both? That's what we say.
Important and in
poor, terrible
taint.
But not impotent.
Nor impotent.
Neither of those.
The potency of the church
hasn't died down, friends. Sure.
The exes didn't come.
We don't know what year this is.
We don't know what planet this is.
That just means we get to do it again next year.
And judging by
the beauties in the
baptismal pool this
year, it's just
it might as well have been on the escape
vessels of the sex goddesses.
Truly. But let's hope they don't catch
on to that one so next year there
can be more of the same frolic
some antics. Well, we
you know, we don't ever since we quit allowing
cameras in the
naked baptismal
pool, which is an actual swimming
pool. This isn't some mud pit
or playpen that we fill up with
water. It's the campground has a
nice pool. We fill it
up with the
seekers and the saved
and we resave them.
And most
of them take their clothes off
before they save me.
It was chubby chaser
heaven, friends. Well, yes,
not only that, but
I was privileged to have a
conversation with one of
the loveliest pilgrims
out there while she
removed everything.
I was looking into her eyes.
That was very
gentle. Well, I didn't
want seafoods to come down on me
that. Yes,
right. That's a good idea.
But still, that was a devastating
experience for one who
has an essentially romantic soul
and just one of the many smorgasbord
of sensations
available to one who makes
the pilgrimage to travel for
the end of the world, which we are
now absolutely sure must
take place next
year. The Baker's Dozen
13,
the clock striking one
stroke past midnight
is surely the hour
that the exists come.
Not the eleventh
hour or the seventh
hour or any of those other puny
theories which have been apparently
discredited by
time. But, of course, there are those
who say that time is as full of holes
as cheesecloth, and it's all
the fault of people who are
astrally projecting without
looking where
they're going. However it is,
our own concept of what
year it is, what time it is,
and what ex-day it is, even
as Reverend Stang suggests, what planet
it is, may need
violent and immediate
restructuring.
Yeah, 13 ex-day,
the lucky number, friends. This past
ex-day was 12 ex-day, and
I
wasn't terribly surprised
out there. Was
that really this morning?
7 o'clock this morning? It was. This
morning, the planet Earth escaped
an immolation by fire
predicted by Jesus
Christ, the Son of God, who sits on the
right hand by the celestial
throne. And I wonder if the word
omnipotent would
be appropriate in this context.
Omnipotent? Well, we know
the old Jehovah One
is needing a lot of patchwork
and bodywork,
filling in those dings.
Senile
space god, I thought, was the
way he was described.
Omnipotent. Right, yeah, that's a good
one. Yeah.
Now, I have a theory. New vocabulary word
there, kids. I'm
sure Ragnar has already taken it down,
but he has a theory. Omnipotent, yes.
Or omnipotent. But
I have a theory why the exes
don't come. It's because too many of
us have too many places listed
on our do-not-destroy list.
Huh. Well, those are just
special exceptions that
surely don't really get in the way
of the operation, but that's a novel
theory. What's your
thought on that, Stang? Well, I
do have a pretty long list of
Earth places that I was
going to say. Yes, everyone knows about
all those museums that you have
your deep down. Right, sure. But
that's just a tiny fraction of the
I was going to, most
of New York City, most of all
big cities and everything in between would be
scoured of
pinkness. Well, isn't it the pre-release?
Is it prerogative of a conqueror just to
scoop these treasures up because
you can? The way Newt Gingrich
marched into the Smithsonian and took
their Tyrannosaurus head? Or
the way
many other tyrants throughout history?
The Nazis. Hermann Goering, who was
the cuddliest, chubbiest,
most lovable head of the Gestapo
you'd ever meet, took lots and lots
of people's art
because he could.
One of the world's great art corrections.
Careful about mentioning Hermann
Goering on this program. We might get a call from Bernie.
Oh, he's a Goering
fan or controversy list
or something? Well, no,
but Robert Byrd, the senator from West Virginia
is.
Well, he
talks of Goering then constantly.
He should get over it. That was years
ago. Yeah, really.
For real. You know, and Goering
himself cheated the
hangman with his special
sealed ampule of
cyanide, which some
people would slip to him by one of our
guys. I don't know if you've been
following the latest to-do about
World War II, but it seems like
it might have been an inside job.
Cyanide? I didn't
know that. I hadn't heard anything. Because
Goering actually was a lovable
guy. I mean,
he was hideous, evil, and so on,
but he had the ability to make
people like him, and that's how he got into
power, and he wasn't interested really
in the politics. He
knew Jewish people who he personally
saved, even while he allowed all
the others to be destroyed, and he
had one of the greatest electric train
collections ever.
His warm, cuddly nature was the very reason
he was allowed in the bunker in the last days of
Nazi Berlin. Well, he was not
allowed in the bunker after he
misunderstood the Fuhrer order, which
Bormann distorted,
suggesting that he succeed Hitler
if the reactionary
masses and Russian
communists and Jewish plutocrats had taken
over the bunker, then Goering automatically...
became the supreme head of the
state, but when Hitler saw
this, he thought in his paranoid
drug-induced rage that
all the... Hermann was
pulling a fast
one. Was Goerbels in the bunker?
Goerbels, of course, was in the bunker.
I was confused, I was too. Poisoning his
children and otherwise serving the state
right to the very end.
But Bormann
always wanted to get at Goering. This is
the way everyone always was trying to
stab or slice each other just to get them.
To get the Fuhrer's favor. And so
he spun it as
though Goering was
laughing at Hitler and taking
over the state. So Hitler stripped him of
all his offices, each
one for which he had an elaborate
uniform designed specially
for him, covered with tassels and medals.
And the most elaborate of all these
was his Falcon Master
of the Reich uniform
where he had little lederhosen and
a Tyrolean hat with a feather and
all this stuff as the head
of all falconry in the Third Reich.
And Hitler said, and he is even
stripped of his Falcon Master
title. That fat
drug addict will sludge no more
falcons into the sky.
Aye, the Fuhrer demands.
Look at the way how flings his arms around.
To get the right
Hitler thing you have to fling your arms around.
What drugs
were Hitler on?
Well, they would swab
the nostrils of the Fuhrer with cocaine
sometimes while he was asleep.
Just to bring him around because
it took a lot to bring him around because he had
this doctor who's been called a
quack, Dr. Morell,
who gave him all these
monkey gland injections and
other things and huge loads of
amphetamines and drugs
like that which, you know, the modern
understanding of them didn't
exist. They were commonly given to
pilots. It was considered a military
thing to do it and if
the German superior soldier
could do it, then the supreme soldier
could do proportionately that much
more. And that is what
kept his mustache shiny and
glossy and twitching.
JFK
was given injections of amphetamine.
Yeah, he would ask for it
because, you know,
you're the guy in charge.
You can't nod off in your rocking
chair. You've got to be crisp
and frosty. That calls for another one of these
jolt caffeine energy mints.
Give me two.
Say, I hope lonesome
cowboy Dave manages to make it down
to this studio for this historic
bobcast. We're expecting
him to make it in by wire.
Wire?
He's going to be calling.
Any minute now.
Dave did
make it to X Day and
verbally jammed
with us and helped with the auction.
He did. The bulldada auction
which was fabulously successful
this year. Right on our brushwood stage
while they were bidding for everything.
Friends, we have auctioned
off things like a dollar.
A plain, ordinary
dollar for like $20.
And don't forget the year we
auctioned off Wellman's front
teeth. The front teeth of puzzling
evidence in itself. The
teeth past which the wind
of so many strange statements
about Guam
have passed over the airwaves
on beautiful KPFA,
our sister
weirdo station.
There's quite enough
on those teeth too.
G Gordon Gordon auctioned
off the septum of his
nose which had been removed
and replaced. A hideous
loathsome sight. Which was
the subject of a velvet painting by
Lies.
Yeah, which was painted on black
velvet. This horrible chunk
of nasal septum which fell out
because of too much
overindulgence and certain
stimulants. I wonder
if next year I should auction off my house
at the Bulldada auction.
It would be rather
awkward, a bit of a pain to have it
transported all the way out there, eh?
What?
Well, no. We'd have to have an open
house right there on the
stage. They'd have to inspect it or
you'd have to pay for flights so that they could
come and troop through your living room
and kick over your loose under
drawers. I don't know, I think
you could always shoot a
video record of the interior of the
place. You won't need a house next
year. That's right, you'll be cradled
in arms of the sex
goddesses aboard those giant saucers.
That's right. It's a lucky number, man.
13, X day. And that's right.
Next year I'm coming to X day
house or no house.
Our faith remains unshaken.
Our houses may have
been destroyed by earthquakes, but
our faith is solid as
a rock.
Yes. Or a bed of
quicksand.
We'll be right back.
Bob? Bob? Bob?
And welcome to the program.
Is this synesthesia?
This is synesthesia.
I was just wondering, I missed a part
about the neo-rosicrucian orbs that were
circling in the encampment.
It wasn't exactly a circle,
it was more of an ellipse.
Those did cause some confusion. Every year
these other
unidentified alien
craft or whatever
they are, swamp lightning,
whatever, show up. Did you see the
X's in the sky once again?
I missed that, but we did have the
chemtrail X's in the sky over
Brushwood on another X day.
It's almost as if they're deliberately
tormenting, teasing us.
I even saw the cadaver Bob
with the X's on his eyes.
Oh, somebody took the
pennies. Boy, you can't trust
anyone. One year
we spent them. In order to attract
the X's, we had
everyone at the campground pull down their
pants. We set them up in a
to spell out the name Bob.
And had them all
pull their pants down and bend over
so that their behinds
were facing upwards at the
sky, spelling out Bob in
buttocks, including the quotes around his
name. Dr. Howell had painted each
buttock a very nice, like, plump
like with shading and stuff, and it was really cool.
Not this year, although I, oh well.
Unfortunately,
we didn't have a camera up high enough
to prove that we were spelling out
Bob in butts.
Oh, don't worry, Google had a
satellite watching us anyway.
Not at that time.
This is before they had invented Google Earth.
In fact, Earth itself had
possibly not been invented. We may still
have been on Mars then. We still don't know.
Yeah, no hot air balloon
that year to get a picture from.
No camera on a balloon.
Hey, you know who was one of the
first aeronauts?
That was George Armstrong Custer.
He used to go up in a balloon.
Custer was a hot air balloon rider?
That's right. He was at first
terrified and he thought the basket
was way too small, but he got
good at it and enjoyed it.
For a spotter during the war between
the states, that balloon would go up and nobody
would shoot at it either. You could see the
Shenandoah Valley for miles
in all directions.
And that was how Custer escaped
Little Bighorn. This is a little known fact.
But then he was...
The storm came and he was wafted away
to a mysterious island
where he lived in a
cliff cave with an orangutan.
Until finally he died of
madness and starvation and the
orang skipped town.
Yeah, he deserved it. He was a
jerk. But for a while he thought
everything he touched
would turn to gold.
He was a great hero
of the Civil War.
He was, interestingly enough, last
in his graduating class at
West Point, but most of
the interesting soldiers of that period
actually were the last
in academic standing
who could just get by and not be
cashiered.
A very tough, tough crowd. This person
was always known as the goat at
West Point. And Custer was the goat.
Why a goat?
I've never understood.
But that question has been asked.
Why is the last to pass
in West Point called the goat?
And modern West Point is trying to
get rid of that tradition,
discouraging the whole goat thing.
Still, everybody knows who it is.
And when that person crosses the stage
to graduate, there's always applause.
And the goat is considered to be
lucky for the school, too.
It's all part of their ancient tradition.
It's a tradition.
It's like what Dave is.
So Dave is the goat at X-Day.
The X-Day goat. Well, at least he's not
the bellwether ram who leads
the bleating sheep into the mechanical
jaws of slashing death.
I've seen goats at county fairs that actually
fart into balloons
and things and blow them up for the children.
They actually do blow balloons up
with their own breath
and stuff. But I was just going to remind you
that Custer did have his ears
removed by many of the, um,
well, he was maimed only in the
ears because he didn't listen.
They did not remove his ears, actually.
What you're thinking of is that the
women took awls, long
awls, and drove them into his ears
because he just never listened.
If he had only listened to what they
said, he would not have been
in this pass, you know.
They did not mutilate his body, although they
mutilated just about everybody else.
Actually,
I have heard very
different stories from my Lakota
friends. Wonderful. I'd love to know
what they are.
These are all only from accounts of people
who were on the scene, and they did tell
different stories. Right.
How about the awl thing? Did that happen?
I never even heard of that.
However, I was
involved with
the Lakota Medicine
Men's Association. Yes, you see
we in the Church of the Subgenius
must often consult with our
brother sorcerers and magicians,
and so happens you do have that
native
bond. I was informed
by somebody I had
perfect no reason to distrust
that in fact
the Lakota mutilated
the hell out of Custer's
body, and
that his regenerative
organs were still in the possession
of the
have been passed down from hand to
hand, so to speak. That happened to almost
all the men, but I had heard that it
didn't work. They say that, yeah,
Custer was, they had respect
for him as a warrior, and so they didn't do that.
Well, that's a bunch of hooey.
Supposedly they arranged it.
Who are you going to believe?
The BIA Indian school, or the Indian?
Yeah, the Indians themselves have
their own tradition. Another thing I read
was that they arranged a dead guy
with his butt sticking up
to the sky, and then filled it with a thousand
arrows, you know, so it was like a pistol.
They left that as a mark
for the whites who were going to come and find
this battle scene. They were a little
angry at the time. They had a right
to be, because the entire thing
followed the Ouachita
River Massacre, which
was sort of like in Vietnam
when they burned the animals.
Yes. The same technique.
Actually, that's
a bunch of hooey. That is a bunch of hooey.
Extinctified so many
species on this continent, it would
make you sick. They were in
the business of killing off the
local animals too, but a lot
slower, and with a lot less
efficiency. Well, but the animals
in the New World had not evolved
around people, so you could
practically walk up to a North American
moose and knock it on the head with a
tomahawk. Not just mooses,
or beasts, as we call them. Indians did have dogs, though.
They did have them extricated. The local elephant
was killed, and
the American horse, as we were talking
about on the way back from
Ex Day, was exterminated
by the native population for
food, and never
was developed as a draft
animal, or used as one, until
the Europeans reintroduced it.
Which they did
with great speed.
Which many people don't know,
the cultures blended very quickly,
and the Indians were doing
pretty well until some,
they were over, I even heard
tales of Indians
making their own weapons, rather than
the idea of weapons,
weapons chauvinism that we
have now and stuff. Sure, they made their
own weapons, they were very well specialized
things too.
Their own guns, I mean. They said,
hey, well, we can do that too, and used
their arch of
metallurgy, which were not quite
as advanced, but still
quite nice.
Well, as far as I know, they didn't make
guns, which takes a factory,
but they did make their own
ammunition, and did know all about that,
and were in possession of ammunition
molds that they had captured, and
Custer and his men
found a whole bunch in the
deserted village
that they attacked.
They would find all the treasures of the Indians
and set them on fire, and shoot their horses.
Clearly they needed more ammunition.
And this is all just a metaphor
for what's going to happen
when the true X-Day comes.
I'm afraid so. Did the conspiracy think
it couldn't happen to them? It's just that
the space cavalry is
just as ruthless in its own way, and it's
a strong desire to clean out
the riff-raff so they can set up
what they've always wanted to have here.
Well, I did hear them blow charges
last night, but so far
I think we're still in the same dream that it
really happened, but we keep
going back there because we don't
think it happened, and so, you know,
every day we've been aboard the vessel
doing what we wanted to do.
Right, but our imagination is so limited
that our escape
vessel looks just like our grimy
apartment on Earth. And not only
that, it was a great trauma when the
Earth was destroyed. We
were all part of the Earth, and this
elaborate construction that we
actually comfortably live in
protects us from the
eternal sorrow we would otherwise
feel at the fate of
the old place, even though we ourselves
were canny enough to
escape the fate that befell
the helpless millions.
Imagine the eons of re-education
we had to endure. And we thought it
was perhaps maybe two, three, four
years since the last extaeon. It had been
millennium, millenniae.
No wonder we had to flee
to frivolous amusements to
console ourselves.
And it all became part of one fabric,
these frivolous amusements and constant
unending re-education.
You can view the
frivolous amusement tapestry
by invitation
at, uh,
well, I guess, you know, it's radio,
we can't, uh, anyway.
Oh, but look at some of the wonderful pieces
hanging below it that look like little pieces
of angel pubic hairs.
I think they are, because the
winged messengers of God tend to fly
so close to these pictures just so
they can see the fine detail
which is, uh, exceptionally
fine when you consider the
sensory, uh,
array that an angel possesses.
Quite, quite remarkable.
The entire spectrographic
array appears to be
emanating from the bottom there.
Well, they can see a huge range
of vision and even the devils
in hell can see
a great deal of hell.
As Milton says,
once as angels ken,
meaning the fallen Satan,
he views the dismal situation
waste and wild.
So he sees more of it than you would
if you were plopped down into it, which is
is just, uh,
all the more saddening and irritating
because the next stanzas describe
how awful the place is.
But of course, Earth, uh,
that was just a dream, wasn't it?
Yeah, yeah. I was gonna ask,
uh, do we know this, uh, material
about angels and demons from
fossils or from Swedenborg?
I thought they came from, uh,
mimeographed or xeroxed
sheets which were included
with the subgenius registration
packet. Oh, that's right.
We never actually got to that matter
on the docket, uh, this year.
The one gene, remember the one gene
that got thrown on Goddammerung?
The one, the crazy guy
that you said kept on accusing you of being a, um,
a Hungarian or something?
You mean Ragnar Rockenvold?
It's something similar to that, but yeah,
it's a sort of a low-key
entertainment, but boy was I Thor.
That's what Thor, yeah,
that, yeah, at least feeling very Thor.
Kind of, uh, a ridiculous
story, uh, balderlized
than one might expect. Speaking of, uh,
Ragnarok, this is WCSB Cleveland,
and if you want to get on the, uh,
air to, uh, say something
real quick, uh, you can call Bob. We got a
taker right here.
...gelly-like fluidy
orbs and rosicrucian...
Oh, uh, thank you.
...chicken down.
Morse code.
Are they speaking morse code now again?
Yeah, but all they said was...
That's the sound of their
That's one dash.
...buttonism.
They're enduring, uh, some sort of, uh,
genital, uh,
rearrangement. Uh, LonesomeCowboyDave,
where
are you? What is it that you're looking
at right now? I'm
looking at, um, at some sort
of bowl, and there's a glowing
orb inside it. It's not like
the jelly consomme, neo-rosicrucian
orbs. Oh, yeah?
Well, it's not like them, but I guess
maybe it is kind of a copy.
And if I look over here
to the left a little bit, I can see it's
shooting out little, little tiny
yellow filaments of white.
Wow. The rosicrucians tend to do things
that are rather sub-rosa, don't they?
Well, they don't. Off the cuff, as it were.
Are you sure that's not your, your, uh,
lucky, uh, eight ball?
Yeah.
I prepared your canoe with cedar
boughs.
It's time for you to leave now,
William Blake.
Time for you to go back to where
you came from.
You mean Cleveland?
Back to the place where all the
spirits came from.
And where all the spirits
return.
I'm sure you've heard
this before.
This world will no longer concern you.
Hello, you're on the air.
That thing is...
Hey, the SELSA's coming up, huh?
What's coming up?
I got a tortilla chip calling up here.
The SELSA you were talking about earlier?
Yes, that is coming in a wave
to inundate us all in, uh,
mild, spicy, and
hot.
Oh, yeah, it's kind of like the tortilla chip of the show, you know?
A tsunami of, uh,
red sauce shall pour upon
our terrestrial tortilla.
Well, I'd love to witness
Cleveland undergoing one of those
once-in-an-eon Great Lakes, um,
tidal things.
Well, it feels like we were spared
this year, but of course we've been saying we
don't know whether that really happened
or not, and our listeners may have to
make up their own, quote, minds,
unquote. Me being a listener? I got my own
opinion. Oh, yeah, well, good for you,
buddy. I'm glad. It's people like
you who make me satisfied that we've
got a future. Who's gonna fight the next war?
Uh, put her there, pal. Yeah, who's the next
hero? I was thinking about fighting you, not at
war, man. Oh, yeah?
Do you want to do it?
Do you want to do it? Yep, yep. His parents
were monsters. I don't mean that in a mean
sociographic way. That's all right.
I mean, they were on feet for the feet. One was a werewolf.
One was a werewolf.
R.C., don't even bother saying your prayers. You're already gone.
And the fell witch of Glokheron, whose long
strong hair hung down over her
jagged teeth and pendulous
breasts. He puts cadavers in the wagon.
Cannot stand up against this mighty
juggernaut here. Excuse me, I didn't
realize you were in the
studio. Is my countenance
crimson? Are we going to be planting
any cadavers along with us when we
take the rest of the wagon? Well, that's up to you.
Pardon? That's up to
you if you want to plant cadavers
That corpse you planted
in your garden, has he yet began
to sprout? Make sure that friend
to man, the dog, does not dig
him up again with his nails.
Or good lord, Tion Grandma. We'll be launching a
space shuttle from Cape Cadaveral.
Hey, we've been kind of out of touch
with events in space. Was the moon
bombarded during this last
epicycle? Well,
this X-Day was quite lunar as
the size of the moon was enormous in
Shermansville. Sure, but I'm talking about
NASA's plan to smack
the lunar ice into space
so it can get spectrographically
analogized
by orbiting space.
I didn't hear about that. Wow, me neither.
They were going to blow a chunk off the moon so they
could get a kind of a good look at it. Incredible violence
has been done or is about to
be done to our satellite
by NASA. You see, they want
to find the water that is supposedly
on the moon, but the only way they can find it is by
blasting it into space
high enough so that it can be spectrographically
analyzed. You know, in honor of our
Independence Day, I want to show my
true patriotism by demanding that
NASA launch a series of nuclear
missiles onto the moon
such that the
face of the moon will say, America
F yeah. Why not just
a first strike for an ancient
case? There
may be a war on the moon at some day
in the future and we don't even know if there
are lunar beings who
could pose some capable
threat to us. Well, they're not threatening
us. They are... But they're
flying on the Earth. They could. They could and
very often their leaders are very despotic.
No, you see, we project our behavior on them. I'm not afraid
of... I'm not afraid of the... The lunarites.
The selenites are no... No, not a threat to them,
are you? They are obviously an enlightened
race because they had the good sense
to get off Earth millions of years ago.
Well, I suppose you guys aren't afraid of Martians
either unless maybe one or two or three of you
in that studio there are Martians. Oh, those bone-dead, dry monsters
from another world will
never affect me. Now, on
the other hand, the horrible, squishy,
incredibly super hot
Venusians are a different matter.
Hey, watch your lip, buddy. We're not incredibly
horribly sausagey. It all depends
on your point of view and, uh,
just to be near a body that's
so radiant that it can roast
you and... And I have to say,
most of you guys are clumsy and, uh,
you don't understand that humans
exist in a delicate
range of life
that you can't suddenly be
broiled and barbecued because
one of you guys forgets to
zip up his uniform.
Well, the uniform's like
And if you think I'm gonna live in a neighborhood
after all the time I've lived on this Earth and have
the nukes moving in next to me,
you've got another think
coming with that supplementary brain
of yours. And I don't mean any offense.
Don't you hate when the nuclear family moves
in right next door to you?
Well, as long as I have my own, uh,
uh, detector, I'll
feel a little bit better.
One proton, one neutron, one
electron, some orbits
going on. Yes. And then two kids
and a car of some kind.
Forty acres and a mule.
Maybe next year we should launch one of those nuclear missiles
at Jupiter in honor of, like,
2010 and just
turn it into, like, a mini sun.
No, that was a bad, uh,
science fiction movie,
Roknar. It would not be a good idea
to have another sun in our solar
system. I thought this had been firmly
decided. Um,
the one we have is quite sufficient
and our position as an inner solid
planet would not be improved by being
between two suns.
So you'd never get any sleep?
No, it would never be dark.
It would never be night. I suspect
the motives of anyone
who suggested this.
Sun going up, sun going down.
It was a dark morning. It was a gray morning.
There was no morning. There was nothing like that.
It was eternal noon.
Noon lay heavy on flower and tree.
They would sure cut
down on vampirism, though.
Oh, it would be, uh, coitins for them.
Just coitins. At least on one.
That is the...
There's always the, uh, no, there's no way you could
escape except maybe in those, uh, lunar
craters where the ice, uh,
was or is or
used to be before we blasted it, uh,
out to see if it was there.
That's, we'll find out too late that that
was the temple of the grand lunar.
The only ice. I don't see why they have
to destroy the ice
they're looking for.
The archives of the civilization that had
grown on the moon were
right in that spot that we blew
through, uh, past through their books. You know, there is...
It sounds goofy to say it, but the
idea that there might be lunar vegetation
or even lunar life,
something like that described by H.G.
Wells, is not too far off.
I have a very interesting British
book written by a very
learned astronomer called The Strange
World of the Moon. No, it's not
Schwa, although we did
offer Schwa's book, uh,
at our Bulldada auction,
and it was snapped right up
as a shark snaps of a tooth. A clavicle.
Eleven ducks. Eleven ducks?
But, uh, are you talking about
underground, um,
lunar... Yes, he's talking about underground life
and he shows how it could be so
and how the, the, uh,
underground wind caused by
the heat of the outside would blow through
it and so on. And interestingly enough,
recently it was discovered that the moon is hollow.
When it was hit, it
rang like a bell.
It's not solid like the Earth is.
The moon is very light. No one can hear your bell ring.
And, uh, does not, uh,
it's not volcanic at all.
The moon is completely, uh,
non-tectonic. Um,
but of course, constantly
being whacked and banged by everything that comes
along is enough for
geological change. And its orbital
movement itself is enough to keep it
going just like Tekel Brahe knows.
The Earth also cracks the
lunar regolith, just as
in a far greater way the
moons of Saturn, like
Enceladus or the Jovian moons,
are tremendously stressed by the
gigantic, uh, tidal drag.
But the moon is small.
If you took the disk of the moon
as seen from the Earth and put it as
a flat disk on the Earth, it would
just about, but not quite,
uh, cover the, uh,
North American continent. That's
the size, uh, if you can,
uh, consider.
Well, and people call you a kook
if you point out the obvious fact
that the moon is just the skull
of a gigantic space monster
that once threatened the Earth.
I remember after...
A comic book.
One of the comics that
we were discussing had the idea that
the moon was a giant egg of some
incubating creature.
And of course it hatches in
the comic, uh, I think
it was a Jack Kirby, uh, comic.
Well, no, no, this goes back to the
ancients, the idea of the cosmos being
an egg. This is almost Aristotelian.
Yeah, that's
true. Or Salvador Dali, who
drew that egg, uh, in
its first moment of hatching. Also,
a drop of blood to show that
with birth, there is pain.
I just
wanted to tell you guys something really important.
Yes? My ex-wife
found a huge dinosaur head in
their backyard, and this is kind of true. It was like
a fish. Oh, really? It was a fish.
And it's, even the
mandible thing area
where the teeth came out were
still, um, intact
enough so it didn't fall apart, and they gave it to the
Cleveland Museum of Natural History.
Because I guess the Great Lakes were
at one time at the bottom of the Atlantic
Ocean before something real bad happened.
Was it a member of the species
Xiphactinus?
I don't know. It was a, it was a fishy-like
dinosaur. How big? You guys are the dinosaur experts.
How big was this, was this dude?
How big? I would say that what
this jaw thing that they discovered
was almost a foot
in length. Okay. At least
a foot in length. It could be.
There might be the Dunkleosteus. Immature, juvenile.
A small Dunkleosteus.
Perhaps. If this was in a...
That name rings a bell. Is that a real name?
Yes. Dunkleosteus
is a name. It's one of the
neo-paleontological names.
Those who are classically trained
will think of the same creature but give
it the name Dynichthys,
or terrible fish.
But like many of the cool
paleo names that's since been changed
to a boring one by modern
science, and now it's called Dunkleosteus.
Well, it was discovered by
Professor Dunkle.
And quite properly,
he has the discoverer's
privilege of naming the
specimen. Incidentally, only the
jaws and teeth are known.
No one knows anything about the rest of the body,
but judging from the enormous
size of the head, that
must have been one mosh-headed lunker down
there, I gotta tell you. Well, if this
was an infant, then the
mother would be over 400
feet tall. And
she knows where you live.
That was the Gorgon.
The Gorgosaurus. Yes, I remember
how Ackerman wrote in
Famous Monsters, the poetic
line,
When Gorgon's mama comes to town,
London Bridge is falling down.
Oh, that's great. It's true.
That is sweet. At least
in that movie, the monsters trash everything
and then don't get killed and just walk off,
you know, together into the sunset.
And the little boy gets tears
in his eyes. I sure got tears in my
eyes. He got tears in his eyes, but what about
those other little boys who ran down
the docks to see the excitement and got
seared and burned by the flamethrowers
of the military while they were trying to dispose
of Gorgon's mom? Well, now,
you can't drag a movie down
with those kind of little details.
Oh, it's necessary to have those
deaths. And as Stalin said,
the death of a million is a
statistic, but the death of a single
person creates sympathy
and pity, so it's
best to kill as many as
possible at once. Well, that's
a rule of thumb. If you could
get out of the entire process by just
killing everything, that,
I don't know if that would really,
would that improve anything?
According to a tyrant, didn't Caligula
once say, oh, that the Roman
people had only one neck?
That's a wise leader.
I've been listening to a few since Caligula
that said that. Yeah, it's
funny how this show we've been
talking about tyrants and
dictators and bullies and
there's something
that makes us realize
that we've escaped a great calamity,
or have we,
from 12X day,
but it was
not without certain scars
of passage.
Boy, that one guy showed me the scar,
you know, this scar here.
Well, he had tried to leave the campground
the year before without getting his
electrostimulonegative reinforcement
wristband neutralized.
Yeah, he had a little hand growing out of that scar
by now. I blew his hand right off.
And it had to be replaced. That was
Reverend Brain Leak.
Well, you know, a chick's dead scars
becomes necrotic immediately.
And you have to reconnect everything.
But these days, that's a snap.
In today's hygienic, modernized
hospitals and reattachment centers,
your wayward limbs can be
on as an outpatient procedure.
Yeah, in Dobbs Town,
thousands and thousands of patients
are being retreated and
reexamined by having all
of their molecules rearranged.
Well, but did you hear about that poor
guy in Germany who got a
foot sewed onto
his arm and a hand,
his hand,
under his foot because of
bad paperwork?
Well, uh,
I don't know.
...as a cosmetic kind of a design thing
as a statement. Oh, someday all the kids
will be doing it. Just because we said it
on this show. Maybe with that
one ought to be run through Snopes, uh,
dot com. But I have to say,
it's a common surgical procedure to do this
for a temporary period of time because that
gives a blood supply
to the, uh, part
which is ultimately to be surgically
put in the right place.
And you have to, you know, you can't
deal with dead tissue
when you can keep tissue alive,
as Victor Frankenstein always used to say.
You mean you have to keep on
a different body part?
They do it.
How about this technique where they
have a human ear attached to a mouse's
back? In this case, our little
mouse friend gives a blood supply to
this human ear before it
can be reattached to a human
door. But once again, that's a social statement
right there. A rodent with a human
ear on its back. I mean, think of that as a
logo for some kind of new business. Well, you know there are some collectors who have the
mice with the ear on its back
just for that, you know, and that ear isn't going to be
attached to anybody, realistically,
given human nature. There's some
one out there with a whole terrarium full of, uh...
And it may be
it makes you feel a certain way when you look at a
rodent with an ear on its back.
And speaking of ears, now that I've got
your ears, real quick
I have to remind everyone, portions of the following
broadcast may be found objectionable by some
listeners in the audience. Therefore, listener discretion is advised.
And the views and opinions expressed
on this program are not those of WCSB
or Cleveland State University.
That having been said, uh, we want
to continue in just a moment here, but first we want
to pause real quick. Guys, I
hope you'll stay on the line for a moment.
Thank you for your time. We'll be back in
just a couple of minutes here.
Should be back in less than
five minutes.
No, Dr. Sinister, we won't be back for exactly
one week, and hopefully by then I will have
had time to pour through, compare, and edit
into a proper documentary the actual
location recordings from
12X Day, and the
rest of this post-drill show.
Uh, we had just returned from the
grueling, gruel-fueled tomfoolery
of the five-day camp out in Special
Olympics, so we were a bit exhausted
from the crazed mood that
shall be evident in the future
episodes made increasingly
from actual location recordings
as they happen.
Meanwhile, this is Hour
of Slack from the Church of the Subgenius.
For more about the church, see
subgenius.com. For more
on Dr. Sinister's show, see
WCSB.org.
But
for sheer tear-jerking
slack, listen to this breathtaking
new version of the Phineas
Narco version of the song,
Bob's Way.
...
And now
the end is
near
We sit and face
the final
curtain
Bob Dobbs
will kick
their rears
their pink bright butts
...
a life that's full
we
didn't go
the pink boy
job way
but more
much more than
this
we did it
Bob's
way
regrets
we had
a few
but then again
too few to mention
cleave
their world into
and blast
off to
the X
dimension
Bob's
pipe is stiff
and hard
and it will smite
them
here on
X day
he'll
pulverize
their little
world
he'll do it
Bob's
way
yes there were times
you often knew
the pink boys
beat us
black and blue
but through it all
we
we didn't stop
we took the pills
and smoked
the frog
we faced the car
and we moved
on
and did it
Bob's
way
oh sure
at times we cry
but we
we cry
but they'll be the ones
we'll be abusing
until the last
pink boy has died
I'm sure we'll find
it quite amusing
to think
we'll do all that
from Bangor, Maine
down to Zimbabwe
oh no
oh no not us
we'll do it
Bob's
way
for what is
a sub
what has he got
if not some
slap
then he has not
to say
the things
he tries to say
truly feels
and not the words
of those who kneel
the record shows
we dealt the blows
and did it
Bob's
way
thank you
Bob's way
brothers and sisters
for coming to the end of the world
and beyond
and for doing it
Bob's way
I'm going to be
Does my idea
sound real?
Have I slipped
you locked?
compost day
Then I took
the
gun
to
Bob.
When you lift up this ruby block, instead of the penny, there on the table is a white king soap box top.
The terrified natives believe its curious, hypnotic actions are caused by an evil spirit.
My mother.
What's the matter, Dick?
It's Bob.
Thank goodness.
It's not Bob.
Look at the collar.
Oh.
Thank goodness.
If it would make a difference, Bob can come with me.
Captain, here he comes.
Yes, Bob.
Come along.
Well.
Give them a hand with the luggage, Bob.
Go on.
Hurry.