Uh, uh, thanks. Thanks, uh, uh, Fred.
And, uh, yes, dear friends, well, you know, I...
This is your host for the hour, Slack, Reverend Ivan Stang,
and why I just looked at my calendar
and realized that I wasn't behind only one show,
but I was behind two or three shows.
Need to catch up real quick,
because it's going to be a busy, busy month.
So, uh, friends, we're going to get into reruns.
Yes, reruns of the old, uh, the old sad stuff
and the old glad handing stuff of, of, uh, stuffings of Bob.
Uh, you know, there's so much wonderful material coming.
I know it must be wonderful.
But I haven't had time to pre-screen it.
And, uh, I really must whip these out.
But, by the same token, you know,
most of the stations that are carrying Hour of Slack now, uh,
weren't carrying it, uh, five years ago, six years ago.
This, uh, show, I think I'm going to...
I'll probably do a little, uh, combo.
You know, I'll be doing some editing off of the master tapes of...
Uh, these are... This is...
Technically, tonight, we're doing Hour of Slack.
Hour of Slack number 469.
That's how many there have been.
But I'm going to play the, uh, the work tape material
from Hour of Slack number 123,
mixed somewhat with number 125.
And this dates from, uh, March of 1988.
So that's, like, more than six years.
And I doubt if any, uh, carrier stations
have ever played this particular show.
Uh...
So why not?
You know, let's...
We'll take a peek into the past,
the dim and distant past of the, uh, Hour of Slack
and the Church of the Subgenius.
Uh, some...
Some of the familiar voices sound so young,
little thumb-sucking Reverend Stang.
And... And sort of insecure.
It's sort of...
Oh, it's more homey, in a way.
You know, we've... We've gotten so, uh,
well, not slick, but, uh,
we don't... We don't care so much anymore
whether you think we're stupid.
So let's, uh, take a quiet trip back
into the nostalgic times of the past.
That one time.
That... That one good old time back then.
Uh, before we were quite as rich and famous or...
or poor and...
harassed.
Ah, yes.
Oh, we love you, dear friends.
And Bob loves you.
Even while he decapitates you.
Ah, yes.
Oh, I almost forgot to tell you, my friend.
Um, there's, uh, this particular show, number 123,
is of slight historical significance in that
this was the first and, I guess, the only show
that prompted a
a bomb threat to the station.
This was broadcast on, uh, KNON in Dallas.
And probably, uh, it may have also gone out on WFMU
in New Jersey, the, the, uh, first other station
to ever carry this show.
And still does. Praise W...
And support WFMU, you listeners.
You know, they're... They're having a rough time of it.
I sent them some money. I really did.
Believe it or not. Not much.
Anyway, uh, yeah, we got a bomb threat.
Uh, in the course of, of this show, um,
we weren't, uh, going on the air and talking about it,
I don't think.
Uh, I... I haven't...
I tell the truth, I haven't, haven't listened to it.
But it upset somebody so much that they called up
and told Will O'Dobbs, who was answering the phone,
there's a bomb in the station.
And they hung up.
And we called the cops.
And the cops came out and said, uh,
what kind of a show is this?
And we said, oh, it's a funny comedy show.
It's a funny comedy show, sir.
Uh, it's like Mad Magazine.
And they said, well, oh, well, well, that sounds great.
We'll be listening.
We don't think there's a bomb here either.
Uh, so...
Yeah, back...
Back down memory lane, dear friends.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah.
K-N-O-N 90.9 in Dallas, Texas.
Where we teach you how to give mouth-to-mouth resuscitation
to a timber wolf.
Oh, excuse me.
You are about to experience a full-length subgenius show
the way it was meant to be heard.
Uh-huh.
In full frequency modulation stereophonic broadcast sound.
So relax.
Three beats per measure.
Sit back.
Exercise one.
And enjoy our feature presentation.
Welcome to the subgenius radio ministry hour of slack.
Sponsored by the church of the subgenius.
But when you get right down to it, good triumphs over evil.
And the forces of light trample into bloody pulp.
The sickly powers of darkness.
So remember as we wander through this charnel house, this abattoir we call life.
That even though the future promises nothing.
Destruction looms ahead.
And the end of all joys.
Old age robs us of everything worth having.
There are some nice things in life like a shaft of sunlight.
Drifting down.
Down.
Down to what to do next.
But you helped Bob create the church.
Well, Bob was the founder.
He founded the church in 1953.
But he kept it secret.
And just bided his time planting evidence of his presence everywhere out in the world.
Friends, I bet in your neighborhood there's a Bob's TV repair.
That is owned by J.R. Bob Dobbs.
I bet in your neighborhood there's a Bob's Cafe.
Bob's Auto Body Shop.
I know.
Yeah.
There you go.
Bob's Diner.
Bob is, he's with the small business man.
He's not into these giant monopoly capitalism.
He's into the individual making a buck.
You wouldn't see the Bob Corporation.
You wouldn't see Bob Co.
Bob Co.
Well, I may cash my checks from Bob Co.
But you wouldn't see it.
No.
But friends, you know, you don't even have to.
You don't have to praise Bob.
You can hate Bob.
That's the funny thing.
He's a short duration personal savior.
He's the kind that, you know, he goes with this plastic culture that's come along where
you, you know, you buy something and use it up.
A spouse.
You buy a spouse.
Use it up.
Throw it away these days.
Or a child.
Well, you can do that with personal saviors.
So take Bob into your heart just for this month.
Send us your $20.
Friends, you'll start to guess what slack really could mean to you.
And if you're not of the wasteful bent, you can also recycle.
You can get a little bit of your salvation that you can get from the church.
That's right.
The death and rebirth thing we do, people, they love getting killed so much.
They come back over and over again just to be re-killed and reborn in Bob.
I love it.
It's like, it's like an orgasmic experience for some.
We finally, until their money runs out.
And then that's the last time they get to die with us, baby.
F***.
I can stay.
Well, if you can't tell the difference, you ought to realize by the sound,
a baby makes a completely different noise than a accordion when you squeeze it.
And when you stretch it, it doesn't even take in air.
Rigidity is...
That expels it.
Ridiculous.
Somewhat in the manner of the common...
Random.
I've had the Secret Service come to my door going,
Reverend Stagg, what do you think you're doing, man?
Because they're in Dallas where we teach them to shoot at presidents
and at people who shoot at presidents.
They don't get...
Our so-called jokes.
Our dogma jokes.
Friends, the...
The Church of the Subgenius, if it is a joke, could be the greatest joke ever told.
If Earth can make it to the punchline.
So you better hope old Bobby is in control in 1998 when those aliens get here.
Oh, yes.
It's a joke all the greater because it's not funny.
Well, that depends on how you look at it.
And it's not art.
You know, what...
That's what people out there should understand.
No, certainly not art.
Well, unless you call the Sistine Chapel art or Bach's most beautiful religious hymns art.
But no.
No, those are...
That's religion.
And this is religion, friends.
And we get down to the basics.
It's all about hate these days anyway.
This is a religion where you are urged.
We just come right out and say, go ahead.
Hate them.
It's all about us versus them.
Anyway, there's only two races in this world.
And we're all gonna have to fight to get to the bottom of it.
All the rest are just skin colors.
The only two races are us and them.
And them can't take a joke, friends.
So you know what to do.
Basically, two factions out there right now is us and them.
And unfortunately, them is much, much greater.
The fortunate thing about it is that we know that them are actually working for us, but
them doesn't know that they're working for us.
And they're working for us.
What do you think will be the next obstacle the Earth people will put in our way?
Well, as long as they can think, we'll have our problems.
We are gone, aside the universe.
We stand at a crossroads.
The tenuous slack that a subgenius may occasionally enjoy
could be rent to shreds at any moment.
For the human puppets of the elder gods
continue their senseless plunge into madness and anti-slack,
dragging us and our whole beloved planet
ever closer to the brink of destruction,
be it by the nuclear kiss of Jehovah One,
ecological disaster, or invasion by hostile aliens.
Which will it be?
Destruction of Planeter,
or eternal slack under the benevolent rule of Bob?
Or are the two the same?
This world is destined for destruction.
You say it can't be true.
Jesus began to give to them the signs of his coming in the end of the age,
and one of the signs he referred to was the abomination of desolation
that was spoken of by Daniel the prophet.
Exactly as Noah getting in the dark triggered the deluge that destroyed the Earth in his day,
and that it's very highly possible,
that when this all takes place,
that a great cataclysmic judgment will do that very thing.
God will destroy this country, cities, and America.
Cities in this state can literally instantly destroy.
Well, we've done it.
To quickly defeat another civilization shall be enough to
Notегare
Joshua
well,
budgets of the years so blue and green with a Medicare fund she started on the faze success is a Shelby winter school, which did she did she gets a job, planning, operating this pot, it looks like more than anything else, but there's Meerates at theニ様
We'll be right back.
Oh, yeah.
Well, twist, twist, twist, little sister.
Out of the grips of a mean old mister.
President of the United Fools.
Hot, hot future in fossil fuels.
Oh, yeah.
And long johns for a cold, cold winter.
Then we saw the outhouse glitter.
And there said Paul with his overalls deep.
His sins cataloged and his rosary beat.
And the wind took, the clouds took.
And me and my baby traded one last look.
The heavens.
All for nothing.
No.
Thank you.
You're so confusing.
Over here we have a marvelous attraction
I think you might like.
It's the Brimstone Baths.
And there are the California mud goddesses.
And Reverend Ivan Stan is here with us today.
Yes that's right.
I'm afraid I really am here.
I didn't want to be.
It was like a nightmare.
Now it starts to sink in.
A nightmare come true.
All right, all right.
Thank you, thank you.
Down here at the little live station
with all the live little doctors.
We make you almost as free as Jesus at this hour.
Yes, but it costs the people of California
a lot more than Jesus will ever cost them.
Their lives, their souls,
and now, yes, we want their pocket change.
Hello.
Could you hear me?
I can hear you.
Oh, and now the listeners can hear us too.
We're here again.
It's that show poltergeist again.
Well, the truest question,
now that the listeners can hear,
what can we do as people unto Bob
to bring the fear of Bob to other people?
Well, now, see, this is the big difference
between this cult.
This cult, if you want to call it that,
and other mind control organizations,
and that is that we won't tell you what to do.
You have to, we give you the benefit of a doubt.
We figure they're subgeniuses.
They don't rationally figure it out
because they're not geniuses.
They're subgeniuses.
They just, they can tune into their own stoop brain,
so to speak.
That's the special part of the brain,
the deepest part,
almost all the way back to the medulla.
You can tune into your Bob self in a way,
you know, you're connected to Bob.
And see, we want, we could, you know,
when you send off for the book or whatever,
the book of the subgenius,
we, you know, it gives you all sorts of instructions
as to how to run your life.
But, you know, frankly, that's for the Bobbies.
That's to give the Bobbies their money's worth
because we know the true subgeniuses out there,
the ones that are ready to kill Bob,
as well as love him, you know,
kill him in their love for Bob.
They'll do whatever they damn well please anyway,
you know.
You know what I mean?
There you are.
So that's how you know you're doing the right thing.
They're quite significantly altered.
At that very moment,
Jesus just rushed right into my room.
What happened, Jim?
But the light was so bright,
12-gauge shotgun,
and I stuck the barrel in my mouth.
The coup de grace administered by Satan himself.
Joe had a heart attack with my thumb on the trigger.
At that very moment,
Jesus just rushed right into my room.
What happened, Jim?
But the light was so bright, you know,
12-gauge shotgun,
and I stuck the barrel in my mouth.
The coup de grace administered by Satan himself.
Joe had a heart attack with my thumb on the trigger.
At that very moment,
Jesus just rushed right into my room.
Courtesy of the Subgenius Foundation,
located in Dallas, Texas.
The address, if you'd like to write to them,
for any kind of information,
at the mouth,
the address is P.O. Box 140,
306, Dallas, Texas, 75214.
And they're more than happy to receive mail
from people out there in the atmosphere.
Ivan Filo and Mr. Opinion made mention of
past, present, and concurrent lives in that interview.
Now, that's a concept that requires some elaboration.
Did you ever have that feeling that you've been here before,
or that you've experienced certain events
that are far removed from this culture or in time frame?
Were you the Queen of Sheba or Julius Caesar in a previous life?
Oh, phah!
On the pink and simplistic notion of reincarnation.
It's a conspiracy-thrusted idea geared to make normals believe
that their lives could be more interesting than they really are.
In a subgenius reality,
reincarnation is not an overblown linear idea.
It's bulldada.
For example,
extensive inventions,
and even the most recent investigation has revealed
that in my past life,
I simultaneously was Salvador Dali's mother
and the cartoon character Felix the Cat.
Concurrently, I have an alternate life
in the form of TV devangelist Dr. Gene Scott.
Subgenius souls are not single entities
with a beginning and an end,
but rather are like shreds of habifrop zipulops
tangled together in Jehovah One's universal joystick.
When a subgenius dies,
it's just like the oxidation of a segment of flesh,
a frap that's carried off into the atmosphere
for future fertilization.
But what is frap, anyway?
You've probably heard us mention it on the show before,
if you're a regular listener.
Or you may have read something about it in the book of the subgenius.
The fact is,
some of the secrets of frap are still a mystery,
even to the doctors of the air.
The chemistry of frap is complex.
Many organic compounds have been isolated by subdoctors.
These include tetrahydrocondylase,
tetrahydrocannabinol, carboxylic acid,
stereoisomers of tetrahydrocannabinol,
and cannabichromine.
Many frapistic acids are the precursors
of an oily, sludge-like mixture
of several isomers,
non-nitrogenous organic compounds
derived from terpenes.
But we don't want to get bogged down
in a sludgy swamp of technicalities.
The most important thing to remember about frap
is that it's just good, plain, clean fun.
And you can't have any,
unless you subscribe to the precepts.
Let's examine the ingredients of frap.
U.S. certified sludge,
water, sucrose, muscimol extract,
ibuprofen, muscazone,
dimethyltryptamine, serotonin,
natural sludge flavorings,
contains 1 40th of 1% gabofrap,
an artificial mood enhancer
which should be used only by those
who must restrict their intake of ordinary humor.
product may be habit-forming.
Do not operate heavy farm machinery
or use any of the following products.
Do not operate at speeds in excess of 70 miles per hour.
Do not attempt to explain yourself to others.
Maintain aspect of normal human.
Consult your sub-physician
or any doctor of the air if condition persists.
The American Mutant Tape Association
has rated the following presentation
Q.
The subject matter contained in this presentation
is considered questionable
and may be unsuitable
to be heard by deaf children
under the age of 17
unless accompanied by six cans of Crisco
and a proctology glove.
...and the big pink guitar strap...
...and the set of suspenders...
Okay, Berrien.
You dig the hole.
I'm taking over this show now.
Okay.
Well, what do I do with it?
Uh...
Who wants it?
Well, your show lesson is...
We're down here at the show cafeteria.
Well, the first thing I'm gonna do
is move it up to 9 o'clock at night.
Yeah, that's...
Everybody already heard it like that.
Wait a minute.
Come to think of it, I already have.
Okay, we're on the plane now to Dallas.
Fly us here every week just to do the show.
Oh, sure.
The nightmare starts again.
The pilots and the little PAs
all have the voices of a show.
I hate show.
Never alone with Frank Zappa.
You're never alone with Frank Zappa.
Maybe we could get Frank on The Atheist Hour
as a guest speaker.
They were totally empty!
Totally empty!
And their lives were really useless.
So what the f...?
They didn't have no sense of humor!
Puddleing up!
It takes me back, my friends.
Whoa!
I'm going to take this silica gel back a little bit.
There's some credits there.
Oh, well, you heard Dr. Howell there talking about frappy and chemicals.
The chemical nature there of it.
Oh, and the little ad there was by the good Reverend Nick Smith.
Yes, he had a whole tape full of those things.
They may be popping up again soon.
Nick Smith from Houston.
Oh, we heard Sister Chris.
Oh, boy.
Boy, that's been a long time.
Sister Chris used to run the hour of slack on WFMU
and do wonderful little rants in there.
And, of course, lots of KPFA, Dr. Howell, and puzzling evidence,
and the Hell Pope Huey occasionally.
Oh.
We'll be right back.
Pride welled in his breast.
He thought it unseemly for him to serve.
The devil and his band of followers who likewise suffered the sin of pride
were defeated in battle by the Lord and his host
and were banished to the outermost depths of hell,
never to know the presence of the Lord or look on heaven again.
I just can't wait until I get to be with the love child.
Sorry, Gary.
You've been judged.
X.L.F.
Better luck with me.
Go ye to the lake of fire.
Carry the broke friend.
The fire for me is the fire.
I'll smear it into the eternal lake.
I'll ride my chrome skateboard across that lake of fire.
Ivan, fight your leg on the way back.
Fire at the caller now.
The silence of the soul.
Sure is nice out here.
I hope the boat comes, though.
Fellini knew how to use silence.
But that horrible boatman with his grizzly hands.
Yeah, I know. Don't touch him.
A giant flaming oar.
Mr. Boatman.
Please, Mr. Boatman.
And look, you have to put a coin on his tongue and it's all black and icky.
Climb aboard, Dr. Howell Robbins.
No, no.
And be prepared to go past my dog, my three-headed dog's cerebrus.
Oh, he looks rather cerebral.
The triple-brained.
Monster which guards the gates.
The gateway.
Abandon hope all ye who enter here.
What's he reading from?
Yes, I am a way.
It's a B-movie script.
Into eternal fall.
I am the wage of forsaken people.
Gee, you're right, Virgil, said Dobbs.
It is getting hot in here.
Yeah, I've seen that movie, the Virgil movie.
Made beyond me and beyond time, my son.
Yeah.
Bob and Virgil went several levels.
Sure is nice out here in the ocean.
Further down into hell.
Suddenly, Bob, shifting his plate from one hand to the other,
pulled out from his voluminous ditty bag
a sop of cakes with wine and honey,
fermented, which he threw dexterously into the slavering three mouths
of the three-headed monster which guarded the cavernous entrance.
And in return, he was given a mighty blivet by Satan.
And a mighty belt shook the canine's bulging stomach.
This three-headed, uh, this three-headed thing
You're not going to get me to mention that.
That's enough of horrible horticultural facts from the world of mythology.
His horrible three foreskins quivering.
His gigantic, postulous, scabrous hide quivered unspeakably.
As with canine lust, he scraped his hindquarters across the floor,
howling and dribbling from all three heads simultaneously.
Huge ticks the size of small land crabs leaped from his fur-sparse...
...epigones.
Suddenly, the dog leaped across the vast expanse of hell and saddled up to Ivan's leg.
Yes, he was forced to be on the show hour after hour.
P-Dawg, why did you make me do that horrible thing?
Yes, the bells of hell go ting-a-ling-a-ling for you and not for me.
Take my glands away, cute P-Dawg.
They bang and bong and bing-a-ling-a-ling and ring eternally.
Yeah, they don't ever stop.
Yes, from Cerebus the P-Dawg, they all go for Ivan's leg.
Ow! Get that too!
Get those horrible...
...little poodles off of me!
I hate poodles!
I got the wrong attitude.
I should see the chap and get straight with Jesus.
Jesus Christ, eat sugar!
Damn you.
Are you hung up?
Out of sight, yeah.
Listen, um...
Are you hung up?
Ha ha ha!
No.
Is it?
Oh, I got you in the...
It was straight out of...
I just...
I can't understand.
Out of sight.
Out of sight, yeah.
Listen, um...
Are you hung up?
Are you bored?
Are you jaded?
Has our enthusiasm faded?
At the onset of my departure from the shop mansion last evening,
I noticed a set of soiled underpants lying in the courtyard.
It was then I knew, quite obviously, that the hideous ritual had not ended,
nay, nearly gained momentum.
I first caught wind of the whole ordeal at the annual Snail Pelt Poach Fest
whilst purchasing an antique pelt belt.
You wouldn't have believed it, Bubba,
that these giant slugs with turbans held me down and slimed me
while a band of renegade geriatric mimes took off my pants and stole my underwear.
Now, no one, even President Reagan, is safe from the horrid reality
of the Forced Underwear Application Act of 1710,
a secret ceremony started by the Illuminati
January 1, 1877,
and the
17th of January 6, 1710, at an old run-down temple known as the Infernal House of Royd reading, and used tiki medallions.
Yes, tiki medallions did exist even before Elvis, and date back to the birth of Christ on Easter Island.
Elvis was not in fact Jesus, but an incredible simulation.
We got a letter!
It's a letter from the Lord of the Rings.
It was in the mail the other day.
It came to the church, and this is for real, okay?
It's going to sound like a joke.
But, uh,
It was from the Citizens for Normalcy.
We have, we have talked,
Okay, now get this, get this.
We've talked about the Citizens for Normalcy before,
and we thought it was a joke we had made up.
Now it turns out, it turns out, that in San Francisco,
we had a terrible joke.
So this organization actually has been formed and does exist.
And it may be, that, that subgenius is much more well known in San Francisco than it is here.
As you can sort of imagine.
And their, let's see, their little logo here says,
Citizens for Normalcy, freedom for minds means freedom from minds.
Which, you know, is more like, heck, not either way.
I think I am, therefore I am, I think.
Yeah, it says, here it is.
There you go.
Uh, dear Reverend Stang,
your organization has recently come to our attention through the complaint of a Mrs. Donald Baumgart,
a member of Citizens for Normalcy for over ten years in good standing.
It seems Mrs. Baumgart's daughter attended classes at the University of California, Berkeley,
and several months ago was handed a Xerox flyer concerning your, quote,
church of the subgenius, unquote.
Brenda Baumgart, up to that time, had been a good student with a 4.0 grade average.
She was in the same class as you.
.
. .
Dr. .
.
there. Mrs. Baumgart has not seen or heard from her daughter now since that dreadful Christmas day.
Repeated attempts to contact her have been met with obscene threats of violence for, quote,
pardon me, anyone who with Bob. They didn't do it. They used pretty little stars there. But that's
apparently what puzzling evidence says in the words of the person who answers the door of the,
quote, Oakland Temple, unquote. We have contacted the Oakland police about this situation in no
avail and we suspect that even they might well be under your sway. Word that it were so, my friends,
word that it were so. Mr. Stang, Mr. Stang, I wish to tell you that Citizens for Normalcy is a
national organization with a budget of $10 million.
a proud history of combating anti-Christian hate groups and secular humanistic enemies.
They got us all wrong.
Among our tens of thousands of members, we list two former presidents,
Supreme Court justices, senators, and all this stuff,
and various military and intelligence branches.
We are not intimidated by your cheap threats, they say.
Since our reports discovered that Brenda has dyed her hair pink
and now only refers to herself as Bob Monk 244XY.
They go on to say that they're going to uproot all branches of the foul, unclean church
and all it stands for in our base deed shall not go unpunished.
Oh, that's worse.
We bear children as hell-bound as ourselves who also go into...
The corruption of clean Christian youth of our great land will end.
We will crush you in our mighty hand like an old beer can.
Bob is an old beer can.
Crush him!
You can crush him, but you can...
But he's an ever...
But you can recycle him!
That's right, ever recyclable.
But you don't get as much each time.
It's a joke to mock our only Lord God and defile the U.S. postal system.
It's pretty sad, isn't it?
Or maybe you're too busy counting the profits to notice.
Well, you're...
You're Nazi-like rallies during financial district lunch hours
only offend and repel honest people.
All right.
Your book of the subgenius never made...
It made it to the bestseller list.
Did it?
Well, it never will.
We can help us.
This was signed Stephanie Rechtel.
Oh, president.
Oh, oh, and the last thing.
The last thing here.
We're starting a full media expose.
And they do that, actually.
As well as on the Subgenius Foundation,
as well as a sick radio station, KNON, and KPFA in Berkeley.
Oh, y'all are from Berkeley?
Yay!
Jeez, man.
We will make you regret licking that first stamp.
We've also introduced and will fully back Senate Bill 46277,
which calls for you and your members to be shipped to the federal penal colonies
on Venus, our beautiful sister planet.
And at that point, dear friends, the tape ends and suddenly cuts to
a recording of the...
of the cops.
Who came to investigate the bomb threat.
It's a very bad recording of myself and Will of Dobbs talking to the cop about the bomb threat.
And, uh, but I don't want to play that to you because it's just too ugly sounding.
We'll, uh, we'll give credit.
Yes.
Um, oh, that, uh, Citizens for Normalcy letter.
It was actually written by St.
Palmer Vreves.
Yes, it was the Lies Corporation.
I think that recording is from a science fiction convention here in Dallas, uh, in the, uh, late eighties.
Uh, we heard the, uh, underwear ad.
Got beautiful piece there by Nick Smith, uh, of Houston.
Uh, some, um, uh, collage material prior to that.
It...
Uh...
By, uh, the Hell Pope Huey, formerly of Houston.
Uh, and of course, uh, Dr. Howell, Puzzling Evidence, KPFA stuff talking about the boatman of hell and, uh, Cerebrus and so forth.
And, uh, um, well, while I'm on oldies, I might as well just continue playing this old work tape.
There's, it's marked on the back of the tape.
After the bomb, I think apparently I, I used this, um, it was the only tape I had.
I had with me and I used it to record us reporting to the cop.
It's not that interesting.
But what follows it is labeled Ear of Bob Safeties, which means it's, uh, kind of a safety master of the, some of the songs that are on the Ear of Bob, uh, subgenius music tape.
Which, you know, I probably haven't played that stuff in, why, like, nigh on to years here on this show.
So, something about...
Some of it.
So, well, let's just see what's in there.
I know the first one up is by the good Reverend Bleepo Abernathy.
Uh, thank y'all.
Ear to Bob.
Bob.
Bob is a rock.
And Bob is a tree.
Bob.
Bob is a bear.
And Bob is a bee.
Bob.
Bob is truth.
And Bob is lies.
Bob.
Bob is cakes.
And fruits.
And pies.
Bob's my hassle.
Bob's my wash.
Bob's my sandwich.
Bob's my crunch.
Bob's my toothpick.
Bob's my brain.
Bob's my ugly.
Y'all will stain.
Bob's my cactus.
Bob's an itch.
Bob is take off every stitch.
Bob's my master.
Bob's my slave.
Bob will rob me.
Bob will save.
Bob's my toaster.
Bob's my fridge.
Bob's my little sister.
Bob will cost you.
Bob is free.
Bob's a rock.
Bob's a tree.
In short.
Bob is the man.
Bob .
Who used your leg as a frying pan.
Bob, Bob.
If your mind is a jar.
You can pour it out of a sink.
In a subgenius church.
This is a missing link.
Damn it.
Well, I went on down to my girlfriend's shack
To see how they did hang
When I got there, her cupboard was bare
I couldn't ignite a thing
There was no shard, no bone, no trig
I brought my comic book collection
Was about this big, yeah
Well, frop without slack is like slack without frop
But where the hell else am I going to cop?
I found my dog food collection about five o'clock
But all that food was stale
I thought I'd call that rip-off schmuck
But I forgot he was in jail
Ended up killing a porcupine
Just to see how he was doing
If I could smoke his rhyme
Oh, frop without slack is like slack without frop
But where the hell else am I going to cop?
Yeah, frop without slack is like slack without frop
I don't know what I am going to do
I just know that this here trip ain't through
Oh, frop without slack is like slack without frop
But where the hell else am I going to cop?
Yes, but where the hell else am I going to cop?
I know, I know that this is just a nap
Once again, as usual, I admit that this is really a alt sim
I'm getting this too long
Oh, the fuck's with you?
Oh, snap out of it
Get out now
frop without slal
Race is, man, rap
They feel like a
No, they don't
Okay, did you learn that?
I should get my own
basic
Bob.
Bob is sex.
Who told you that?
Bob.
Bob is sex.
Bob is...
Bob.
Bob is sex.
Bob is...
Bob.
Bob is sex.
7 am. July 5th, 1998.
1998. What will it be like?
X-Games!
And he gave me some rock.
I can handle reality now that Bob made a man out of me.
We now know that LSD is the most mysterious and powerful substance ever invented in any laboratory.
It goes into the body of the doctor.
Don't know.
I left out a statement.
I want to be under the table.
So in an effort to be regular at party, my darling Diane tried LSD.
An unknown to me, this poor, tortured girl had been suffering through terrible flashbacks.
We know that LSD is the most mysterious and powerful substance ever invented in any laboratory.
It goes into the body of the doctor.
We will keep recurring Bob's fans for as long as two years until sometimes people are drilled out of their minds by what occurs.
But it never happened to me.
He's Bob.
Bob don't ever change.
Always will be Bob.
His face is the one big assembly of dots that shine in the dark.
His grin is the one that looks friendly, but so does the grin of a shark.
He's Bob.
Bob don't ever change.
Always will be Bob.
His hair is the one.
His lips the highlight.
That shines on the pompadour.
That glimmers and gleams in the twilight.
It's clear he knows what it's for.
He's Bob.
Bob don't ever change.
Always will be Bob.
His pipe is the one with the doddle.
That rains on the roofs like fire.
His neck is the wood.
the one with the waddle in flaming folks desire he's bob bob don't ever change he's bob always
will be bob
pinker my bob than thee pinker than thee though pink boys are everywhere
pinker than me pinker my bob than thee
pinker
my bob than thee pinker my bob than thee pinker than thee
pinker than me monier de la mio
panther ran for pá
Space
Wikipedia
On
on
The
le
guitar solo
solo
On Pharaoh's commission, the slaves bled
Used blocks of granite, they were stuck in the mud
Buried away, deep in his tomb
The money lies like a cocoon
Pyramid power is in my soul
Pyramid power, it makes me whole
I heard the mention of the rising star
Was a scientific and it worked for all
Did you really think that it had your luck
Or was it a gimmick
Just for a moment
Pyramid power is in my soul
Pyramid power, it makes me whole
Perfect health, what more can I ask
Extreme guidance throughout the past
Everything to me falls in line
With answering questions
And more questions
Pyramid power, it makes me whole
Pyramid power, Colour ab actors
In my mind I only got one part
My heart is full of eş
Art is a piece of a pension
And in that I shed so little
Have you ever photographed
What pictures義
What people used to turn to
?
.
That's Box 140306 in Dallas, Texas 75214.