This is Hour of Slack something.
We are about to leave on a very long trip.
We've just packed the car, and the timing is just horrible
because I have a terrible cold.
So we'll be having the adventure of a lifetime,
or rather embarking on another adventure of this lifetime.
Sick as a dog.
A dog, I say!
Like a dirty dog.
A low-down dog.
It's funny because I haven't had a cold in, I mean, like five years.
This is the first time I've been sick in that long,
and I'd have to get sick just on the day of packing and leaving,
which in the case of Subgenius Foundation,
packing is pretty complicated
because I have to take the entire mail-order business on the road
and I have to get it done.
All the computers, all the data, all the manufacturing equipment,
CDs, paper, boxes, pens, membership packs, everything, books,
takes up the whole back of the I-van.
And then the whole front is taken up with survival goods and crap.
Christmas presents.
Christmas presents, yes.
X is less than S-M-S presents.
Yes, this is actually December 2nd.
I'm hoping to make it to Texas,
Stangville, Stang Ranch, by December 16th.
This may be the last time you hear from us without
engine noise or puking.
You're normally such a slacker.
It's the first time you've heard of me.
Are all four of you guys in here?
Is Phil in there?
He just, yeah, yeah.
Can we?
Doing with four?
Yeah, all four.
Okay.
What are we doing?
How do we?
This is...
Oh, yeah.
How about this is Phil, Phil, Pete, and Dave of the Firesign Theater.
This is Phil.
Phil.
Let's take it again.
Oh, Pete and Dave.
Okay, there we go, yeah.
All right, you over here?
You just shut up.
This is Phil.
Phil.
Pete.
And Dave of the Firesign Theater.
And we're listening to The Hour of Slack.
Hack, hack, hack, hack.
Because we're subgeniuses and we're slacking off.
And we've just...
Decided not to leave today because I'm just too sick.
I mean with illness, not the way you're used to.
We're...
We decided that rather than drive into West Virginia on a Friday night,
going over twisty, twisty, twisty, turny hills
full of West Virginian drunks,
at 11 at night wasn't a good idea.
Instead, we're going to begin our vacation here at home by slacking off.
It seems to be a brainwashing facility of some type.
Wherever there's a brainwashing cult,
there's always a power-hungry leader behind it all.
Hurry home early.
Hurry on home.
Boom, boom, and scene is fighting.
Bobby, Bobby, Bobby.
Congratulations, Bob. You just hired me.
I live here, Bob.
I'm not looking for work anyway, Bob.
Good night, Bob.
I don't need any help from that damn Bob.
He offered me a job.
How would you guys support yourselves?
Haven't you ever heard of Bobby?
The best thing you can do is just lay on your back,
and you're going to bob around,
fairly high up in it.
I want full newspaper coverage.
I want magazine stories.
I want books.
I want films.
I want TV.
I want radio.
I want us on the air 24 hours a day.
This is our moment.
And a billion people around this planet
will watch it,
hear it,
and read about it
from the
Self Genius Hour of Swag.
There's no news.
Like bad news.
Bob News, everyone.
The Large did it.
And with this episode,
we begin a series weaving
the, uh,
oh, regular, quote-unquote,
hour of slack material
with on-the-road reports
from the 2010-11
subgenius family vacation
working and wonking
road trip,
which had a rough beginning and end,
but a great middle.
But first,
from Lemur,
this.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm in an alleged plot
to murder a Swedish cartoonist
for drawing a cartoon of tax breaks
for individuals and businesses
that expired in 2009.
A cartoonist would be eligible
to receive benefits
through the end of the year.
On Wall Street,
26, 10, 578,
11, 2343.
Iraqi election officials say
you're listening to PR News,
which is affiliated with
Northern Ireland's legislative
assembly.
The Northern Ireland assembly
was perhaps noisier
despite personal lobbying
by George W. Clinton,
88 to 17.
After a historic vote,
the White House is condemning
PR News.
The wonders of
subgenius family vacation.
We postponed our trip
for a day because
I was so sick,
I couldn't do anything but cough
and then groan in pain
because the coughs
were so ravaging on my throat
that my throat became
a bloody sore,
one might say.
His body was all coughing
and wracked with pain.
Yeah, so I laid in bed
all night long,
waiting for the next cough,
basically,
and a hawking spewed him down
into a little
trash can next to me.
I missed a few times
as I discovered in the morning
there was this,
like, collection of
yellow, green, brown
snot on my bed.
Now we're on our way
to Potter and Petal Nostrils
place in West Virginia.
We'll still end up driving
through twisty-turny
West Virginia hillbilly roads.
I still feel like crap,
but before I felt like,
well, what's worse than crap?
I guess I only feel like pee,
now.
I feel like pee,
but it's better than feeling like crap,
and it's still gonna be
somewhat dangerous,
but what the heck.
Hear how much better it is?
Uh-huh.
Sounds great.
It's actually a little bit
more productive now.
Comparatively.
And I've got a,
soon I'll have an empty cup
next to me to put my spew to me.
Ew!
I'll have a collection.
Hello, you.
You're on the air.
Oh, Dr. Sinister.
Ah, Reverend Stang.
How's your journey going?
Oh, it's fabulous.
I have been spreading
the Cleveland cold,
or the Clevelandia flu,
as the subgeniuses are calling it,
all the way from Ohio to Texas.
Everybody that we stayed with,
which was quite a few
of the better-known subgeniuses,
all got sick.
It affects every person,
completely differently.
For instance, I got it in my lungs
and coughed like a dinosaur
all night long, every night,
for a week and a half.
Had to sleep sitting up
like the elephant man.
Princess Wee, it caused her
to have a high-pitched squeal
in her right ear.
Impacted stuff.
That happened to me,
actually, recently.
The ear thing.
Well, we went to a party
in Madison, Ohio, just, you know,
it was at Thanksgiving,
and the host of the party
had it then.
Several other people that we know
got it afterwards.
One of them hallucinated,
got a high fever and hallucinated.
Those are the best kind of hallucinations,
the fever-induced ones.
I had a couple of nights of fever,
and it caused me not exactly fever dreams.
It was more like a completely random surrealist,
or more like a Dadaist slideshow,
because there wasn't anything
interesting or fun in it.
It wasn't pornography.
It wasn't memories.
It was just, you know,
an image of an ironing board,
an image of a sink,
an image of a cup.
You know, just like really stupid
hallucinations.
I'm over it now,
and I'm hoping to pick up
a new stomach virus
from my sister-in-law here.
Oh, that's great.
I'm going to get it west.
But, yeah, they're calling me
Typhoid Ivan now,
or Patient Zero.
There you go.
Or Captain Trips,
as I prefer.
Stain County, Texas.
Come for the lungful of phlegm.
Stay for the fever-induced hallucinations.
Well, we're about to leave
Potter and Petal Nostrils Place
in West Virginia.
Had a good night's sleep
and got fed wonderfully.
Mm-hmm.
And I'm still sick.
Pure slack was served.
Well, and that medicine,
Jane Hash's killer death medicine,
the potion.
Keeps us alive.
Yeah, it was pretty strong stuff.
It's like onion, horseradish,
ginger, hot pepper, garlic.
And cider vinegar.
All stewed together.
And garlic and garlic.
Pure raid.
Nothing cooked.
Yeah, I was hoping it would...
Raw.
I was hoping it would have instant effects,
but it didn't.
We can give you another dose.
It's a potion, best sir.
Yeah.
It's got food on your stomach.
Anyway, we have to leave
and try to make it to...
Find your way out of America's own third world.
You must find your way out of
America's own third world.
Oh, but we have a GPS.
That's a first world machine.
It'll tell us everything.
That's our GPS, Jack.
Jack sometimes doesn't know shit.
Because he will often direct us
in just the opposite way
that our friends direct us.
And I'm beginning to suspect
that Jack was programmed
by redneck cannibals.
To take you ever further
into redneck cannibal land.
You know, it's like technically,
yeah, this might be a quicker way
as the crow flies,
but we're not crows.
And its natural tendency
is to put you on the interstates,
but sometimes we want to take
the scenic routes,
and we disobey Jack,
and he has to recalculate.
Sometimes he's cooperative,
and other times what he says just...
doesn't make sense.
Potter said to go into Charleston
to get on 60,
but Jack was going to send us
into redneck cannibal territory
first to get on 60.
And I just don't trust Jack that much.
No, he's twisted.
I think you're right.
I think he was programmed
by some redneck...
Cannibals.
Cannibals, yeah.
Yeah.
Chainsaw Massacre folks.
West Virginia Chainsaw Massacre.
Yeah.
You sure have a pretty mouth, boy.
Why don't you just drop them panties?
I want you to pray,
and you better pray good.
It might be worth it in terms of
fun dilapos to photograph.
Or lappies.
We've shortened it now to lappies.
On our first trip,
we were always looking for
dilapidated buildings,
which got pretty quickly shortened to dilapos.
But now we're just basically going,
oh, that was a good lappy.
I think I got a picture of it.
The best is yet to come.
Are you driving on those vibrating wheels?
We did.
Yeah.
We're going to the
The vibrato stress.
Yeah, it drives me nut.
But the point is that we're free here,
free to bendy about the most offensive,
concept. We had Nazis
on our stage belching
forth hatred and
we've had terrible fights
in our midst with
radios being smashed,
crockery fractured,
and tears and
departures of indignant
subgenie and subgeniettes in a huff.
So sad.
As the fatal hour
grows closer,
so will not the tensions
until finally
like a boil giving
way to erupt in
turbulent matter, the
tensions will resolve themselves
one way or the other. That's why we
need that big hygienic
gleaming to come down
and save us from our
human predicament.
We're
still trying to get those
exists to pay attention
to our navigational signal
and when they
do,
we'll get this little matter of the landing
fixed.
And that's my ruin.
So we're traveling along,
jogging along the ancient roads
of subgenius doctrine.
It's like a dream.
I wish I'd brought more bob heads.
Somebody oil my wheelchair.
I wish I'd brought about a half a dozen bob heads.
There's old man Stang,
a victim of senile dementia.
Cranky, liable as anything to whack you with your
special steel tipped, gold bob headed cane.
I know Bob Dobbs for what he was.
I know subgeniuses for what they were.
What's that old timer?
Speak into the rectifier here for our listening audience.
While crossing the plains, my family was rubbed out
by a tribe of wild subgeniuses.
They were massagers, masseurs?
I was raised among them.
At least they had that effect.
I learned their ways.
Hmm, their ways, eh?
Later I became a wild subgenius.
I was a wildlife photographer and I became the Jane Goodall of the pagans.
They would accept me among them and I was able to photograph their strange rituals.
That's pretty...
They's just like monkeys to you.
Well, I...
No, don't you confuse chimpanzees with monkeys and pagans.
Absolutely.
They're different.
They's just like chimps to you.
They are quite different, the monkeys and pagans, and especially chimps.
Well, chimps and pagans are quite similar.
They make good girlfriends and boyfriends for subgeniuses.
I had a chimp.
But what about that story?
He was a pagan chimp.
That story that Russian scientists tried to create a hybrid of chimpanzee and human as
a perfect soldier for the scientific socialist state.
That explains a lot.
I was reading that same article in Playboy at Pappy's house.
It's true.
There was a history article.
They brought him to the hospital.
And the Russians really did try to create a hybrid.
And it's not entirely clear that they didn't.
I know.
That's the terrifying thing.
They...
They're...
You can't know for sure that they did, but there's also no evidence that they did not.
Hello.
You're on the air, in a manner of speaking.
Are you there?
Dierks.
We're about to be in Dierks.
We're going to be in Dierks.
Amen.
Dierks.
My leg hurts, but I'm fine now.
I remember Dierks.
Dierks.
Dierks has a cafe in it!
Dierks has a gas station.
Dierks has a gas station!
Dierks.
We're going to be in Dierks in a second!
Dierks!
Dierks
The first assembly of God is in Dierks
There's the Church of Christ
I remember this
I remember it's up in that hill
It don't look like a church
It looks like a junkyard
It's beautiful
It's the Lord's
It's where the Lord lives
There's top of the hill
Dierks Drive-In
Dierks is my favorite town
The Forestry Commission Headquarters is there too
Here in Howard County
Hello my friends in Dierks
I'm happy to see all you folks in Dierks
Oh there's a good lappy
I'm lappy happy
I like them to lappos
Outlaw Quick Clean
Outlaw Quick Clean is the best
Here's the Mayor's House
Oh
Sorry it closed
Down here at the end of the street
There's the place we stop in
To see my girlfriend
Your girlfriend?
Yeah
Don't you remember my girlfriend from Dierks?
No
My girl in Dierks
There's Dierks Pharmacy
Farm Bureau
Mattress
Trans Clothing Boutique
What's gone wrong with you?
What's going on with Dierks?
Ravens Flower and Gifts
They have beautiful things in there
Dierks is so beautiful
Dierks is my favorite town
This is it
That's got the whole super stop
Am I supposed to stop there?
Well it is Dierks
And it is the super stop
But that's okay
We can find a Cheeboogie
Maybe there'll be a Cheeboogie there
Cheeboogie here in Dierks
They modernized quite a bit
Dierks has grown up
Dierks is a big city now
There's the prayer center
It's not very big
God can hear tiny prayers
You did see that Newt Gingrich
Wants to have a giant lunar city
Constructed by the end of his second term
In office
And it'll be the 51st state
Man that sounds cool
Yeah no other candidate
Has announced that
That gets my vote
For that one thing
I don't care about anything else
Herman Cain's Plan 9 from Outer Space
That was a good one too
So they have Moonbase Zero
Dimension 4
Moonbase Zero with Commander Newt
At the head of
Do you think they'll have like shuttles
That go to the moon and we can go up there
And check it out
First
The guy's got to get elected
This is your radio operator
Doug Smith
We'll bring you a piece of that green cheese
For sure
We're recording
I'm gonna vote for Newt
Just because
Everything's going fine
If he gets
If he does
I just thought I'd try the
The phone thing
Yeah try the phone again
Anybody there?
Hello?
Is anyone there?
Is anybody out there?
I heard somebody
I don't hear anyone the way I'm supposed to
But now I pull it near
Near my hate
I'm now speaking to you
I'm speaking to Pete Goldie
But he can't be heard
Over the equipment
Because of a strange
Electrical disturbance
Try holding the
But as you know
We're doing the
Can we be heard over the equipment?
Subjects All Stars show here
And I hope you're enjoying it
Up to now
Hold Pete up to the mic
And see if we can hear
A tinny little Pete voice
Pete?
Yeah he could turn on his speakerphone
Leslie suggested
So I can hear him
Alright
It's like a ghost
It's just too
He's got a deal working with
Newt and his moon colony
I'm gonna see if I can amplify
Yeah he sounds like he's coming from
Simple thing
I'll just keep talking about
My future on the moon
Which I cannot wait
To join the other moon colonists
And live in the moon
That's right
I wanna vote for Newt too
It'll be a wonderful time in the moon
And the best part about
Yes but
We will finally have the chance
To beat the moon people
It'll be great
Once and for all
Thanks to Newt
Thanks to someone with foresight
It's going to be a wonderful time
Thanks to near Kingridge
Me and all the other supporters
Of Space Commander Newt Kingridge
But he has to be elected first
And also Neil deGrasse Tyson
Was saying he was off base
So to speak
Bring back Dr. Howe
Do you think he'll really keep
That campaign promise though
About making the moon base?
Absolutely
Newt Kingridge is the man of his word
We have never seen him
Who's backed down
On anything he's ever said
He is the man who will take us
To the moon
And defeat those moon people
Well you know Dr. Goldie
The Ask Dr. Howe show
Doesn't give political endorsements
To potential candidates
I know he's never backed down
On two marriages
We're not asking for your endorsement
We're just asking for your acquiescence
To the overpowering vision
Of this moon man
Well I brought him here
To put it up didn't I?
I thought it was worth mentioning
Didn't I?
So
It is important
And thank you for bringing it
To our attention
That's right
Why's that?
Yes
Now remember folks
You can be an atheist
And a subgenius
Right?
Because you can be alone
With Bob
And Bob's not necessarily
Your god anyway
I'm returning
And thank you so much
Pete Goldie
I mean I don't want to
Worship him like a god
That's okay
When they get to the moon
They're going to find
A British flag there
Put there in the year
Of our lord 1899
You can turn your mic down now
Dr. Howe
I will
And I'm terribly sorry
I had it turned completely up
Because of that
That's why I kept saying
Stay away
You need to stand back
Yes
It was the
The Pete Goldie
I was about to slug you
Well I'm glad that we
Now you can turn it up
Before then
I think you need to be louder
I sometimes
Think of
Daffodils
Hollyhocks
I'm not a control freak
Tiny
Juttering
Leprechauns
Weeping over them
We're going to get some food man
Yes you need to satisfy
The inner man
To get some beef
That will stick to your ribs
Maybe beef ribs
So
I
A bean burrito would work
Bean burrito
Ah well
They have those
A plenty
I like them
Because they bark back later
I want to
When I go back
We're going to go through
Gilroy
And try the garlic ice cream
It's an unfashionable belief
In the atheist community
But truth
Just needs to be stated
It doesn't have to be hyped
I know
I do a lot of hyping of atheism
But remember what Bob Dobbs said
I'm not a fan of atheism
I don't practice what I preach
Because I'm not the kind of person
I'm preaching to
There is no God
And that's a simple truth
If every trace of any single religion
Were wiped out
And nothing were passed on
It would never be created
Exactly that way again
There might be some other nonsense
In its place
But not that exact nonsense
If all of science were wiped out
It would still be true
And someone would find a way
To figure it all out again
Reverend Penn Gillette's
Audio book
Of his autobiographical musings
Called God Know
Quoting Bob
That book is hilarious
And brilliant by the way
At least the audio book is
And now a clip
From WCSB Cleveland's
Radio Synesthesia
Called Into from California
By Philodrum and Puzzling Evidence
Yours truly
And the buzz of Lonesome Cowboy Dave
I'm experiencing a funny sort of an echo
Philo's on the other side of the closet from me
And yet when he speaks
I hear him on the phone
About half a second later
You're like doing the Groucho and Zeppo
Like mirror routine
That's like talking to people
That was a classic man
On their way to the moon
I used to have
I used to have that movie
It was a duck soup
That was what it was in right?
Yes
I used to have that
A VHS tape of that movie
And I wish I did
It takes a long time to get
To the other side of the closet
Reverend Stang
The big closet
I've personally had nightmares
There are really big scary closets
In this place
Yeah
Each closet has another sub-closet
Behind it
It's like the closet
That Dr. Stanger Gary or something
Each one is inhabited by this tiny little creature
That sings or something
Or maybe that's a lady
In the radio
Or a radiator or something
But you know what I mean
The Akashic Records
Kind of
A little tiny singing lady
No bigger than a pipsqueak
Yep
As new as
Large as
Little radiator twins
That bring Mothra
Only in my version
Oh yeah
David Lynch
I love those ladies
Mothra
Tinkerbell
For instance
I like that
Tinkerbell is a good example
I don't believe in fairies
I just killed three of them
You just killed?
I just killed three
It's like shooting fish in a barrel
I can't believe how
I am
Hey man
I am Dr. Sinister
Okay
Right
You know
You are a cruel and evil type of guy
And so you
You feel
You're compunction to go around
Killing millions of fairies
Just by disallowing their existence
In your
You know
I'm trying to remember this
I had this conversation
The other day
Talking about some
Some you know
Pen and paper role playing game
And I'm trying to remember
Which one it was
There was
There was some kind of game
In which like
People would use magic
But like
You could have like
A skepticism skill
Or something like that
And like
If you scored high enough
On this role
To disbelieve
Then you could nullify
Someone else's magic
Did that actually happen or not?
I can't remember
If that was a particular game
It was a game
A role game
I want to say
It was in some
It was in some game
I played once
But I don't remember
Real life
I don't
I don't believe
Then all the religions
Would go away
And God would get some rest
For a change
Without all that whining
And whimpering
People begging for stuff
All the time
Really?
Oh my
I concurred with that
Naturally
I just love it
How like
Athletes
Become like
Really super religious
So they're like
They thank God
For their victory
Yeah
Because
They proclaim all their deity
And so forth
And give everybody
Athletes
Feats
The nice deity
Did help them
They did
See if they just
Let Jesus wash them
They wouldn't have that problem
That's right
If the Lord would sit down
For a little while
And have a little
Footy wash
Cheeky smooch
And everything would be
All about
Logos
Placebo
Fire
To smoke
Their enemies
Behind them
Aaron
David
Or
Somebody
Moab
Or
Jason
The Argonauts
The Shepherds
Something like that
Yeah
That's all I could understand
Was something about Moab
Being you know
While he's a
I may have gotten
Some of the details
Confused
But it's something like that
Pretty close anyway
You could you know
Delete the first few sentences
And invert the other part
But then
It wouldn't make any more sense
Than it did
Yeah
It wouldn't make any more sense
Than it does now
That's right
Well that's for sure
Whoever said it had to make sense
Yeah
It's a
You don't use your mind
To think about your religion
That's wrecked it all up
You're trying to make
You're trying to make sense of it
What's the point of having a religion
It doesn't make no sense
That's why it's a religion
I think your brain's exposed
Saving your skull
With those
Spoons again
I'll
Do something about that
You can't taste your tongue
You can't smell it
Yes you can actually
I mean what's a booger gonna smell like
But
Actually
What does a booger smell like
Actually you know what
I'm going to say that I do know
What my tongue tastes like
And I
Do know what a booger smells like
What does a booger smell like
Are you eating a booger
It's actually not very pleasant
Is it all your bodily parts
Or the essence and juices
It's got kind of a mucusy smell too
I think you know what a booger smells like
But this could be subject to debate
I knew of people in the school
When I was very young
They had the old radiators in them
The old buildings
And if you put your booger
On the radiators
It would make this really rank smell
That would get you thrown out of class
As a troublemaker
And that's true
It would get you high though
That's the question
That's
See that was the secret to my childhood
You know it's like
I tried to get into as much trouble as I could
While I was still young enough
To get away with it
And still be able to levitate too
At the same time
Cause you know
When they start shooting at you
I was never able to levitate
You can't embezzle
Fifty million dollars
When you're like
You know in fourth grade
Everybody got pissed
Guess now you better not do that again
You do it when it's grown up
Oh
All of a sudden
It's federal offense
Seriously trying to take
All the fun out of life
I think Stan is speaking directly
To a very important issue
We should all be trying
To get children
Who's yodeling?
A pickle
The gherkins
I think it's a
Lonesome pickle
That's my yodeling pickle
Don't be
Don't be jerking us you gherkin
No it's the jerking
It's the only thing I could
It's an intelligent pickle
They grow them out here
And it's the only thing
We can teach it is one thing
And I taught this one to yodel
Yodeling
Huh
Now that
That to me sounds like a
You know what
This is
I had to think for a minute
What cruel game was he playing?
WCSB Cleveland
That's correct
Now look inside Mr. Danger
What do you see?
That's easy
That's a good one
A pickle
Very good
Now I think you're ready for this
New and improved pickle
Yep
That's how it works
See that sounds like
Rocky Rococo
Doing the old
Seven-five on the jive hive
Is that what's up
With down in the land
Of Piccolo Pocono, Daddy?
That's where all of the
Inspiration comes from
The Fireside Theater
And the committee
And the association
And
Nick
Oh Nick
I just noticed
You were
In the address
And a pair of
Which gave birth to
Second City
Saturday Night Live
Which gave birth to
Dierks
What is Dierks?
Dierks is in our past now
Well at least we still got
Dequeen to go
King and Dequeen isn't it?
King is near Dequeen
But we don't go through King
No
Dierks is a city of beauty
And culture
Center of culture in
Western Arkansas
I did not have sex with that woman
He came to Arkansas and his voice turned into
William Jefferson Clinton
Bill Clinton even
My brain doesn't work anymore
The spirit of William Jefferson Clinton took over
And I did not have sex with that woman
I jacked off on her face
And got a little bit of a blow job
A couple of times
And I just said
I came once
I did not have sex with her
Sex is when you put your dick in their pussy
Blow job isn't sex
No I didn't have sex with them unless you count blow jobs
Stumpy don't mind
Stumpy don't care
Stumpy doesn't mind
Uncle I have a big revenge on Edward
Fjas
ASMR
on my right ear, and I hear it later in time B in my left ear.
He's freaking him out.
Mental vertigo.
This has been a season of time control.
Right.
It's not synesthesia.
With that kind of...
Wait, it is synesthesia.
It is synesthesia.
I think they're trying to steal the contents of your mind, Dang.
That's what's going on.
We just emptied them out.
You can't steal what ain't there.
We're going to start to scale our reproduction.
Right, yeah.
I was going to say.
I don't think we have a lot of population.
This mind isn't everything, isn't it?
Hey, let's steal this empty box.
Hey, who's kissing the donkey back there in the background?
Stand up or be fleshed out.
I can see you.
I know who you are.
Is somebody imitating me, you know, copulating with a burrito or something?
Really?
That's an automatic noise that comes out of...
Speaking of which.
We've got to pause to remind everyone.
This portions of the following broadcast will be objectionable to some members of the audience,
which is why we advise listener discretion.
The views and opinions expressed on this program are not necessarily those of WCSB or Cleveland
State University.
And let's continue.
Not necessarily.
I like that.
Or any other station that might get played on later.
You know what I heard?
I heard an awesome...
I heard an awesome, awesome story yesterday from our general manager.
So those of us who live here in Cleveland and listen to this podcast, we're going to
the station locally over the good old fashioned FM airwaves, are probably familiar with
this situation where this Canadian Christian station kind of bleeds in on us sometimes
due to an atmosphere condition.
Apparently...
Apparently it works both ways.
Oh, very good.
And apparently there was a lot of interference from us on that Canadian Christian station's
broadcast during a program called...
During a program called The Satanic Rites of the Day Man Lost.
Yay!
Which airs every Thursday night from 9 to 11.
Wow.
How could it get better than that?
Documentary radio work.
I mean, that's...
And we apparently...
Apparently some listeners from that station actually contacted us and said...
Man, what is up with those screams?
I find that kind of obnoxious.
They're dirty haxters.
That's phylogrammins being obnoxious.
How could you do that to a bunch of innocent Ontario natives sitting there thinking of
the Lord Jesus X Cripes in the middle of the night?
Their basement or some other near place.
How could you do it?
And then they get to hear the song Slut Cutter.
Did they play the song Slut Cutter during...
I don't know.
I know...
I know Hughes plays that quite a bit.
Right now you're in the subgenius funhouse.
Yeah, at least...
Yeah, it's a shame that it didn't bleed over during one of WCSB's religious shows.
Like Hour of Slack.
Right.
Or...
Atheist shows like Synesthesia.
Oh, I'm not just an atheist show.
That's just part of my perspective.
You're a Christ killer.
A Buddha killer.
You'd even kill a mere philosophy if you could get your hands on it.
A mere philosophy?
Even a mere philosophy?
All philosophy is bunk.
The younger it is, the happier he'd be to kill it.
If it's a baby philosophy, all the better.
A helpless baby religion.
I suppose you hate the Mormons.
Oh, I don't hate anybody.
I hate the Mormons only part of the time.
I'm not one of those eloquent incestue rarities that you hear in the background.
I love the Mormons because LDS is almost like LSD.
It is like LSD.
If you believe Joseph Smith saw the future and the past at one time, it could...
That's my great-granduncle, by the way.
That's right.
Well, did you know that the Mormon church has much...
Not only in New York State and out there in Utah, but right here in Cleveland, Ohio.
Kirtland, Ohio.
Did you know of the Kirtland Temple, Rob?
I have not.
And, yeah, I have not actually been to the temple, but I'm aware of its existence.
There was a...
One of the earliest Mormon settlements was in Kirtland.
Is it still an operating Mormon spiritual gas station?
Yes, and it...
Well, I don't know.
I think it's more of a museum now, but it's very brightly...
It's painted.
It looks rather gaudy.
It's a spiritual gas station.
Are you calling it a...
Are you saying that the Mormon church is full of gas?
Is that what you're saying?
No, you're saying you can...
Any old church is full of gas.
You can just pull in there and fill up.
No, not yet.
You just plunk over one of the pews, and they stick it right up where the sun...
You know?
Yeah, the sun won't shine.
And you just walk away and have a grand old time.
Well, they don't say that...
At least that's the way it used to be.
That's the thing.
Now they're reapportioning everything, and it's tiered.
Yeah, Kiro is redeveloping it.
They have Deacon, and there's the Beacon Deacon,
and then there's all these other little incendiary devices below that.
And then there's some explosive laughter accompanied by a loud vomiting.
As far as I'm concerned, you can take the entire lot and send them back to Jabzibu,
or whatever they call it.
The Mormons teach that if you're a good enough Mormon, your skin will become lighter colored.
White and delightsome.
I like the Mormon you love to do this.
I heard they actually try and say that.
To people in South America and Africa, when they try and convert them.
Yeah.
I've heard that's a selling point.
Well, I worked with a lot of American Indians.
Well, oddly, I know a guy who's half English descent, and half Ute Indian, and he claims to be a Mormon.
You mean the lost...
You don't mean Native Americans.
You mean the lost tribe of Israel.
The lost tribe that was dark.
Yeah.
They've gone to the Buchenwald and places like that, just taken the names, wrote them down, said they're Mormon now.
Same thing.
Baptism of the dead.
Now this is...
They had already condemned them to hell, and they'd already gone to hell.
And then down there, like, one million years...
Let me tell you something about a little conflict.
...the rivers of B.C.s.
Yep.
And then suddenly, a week later, Granny prays for them, and they come flying out of hell so fast, they're back in heaven.
Let me tell you a little story about a...
...treatment, bath oils.
...bath oils, bath balls.
They just made them re-baptized.
Okay, I'm sick of having to say, can I tell you a little story?
Okay.
I want that.
Review mirror.
A little story about a conflict...
I'm not even making this up.
Okay, shut up, dude.
I want to hear a good story.
A little story about the, uh, about the conflict that's actually arisen between, uh, between Satanists and the Mormon church, because of that whole practice of baptism of the dead.
Alright, because we all know that, you know, that true Satanic witches will make an ointment out of the rendered fat of unbaptized babies, and it allows them to fly when they wear this ointment.
And what'll happen is a Mormon will baptize that dead baby...
...and the witch falls from the sky.
While the witch is flying and the concoction of the con-
...and the witch, yep.
...and the concoction of the con-
The Mormons have conducted a number of strikes against the Satanic, uh, witch community.
And there's no regulation to...
Satanic witches are flying across the sky, minding their own business, and the next thing you know, there's a Mormon praying for a dead baby, and the witch goes crashing to the ground.
Mormons are mean.
And the, and the witch, better caveat, are emptor because the buyer has to beware.
Yeah.
The buyer of the witch.
And they have strange, uh,
Like the witch was on her way to a job.
Actually, I remember seeing, like, commercials...
She was just on her way to her job! She wasn't minding, she was minding her own business!
I remember seeing commercials for the Mormon church when I was a kid.
Where they'd say, hey, it's good to be different! Like, and it was a commercial for the Mormon church.
Did the baby even know the difference?
Yeah.
Yeah, right now on YouTube and other media outlets, there's one...
Hey, it's good to be homosexual, where pink bell bodies and unborn...
...showing you how normal they are, and...
...and have earrings that...
I, I would almost...
...be tempted to join, except I'd have to quit drinking.
Oh, man.
Yeah, and you have to move to Salt Lake City and, like, get in the desert with a hundred men.
And you have to quit, like, wanting to have more than, you know, ten wives.
Yeah.
Ten wives.
Dude, I can't even imagine having one wife, let alone ten. That would just be, like, exponentially harder to live with, I would imagine.
Well, if you were in a real grossly panicked, patriotic, anarcho-macrosnical...
Patriot, psychotic, anarcho-materialist?
...society, you would just order the damn wench to do as you... wenches... to do as you please.
I just wanna wear the fancy underwear.
The magic underwear.
Magic underwear.
Well, you can do that just by joining the Masons.
You know, the subgeniuses have magic underwear.
What kind of dental plans do the Masons have?
Yeah, there's certain Jewish groups that have magic underwear, too.
Yeah.
The dental plan that the Masons have is pretty good, but it's not actually as good as the ones...
I think the Church of the Sphinx...
...that the, uh, that the Tylers have in the...
...the Carpenters have.
The Carpenters have a better one.
...Rubinstein, we need to make some magic underwear.
I know the church followers would wanna have some.
Yeah.
I, uh, I, I, I had a pair of magic underwear, but I kinda soiled it.
Everybody had magic underwear, and like, where are we today?
That's what you need for magic underwear.
It's just a perspective of time, I suppose.
It's just spiritual soil.
You can't really see it.
It may be lost long...
It's spiritual soil, so it's pure as the wind-driven snow.
...in a few incorrect directions.
But overall, we can only assume that things have been better.
This... this magical soil...
Here.
Feces is like pure gold.
...definitively like pure gold?
Your magic underwear...
...is made of pure gold?
Let me get this wrong.
Well, the magic, the magic pants, the magic, uh, underwear...
Woven from the Golden Fleece.
... coun likes the alchemical reaction.
Oh, OK.
... cause the alchemical reaction of the earth."
We slipped some on Reverend Stang earlie....
It's woven from the Golden Fleece that, uh, that, uh, Jason stole.
Uh, and then...
But first you can pull it over your nose, too.
You know, he could be like...
Yeah, the golden feces become the golden fleeces.
Endangered feces.
A coprolite in the mind of God.
That's this planet Earth, a coprolite.
Engendered and endangered at the same time.
For your listless pleasures.
It's human feces from the years that so dig it while you can.
Wow, frozen coprolite.
I saw a...
When I was in biology class in high school,
the teacher showed us a video called The Wonderful World of Dung.
Hey, nice.
Where's that tape?
It is The Wonderful World of Dung.
It sounds like a Broadway musical.
I mean, well, no, not...
Well, we figured out on some show...
Somewhere that dirt is mostly feces, and feces is mostly corpses.
Right, and the earth was...
It's like a world of corpses.
There's rocks, sticks, and corpses, and that's about it.
Yeah.
And animals like that.
The actual earth was only about as big as a golf ball in the beginning.
Right.
And by then, you had to accumulate so many turds and other...
The rocks and animals, sticks and vegetables, and corpses are animal.
And yet they're still teaching creationism and evolution in schools.
It's crazy.
They're teaching cooking classes.
Everyone knows that in the Garden of Eden, Jehovah One made Adam out of feces.
Oh, you never would have said that.
In my Bible classes, women there are...
And then Adam made pornography out of more feces,
and then God was ashamed and made Eve to distract Adam.
Yeah, but what if it was real luminous...
And woman has been nagging man ever since.
And Adam and Eve was Adam Weishaupt.
Adam Weishaupt, yeah.
Oh, man.
What if it was...
That's...
The mother of the Bavarian...
Madam, I'm Adam.
Yeah.
Oh, madam, I'm Adam.
Go hang a salami.
I'm a lasagna log.
It's Stern Commanderson.
It's a miniature.
Oh, it's a little prescription to view in our mind.
I had this book once.
I think it was called Crazy English by Richard Lederer.
There was a chapter about this guy who spoke only in palindromes.
Good Lord.
That's hard work.
It was funny.
Well there is a weird owl take off on Bob Dylans song.
Didn't we say, one of the palindromes being an island?
When I draw really.
Well really.
Right, right right.
Really?
Really.
Right, right, right, right, right.
Right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, right,
right.
Right, right, right, right, right.
Hey, brother.
Stephen, Eric, John Keaton, correct?
But that means, we are almost in tingling.
Turn right on.
There is a very big clean in the queen.
There really is.
goal  on parking.
Yes, I know. There's a Sonic and a Burger King and a Dairy Dick Queen in
Dequeen and look, Dequeen is right near Fort Smith and I know Smith. I don't think many people know Smith, but I know him.
A Dairy Dick Queen? Dairy Dequeen. Dickween.
Oh, I can't wait to get to Dequeen. It's almost as beautiful as Dierks.
Well, this would be the worst subgenius family vacation because I'm still sick and really sick.
He is sick. I shouldn't be laughing.
But our hosts are so nice.
Yes.
We're at Pisces and Suds in historic Charlottesville right now.
And the way here was really fun. We went on sort of a back road that was through West Virginia that was loaded with one of our favorite kinds of sites, which is dilapidated buildings.
The dilapos were fabulous coming down here.
Uh huh.
People have accused us of being classist elitists.
And they may be right.
But the fact is that things falling apart look cool.
And that life after people thing fills me with joy.
I like to see nature destroying the works of man.
Especially when they're easy to destroy like old abandoned barns.
They are cool looking.
After coughing all night and then sleeping all day.
We're venturing out into the city of Charlottesville to look at the weird occult symbols of this old, old town.
So we're a walking disease factory.
Or I am. Princess Wee doesn't have it.
We're coming up to the Rugby Secret Society according to this map that was hand drafted for us by Suds Pasha.
Uh huh.
We'll take a good picture of it for you, the radio audience.
Lots of brick and columns.
Yeah, it's pretty colonial around here.
Oh, there. Look to the right.
We're supposed to be looking at Monticello.
When we look over this thing with the columns.
There's an ancient mansion somewhere on that hill that's Thomas Jefferson's house.
So I can sort of see a lump over there.
Yeah, that lump is Monticello.
Okay, now we're seeing Monticello. Let's go.
I want to go down in there.
Okay.
Look at this crumbling brick wall.
That's cool.
Don't get me wrong.
I, like my fellows of Genie E, am far from perfect.
I admit that I am guilty of many acts of stupidity.
Some more recent than I care to admit.
And some I look back on and wonder why I'm even still here after pulling such a stupid stunt.
Well, the old proverb, wise as the admitted dumbass, has never been truer.
And this dumbass looks back on his experiences with hard-earned wisdom, humility, and a better understanding for the stupidity all around us.
Six billion points of stupid.
Of course, I speak of the mindless, glorps, pinks, and asshole figureheads within the conspiracy who robbed the slack of the true Yeti.
Tools. Every last one.
Unworthy of the edict of Bob they bumbled to and fro, stupidly clinging to any shred of false slack they think they have.
Praising their lord for giving them something they've never known and wouldn't recognize it if they had.
Those who continue to piss in our cornflakes.
Those who love nothing more than to stick their dick in the birthday cake and, quite frankly, I'm a little tired of it.
All around us, the mental health of the people who are in charge of the society.
The mental midgets of the pink race, bobbing their heads to the pronouncement of morons.
Their eyes glistening in a bovine glaze of intellectual laziness.
Utterly oblivious to the cliffs the conspiracy shepherds them towards.
Flagrantly disregarding scruples while aiding criminals aiding criminals.
Guilty of the very crimes they themselves try to create.
And all under the umbrella of thunderous applause and thudding back-patting over the fattening of coffers.
On all sides they come.
Armed with the stinking madness of their fear.
They file in, shoulder to shoulder, jackbooted fools.
Baying and bleeding like legions of demented sheep.
Launching their blitzkrieg of bullshit and incompetence on the heads and hearts of all they do not understand.
Decimating the very ground under their feet with the sheer weight of their crusade against rationality and common sense.
This inundation of the most vile and despicable creature to ever slither and slink its way up from the depths of the primordial sludge.
Those who are unworthy of sucking farts from the arse of Cthulhu.
Who bleat monotonous amounts of mental deficiency.
Regurgitating ineptitude at levels that even most pinks are incapable of.
These putrid imperfections of protozoan puke permeate the dark recesses of the church far more than I ever dared to believe.
Hiding behind their dobbs head t-shirts.
Pretending to know the paths to frenzy.
Blindly following the edicts of those who would and will take advantage of them for their own good.
Their own deliciously demented yet tastefully slackful purposes.
Do not underestimate these vile and disgusting abominations.
Watch them wobble like bobby heads in the hot wind of nuclear destruction.
Listen to them cheer for the spiritual enema hand delivered unto them by their own obsession.
You moron go back to giving yourself a spiritual swirly.
Take a hearty dose of sit the fuck down with a tall glass of shut the fuck up to watch it down.
You shit for birds.
You brain's pink ass motherfucker.
I'm about to unleash a serious round of overman rage on your candy ass.
Oh yeah motherfucker.
Just because you think your hot shit doesn't help the fact you're a pink dumb fuck whose lady luck ran off with your best friend who was smart enough to pay his thirty fucking bucks.
You needle dicked incompetent fucktard.
You and your twat booger girlfriend can go back to Podunkinville ass hatsaw before I shove your head down your throat now you're fucking asshole.
You degenerate feces flinging monkeys have wasted our time.
Worse you've wasted our slack and that is unforgivable.
As for your punishment we shall continue to use and abuse you for our own entertainment.
You shall suffer never knowing the reasons why Bob has never seen fit to grant you true slack.
Your suffering will be delicious candy for all across the corporate galaxy.
Your actions shall be remembered come next day when the legions of card carrying church members shall be enjoying the immaculate madness.
Of sex hurt and ooze squirt.
Laughing with the uber sex goddesses over the destruction of you bobbies and your pink brethren.
And in any case Bob will keep your money.
That's subgenius.com.
The dot com bank.
And this is the hour of slack.
And that was Reverend Frodis Suds Bashaw from his YouTube video sermons with Suds part six.
Uh before I put my disease on hold.
I'm going to put my disease in him.
For he and his fiance priestess Pisces uh against our advice let us stay in their home and they both got the Clevelandian virus.
And you can too at subgenius.com.
Uh after planting the parasite in its new host we and I moved on.
And so next week more victims.
Uh the music in the background here is the Rudy Schwartz project.
The year they switched to cornmeal.
Praise Bob.
And uh thank you all.
We're leaving Charlottesville and we've been driving around looking at the University of Virginia.
Which is ancient and cool looking.
Yeah.
We just saw a statue of my ancestor George Clark of Lewis and Clark.
Conqueror of the Northwest.
He was on a horse.
He looked like he was about to run down a bunch of Indians.
He looked really pissed off.
I don't think that's what the impression was supposed to be.
But that's kind of.
They had to cram every all the figures together.
So that's kind of how it comes off.
Boy we sure were treated like visiting royalty by Suds and Pisces.
Yeah.
Well they're they treat everybody real nice.
Or actually they treat everybody as they deserve.
That's what I like about Pisces.
If you're a real jerk she treats you the way I would treat you.
Like a jerk.
She's just better at it.
She's really quite diplomatic about it.
You wouldn't.
Despite what people say.
Their apartment was pretty loud with people late at night.
I'll take your word for it.
I couldn't hear much of it.
I was glad I had the earplugs in.
How could you hear it over my snoring?
Now what Jack? Forward or turn?
Here I'll turn Jack's voice on.
Instead of Jack off we'll have Jack on.
Recalculating.
Well we can't be as funny as Dr. Zeronius and Todry Milktoast when they were driving through Kansas.
Because we're not as miserable.
Because this isn't Kansas.
It's rather scenic here although it's rainy today in Virginia.
We're heading for North Carolina and the house of Reverend Pockets and Dr. Leguien.
To put our disease in them.
They can get down with our sickness.
Mmm. I haven't looked inside my coffee mug full of phlegm yet.
When the cops pull us over that's the first place they're going to look.
And he's going to go, okay I know what this is.
Jinkum. You're busted.
It's like what? Position of excrement is against the law now?
Do you want me to give up all of my excrement sir?
Move over. Let me pull my pants down.
I'll give you all my jinkum.
It's your lung.
Yeah. Yeah actually that is what it is.
Well lung technically is scraped from the lungs of a person who's died.
Who was a very heavy prop smoker.
And so it's like concentrated lung hash.
As opposed to jinkum which is butt hash.
That's butt haze.
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show.
And we're even more glad that some listeners have donated enough to help us keep on going for another couple of months.
Not just this show but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob and want some of that slack back to rebound to you.
You should go to subgenius.com front page or especially the radio page or the catalog store pages.
And help out financially as best you can.
Now we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty.
And we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference.
Even if it's only once a month from enough of you.
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that blow jobs could go the way of Steve jobs if you don't pay Dobbs.
We also take checks and money orders to subgenius foundation.
P.O. Box 181417.
Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Thanks for anything you can do to help let there be slack.