Bob
Everything's a damn about it
And it comes down the street like a garbage wagon.
Okay.
So their brains may live on forever.
Fresh venison.
Or has he created another?
By the miracle of recording.
I'm not very good at singing songs, but here's a try.
Well, better make it quick, kiddo.
Ridiculous theory of evolution.
Peace or annihilation.
And thanks to Lee Murr for all that mess we just heard,
except for the very last part, which was by new guy Jason Myrick.
And welcome to another non-standard Hour of Slack.
I, your host and prayer partner, Reverend Ivan Stang,
was looking at a whole mess of editing I'd have to do
to polish up another show made from live winter star footage
or chopped up puzzling evidence or even a best of oldies show.
But I've got a ton of other stuff to do for Bob.
And then it struck me.
At some point in the past,
I had compiled enough new hymns and songs of a subgeniously nature
to make a seven.
Bob song CD.
But I'd never gotten around to making the packaging.
So this stuff hadn't been released except in dribs and drabs
on ancient hours of Slack from 2006.
So that solved my problem.
Here then is our of Slack number 1246
and all Bob songs episode and a sneak preview of our next official CD release,
which you now already have on MP3 from downloading this show.
But oh, well, Slack must come first in the life of every initiate.
Lee Murr.
Lee Murr shall start us off.
One, two, three.
Bob.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
That didn't look like me at all.
If you were turned inside out, that's a laser.
Apparently, Bob came and did something with all of us.
Raise a bar.
Quiet numbskulls.
I'm broadcasting.
Let your ass go to radio.
It's not a nightmare that's going to end.
It's just beginning because it's inside me.
You have to love Bob.
He loves you, Bob.
You love Bob.
You have to.
Or else what happens if you don't love Bob?
He'll kill you.
He'll bob you out.
Right now, I will give you all my money.
I will give you all my money.
...
Bob bob
Bob...
Congratulation!
Are you here scary all night?
I won't bite.
I'm gonna rip it open.
Hey, stop!
Shut up!
Attention.
Vouny.
Who are the overlords of the UFO?
Attention.
Look, if he starts this thing, he won't be able to stop it.
It's immortality.
It's more costly than death.
Attention.
The world stops spinning and the clock stops moving.
But something's still ticking and wearing on the inside.
Attention.
And every time you let it go like I'm doing right now,
you can feel the wear.
I know from 342 years of experience that
time control can only go awry.
The third world war might begin any minute and we'll all be killed.
Why should we bother about giant turtles?
Yes, maybe you're right.
I know how much you love your turtles.
But there are other things in life just as important, like having friends.
Our ancient legends did mention fire-eating turtles.
But they repeated this a thousand times.
We can still beneficiaries of the nature's further
believingitting the die by a drop of보다 byancer.
18- considerable película de Martin Shaw's
Noral Preff and his composition Love Church.
It makes you feel real big.
Go, go, go!
Love Church.
Bob!
Yes, giving.
Love Church.
Bob!
Come join the fun.
All of you have heard of Bob.
Love Church.
It makes you feel real big.
Yes, giving.
Bob!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
We all thought you were dead.
No, no, still here.
How are you, Bob?
Brothers and sisters,
we must confront ourselves
with
the fact that
we know that all men and women
are created good.
We must understand why you have gone bad.
You cannot play checkers with your life,
jumping around like an old whirlwind,
wrapping your dishes and plates,
and then unpacking them and placing them back on the shelf.
This is not the way the Jehovah One has designed you to act.
Unless,
you are willing to do something.
You are willing to admit that you are a gnome,
a pink boy,
a nanny,
a twig.
Only then can you decide where your path shall lead you.
But we know inherently that we are all created good by Jehovah One.
Some of you got such bad luck sometimes in your life,
you couldn't hang yourself with your own necktie.
This is when you should look to Bob.
When you look to Jehovah One and say,
Bob,
come into my life,
and you shall see one set of footprints in the sand.
And that is when you will know that Bob has charged you $5.99 to carry you to the nearest
taxi.
Praise Bob in his divine ways.
You got to know that life is like a vanishing twin,
a vanishing twin,
fading inside of a twin,
inside of a woman's belly.
That's how confusing this wiggly world can be.
You got to raise up above this wiggly world and grab the hand of Bob.
Praise him and all that flows from Bob.
And praise Reverend Raymond Lafferty who did that classic.
Uh, wiggly world indeed.
To help solidify things, we'll now hear Bob's audition by,
not Bob, but the Psychoskeletons.
Feels kinda like I'm in Spaceland.
That's a contradiction in terms.
And Bob's shining down on me.
And no one's aiming a rifle at me.
Holy dammit.
That's a contradiction in terms.
And Bob is the giant hepatitis penis of destruction bursting forth from the portable Johnny.
Now let's all be a contradiction in terms.
Herds of benign cattle wander across the acid-washed,
flush-drained landscape,
all belonging to their own friendship families,
none loving any other than Bob.
The flow between adjacent points of reference,
points on the line segment between the concrete to absolute oblivious eternity,
sweet lord Bob.
When we all act together as men, as people,
we could distinguish ourselves and betray any other.
As it was before time, but still within space,
all who bow down and submit to their fractals.
Mom, would you if you will, would you believe in—
Don't tell me, would you take me in, in
BELL sécher's쳐stVA.
GET coming up, like B Above Vincent Pratt.
It feels like Eastwood……
I hope we'll do a 7-in terran countdown.
Second one, look, we've got these abusers like you off and down telling songs that really
make itlements right, like like horror.
My shorter persevere
Bound down
Just like the sky, the sun, my slack goes on and on and on
Just like the sun, the sky, my slack goes on and on and on and on
Praise Bob!
Just like the sky, the sun, my slack goes on and on and on and on
Just like the sky, the sun, my slack goes on and on and on
Praise Bob!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Another song by Reverend Ed Fred entitled simply, Pink.
Hey little brothers and sisters, why don't you get around?
I've got something important to say to you, something I think you need to hear.
Come on now!
Are you sure you got your life together?
You think you're on top of the world, but reality is about to rear its ugly head.
Listen my friends, are you ready to face the music?
You're pink!
We think!
You drive that big ol' SUV,
Draining your wallet in the used to be.
You're in a material race,
You just can't get out.
You can't win.
Following society is your greatest sin.
You are destined to fail my friend.
You're gonna be poor and alone in the end.
You got your treasures, you got your hoard.
But you're only gonna end up broken board.
Come on friends, it's time to turn over a new leaf.
Unleash your weakness and get some relief.
Slack is king and nothing else matters.
Don't be pink.
Pull yourself up by your latex undergarments.
Toss away all your commercial influences.
The slack within you can be born again.
Act now.
This is limited time offer.
Get yours now while supplies last.
Offer void in Alaska and Hawaii.
Be sure to consult your doctor about any risks that might be associated with slack.
Yeah, I hope you learned something today.
Now I'm going to get myself some slack.
Waste chopsticks.
Are you lookin for slicingAK?
facility
I have a great idea.
We thought you were macaroni.
Did you get a buck nervous after earmuffs?
Party back at scale!
This is the POTATO FIRE TOUR.
Part two, ladies and gentlemen.
Tune in next week for a big 1987 movie of the Master Biology and also foroster episode of Christmasなん Mega гарminusuu
and aquesta första not just ustedes but every squad like the name of the character themselves.
Bob?
Who are the overlords of the UFO?
I bring you a warning.
Every one of you listening to my voice, tell the world.
Tell this to everybody wherever they are.
Watch the sky.
This is Doug Smith, radio operator.
I'm going to bring you a piece of that green cheese for sure.
Shazam.
And I say it is possible for a giant lizard to have lived there for years without being sick.
Watch me.
You, you, you, you bloated idiot.
You stupid.
I have you.
There are a bunch of art critics and we're looking for people who like to draw.
You are not safe.
I'm safe from this.
Come on.
I'm going to get you there.
Watch out and then you'll know the truth.
There are thousands of words of fun.
It's quite a joke.
I tried to prop.
Groovy.
Right, Bob?
Bob?
Wait a minute. How did this happen? We're smarter than this.
Apparently not.
Bob?
Long cow Dave, don't you know what they're doing to yourself?
Apparently Bob came and did something with all of us.
The drugs I took seem to light up my brain.
I'm gonna take a little nap now.
I'm gonna take a little nap.
Bob!
And I say as long as you're alive,
you'll make noise.
You will make noise.
Grave Bob.
You'll shine up like hell.
And you ain't earned the last, Ernest T. Bass.
Praise Reverend Ernest T. Bass.
The last four minutes there were collages by Leemur, Byron Werner, and others,
remixed by me with my music.
I can't remember if I ever made a video with that one or not,
but now from a group or individual, I don't even know which,
called Da Binchy,
a tune called Eslactica.
Diffrm новая Mhängorge
Facepalm
And I perform the head.
The head.
What about the head?
What about the scary poster dog thing?
That evil head.
There's no sign of Wellman.
We're just landlady.
Wellman's gone.
And hoping that we can get in touch with him.
Yeah, Wellman's gone.
But if we can just get the head inside that lead-lined vault, we'll be okay.
Friends, beware that head.
Safe.
I left a little Wellman at home.
The bleeding head of Arnold Palmer rose slowly above the trap between the 3rd and 4th greens.
Down at Onion Creek Country Club.
And gone.
Off course.
Thumping slowly like an over-enlarged fig, the bleeding head slowly rose at a gentle angle above the green, dripping blood.
It hovered briefly over the sand trap.
And then slowly ascended towards the constellation of Orion at an angle of about 44.325 degrees.
Like a shot off a shovel.
There was no doubt that it was the head of Arnold Palmer.
That moon-faced smile was unforgettable.
The population, the population of Southeast Austin went wild.
They tore off their clothes.
Danced in the streets and said, the bloody head has come.
The time is here.
Take off your clothes and be somebody.
The bloody head of Arnold Palmer was above such things.
The bloody head of Arnold Palmer rose gently.
Buffeting itself slightly as it passed among some ancient pecan trees.
And slowly, still, ever moving upwards, it wobbled slightly.
Spraying a small glissando of blood, so to speak, on the people below it.
Healing two old ladies.
To get the blood out of their bodies.
giving an old man a substantial gland rebuild.
At 14 minutes after 9, the bleeding head was sighted on the forward control radar access
plant at Barksdorf Air Force Base.
Three interceptors were scrambled, one of which crashed on takeoff.
They could find nothing.
The radar was still tracking the head.
The bloody head moved north, rocketed over Dallas and Fort Worth.
The radar at Caswell Air Force Base gave subsequent indications that something large and wet was
moving north-northeast while ascending still upwards towards the constellation of a comet.
The bloody head moved on.
Fourteen ex-virgins were rejuvenated in Lubbock as the head passed through.
Keep your hands out of each other's marsupial pockets, boys.
That's right.
Yes, the ballad of the bleeding head, a real oldie from the great Dr. G. Gordon Gordon
and Doctors for Extreme Prejudice.
I'm not sure, but I think one of the musicians on that finally got out of prison after serving
a term for murder.
And now, the news.
From NPR News in Washington, I'm delayed by heavy snow.
Pope Benedict XVI is instructing Irish Roman Catholic clergy to cooperate in the sex involving
priests and children.
The Vatican says Benedict does express,
found sexual regret, this time at the Vancouver Olympics.
On Wall Street, 151021421.
Pope Benedict says this is PR.
Your news is flawed.
Three instead of three and a half.
President Obama says,
And this is only the tripling.
Astronauts killed 18 people and injured 71 others aboard the International Space Station.
The astronauts need to encourage development of PR news from Washington.
Come on.
He must now recall what'siroềI
a
A
b
以及
Thank you.
solution by the Psychoskeletons. Another song that also brings to mind Captain
Beefheart, although not for any good reason, is this masterpiece by the great
Dr. Gary Gaprog-Fran titled Tar Baby of Bob.
I've got no money but I've got no Bob Stuck to the Tar Baby of Bob
I wish I was stuck in a big ball of frog
Instead of this church where my socks just rot
Tar Baby of Bob
Somewhere in hyperspace, Bob has prepared a place
For those he lusts for who will pay
The X's will come again and make us sober
And countdown's getting higher on X day
10 and 9, 8 and 7, 6 and 4
Send your thirty bucks while you're alive Two and three, how rich we'll be when humans
take a dive The countdown's getting high at our food drive
Bob Dobbs was shot for you, met with the devil too
But in deepest hell he did not stay Satan done let him out
And while we scream and shout The countdown's getting high
at our food drive Two and three, how rich we'll be when humans
take a dive The countdown's getting high at our food drive
Ten and nine, eight and seven, six and five and nine
Send your thirty bucks, you're out of time Forty-two, boy, did he get you?
Salvation should be a crime The countdown's getting high on froth this
time
So, where's the dirty that we just straightened out?
Reverend Self Slayer did that quaint and quirky little X Day Folk song
now echoing a song from last week's show, Reverend Phineas Narco of nationalcynical.com
brings us this subgenicized version of a John Lennon song that probably doesn't deserve this
kind of treatment.
I'm a son of a bitch and I'm a son of a bitch
I wonder what you'd do
Can't get an
ATM card
And no computers too
Imagine all sub-dini's
Living life in slack
Imagine there's no modems
And Sid comes on TV
We'd hunker down in mud huts
And take some
L.A.
L.S.D.
You...
Hoo hoo hoo!
You may say I'm some genius...
But I'm not the only one...
God I wonder if I'm really one...
What I'm losing out on?
Imagine no McDonald's...
And no Big Mac with cheese...
No E-Mail and no voice...
And no more songs like these...
Imagine the subgenius...
Life without the con...
You...
Hoo hoo hoo!
God I wonder if I'm really one...
What I'm losing out on?
Look into my eyes...
What do you trust?
The Church of the Subgenius...
I know your slap...
I know your trap...
I've been everything so spit and cuss...
I'm the Church of the Subgenius...
Like El Pupule...
And Reverend Sten...
Church of the Subgenius...
You're being a delirious coward...
Don't trust yourselves!
Dr. Howard...
meidän م ries ow!
Mais la fois transpschrägme!
Imongesı bul destructive în Проodiک Onlyאבا
ην tenido قل 어제...
Tu Directoramentă,…
だけ c Hadi Define
I smell the things you need to be Church of the subgenius
I explore you, don't make a fuss I tell you one and one and one makes a fuss
I'm the Church of the subgenius Like J.R.R. Bob Dobbs and Old Festus
I'm the Church of the subgenius Church of the subgenius
Church of the subgenius
Lonesome cowboy pig, I love women
A subgenius
A subgenius rants, that subgenius lies
You don't have to follow me
Only you can pig freely
Freely you cavemen frog
Dr. Powell, Princess Queen, Mr. Lemur, Lemur, Lemur will crash the next, next game
You don't have to follow me
Only you can pig freely
Freely you cavemen frog
Freely you gave me NZA
Freely you gave me MA
Freely you gave me T
A great subgenius anthem created by Nor El Pref of norelpref.com.
Loaded with inside references, as is this one by Reverend Oroboros Rex.
It's an X-Day song.
This one and the following song by Phineas Snarko are placed down near the end of the show for maximum tearjerker effect.
This is a song by Phineas Snarko.
Now the drills go by so fast
And it's one more day up in the saucer
And it's one more night in Rushwood
If a Friday Jones could be my island
I wish she would
Na na na na
Na na na
Yeah
The smell of big boys and of normals
And the feeling that they all can't help but sit in my face
With my third eye I look across the mill
No way to see he exists
But I know he exists
On their way to burn this place
And it's one more day up in the saucer
And it's one more night in Rushwood
If saucer dreams alone could bring me Susie
Maybe I could
Na na na na
Na.
La la la
Laaaaa
Na na na na
Yeah
I cruise this堪اء 61 0000 000000 000000 000000 0000 Torah
Some time after 2 a.m.
And talk about alcohol in danger
a little while about the church.
But the conspiracy makes you move a little slower,
makes you talk a little lower
about the day that we take over.
It's been a while since X-Day,
and I guess I will believe
maybe next year will be better than the last.
I can't remember all the times I played the hour of slack
and wished my religion would make it come to pass.
So it's 6.59 on Gordon's Saucer.
But it's 7.01 in Brushwood.
I have never made it to an X-Day.
I guess I should.
Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na.
Na, na, na, na, yeah.
Na, na, na, na.
In the time of chimpanzees, I was a yeti
Church air in my veins and my fur is getting shitty
While the plastic-ass pipes spray paint the palmer head
Dog food vendors with a beefcake suit-a-fed
Kill all the pink boys and put it in neutral
Issue happens flamin' in the stag-meltin' capitol
Bobby's in Sherman, tired of fightin' the bike
Got a couple motel rooms, sleep on the floor tonight
Someone keeps sayin' I'm insane to complain about a round-trip ticket when it's all gonna
end
Why believe anything that ain't nice when you got Reverend Surnow and the Jader device?
Just watch the face smilin' there in the dark Burn all the money when they decimate the
Taylor Park
I'm a rocker, I'm a rocker, I'm a rocker, I'm a rocker, I'm a rocker, I'm a rocker, I'm a rocker,
I'm a rocker, Mil Curious about callin'
Now tie my paddocks up, you would not buy Stone and G Pause
Santers of genius
I'm subgenius baby
So why don't ya kill me?
Say pal, no such thing as Judas
I pulled up the Pantgros
Santers of genius
I'm subgenius baby
So why don't ya kill me?
Food version lifting
Subgenius baby
Burned up the Pantros
Santers of genius
And a sock fist pounding down the door of the world
Cause one's gotta rant and the other's gotta brag
Bob's on some window painting, Connie's on the rag
With the radio shows and the backstage world jobs
Can't get invited to the first week of the summer
Burn to death like a Buddhist priest
Yes, men starving at the subgenius feast
And it's all for those who fulfill their fate
Trade the cash for the pills for the bodies for the hate
And the time is a piece of crap
Falling down the toilet
With Bob's hand on the handle
Samper subgenius
I'm subgenius, baby
So why don't you kill me?
I'm a frog, you're lost
Samper subgenius
I'm subgenius, baby
So why don't you kill me?
You shouldn't kill me
Lo do your best
You're gonna do great
I'm subgenius, baby
You should WHAT?
I'm submen up
Everybody's gonna pay
You'll catch me when I municipi
Listen to me, bob
You're better than me right there
I've done run over my wife
Doctors for Bob
And everything for him and his wife
He's got the blues
But that damn pickup done run over his wife
Doctors for Bob
We're doctors, we're doctors, we're doctors for Bob
We're doctors, we're doctors, doctors for Bob
Doctors, we're doctors, we're doctors for Bob
And in the open we'll be broken
Not Gregory, we'll be broken
Steve LeBlanc. Not Rodriguez
We're doctors, we're doctors, we're doctors
Doctors for Bob
Destroy the Indian Outfits
Destroy all the rules
Hand state the Germans the Jews
We shall rule.
We shall be free.
We are the story of the people.
We are the true church.
Doctors for Bob.
Everything's real in his life.
He's got the blues.
Because that damn pickup gun run over his wife.
Doctors for Bob.
Bob?
All right.
I'll sing you a song.
About Bob.
I'll sing you a song about Bob
I know
I'll sing you a song
about Bob
I'll sing you
a song
about Bob
I'll sing you
a song
about Bob
I'll sing you
a song
about Bob