Well, I saw the thing coming out of the sky, but a one long horn and one big eye, like a Mr. Shakin' in the city. It looks like a subgenius, our old son.
The predicament of man forced to live in a barren, godless eternity, like a tiny flame flickering in an immense void with nothing but waste, horror, and degradation, forming a useless, bleak, straight jacket in a black, absurd cosmos.
Thank you, Bob.
Uh, yes, yes, yes, dear friends.
Welcome to Hour of Slack number 13.
1029, which is brought to you this time entirely by Reverend Susie the Floozy and WREK, the greatest station in Atlanta, Georgia, which happens to be at Georgia Tech.
Now, some of you may remember Hurricane Katrina and New Orleans and the insanely late, wrong, and insufficient actions by FEMA and the completely unqualified George Bush.
For those of you who don't know, I'm George Bush.
I'm one of the frat mates who run it.
We did our subgenius take on that debacle when it happened, and so did Reverend Susie the Floozy.
Bob, howdy, did she?
In fact, she did four episodes of Bob's Slack Time Funhouse on Hurricane Katrina in her truly inimitable media barrage style, starting now.
When my bad dream came to me.
Piercing the future.
The future's bail right through.
Our theme this year is Louisiana, where the fun begins.
And old man Reverend?
Well, he helps carry that fun throughout the state.
Yes, from the mouth of the Mississippi at the Gulf of Mexico to the Delta region.
Louisiana.
Louisiana's got fun.
And fun people.
Like in the mouth of the river.
We've got probably the most fun people of the state.
Denizens of New Orleans' lower depths, its back streets, its out-of-the-way neighborhoods, its odd speech, its ethnic whites, incredibly true-to-life dialogue, and the zaniest series of high and low comic adventures.
Oh, what in heaven's name is he talking about?
In such poor taste.
This is making me so nervous.
I'm so depressed.
Oh, man.
Cheer up.
The world's going to end in ten minutes anyway.
Long before the Superdome, where the saints of football play, lived a city.
The city.
Way down, down in New Orleans.
In the land of those creatures.
Oh, there's a garden of Eden.
Do you know what?
I mean
Creole baby with flashing
eyes
Softly whisper with tender sighs
And then you stop
Won't you give your lady
a little smile
And then you stop
You bet your life you'll
give her a little
ah ah ah
Never ever ride it on
with a beautiful
dream
Way down yonder in
New Orleans
Alright boys let's go
Let's go
Ah ah ah
And then you stop
Won't you give your lady
a little smile
And then you stop
You bet your life you'll
give her a little
ah ah ah
Never ever ride it on
with a beautiful
dream
Way down yonder in
New Orleans
New Orleans is, on the other hand,
a comfortable metropolis which,
as a certain apathy and stagnation,
which I find inoffensive.
At least its climate is mild.
I think not.
Why?
Hurricane winds can toss debris
that will shatter even well-protected doors and windows.
You should expect winds of 74 miles an hour or greater
or dangerously high water and storm surges.
Frankly, my dear, I don't give a damn.
Cheers.
The witness made a drinky, drinky motion.
As far as the natural threat from natural disasters, from hurricanes,
we sort of push that to the side and say,
well, didn't happen last year.
You know, it didn't happen the year before,
so maybe we'll slip by again.
Oh yeah?
That's what you think.
I think not.
Look, I don't know what the hell your point is.
To defend against the tide that rushes in on them,
construct a bowler to drive the sea from land.
What the hell are you talking about?
Whack him.
All right, mighty man.
Whatever you say, pal.
Move right along here.
The money was in place.
But now, because of the issues of Homeland Security,
that money has been diverted.
The project has been postponed.
We don't know when it will be completed, if ever.
This move was predictable.
In the same manner, those banks were made.
Anything for a buck.
Well absorbed.
The one who built them did not make them as high or thick,
whoever he was.
Why, what a marvel.
So that's very, very frustrating to have to deal with that.
I only hope there's no leak.
Oh, my.
The river, old man river, don't say nothing.
He must know something.
Old man river keeps on rolling along.
The Mississippi River is famed in atrocious song and verse.
The most prevalent motif is one which
attempts to make of the river an ersatz father figure.
Actually, the Mississippi River is a treacherous and sinister
body of water whose eddies and currents yearly claim many lives.
I have never known anyone who would even venture to stick his
toe in its polluted brown waters, which seethes with sewage,
industrial wastes, and deadly insecticides.
Even the fish are dying.
Therefore, the Mississippi, as father God, Moses, daddy,
phallus pops, is an altogether false motif, begun, I would
imagine, by that dreary fraud, Mark Twain.
So look out for me.
Oh, my.
I'm a dirty water.
You're Mr. Freeze.
Hockey-bound wise.
And I gotta need more noise on this ship.
And I gotta need to climb up on your back and ride.
Got a problem?
Where's Uncle George?
Oh, Uncle George.
Oh, he's in the den typing.
Why don't you run in and say hello to him, but don't disturb him.
We won't.
All right.
And so we're constantly, um.
George was pasting the article.
And the junior achievement scrapbook that was one of his mementos from his last semester
at school.
George's mother, on the other side of the living room, hopefully watched her son work
on his school scrapbook.
She and his father didn't seem to be able to do anything with him.
Palestine.
No.
What chance did a boy without a high school education have nowadays?
What could he do?
Depends on how far a man wants to go for a couple of million dollars.
And he's a good guy.
And, um.
Ask the president.
There was something funny about the whole business.
You just can't shake that off.
Not a couple of million.
I mean, that is big.
That is not nothing.
Maybe there's no oil there at all.
Yeah?
That's what you think.
Here's the tape from the seismograph.
Holy smokes!
The oscillation of this line proves that there's definitely oil there.
And a lot of it.
Meaning?
Ask the president.
Gosh, you're a duck.
I'm gonna try to keep forgetting those.
We've got to get our act together.
I'm thrilled and honored.
That's my boy!
The choicest iron comprises his head, but the right foot of clay, on it, more weight
than on the left is pressed.
Sign here.
He picked up a black fountain pen from his blotter and affixed his signature to the bottom
of the document.
Get it?
Yeah!
Woo!
Now the fun begins.
This is the siren, but the siren is actually more powerful than the siren.
The right foot bears a crack, a fissure dripping tears.
The final hour is approaching for the people of Earth.
That's great.
Give it to me.
Great.
I can take it.
They said the government triggered the wetlands crisis when it tamed the Mississippi River.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Sure.
Yeah, right.
Now they want to unleash the river to undo the damage.
What?
No.
Isn't that wonderful?
Eyes are tight, everybody.
No fault.
It's science run amok.
The propagation of such a weird, fantastic, and impractical plan as concentrated by the
defendant is capable of formatting a disturbance for which the company may have to recover.
Whatever.
It is our duty to stop it.
What do you mean?
How do we know that?
It's terrible.
Meanwhile, far below the Earth's surface, everything was quiet and kind of peaceful-like.
What's that?
My God.
What is that?
What?
It's awesome.
Just speaking the vernacular of the passenger, it's a storm-blower-lubber-whopper.
Hurricanes bring high winds that can damage property.
Bring in lawn furniture, toys, and garden tools.
If you can't bring them indoors, anchor them to a permanent fixture so they don't blow away and cause even more damage.
Ooh, I better go take down the manger seat.
If baby Jesus got loose, he could really do some damage.
Hey, hey, look at that.
Oh.
It's gonna rain today
Cause you just walked away
The clouds are here and soon
The rain will fall
And the rain that falls today
Will wash my world away
And this will be the biggest storm of all
On the day that I first met you
I thought
I thought my love would change
Your shining face
Turned all the clouds away
Now as I sit crying
The clouds are back again
Today is gonna be
A rainy day
It's gonna rain today
Cause you just walked away
The clouds are here and soon
The rain will fall
And the rain that falls today
Will wash my world away
And this will be the biggest storm of all
You gotta be here soon
He was probably quaffing a liquid lunch
In one of the many taverns
In the vicinity of our organization
There is a bar on every corner in the neighborhood
An indication that salaries
In the area are abysmally low
On particularly desperate blocks
There are three or four bars
At every intersection
Muscle relaxed
And quickly pleased
The world's about to end
Oh, yes sir
Nice weather for you
Last orders please
This failure to make contact with reality
Is however characteristic
Of almost all of America's art
Any connection between American art
And American nature
Is purely coincidental
But this is only because
The nation as a whole
Has no contact with reality
That is only one of the reasons
Why I have always been forced to exist
On the fringes of its society
Consigned to the limbo
Reserved for those who do know reality
When they see it
Plan ahead to survive the next hurricane
A hurricane watch is issued
When there is a threat of hurricane conditions
Within a 24 to 36 hour period
You may still have time to take precautions
If there is a hurricane warning
You may be advised to evacuate the area
Make sure that there is plenty of fuel in your car
If you are advised to evacuate
You may have to drive up to 50 miles
To reach safety
Check the contents of your emergency supply kit
And fill plastic water bottles
With one gallon of fresh water
Per person per day
Look I've spilled my martini
On my most priceless jacket
This party stinks
Let's go to a smart bar
Where is my coat?
This is making me so depressed
Let's go to a smart bar
Let's go to San Francisco
Oh what in heaven's name is this?
What in heaven's name is he talking about?
Mike!
Adios!
Hasta luego!
Sayonara!
Gotta get out of hell
What's the best way out of here?
The best way
Come on let's get out of here
Oh no you won't
You're gonna stay here
He really didn't have enough money to go anywhere
Oh dad
The best thing was to stay at home for a while
I gotta get out of here
Gotta get out of here
The Greyhound bus line is sufficiently menacing to make me accept my status quo
And I am certainly not perverse enough to attempt air travel even if I were able to afford it
Actually even riding in a car affects me enough
Of course the worst thing is riding on top in one of those Greyhound scenic cruises
So high up
I vomited several times
Oh no!
I shall not leave
No one can deter me
Oh no!
Get out of my trailer I won't get out
Gotta get out of here
Load up that Land Rover in the garage
Pick up Dutch and the kids and head for the hill
Yeah
Oh my
You really know me
Oh no
I think I'll go pick up the stuff for you
You crazy bitch
Where you going with that suitcase in your hand?
Oh no!
Don't you know more than some of what we play?
Where you going with that suitcase in your hand?
Hey!
It's full of money
It's full of change
You're never making it outside
Everyone's strange
Where you going with that suitcase in your hand?
Hey!
Everyone is chained to their honey
I said I
I
Oh yeah
I've got a Porsche
Get the hell out of there
Oh yeah
I said I was going to pick up the stuff for you
I'm awesome
Because it's stormy Monday
And two-s-day just as bad
The cold, it's stormy Monday
It's a twister! It's a twister!
I am where all light is mute
With a bellowing like the ocean
Turbulent in a storm of warring winds
The hurricane of hell in perpetual motion
Sweeping the ravaged spirits
As it rends, twists, and torments them
I saw souls come uttering cries
Wind-tossed and lofted by the storm
Master, I cried, who are these people
By black air oppressed?
The answer is floating away
Oh, this is terrible.
Terrible?
Look over there at that wrecked fuselage.
What wasn't smashed seems to have been burned.
Yes, it's no use.
Not even a clue the size of a pea.
We wanted to examine the wreckage, but some tough guy wouldn't let us go near it.
Well, why didn't you show him your credential, Kay?
I did, but he said there might be an explosion.
Why, there couldn't be any possibility of an explosion now.
When will they learn?
Oh, God, I've been misinformed.
Jim, get up.
They're after us.
We ain't got a minute to lose.
I ain't got all the provisions of war yet.
Forget that.
Just shovel out and I'll lay into that pole, Jim.
This is happening way too fast.
And half.
Look out for me, oh, muddy water.
Your mysteries are deep and wide.
And I got a need for going someplace.
And I got a need to climb apart.
Go back and ride.
Looking up, he saw the Mississippi beginning to descend over the foot of Canal Street.
Oh, Jesus, when are you going to cut me some slack, huh?
The question that the world is asking right now, why did God let this happen?
God can use nature.
He can use the elements he has in the past.
And he can.
We read newspapers of catastrophes that have taken place in the world.
And a hurricane comes and sweeps a town or a city off of the face of the earth.
Doors die.
God shatters cities.
Buildings crumble.
And the earth opens up and swallows humanity.
And the newspapers and the news media calls it an act of Satan.
The terrible storms that rip through this planet earth and cause so much destruction.
Has it ever entered your mind?
Well, why do people die, Brother Swagger?
They die because of the evil from God, Prince of the Powers of the Air?
He steals, he kills, he destroys.
God is a death-god.
That's the kind of God he is.
Stop and think a moment!
God is the despot.
God is the dictator.
God is the fast gun riding at high noon wearing a black hat.
God is the Internet.
If it keeps on raining, the levee's gonna break.
But when the levee breaks, we got no place to stay.
You think of God and there is an acid taste on your tongue
because you see him as arbitrarily reaching down without thought
and snatching something away that means more to you than anything in the world.
The mean old levee talking to weep and moan.
You know what God would have tasted to make a mountain out of his home.
Oh well, oh well, oh well.
How many of you have thought those things?
How many of you the television that's been in your mind gets turned to off?
Deep down inside the question rooms it eats like bitter bread.
Jesus, what kind of God is that?
Who would want to serve him?
Because God is a killer.
God is a destructor.
He's a destroyer.
He is long-suffering, not willing to end as you've been left alive.
Oh, don't it make you feel bad when you try to find your way?
And you don't know which way to go.
Oh, when you're going down south and there's no one to give you.
So you go down to Tupelo.
Yo, yo, Chicago.
Yo, yo, Tupelo.
God loves the caskets as much as we do.
God loves...
God loves the tombstones in the cemeteries as much as we do.
Well, crying won't help you.
Well, praying won't do you no good.
Because when the levee breaks, Mama, you've got to move.
Oh, last night I sat on the levee and moaned.
Oh, thinking of my baby and my happy home.
You're going to Tupelo.
Tupelo town, baby tupelo town.
I'm gonna take you down to the way, baby
I'm going down
I'm going down, down
I'm going down, I'm going down
I'm going down the city
To the world, sir
It's an emergency!
Everything was going wrong.
We had a storm, but then before we could come in
and begin the rescue effort and the evacuation effort,
we had a second catastrophe.
That was the levee breaking and the flood coming.
19% of all flooding occurs outside the identified flood hazard area.
Oh, honey, don't be so naive.
That's how the world works.
We've had to contend with the fact that it's very difficult to move around.
The flooding has also had an impact on the availability of buses.
It's had an impact on the availability of gas and drivers.
How do we know that?
We're doing the best we can.
Silence! Silence, you perverts!
Let me reassure you, your fears are groundless
and you're complacent.
Silence, moronic!
That's good.
This film will explain everything to you in words that you can understand.
This is a public service message from FEMA.
Go to the basement or to an inside hallway
at the lowest level you can safely reach.
Get onto a piece of sturdy furniture,
such as a workbench or heavy table or desk,
and hold onto it tightly.
This could be bad advice.
What do you need right now
to get control of this situation?
I need...
500 buses, man.
We're talking about, you know,
one of the briefings we had,
they were talking about getting, you know,
public school bus drivers to come down here
and bus people out here.
I'm like, you gotta be kidding me.
This is a national disaster.
Get every doggone Greyhound bus line in the country
and get their asses moving to New Orleans.
That's they're thinking small, man.
And this is a major, major, major deal.
But you know...
Tuesday just as bad.
And, uh, uh, that's, that's reality.
Yes, it is.
I was of the city that chose to leave.
I wouldn't worry too much about selling out.
I could never really accept the party line.
Where it kept changing.
Monday's Tuesday, Tuesday's live.
I could never really manage that.
And then I started thinking for myself
and asking questions and then...
We're not gonna allow it.
Oh my God!
Run, folks.
He might kill us all.
The jar had widened.
The great chain of being had snapped
like so many paperclips
strung together by some drooling idiot.
Death, destruction, anarchy, progress,
ambition and self-improvement
were to be his new fate.
And a vicious fate it was to be.
Now he was faced with the perversion
of having to go to work.
So I, I, I, I...
No goodness whatever adorning his memory,
arrogant in his vice was that one when he lived.
Understand the relief efforts
and the extent of the relief efforts
and the progress of the relief efforts.
After all, we're dealing with
one of the largest relief efforts
in our nation's history.
From time to time, well, maybe a lot,
he would doze off in meetings.
Perhaps fall sound asleep is a better description.
He'd sleep solidly for a few seconds
and then awaken as though he'd not missed
a beat of the discussion.
We marveled at his ability to catnap
and at what became known as the recovery factor.
This might consist of waking up
and immediately writing something,
anything on a pad or a vigorous nod of approval
as the speaker made what might have been a telling point,
though he hadn't heard a word of the presentation.
The federal government will do its part
to help the victims of Hurricane Katrina.
But the private sector needs to do its part as well.
Trade from people like you is the kiss of death.
And that's why I've asked Presidents Bush and Clinton
to lead a nationwide fundraising effort.
I knew that I still had to behave lawfully
without being particularly helpful.
But worst of all was the disgrace.
Did I want this to come out? No.
Was I embarrassed about it? Yes, absolutely.
How unbelievably gross.
First of all, you can't take that personally.
You've got to cut out the crap.
You've been drinking.
The President is...
And I said no.
I didn't even know about this.
I wasn't aware.
No one should be telling anybody.
Why don't you go home?
Leave it off.
Now that's all I know to say about this.
Constant, unrelenting leaks into face
is not sexual relations.
I love a bob.
Yeah! Yeah!
Come on.
It was no big deal.
Must have been urgent.
And how.
In the days ahead, the former presidents
will ask Americans to open their hearts and their wallets
to those in need.
Dadgum!
Government, you sorry rack of fractures.
You got yourself an itch and you're walking
made of scratches.
Well, you're dadgum.
Yeah, you're dadgum.
And the federal government's got an important role to play.
Oh.
If you believe you can come in here and wreak havoc,
get ready because we're prepared
and we're not going to let you turn your back on us.
We're going to turn this into a lawless town.
It is later than you think.
Oh, and then to my heart and the basement.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh.
Crash on the living, mama.
Water gonna hold.
Oh.
Water gonna overflow.
Oh, oh, oh.
Swamps gonna rise.
Ain't no boats are gonna roll.
Oh, oh, oh.
Now you can train on down to Williamsport.
You can bust your feet and you can rock this joint.
But oh, mama, ain't you gonna miss your best friend now?
You're gonna have to find yourself another best friend.
And somehow it'll happen to you.
Uh, that's, that's reality.
George Bush is the perfect wise man.
And her.
And all.
During the 60s, the Tug Valley Flood Control Commission was founded.
The citizens needed a chairman.
Someone who knew and loved the river.
Someone who would stay awake at night while the populace slept.
The newspaper carried the story.
The headlines read, Mayor Bob was to be the chairman.
After serving with great vigil through numerous floods, Mayor Bob never missed a flood.
Then the waters came in the fall of 73.
The rivers started rising.
The people started worrying.
Where's Honey Bob?
The crowd went out.
The word finally came from all around.
Mayor Bob is out of town.
Even the sheriff's out of town.
Oh, we can't have a flood without the mayor.
And when he gets to that promised land, Noah from the ark will say, Mayor, welcome today.
Soul-selling, no-good sons of a dead shoe-fitting fire starters.
I ought to tear your no-good, goddang preambulatory voting frame and nail it to your government walls.
All of you, you bastards, dadgum.
Oh, we can't have a flood.
Without the mayor.
Really?
I know you don't feel that way.
Well, I'm probably going to get in so much trouble, it ain't even funny.
It's funny.
Now, you mean to tell me that a place where you probably have thousands of people that have died
and thousands more that are dying every day,
that we can't figure out a way to authorize the resources that we need?
Come on, man.
You know, I'm not one of those drug addicts.
I am thinking very clearly.
And I don't know whose problem it is.
I don't know whether it's the governor's problem.
I don't know whether it's the president's problem.
But somebody needs to get their ass on a plane and figure this out right now.
And we shall learn more of his wisdom later.
Come on.
Please hold up in the Elysian Fields project.
She got spooked.
She took off before I could get anything out of her.
Hold up.
Before you go farther, be aware that now you are in this, the second ring.
Look well, for here one sees things which in words would be incredible.
Nobody's doing it.
On every side, I heard wailing voices.
For God's sake, everybody's coming.
Nobody's coming.
I get to feeling funny when I'm alone.
Those carols are down there.
Don't forget.
And I can't stand being in this plane half with them.
And I can hear them screaming, screaming and crying.
And then I get all nervous.
Now go to your room, Sally, and stay there until we summon you.
It was only playing.
I won't ever...
Stop that gammering and move.
And don't try anything funny or you'll be right down there with Susie.
And how would you like that?
Oh, please change your mind.
Don't you look at me, freak.
However, in spite of this urging and warning,
streets and highways are...
...packed with stranded people trying to...
...or apparently can flee just anywhere.
I repeat, the safest course of action at this time is simply to stay where you are.
...the Coast Guard area in area waters.
Stand by for special instructions.
Make search of all suspicious craft or blueprints...
...for an urgent public safety message from FEMA.
Hurricane force winds, rain and floodwaters can make streets and bridges impassable.
In a hurricane,
you may be cut off from your home and family.
That's why every family should have a family emergency communication plan.
A plan for getting back together if you're ever separated during a disaster.
Listen to this station for more information from local authorities and...
Police attention.
Stop and search all vehicles and persons leaving...
Stay in your homes.
Those found without specific military orders are subject to summary execution.
Repeat, Conrad Channel.
This is a Class 1 emergency.
All civilian traffic is barred from streets and highways.
Hey!
Where do you think you're going?
Daddy's having talks.
Whee!
Excellent.
This message from FEMA Recovery Radio.
Just Stay Put is the message from FEMA.
FEMA Director Michael Brown.
Don't let your guard down.
We often think that now the hurricane has moved out of this particular area that it's pretty safe.
What they need to be cautious about is there'll still be floodwaters.
There still may be some structural damage in the...
home that's not readily visible to the naked eye.
There may be downed power lines.
There's certainly going to be a lot of debris in the area.
So the dangers of the hurricane still exist.
They need to be careful when they go back into those areas they live.
Try to be patient.
Don't rush out and get in the way of emergency workers endangering them and yourself.
Federal and state help is on the way and we'll be ready for you when you're ready.
FEMA will do everything possible to help victims get back on their feet.
We'll be here as long as we're needed.
This message from FEMA Recovery Radio.
They pushed through the dispersing crowd and started walking rapidly down Canal Street.
They've made slight splashing sounds in the cold dusk, reflecting in the streets dampened by the light mist that had been falling steadily for some time.
We got us a big crowd on Burr but looked like we could have us a football game.
The irony involved caught my fancy, I must admit.
Something from Joseph Conrad sprang to my mind, although I cannot seem to remember what it was at the time.
Perhaps I likened myself to Kurtz in The Heart of Darkness,
when, far from home, I was in the middle of the desert.
Far from the trading company offices in Europe, he was faced with the ultimate horror.
I do remember imagining myself in a pith helmet and white linen jodhpurs, my face enigmatic behind a veil of mosquito netting.
When I was just a little boy, standing to my daddy's knee,
my papa said, don't you let the man get you, do what he's done to me,
cause it'll get ya, get it right now.
I could remember the fourth of July, running through the backwoods bay,
and I could still hear my old hound out the parkin', chasing down a hoodoo there,
just chasing down a hoodoo there.
Ballin' on the bayou.
I know these backwoods boys, they're another hand that scares me, man.
Ah, child.
What?
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
We need help.
Really?
We want help! We want help!
Metropolitan area, people are stranded, and people are trying to reach them now.
Help! Help! Let me out of here! I know you're out there! Yes!
Why isn't anybody doing anything? I know you're out there! I can hear you screaming!
We'll do all our power to help.
Oh, yeah, right.
No, seriously.
Yes.
There ain't nobody that would lend me a helping hand.
I'm searching for help all over this land.
I'm stuck in the mud, y'all.
Oh, Lord, and I just can't seem to get out.
I'm having trouble, and I'm having such a whole lot, y'all.
And it's beyond, oh, beyond the shadow of doubt.
I don't think you know what I'm talking about, listen.
I'm going everywhere where there is something free.
But I can't seem to find no one, no one who wants to help me.
I'm stuck in the mud, y'all.
Oh, Lord, and I just can't seem to get out.
I'm having trouble, and I'm having such a whole lot, y'all.
And it's beyond, oh, beyond the shadow of doubt.
I don't think you know what I'm talking about, listen.
What's up, man?
Bad house!
Bad house.
It's terrible.
Fallen to pieces.
And people here should know that it's a bad house.
I've had to do this forever.
Can you tell me what that means?
That's your car.
That's a good news truck, isn't it?
Is it?
I got my Sondheim S 500 Eco-Sities.
Four notice signs are going around everybody.
I've got a V IPS out and there's the S 50 Ecovite on the back.
Looks more like, like I love this stuff.
The pilot, yeah, he's in the back.
Wow.
Yes.
Oh man, I just wish we could see their tears.
Nobody's coming to get us.
Everybody's promised.
It brings a tear
into my eyes
when I begin
to realize
I cried so much
since you've been gone.
I guess I'll come
and my heart will tear.
I'll sing
and cry
just like a child.
My pouring tears
are running wild
if you don't think
you'll be home soon.
I guess I'll drown
oh yes
in my own tears.
I know it's true
into each life.
Oh, some rain
rain must pour
into my eyes.
I am so blue
here without you.
Here without you.
It keeps raining
more and more.
I am blue.
Come on.
Oh, yes.
Oh, I won't
be all alone.
If you don't think
you'll be home soon.
I guess I'll
die in trial.
Oh, don't let me in.
Drown in my own tears.
When I'm in trouble, baby.
Oh, yeah, me.
And don't let me in.
Drown in my own tears.
I guess I'll drown
in my own tears.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh!
I'll drown in gimmick.
And don't let me in!
And don't let me in.
Why?
Senor, come on.
You just keep going on
Come on!
There ain't, I just can't breathe!
Yeah, he's alive!
Shrek!
Are you all right?
Oh, my God!
Your
All Mitt's
of these patients up here uh thinking that we were going to have this rapid fire evacuation
with choppers jumping down etc already all lined up all triage and then the feds apparently pulled
the plug warning power failure oh no yes i i i i uh be assured we'll do everything that is
humanly possible this is a matter which involves the military strength of our country this could
be bad advice
i'm enlisting
help with the mate
get the expert
a mademoiselle
he could diffuse
any but share if i could only be tough like him then i could win my own small battle of sexes
and sergeant lock is going to have a good time
the final hour is approaching for the people of earth hear this you are to command the forces
that mop up no one must survive you are to seek out and kill every human being
by your command
because it's true in the dark uh fight for the weapon the weapon went off and you got one of our
guardsmen in the leg
the police won't even stop and turn to nobody
unleash the mighty united states military and they have not let us down
fire
help it's a takeover it's a violation of the constitution i mean you can't keep up with the
number of rumors spreading
so fast unless you hear this directly from law enforcement or us then you know don't give any
validity to this because it's creating a lot of problems better look out there ain't no explosion
during the tug valley floods of 1963 residents of the black gym area of palm creek in pike county
were being evacuated by a norfolk
western engine one of the women residents who had had to move during many floods in the past
was overheard to say another flood like that will do us in this is the fema radio news service do you
know that your homeowner's insurance doesn't cover flood damage prepare find out if your property is
at risk and what your options are to avoid financial losses get flood insurance before a storm strikes
that's great another rise on palm creek another inch of rain another foot of water
we ain't got no flood protection not a sandbag can be found we've lost all our possessions and
that's tree and dog just drowned and she drowned nobody's coming together why couldn't they drop
the 3 000 pound sandbags they said it was some pulleys that they had to manufacture but you know
in a state of emergency man you you you are creative you figure out ways to get stuff done
then they told me that they went overnight and they said they're not going to do it again and
they built 17 17 concrete structures and they had to pull his on them and they were going to drop
them i flew over that thing yesterday and it's in the same shape that it was after the storm hit
there is nothing happening and they're feeding the public a line of bull and it's spinning
and people are dying down here i will make brief answers they have no hope of death
but a blind life so
they envy any other thing please kill me all right i'll give you your chance
oh my god
nobody's coming together everybody's promised nobody's coming together so the next time you
see him shoot him a smile that was shooting going on that was sniping going on this is
this is
put this series you all have to and you too too many of us you are i'm a bit stuck with
our
finishing
today
well
okay
The rest of the world is unfair to the Americans.
Do you remember the last time a Korean family adopted an American child?
Did you ever receive a care package from Pakistan?
The United States has sent millions of dollars in clothing abroad.
And now, while young people are running around naked on their college campuses,
has anybody sent them a pair of shorts?
Oh, Dad.
Nobody ever helps the Americans.
Nobody would even lend me one gallon of gas.
Nobody helped.
If you need any help with your coffee, call me.
What am I going to do about it?
Well, all I need is the moonshine and someone playing the harmonica.
And I'm as happy as a pigeon's flop.
Holy smokes!
What a mess.
So look out for me.
Oh, buddy.
I'm going to the water.
Your mysteries are deep and wide.
And I've got a need for going somewhere.
And I've got a need to climb upon your back and ride.
A ride.
Now that's a good idea.
Come on.
We're going to go for a joyride.
Joyride.
What the?
Yeah!
Yes!
Good!
Whatever's been in there, it's been in there for years.
We've been swimming in it.
We've been playing in it.
And we've been swallowing it.
Oh, how awful.
We traveled on through a great arc of swamp between that slough and the dry valley.
All the while with eyes turned towards those who swallow the much below.
I shall perhaps recount that pilgrimage through the swamps.
A journey into the desert from which I returned broken physically, mentally, and spiritually.
Is anyone here not a downer?
Anyone?
Redoomed.
Leaving New Orleans also frightened me considerably.
Outside of the city limits, the heart of darkness, the true wasteland begins.
What's the matter, honey?
Are you lost?
I'm looking for my sister, Stella.
My name is Blanche Dubois.
I thought my life would be a Mardi Gras.
A never-ending party.
Ha!
I'm a faded southern dame without a dime.
Okay.
Let's get cleaned up.
I need a drink before the bar is closed.
Where in the world did he come from?
He's truly mad.
Not even vaguely attractive.
Look!
What's that?
This is a public service message from people.
Okay.
I mean, I understand the anxiety people can grab.
So there is frustration.
But I want people to know there's a lot of help coming.
Help!
Help, I need help!
This is a public service message from people.
Help!
Okay.
I mean, I understand.
This thing's gonna die, man.
This thing's gonna die.
Look for me when you see me coming.
I may be running.
I don't know.
I may be tired and running.
I may be having fever.
But I'll be headed south to the mouth of the Ohio.
So look out for me.
Full mud and water.
Your mysteries are deep and wide.
And I gotta meet the far-going sun with you.
And I gotta meet the time upon your back and ride.
Bitch, I'll f*** your ass up.
Yeah!
Woo!
You!
And the people!
You and me!
We sweat and slay.
Body all ached and loud.
Wrack with pain.
Toad the barge.
Lift that bale.
You get a little drunk and you land in jail.
Oh!
Keep a-weary.
Sick of trying.
Tired of living.
Freedom's dying.
Oh!
My liver keeps on running a-long.
Martha!
The horror.
Don't you worry.
We're leaving.
We certainly are.
Now get in this go-cart and get us out of here.
Wait!
I mean, first of all, understand that when you do have to leave, make sure you have the
kinds of things you want.
The things in the car that you're going to need.
Cash.
Medicine.
Hold on.
I left a lot of tablets behind, she said and ran into the house.
She came down the steps with another load and stopped on the brick sidewalk, turning
to look at the house.
Ignatius could tell that she was attempting to record the scene.
Eliza crossing the ice with a particularly large subgenius in her arms.
Now my nerves are totally frayed.
We better get out of here, baby.
She slid into the front seat and started the car.
We're going to have to go.
Where do you want to spend the night?
Spend the night?
We're not spending the night anywhere.
We must drive straight.
I've been in this car since yesterday morning.
I'm about to drop dead.
Well, get across Lake Pontchartrain at least.
Okay.
We can take the causeway and stop in Mandeville.
No!
We can't stop there.
The water's polluted.
They're having an epidemic.
Barges are always huddling into that causeway.
Then I'll take the old bridge to Slidell.
Yes, it's far south.
This is not a safe course.
There's no road .
This is obviously some strange usage of the word safe that I wasn't previously aware
of.
Let's get out of here.
Quick.
No, no, no.
I need a place to stay.
I need another day.
My soul is lost.
It's lost, it's lost its way. It's been living in this lost, this lost highway.
No, no, no, no. No, no.
Where are you going?
I thought we'd make better time by taking this blue highway I found on the map.
The river.
We'll plunge into the lake and drown.
Just run.
This is a public service message from people.
I understand the anxiety people have.
But I want people to know there's a lot of help coming.
This is a public service message from people.
I understand the anxiety people have.
I think that I'm beginning to bloat.
Even the river has bodies floating.
But you tell me.
And over and over again, my friend.
How you don't believe we're on the eve of destruction.
I take responsibility.
Not.
You have been listening to Hour of Slack number 1029,
which is really Bob's Slack Time Funhouse by Reverend Susie the Floozy on Atlanta's WREK,
which is always on.
And...
And streaming from WREK.org.
The music in the background is by Ego Club with EbolaMusic.com.
For morons of the Church of the Subgenius, see www.subgenius.com.
Praise Bob!