Just listening to what I'm telling you now can be the turning point in your life.
This is Doug Smith, radio operator. I'm going to bring you a piece of that green cheese for sure.
No trouble. Just get set and get going.
According, everything's going fine. No trouble.
Bob?
The message is now part of and registered in your subconscious mind.
Welcome to the Subgenius Radio Ministry.
Hour of Slack. Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
This is Reverend Ivan Stang, sacred scribe of the First Orthodox Megafist Temple Lodge of the Church of the Subgenius.
Before the sermon, a message concerning Bob Dobbs, living avatar of Slack and saint of sales on planet Earth.
The idea that America or any country values individuality as the highest ideal is a cheap myth.
Everybody's an individualist, but they don't like individuals.
Perhaps in simpler times it was true, but no modern industrial death culture can really afford a population of unpredictables.
This shouldn't surprise you.
The long history of persecution by the conspirators...
...as he goes back for generations untold.
Subgeniuses come from a better world and they're going to a better world.
They descended from abominable snowmen and will evolve overnight on some evening in late 1998 into overmen and overwomen.
It is an unbroken line of continuous change as opposed to that of pinks who are an evolutionary dead end and have been spinning their wheels as mere humans for the last million years or so.
I think it's a real nightmare that right now when you open a science book you'll find creationism.
You'll find evolution on one page.
But where's the page on where subgeniuses came from?
Hey it's me, Buck.
I'm not really here.
But through the magic of the automotive tape deck studio you can hear us now.
That's right.
Friends, we're once again we're live on the air while driving a car.
We're eating a prop, driving and doing a radio show all at the same time.
Even though it's illegal in the state.
The state of Texas to eat on a prop stick while you're driving and doing a KNIS show.
And I've got the...
Oh and by the way, this is a public service announcement.
We can do a traffic report now since we're mobile.
Oh that's true.
And what neighborhood are we in?
Traffic on Wycliffe rolling south through Oaklawn past Hall Street is light.
There's only two other, three other cars I should say.
A couple speedy cars and one very nice Plymouth Valiant with a lot of people in it.
I'd say there's about, all about nine cars.
Eight revelers and one little Plymouth Valiant.
And all the lights are on in this car.
That's right.
And we're going by a fellow reverend's home.
We're heading for Reverend Moore's house to pick up a video deck.
A stolen video deck that we're going to sell for money for the church for the home for slackless children.
And while we're visiting with Reverend Moore, while we'll just put a tape on here in the car.
And you'll, we'll be able to hear this beautiful media branch tape and these lovely songs.
By these obscure stars that you'll wish you knew who they were.
And you can call them.
Do you wear designer jeans?
Do you feel alike in your teens?
Are you more than a man of means?
Is everything less than rough?
Are you middle class enough?
I have five monsters in my family.
And we all have a lot of fun.
Two fairy sisters.
Scary husband.
Fancy wife.
And hairy son.
That's me.
But you're dead as a beaver hat.
They're gonna think you're insane.
If you have a chance of dying, you're dead.
So these people want to hypnotize us into cutting their brains out with chainsaws.
I mean, if people, if people psychically will us to beat their ass, I mean, I don't see how we're responsible.
I mean, I don't see how we're responsible.
This is Boston's subgenius boot camp.
Drinking coffee and staying awake.
Stand up there.
Here, stand out in the rain and keep awake.
Here, have some old Bob Cologne.
Do you call yourself a subgenius coming to drill with a beard?
That's two demerits.
All right, Mr. Hughes.
Three more demerits and I'll get that new baseball glove.
Look at the knees of your uniform pants.
That's disgusting.
I'm docking you five more demerits, Mr. Hughes.
Oh, gosh, gosh, get a new car.
What are you smiling about?
I hate Bob.
My Bob made my daddy go crazy.
My daddy used to make money, but now he just sits around all day.
I hate Bob. He's a bad man. I wish he would die.
This is part of the conspiracy.
It would appear that the government at the moment
is practicing a lot of this religion in absentia for many folks.
It was a trendy thing.
We're actually the conspiracy.
You've always heard of the conspiracy, right?
Yeah.
Well, we're the conspiracy behind the conspiracy.
We've decided to come out in the open.
You're the unnamed.
We're the unnamed source.
That's us.
One of them.
Well, you've certainly heard of the Public Creatinization Society.
And now learning to apply creative and corrective procedures
and to bring back to normalcy and a state of perfection
any abnormality or imperfection found within any given manifestation of matter,
any given plane, any given depth.
I can easily do anything that I want to do.
I can.
I'm a winner.
Pursuant to Section 28A, Article 4B,
paragraph 2 of the Internal Security Regulations,
I now hand over to you rejected applicator number 578293BO21.
And so white on his face.
Hey, I'm going to Margo to get paid.
I hate myself.
I hate everyone else.
I'm going to die.
Can you hear me?
What the heck is going on out here anyway?
I need to talk to Bob.
Bob.
There is no typical subgenius.
There's no profile subgenius.
The subgenius is the person who is an outsider,
who has been different somewhere or another since birth,
a person who was born with slack,
and we're all born with slack.
Original slack.
Original slack,
but the conspiracy,
the conspiracy of normalcy, really,
is what it is.
It takes it away from the minute you are born.
They give you that first whack,
on your behind to make you cry. From that moment on they're taking away your slack.
He was alive one minute, then he was dead.
Why not?
There must have been a reason they couldn't just barge in here and drag him away.
No reason.
What right do they have?
Stretch 22.
That's right, you're all fired.
You can kill yourself off or not.
Don't make no difference to us.
There's nothing you can do about it.
Oh, faceless surgeons, our new razors cut out our imagination.
Ah!
Yes, they creep up on you.
Conspiracy bugs.
Conspiracy bugs, they creep up on you.
They breed fast, don't you see?
And also, they don't need much to live on.
Just a constant supply of mindless entertainment and food and false slack.
That's all they need.
And false slack is so much easier.
It's so much easier to get than real slack, my friend.
So much easier.
All you have to do is work a 9-to-5 job.
Or, you know, the equivalent, whatever you do.
You know, it doesn't have to be a 9-to-5.
You can be your own boss, entrepreneur, whatever.
It doesn't matter how you get the money.
But the money can buy, can, can, false slack can only be had for money.
Ah, true slack.
True slack can be had for money.
But you've got to have, you've got to have a, a slack, a slack awareness, my friend.
More than you need money.
You don't need money.
You don't have to have money to have true slack.
And that is the God's truth.
Oh, no. I'm dreaming.
None of this is true.
I think it's my bad.
It doesn't work that way.
They don't know that this is a conspiracy.
This is for real.
They're agnostic.
They don't know.
They have to see it in front of them before they know.
Yeah, they have to see it.
And even then they deny it.
The thing is, is that these people are real.
And the pinks are the ones who actually do not exist, because they're not awake enough
to actually have consciousness.
They haven't turned into a dog yet.
They're not, they're not, they're just things.
They're, they're just, they're tubes to be filled with video images.
They're shadows.
They're spirits, but they're not, they're not real.
By recreating body and mind out of remembered fragments, I was to program my own inferno.
Good God.
Well, he certainly lost his mind.
Listen.
In effect, my soul was a monstrous cancer, continually creating within itself the means
of my destruction.
And I'm not saying that I'm not.
I'm not saying that I'm not.
You learned, you've been through the process of being a lost soul, a lost soul, a lost soul
is one that no longer controls its own circuitry.
The virus has been taken over by the enemy, which uses it to destroy me, to destroy you.
The sensation is like spontaneous combustion.
Ah, I should've taken it off the hook.
Oh, let it ring.
Andy, take a message, would you, and leave it off the hook?
Yeah, OK, OK.
I'll get it.
Go on then, Randy, go on.
It is this control of the circuitry,
this ability to send phantom signals to real bodies
through their remembered images,
like pins stuck in a doll,
that gives hell its power on earth.
Hell is not a place,
but a system for disrupting the plans of God.
She thinks you can cure the world by kindness and rules,
but it's too small.
The Lord's Prayer on a pinhead.
Some make rules, some obey,
but the rules are for the fools, is what I say.
The system makes me sick.
I wear the wrong clothes, I ask the wrong things.
You know I can't dance my feet off much, do I?
Who thinks you set the trends?
You wear your head straight, your clothes are out of sight.
Your house is modern, really kitsch,
you got it so macho in there, bitch.
I feel like I'm in a club,
I'm going to work.
I see them go to sleep.
I see them on TV.
I see them laugh and cry.
I'm on the outside.
It happens.
Look around you.
Look all around you.
The rude clerks in stores that hate their job
and take it out on you.
The thing about the normals is that they
conceptualize themselves to be
hot sinus effluvia on silver platters,
but in reality,
they reveal themselves to be cold mucus
encrustation on a paper plate.
But that's the way religion is.
It's been a constant battle since the very beginning.
The first man to try to guess why he climbed out of the slime
was the first man to pick up a stick and hit his brother.
We've been programmed.
This is the very beginning.
Our slack was taken away the moment we entered this world
where he's treadmill.
And we've been running like little,
rat through a maze.
And the only way you can get away from that is to deprogram.
Edit your own memory.
Take those bad memories.
Take those horrible training regimens that you were subjected to as a youth.
Flush them down the toilet as you excremeditate.
Let me ask you.
Yes, sister.
Did you ever own a guinea pig?
I ate my guinea pigs.
I grew them and I ate them.
That's dick, Craig.
They were food.
I'm a carnivore.
I can't help myself.
Kids need slack, too.
No, the guinea pig is so difficult to remove.
Doctor, doctor, here.
Take some more of this.
Have some of that.
Maybe the show will finish and we'll get to make another tape.
Oh, no. More prescriptions again.
I don't know if I can keep up with all these prescriptions and all these collars.
Do it, doctor.
It's good for you.
I'll take care of the collars.
Fake shows.
I'll take care of the fake collars on the fake show.
Oh, my God. This is a genius thing.
It's more than that.
Just take the pills, doctor.
I can't.
I don't think I can keep up with it.
I mean, it's like there's too much of it.
Pull yourself together, doctor.
These letters that come in the mail.
These weird magazines.
These characters that show up at the door.
Doctor, take your medication.
These bobbies.
They want to know things.
They want to know how to run their lives.
What should I do?
What's the worst thing about this?
About my girlfriend?
My girlfriend that wouldn't want me to worship?
What should I do, man?
Relax.
Relax, doctor.
I'll tell you what you should do.
It's like, doctor, you should do this.
No head launching, doctor.
Oh.
Take the pills.
Light the fire.
Oh.
Try some of this false slack.
But we can't talk about that because it would leave this station open to libel and slander.
That's our lawyer now.
Oh, my God.
He's here.
Gee, I feel much better now.
Oh, man.
I'm sorry.
I have to go.
Okay, bye-bye.
Bye-bye, открыz heading.
Bye-bye.
Hello, hey, I got thumbs on that one.
But I'll kick your ass and then throw up the whole fucking place, but I'm fine.
It makes me a little more lips in a round.
Whoa-oh.
I think you're driving me nuts.
Oh, man.
Go on, pop some cigarettes.
You don't have the t»
Now that's what I call soul!
Let me try some of that.
Jesus, that must have been a fairly intelligent normal.
Oh no, that wasn't a normal, that was...
God, I think I got some of his memories off of that.
Wow! Yeah!
It's like I'm seeing this little woman in the 40s, just for a second.
That's probably the guy's mom.
Yeah.
God, you can snort their souls and these little primal memories come in.
You've just got to give them final unction and dry them out first.
God, how long have you guys known about this?
I mean, was this something the Indians had down there?
Yeah, yeah.
It's too rainy to light a fire to smoke a soul a lot of times,
so they just dry it and keep it with volcanic rock as an absorbent.
Oh, yeah.
And they just grind it up and snort it through huge, huge caves.
But they didn't have the technology to extract souls.
I mean, how'd they get them under pressure?
How'd they get them into the canisters?
They don't do it that way.
They just feed them the right amount of herbs and plants
and the soul just drips out of the nasal and anal and...
You're kidding!
No, it just...
Why can't we do that?
We can if we've got the right pills.
It's kind of, you know, it's all organic.
I mean, you know, there's two ways you can extract.
You can go high technology,
or you can go with just kerosene and a couple of guys with bare hands.
Why did Bob set up these extraction machines?
Well, all you gotta do is you dig a little pit.
You dig a little pit in the ground, you line it with plastic,
peg down with wood, and then you put the body in.
A normal, right?
Yeah.
Any normal?
Any normal.
Any normal that isn't dead yet.
The stole is still in him, right?
Okay, then you cover him with kerosene and acetone,
and then you just jump up and down on him until it turns kind of green and thick.
Then you remove him, strain the liquid, then you boil it, and you add sulfuric acid.
But then there's some kind of ritualistic...
I mean, what actually causes the transmutation?
Well, there's a group of people around the pit adding a psychic element of the alchemy, you see.
That's...
They concentrate.
Oh, yeah, because they don't have the soul amplifier.
Right.
So it's just done with psychic methods.
Oh, man.
And then, after it's boiled...
God, that's incredible.
After it's boiled, they add...
A bunch of Brazilian tribal jungle people...
Ambulibians.
Both.
They both do it.
In the lowlands on both sides there.
And then you boil...
They boil the soul.
They actually boil the soul.
Little comba souls.
Yeah.
They boil...
And little coya souls, too, you know?
And they boil them, and then when it starts to thicken, they add another liquid.
It's some kind of corrosive, I believe.
And then it turns into a thick white paste, and they just spread the soul.
They just roll out into the sun, and it dries, and then you just have to chop it up.
They'd probably think we were idiots for crystallizing them and compressing them.
Yeah.
I mean, it's...
I mean, it probably doesn't cost them...
You know, it costs them a couple of necklaces or a, you know, a taper.
Well, they don't need electricity to do it.
That's the thing.
Their pet taper.
Yeah.
Well, going...
The most expense they've got.
And it costs us a hundred grand a year to keep these things pumping along.
Well, you see, we use a lot of...
And not to mention the bodies and the souls and the...
Getting rid of them.
Well, that's the thing.
See, the body dissolves.
Storing them.
The body dissolves in the solution completely.
Well, do you do up the body, too?
No, they just strain it out with a solid waste.
What do they do with that?
With that?
They put it on the...
They press it into little cakes and burn it, like for fires and stuff like that.
They usually give it back to the guy's family.
How come the...
How come they...
How come this was...
Like, how come the Western civilization didn't discover that?
Well, you see, it's because...
How come they haven't been ripped off yet?
How come we didn't rip them off?
Well, because we can pay for soul and get it a lot cheaper from them than doing it up
here because, you know, like down there, nobody complains if you go through four or five hundred
bodies in one night, you know?
You can sit around and smoke all the soul you want to.
Yeah, I guess it would be kind of questionable to...
They got a lot more soul...
To be digging pits in your backyard and throwing normal bodies in there.
Well, it's just little pressed cakes.
Noisy, if nothing else.
It's just little pressed cakes.
Most people barbecue on them later, you know?
Well, the senator got indicted.
Bob never forgot him.
You see?
Well, and then we've got to give half of them away to the...
Whatever, wherever they're taking on Jupiter.
Well, of course, the thing about a lot of...
That weirds me out, man.
A lot of things weird me out.
The fact is that you can't get any good soul here in the States, dry or liquid.
It's always been cut with something.
And I like my soul unstepped on myself, you know?
Oh, yeah.
They'll use monkey souls, chimpanzee souls.
Hell, they just take up crystallized...
There's probably two-thirds...
They just take crystallized emotions and mix them in, for God's sake.
I mean, you get a bad blast of rage mixed in with your soul, and the next thing you know, man, you...
That's probably what happened to me last week.
They put a lot of anguish in it, too, you know?
It just makes you depressed.
Where it's...
Pure soul is nothing more than a psychic and, you know, almanic amplifier.
And, you know, if your soul's in good shape when you do pure soul, I mean, it's even better.
But, you know, like, you put...
The stuff that's been stepped on and...
Mixed with monkey soul or alligator...
Yeah, next thing you know, your soul is...
It's tainted.
Very tainted.
Got holes eaten through it, you know?
Man, I wonder if that's what happened to Jane or...
What happened to Jane or?
Yeah.
Jane or shoots soul.
Oh, no.
He's all...
I mean...
He's back there firing it.
He magnetized my Palmer head.
He calls it.
Yeah.
Hey, you need to give me some of that re-magnetized Palmer head.
I won't do any demagnetized Trevino head.
See, that's a problem with Jane or is doing it.
That Palmer head, you know, it was not a good molecule to begin with.
And, you know, he's just synthesizing more and more of bad stuff.
Mm.
And making it purer and purer.
And each time he makes it purer, it's more pure bad.
Mm.
That's his basic problem.
Running up demagnetized soul, bad golfer souls.
Yeah.
Can you imagine?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I made Monday our
day.
Sadie don't believe me, she's pretty sexless
Who knows what else is the image of me?
I make my friends, I make my friends
I dance with David, dance with David
I make the world a place where she makes me play
I'm a sign to the tower of my kind
And forever I will say what I will not believe
I'm a sign to the way you just became a slave
And I'm a sign to the way to be
I'm a sign to the way to be
I'm a sign to the tower of my kind
And forever I will say what I will not believe
I'm a sign to the way you just became a slave
And I'm a sign to the way to be
I'm a sign to the way to be
And I'm a sign to the dis hobby
And I'm a sign to the way to be
And I remember
I still have to live
Yeah, I mean I know how it works
But I'm not sure if you got my head on it
Why didn't I know better
Manager!
Uh-huh
I heard in the other building
writer
I'm not sure I didn't know
The fuck did I think of that?
I fell for that
That I knew
My baby!
My baby! My baby!
Perrier hairspray
Waterbeds for two
Jogging elf foods
And lots of social good
Khaki pants
White shirts with those alligators
Mercedes Benz
How about tennis slater?
Twins
Red bull
You'll never know
Where the subdues beach party is
And don't you wish you did
Oh dear that dingy
Well Dr. Howell is there any way you can fight through the sound effects
And tell us about their relationship
Between the demopods and the ussopods
Well the demopods and the myriapods got together
Demopods and ussopods?
Oh the demopods
I didn't understand that
I thought you meant this script right here
The one with the red lines on the cover
Listen never read anything with red dots
I never believe anything with red dots
It says read addresses that people don't like on the show
Too many buttons to push
Too many tape recorders to watch
It was obvious that during the game
They should not have launched ahead with that size of rocket
They should have used a smaller rocket
Not hurt so many people
Some perhaps but not so many
As it turned out JFK was turning to Governor Connolly
To tell him the name of the band
That dare not speak his name
And was shot because of that
Thank you for your input caller
What does it sound like where you are?
What is weird?
It's a weird DJ dressed up in a crown of thorns
And a dirty
Dirty sheet
Starts kissing on you
I
And don't forget
Come on
Oh hi
I just wanted to remind you that the elementary school kids
Are coming in for their annual tour
And this year try not to scare them will you
All that making faces through the control room window
And wearing your toupee sideways
Didn't do us any good you know
Some of the teachers insist you're an idiot
It's ho for horse
Or meth or green
To spark a swinging mood
While the rats run up my trouser legs
Roaches share my food
Rats and roaches
Nuzzle me
When it's dark and hot
Love love it's all the same
Mixing speed and part
First a rat and then a roach
Or both a rat and then a roach
Both as like as not
If I can't find a fix tonight
My marrow bones will rot
Goodbye transcendent
Pumpkin square
I haven't long to stay
A double jolt of heroin
And I'll be on my way
Let's
Ah yes dear friends here we are
At home
At uh on the airwaves
This is Reverend Ivan Stang
With Dr. G Gordon Gordon
And
I'm going to stop and explain just
In credit at least we can't ever explain
Who those fools making those weird noises were
That we were playing on your radio
Let's see the music started off
With a band called They Might Be Giants
Which Reverend Bleepo Abernathy
In Boston has been sending tapes of
You'll hear them every now
And then
But uh quite a bit of their
Was
The um the show
Less than an hour
Or less than a show more than an hour
And then they send
The Berkley Show
Puzzling evidence Dr. Gary Gbrog-Fran
Dr. Howell
And um various insidious guests
Mobius Rex and so forth
And evil subgeniuses
Intermixed with a uh
A tape from uh
Bishop Huey of Houston
The Bishop of Archbishop of Houston
On uh a sister station down there
He sends these tapes that
Are always labeled collages from hell
Of volumes nineteen
Through forty
So
Dear friends once again as we saw
Uh we come to the end
Of this side of the show
Once again you'll have to
Turn your radio over
Flip it so that you can hear the rest
This is the subgenius radio ministry
Hour of Slack
Ah yes dear friends
This is old
Reverend Stang in the year of
Twenty twenty
Explaining that we're listening to
An even older
Show from nineteen eighty five
This is Hour of Slack
Number six
Uh with a lot of G. Gordon
Gordon involved
Yes Claudia
That's right
Everything's okay
Uh otherwise you could
Call this Hour of Slack
Number one thousand seven hundred and
Ninety nine but it just makes me
So tired to even think about
That
Right Claudia
I can't believe you're
Talking about
The radio show
Uh yes dear friends
We're back and boy
It's getting tough doing these
Shows night after night after night
It's easy for you
You only have to listen once a week
But we do ten shows a day
We have to keep up
Stay ahead
What is that noise
I have no idea I think it might be the
Exes on the outside of the hall
No no
Yeah I can hear the hiss
The air noise
We're still on the fringes of the atmosphere
You know that's just a few molecules
What happens if I push this button
What
Running up demagnetized
Oh you can hear us
What if we flip
Is that a whole week show there
Here we go
Up there went the mystery in the magic
Right there
Why did you have to say that
Time was missed
Hey is this that time magazine ad
About Vietnam
Yes it is
Jump ship before it's too late
A feast for the eye minded
We don't want to do that
I think he's right
He what do you mean he
No I used the term he
To describe all aliens that call the show
I don't think humans ever call
The show
If that's an it
What is that
If it's an it
I mean why not
The show was getting fixed
They were fixing the show
And nobody knew exactly where it would lead
Now subgenius publishing guides you through this intriguing realm
In a unique and spectacular family library
The book of the subgenius
Here we go
Up there went the mystery in the magic
Right there
Why did you have to say that
Well Gary we just thought we'd say it
There went the mystery in the magic
Yeah it's all over the place
You use a million gigawatts of electricity to extract souls up here,
the energy is released psychoactively and with simple chemicals down there.
And we never freebase soul either.
I mean, that's really bad.
Just drinking it, that's all.
Drinking it and snorting it.
I like a little iced soul myself.
I like it best out of balloons, to tell the truth.
That is my favorite way of doing up some soul.
Yeah, tank soul is good stuff.
High-pressure tank soul, I like.
Just the pure stuff, straight out.
Straight out.
That's just, they cook it, you know, and then it turns into a gas.
And then they pump it under pressure.
They scrub it through dog meth filters and stuff like that to make sure,
because when you get it into that excited state,
every little part of the soul separates from every other,
so you get little pockets of, you know, stuff that was like childhood dogma rammed into you.
So they scrub that all out.
So it becomes, it's the most pure form in gaseous form.
Oh, yeah, but the only problem is that, you know,
the people that end up banging their head against the wall all night long
because they can't stop, they're in such ecstasy or whatever.
People have fallen down the floor a lot.
Pure beingness.
The beingness.
The beingness of it, they, you know, makes them, for some reason, chew the ground.
Man, that's what I did.
That's how my jaw got messed up.
You know, you can tell someone's...
Woke up chewing the ground.
Yes.
Woke up chewing the...
I loved Mother Earth.
I woke up chewing the bathtub.
I made a big mess.
Yeah.
You can tell that the soul really affects people more in gaseous state
because the minute they speak, their voice isn't the same, you know.
Well, it goes directly, directly to the main gland.
Yeah.
I mean, it's...
It just diffuses in the blood so fast.
Put the Barry Manilow music on.
Here we go.
That's a scrambled signal.
We have not been able to figure this one out.
You can slow it down and it's like old TV shows,
but in between the lines are these even more,
these incredibly fast little, like, micro blips of sound
that we have not been able to stretch out enough.
Stretch them out?
Even, I mean, the best visual...
I mean, the space between the blips...
You can't slow it down enough.
Maybe the space is between the blips of the actual message.
Yeah, but we can't slow it down that much.
I mean, you can't differentiate.
The machines won't...
It's alien.
It is a truly alien signal.
It's there.
Play the music.
But...
Yeah, that was a great band, man.
I wonder whatever happened to them.
They're playing the hydrogen line now, I think.
Woo!
I think this is one of their...
The number's coming in right now on Channel 7.
Channel 7.
Cell phone rings.
The thing's frequency modulated.
It's got another burst in the ultraviolet that's recorded.
It's got digitally extended equalized components.
I mean, it's incredibly complex.
It's magic.
It's probably got a pamphlet coated in it.
No, they have their own pamphlets.
That's what I meant, their pamphlet.
Yeah.
I think it's definitely next to the same.
That's what scares me about it.
I mean, it would do to us what ours do to the little people.
Well, it's the way it is.
You know how it is.
There's only two guys you need to cop are little people.
You know what I'm saying?
Or skin jobs.
Yeah.
Take you out with me to hear what it's like outside where I live.
Notice you don't hear too many cars.
But you hear a lot of cars.
A lot of bugs and a lot of birds.
That was Bubba Gee.
Say hi to the people.
You care about your special friend, and it cares about you.
That's how the Care Bears came to be.
Just listen and turn the page when you hear the music box.
We've entered the final tribulation period.
I believe we'll know when it happens.
I don't know yet exactly how we'll know that it has happened.
But I believe with all my heart that when we get there, we're going to know it has happened.
The true believers will know because they know what the character of the final tribulation period is.
The final tribulation period is that time when no one else is being...
saved.
And when the church has become so apostate, the denominations and congregations,
it's almost impossible to find one that is left that is true to the word of God.
The day the world ended is here.
Shocking, terrifying horror.
See the world ended by atomic fury.
See the horrible mutant who seeks a mate.
See the terrifying beast on the ocean floor.
See the battle for life at the bottom of the sea.
Yes, see the fantastic world of...
Death and horror in the top shock show of all time.
Generic giant crab music with overlord Huey.
Food fights of the gods with your personal friend, Bishop Huey.
Well, this is your pal, Colonel Huey, and this is Nightcrawler's Lament.
I want you to talk like a horrible Texas trucker in no time.
Well, despite numerous protests from leading substantial citizens, here I am again,
your pal and temporary father figure, Mr. Huey with another danger run.
This is the club car and the hill-bound train.
Why it's called...
Shhh!
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh-oh-oh!
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh-oh-oh!
Shhh!
Don't forget, boy, look over your shoulder.
Cause there's always someone coming after you.
Oh-oh-oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh-oh-oh!
Sightly! Sightly!
Sightly!
Okay, it's about...
We are advancing constantly, and we're not interested in holding on to anything except the enemy.
We're going to hold on to him by the nose, and we're going to kick him in the ass.
We're going to kick the hell out of him all the time, and we're going to go through him like crap through a goose.
You have reached the correct number.
However, your call has already been analyzed and rejected.
This matter is out of our hands.
As soon as we are able to transcend the time problems inherent in life on Earth
and gain control of the situation, we will return you to your previously scheduled conversation.
If this had been an actual phone call, you would have been instructed to leave your name, number, time, and message when you hear the tone.
Thank you.
Somebody playing a duck.
This is oral fixation.
This is oral fixation, which is a bunch of members of the Severn Institute.
It's their selection of material that is the best thing.
And these guys play...
Uh...
On stage, they do this as a live show, but they don't actually sing.
They play the tape.
It's true.
Uh...
The drums are great!
This guy standing beside you...
Oh, my God!
Oh, my...
Oh...
Look at that monologue battle.
What?
This is real neo-psychedelic.
this is when after the day after this will be rock and roll you know this is a vision of our
future yeah well nothing electrical will work no no magnetic motor will work except tape decks
no the tape won't work nothing will work that isn't what and this is going to be rock and roll
after the apocalypse after the the the kiss the lightning kiss of wotan's judgment oh yes
yeah this is their breeze gentle breeze from wotan's armpit
oh no they're stuck
the cranes of greater baltimore
as related to uh the crank boys yeah they're part of the crank boys
yes sir if you want to get your heads milled at 4 45 in the morning
call the crank boy all crank boys that's now now now now yes in greater baltimore ask for doug zero
i hope they do it
i can't keep up with this stuff anymore look at all this trash it's too many shows it's uh
yeah we're gonna go to missouri for their show now we need some help from a thousand doctors
we need yes at least 1 000 doctors
once doctors for wotan this is dr phylo drummond and his and the band of now called swinging love
corpses or the cups a great neo-psychedelia band that started out once as doctors for wotan now
including other members such as sphinx drummond and that crazy ray hay oh ray wow guitarist
here we go
,
for
a
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
Where am I?
In the village.
What do you want?
Information.
Whose side are you on?
That would be telling.
We want information.
Information.
You won't get it.
By hook or by crook, we will.
How many more times do we have to listen?
How many more times do we have to hear the worst song ever?
This band is terrible too.
They just want to fall asleep.
Yeah, the audience is going in every different direction possible.
This.
Sick of them.
They're sick of the Cafe Depresso.
Yeah, they're sick of everything here.
They only know three chords, but you're only going to see them play one.
I'm so tired of these guys.
This band's bad.
It's no surprise.
I wish they'd just pack it up and go away.
They're not going to let us go.
They're going to never stop.
Well, how many times do we have to play this same song over and over and over again?
I'm going to die.
Well, Grta, Grta, Grta, oh, Grta, let me clean your toes with my mouth.
Sonny, if you want it, here it is.
Come and get it.
But you better hurry.
Because it's going fast.
You better hurry.
I told you that faulty autopilot module was going to give us some trouble sooner or later.
You got the whole damn side of the show caved in.
Oh, well, it's my cousin worked on it, see?
That was the problem.
I took it to my cousin instead of letting the Tibetans, the old experts, fix them.
Well, you know, we got to dock with the show in eight minutes and 32 seconds, show number four,
and look at that.
And if we run out of tape before that, then we won't be docking with nothing.
We'll be cast adrift in the airwaves.
No, if you're not on tape, friend, on the airwaves, you just, you're ripe for piracy.
Yes, indeed.
Airwave piracy.
They're bootlegging us right now.
Everything we say right now is being sold.
Sold somewhere.
Somewhere.
Being sucked out of the heavens, out of our orbital transmitter by some big old pirate
ground.
Of some big old British bootleggers.
Stinking bootleggers.
But they're gonna find out you can't bootleg Bob for too long.
You gotta pay your dues to Bob and the Foundation for Salvation, friends.
Any old Bob show, you just pirate and start sending around.
People are gonna start falling down and not remembering what they listened to and foaming
at the mouth and having strange hallucinations.
Yeah.
All kinds of excess buzzin' around their rooms.
Confusing.
Tap on their telephones.
Beating on their walls.
It can be difficult.
making their TV sets not work right,
and they're saying,
why me?
What did I do?
Yeah, you didn't pay your dues.
That's very, very interesting.
Very interesting.
That's not interesting at all.
I mean, that's why you may be wondering,
just why do I have to keep listening to this show?
Why do I even care what the answer could be?
Take your earphones off.
That's what I did.
You don't have to listen to me.
Deep down inside,
deep down inside, friends,
you know that this is
the truth.
The ultimate truth.
Amen.
Now the announcer will give our mailing address.
That's the church of the subgenius.
Write for information to P.O. Box.
807 Glen Rose, Texas 76043.