Men and women of all races and creeds pause to destroy the earth.
This is the story of the subgenius power of the sun.
It still seems warm, still living out its useful days.
It can adjust to circumstances. It can endure with an immortality all its own.
It can overcome obstacles, split rocks apart and travel far in search of water.
All across the American continent, thousands of people contribute to this journey.
They were known as nuts.
But let him who says this look into his own heart and produce for us a thought
that will warm the hearth of a friend or endure a thousand years.
I'll be joining you soon.
For more transcribed stories from the Reader's Digest, past and present.
But until then, this is Boris Karloff saying,
Praise Bob.
Bob.
We occasionally discuss the state of Bob.
I'm honored to have as a guest today a gentleman whose name is very well known, I think.
Obviously well known.
Bob, this gives me the heebie-jeebies.
Erks.
Look deeper and deeper.
We're discovering more and more things.
Well, wouldn't you want to drive it deeper?
Am I screwed up?
Absolutely.
Very, very deep.
My career did begin a year 1955.
You just gave me goosebumps.
Stopped at the grocery store and we picked up some baggies.
And so Bob could have something to dig.
Bob goes down on the levee, starts digging.
There's a swarm of mosquitoes around Bob.
And up on the top of the levee,
the wind's blowing.
Trip.
Bob.
You need to invite people in that don't think.
Bob, you know, Bob, you're just continuing to make a bunch of enemies.
And Bob, you can use a car to go out on a date.
Bob, where have you been and what have you been doing?
Bob, I can't thank you enough for sharing your time with us today.
And now, gang bangers.
Gang bangers.
Presented with federal police force throughout the United States.
History is.
Tonight, gang bangers presents the case of the fist.
Gang bangers is asked for less.
You stand accused of conspiring against Bob.
How do you respond?
I'm guilty.
There is only one punishment.
Fever, fever, scratchy throat, whatever, whatever.
Seems like a good source of protein.
I suggest you eat it.
I know.
Go, go, go, go.
Strip.
Yes.
Go on.
Show me.
Give them to me now.
Yes.
Silent, silent.
Ow, ow.
No.
This human.
No doubt.
Severe punishment.
I'd like a chance to defend myself.
He's distorting the truth.
What is this?
Doesn't matter what you believe.
A planet?
You're all perfectly happy to ignore what you don't want to hear.
Nothing like a good history lesson.
I have.
Irrelevant.
Any response?
Food processors failed.
So.
Nothing unusual.
Can you modify a torpedo?
How long?
So.
I'm sorry.
A little more information.
227 Mark 4.
4,000 meters.
3,000 meters.
2,000.
800 meters.
Not.
That is absurd.
Gas giants.
Yes.
Now.
All young people want to do is take up weapons.
As soon as they can hold them.
Six months.
A year.
A frozen cave.
Enough.
We're deep inside.
Oh, please.
You all right?
Perhaps I.
I'm ready.
Leave him alone.
You don't kick a man when he's down.
So.
Stupid.
It bend.
I.
Huh.
Playing my part.
Tongue.
Go.
Thank you.
L-e-t-rick my mother.
A baby stay wait.
Oh, oh, Oh, Oh.
No, no food to drink.
What are they?
Whoa.
You have never been just a circus than aLe Wiggy and ACним.
Wait, what?
I mean all the next you and your Lehrer played been people all the time.
So.
I felt that he had just a little too much pizzicato in the Andante.
Uh, didn't you?
No.
Good PR.
PR.
Lumpy and delicate like folding oatmeal.
The news.
From PR News in Washington, I'm mishandled.
Prime Minister Tony Blair supports PR News.
PR News.
PR's crude.
Wall Street closed, however, open today.
This is PR News.
PR's bad.
Authorities say they smashed into a park locomotive.
They found signs of PR News.
Authorities caused a fire and release of PR News in Washington.
Today is a day your life can happen at any time.
I was wiped out.
I fell out of the sky and went back.
I felt upside down.
Chicken soul for the soup.
One minute.
Soup.
Like.
Corporate downsizing, restructuring, and mergers.
We have to adjust.
Like.
Create anxiety.
So I thought for a while.
Not.
Like.
A man with enormous scope and powerful.
Sit back and relax.
However, be prepared to have something deep inside of you for the rest of your life.
Follow it.
Transforming life itself.
When he's the genius.
Sub.
In.
Us.
Sub.
In.
Us.
Sub.
In.
Us.
Sub.
And, uh.
I think we heard.
I think we're hearing brain rot in the background.
Yes, it's.
Or is that the CD?
That is.
Psychopath finder is a.
Emotional problem right there.
Old psychopath finder.
He found the path and then we lost our way.
What is it all about I wonder?
I mean, where am I going?
We're going to find brain unlimited.
But what does it all mean?
It means the search for higher intelligence.
A hundred thousand times our normal rate.
It means.
It's not just a rhetorical question.
It is.
Brain unlimited.
Why not?
We have the technology.
We have the medical knowhow.
Why can we not push the frontiers?
Push the envelope?
We have the plutonium bowling balls.
We have the chemicals.
We have the psychic spit wads.
We have the connecticated tissues.
We know something about something.
The brain works on a combination of electrochemistry.
And chemistroelectrons.
Something.
Oh, wait a minute.
Don't we have a.
And we know we're only using a teeny tiny bit of.
tiny, tiny, teeny amount of it.
Well, most of it's being used up
by the Hour of Slack contributors, friends,
such as Reverend Norrell Preff of norrellpreff.com,
who did so many of the collages that we heard
up until it got so noisy.
And from Mr. Fernandanande Lemur,
of course, who always puts the intros together.
And in this case, Reverend Maynard Brainard of Warren.
What is this noise in the background, man?
It's ripping my brain in half!
Oh, that was stopped just when I was about to get off.
God, I hate it when that happens.
See, that's a pluralistic orgasm,
when you have a democracy where everyone has an orgasm.
See, in your fascist theogony,
in your democratic regimes,
only the head imams, the feisty...
Why did he actually portray himself in it?
You just had to see.
You kind of just had to see what happened, wouldn't it?
He just almost got there,
and then the music stopped,
and, you know, it just wasn't annoying enough anymore
to be exciting.
But it is now, with the help of Zug's Rift
and the Rudy Schwartz Project in the background.
So, I guess,
what was in the news today?
Iran banned mullets or male eyebrow plucking
because that's all too Western.
Also, body piercing, fashionistic idioms.
Well, I don't think they even know about that yet.
Well, I shouldn't say that.
And, once again, reconnecting the tissue and the collagens
to create new faces and new heads.
This is one that's been a problem amongst the Persian Empire
for quite so many years now,
is the reproduction of inhuman faces.
To create a false carnival party atmosphere
during the Feast of Gorak,
which was not a Muslim saint or sage or prophet
or avatar type guy, or what do you call it?
Can we use those at our X-Day parties,
that face of Gorak or whatever you're talking about?
Oh, yeah.
It looks like the old nitrous oxygen,
nitrous oxide specked up.
Would you like to just walk up there
and fill up a balloon, perhaps?
Or if you had a homeostatic bag
you got from your grandmother's funeral.
Boy, those were the days.
My grandma had one of those nitrous oxide dispensers.
Right.
What a gas.
She was a gas, we used to say.
Her colon would expand at the same time.
Yeah, it was fun.
But then it became less fun when they were policed.
Remember those days when suddenly, you know,
thousands of one-armed guys would break into the room?
Well, we did discover that the hospital padlocked
the gate full of nitrous oxide canisters after that.
Just because of you?
After that one time, that one party.
Sad, sad day.
But this never happened to we.
They opened the doors for her and said,
come on and get your gas, baby.
But also in the news, the military has legalized
Dobbs Head tombstones, right?
And also pipes.
Or was it witch tombstones or something?
Yes, both.
You told me originally that the Wiccans
got their five-fingered stars.
They finally, after 15 years of fighting wars
against the VA, it was the Veterans Administration.
Well, what about the followers of Khaadu
and the Babylonians?
That refused to allow certain types of religious symbols
on the tombstones of fallen servicemen.
Of the extended middle fingers?
Because apparently some religions weren't good enough
to be displayed, even though the guy might have died for them,
or for the freedom to have those religions,
such as the much maligned Wiccan religion,
which, corny though it may be,
Is still a religion.
There's not a law in this country against believing
whatever kind of foolish nonsense you want to believe in.
That was part of the whole idea.
So of course, if a subgenius is unlucky enough to get drafted
or actually applies for the, as Dr. Leguim called it,
the worst job in the world.
That's a very small percentage of subgenius
actually apply for the job.
Well, actually, that's not true.
I've done quite a few subgeniuses with military backgrounds
who somehow survived and they didn't even know
how to get kicked out.
Some of them, like Leguim did.
See, all the guys I knew all got the old 4F,
or they were excluded from service for being...
No, some of them were career guys.
But if they died, up until recently,
they couldn't get a pentagram on their grave,
and they couldn't get a dob's head.
There was like a limited booklet of symbols
that you could have on your tombstone
if you were a dead soldier.
The pipe was also forbidden.
You couldn't have any of them until you were a dead soldier.
But once you were dead, then you could have whatever,
you know, thing represented your religion.
As long as your religion wasn't Wiccan or Bob
or anything kind of silly.
Was an approved religion is what you ought to say
if you're wearing diapers right now.
What do the atheist soldiers get?
They don't need any design.
It's like a little atom or a picco of a microscope or something.
I would say no design whatsoever.
No design, you know.
Well, that's the way it looks to me.
Or there could be a random pictograph of people slaughtering people.
Slaughtering each other with cheeses.
That's kind of a complicated graphic.
Well, it would be oblique enough for many of them to get it.
And they'd say, like, what's it all about?
Where am I going?
Oh, the Discordians would have a gold, a little apple.
Right.
And the Cornucopians would also have a...
What would the Unitarians have?
Do they have a logo?
Yes, they have a logo of a...
A one, a number one.
A cauldron, I believe it is.
A cauldron?
Why don't they just use a goat head?
Sorry, it's a chalice.
It's a chalice.
Oh.
A chalice.
One of those sea...
Is that what they're calling them now?
...religious sea words.
Yes, yes.
I was thinking of chalice.
It's the Eunice of Cripes, as they call it, in the lesser dogmatic religions.
That's the nice Unitarians.
It's actually considered the vessel of the Grail.
Unitarian Universalists.
The Grail vessel.
Or grain whiskey or something like that.
But it has to do with something being distilled into a small container and then whiffed by
the Orificer.
When my son was about 14 and saw...
Jesus Christ Superstar for the first time...
I thought you were gonna say...
...and started to get religion...
You sodomizing that religious picture.
He went and said, he said, Dad, Mom, I want to start going to a church.
And we went, oh God, oh no.
Isn't this one good enough?
Well, and he goes, so what church do you think I should go to?
Because I saw Jesus Christ Superstar and, you know, I have those feelings.
So we said, why don't you...
Oh, the Universalists.
I mean, the Unitarians.
Unitarians.
You love the Unitarians.
So I...
No, I mean a real church.
He could tell by the...
That we...
If we recommended it, that it wasn't gonna be what he was looking for.
It was a halfway...
So he decided to go...
...a pre-doctoral...
There was a Lutheran church down the road and he had us take him there and drop him
off.
And when I picked him up about three hours later, he said, Dad, it's...
It's...
It made me want to worship Satan.
He never went back to another church again.
And he realized, like Reverend Carter LeBlanc did, and so many others who saw Jesus Christ,
Jesus Christ Superstar, it wasn't God that got him feeling that way.
It was the rock and roll.
Meaning...
Meaning it was Satan.
And now they're playing Sympathy for the Deaf.
Right.
There...
So there you go.
And that's...
When...
But I'm not saying that Jesus don't rock.
And I ain't saying that Jehovah ain't the rock of ages.
But I'm saying that their fan club is taking some of the fun out of it in some situations.
I certainly wouldn't want to generalize.
That wouldn't be fair.
We subgeniuses are always fair.
Especially with all those different things you got growing out of the side of your head,
Stang.
What is up with that?
Well, I'm getting ready for X Day.
X Day is coming.
The pinks are bumming.
Really getting ready.
I'm sorry.
They're jangling.
I thought it was the things coming out of the side of your head.
They are.
These are X Day preparations.
They're like sparkling and making those sounds.
Oh, they make you look pretty.
Kind of like an...
I don't know.
Yvette Duggan's look.
How do you do that?
Or what's your...
What was her name?
Back in the 1980s.
1940s.
Now, speaking of tombstones...
Veronica Lake.
You look like a huge...
Never mind.
We were at Veronica Lakeview Cemetery yesterday.
Princess, we and I were.
We were urban spelunking, you might say.
Now, that's a fun graveyard to begin with because it's ancient and huge.
And all those Italian stone masons worked really hard on those huge...
Those big holes in the ground right nearby.
Those huge phallic symbols for the tombstones.
For all the great men who were planted in Cleveland.
But we...
Masonic symbols as well.
We wandered off the beaten path.
Actually, we looked down this...
Off of a little bridge and we saw this waterfall off down the creek in the distance.
You could hear the waterfall first.
Yeah.
And we went, let's sneak down there.
Well, Reverend Stang, to be honest, found a space that...
We found a little bridge.
A little bridge that wasn't roped off.
And it didn't say anything at all about not going there.
And it didn't say anything about keeping out.
In fact, there were a few old tombstones back there.
But there were voices.
You could hear rotting voices and absurd sounds in the background.
Well, we went back in and we found this idyllic, wonderful little pleasure area of limestone
waterfalls hidden right near Probability Field Road and near that ancient cemetery.
But it was so...
It was this beautiful, idyllic place.
Princess Wee, however, was paranoid and said, you know, this is probably unauthorized and
we're not supposed to be there.
And we later, as we came, found a road out, we discovered that it in fact was completely
an unauthorized area.
But...
Oh, so beautiful.
She was so paranoid.
She was going, well, we're going to get mugged.
Somebody's going to come down here and mug us.
And I laughed her off.
It was gorgeous, though.
As a paranoid, crazy woman.
Dave, however, has informed us that that little place where...
Oh, so beautiful.
...where I laughed at her about muggers was also known as Kingsbury Run, where which mass
murderer stashed his chopped up victims?
The mad butcher of Kingsbury Run.
Yes.
He was modeled a bit after Jack the Ripper.
He was supposedly the son or daughter with a medical background of a very wealthy, who
knows, could have been presidential family.
Oh, they all are.
All the serial killers are the children of kings and queens and presidents.
Well, he was taken care of quite well.
He was some big industrialist, I think, because they kept on getting letters from an insane
asylum years after saying, I am the mad butcher of Kingsbury Run.
But...
Why are you shaking your head?
Was I lying?
It's like that movie Sin City.
No, it's just that I had this premonition.
She was down there.
She had a premonition that this beautiful place might be dangerous.
And it turned out later that it had been dangerous for some butchered victim bodies.
Mostly homeless and prostitutal types or, you know, people who are...
Now, is that the same as the torso murderer of Cleveland?
I think it may be the torso murderers because the torsos were so eloquently disposed of.
Yes, I do think it is.
I'm not sure, but I think so.
How many mass murderers or serial killers has Cleveland had?
I don't know.
You remember the great East Ohio gas fire in 1940?
No, I'm sorry.
Now, there was another serial killer, another unoriginal copycat, lone nut, crazy guy.
Going berserk in another shopping mall today.
Now, you know, on some wonderful national holiday, there's going to be one in every shopping center.
I would love such an event.
It will all happen at once.
Dave, don't say that because...
It will happen.
It's like your Ouija board.
It will...
What is the thing?
If you say it...
If anything that two subgenius businessmen say will happen.
Yeah.
Now, that's the philosophy of synchro plus bad da da bullsh.
Aha!
Is that what it is or something like it or...
I'll take your word for that, Dave.
No, it's as you say it, so is it, moat, and you better stand back or you're going to be
smoked or something or...
I love the smell of the hunt and the taste of the shunt.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
The stunt.
The shunt.
No, that's something we society people do, Dave.
You wouldn't know about that.
Don't worry.
A shunting is what you...
You wouldn't enjoy it.
What is shunting?
It's...
What are you on about?
Oh, nothing, Dave.
Oh, that's the mad butcher once again, right?
And the guy was a shunter?
It's a society thing.
No, it's a society thing.
People in society, not you, Dave.
I know, but...
People in society, not you, Princess Wee.
What do they do?
Actually, Princess Wee is the ultimate...
But it's like another...
It's another...
Her royalty is on another system, another global system.
That's why her only handmen and footmaidens are me.
I see.
I'm a blue-blooded orangutan in another space.
I am quite blue.
Well, we can all say we're princes from some other planet, but she's the only one that
can prove it.
No, I've documented proof.
Which all you have to do is look at her and you can tell.
She looks like a child who was removed with forceps.
What do they call it?
A forceps baby?
You know, where they just clap those...
You know, that's not funny because a lot of people call you forceps head.
Did you know that?
Oh, of course.
I figured they would.
Because of those two dents, those depressions on either side of your temples.
They never went away.
They said they were going to go away.
Yeah, I know.
And there's thumbprints all over the top of his head where his dad thought, oh no,
it ain't going to stay.
He was disposing of excretia.
You ought to see my kid's head.
It's shaped like a dinosaur.
Your children's heads are shaped like dinosaurs?
Well, you know, I used to sculpt.
And when they were born, if you keep moving them...
So, therefore, I was thinking about Harryhausen as I was popular.
They have soft, they have real soft heads.
But they're not like the ones you see in the movies.
They'll form, they'll hold in position for a little while.
Oh, yeah, babies, for sure.
Yeah, you could do all kinds of things with babies.
Yeah, my son, when he was the first, like, day that he was alive, I was able to make
his head, the top of his head into like a little brontosaurus.
It didn't have a very long neck or tail, but you could tell it was supposed to be a dinosaur.
That's a good gag.
That really is.
20 years later, man, that is a great gag.
I couldn't make a triceratops.
Conehead, even a standard cone or pinhead is a great gag 20 years after the fact, you
know?
So...
It's a gift.
Guys, you're so messed up.
You are really seriously de-gagging.
It's a deeply messed up gift of the odious to the bloated.
You're familiest.
That's all relative.
What does messed up mean?
Does that mean, you know, running a society into the ground by human laziness?
Like any good art, it means something different to each listener.
Does mental illness...
Messed up.
What is that?
Exaggeration is the key to art, so mental illness is...
Does it mean you're a member of church's subgenius?
That's what some people think messed up means.
It's vagueness is its key.
It's insane.
Well, sometimes this key is lost and found in very, very unusual places with a lot of
hair and gum around it.
Eww.
So I don't know if that should be explored or even mapped.
Let's not and say we did.
Eww.
Yeah, I think it's a stupid idea to name yourself after a substandard form of anything or being.
I mean, where'd you get that idea, man?
You know, you're sitting around, you're in filer or like...
No, JR thought...
I mean, I think that Bob Dobbs was told of the existence of the subgeniuses by alien
entities or rather a collective mind calling itself variously Jehovah One, Wotan, Ra.
It's gone under many different names, but it was a hive mind from outer space which
informed Bob that there had been a conspiracy of normals stealing away the slack of the
abnormals, which were called subgeniuses.
Not because...
The artist's fist excludes you.
The fact of it is that intelligence has been misdefined for all of this time.
The conspiracy has misdefined intelligence.
And in fact, the lucky idiot twiddling his thumbs happily is a much more important creature
in the great plan of things than a clever mad scientist creating the latest deadly weapon.
Don't you see?
And so thus we find the peaceable, simple-minded subgeniuses.
Like Dave here.
Or more beloved by Bob than the brilliant mastermind such...
Well, I wouldn't want to point to anyone in the room, but...
You know, that's why as Wren said so astutely, they always love the stupid one best.
Everybody loves Curly and they'll...
And Larry, you know, he's pathetic, but nobody...
You don't really dislike him.
And everyone despises Moe.
Nobody likes Moe.
But Moe's the one that makes everything happen.
They despise him, Stan.
Yeah, sure, but we all despise him.
Secretly.
I am a Moe.
I know I am a Moe.
And when you were in class, when you were very young, you could hear people whispering
under their breath, they go, Moe.
And watch out or he'll...
What?
He'll smack you.
He'll try and pierce your eyes with his index and his other finger.
He will try and do something physically harmful to you.
That's why you were despised as a Moe.
Because you hurt the other children.
And you're still hurting adults now with this insane religion.
That's what's wrong with you.
You want to torture things.
If they can't take a joke, man, then I think you know what they can do.
I can't remember, but I think you know, man, what...
It has to do with mounting, I believe.
Something about mounting...
Let them mount up upon themselves if they can't not see the humor in it.
That's it.
That's the old Gaelic version.
Shakespeare.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
South Georgia is burning, I understand.
It's worse than a drought.
Because of God.
God sent a drought to the Georgians.
There's another great guy I'd like to slap one with.
Are you angry at God, Dave?
Who isn't angry at God?
He screwed us all.
Well, now he gave you life.
He called it...
He invented screwing.
He called it love, and it was actually subgenusoid hatred.
I can feel the...
You don't know anything.
Of course I don't.
And what about hot pastrami sandwiches?
Well, that's a form of love.
Okay.
But then other things.
What about...
Oh, I'd rather have a pastrami sandwich, but I can still think of plenty of bad stuff
going on right now.
I'm not the God-hater around here, man.
I don't care.
It's not important.
If there is a God, why wouldn't he forgive me for saying such things to him or her or
whatever it is?
Well, because he's just like a human.
Right.
Small-minded, petty.
Vain.
Yeah.
Extremely vain.
Jealous.
Totally, yeah.
Many of the other attributes of his nom-hood.
Yeah.
That's what they...
That's what it says in the Bible.
But he is a jealous and vain deity.
We're made in his image.
That means he's dumb.
Right.
So what?
He's a gland-controlled primate.
The word doppelganger.
Who thinks he's making rational decisions.
A gland-controlled pirate.
But all the time is really just...
Can you say that?
I don't know.
Just doing chimpanzee politics.
Can I say that?
That's true.
We're all just a bunch of funny little monkeys.
And if we're made in God's image, then he's descended from a damn monkey too.
But that sounds blasphemous.
Now, don't it?
That doesn't make any sense.
That's kind of an acid-heads philosophy, you might say.
I would say so.
And you can't live by that.
It sounds good while you're on the drugs, but you can't live that way.
That's what it's for.
It's for living...
It's like saying too much is always better than not enough, when obviously too much of
some things would kill you.
But why pay attention to such lack-ritudes?
And yet it sounds so good why we live by it, don't we?
And that's what religion's all about.
It doesn't have to be.
It doesn't have to make no sense.
It's just something you've always been told.
It is what it is.
You live by it.
You know, so don't you...
You can make fun of my God, my Elvis, but don't make fun of my Bob.
You see what I'm saying?
I can smell it anyway.
Know what I'm saying?
Know what you're saying?
No, I'm not.
I'm just saying.
Whew.
See, that made my adenoids drizzle.
I don't know if you're some sort of subliminally whacking weird things in my brain when you're
talking about the...
It's the background music.
All I can think of is...
I think it was 1975.
That's Joe Newman.
I think it was 19...
Rudy Schwartz Project.
I remember it was 2004.
The people of the elbow room had just laid down in a concubinibus of snakes.
They were disagreeing with each other about how to reach the highest platitude.
Oh, there are lots of elevations and lots of ways to boing, boing, boing as you go, but
every way is marked.
There's a marked exit.
Some of them are marked on top of your head.
Those are the ones that are dangerous, but we all have to live with it because these
are mortal wounds we're forced to endear.
Excuse me, is that your name?
Indira.
Yes.
You with a dot in the middle of your ear.
Yes, I'm Indira.
Would you like to check my collection?
I'm well prepared to go.
No, I'm too shy for that.
I thought you were a collection checker.
I'm ready to board one of these space vesicles and I'm ready to go.
I'm hoping for a big time once I've paid my, what is it, 79, 20, 30, 50, 40 bucks soon.
We will be boarding.
Bertha might do it.
Let's see if Bertha can.
Bertha.
Did you hear that guy with the nasal clippings?
Yeah, what do you want?
He's going.
Okay.
Did you hear the guy with the sedentary eye?
He's going.
Okay.
We're all going somewhere.
Let's go, baby.
Let's go.
I ate some bad ham and I got really sick and in a puddle of my puke where the puke was
most thick.
A mouth, dude.
A puke.
I ate a little bit of a beer and it beckoned me near and it whispered the following words
into my ear.
It said, kill the pink boys, quit your job, mock the world and praise Bob Dobbs.
You'll build a ship and take a trip.
Go on, go get a pen, write the coordinates.
Six and a half months hold up alone.
Circuit boards duct tape and turkey bones.
The ship appeared more than disaster prone but the vomit assured me that far weirder
ships had flown.
The project was finished.
The ship would hold 20.
The power source was anything the crew would think was funny.
We didn't need the slack list or hapless.
Our mirth proved its worth in escaping a star fixed.
On our way to Planet X for sex that wrecks necks.
A prairie squid and every pot of money shot a coney twang.
It's an all-hoss hour of bonanza.
It's like a world without Tony Danza.
We're friends of a pink shit that hates the charts.
In a world of dead art, simultaneous lobotomy and sodomy.
We take a moment and we pause to reflect on the pinks that we killed and the planet that
they wrecked.
Then we laugh like banshees and howl like Comanches.
Do a victory dance in our own little world.
We're kangaroos in panties.
Our fantasy is a reality.
Earth turns to dust.
It's Planet X or Bustos.
Men and women of all races and creeds pause to destroy the earth.
Oh, it's time, hand in hand.
When the trumpet calls, extend.
And a brother and sister bend.
While they blow the window out.
And the world is in chaos.
And a brother beware.
The返
Annë
Have paradise
Subtiny of the world
Unite
And we'll start
Every night
Subtiny of the world
Unite
Next days are coming
And the pigs are coming
Sure when the rupture hits
We'll all be in our first class window seats
On the pleasure saucers
Watching the little pink boys fry
Turn on
And
You certainly don't want to preach to people
Next days are coming
And the pigs are coming
Ah
Sure J.R. Bob Dobbs is my savior
And of course I want more slack
And I'm smoking prop non-stop
For what I really want
Oh yeah, that's right
Those lovely alien nympho mutants
Non-stop orgies on the pleasure saucers
Welcome to your saucer
And pleasure goddess CV456100
Sexual gratification and desire for film will begin in a moment.
First, we invite you to look out your window, say goodbye to the pinks who were left behind.
Now unzip your pants.
Just sit back and relax.
Feel better?
Bob and Connie shall be teleporting over shortly to Congress.
I congratulate you on your success as a subgenius.
The option to copulate with either
can be taken advantage of then.
I have taken the liberty of preparing a warning prop.
The time is 8am July 5th.
I shall leave now, press the blue button.
Should you need me, goodbye.
The secret of X-Day.
Am I evil?
I don't know, my son.
All my life I've been a little man.
A happy little fellow.
But in the dressing room...
I, uh, I don't understand.
Did you ever hear of X-Day?
No.
You mean...
Yes, yes!
A chance to grow to normal size!
Please, please, please!
Please let him do it!
Just what does this X-Day look like?
Uh, uh...
A rag.
I had grown.
I was growing!
You've grown, but not so much that I can't handle you.
I was normal.
Normal.
You look good to me.
I do?
Well, I always did go for big men.
Big?
Yeah.
I was vaguely disturbed.
I'm afraid of you, John.
You're too big now.
Yes, I'd grown at least six inches.
Now I was a freak again.
Truth is fiction.
This is...
This is genius or off-snack.
It contains the weird, huge, naked souls.
And if you let Bob do your thinking for you,
you won't have to worry about nothing
come July 4th, 1998.
Ha ha ha!
When Bob comes down in his giant mothership,
looking kinda like a big pillbox,
Bob'll be landing,
and you can climb right in,
because he's gonna know!
He's gonna have your name on a computer printout.
Yes, sir, dear friends,
and that CRT tube available.
Right there at his fingertips.
He can call your name up,
and he'll know exactly what you done for him.
He'll know exactly how much money you made,
and how much donations you've taken in.
He'll know exactly how much money you've given to the church.
Now, now, do you even know exactly how much money...
Can you intuit the correct numbers
without addition?
I know exactly how silly everything is.
...forms of abstract mathematics.
And that's exactly too much.
Can you divide the template into three separate parts,
and remember that one is the dog's head,
the other one is the foot,
and the other one is the restless Bambino?
The chickens are alert.
Look around you.
Wildlife is suffering.
What?
Did you say something about the chicken Bambino?
What do I...
What the...
Friends, we were just...
Those bits we were listening to,
going from the beginning,
the song Planet X or Bust,
sort of like a rap.
The only song I know of that mentions,
is the song,
is by the El Queso All Stars.
We heard the subgenius anthem by Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
I think that was recorded last X Day.
How old are you, Princess?
X Day Drill, I mean.
X Day Drill.
X Day's a-comin' by the great Bill T. Miller,
King of Slack.
The special saucer sex goddess talk there,
from the stewardess,
was from Heart Ignition.
Sex, sex, sex.
Secret of X Day,
provided by Norrell Preff.
Secret of X Day, provided by Norrell Preff.
That was about me.
I was a little man.
I wanna be a big man.
I wanna be a normal freaking...
And, uh...
He made a big sound.
Fernanda Nettily murdered that, uh,
Hour of Slack promo,
and then we heard Dr. Philo Drummond
asking about your donations, friends.
When was the last time...
you had you a big ol' steamin' hot
bowl of Wolf Brand chili?
Well, that's too long.
Ow!
Oh, man.
I was wondering how Dave was making
both of those noises.
I turned around, Princess Wee was making the...
She stabbed me.
...the Dave-ly noise,
and Dave was making the Wee-ly noise.
Did you see the fake billy goat she stabbed me with?
No, I can't see anything when I'm doin' the show.
Oh, really?
That's...
Does that have to do with the, uh,
tonal bestiality?
I don't know.
I can't hear anything either.
Well, that's...
That's tonal, uh...
Tonal, uh,
incorrection or something like that,
but I think when your eyes go,
you should find out at least where they're going,
because they could get out.
Yeah, right.
How can I find them if I don't, if I'm looking?
It's like looking for your glasses.
You need help.
A part of your personality is going to be off having all kinds of fun looking at stuff,
and you're going to be wondering where in hell your eyeballs are, actually, your optic nerves.
That's what everybody's like when they don't have Bob.
They're like a nose that's smelling stuff, but there's no brain to interpret what that nose is smelling.
That's what I've heard.
It's like an eyeball rolling around seeing things, but there's no, it's not connected to a brain to see what the eyeball's seeing.
So it's a...
That's what, if you don't have Bob in your life, you're like a mouth that just flaps.
It doesn't have, doesn't even know what it's saying.
Amen to peace.
I've got a news thing here, so I don't have to think about what I just said.
This came from the Princess Wee office graffiti wire service, you might say.
Right?
That is correct.
It was found in Princess Wee's...
Okay, we have to make newsroom sounds.
This is news time.
Newsroom sounds.
And take this copy up to Bill, the chief editor in charge of being editors.
Wait, look, read this copy right now.
Okay, here goes.
A major research institution has just announced the discovery of the densest element yet known to science.
The new element has been named Bushcronium.
Bushcronium has one neutron, 12 assistant neutrons, 75 deputy neutrons, and 224 assistant deputy neutrons,
giving it an atomic mass of 311.
These particles are held together by dark forces called morons,
which are surrounded by vast quantities of lepton-like particles called peons.
The symbol for Bushcronium is W.
Bushcronium's mass actually increases over time,
as morons randomly interact with various elements in the atmosphere
and become assistant deputy neutrons in a Bushcronium molecule, forming isodopes.
This characteristic of moron promotion leads some scientists to believe
that Bushcronium is formed whenever morons reach a certain quantity in concentration.
This hypothetical quantity is referred to as a critical morass.
When catalyzed with money,
Bushcronium activates foxnusium,
an element which radiates orders of magnitude more energy,
albeit as incoherent noise,
since it has half as many peons,
but twice as many morons.
From the Princess Wee News Service,
could I read this for show?
Oh!
Did you want to read it for show?
Or just...
I think she originally wanted to, but then when she heard me do it...
I think she was talking about show and tell as in...
It's just got that glib newscaster thing that...
I just don't know what happened to him.
Could you read it backwards with a slight werewolf accent,
or like you could pinch your neds together sharply and go...
A major research institution has just been asked to discover
the densest element yet known to science.
The new element has been named Bushcronium.
Welcome to the monster!
The monster club!
The Church of the Subvenience has been remade as the monster club!
There was a Vincent Price low-budget movie called The Monster Club
in which a human is being nominated for inclusion in the monster club,
and at first all the monsters are going,
No, no!
But Vincent Price does this great rant about,
Oh!
No, no!
You don't understand why the humans have been responsible
for more mayhem, torture, atrocities than any group of monsters.
Then he gives like a whole history of humans,
and in the end they're all going,
Oh, the humans are the greatest monsters of all!
That was the inspiration for a bad song, also.
The monster...
Well, then we lost Bobby Boris Pickett,
of course.
The author of The Monster Mash.
That was my favorite song one year.
We didn't really lose him, Stan.
I think he was just tired of listening to you talk about Bob.
He was there one minute, and the next minute he was going,
This guy, you know, he's driving me nuts.
Give me a break.
And Stan kept on going on and on and on.
And he just disappeared.
He just left this mortal plane, that's all.
No, well, it's not like...
Not just mortal plane.
He did The Monster Mash, so he can be brought back to life every Halloween.
Yeah!
There's so many wags.
Already said.
He always will.
That's why it's a good idea to always have yourself sacrificed
on a duly appointed holiday of any disconnected value.
For instance, if you were to croak off on the day before Christmas,
you might not be well known or remembered.
However, if you went down for the count on October, you know, 30th or something like that,
you'd be a Halloweener.
You know what I'm saying?
As far as the rest of the engorged public was concerned,
you would be a Halloweener.
Or at least a feisty little kid without,
you know, any direction in life.
But empty inside.
Empty.
Empty like a...
A balloon hot dog of a man.
Like an evacuated bladder.
A nothing...
A deflated little pipsqueak balloony man.
One of the millions of dust mites that are shaken from your rugs every year.
I'm the old pincushion man.
Terror of Balloonyland.
I forget what that was from.
I'm not supposed to remember.
Balloonyland.
That's a great car.
Oh, the car.
It's a cartoon.
Yes, a classic cartoon.
Balloonie...
The memorable thing about the Balloonie Man cartoon
is that the old pincushion man has a big pin
emerging at an upwards angle from his lap.
A huge pin.
Yes, he does.
And he stalks around waggling that great big sharp pointy thing.
At the little balloony boy and girl who have wandered,
as they were told,
not to do.
Don't go into the pincushion forest,
little balloony boy and girl.
Why couldn't he?
But they do.
He carried...
Of course.
Because they're kids.
And you know how kids are.
They go creeping around graveyards
and get down into the unauthorized areas only.
And, you know,
then next thing you know,
they run into the mad torso of Kingsbury Run.
And then they run, baby.
Man.
Just as so much as you did the other night.
It's the circle of life.
At twilight.
Screaming.
Don't give me that circle of life crap!
Your heels are...
The circle of life.
The circle of life is a circle jerk,
if you ask me.
That concept,
I hate that concept more than I hate
the Church of the Subgenius.
It's supposed to make you feel better
when you lose a loved one.
Right?
Yeah.
But it's a trick.
It's a lie.
It's a cheat.
It works in a Disney movie,
and we saw that movie,
The Fountain.
Yeah, The Fountain.
That was the most elaborate,
lovely, tasteful version
of the Disney circle of life ethic,
philosophy I've ever seen.
No, I didn't know
Walt Disney was a circle of life.
It just made you feel so good.
I'm so sorry and sad
that that lady died,
and then...
A cryogenic guy.
And then all of a sudden,
it's, oh, it's okay,
because when we die,
we're sacrificing for the rebirth.
Well, I don't care about
what gets reborn after I'm dead!
I don't want to die!
It just ain't fair!
That's an admirable bird
you're wearing around your neck.
What was God thinking?
He was thinking of phalluses
and donkey hopes.
He was thinking of the children.
Right.
They wouldn't have to smell
old people forever.
That would be a big problem, Stang.
That is true,
that a lot of decaying flesh
laying around...
Is still alive and voting.
What if we let them drop
where they were
and just went on without them?
Think about it.
Well, you don't have to
entertain the thought for too long,
but...
Now, my friend Palmer Vreedys
had...
We were going to write stories
for this Living Dead series of books
that these guys were doing,
and neither one of us
ever did ours.
I was going to do
Living Dead in China,
which, because it's overpopulated,
would really be pretty dead.
A lot of the people
that we count as actual people
in China are dead.
But Palmer's was,
what if everything dead
came back to life?
Well, everything dead means...
It's impossible.
The protozoan skeletons
at the bottom of the ocean,
it means the bacteria
in your bowels that died
suddenly come back to life.
All the bacteria,
all the germs,
all the bugs come back to life.
All the dead leaves.
And for how long?
Yeah.
Well, until they...
As long as they can keep eating brains.
Oh, wow.
As you know,
that's what dead things do
when they come back to life.
Dead trees come back
and eat your brain?
What about all the hamburgers?
Yeah, because it hurts to be dead.
I always wondered about that.
I always wondered about that, too.
But in one of the movies
they explained it.
I think in the second Return of the...
No, it was the Return of the Living Dead.
This old dead torso lady goes,
they're going,
why are you trying to eat our brains?
And she goes,
it hurts to be dead.
Oh, no.
That's bad news.
That is awful news.
I really didn't want to...
For living people and dead people.
You know,
what a thing to look forward to.
Well, now, see,
that's why there's no proof.
You can't get a real good proof
of an afterlife
because as soon as that happens,
you know,
if there's anything good about it,
everybody's going to jump off a bridge
as soon as the bills stack up.
But remember,
many dead people's vocal cords
don't work that well.
In fact,
they're probably totally...
Right.
I mean,
what are you guys thinking?
And so, therefore,
they must resort to...
Right.
Sometimes they're just asking...
...other means to communicate their messages,
which usually consist of,
you know,
driving you off a cliff
or letting your feet swell up.
You know,
they want to...
Like, for instance,
a hypothetical living dead person
might simply want to know
what time it is,
but you're thinking they're...
And they're going...
You think they're saying,
I want to eat your brain,
so you blow their head off
with your automatic weapons.
Don't blow off.
Well,
maybe that's a little...
Maybe.
Maybe the dead person
is full of other people's brains already
and just wants to know the time.
Then it would be better
to eat their brains
and enjoy the double deliciousness.
What happens if you eat
a dead guy's brains
who's been eating
lots of live people's brains?
It would be like triple strong.
I think you'd turn into
a living dead guy, I think.
Yeah, right.
Because it's a virus type of thing.
Contact type virus thing, yeah.
I'm a born-again zombie.
What?
She is.
She...
You don't look like a...
You don't look very zombie-ish.
You're supposed to go...
That's funny.
I'm a born-again zombie.
Again and again and again.
No.
Yeah.
Oh.
Is that an old joke or something?
I'm supposed to...
No, it's what I am.
It's a recurrent nightmare.
I am a born-again zombie.
I was just stating a fact.
I wasn't trying to be funny.
I thought you had something new.
Jeez.
I'm a flatulent...
I thought you knew.
...indolent...
I know nothing.
...pirotechnician.
I'm an indolent pyrotechnician
and I'm okay.
Harlecker and Wunderslander
and Psycho...
I sleep all night
and alight all night.
Hold on.
I read that.
I'm trying.
Aye.
Oye.
We should have an Oye song.
That's...
I hope the Oye fellow is listening.
He was a chronic masturbator
who's known for calling
the shows on the station
and going,
Oye.
He died from that.
He died alone.
Oye.
Masturbating...
Delight masturbating?
Oye.
I think he may have
suffered a massive malocclusion
of the brain
and just simply perspired
right on the spot.
Oye.
I think you're making that up, Dave.
Yikes.
We've got something more important to talk about
which I'm not going to talk about
but I'm just going to play some tapes.
That's X Day.
Oye.
And also Tex Day
which you can't mention.
Oye.
No, you can't mention it.
No, text date is pointless because by the time anyone outside of this show, this moment of this show.
Yeah, for the future guests, they won't know.
It won't make any difference.
We'll be playing tapes of this year's X Day by the time they hear this.
By that time.
Have you ever played that?
But that's them because of the beloved sister stations.
That's then and this is now.
Let's keep our temporal artifacts in order.
I mean, let's not go from the past to the future as if it were some sort of thing you could do just by twinkling your little nose there.
I saw three movies about that very thing just in the last week.
About quick movements between illacrid moments?
Oh, yeah, time movies.
Time movies.
Okay, okay.
Friends, on July 5th, 1998, the world will end at 7 a.m.
when the men from Planet X arrive to rupture up the dues-paying subgeniuses
and destroy.
Slay or torture all who were, well, everybody else.
At the present time, they are observing us.
They wish to help us to help ourselves to attain a higher understanding of life and its meaning.
What do you think about Bob?
Who's Bob?
All right, well, what do you think about the UFOs?
Sure.
We're presently going to, which are presently in formation,
to blitz the Earth and put particle beams through the head of everyone that doesn't know Bob.
You're out of your mind.
Spacecraft entered the moon.
...in the sixth segment of the flight.
The gravity of the moon is one-sixth of that on Earth.
The orbit around the moon was flown 66 miles above the moon's surface at 6,000.
The moon's orbit was about 10 miles an hour.
At 10 after 9, the beeping began.
Went down to the reserve fence, watched through binoculars, and we did see this thing.
Now it's about the size of the moon, with a small crescent at the bottom that's well lit like starlight.
The top is a dark gray mass.
It came down through the trees, whatever it was.
Have you ever heard of one?
Have you ever been in one?
Have you ever seen one?
Have you, by television, ever seen one?
If you haven't, it's the greatest sight this side of heaven.
People from this Earth have already seen some of their spacecraft,
which they call flying saucers,
and other flying objects which they cannot describe.
These objects are real and are spacecraft.
The astronauts returned to Earth on the same day.
On the sixth day of the week.
The mutants must appear.
The mutants must thrive.
The saucers will fly.
And the nervous mutants die.
The UFOs are appearing outside the window again today, the 5th of July.
And, you know, sometimes when they do appear,
other lights start flashing on and off them, like this newly built house.
Like these newly built houses right next by this house that I'm in.
So, I'm not sure.
I'm not sure what they're living in.
Sometimes the lights flash on and off when they appear or don't appear.
The UFOs have come back.
They're outside my window as I speak.
I can see them.
I hope it means that X-Day is coming.
Doctor, doctor, doctor, doctor, deep, doctor, deep, deep, deep, oh.
Oh, yes, friends.
Yes, friends, it's scary.
It's scary indeed.
Because it's the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
And if you want to know more about the Church of the Subgenius,
you can, if you wish, check out www.subgenius.com.
This music in the background, I believe, is by Reverend Just John.
Thank you for watching.
Doctor, doctor, doctor, doctor, doctor, deep, doctor, deep, deep, deep, Oprah.
Eternally obsessed.
What is the meaning of eternally being obsessed with soap opera?
More, more, more, more.
Control issues.
Give it up.
Doctor, doctor.
That's what we're talking about.
Marianne.
How do we do it?
How do we do it? How do we do it? How do we do it? How do we do it? How do we do it?
Focus, focus. Hypocritical one. Hypocritical one.
Hell. Hell.
Anthropologists have found cult. Cult. Cult. Cult.
Began inventing religions for themselves.
So, so, no I do not think. No I do not think.
We live in a, um, in a world. In a world.
Pain is deep. Real deep.
Slack. Slack.
Somebody's miserable.
Because I don't care. Because I don't care.
I can be miserable.
You will always be suffering.
Pleasure.
Quick fix. Quick fix. Deep.
We see what we seek.
What is it?
The mother load.
Narcissism. Narcissism.
Commit suicide Monday morning.
Quit jobs.
The world is falling apart because adults aren't thinking for themselves.
Good mothers.
Poor self esteem.
How does your body feel?
How do you feel?
Thank you.
98.75% of everything.
That's what we're talking about.
I don't personally believe.
And I don't exist.
Just too frightening.
Well I don't know.
Wallow in your life.
In your problems.
Dog. Dog. Dog.
Religion is a problem.
Dog.
You can fall on your face.
Getting sick.
Dog.
This is a news minute.
President Bush is guilty.
He was operated on three times and a metal rod was inserted.
Administration under siege.
Floating weightless.
This is a tragic situation.
Admitting their guilt.
Marijuana distribution and unlawful transport of firearms.
Repeat the mistakes of Vietnam.
I will.
Drag on. Drag on.
The agony of Iraq.
Mission defeated.
We're strongly behind.
Behind.
Carnage and division.
Incompetent individuals at work.
Grand conspiracy.
Burned out President Dick.
Must be disrupted.
End the war right now.
It was a lie.
Violence continues.
Petty crimes.
Corruption in action.
Give up.
Let your doubts get the best of you.
Taste of failure.
Oh I loved it.
It was um.
It's unclear.
I'm the most.
Mission defeated.
Person who ever lived.
I believe that life on earth is at an ever increasing risk of being wiped out by a disaster.
Long and hard.
Penis.
Probed.
President Bush.
Harder.
Talk about the thrill of a lifetime.
I could have gone on and on.
Here I come.
Again.
And again.
Uh.
Long and hard.
Five active members.
I'm here simply to ask you to think.
Fly.
RLcraft.
Lemitations.
No storytelling or links tobdonk0tlg