I am seeking information about Bob. Let us see what is on the radio.
You're listening to PR News.
No, I don't think I can accept that program.
Nor that one.
The Self Genius Power Rolls!
Well you know what? I'm high. It's simpler than you think.
By the time we finish, you're all going to know everything that you need to know to be able to get high in a flash.
I'm going to show you how to get high with two hands.
I never do because it takes too long. Tonight at 9.
Let's get high!
And have fun!
I'm falling.
And I can't get up.
Calling Dr. Howard. Dr. Fine. Dr. Howard.
No, I'm a doctor, not a mechanic.
We're losing potency in our anti-matter parts.
My mind is growing.
I can feel it.
You see? You see?
Your stupid minds.
Stupid. Stupid!
Are you talking about the mind shafting gap?
Where you've been shafted in the mind again?
Right in the gap?
Huh! Huh! Huh! Huh!
Wow! Wow! Wow!
It's a beautiful moment!
Yeah!
Huh?
Being of a blood mind...
Does that hurt?
...do hereby bequeath...
Benadryl.
...easiness.
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up!
Ah!
Hey!
You're bloody stupid.
Who in this dead-end un AK?
Your educational career,
at least volume 100,
Ethan's...
it seems to...
besides love.
...arguing with...
Nothin'.
So long, Ethan.
What's up, presenting.
a brain phone called Ray. That's R-A-Y. Ray is a small chip that attaches right into your
brain, right next to the antenna. Takes about 20 seconds. Once in place, Ray's patent-pending
subtle energy technology immediately begins to counter the effects of the government without
affecting your brain. The cost of Rayway, only $5,444.95. Order right now.
www.now.com.
We enjoy the rich flavor of the products we've made with our minds.
The human mind is capable of more than you know in your show, your dog and pony show,
your light and dark shadow show.
For one thing, the human brain is fattening.
For another thing, it's fattening so much it's going to take over very soon the rest
of the body.
Deep fried.
But it's buttery and sugary.
So, well, some of the human brain. Other parts are bitter and sour.
Have you ever checked?
Have you ever wire tripped?
It was dareable! It was just dareable!
I'll never get over as low as I limb.
Radio activity's a costant thing.
Let go.
It's alive!
Deadly churns are spreading over the earth, killing every human in their path.
Radioactivity is a constant thing.
It's alive!
Oh, Phineas Narco from Midnight Voice Jail did that.
And before that we heard some ESO swamp radio from WCSB Cleveland.
Host Chaz Smith with lonesome cowboy Dave.
Yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang and Princess We Are Doe.
And friends all hours of slack, it seems, are laden and dripping
with collage pieces by Fernanda Nande-Lee-Murr.
This particular show, hour of slack number nine hundred and five,
is an educational show with the subject matter being drugs.
Yes, it is educational.
Now, well, now let's go back to ESO swamp radio.
About a month ago we had just gotten back from doing field research on entheomusicology
at a conference of scientists who specialize in that.
It was slack-filled starwood, as such things go.
Partly because it rained so much there wasn't much to do but hide out with your loved one.
People don't know what the hell we're talking about unless you were there.
Well, starwood's of this outdoor festival run by the...
Crazy people and crazy people perform and it's just insanity in the mud.
Late at night you see these neon giants stalking the campground.
That were actually...
Not hallucinations but giant puppets, rod puppets twice the size of a person.
They're kind of tied like Waldo machines to a human.
But you didn't even see the human because they'd be in the darkness.
The puppet, the giant puppet is lit up to freak out those on ketamine,
which was going around that campground, that particular...
Now is that a legal or illegal substance?
Ketamine is legal if you're a horse that needs to be tranquilized.
Or if you're a vet who needs to administer the tranquilization.
If...
I didn't touch that stuff.
Those kids.
I saw that movie Altered States.
It turns you into a caveman.
And you run to the zoo and rip up the taper throats.
I ain't gonna mess with that.
Crop circle makers were there?
Reverend Circle Maker was at my house.
I just sent him off back home to Wales.
The other day.
We had one of the many crop circle artists.
The people who make crop circles for the aliens.
We're not saying the aliens don't direct the making of the crop circles.
Or anything like that.
It's just that most of the crop circles were made by these British coffee drinkers, let's say.
Who like to stay up real late at night and make artwork out of farmers' fields illegally.
I was talking to one of these K people and they talked all about going down the K hole.
Yeah, the K hole of Special K.
Yeah.
The Ketamine drug.
And they told me it was a club drug.
And I couldn't imagine it being like a dancey kind of a thing.
No, I've been told just the opposite.
Really?
Yeah.
That it's a what drug?
Well, the guy told me he took some.
He got up about 30 seconds later and started to change channels on the TV and fell to the floor.
And at that point he said in very slow motion,
I don't think this is a club drug.
And that was the last thing he was able to say as he lost contact with his body but went onto another planet inside his own head.
Yeah.
Apparently, one person.
I don't think this is a club drug.
One person said, it's just like being real drunk.
It's like drinking a whole lot of vodka but without swallowing.
Yeah.
But the guy who said it didn't sound like he was very drunk when he said it.
So I didn't believe that exactly.
I think the numbness and disconnection from your body is the vodka-like aspect.
But then there's some kind of a weird interior head trip that you do.
And you know, Ketamine is classed as a telepathine.
Wow.
That is, it causes people to think that they're experiencing telepathy.
Especially with somebody else who happens to be on the stuff.
Yeah.
There's a very interesting article about that in Paul Craster's new book, Magic Mushrooms and something something.
About going to John Lilly's house and taking Ketamine and getting in the isolation chamber and freaking out.
But then hearing John Lilly's mind speak to him to calm him down.
Which somebody else later said, well yeah, he did go and sit outside the house.
And he was sitting in the tank with his hand on it while tripping.
And he didn't say anything but he looked like he was beaming calm down trip guidance into the tank.
And you picked up on it, man.
If you believe that sort of thing.
You picked up on it.
Personally, I've found that when people get drunk as a lord on psychotomimetic drugs, what they want to happen sometimes happens.
Like them red lights on that phone.
You think that might be Dave?
CSB?
Man?
Hey.
Who's here?
That's not Dave.
I'm not Dave, dude.
How you be?
It's Echo Man.
Echo Man.
Is this the Ketamine dude?
He knows me.
How you doing?
Is this the disembodied spirit of Sam Phillips?
I finished a job for a world premiere and here's a book loading an iPhone.
Will it beep, beep, beep, beep?
D'it move it forолод potatoes!
Hein?
Balloon man?
Call you at no end.
Balloons are smart.
estructural structure and materials to test the therapy.
Simmer on.
Are you ready to play?
Let's play.
All right, today's first word ends in O.
O?
And the second word starts with O-R.
Okay.
All right, number one is a floor rug made into something you smoke.
You might say, what?
Okay.
The first word is pipe.
Oh, pipe.
You might say, the first word is James Bond's zit.
Oh, sure.
You might say, the first famous broadcaster of Japanese zits.
Nasty mouth.
You might say, the first word improves old zits.
I enjoyed the tongue infection.
And your last one, a cry at a Washington zit ball game.
You should have listened to me.
Goodbye.
Watch your captain.
Don't take your eyes off her.
All right.
Drop the gun.
So, let's look at Bob.
I use it almost every day of my life, even if just for a minute or two.
So, in something like one or two seconds, you've gotten the buzz going with the gentle inner's pure dynamite.
Believe me, you'll know it when you have it.
I don't know.
It might be pretty scary in there.
Oh.
Ah!
And you hold on to that as you're Bob.
And pump up that tender feeling coming from that smile until it just becomes.
Take off joy life.
Do it.
And get that want motor revved up for wanting brings passion.
Passion brings Bob.
Bob brings more wanting.
But also stake your claim for universal or intangible things such as.
The
The.
Now, here I stand because of you.
Because of you.
I'm no longer an agent of this system.
I've changed.
I'm unplugged.
A new man.
So to speak.
Like you.
Apparently free.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Friends, you're floating in a sea of pills.
A sea of Bob's pills.
But you're just too blind and empty.
Done to see them.
Oh.
Oh, friends.
I know you're not.
The dumb, astigated type.
I know you're the smart, astigated type.
Oh, but people say, Reverend Stagg, what is slack?
I want you to tell me what slack is.
You know, friends, the television doesn't have to watch you as long as you are watching
the television.
And a lot of people, a lot of people think that slack is that much more than just a little
Miller beer commercial where everybody's good looking and you're rich and your team
just won the game and you're drinking Miller beer and your favorite show is on.
And you know that's bullshit because slack is not laziness, friends.
Slack is getting into the zone.
It's being awake and alert and doing what you wanted to do until your eyes snap open
and you're smart enough to realize that you are God.
Life is worth living.
And everything is just as psychedelic as an old t-shirt that you can't fit into anymore.
Now, hold that thought.
Hold it in your head because that is what slack is all about, friends.
Slack is something for nothing.
It's not the right time to be sober.
Now the idiots have taken over.
Spreading lies and social cancer.
Is there an answer?
Men's membership exceeds the average.
The white man's brain is bleeding.
Tell me why and how are all the stupid people breeding.
What's in it's really elementary?
The ingestible revolution has flipped the fish on evolution.
The benevolent and wise are being wanted and ostracized.
What a bummer.
The world keeps getting dumber.
Insensitivity is standard.
And faith is being fancied of reason.
It's always rolling over and it's coughing
Cause I think it starts surviving much less often
Now everything seems to be reversing
And it's worsening
Someone plopped a steamer in the gene pool
Now angry, my mentality is no longer the exception
It's the rule
And I'm starting to feel a lot like
Strong Heston
Stranded on a private planet
Apes and orangutans that ran into the ground
With generals and the armies that obeyed them
Followers following fables
Philosophies that enable them to rule without regard
There's no point for democracy
When ignorance is celebrated
Political scientists get the same one vote
As the walking saw in bread
Majority rule
Don't work in mental institutions
Sometimes the smallest office voice carries the grand
PG solutions
What are we left with?
A nation of God-fearing pregnant nationalists
Who feel it's their duty to be free?
Energy and
Business
keer
I hate fund for the
THIS BE GAY
SPACE
PLEA
IT'S COOL
I HOPE
WE DON'T WANT
IRA
FENTANYL
GATA
AREN'T
Advan store
The idiots are taking over
They're taking over!
NoFX, friends, was the name of the band that did that.
Before that, me and ESO at XX Day in 1999 in Brushwood
with some clips from my cousin, Agent Smith, from the Matrix Rebloated.
And the Bob Meditation Collage was by Reverend Jartow.
Now friends, you understand that Bob, J.R. Bob Dobbs, replaces drugs.
This church is often misunderstood in that respect,
especially by the man and idiots who glean everything
they know only from surface appearances.
But, as you well know, appearances can be deceiving,
which brings me back to the reason why we're here.
We're not here because we're free.
We're here because we're not free.
There's no escaping reason, no denying purpose,
because as we both know, without purpose, we would not exist.
It's purpose that created us.
Purpose that connects us.
Purpose that pulls us.
That guides us.
That drives us.
It is purpose that defines.
Purpose that binds us.
Can I have some coffee?
Can I get you a cup of coffee?
Or some water?
No, no, but thank you.
This is good coffee. It tastes awfully good.
The hot in the world of me? That's torture.
I mean, we have this totally unbelievable life-altering sex
and then you just disappear.
I know, I know. I had to go get coffee.
You stopped drinking coffee.
Who's Johnny Potsmoop?
There's a new movie about Napoleon.
That's my alter ego.
No, I thought that was my alter ego.
There's a new movie about Napoleon.
That's my alter ego.
And he's played by Ian Jones.
Johnny Potsmoop?
Johnny Potsmoop, from Meets Napoleon.
Wow, cool.
Oh, didn't they already do this in Bill and Ted's Excellent Adventure?
You know, in that Terry Gilliam movie?
Where's the computer in Transfunction?
Why Johnny can't smoke?
Why Johnny Cash smokes pot?
I knew Johnny Cash smoked pot, though.
He doesn't know how to spell it, do you?
He's so bad.
Um, okay, uh, let's backtrack a little bit and make sure that we're on the same page here.
I wouldn't want to be at cross purposes.
Cannabis or us?
You haven't heard of that, Joe?
Hey, Neil, we're gonna have to kill Johnny Potsmoop.
No.
I want each and every one of you Johnny Potsmokers out of the air.
Johnny on the spot.
What's the deal with you?
To what?
Or Johnny on the spot?
The caller has lost control.
He comes out, and we'll smoke some more.
Um, the chain was sailing away on the briefest of fogs.
Harrison?
Yes?
I'm listening.
I saw the new day.
Down the road I look, and there runs Mary.
Green, green, pair of black cherries.
It's good to smoke the green, green, black cherries.
And the green grass of home.
Yes, they'll all come to-
Green Acres is the place to be
Farm living is the life for me
Land spreading out so far and wide
Keep Manhattan, just give me that countryside
The Chars
The Stars
Fresh Air
Times Square
New York is where I'd rather be
I'd rather stay
I get allergic smelling hay
I just adore a penthouse view
Darling, I love you, but give me Park Avenue
You are my way
I said goodbye city life
Green Acres
We are there
We are there tonight
court
Free
This is English Present
our way of spinning a fizzling
punctual Jaebees
When kicking before the speeches
Their test for novelty
Not normally
No no thank you
Tarek is always at my service
Let's have our dessert and coffee in the living room.
Oh, thank you.
Hey, everybody.
Hi, Google.
Google.
Super.
You know, that's funny.
Shows what greed will do.
Oh, yes.
Changes a person completely.
Oh, that makes a lot of sense.
Yep.
Yes.
Shows what greed will do.
Right, eh?
Yeah, well.
What time you got?
Well, come back.
I'll be going.
Shows what greed will do.
The Fool Who Stole Your advocat prince's superintendent in environments Given your
selbstresearch
Thank you for purchasing your pharmaceuticals.
Is your co-payment ready?
Bob is my co-payment.
I wonder...
accept bud as a copayment. Will you accept Connie? No, I'm sorry. Well, what will you accept? We
accept orange plastic dildos. Damn, I'm fresh out of dildi. Do you have any slack tokens? I have a
dead cat. We do not accept dead cat as copayments. My tumor has gotten bigger. My best friend is a
tumor. Would you like to touch it? Wow, can I? That feels good. It is green. I am very proud of it.
You should be. Would you accept a chunk? As a copayment? Yes. Sure, have a nice day. Thank you very much.
Art Ignition did that. The HMO fiasco, it's called. And a little while before that, Green Haze was by
Elvis Hitler. And everything else around it was cut up by Mr. Fernand and Anderle Mer. And now,
a cut up by Barak.
And now, a cut up by John, whoever that is, really. I got it off alt-binary slack. Featuring Terrence McKenna from the new album Conversations at the Edge of Magic, which was recorded at Starwood and is available through www.rosencomet.com, the ace website. Oh, I should mention this background music is by Hell Pope Huey.
And now,
Terrence McKenna.
And here is my answer to this riddle, Where Did Human Consciousness Come From? It begins like this.
And in highly sexed animals, small amounts of psilocybin mushrooms would have naturally been eaten at the time.
by extraterrestrial scientific proof.
Some of these mutations will be positive
and most will be lethal.
And so you see, my young friend,
here we have a case where the use of drugs
actually introduces us to a more true vision of reality
than if we had avoided the drug!
Some of these mutations end in highly sexed animals, small amounts of psilocybin mushrooms,
and exotic pseudo neurotransmitters.
Is that when you take slightly larger doses of psilocybin,
one of these mutations will be positive, most will be negative.
And that is the psilocybin containing mushrooms that grow in the dung of cattle.
Mommy, whip me up a plosive bee, I'm about to lose my noodle.
I'm getting spiritual now.
I've taken all the pills I can take.
I feel so relaxed now, but I certainly don't look forward to what I have to do.
In a few short minutes, perhaps a few short hours, weeks, days, I don't know.
Some expensive time there's going to be a lot of trouble here about.
A lot of trouble in this dumpster.
The backyard.
Back of my head.
Sure, yeah.
You think it lives there?
No, no, it can't live there anymore.
There's not enough meat.
There's not enough meat for it to survive.
That's the dumb day.
It's time.
Hello.
My name's Terry and I'm a law-abider.
There's nothing I like more than getting fired up on beer.
And when the weekend's here, I exercise my right to get paralytic and fight.
Good bloke, fairly.
But I get well-airy when gearing up.
Jesus, look at me funny.
Bouncin' round like bunnies.
I'm likely to cause mischief.
Good clean grief, you must believe, and I ain't no thief.
Law-abiding and all, all legal.
And who cares about my liver when it feels good?
What you need's some real manhood.
Rasher, rasher, burning catcher.
Putting people's backs up.
Public disorder, I give you public disorder.
I down eight pints and run all over the place.
Spit in the face of an officer.
See if that bothers ya.
Cos I never broke a law in my life.
Someday I'm gonna settle down with a wife.
Go on lads, let's have another fight.
Erm, hello.
My name's Tim and I'm a criminal.
In the eyes of society, I need to be in jail.
For the choice of herbs I inhale.
This ain't no wholesale operation.
Just a few eights and some Playstations, my vocation.
I pose a threat to the nation.
And down the station, the police hold no patience.
Let's talk space and time.
I like to get deep sometimes and think about Einstein.
And Carl Jung.
And old kung-fu movies I like to see.
Pass the hydrator, please.
Pfft, yeah, I'm floating on thin air.
Going to Amsterdam in the new year.
Top gear there.
Cos I take pride in my hobby.
Home-made bongs using my engineering degree.
Dear leaders, please legalise weed for these reasons.
Like I was saying to him, I told him.
Swap with me and you won't live.
So I smacked him in the head and downed another carlin'.
Badda badda bing for the lads like.
Mad fight, his face a sad sight.
Vodka and snake bite.
Going on like a right geez.
Ease of twat.
Shouldn't have looked at me like that.
Anyway, I'm an upstanding citizen.
If a war came along, I'd be on the front line with them.
Can't stand crime either.
Them hooligans on heroin.
Drugs and criminal.
Those thugs are the pinnacle of the downfall of society.
I've got all the anger pent up inside of me.
No, I don't see why I should be the criminal.
How can something with no recorded fatalities be illegal?
And how many deaths are there per year from alcohol?
I just completed Gran Turismo on the hardest setting.
We pose no threat on my settee.
All the pizza's here.
Will someone let him in please?
We didn't order chicken.
Not a problem, we'll pick it out.
I doubt they're meant to mess us about.
After all, we're all adults, not louts.
As I was saying, we're friendly, peaceful people.
We're not the ones out there causing trouble.
We just sit in this hazy bubble with our quarters.
Discussing how beautiful Gal Porter is.
MTV, BBC 2, Channel 4 is on till six in the morning.
Then six in the morning, the sun dawns and it's my bedtime.
Causing trouble?
You're stinking rabble, boys.
Saying I'm the lad who's spoiling it.
You're on drugs.
Really bugs me when people try and tell me I'm a thug.
Just for getting drunk.
I like getting drunk.
Because I'm an upstanding citizen.
If the war came along, I'd be on the front line with them.
Now, Terry, you're repeating yourself.
But that's okay, drunk people can't help that.
A chemical reaction happening inside your brain causes you to forget what you're saying.
What?
I know exactly what I'm saying.
I'm perfectly sane.
You stinking student lame-o.
Go get a job.
And stop robbing us of our taxes.
Erm, well actually, according to research,
government funding for further education pales in insignificance
when compared to how much they spend on repairing
a lairy of drunk people at the weekend in casualty wards all over the land.
Why you stinking little swine, come here!
I'm gonna battea!
Come here!
The irony of it all by The Streets.
Original pirate material.
And now, a live revival recording from the 5X Day in London, England, yes,
where Pope David Lee Black can be heard perusing the radio.
And now, performing a healing.
Now each, now a sub-genius church service would not be complete.
Unless we had a what?
What's that?
We gotta have a healing.
We gotta have a healing!
And if we can't have a healing, we gotta have a sickening.
Sickening!
Is there anybody in the audience who has a problem, have an ailment, this,
that something bothering you?
Somebody, somebody's gotta, you sir.
There must be someone as sick as me and I'm dying!
Yes sir, we have one.
Sir, sir, tell me, tell me, what's ailing you?
At the moment, I've got chronic alcoholism.
He, did you hear that?
So what?
He has chronic alcoholism.
Alcoholism!
Well, I've got some good news for you.
We have a, we have a, we have a cure for that.
I want you to close your eyes.
Alcoholism isn't an ailment, it's a blessing from God!
We have this holy elixir here.
Fear!
Obstinate!
I want you to drink it, when you've had it, come on, drink it.
Drink it all.
And this ain't, this is a church of excess, not a church of obstinates.
Come on, drink it!
Come on!
Drink it!
Get your fucking neck!
Get it down your fucking neck!
I'm coming through this here!
He's an alcoholic, my friend!
Bob has rubber stamped his alcoholism!
Yeah!
And there is whiskey for Bob!
Whiskey for Bob!
Whoo!
I'm not afraid.
I like it out there.
Did you go with me?
No.
He defies all the laws of man and God.
Lies!
There may be an entirely new set of laws, Jim, that we know nothing about.
Come out and say what you mean.
I'm only guessing.
Someone sing in my yard.
Kumbaya.
Oh, Lord, kumbaya.
All the way your world was made.
With your majestic, superior, cackling hand.
Your people I do not understand.
So do you, my shambhala fans.
Shambhala.
A place we all believe that someday will take us away.
A place of refuge.
With every dark feeling that grows within us.
And understanding develops.
Someday, in Shambhala.
We shall fight them with sticks and toads.
We shall bring them down and squish them with our mighty mortars.
We shall pray to them on altars of cheese and peanuts.
And sing while the devils dance around us.
Ah, Shambhala.
What was that about fighting them with sticks and toads?
Just exactly what kind of toads are you talking about?
Mystic toads, my friend.
I am talking about mystic toads.
The kind that drip from your cerebellum when you are stinking in your sleep.
Everybody loves the hypno-toad.
Oh, yeah, of course.
But I don't think that's what you're talking about.
It's got three eyes.
No, I wasn't talking, senor.
I was just informing you how it's going to go down over the next 25 years or so.
The world's in a collision course with its own self, see?
Prophecy.
Obvious-y.
Obviously.
The Earth and the Moon shall come together and have unnatural sex like a priest and a schoolboy.
Children shall all be born with a third nostril very, very visible to those practitioners of the Church of the Evil Sabiones.
This man is absolutely dangerous.
Do you realize how many children are out there probably looking at this program and you're telling them it's not dangerous to use drugs?
I can name you.
I can name you 15 people on crack, crack cocaine alone, and my stepson got on it and he is in prison.
The child was a good Christian man and he got on cocaine and he is in prison for stealing because he could not support his habit.
And these children out here are listening to you, man.
Can I compare alcohol?
Alcohol is addictive.
Cigarettes are addictive.
Nobody should do none of them.
Don't compare drugs with alcohol and say that it's all right for the government to sell alcohol and it's not all right to sell drugs.
You're dangerous, man.
And the fellows that fell down...
I have a coffee.
A double latte.
To hell.
All the way down to hell.
It has milk in it.
They bounced on the leaves, the acid.
No, no, no acid in mine.
And then fell, fell.
I would also like a...
Faster, faster, falling freely into the abyss, into the deep, deep dark abyss into which the psychedelic sounds nightclub was in the bottom of the abyss.
And then there was thousands and thousands of cockroaches swarming, seeking out the female fugue.
Scope out the action that this mall, here in the puzzling evidence of states, stretching and sprawling over mile after mile, will reconquer the...
They were stolen from them, but Bob...
But what happened?
Bob paid to bring them all back.
When high altitude air force planes split the sky with a glowing contrast...
Bob paid for the return of your orgasm with his self, with his pain.
I can't be...
Oh, Bob didn't have anything to say.
He didn't have anything to do with that file.
...
88888888888888...
888888888888888888...
Hello, you're on...
Am I just doing this for the benefit of some other doobie dealer?
...
Well, but you're under no obligation to go to the dealer.
Yeah.
I'm asking 170 bucks.
Don't forget that they will break things for free.
...
Okay.
Alrighty, bye bye.
Oh god.
Good luck.
Yeah.
Jesus.
What a stupid f***ing home now.
Hey, no!
And speaking of enjoying things, who can leave out the very basis for our fate?
Our famous, most holy and revered world without end reason for life?
Binsky's Nuclear Beer!
It's the same as the fine amphetamines you are surely familiar with.
It allows us to do our vastly needed work for the economy.
And expands our awareness that we may fully appreciate the wonders that our hardworking
bozo leaders have provided us.
And we are generously allowed injections five times a day.
It helps us mature faster.
Our eldest citizens are 25.
Like football?
Well, wait till you see the war against Mars.
The finest teenage champions have been bred for these gala celebrations which keep alive
the tradition of skillful combat.
Colorful but simple, rugged but rewarding both to winners and losers, the best of the
best.
It's just like the Quirrell days.
A grueling test of stamina with two entire planets aboard.
Watch our Earth team fight for our Binsky's which those Martian speed team just can't do
without.
Whoops, looks like that Martian won't score.
Sorry Mars.
What anti-drug film are we in right now?
Which drug?
Which drug are they trying to warn us against?
That's what I'm...
I don't know.
Dave are you handing out...
Those are...
Red.
Man that's not medicine.
Yes these are.
Or candy.
It's red medicine.
These are communist medicine.
Those are Martian pellets.
These are...
Oh my god.
These are Martian pellets.
Little red children orphaned Martian children from Mars that came in after the war.
No way.
Which war?
The ones that lost their antennae.
The war against Mars.
Ah makes them sound...
For the beer.
The beer war.
Oh I thought you meant the dinosaur war.
Remember no sperm for beer and all that.
Yeah.
I totally forgot about that one.
I remember the dinosaur war.
You were supposed to forget about it.
I remember when Carter was there.
You know, Carter of Mars.
Yeah, Carter.
Jimmy Carter of Mars.
Those were the days.
Gerald Ford of Jupiter.
The really advanced presidents were like overmen.
They were highly trained in the mystic arts and could expel a pineapple from their nether regions.
They didn't need armies.
With unchewed and undigested.
They could swallow it down and expel it a day later completely whole.
Bringing the entire village good luck.
And then they could make...
Garfield could do that.
And making smoothies for all.
In fact, how do you think Garfield won the 1884 Transcendental Reerections?
Right, right.
Because, you know, Ohio is the father and the bad mofo of presidents.
Very strange and chanting.
They say he wandered very far.
Very far.
Over land and sea.
A little child.
And so...
Very wise was he.
So beautiful.
Very Well.
A littlejekky.
Stinky.
Stick to your thumb.
Index.
Little ring.
Pinky.
And the brain.
So the first thing was to provide setting for proper cultivation.
Discrete location.
Ten by ten foot spot.
Led up by a thousand watt lamp.
Plus two air vents for the air to circulate.
I calculate thirty gallons of water a week.
I'm really into this.
Now all I need is some good fertilizer and some photosynthesis to proceed.
After I choose the right seeds its all in motion.
With a little love and devotion.
I can make the front cover of high times.
I hope I'll never get.
Busted and have to pay some fines for having a
Secret garden like Barry White
I must not tell anyone
And keep my lips still tight
I got the growth
If you ain't never had the homegrown
It made you choke
Put your hands in the air
Zen note
And if you're high already
You can't take another toke
Put your hands in the air
Zen note
I got the growth
During the first stage of growth
The seeds germinate slow
Start a root system
Sprout up some leaves and grow
Towards the light
Make sure the temperature's right
I was told by this one guy
Watch your plants closely
You're aware of bugs and fungi
The hurt your garden
They'll only interfere with the vegetative growth
That lasts about two months to a year
When full grown flowers bloom
Big buds and leaves
Watch out for thieves
People like to stash it up their sleeves
It's now been three months
I'm tempted to break off a piece
And roll some blunts
I wonder what it is
Is this some skunk?
I see some purple stems and orange hairs
Could it be the humble mixed with Maui?
It's a hybrid
Look what I did
I got the green thumb
Observe the superb herb
Bushy branches loud
Smell light green pastel
I got it on deck for all seasons
And if anyone asks
It's herっと
Ne activated
Although veterans beef
We eat it
Like a
How cool is this?
What?
Where'd it come from?
room with dry air for two to three weeks and I'ma be waiting right here with my loose leaf
sheets to lovely harvest it came in different amounts four trees each one just a few grams
shorter than my family I can't wait to smoke it I know this this bomb been waiting so long
make me want to write a song I guess I'll sell two ounces and puff on the rest find a recipe
to sprinkle herb on my filet of chicken breast pour some tea chalk for the THC hit the bomb
cause openness wishes sweet then come off on me man stuck to my fingertips as I tried to break
it down it went limp the food was earthy the taste was profound it had me buzzing
for a light year and you best believe I'll have some seeds and be at it again yes indeed
if you ain't never had the homegrown they made you choke put your hands in the air and say no
and if you're high already you can take another coke put your hands in the air and say no
I got the
Put your hands in the air and say no
I got the flow
Grow Room by DJ Poo
And Mr. Grimm
And before that, Nature Boy
That very strange piece was by Artemia Salina
Hi, this is Jeff.
It won't take the government to interrupt our food supply.
There are scores of other man-made disasters
like a comet or an asteroid impact
that will do the job just as quickly.
Are you prepared for relief agencies
to get contaminated food and water to you in a major crisis?
One phone call and a food counselor
will come right to your family
and tell you that you're in a crisis.
You're in times of disaster.
And by then, it might well be 1953.
Call right now.
Free.
Right now.
Force Food.
24 hours a day.
The wait.
Force Food.
Is over.
Dr. Louis Therese is now available.
Nostradamus gave spams.
You're all ruled by the power of the Truth Seeker Company.
24 hours a day.
All right, go ahead.
Yes, sir.
Oh.
Who's that?
It's Micah, Paul.
That's what I was afraid of.
Micah.
I can smell you.
Well, I haven't had much breakfast.
The years haven't erased your stink.
No, he volunteered to take a bath.
All right.
Turn around.
Nice and easy.
Oh, go ahead.
Hold it, mister.
Throw that marshal down with your hands up.
Oh, boy, this is awful.
Oh.
Hey, I guess you're right.
I'll see you later.
That's it.
You passed the math test.
Oh, yeah.
That's right.
Don't leave me for so long
I'm a dear, a female dear
Little lady
That you bring us back to normal
Can you get to me?
I wanna know if you can get around
Can you get to it, baby?
It's not so far away as the crow flies
But I'm like a giant bird that can engulf space like a breath
Oh yeah, that'll take you there in no time
Hyper, hyper, hyperspace
With the back of your cerebral cortex passing away
You've taken too much, you've taken too much, you've taken too much
Ha ha
You sit and watch the evening news
In a trance, piss in your pants
You think there's a man outside
With a gun or a knife ready to take your life
And he sits there waiting for you
Behind the wall outside of your view
Your neighbor hears you screaming tonight
But you're too busy smoking
Yes, God
Too bad your mama found out
Supposed to be something
Not a target for a shot
Downtown, there's a room upstairs
Where nobody cares
You can yell all night
He got picked up at the bus stop
Had to get away, they had his DNA
How many broken bodies
Been inside the trolley?
Your baby's mama is crying tonight
But you're too busy smoking
Yes, God
Too bad the bottom dropped out
Too bad your mama found out
Ha ha
Who stopped the baby
He's singing and he pees
Yeah, intense
Peeing
To her
And that was by CB Truth from the CE Chemically Dependent.
Their name is like the object, CB.
And in fact you can check out www.cdtruth.com.
That's a C and a D and truth, all one word.
And now more no effects.
Whoops I OD'd.
Shorty, shorty, shorty, shorty.
So you guys know why you're going out on your side, right?
So we're running, possono.
反 никогда.
Cut my life
No second chance
No guiding light
I never meant
To cause
You pain
I never thought I'd be the one who took the fall
I got lost in the moment
Assholes like to test the limit
Six minutes down
Breathing machine
Brain not feel right
The look on you
Is killing me
Drowning in shame
But don't feel bad
Cause I
Never feared consequences
Hate regrets more than apologies
A year in
has passed Like photographs
My life is just A scrapbook of
Old friends and faded memories Looks like I pulled the rug from under myself
The fall's too much for me to recover from It's been real fun
But now I must say goodbye I'll see you all at Okie Dog's
See you all at Okie Dog's
Game! Game! Game! Game! Game! Game! Game! Game!
Come down!
He died too soon
Did he? I wonder
Men, friends, you have been listening to The Hour of Slack from the Church of the Subgenius
For more information, see www.subgenius.com
Or you can actually email me
stang
at
subgenius.com
stang at subgenius.com
Praise
Abe
Well, I've told you before that I will not tolerate brutality in this penitentiary
Why, you
Here, here, stop that
I'm sorry
I wasn't ready
Okay, please, answer me
I'm the passe pusher
I'm his best friend
Je bend unschuldig Woods
The type of soldier we had He would not mistake hoy in the ведьer read the spelling and order of sorcery
He creates muzzleudi campaigns when the death is a Barnachusetts shape spell
They combine to become one single blasphemula,
which makes a last tug of mycotic cell division,
and voila, there are now two worms where there once was one.
But what becomes of them now?
We'll learn not only that,
but also why the peen worm is so crucial to our nuclear beer
and even the Martian War in Series 9.
This show, The Hour of Slack.
If you need more information, please see subjeetius.com on the internet.
Please, Bob, I'm hoping now I can give out your phone number,
your own phone number for people to call me.
And now we'll copy the Firesign Theater again for those of you on drugs.
Okay, friends on the internet, where I can flog our swag legally,
if you want to help yourself and the Church of the Subgenius
and get a pretty cool package with like 25 different nifty things in it,
like pins and bumper stickers and a real preacher card,
you need to go to subgenius.com and click to become a minister.
You'll see photos and a list of all the stuff you get,
and you really do get to go to the,
the Subgenius Forum, which is members only,
and we talk in ways that people don't talk on Facebook.
Much, much smarter ways, ironically enough.
Isn't that funny?
We also have things like T-shirts and damn near everything you can think of
with Bob's face on it.
That and a huge selection of other subgenius graphics on coffee mugs and so forth.
And we sell several very weird DVDs and CDs of the Bob songs
and old MP3 stashes.
And you can buy all of that waiting for you at our online store.
And best of all, from our main online store,
you can buy The Book of the Subgenius,
which is by far the greatest thing we have ever done.
It's an actual Simon and Schuster book,
22 bucks, in print for over 30 years.
And every copy that we send out is signed by yours truly.
For that matter, your address on the puffy envelope is handwritten by me also,
so,
keeps my fingers nimble. That's subgenius.com. And remember, it's only money.