What, what, what?
The station's full of aliens.
And I'm sick to my stomach.
Look at this thing.
A fetus.
They've changed the way the boards are set up.
Yes, my friends, but we will persevere
because this is the hour of slack
on which we can only but, but seek
to find that which will play our takes.
Dr. Smith, radio operator.
I'm gonna bring you a piece of that green cheese for sure.
No trouble.
Get set, let's go and aim.
According, everything's going fine.
No trouble.
Oh, yeah.
Yes, dear friends, this is hour of slack number 1021.
Except that it's really a rerun of, get this,
hour of slack number three.
Yes, the third show.
Ever done.
And it was done 20 years ago this month
in early November 1985.
And it was done at the once good Dallas station, K-N-O-N,
the day after a big subgenius revival at a bar
called the Twilight Room.
It was a Halloween revival, which we called the Scary Ball.
And it was a show that starred Doctors for Bob
and Brother Cleve Duncan
and all sorts of guests from out of town,
some of whom were in the studio
for this third hour of slack,
including the baby Gary Gabrog-Fran
from the Puzzly Evidence Show,
the baby Dr. G. Gordon Gordon
in for Dobstown 3 in Brazil,
and the baby Dr. Onan Canobite,
all of them in the studio.
And we had really good,
good tapes of Doctors for Bob
live in concert the night before.
And you'll hear yours truly,
Reverend Ivan Stang, as a baby
and all hoarse from preaching
and confused at being a DJ at the mixing board
because it was only my third time.
I was 32.
An infant.
Still, friends, it proves the rock-steady
historical bedrock of slack.
It's so as evidenced by this ancient show
and then 20 years later,
this great music behind me,
which I'm playing right now,
which is from the new album
by the Flying Ryan Brothers
called Blue Marble.
Incredible instrumental dual guitar music
by these Flying Ryan Brothers.
Friends, you can get more information
about that from,
uh, ryanetics.com.
Uh, yes.
Sort of like Dianetics,
but it's the Ryan Brothers.
R-Y-A-N.
Ryanetics.com.
Uh, yes.
And, uh, so prepare yourself
to go back in time 20 years
to Hour of Slack number three.
R-Y-A-N.
Welcome, potential initiates,
and remain with us
for the next 30 minutes.
Mob?
The message is now part of
and registered in your subconscious mind
every time you say,
see, hear, or think.
What about slack?
That's your key phrase.
It will trigger the entire message
without your being aware of it.
Welcome to the subgenius radio ministry
Hour of Slack.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
This is Reverend Ivan Stang,
sacred scribe of the First Orthodox
Megafist Temple Lodge
of the Church of the Subgenius
with Pastor Buck Naked
of the First Naked Church of the Subgenius.
The opinions,
the opinions expressed
are not necessarily those
of this radio station.
Before the sermon,
a message concerning Bob Dobbs,
living avatar of slack,
and saint of silence
on planet Earth.
Are we controlled by secret forces?
Do you ever get the feeling
that free will is a joke?
Do people think you're strange?
Do you?
Then you may be on the right track.
Are you abnormal?
Then you are probably better than most people.
Yes, your time shall triumph.
Now, at last,
the step-by-step process is revealed.
This is it.
The only faith that promises
action, thrill, success in sex and business.
Bring your weirdest dreams
to rampaging life.
Stand erect for your own abnormality.
This is a way of life to millions.
Yet, half of them don't even know it.
He's the one true living slack master
with the spiritual know-how
to help you bash through the locked doorway
to financial heaven.
He is the one real shortcut to slack.
Now see another dimension on your TV.
Yes, fear the sharpest of removal no longer.
Become physically attractive overnight.
Attain status, luck, prosperity by blowing them off.
Bob's promise is to widen the scope and nature of abnormal behavior.
To explore new ways of going over the edge.
And coming right back.
Plus, bring back those who couldn't make it on their own.
To help you create the highest possible earnings.
From the psychodynamics of abnormality.
To turn conspiracy and blinded personality disorders around.
And channel them into an illusion of creativity.
That will fool normals and get you sex.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
Welcome, welcome once again.
And, uh, yes, after the usual slow takeoff,
it's hard to get these shows off the ground,
especially when you're at the very end of your so-called rope.
And, uh, indeed we are, folks, because we,
if any of you were at the amazing subgenius masquerade scary ball
last night at the Twilight Room.
More rope in here.
We came to show off the ground.
We're gonna make it big.
Yes.
No, there's no, you can use chewing gum and stuff.
That's the way this station is held together.
And, uh, oh, this station is on KNON 99.9 FM
in Dallas, Fort Worth, and Arlington.
Put one right in this, uh, in this thing.
Yeah, this, uh, body shrimp.
Now, who are you?
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
There's this, there was only supposed to be one person on this show.
And all of a sudden we've got shows from San Francisco and Brazil and Tennessee.
Yeah, yeah.
And we have walked in to the, uh, radio tabernacle here in Dallas, Texas.
Oh, yes.
Dear friends.
Reach for those checkbooks.
We're so...
That's right.
Reach for those checkbooks.
But you can't write that check to the subgenius foundation
because we can't pray for money over the air.
That's right.
Uh, with this FCC license.
But, but we can pray for you to send money to...
This station.
But we can ask you to bring all those things down to the stations now.
Yeah, more of those things.
The things that you keep in your drawers.
That's right.
Those little things that...
Without...
You don't want the...
You're not supposed to talk about drawers on this radio station.
Okay.
Dr. O'Brogue fan.
Keep in the bloomers.
Uh, bring those things.
Yeah, bloomers.
That's right.
That's it.
Okay.
Yes, bring those things, ladies and gentlemen.
And your parents.
Tell your parents to loosen right now because this is going to be the most offensive piece
of radio you've ever heard in Dallas, Texas.
Let's try.
We'll, we'll try.
We'll be...
Let's put it that way.
Uh, strangely enough, somehow the show has ended up with a number of subgenius,
celebrity guests.
That's right.
Dr. Gary O'Brogue, friend, star of the amazing subgenius show in Berkeley, California,
which you will be hearing on and off in a most confusing manner, uh, as we, as we slowly fade in.
Oh, wait.
What?
The collars?
Are there...
We finally got collars here.
Thanks, folks.
Poor girl.
She's in a bubbling vat of jokes.
We're going to throw a tarp over it and protect it from the elements.
Yeah, we may throw a tarp over it, but we probably, that's all we'll cover it.
This young lady has the jokes.
All day, yeah.
She's soaking in the jokes.
We didn't go to use them.
We're at the station right now.
We'll cover you up with something soft and warm, too.
We're going to have to reverse the charger.
This is a tarp that's been soaked in water.
You're already covered?
Well, yeah, good.
She has one of those champions.
Actually, you know, a lot of depilatories can help in these, uh...
She was covered pretty well, but maybe not.
With these little dishes, they're covered by the horrible fur that the KPFH...
See if you can get a good bow.
...each of their customers...
My screen.
Don't yell.
It's the only phone you have.
My screen's dark.
Okay, there we go.
What's happening to my picture?
Okay, that's very broad.
I don't know.
I wish I could go to sleep and forget about it all myself, but...
Listen, caller, okay, are you getting...
All these guys are dreams in my head.
There's a storm in here.
I'm getting cold.
I don't like it.
I'm in the dark.
I...
I do like it.
It's...
I want to go home.
This is the most miserable thing I've ever seen.
It's joyous.
I can't even see Mobius Rex now.
It's as dark as a poor thing.
Bit.
Bit, bit, bit.
We're having some more serious...
Serious technical difficulties here on the show.
We seem to be colliding with shows from other states.
It's so hard.
We gotta drag this show out into the big part of the auditorium, Doug.
No, no, no.
It's illegal to get this show out on the street in Dallas.
You're kidding.
Buck and I got...
We're almost arrested last week for driving this show up and down Central.
It's so hard.
What is this?
Story with this station.
At least they could give us air in here.
Well, it may be...
It may not be entirely their problem, Dr. Gabrog, friend.
It may be the fact that we've also got subgeniuses in this room from as far away as, yes, Brazil.
The incredible and rather disgusting Brazilian clench has been represented.
See, when we do a show at the Twilight Room, oh, people in Dallas.
People in Dallas, oh, they can't...
They don't always make it, but people from Knoxville, Tennessee, Santa Barbara, oh, Brazil of South America.
So we got the Dr. G. Gordon Gordon, mercenary of...
Slack from the Dobstown 2 plantation and zombie skull farm in Brazil.
Welcome, Dr. G. Gordon Gordon.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Yes, he's by far got the classiest accent of any subgenius.
Thank you.
And you see, these creatures that have entered this station are actually fallout from the incredible devival.
And it was a devival last night.
It was...
I feel thoroughly devived.
Yes.
I feel like I could just use a bit more, just a bit more of that liquid slack.
Pass another cup over here.
Here, here's a half-pound ton of slack.
Yeah, for those of you who were at the show last night at the Twilight Room and couldn't hear it,
we do have the amazing tapes that were recorded there.
So we will be cutting...
That's what we're saying.
No, no, that's why we're here, for people giving us things.
And we want people to bring those things down.
We want people to come to the station.
Yeah, this is a religion of...
We're asking for forgiveness, everything.
We want forgiveness from you and for us.
Yeah.
And hate from you for the conspiracy.
That's right.
The conspiracy that makes you not understand what we're talking about.
Because if it weren't for them, why, it'd be nothing on the air in Dallas except subgenius shows.
And you may groan to think such a nightmarish thought, but actually the...
Yeah.
We've decided...
Yeah, listen to them.
Even the subgenius doctors themselves in terrible, terrible pain.
We're near death here.
And believe me, we can't just ask you to walk out and kill normals.
We can't ask you to do that kind of thing on this station.
We can't ask you to do what would be the rightful work of Dobbs.
No, because it's against the law.
It's against the law for us to do those things.
Gary, would you get the show off Reverend Onan's foot?
I think it's perfect.
Oh, man.
The show...
I don't want to touch that show.
You know what happened last time?
I stuck my finger in the show.
Well, friends, we don't want to be talking about that.
There's just something wrong.
But we do also have Dr. Onan Canobite of the amazing subgenius band, Dr. Onan's Wotan Band,
as well as the famous occupant.
Yes.
Yeah, there.
Yes, you can hear.
Yes, yes.
Now, Dr. Onan is only a tape recording.
Yes.
And yet at the same time...
See, we've got a crowded show tonight.
We have over 100 guests.
Over 10,000.
And too many listeners.
I don't think that we can cram the show into that many radios.
I don't think it'll...
Just line up and keep it quiet here.
I haven't got enough room.
It's going to thin out.
Right.
If we try to reach too many listeners, it'll just dilute it.
Now, a subgenius church can be a franchise in your own area.
And it's also called, in church jargon, it's called a clench.
It's called a clench.
Now, Onan was the one who figured out...
Who started his own solo clench.
And it's schismed all over itself.
So tell us about that.
That's what you're most famous for in town.
I want you to know that.
I see.
Yes.
The solos...
The stark fist acting upon a solo clench resulting in ultimate schism.
And friends, you know, most of these religions...
Most of these religions...
They indulge in tremendous infighting between denominations.
We encourage...
We encourage infighting between denominations.
No two subgenius denominations should ever dominate one another,
especially not if they're the same.
And if any two subgeniuses are the same, one must die.
That's true.
Because this is...
It's different.
You know what I mean?
I was going to ask, Dr. Onan,
were you the one that had the first church in the round, the circumschism?
No, that was just hearsay, just rumor.
Oh, it's reverend hearsay.
Yes, I remember that.
Reverend hearsay.
These are the kind of things that we can't say on a radio station, KPFA in Berkeley, California.
These are the kind of guests that we can't have on our station.
Yes, but KNON is a non-station, you see.
And because of that, we can get away with things that they would never suspect anyone of.
Especially not us.
But we're going to...
We've got to...
See, the problem is...
We have so many great tapes that we can play for you, all by subgeniuses.
And you would think, no, I don't want to hear a bunch of amateur...
Garage bands.
But, you see, music by subgeniuses could include...
And let me name drop, boys.
Let me name drop.
Music by subgeniuses could include George Clinton, Devo, Ernest Tubbs,
and even Dr. Onan Canabite, who is here and whose tape we are about to play now.
You can buy this tape, friends, from the Subgenius Foundation,
but it's against the law for us to tell you that.
So, turn off your tape recorders.
And indulge in a little...
And after Dr. Onan's, I think we'll be flipping Wellmans out
and going into the next little Wellman of the revival,
the Scary Ball revival.
Last night.
Thank you, dear friends.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Thank you.
Yes, dear friends, that was the amazing Dr. Onan.
Well, that was actually Occupat.
And they're a panting bunch.
Now hold it.
What was that?
Clown the ballerina here and there.
Clown the ballerina air feed.
Oh, no, that's not.
That was mean.
Why'd you do that to that little girl?
You've got to get the babies out of this room.
It's hard to find a place to sit or walk.
You guys act like a bunch of babies.
What are you doing on the air?
A bunch of stinky little subgenius rats.
Well, what about Roo Mouse and what about Paul's kitty?
Well, it's also illegal to talk about California deities in Texas, Dr. Gbrog.
Friend, there's only room for so many religions in this corporate state.
What happened to ecumenism?
Whatever happened?
I mean, how come we got California deities and Texas deities?
Is this a state church?
What is the problem here?
Exactly what?
I can't.
I can't worship Bohandas and the radio station in my house in Texas.
All hail Roo Mouse and Bohandas.
And we shouldn't be peeking out the meter so badly.
Yeah, but what about Bob?
What about Slack and what about the conspiracy?
What about them?
Yeah.
The conspiracy.
The conspiracy has given me so much more than Bob ever gave to me.
Yeah, it's true.
The conspiracy does pay better than Bob Dobbs or, for that matter, almost any other religious savior.
But the conspiracy isn't.
It's not quite as much fun.
And we had a...
Did you get the check in the mail?
Yeah, I got the check.
You see what I mean, folks?
Go tell Stang.
I just...
Go tell me.
The Bob said came down and said the check's in the mail and I haven't heard from him since.
You guys are going to have to talk to doctors for Bob about that.
Hey, where's my...
Okay.
Well, folks, for those of you who weren't at the scary ball last night, that's too bad.
But for those who were and still couldn't hear it because of the strange acoustics that go with rock and roll,
performances, we are bringing in some beautiful lilting melodies from Doctors for Bob,
most of whom could not be here tonight.
Some of them are lost in the station and we're digging through these boxes of cassettes.
I want to say I just stepped on Buck.
That's right.
Oh, poor Buck.
It's okay, Buck. Get up. You'll be all right.
Okay, well, the Twilight Room...
We'll just go ahead and play this lovely...
Just remember, if you'd been there last night, you'd be changed.
But we're going to start off...
We're going to start off with a religious gospel hymn from Doctors for Bob called,
You Can't, and that is, Can't Hide from God.
Because he's mean.
You can't hide from God.
Because he's bigger than you.
Help me, somebody.
You can't hide from God.
Because he's bigger than the whole universe.
Help me, somebody.
You cannot hide from God.
Because he's bigger.
All reality.
Help me, somebody.
You cannot hide from God.
You cannot run from your own legs.
Is there a person in this place tonight who can run from their own legs?
You can'tool see your own eyes.
You can't turn them inside out.
I ain't gonna see your own eyes.
You can't see your own eyes.
But if you put your Bible up, if you put your Bible up...
You cannot see your own eyes
You cannot run from your own legs
You cannot hide from God
Help me somebody
She ain't got no legs
My legs on fire
They're a problem
My mind's still okay
Right side
You cannot wet water
How you gonna wet water?
You can throw water on it
That's gonna make more water
You cannot wet water
You cannot see your own eyes
You cannot run from your own legs
You cannot wet water
Hey look!
Prepare for the auto-cataclysm of my hoarding food
Gold, guns, ammo, and gas
Long-term survival techniques
and learning
Of course, you don't want to kill a subgenius believer.
God's judgment is going to come and fall again upon a godless, Christ-rejecting, blasphemous society.
Well, if this sounds paranoid, you're right.
But I think I have good reason to be paranoid.
It's a strange world out there.
This is what life is like at a bottom-line level.
And I'm not going to make you cut through a lot of other stuff to get through it.
Here's what it is.
There's no gimmick about that.
It's straightforward.
It's strong.
And it's elemental.
We are heavy stuff.
Rich crap.
Voodoo.
Devil worship.
Wild.
Gnome.
Animal hunger will grow in you.
Learn our need.
What about Funto?
Because those confuse people.
Bohandas was walking through Tokyo.
Bohandas is the friend of all the little children.
And what about Wolwo?
Yes, friends.
Halloween is getting closer and closer.
And it is going to be very scary.
Very scary in the subgenius world.
And even out there in the world of reality.
Stand up on your feet.
Everybody wants to have three ladies and go bar soup.
I can't take it.
You can't clean.
You can't wash soap.
What are you going to do?
Cut that bar of soap in half and rub it against itself?
Soap is the cleanest thing known to man.
You can't wash this show out of your ears either.
You tried scrubbing it out.
You tried rubbing it out.
You tried scouring it out.
This is the show that stinks.
You go listen to six hours of Beethoven right now.
And I can guarantee you, you'll still hear this show tomorrow morning.
That's right.
That's the thing about these subgenius shows is you can turn off your radio.
You can stop your car.
You can run away from it.
But you keep hearing it laying in bed at night.
Close your eyes.
You can even put the cables to your power supply and you still get the show.
Oh, it's a scary show at times.
It's in my ear.
No, no, that wasn't.
That's not the show.
That's one of those creatures that are with the show.
That's right, Dr. Jewell.
That was that thing that was growing on you earlier today.
Oh, no.
It's in my ear now?
It's in your ear.
Oh, no.
I'm going to have to change shirts as well as shorts.
This is awful.
Well, doctors, what do you think?
I'm going to have to change my clothes.
I've got a whole stack of Wellman hair and we've got everything from more of last night's
Twilight Room to more sick music by Healthy Sub-Gene Eye and vice versa.
Let's vote.
Call into the station right now and vote.
That's right.
Even though we can't take your calls on the air, you can still call this station.
You can vote.
Pastor Beckett will take your calls.
By your own personal biorhythms.
Calculate your vote.
Even if we give you your own phone number over the air.
Yes, call in.
What is your phone number, by the way?
And we'll call you.
That's right.
Go ahead and call us and tell us your phone number.
Because we can't remember our phone number over here.
Oh, you want the phone number?
Yeah.
What is the phone number?
Okay.
To call us here, Sub-Genius calls it.
Why not?
Here's your shit.
Do it now or you might forget.
Boy, Buck does that so nicely.
He does.
Buck is a professional.
Can you call out to California and say his station ID for us?
Cool.
Buck underwent four operations to get his vocal cords to be able to do this.
I'll do that.
But he still hasn't been Wellmanized.
Well, let's do that to him after the show.
And I'll inform the head.
The head.
What about the head?
What about the scary poster of Doc's thing?
That evil head.
There's no sign of Wellman.
We're just land loading right here and hoping that we can get in touch with whoever that
attack is.
Wellman's gone.
Yeah, Wellman's gone.
But if we can just get the head inside that lead-lined vault, we'll be okay.
Wellman's gone.
He's gone.
That's a good lead on Stoke.
Friends, beware that head.
It's safe.
Yeah.
I left the little Wellman at home, but he won.
The bleeding head of Arnold Palmer rose slowly above the trap between the third and fourth
greens down at Onion Creek Country Club and Golf Course.
Thumping slowly like an over-enlarged fig, the bleeding head slowly rose above the trap,
gentle angle above the green, dripping blood. It hovered briefly over the sand trap and
then slowly ascended towards the constellation of Orion at an angle of about 44.325 degrees,
like a shot off a shovel. There was no doubt that it was the head of Arnold Palmer. That
moon-faced smile was unforgettable. The population of southeast Austin went wild. They tore
off their clothes, danced in the streets and said, the bloody head has come. The time is
here. Take off your clothes and be somebody. The bloody head of Arnold Palmer was above
the Repository圖Way area, lo했다 above a tower and was with a
ors Kim void. I joined upon a
p DW
driving
...
o
P
.
14 linear. 20att
At 14 minutes after 9, the bleeding head was sighted on the forward control radar access plant at Barksdorm Air Force Base.
Three interceptors were scrambled, one of which crashed on takeoff.
They could find nothing. Radar was still tracking the head.
The bloody head moved north, rocketed over Dallas and Fort Worth.
The radar at Caswell Air Force Base gave subsequent indications that something large and wet was moving north-northeast,
while ascending still upwards towards the constellation of Orion.
The bloody head moved on.
Fourteen ex-virgins were rejuvenated in Lubbock as the head passed through.
...raise those tapes properly, they'll just go out on you and come in at all hours.
The prodigal tape returns.
Yeah, you raise them no matter how much trouble you go to, to raise these tapes right, they go awry.
Rub magnets on the back of those.
Yeah, and they still go out.
Yeah, it's lovely. It's a miracle.
What's happening?
I don't know. I think the show just died.
This is Saturday. Are we in Little Rock?
No, no, we were in Little Rock on Wednesday.
Yeah, we're going to be in Sanford.
We're going to be in L.A. next month.
Is this subgenius?
world revival crusade continues next cities are are my my hometown of san francisco i know there's
a lot of people that are afraid to know there's a person from san francisco in town because you
think you might catch something you're from san francisco get out of here you guys run
but i want to tell you liberalism is not contagious folks
stupidity might be jobs
have some more pills go right here the whole bucket yep we got the famous bucket of pills
here we didn't bring the bucket of pills to the scary ball at last night because only a
you know only three or four thousand showed up yeah there weren't enough people to
yeah i mean i've heard that expression you're a really great audience before but
but why lie exactly really
yes at the
you
Twilight Room, folks, you'll find at least 50% of the people,
although it is a wonderful club and they do let us go in there and hurt the audience,
half of those people spend $30 on haircuts that are supposed to illustrate
that they don't care how they look.
But it's very important to them that they are seen looking at bands
with a critical expression on their face.
And a $30 haircut.
Seeing as how they're too, well, let's just put it politely,
cool to be actually up there on a stage attempting to injure the audience themselves.
Or make a fool of themselves by dancing and responding to music.
Who called Doctors for Bob a band in the first place?
An act.
Yeah, they dared call it.
John Anders called Doctors for Bob an act.
Well, if Doctors for Bob is an act,
then that woman who came home bleeding to death from losing her legs last night
deserves an Academy Award.
Copy.
Right, 1985, Jane or Hyperveet.
Well, we're going to return to that lovely, lovely experience.
My legs are on fire.
The studio's on fire.
Yes, we'll be returning to the Twilight Room right about now.
We feel like there needs to be an explanation for our very existence,
so we've got a little piece here that's called The Explanation.
For that very reason.
Before we go on,
we'd like to thank our sponsors.
We are the
Quote
Version
Unquote
We'd just like to take this opportunity to state briefly and for the record
that my fellow Doctors for Bob and myself
are members in good standing of a church.
But not just any church.
For the church to which we belong
just happens to be
beyond a shadow of a doubt.
The world's only bogus true religion.
Of course, I am referring to
the Church of the Subgenius.
To the city!
Now the Church of the Subgenius,
as founded by J.R. Bob Dobb,
Santa Fe, El Paso, and 1953,
is the grand religion of the future.
Uniting superior mutants,
social renegades,
twisted geniuses,
and sci-fi.
Unite!
Unite sinners!
In a worldwide
rrrrrrrr lamp-frame
of em-mari
and prophetic
yucks
and grins!
Yucks and grins which will hopefully, inevitably, lead us directly to a commodity all through the after.
And today is Father's Day and you go vote society.
And that commodity, grins, is
SLACK!
Now slack is what the conspiracy wants to take away from us.
Slack is what the conspiracy wants to drive us.
Slack is our way of grabbing money.
And we're not going to be locked by the lapels and screaming at it.
Now back in the 50's, Bob himself noticed a decided lack of slack in our culture.
He noticed an awful prevalence of normalcy.
He noticed that the normals formed a vast conspiracy against the different.
An insidious conspiracy dedicated to squelching our natural rogue instincts.
Dedicated to wiping out our fun factors.
Dedicated in short, to the total and utter eradication of the original slack with which we were all born.
Well Bob wanted to fight this conspiracy, ladies and gentlemen, and what better way I ask ye
than by the foundation of a major new world religion.
It's the Church of the Subgenius.
Praise Bob!
Oh, help me somebody!
Now many people I know view the conspiracy on a very tiny arcane and mealy-mouthed level.
You see the conspiracy only at the US government, the CIA, FBI, Lutheran Church, Missouri Synod, Catholic Church,
Jewish and Minstrel League, Council on Foreign Relations, or Trilateral Commissions.
Other more occultated individuals can see to the next level.
You see the conspiracy as the men in black, the green energy demons, the advanced supersonic Nazi hell creatures from the hollow earth,
the henchmen of Negian, the Yakutism.
But even they don't have the full story, ladies and gentlemen.
For I'm here to tell you tonight that the conspiracy exists as none other than Jehovah One,
alien space god of wrath from some corporate sin galaxy and his stark fist of removal.
Oh, help me somebody!
Not many of you here tonight, I'm sure.
The Church of the Subgenius may sound a bit, oh, demonic.
And you're right, it is demonic.
But well, speaking of benevolent demons, here, well the Church of the Subgenius does recognize it.
Every major deity of every world religion, Jesus, Buddha, Krishna, Mohammed, Elvis, Earl, Hank, Buck.
Rather than having one central authority great figure, the Church of the Subgenius possesses an entire pantheon,
or subgenion is the word, what are referred to as short duration personal savior, or surdurper sa.
Now, as in any other major world religion,
the Church of the Subgenius has certain inalienable tenets,
certain basic precepts around which a life philosophy can be formed,
the most important of which are...
Too much!
Is always better!
But not enough!
Not enough!
Too much!
But is it always better than that?
Make your children pray to God!
Help me somebody!
One soul per breath.
I've done you a little more money on that soul.
This soul's already hocked up to its neck.
Jehovah 7, Jehovah 12.
Guy, that's gonna cost you another soul.
There's three more souls.
Give me a double smudge bucket of that air.
Here at the station, we don't have to worry about this.
We've got the souls of the listeners on the way.
Listeners out there, I'm like, I'm sorry to have to tell you this so late,
but after listening to a subgenius show for more than 43 minutes,
we can put a lock on that soul.
Ah, yes, smell it.
And you know, we use your souls to generate new church air
for we the famous subgenius preachers.
That's right.
While you're at work, we're here spending your money and breathing your air.
15 bucks at least.
That's right.
And that's the red scent for entropy.
B.O.D.
B.O.B.
Bop.
Grrr.
Thank you.
You know, they sneak in here.
We're foolish enough to let Dr. Gabrog Fran sneak his California-isms into this beautiful and native Texas show.
Yes, remember the Alamo.
Remember Bob Dobbs.
I can't wait to get home to go ride some waves.
I'm going smurfing, Gary.
I'm going to go to a smurf burning next week.
Come on, no smurfing so far out.
Well, folks, we've got a choice between playing.
You know, it in some ways is less than an hour and more than a show here.
I think it's less than a show and less than an hour.
Yeah, it's kind of.
It's like three-quarters of a show in 45 minutes, basically, is what you're getting.
Yeah, but that's good because that means we can go home and go to bed.
Crack the statues on their own.
Doug, the people know that we're already home in bed.
This is taped.
We're not here.
And my name isn't Doug.
I'm not Doug either.
So I think we come to an excellent.
Yes, the Ching flings.
The Ching flings.
Oh, no.
Let's throw one of those icy Chings and see how it melts and see what it tells us of our future.
Which anagram does it say?
Or hexagram or whatever they call us.
It says.
Milligrams.
Ice.
A milligram of your fortune, friends.
Bad news tomorrow.
It's Monday and you've got to go to work.
But we don't.
Yeah.
Well, speak for yourself.
Speak for yourselves, boys.
Reach out the chair.
We subgenius preachers never die and we never stop working.
It's a sad, sad.
Except when we spend all that money that those people send in for us.
That's right.
Remember, your subscription money goes directly into.
Listen to that money burn.
Listen to Dr. Gordon burn the contributions of those who spend brave enough to send some money to the subgenius church.
Wait a minute.
These are cruzeros.
These aren't dollars.
I can't spend those here.
They got the wrong print.
Dead president on them.
Oh, there's a dead American president.
They're a lot easier to spend.
Well, it seems like soon we'll have to go into our lovely, amazing sign off music, which is, by the way, done by another famous subgenius.
A couple of subgenius famous ministers.
Reverend Mark Mothersley and Reverend Byron Warner.
Even others.
Yes.
And so we find our time is running out.
And it's sad that we have only one hour for each.
And we're outcast.
But you know, it all balances out.
One great religious evacuation.
And I would recommend reading for scriptures 16, 14, 17, 18.
And you can write for information on how to order these wonderful, precious tapes.
Get your pencils ready.
And we'll be reading the address very soon.
We need that money for the home for slackless children.
And your contributions also keep those we hate starving today.
I command you to spill your gifts.
See, plan to one hundred pounds of dollar bills on.
Dr. Gordon's lap.
And this will buy only clay and transform her toys for those poor children.
Dogs will bless you for coming to see Faith.
Amen.
And now the announcer will give our mailing address.
That's the church of the subgenius.
Write for information to P.O.
Box.
181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
WWF.
www.subgenius.com.
Thank you, friends.
This is Reverend Ivan Stang with Dr. Gary Gibrote, Fran Pester, Buck Naked, Dr. Onan,
Kenobite, G. Gordon, Gordon, and all the other nameless subgenius doctors.
Doctors.
We just found out this is the subgenius minister, the great saint of subgeniosity,
George Clinton.
That's right.
You're going to watch him .
It is now20 analyst.
Cook with now19art.com.
¶¶