And, uh, gosh, tonight, friends, I had to bring my little dafter, Sivit, the Blivit, down here.
I guess just to show off to her friend, Em.
Tell Em hello. Go ahead.
Hi, Emily.
Okay, that's done.
And, uh, we can soon get into the show.
The horrible show, tonight's show, specializing in the, uh, or featuring the oral tradition of the Pobucker.
Ah, yes.
This film is shown to you not only for the benefit of your own personal good health, but for that of your entire unit.
Lights out.
Some of the things that you'll see...
...that you'll soon see are highly spectacular.
But let me assure you that they are authentic in every respect and are dramatic proof of the excellence built in to your...
...subgenius.
Our most watch.
Now, see for yourself and take what you find here and put it to work.
I am authorized to assure you that so far there is no reasonable cause for alarm.
Cover yourself with wet newspapers and lies.
Stay still until the blast has subsided.
Oh my God.
Have no fear.
You will not be hypnotized.
You will not lose consciousness.
Nor will you be made uncomfortable in any way.
Bob?
The message is now part of and registered in your subconscious mind.
Every time you say, see, hear, or see something, you are not alone.
Think.
Bob?
That's your key phrase.
It will trigger the entire message without your being aware of it.
We are controlling transmission.
Now, did you ever see anything as new and as fresh looking as that?
It's so new, it's almost too new to be true.
Don't kill that.
Well, we take our initiates and we string a little tendon between their heels...
...and drag them three times around the radio station before beginning.
Then we dip them in the sacred waters of the slot.
And what exactly does this do for them?
Well, it causes them to forget everything they've learned...
...and it prepares their mind for the slate-like impression, the imprinting of the true subgenius.
You know, by golly, he's absolutely right.
Wake up, puppet boy!
Oh!
Unbelievably big sea monsters.
Sea. Man-eating bugs. Bigger than buildings.
A spectacular adventure on the Angry...
Subgenius Hour of Swatch.
A Mother Nature-grown berserk striking back at the industrial society that has exploited her.
We must stop it. Mankind hangs in the balance.
It's just crazy enough to work.
Oh, Jim. Don't make me relive that nightmare.
The Subgenius Hour of Swatch.
Clean, aristocratic, modern styling. Truly distinctive.
There it goes. A little scuff, but basically undamaged.
That's us, friends. A little scuff, but...
Uh...
Yeah.
Yes, it's gonna be a study in Pobuckerdom tonight.
A study of the oral tradition of the Pobucker.
We have many funny and revealing, and yes, telling, telling...
...archival recordings of Pobuckers, both subgenius and pink, in top spouting mode.
And also some of the all-time great...
...moments in talk radio.
Uh...
You'll certainly want to have your illegal bootlegging equipment up and running at all times.
But before...
I guess before we sing the song of the Pobucker, we'll let...
We'll go into this, uh...
...this little section of tape.
Jane Eyre Hypercletes, I think, is mayhaps the...
...the greatest of the subgenius Pobucker scholars.
And we'll let him speak for everyone.
Here we go, here we go!
Ah!
Savage and deadly, their one hope is to rule our planet as they once had thousands of years back.
And that ain't all...
...since!
The Pobucker's Pobucker
They steal cars!
There's just certain areas of Southwest City that are designated as Bobby-Free Tollway Zones.
You park in a Bobby-Toeway Zone, that ain't your car anymore, that's Bobby's car.
Hey, wait, where are you going with my car?
Sorry, this ain't your car anymore.
Check your city map, you in a Bobby-Free Tollway Zone.
But there's not any kind of sign!
See that cigarette butt?
But laying on the ground, that's your sign.
No, don't steal my car.
You can have my incurable cancer.
You can have my deaths.
You can have my screaming bratty kids.
You can have my bitchy wife.
But just don't take my car.
I'm taking your car, boy.
No, wait.
You can have my personality defects.
You can have my schizophrenia.
You can have the voices I hear in my mind.
You can have my personal problems.
You can have my $3,000 debt.
But just don't take my car and my mistress.
You're in a Bobby Free Tollway zone.
Your mistress is in a Bobby Free Tollway zone, too.
Bobby, no.
Bobby, please.
Thank you, Bobby.
You know, Bobby can steal cars that, even if they ain't whole cars, he can...
Like, I mean, who's going to buy their garden salvage yard?
All there are are just rusted out frames out there.
Bobby just got in the chassis of a...
A rusty, rusted out old 57 Chevy.
It didn't have an engine.
It didn't have tires.
It didn't have...
It didn't have a body.
It didn't have nothing.
I just...
Don't ask me how, but Bobby somehow hot-wired it.
Drove that sucker home.
He said all this needs is a couple of lug nuts.
He just put a couple of lug nuts on there.
Lo and behold, there was a car.
There was one old car.
There was nothing left of it but a camshaft.
Just an old camshaft laying there on the ground.
There wasn't anybody going to guard it.
Just an old camshaft.
Now, don't ask me how.
Bobby Free just started it up and just drove it off.
Just an old camshaft.
Then Bobby can just change it into a brand new car.
He just took some paint out.
He took some spray paint.
He painted it.
There was a car sitting there.
Freaked me out.
He sold it to Billy Ray for $20,000.
Billy Ray took his gal, Charlene, to the drive-in movie.
He was making out with her.
I was sitting in a bar with Bobby.
All of a sudden, Bobby just said,
Look at this.
Took two lug nuts out of his pocket.
That car just disintegrated.
Just turned back into a camshaft.
Science was baffled and powerless.
This is confusing.
A terror-stricken humanity knew that it was on the brink of total destruction.
Well, things are looking up.
A once proud civilization now had to place its trust and hope in Godzilla
and his powerful ally, Bob.
Type.
Make-Ins Titan.
Giant against giant in the most spectacular battle yet.
You'll see it all in Godzilla vs. Megalon.
But things weren't normal.
There were changes.
Ah!
Your mother bit me.
I never saw him by like that.
It's a beautiful sight.
Strange.
Frightful changes.
That night, it all started.
Stop doing that.
Oh!
Take this line.
Boy, here's what I call the McCounty line.
Step over this line, you stand in the McCounty.
You break the law over here in the...
In Arkansas, we got three kinds of laws.
Commissar meter, felony, and sodomy.
Felony will get you sent to this federal penitentiary.
Sodomy will get you sawed, boy.
Cut you in half.
Have some of me and you get busted.
You get busted for a...
Sodomy in their precinct.
They're just gonna cut you a little bit.
You get busted for a sodomy in my precinct, I'm gonna cut you, boy.
I'm gonna hurt you.
I'm gonna cut you in half, and I want you to know that.
You cross over...
I don't know how they do things out in California or Los Angeles or wherever the hell you come from.
I'm just saying that you cross over this line, you're in...
You're in standing in the McCounty line.
You're standing in McCounty.
You break the law in McCounty, I shoot you dead.
You fall over dead on that sidewalk, I give you a ticket for loitering.
You don't pay that ticket for loitering within 30 days, I'll throw you in jail.
And jail's one place you sure as hell don't want to be, especially if you're dead, boy.
You're in standing in the...
...on the...
...rest of the...
...part of your...
...are rewarded...
Oh, boy.
Are you listening to this show on a stereo or a...
Well, you...
Hello, am I still here?
I keep...
Of course, Frank, you're still here.
...being hit on the finger bone by this other person, you know, this other one.
Well, you know, some folks are...
Well, and how...
...they take the show on their fillings and their teeth.
I don't know, well...
I mean, how did you know about this show?
Come on, admit it, fess up, get it off your chest.
I just know my friend told me.
Aha.
Word of mouth.
Okay, put that down.
Now, are you a Democrat or a Republican?
I'll get it.
Oh, I'll get it, no.
I'm...
It just doesn't matter.
I'm not into politics or political things.
Well, they're into you...
And where are you calling from?
...to the tune of a $4 trillion debt.
General Jigar, after you're out on the air.
Yeah, I don't know if they have anything to do...
But it doesn't matter, I don't vote.
Okay, here we go, line 17.
Where are you calling from, mother's maiden name and...
Ah, yes, the tune of the unknown voter in Washington, D.C., our nation's capital.
Oh, yes, we better just vote for these unknown fornits here.
I'll get the word out, probably.
Well, we're not that unknown.
When you cast your vote for us, you're really voting for change that is a spare change for
both of us.
Oh, right on.
I mean, for...
You could call it chump change.
Yeah, what are you saying?
Is it time to change your tape if you're doing a 90-minute tape?
That's right.
If you're taping this marvelous show with its splendid sound effects, it's now time
to discontinue your 90-minute tape and flippancy-flop it over.
Oh, did I do the tape?
Oh!
Flippancy-flop it over.
I'm sorry, excuse me.
That was, uh, I was impetuous, a youthful impetuousness.
I often go off that way.
There we go.
I need a, I need a bucket of ice water dashed across my loins.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I hate to get on your shows, but I do, I do, I do, I do think I make myself a big deal
Then I'm myself again.
Okay, I, uh...
It's that disease I caught in the tropics.
Uh, what...
That's how we wake up for each show.
Oh, that terrible alarm clock.
Then I'd better get off the phone with you guys, because this, I do not want to create
the most enormous phone bill.
Oh, you're calling from outside the caller area.
Well.
Yeah.
Thanks for lending your, dulcet tones.
Thanks for lending your voice and angelic presence to our divine symposium.
Unless you have a, a much more cheaper form of calling.
Well, you can come down and be on the show.
Now we'll get...
some cheap person to call next.
Good evening, Bob.
Good evening, Rocky.
I'm very, very confused.
Well, what are you confused about?
I'm kind of confused myself,
and we all get to that point in our life,
but we have to stop,
sit down, smell the roses,
and try to put our morals together
and see what's wrong,
what seems to be out of place tonight with you.
Well, first of all, Rocky,
I mean, you used to be very, very selective
with who you would call.
Oh, now you're calling just anybody.
Well, I'm going to become more selective
to who I call against.
Gee, some people just don't appreciate good callers.
I'm not too concerned about what Sick Norman says or does.
I ain't never calling that freak.
I ain't listening to his show.
That's it.
Forget about that fat boy.
That man is a real...
real smooth-talking Yankee
that come down here,
come down to my neighborhood,
my Southland,
my Coat-of-the-Hills area.
He wants to tell me
and everybody else
what to do and how to live.
I want my statements made.
I want the people to listen to me.
I am the man on the phone.
I am the man that calls these people.
I ain't got no book in front of me.
I ain't got no magazine in front of me.
I'm sitting here in a phone booth.
I am not fading into an oblivion.
I am going to be stronger, harder.
You talk about your solar-flex machine.
Are you going to break out of the jug again, Rocky?
Oh, no.
My voice might sound a little bit different tonight.
Does it?
Well, yes, it does.
That's because I'm in a phone booth
and it sounds like I'm in an echo chamber.
And I'm in a phone booth.
A lot of times when I sing,
I sing in a phone booth.
You go in the phone booth and sing?
I'm a songwriter, Mr. Lassler,
and I'm also a poet.
I'm also a person that cares more
about people out here
than the people that call in
and they just say,
Rocky's a bum.
He hates everybody.
Authorities believe that he had as many as 18 women
living in a large house there with him
playing the role of wives
in a polygamous situation.
And that, uh, that he, uh,
had at least one of them.
Well, yes, he did.
Please!
Let me out!
Let, let, let, let me out!
It doesn't look good.
You know, sometimes I think all North Americanos are crazy.
If he's dead, you waste your money.
If he's alive, maybe you'll be sorry you find him.
Yeah.
No, we...
We must find Bob.
Now I tell you what I believe.
Yes, what about it?
This beast exists because it is stronger than the thing that you call evolution.
Bob is stronger than...
In it is some force of life, a demon driving it through millions of centuries.
No, it can't.
It does not surrender so easily to weaklings like you and me.
Now look, we're not paying you to make jokes.
Bob loves us.
No joke.
Well, I'll try to explain it to you.
Sometimes a species gets isolated in time.
If the conditions are right, it reproduces itself without change,
skipping a chapter of evolution.
Way back, there must have been some major link between Bob and terrestrial life.
It's just possible that this is it.
Well, that's all there is to it.
And that, kiddies, is our fairy story for tonight.
And now...
And that, Civet, is our fairy story for tonight.
Now we have to get down to the brass tacks, to the real thing, right?
Right.
Like, uh...
Well, how would you define a po-bucker, Civet?
What would you think of when I say the word po-bucker?
Cheap.
Well, maybe we should do the song.
Some, because many, some po-buckers are very generous.
I think perhaps what you mean is poor.
But that's not always the case either, for there are many, many a rich po-bucker.
They're the most dangerous of all.
Let's, let's, let's do our song, okay?
Okay.
This is an old song that we made up a couple years ago on the road in our vacation in Appalachia.
That one.
I'm a po po po bucka I like to cuss and drink
But there's one thing that makes my head hurt Please don't ask me to thank
That's it dear friends.
And in honor of this well some further exploration into that world
Well actually what I should do is tell you what we've been listening to first.
The collage tapes.
The pepper all the hour of slack shows tonight have been a combination of tapes by the good Joe Riley.
Bob Hall.
The tape Beatles.
And everyone else.
Puzzling evidence and so forth.
You heard.
Some Jane or hyper cleats there from the new Southland Corporation rock opera called Tales of Bobby Free.
The pieces we heard were Bobby Free Toe Away Zone.
And the McCounty piece from Cherry Don't Cry.
Jane or Hyper Cleats Southland Corporation.
We also heard some KPFA Berkeley.
Puzzling evidence and Dr. Howell's genius show.
Attacking the callers.
And some of those callers then later came to include.
Well these old rednecks.
Pobuckers and.
Coups crackpots and subgeniuses.
On the apparently the Bob Lasseter show.
This tape was sent in by.
The St.
Dave Mitchell of Headlines magazine.
And I'd like to continue with these pieces from the Bob Lasseter show.
And thank you.
You see this is the point I'm trying to make.
I wish these people would forget about New York for long enough to try to grasp what I'm trying to do.
Here.
They have to realize that.
They're in my neighborhood.
I was born and raised in this area.
And all my ancestors were.
These people are coming in here pushing me around.
Said hey.
I want to raise taxes here.
We want to build a stadium over here.
We don't want that.
Us good old boys.
We want our pickup trucks.
We want our Magnums.
We want our blonde blue women.
And maybe a little snort of Jack Daniels every once in a while.
I heard on the radio.
Today.
They're going to have to cut the water down.
The bridges are falling down because the Yankees come down here.
They don't know how to build a bridge.
Now they're all falling down.
And now they realize that the Yankees can't even build a bridge.
So they got to go to France and get them to build bridges.
They got to get them from Romania and build bridges.
Because we ain't got nobody left here that wants to work for an honest day's living.
It's too hot for them.
They got to spend all the money on beer.
All roads.
I don't care how many marshmallows a man eats.
I don't care how many rich crackers these Yankees come in and buy these stores.
They ain't supporting me.
Yankees are known to eat marshmallows?
They eat marshmallows like they're going out of style.
They do?
They eat them like crazy.
Very rarely do you see a confederate going in a grocery store and buying marshmallows.
You won't see me buying no moon pies and RC Cola.
I won't do it.
And I ain't buying no more Pepsi either.
Now I'll drink a Coke.
But I'm not buying no Pepsi and I think you can figure that one out.
Why?
No I can't.
I tell you because Michael Jackson is behind that.
Oh.
He's up here buying and selling all this advertising, all this Pepsi.
Wait a second.
Don't they have wine over there?
They drink a whole lot of deris and Coke and Pepsi.
When they drink a Coke, they ain't going to buy it.
They're going to put it on the TV screen.
But Rocky.
Go ahead.
I'm listening to you.
I think this Coke hired Lionel Richie.
If he does, it's too bad because I'll boycott both of them.
I'll go to Sprite.
I'll go to 7-Up.
I'll make my own brew.
Well, don't you remember the guy, you know, for 7-Up, that black man with the bald head?
Oh, you're right.
There goes 7-Up too.
You're right.
And Sprite is made by either Coke or Pepsi.
I'm going to go to Sprite.
Coke makes the Sprite.
It's all controlled by the same people.
There was a time in the South when we didn't have Coca-Cola.
The only place you could get that was up where the Yankees lived.
We were happy with our Sassafras.
We were happy with our Shine.
But you had to have all these Yankees come down here and tear down all the stills.
Yankees don't even like the cars.
I don't think we got all the stills.
Well, they ain't got the stills.
They ain't got mine.
Didn't think so.
I got my still up here in Clearwater, and they never, ever going to bust it up.
I don't care if it's an insurance man, the IRS man.
They don't mess with my moonshine.
Nobody messes my shine.
Nobody.
Let them come in.
I got a 12-gauge double-barrel half-sawed-off shotgun.
And anybody that messes with me or my organization or my family is in trouble.
I'm from the old school.
I'm not a liberal.
I am not a liberal.
I didn't think so.
I thought that was all an act.
I ain't a Yankee.
I got a Confederate flag.
I won't even fly this Union flag on a holiday.
I'll fly a Confederate flag.
If my neighbors don't like it, that's too bad.
My name's Terry its math Yamiche his signaling for yes, sir, it was a sampai,
youee, am Scratch get smelly denou Neuer Baron,
Caleb,
Pr güe,
youoch,
the 不是我 ل奇,
reported to the Chamber of Commerce or the SPC.
I am going to write letters.
I spent $800 to get down here.
Alice is listening, and she is not very appreciative of what you've been doing.
Who's not very appreciative?
She's very upset.
Who's upset, sir?
Who is upset?
My wife is very upset.
You've got no business talking about us in this manner.
We are supporting you people.
Don't you understand?
If we quit coming down here, you'll be out of a job, sir.
Why?
And I'll report you, and I've heard about you before in the trailer parks.
What's so funny about that, buddy?
You mean my fame has spread to the trailer parks?
Why, what is so funny about living in a trailer park?
Nothing, sir.
I'm living in an Airstream right now, and I don't think it's very funny about the way...
Wait, wait a second.
You come down here from where?
What was that, Iowa?
Driving a trailer, and you're not even staying in a motel, and you think you're supporting me?
Are you on drugs, sir?
I bet you use marijuana and all this kind of stuff.
I bet you live a life style.
What kind of a life style?
A very loose life style.
Very loose.
I'm listening to you every night, and you've got to remember this, that we might stay here.
Oh, my God!
You might stay here?
I might report you.
I'm going to report you to the...
Trailer Park Association.
I'm going to write management a letter, and you won't like it.
You'll be very afraid.
Sir, my name is...
Lassiter.
That's L-A-S-S-I-T-E-R.
Care of the Lassiter Broadcasting Company.
You're in trouble now.
No, sir.
I own the station.
You're in trouble now.
No, I own the place.
My mother bought it.
And I've heard about the way you talk about our president, and I think it's a disgrace.
Why don't you write him a letter?
I have written him many letters.
Hasn't done you a damn bit of good, has it?
You don't think...
And I don't like the way you talked about Jim.
I don't like the way you talked about Jim and Tammy Faye Baker.
Me and my wife stayed at the resort for two weeks, and we had a lovely and various enjoyment time.
Would you park your air stream there, or would you stay in a hotel room there?
We stayed in a hotel room there.
Thank you.
And we're going to go back, and I will help support his ministry.
Great.
You have done a disservice...
Would you leave tonight?
...to God.
I have never heard anyone lambaste the ministers and the nation in such a sense in my entire life, sir.
Well, you're lucky.
You've heard somebody do it.
Now...
I'm going to write a letter to the manager.
I'm going to write a letter to...
That's Mrs. Lassiter, L-A-S-S-I-T-E-R.
That's the manager's name, Mrs. Lassiter.
In the phone book.
That's right, in the phone book.
Now you're making me scream, and you're making me scream and holler.
That's one of the things I do best.
Sir, why do you carry on in this matter?
This is a very, very outlandish and monstrous tactic you're using.
You got it.
This is...
This is not right.
Why don't you help the old people?
Why don't you help us...
Sir, I'd like to help you out.
Which way did you come in?
Sir, I'm not going anywhere.
I'm going to write you a letter.
And you will receive this letter.
And you won't like it.
I'm going to write more than one letter.
I'm going to write the station.
I'm going to write the Chamber of Commerce.
I, too, will write the Chamber of Commerce.
And the Chamber of Commerce will be up flooded with letters.
Will you put a lot of kisses up the bottom?
I bet you have a surfboard, don't you?
I bet you wear short, cut-off jeans and sandals and beads
and probably wear sunglasses.
All the time.
And I bet you haven't shaved in three months.
Closer to three years, sir.
When was the last time you had a shave?
About three years ago.
Are you married or are you living in sin?
Little of each.
You continue to...
How outrageous.
Well, thank you.
You continue to tell the whole world, the whole public here,
that you're living in sin.
This is monstrous.
I give 10% of my...
I'm going to pay to the PTL Club.
And I will continue to write to PTL Club.
Oh, Jim's living in sin.
And I am going to...
You're going to send me 10% too?
I am going to write a letter to the PTL Club
and tell them what you've been saying about them.
And you may hear from the PTL Club.
Sir, we've tried to get them on the show before.
They won't come on.
You're in trouble now.
Well, sir, I guess I'll just have to wax up my board
and go with the flow, you know?
I'm wondering...
Stay here.
I'm going to call the police.
We're all in trouble now.
I'll call the police on you.
I mean it.
I'm serious.
Whoa.
Whoa there.
You're going to call the police?
I'm threatening now, sir.
You've got me upset.
I'll call the police.
I swear I'll call the police.
Do you want me to call the police on you?
This is funny.
I will call the...
Do I think it's funny?
Are you kidding me?
You're kidding me, aren't you?
You put on my leg.
Sir, I'll lock you up.
I'll have you locked up, sir.
You can't do this.
This is the greatest call I've ever had in my entire career.
You think...
You think you're...
You think that you're...
This is probably the greatest call ever to talk radio.
You think by laughing that you're showing me that you're...
You're not afraid.
That you're all afraid.
I know it.
Oh.
Oh, God.
I've got five letters to write, sir.
Five letters now?
Oh, my goodness.
You've got a busy night ahead of you.
I'm going to start right now.
Okay.
Have a bad night.
Hippie.
They're
standing
in a
room.
My 자것
numbers.
No no,
they won't
give me
I'm a native moment.
Chair, my mother.
I could blow a little bit of glue.
What?
No imagination.
Kill him.
Do not think that you are the lucky one to go on on stage.
Germans know no distinction between one man and another.
I brought the atom bomb.
I think it's a good time to use it.
Talk about stability.
No sway, dive, or shudder.
And now, punishment beyond the call of duty.
The subgenius hour of swat.
Right now, it's being flown to Florida's famed Ocean Harbor Oceanarium,
where the experts hope to restore it to consciousness.
The greatest scientific stir since the explosion of the atomic bomb.
Honda, Honda, Honda, Honda.
City.
It will catch your eye in the city.
Hey, it's horrible.
How horrible?
Are you shocked, Miss Desmond?
No.
Don't last a minute amongst those fiends.
I hope we haven't interrupted you in the middle of a trance or something.
As a matter of fact, you did.
But don't worry, we'll forgive you anyway.
Oh!
The subgenius hour of swag!
Good swag!
Oh, dear friends.
And it is indeed that show.
And I promised some of the classic talk show or talk radio clips ever.
Hey, will you kids quit fooling around?
You wouldn't believe this.
Will Adab, who is supposedly an adult,
They're sitting over here picking hits, hitting each other with Sivit, who's only 12 years old.
She started it.
Yeah, they always say that.
Okay, anyway, yeah, here's, well, I don't know what city this is from.
It doesn't really matter.
But I think that we should all have pity for this young man.
There's a lot of discussion, Eric, that's getting in the way of you really accepting real people.
And I agree, I'd be a little alarmed if I were you, because it sounds like you're retreating into it more and more rather than less.
And what's scary is that the more you decide that these are the perfect women and real women are imperfect, the more that you're going to push yourself into it.
My goodness.
What if you started wearing Little Mermaid clothes?
I have a pen.
I mean, I have a pen.
I mean, actually, last night I had a wet dream when I was with Little Mermaid.
And I think that's the thing that really scared me was when I started to have the wet dreams about her.
And I have, like, a little pen on my jacket.
I have a shirt.
I have an Aladdin shirt, which I always wear around all the time.
And my friends kind of know.
They just kind of make fun of me.
They don't understand, you know, what I'm going through and all.
What would you like them to understand about you, Eric?
That, you know, that it's normal.
It's not crazy to be in love with a cartoon.
You know?
You know, I don't think it's that weird.
I mean, she's beautiful.
She's absolutely perfect.
No girl could ever compare to the way the Little Mermaid looked.
Who turns you on the most?
Is it Jasmine from Aladdin, Belle from Beauty and the Beast, or Little Mermaid?
It might be.
It's definitely between Little Mermaid and Jasmine.
Of course, I think because Belle was always covered up.
She was always fully clothed, except during maybe the ballroom scene.
You saw a little bit of cleavage.
But Jasmine and Ariel were always, they only had, like, a bikini top on.
So it was always.
It was always between the two of them.
And it was always Little Mermaid until when I saw Jasmine.
And she also just stole my heart away.
Mm-hmm.
I mean, she's beautiful.
She's totally beautiful.
I mean, I don't know what I should do.
Like I said, I can't.
I go out with girls, but I just don't want to be with them.
They just can't measure up to the way cartoons are.
Mm-hmm.
How do you feel that girls treat you, though?
On the whole?
Yeah.
I guess pretty well.
I mean, girls who I've been with in the past, I mean, have had some pretty decentable relationships
with.
I had one relationship with this one girl, and she hurt me really, really bad.
This girl back.
Yeah.
How'd she do that?
Well, she, we were like best friends.
We went out, and then, and we were best friends, and I think I fell in love with her.
And then she told me that, you know, we were together for a while, and she told me that
she couldn't handle it, and she broke it off.
Then we got back, and then she broke it off again.
This happened about 12 times, on and off.
You know, every time that she, we got back together, I was so happy, and then she would
break up with me again.
Right.
Well, you know, I think this is really at the heart of why you're so turned on to The
Little Mermaid and Jasmine and, you know, all these other cartoon figures.
Because real love is painful!
I mean, could you really...
It hurt you!
I like your voice.
You were a bouncing ball.
You were a yo-yo, and you didn't like it.
So why shouldn't you be happier having a paper woman who totally would never treat you poorly,
you could make up anything you want about her.
And you're totally in control, because there she is on paper.
I mean, I think she's more than just paper, though.
I mean, I don't know, sometimes I like to think that she maybe exists somewhere, like
some possible way in some world that she actually exists, and maybe I'll find her.
I don't know.
I mean, or Jasmine.
I mean, either one of the two, I guess.
Or I guess I would sacrifice for Belle.
I mean, these are the girls that I want to be with.
No one even, no one could possibly compare to them.
I mean, I don't know what I'm going to do later.
I mean, I don't know what I'm going to do later on in life.
You're going to have a real problem, Eric.
Because you're right.
You know, like I said, I masturbate to them.
I couldn't, I had an erection throughout the whole movie of Aladdin with Jasmine.
And even, like I said, when there was cleavage shown in Beauty and the Beast, I couldn't
believe it.
I got so turned on so quickly.
Well, you're absolutely right, Eric.
No girl's ever going to match up to that, because they get pimples.
They...
They might have a runny nose.
Their hair is oily sometimes.
Their eyes are puffy.
They're grumpy sometimes.
Yep.
They'll never, they'll never match.
You're right.
Oh, but that's okay.
Cut the, cut the poor guy some slack, okay?
John Bartle's here.
Oh, by the way, that tape.
We make good tape.
I'm going to show back to that, because it's so bizarre.
And yet, I bet some of you boys been thinking, baby, last time you saw that, uh, how about
Roger Rabbit?
Cool world.
The invisible girl.
That was the one I, I, well, uh, yeah, Dr. Legume up in Philadelphia submitted that,
that submission.
And, uh, I think with this song.
by John Bartles has a great deal of bearing on the exact same thing.
Thank you.
I'm hopelessly heterosexual, not overly intellectual, and I see you're heterosexual too.
So why don't we cut the crap and give in to this crazy trap and have a hopelessly heterosexual relationship, me and you.
Yep, I'm hopelessly heterosexual, no use in denying it, it's just impossible.
I was born that way, and you were.
We're born that way too.
Don't you see I'm hopelessly heterosexual over you.
I'm hopelessly heterosexual over, over you.
Over you.
Hello?
I just called to let you know that I was sorry.
You're sorry?
I am sorry.
John, I'm sorry too.
Well, would you tell him that I'm sorry?
I'll tell him that you're very sorry.
And also that we didn't use that thing that he did.
You didn't?
No.
Oh.
So I'm double sorry.
You're double sorry.
Yes.
Okay.
But we're going to use the part you're on.
You're going to use the part that I'm on?
Yes.
Why?
I'm sorry.
For what might happen next.
The world revolves around your...
Self-perception.
Even though it's warped by your own self-perception.
Guess it's my fault.
You've got the wrong impression.
I'm sorry.
So sorry.
I'm sorrier than you.
I feel awful.
Yes, it's true.
I take full responsibility for everything you think.
And everything.
Everything I don't do.
I'm sorry.
Later.
I can't believe our eighth's my brother.
Thoughts on Betty Rubble.
Or Marge Simpson.
Oh, they're not pretty.
I think Jessica Rabbit's a real slut.
I mean, my friends told me I should try to think about her.
But I think she's just the horse.
You know, she's a little slut.
I think Jessica will be with anyone.
You know, not like Ariel.
I mean, Ariel's faithful.
I think Snow White also is a slut.
I think she was doing a lot with those Seven Dwarves.
I think she pulled off all seven of them.
You know, I think Snow White's a real slut.
and I don't know about Cinderella, but Ariel's not.
I mean, she's loyal, and she'll be loyal to me.
I think she'll be there for me.
She would definitely be there for me and take care of me if I needed her.
What do you think, Dr. J?
I think you've got to be really careful, Eric.
You're slipping into a little fantasy land here
from whence it will be harder and harder for you to emerge over time,
and I'm worried about you.
You've got to give the guy credit, though.
I mean, Belle and Little Mermaid, they are pretty.
Yeah, sure.
You know what I'm saying?
Well, so is Mel Gibson and Dennis Quaid.
You know, they're handsome, but, well, at least they're real people.
What about Johnny Quest?
Eric, you've got a problem here.
I hate to tell you this because I know you're not happy hearing it,
but the more you slip into doing this,
I would say you have to stop this right away
because...
I see you going further and further into your imagination
and being disappointed with real people,
and that's where I think it comes from,
your disappointment with girls and your hurt from this girl.
Oh, I can certainly understand this guy being disappointed with real people,
but how many real people are there after all?
Now, we're going to get back to our investigations into the world of po-buckets,
and I'm going to tell you a little bit about the world of po-buckers.
I've got a little bit of tape here from one of the great po-buckers of all time, Jim Jones.
Wish I had more Koresh friends because he would also certainly qualify.
Sivit, what was it you wanted to say?
The second word I think of when I hear the word po-bucker would probably have to be...
M-r-r-r-r.
Explores the most controversial phenomena of our time
and tells you everything...
Everything that can be known.
That's us.
The Midwest.
A mother feels a sharp pain in her right hand.
Far away at that exact same moment, her daughter screams as she touches a hot pan.
Just chance?
Or is it telling us something about our own untapped capabilities?
Goes deeper into unexplained phenomena than ever before.
It documents the facts and it covers what people were never willing to talk about.
Stonehenge.
A visitor fashions a wire antenna in the shape of an ancient Egyptian symbol.
He points it at the stones and a surge of power rushes into his arm, knocking him unconscious.
Was it all in his mind or was it much more than that?
Sponsored by the Church of the Subterranean.
They tell us that we lost our tail.
Evolving up.
They tell us that we lost our tail. Evolving up.
Some little snail.
I say it's all just wind and sail.
Are we not men?
We are Devo.
Whoa.
You figure that out if you want to.
Some of you are too naive.
You don't know what I'm...
What Jim Jones is all about.
You can't even follow him.
You haven't even...
You haven't even smelled where he's at yet.
Much less followed him.
You don't even know who he is and you might miss him if you didn't have a real good look
at him.
You wouldn't even know who he looked like.
You really haven't gotten next to him.
But I've got all kinds of things in store.
You...
You who are stupid piss ants and reptiles and lower than the primates.
You can make a hoopie if you want, but your hoopie makes me sicky.
And so you can make your hoopie while I do something that's far more significant.
I got me some big plans, both here, there, and everywhere.
Got lots of plans.
The relatives of Jonestown residents, their contact cut off from their loved ones by dad,
were becoming troublesome.
A group was formed called Concerned Relatives.
And with the prized effectors Timothy and Grace Stone,
the custody battle for John Victor became the center of the challenge.
They also sent a petition to the U.S. State Department
charging human rights violations in Jonestown.
It was complicated.
They think it's anachronized to talk about it.
Odd in the same way that it would be odd
to talk about it.
It strikes me as odd in the same way that it would be odd
odd in the same way that it would be odd
but for some reason
as to stimulate that appetite
as to stimulate that appetite.
We have seen the coming of a savior,
a beacon of slack,
a banner behind which we may all unite.
It is the coming of J.R. Bob Dobbs
and his mighty Church of the Subgenius.
The subgenius
is coming on
in business suits.
The subgenius is coming on in business suits.
He chose that credit
all that's the proof
All we're not fed
We are devolved
DVO
So ready to race
Come in.
Hi Sam, got a minute?
Hi, Paula. What's on your mind?
Sam, I think we have a real emergency situation here.
I'm calling up your office.
Are you aware that we're making some submission deadlines by just one day?
No, I wasn't.
I've been so busy recently that I haven't paid much attention.
Another symptom.
And take a look at this financial statement I just got from accounting.
Endless submission.
And you too can submit, dear friends, to the word of J.R. Bob Dogg, whose church this is.
And, you know, you really ought to write.
It's about time you got around to writing into the Church of the Subgenius for the free information.
Well, it's catalog is what it is.
But what a catalog.
A catalog of sins.
And I'd like to give you that post office box number to write to.
Write.
Now.
We'll give you some.
If you just write to Bob at...
And you can just address that.
B-O-B, friends.
At P-O-B.
That's post office box 140306.
Ah, yes.
140306.
Dallas, Texas.
75214.
Yes, we're not kidding.
It really is Dallas, Texas.
This is Walter Concrete.
We're here on this busy street corner to perform an interesting experiment.
I'm an amputee.
I'm going to ask the first person I see if he can tell if the thing hanging from my shoulder and my arm is really my arm or a prosthetic device totally concealed by new creamy stumps.
Now, you in a stocking cap and cut-off bell-bottom shirt.
Look.
Ooh.
I'm waving a tennis racket.
Around for no apparent reason.
Uh, do you have a quarter?
You're losing this interview, buddy.
I'm wearing creamy stumps.
In reality, I have no arms.
See?
Do you have a quarter?
Eaten away by the new plague tumors.
There's no ozone like no ozone I know.
Everyone is also very blotchy.
Do you have a quarter?
They're in my brain now, too.
See?
I don't know.
Maybe a dollar or something.
No, not at all, my bad man.
Ring.
Oh, hello?
Yes?
Is that?
You don't say.
They didn't say.
Well, friends, that was brain rot radio just then.
And it is, isn't it?
It is.
Ah.
Brain rot radio.
Out of Cleveland, WCSB is where those ugly guys do that, and they are, too.
I, oh, God.
You know, if it, they'd never make it in TV.
I would.
Oh, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Well, friends and others, you know, it wouldn't be a proper Pobucker type show without playing
this Greg Keeler classic, Manly Men.
And Greg Keeler, lone weirdo in Bozeman, Montana, created the song The Swinging Love Corpses
Do A Killer Cover Of This, Dude, Man, It Rocks.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to sell it out, man.
We're men among men, man, manly men, yes, manly men are we.
We're men among manly men, among manly, manly men are we.
Oh, my God.
We'll sail up north and cross the iceberg.
and cross the barren snow fields.
You gotta be tough and you gotta be a man
to club the baby harp seal.
To club the baby harp seal.
We're men among men and manly men,
yes, manly men are we.
We're men among manly men,
among manly manly men are we.
We'll drive out west on a buffalo hunt
in a Venture Bowl and daring,
we'll shoot one again and again and again
while the others stand there staring.
While the others stand there staring.
We're men among men and manly men,
yes, manly men are we.
We're men among manly men,
among manly manly men are we.
When we shoot him down he'll get back up,
so we'll shoot him down again.
But he'll get back up so we'll shoot him down,
because we are manly men.
Yes, we are manly men.
And a man's gotta do what a man's gotta do
when a man is a man among men.
Yes, a man among men's gotta do what a man's gotta do
as a man among men.
We'll hunt the black rhinoceros down on the plains
so dry and hot.
We'll blow him over and take his horn
and leave the rest to rot.
Yes, leave the rest to rot.
And a man's gotta do what a man's gotta do
when a man is a man among men.
Yes, a man among men's gotta do what a man's gotta do
as a man among men.
We'll take that horn and sell it to our Taiwanese connections.
They'll grind it up into medicine
so men can get erections.
So men can get erections.
And a man's gotta do what a man's gotta do
when a man is a man among men.
Yes, a man among men's gotta do what a man's gotta do
as a man among men.
We're men among men and manly men.
Yes, manly men are we.
We're men among manly, men among manly,
manly men are we.
Come on, men, let's kill it!
What are we, women?
Oh, yes, indeed.
Greg Keeler there with, uh,
Manly Men from his, uh, album, uh,
Bad Science Fiction.
Uh-huh. Now, I've...
I got... I have this...
No, this isn't working.
I'm using it for this.
I'm just gonna tell ya.
We got the most, uh, interesting tape
from, uh...
Okay, get...
This is subgenius Tejano music from Ohio.
I got this tape in the mail
from, uh...
The name of the album is Tortilla Diablo.
The name of the band is Cinco Con Dos.
And they are, uh...
Located in Bowling Green, Ohio.
And, uh...
When you look at the cassette label and everything,
it's got a picture of this band.
And there's bob heads all over the place.
It's... It's...
And there...
There's little pipes and subgenius, uh, imagery in it.
Our post office box, 1403-06, Dallas, Texas, 75214,
is in there.
And, uh...
And their post office box, 7004 Bowling Green, Ohio,
43402.
And...
And it's called Praise Dobbs Records.
That's their record company.
Praise Dobbs Records.
And it's, uh, rock...
It's, uh, Tejano-style rock and roll music
against the conspiracy, all in Spanish.
And the liner notes here say,
Hace tres años que se juntaron...
No, well, basically it says,
it's been...
For three years...
It's been three years that, uh,
these four musicians got together.
Each musician had an idea.
Juntos hicieron unos...
They had a...
They wanted to make new sounds.
Uh...
And, uh, what they...
They got into hardcore y...
Music, uh, Tejano music.
Te...
Tejano music.
Músicas Tejana, hardcore y de la música popular de hoy.
Lo que resultó es como...
Chiu.
Chiu, I don't know.
And when, uh...
And...
And when you, with the Tortilla Diablo,
take care that, uh,
you do not fall forever into his pipe.
And, uh, Praise Dobbs,
this...
Here it is, cut...
Um...
What's the name of the song?
El carro demonio.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Matar, matar, no vas a ver.
No, no, no.
En las noches han faltado ocho desde que apareció ese carro.
Esa muerte, esa calavera hecho de fierro.
El poder anda con las luces apagadas para que nunca lo vas
a mirar hasta que ya está muy tarde.
Y ya vas sobre las llantas del carro,
las llantas rojas llenas de sangre.
En las noches frías, solito mueres.
Solito mueres.
Qué pasa?
Es un caro.
Un caro demonio.
Per libro de fondo.
Es un caro de mono.
Es un caro con peligro.
Es un carro, un carro de fondo.
Obrigado.
No hay noche que pasa que no hay muerte.
.
Since that car appeared, that skull, that cold iron with blood on its body.
There are no nights that pass that there are no people who cry,
that they lack, that they put together a person because they did not pay attention to what they said.
A car without lights, running in the neighborhoods,
wanting to fix you for a car, a car of the devil.
a movie by
© BF-WATCH TV 2021