From PR News in Washington, I'm Upside Down.
The government says Bob increased slightly last month.
The good news, corrections officials in California have disclosed a new protocol for executing Bob.
The plan calls for the careful selection of a team to administer lethal injections to Bob.
State officials hope the new plan meets with Bob's approval and he allows executions to resume.
On Wall Street, 5-4-3-5-9.
The good news, PR is down 25% from the level it set a year ago.
PR's bad. This is PR.
The voice you hear is a voice of a half-alive poet trying to sell you a world of his own.
And so it is that we are proud to welcome to our show tonight...
The Self-Genius Power of Self-Work.
This man is speaking to you now. So listen, it might be important.
But Daddy, I can't do that.
What?
But Daddy, please, Daddy.
It won't do you any good to scream.
Gee, Daddy, please don't make me...
Well then, go watch comic books or something.
All right, but I'm gonna have mommy to eat.
All right, dear.
The story of man.
Specimen for scientists to take apart piece by piece, to study, to analyze.
Call it...
Why shouldn't I call it a book dangle? Why? There have to be so many different words.
Words, words, words!
I'm the Mad Hatter.
We're going to free all the people enslaved.
You may join our conspiracy.
Go on. Go on!
What are you doing?
When the civilization began to spread over the Earth, they were learning so much.
Oh, baby babbling is very important.
Very well put, but hardly scientific.
For a long time, scientists have been curious.
Buh, buh, buh.
Eeeeee.
Ooooooo.
Hmm.
Eh, eee, zzz, eh, er.
Ah, eee, zzz, eh, er.
Never kill a snake with your bare hands.
I'm beginning to feel it.
Immortality.
Through entertainment.
Rhythm abnormality.
Oh, well.
Uh, Reverend.
Rhythm abnormality.
Oh, well.
Became the politician.
Think, think, think, think.
Hustler Magazine.
Should be protected.
We should abandon the Judeo-Christian heritage.
Oh, well.
Oh, well, well.
We should not abandon gay marriage, abortion.
We have a, we have a rhythm abnormality.
Oh, well, well, well.
Mold, mold, mold, mold.
Jerry.
Think Teletubbies.
Think, think.
Jerry.
Was gay.
Think, think.
History of problems.
An incestuous drunkard.
Jerry.
Oh, well, oh, well.
Oh, well, oh, well, oh, well.
Jerry.
Oh, well, oh, well.
Think, think, think, think, think.
Oh, well, oh, well, oh, well, to make a point.
Jerry.
Oh, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, reverend.
Well, well.
It's time now for the old time.
Jerry.
An incestuous drunkard.
Oh, well.
OLD.
feminist.
gays.
Lesbians.
Jerry.
Jerry, Jerry, Genie, Genie. He was sold.
Bush is primed and ready for failure.
Bush said, Bush said, and now it is time for fun, fun, fun, fun, fun.
Chaos. Deaths follow the war. Sets the stage for a fresh round of deaths.
Chaos. U.S. deaths follow failure. Death. Failure. Death. Failure. Death. Failure. Death. Failure. Death. Deaths. Mission accomplished.
The conspiracy of the normal people, by the way, is what we're talking about.
I should clarify that. A lot of folks, when we say conspiracy, you start thinking along the lines of standard conspiracy theorists.
You know, oh, you mean the guys that really pulled off the 9-11 thing.
Oh, you mean the crashed saucers at Groom Lake.
Oh, you mean the Kennedy assassination guys.
Well, sure, those are all wonderful little conspiracies, but they are dwarfed by the uber conspiracy of conspiracy.
The garden variety average ordinary human beings, which may even include some of us.
Don't, don't be too ashamed. You know, we can't all have the blood of the Yeti, full-blood Yeti coursing through us.
George Bush is in the studio with me, and I'll be talking with him next.
Recreation of a 19th century world.
For you.
14-inch 69 cuts wood get cut fire fire force of a sledgehammer.
Blackhawk, Blackhawk, this comes first.
Good evening, George Bush.
Mr. Bush landed a short time ago.
He has no brain waves.
Thank you for stopping.
You see, what I think has happened is that I failed.
Unemployment, inflation, trying to attack our economic program.
And I've got to trying to attack our economic program.
And I've got to cutting, stimulating and do this.
Desperate.
Failed the working man in this country.
I don't think, I don't think, I don't think raid come out soon.
I hope.
Who cloaks Klan?
Number two.
Can you see?
See totalitarian government.
Felony conviction.
No brain waves.
Some fun.
Check, check.
The weather's next.
Keep the umbrellas handy.
Weather's next.
50, 50.
Steady now.
72%.
Three, zero.
And that's not bad.
12 inches of hello, ho, ho.
Way up.
Another gloomy one.
An emotional moment Monday.
President Bush.
He broke, broke, he broke, broke down, down.
An emotional moment Monday.
Monday.
President Bush.
He broke.
Broke.
True measure of a man, man, man.
Hi-ya, hi-ya, hi-ya, hi-ya.
Annal, annal victory.
kwik, kwik.
De-fit, de-fit.
Kwik, kwik.
Re-hit, re-hit.
Ha.
Sure measure of a man.
Hi-ya, hi-ya.
Interest rates and inflation.
Why would we want to return to where we were less than four short years ago?
Sure measure of a man.
De-fit, de-fit.
De-fit.
I could dance.
An emotional moment Monday.
Wave of panic through Washington.
It's a fun one.
Wow.
The titillation of the who's who's list.
Disturbing genesis.
Confounding evolution.
Are we going to see more?
There was something illegal.
There are lonely people in this world.
Smear them.
Disturbing genesis.
Confounding evolution.
The titillation of the who's who's list.
Wow.
You're talking to brainwashed people.
Today's distraction from all the real problems in the world.
It's Reverend Ivan, Dr. Stanko.
Stanko.
Our 12.
And not too close to the witching end.
Soon we'll all be blossoming in hell.
Eyes parted with little needles stuck into our skulls.
Twisting the right parts of our brains.
Putting us in the kind of shape we need to get put into.
Because our bodies are going to change, aren't they, Stanko?
We're going to change and become greater.
Stronger.
Hairier.
More.
More manful.
And that's just the girls I'm talking about.
And here comes one now.
Ah, she is indeed hairy.
Look at those armpits.
Wait, don't look at them.
Wait, don't...
That tickles.
Stop it.
Any perceptual gloss of these armpits will cause immediate pierogi damage in the brain or other organ.
Is this a real island we're stuck on or are we just stuck on our own gummy sheets?
No.
It's the island of misfit toys, Prince Dave.
But what if the exards come and let us off the island of retarded toys?
No, no, no.
We're the misfit toys.
Oh, okay.
We are the...
Think about it, Dave.
Yeah.
Right.
Well, no, I got that at first.
I did.
I understood that.
It seems like Princess Wee's mic is always light and little.
What is with that?
I don't know.
Mine was too, but I...
But I jumped right on it like a pig.
Yeah, you hit me.
I'm on it.
I have no control over...
Those two, both are like Siamese twins that go into the same pot.
Wouldn't you say they're more like your misshapen third leg which you brandish at the little kids in the street?
That's the sad...
Another one of those warnings you got from the local authorians?
That's what's so sad about it.
That's why the police are after us all the time.
Why there's a conspiracy of normal people.
People always after us because of what we are.
Sometimes good normals hide us in the basement when the conspiracy guys storm troop on by.
Yeah.
Give us bread and donuts or water, something.
Some nice people have a special subgenius hiding spot in their house where you hide your subgeniuses in there.
We even hear the...
The trapdoor things and so forth.
If we ride the underground railway...
Right.
We might actually get off this planet.
But then there's other rumors going around that somebody has a whole lot of weapons concealed in some basement somewhere and we're all going to grab them at once and go and smack the masters.
We don't know.
We just don't know.
We don't know whether we're going to have to stay on the planet and then be suppressed and persecuted and prosecuted and executed and or whether we will escape as Bob promised.
Whether we...
We know that we will eventually.
Well, Bob...
Bob breaks his promises.
Frequently, in fact.
But X is the reason why, isn't it?
Well, he always lies and he's always right, was the way he put it.
But then, you know, he did say he always lied.
He was a drunk.
That's why he said that.
That's what drunks say.
They believe everything about their...
They believe their own press kits, as they used to say.
I...
Really?
I think.
I'm not sure, but...
No wonder I had so many...
I had so much fun when I was a drunk.
I think I'm going to go back to being a drunk again.
Even though...
I believed in myself.
Even though I was a failure.
Yeah, I was all wrong, but...
I believed the lies that I told myself.
Now I tell myself the truth and I believe it and it's just depressing.
It is depressing now.
When we think about the equipment we could have used back in the early days.
You know, the self-sprouting genetic material that we can just charge up like the way...
Like when Princess Wee snaps her fingers and another mutation grows.
Yeah.
I'd like to be able to do that myself and I'm hoping I can.
Like we used to.
Yeah.
You think you're going to get younger, Dave?
No, I think it's like this.
It's the same as the secret powers.
It's a lost art that's going to dwindle and diminish and atrophy as I continue to atrophy.
And like all things, it'll go the way of Mother Westwind or fade to black, you know?
But are we bringing hope to the listeners or are we just bringing them down?
Both.
Like you said.
It's like we...
It's Bob's pro...
Because the hope doesn't mean anything if it's a lie, I guess.
You have to know the truth first and then the hope means something.
The hope that you won't die too painfully.
The will to recreate, the will to live over and over when there is no will to live left.
Speaking of will to live, in the background, the music here is from Dr. Onan Canobite.
Something called Not Different But Better.
What is it called?
Not Different But Better, I think.
And before that, of course, the cut-ups and things that we heard were by...
Actually, I think they were all by Reverend Norell Preff.
And there's so much more of that and also music at norellpreff.com.
What there's not more of there is the Fernand and Andy Lee Murr collage.
Oh.
Begin every hour of slack.
So wholly.
Oh, yes.
Let us rise up.
With a reverent dive and stand.
Let us erect our minds.
To a higher plane.
Of slack.
And rock, baby, rock.
Yes, yes.
Bob's a swinging god.
This is the church.
This is the subgenius.
We worship this guy named Bob.
J.R. Bob Dunn.
The slickest, smoothest, personal savior you ever saw.
The James Bond of religious leaders.
Actually, I think he's the Doc Savage of holy men.
I think as I grew to become a larger individual, I discovered Bob and it worked out for me just...
Wow.
These and many other testaments brought to you in vast approach by the following concerned authors for decency.
The Reverend O'Rarian Stinks.
That's me.
Clarice Hungadunga.
And Marshall Spax as the interpreter.
C'est moi.
Whoa.
It's quite a crew tonight.
Yes, kids, it's...
It's me.
And you're in for a big, big show.
Oh, yeah.
We guess.
Because we don't actually have any idea what kind of a show you're in for.
We're just hoping and guessing.
Because that's what this is all about.
The guesswork of hope.
And those are the hopefulness of guesswork.
The fact that because the angels won't let us know for sure if there's an afterlife or not,
that's why we don't go jump off a bridge right now since the bills are stacking up.
Well, that and the hot pastrami sandwich.
That and the hot pastrami sandwich.
I'll buy that.
For a dollar.
Oh, friend.
Dear friend.
And this uplifting music in the background is from the Kirkendall void.
From their new album, Stung.
No relation.
And they're from right around here.
Are they?
Oh, yes, of course.
I'd love to get them to X Day sometime.
We'd probably have to pay them, though.
And that's always been a problem with X Day.
Well, if you listen carefully,
Kirkendall void might actually be like one half of a person.
No, actually.
I think it's one person and four half persons.
An avoided executioner.
No, there's actually four halflings in this?
Yeah.
Oh, well.
That accounts for something.
Four full halflings along with the fulllings.
That's a far thing.
Princess, I can't hear you in it, so I don't know if it's because I'm deaf.
I can't hear you either.
I can't hear you at all.
That means you have to yell in that microphone.
I'm yelling as much as I can, though.
That's better.
You weren't yelling that loud before.
Is that true?
What you could do is trade with Dave.
No, that's my button there.
Don't you touch my button.
This is...
I can do that.
Dave.
Oh, yeah.
Now, that's much louder.
But then when Dave gets on, you see...
See?
Oh, we're all loud.
There's something weird about these microphones, Stemple.
Why don't you come over here?
Why don't we all go in...
That's not the only thing that's weird.
That's...
Now, let's...
See, now I'm off.
Yeah, see, now Dave's off.
Dave's mind is off.
Oh, man.
And Princess Weave.
But Princess Weave sounds so pretty.
That is totally unfair.
Hey, while we have you on the good mic,
why don't you read the new food fatwa,
Sifu Sodi posted after, I guess,
doing some in-depth research into the religious...
What is it called?
You go ahead.
It is the People's Committee for Good Taste Issues
Food Fatwas.
Number one, ketchup shall never be used on hot dogs.
Number two, pineapple is an abomination unto pizza.
Number three, there are no edible substances
known as cheese food product.
Number four, likewise, the particulate matter
known as bake-o-bits.
Number five, mayonnaise shall not be spread.
Upon fine Italian preserved meats.
And Princess Weave adds, nor corned beef.
Number six, alcohol is not a food group.
Number seven, fat-free half-and-half is self-contradictory.
It shall be known as fluid.
Thank you, Princess Weave, Ardo, and Sifu Sodi.
That's pretty serious.
We don't have rules there.
We don't normally have rules in the Church of the Subgenius.
And of course, they are made to be shattered.
There's no rules.
Ignored and totally disavoid.
But why must we have rules to begin with?
I hate to pose a question like that.
I know it's a stupid question to pose.
It sets you to glib and continue to follow.
But what is the purpose of regulating others' behaviors, thoughts, actions, and so forth?
What? I mean...
Oh, never mind.
That's a dumb question.
Yeah, it is.
Princess Weave, would you care to demonstrate to...
No, that means she's going to kick me in the blue area.
Right.
No, that's not...
She can go ahead and...
Dave's all blue down there.
Because he lies.
And he lies, he turns blue.
That's new comeback hip talk on the...
...Dave's Blue member.
You should move that mic over to right next to Dave's mic.
And that'll trick you into using Dave's mic.
I don't know how can I do that?
Why is this mic almost evenly dead?
Like this?
There you go.
Now both of you make...
Both of you use both of these mics and be nice and, you know, try...
We have to mic well and nice together?
Nice works, yup.
God almighty.
We have to mic well together.
Tarzan's radio station.
I think staying just doesn't know how to...
No, this is very uncomfortable, especially since we're both females.
Oh, God.
Oh, oh.
I'm alluding to the fact that we're having a lot of fun.
I think we should use one microphone, I mean two microphones as one, intertwined in some sort of a...
It's like Twisted, man.
It works for me.
Really?
Are you like able to hear me now?
Can you hear me now?
And then talk a lot and stuff.
See, it's nearly impossible.
Oh, because you have to bend down.
And she has to stand on two toes.
It's impossible like this.
You see, friends, Princess Wee is only...
How could you not understand...
She's very wee.
She's only about three feet tall.
Dave is like six, nine.
More like three inches.
Now can you hear me?
Yeah, that's good.
I like the way you use that ladder.
It's the ladder of my toes.
No, now I can.
Because my mic is dead.
It only works like this.
Let's not subject the listeners to that.
Let's subject them to this.
Beat it, beat it, beat it, beat it, beat it, beat it.
Welcome.
This morning I have the honor of signing a breast.
This breast authorizes the National Breast Detection Act.
I want to touch this breast.
I appreciate you all coming down to witness the signing.
Jenna Welch was diagnosed with breast cancer at the age of eight.
She is a fortunate person.
I want to thank the Pink Campaign.
I'm a fortunate person about to wear pink.
And we are thankful for that.
Pink.
I look good.
Um.
And yes!
I need...
ills.
I look good.
Yeah, you look good!
I was wearing pink, IH.
Uhm.
I can't do this.
And the TV.
effective program. Since its creation, the program has touched nearly seven pink breasts.
We expect 90 percent will continue to life-saving work.
In the span of my administration, we have spent, along with Congress, $6.7. I appreciate
dollars. A budget for 2008 includes another $7, a chance to spread breast activities,
detect the breasts, beat them. Again, I want to thank the members for their hard pink members,
and it is now my honor to sign the National Breast Detection Program Reauthorization.
Thank you all for coming.
Thank you.
Brother Godwin, I am with child, not Edmonds. The child is that of the Viking, Ragnar.
I suppose you've all seen newsreel and newspaper pictures of a little curly-headed boy who wears
steel braces on his legs and a jolly smile on his bright face.
Throw some water on him.
Well, that little fellow is a sneak thief and strikes suddenly without warning.
Sneaky little rabbit.
And when he doesn't succeed in taking his victim's life, he usually robs like normal
children do.
I like work my razor fast, but light and easy.
And we've got to do our share in the war against curly-headed boys.
And the most important thing you and I can do is to lend financial support to the organization
that makes it possible for science to develop weapons against the normal children
by making contributions to the
So Genius Power of Swag.
Tomorrow, before you leave for school, take what you get from your parents
and turn it into your local office of the campaign in your city.
Don't forget, it's for your own protection.
Yeah.
Rush Limbaugh is irrelevant.
Chum, chum, rush, rush.
Irrelevant.
It was a shot, it was a shot.
I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I.
Loaded, loaded, loaded.
It's a dacus.
Yep, yep.
Irrelevant.
Limbaugh's power has always been a myth.
Closet.
Yeah.
Dacus.
It's, it's.
I happen to be a...
Irrelevant.
Rush Limbaugh is an elephant.
He's also a form of dental disease in parts of Eurasia.
Or neural prep.
This is not a public forum.
This is just a stupid radio show.
There's nobody really listening.
This is college radio.
Independent radio.
Well, no.
Internet radio.
It's everything but...
I just can't.
You know, if this was real radio, there'd be real commercials.
Not public service announcements.
If this was real radio, we'd be playing the latest logo bands, you know, and flop-drop tunes of the coolest new thing.
The new happening logo bands.
Like the Kirkendall Void.
Heard in the background.
But instead, we can only play unreleased material like the Kirkendall Void.
Yeah, man.
Although I think this is a Link Wray song.
Yeah, this is Sloughter on what you call it?
Rumble.
Rumble? Oh, it was very similar to Sloughter on...
I like going into the Kirkendall Void.
You've been accepted.
Please take a seat near the window marked X.
Place your hand on the fondulator.
There you go.
Now, peer directly at your feet.
Within five seconds, you will be elevated and recumbrated.
Stand clear of the snack doors.
Snacks will be served soon.
Mmm, snacks.
Brains.
I have a Kirkendall Void song that is queued up next.
That's about what Princess Wee and I...
refer to as Loshon Hara, which I think is a Hebrew term.
Yes.
Sort of for gossip.
Gossip is akin to using your words coming out of your mouth as bullets.
Right, so when you turn your mouth into a machine gun to shoot people down by talking bad about them.
Because, yes, if you say something bad about a person, it could defame them and ruin their character.
And it could take their life.
Is it okay to say bad things about President Bush, though?
We wonder about this stuff.
This is a chronic ailment.
A malaise that's taken over the entire country.
Is it right?
Does it hurt my body?
Am I doing the right thing by wishing Mr. Bush would jump out of some convenient windows nearby?
Will sticks and stones break his bones, or is it only words that are allowed to hurt?
Well, in the old yoga principles, they are saying what is coming out of your mouth could be very well what is coming out from the other side.
From up and over.
Well, and it almost always is.
Aetheric bevel.
If it's humans talking, then it probably is a bunch of garbage.
And it's probably self-inflicted torchoir.
Filthy slobos.
Slobos.
Slobos with two N's or three Z's?
Or, no, S-L-O-B-O.
No, that'd be slobos.
Isn't it slobos?
No, I said slobos. Filthy slobos coming from your filthy penis.
That's salvos, like you're thinking of machine guns firing out into the distant winds.
Bap, bap, bap, bap, bap, bap.
It's okay, Dave.
Okay, I'm sorry.
I was talking clockwork orange talk, because I got stuck in that.
Oh, slobos.
Like the vodkas.
Gaurav eating their filthy slobos out of their filthy rots.
Their big rots blabbering away.
Yes.
They're gobs.
But that's all, too.
But the vodkas is Russian.
And so is...
Here.
Ha!
Did you know that Burgess was not only a highly sexed animal, he was originally a BBC writer.
Anthony Burgess, the author of Clockwork Orange?
Yeah.
He was not a professional author until after that successfulness.
He was a writer of strange background music for BBC.
And that's the truth.
As far as I remember.
I had heard that he was just some English...
Now, this is all just stuff I heard.
I haven't looked it up on Wikipedia or anything.
Just some dude down at the...
I heard he was just some English teacher dude who always wanted to write a novel.
But then one day some young droogies came in and beat the hell out of him and almost killed him and his wife.
And when he got...
Oh, no, no.
It wasn't that.
It was that he got...
He was told he was gonna die of cancer or he was gonna die of something.
So he wrote two or three novels real fast.
And then they said,
Oh, sorry, we were wrong.
You're not really gonna die.
And he couldn't think...
And he went,
Ah, but I must keep writing.
Good old Tony Burgess.
Yes, I remember frolicking with him down at the Bohemian Grove.
He was just a kid then.
He was one of the tapped?
Oh, we were all into that.
You know, I got...
It got old for me.
I got tired of that.
So what was the next step for you?
All about Satanic Masonics.
Oh, I thought you meant...
Well, I've been at the top.
You know, I had actually run the conspiracy for a while.
They let everybody in the club run it for 15 minutes or so.
Okay, your turn.
You're running the whole world now.
They're all drunk and you see...
Basically, you can...
During that time, you could start a world war if you wanted to.
But, you know, one of the other guys would be sure to kick your butt afterwards.
Kind of broke some precedents, didn't he?
The old precedent.
Because even in the yoga sandals, they say that, you know, certain gods are...
That gods are elected to these...
These high offices until the point they achieve absolute, you know, whatever.
Here's one of the gods playing in the background.
Yeah.
That's Reverend Angry Larry, the god of DNA.
Oh, of Gorgon.
I remember when he snapped.
The first time.
Well, not...
I remember...
I think it was the 15th time he snapped.
Remember that?
No.
They all merged together in my mind.
He's so angry.
The rings are...
You can tell.
He gets...
He works it out on stage, though.
It's not like a drain of venom on me.
This is from X day.
This is from last...
Two X days ago, I think.
Or maybe last X day.
Burn it, Angry Larry.
Burn it.
Well, he's kind of in a holding pattern now, probably waiting for...
Well, that last lick there, I remember was one of the...
I think it was the third time he snapped.
For all I know, this is Dave.
Dave playing.
No.
Well, it could be.
Is this two X days ago?
Is this a jam last X day?
Last X day, I think.
Oh, it might be me.
No, that's not a little too frantic.
They're all going...
Once you go...
You're not well-differentiated from the other musicians.
It's called 1-4-5, and it means you smell badly.
Oh, the other musicians.
Oh, my God!
You're all doing the same thing.
This is actually an Amish hymn.
It is.
If they used it with the octagordion or whatever those little small boxes that sound like an accordion,
like a concertina or something like that.
Have you ever heard of the psaltery?
P.S. you know it's like psaltery.
And they play the psaltery and that's like an electric psaltery.
And the Amish invented the boogie you're saying?
No, they invented the electric psaltery.
Which is their, you know, congregational, convocational music.
It's played on this.
Ah, Tavachkos.
Das Vidania.
Spasibo.
Those are from your old country, Dave.
Those are DeLukians.
Ah, Italiani.
Devo ascoltare.
Chi ?
Cosa?
Chi  Giudice?
Giudice.
Giudice?
Che  il Cina?
Otto e mezzo, no?
Is this eight and a half?
No, it's The Clowns.
The Clowns from eight and a half?
The Clowns by Federico Fellini.
I love this movie.
He's the crazy movie director.
I didn't see The Clowns.
Dave, you weren't meant to see The Clowns.
They were hiding from you.
These were evil clowns.
I remember that word.
It means you're a shameful person.
That's Graziata.
The Clowns is a weird Fellini movie that's like a fake documentary.
He stages in a Hollywood way the idea that he is leading a little camera crew around making a documentary about clowns.
But it's a takeoff on pompous documentary filmmakers at the same time.
I might have known that.
With himself placed in the pompous...
most pompous-est role.
There's a little jig.
What is... who is... who's responsible for this?
Not me, chicken.
This little jig in the background I think is Joe Newman's Rudy Schwartz project.
Tell Rudy that although I love his music, this sounds a bit like a fried chicken shack commercial.
Come on down to...
We're going to...
It's only $7.75.
That wouldn't be the exact...
I'm going to...
I'm going to push over.
But you know what I'm saying?
It's too zany.
The message for you is learn to close the third nostril without causing damage to the cerebral cortex.
Number one.
Number two.
And of course number seven.
Okay?
Follow the ritual...
Z campaigns...
Z...
Follow the ritual devoutly every morning, every evening, and every afternoon before
rising for retirement.
Remove detritus from the third nostril with a handy swab.
Remove piece of flotsam from the ear canal with this...
Watch it!
Here's to...
What is this?
Oh, we were going to play the song, the Kirkendall song, Void, about the bullets coming out of your mouth like a gun.
Yeah, Los Chanhara.
Los Chanhara?
The Los Chanhara song.
Los Chanhara.
Yeah, we can play that.
Let's go.
Hello, I'm Mr. A.
Let's cross the tomb as you prepare to say.
Wear a script and tattooed on the count of them.
Life ain't worth a f*** and it's all because of him.
Yeah.
Put it to the heart.
Put it in the rain.
Everything you say is like a.
Bullet to the brain.
Everything is lousy as you try to explain.
Your face dazed and amazed as you face all of the strain.
I don't quite agree.
And much to your disdain.
I say words from your mouth are like a bullet to the brain.
Bullet in the heart.
Bullet in the brain.
Everything you say is like a bullet to the brain.
Yeah.
I say words from your mouth are like a bullet to the brain.
Hey, everything you do.
And everything you say.
Yeah.
Everything you do.
Is a bullet from your mouth embedded in my brain.
Hello, I'm Mr. A.
I'm Mr. P.
I'm Mr. A.
Hello.
Bullet to the heart
Bullet in the rain
Everything you say
Is like a bullet to the brain
The Kirkendall Void
is this band.
That's what we're hearing.
Um,
you can hear
You can find their website.
It's kirkendallvoid.com
and I'm gonna spell
Kirkendall Void
because it's spelled
K-I-R-K-E-N-D-A-H-L
and void
V-O-Y-D
not V-O-I-D
kirkendallvoid.com
Kirkendall Void
and, um,
I need to
I need to email those guys
and see if they can
you know,
play their CDs
at X Day
and pretend they're playing it live
or something.
They make you say things like
hey man,
is everything
corpacetic?
No, that didn't work.
I thought that might make sense.
It has a little macabre
twinge to it.
Tinge, tinge.
Or maybe it's a tincture.
As does much of the
Kirkendall Void stuff
so it really does fit.
Yeah.
I remember when Johnny
was five years old.
He was bald at birth
and stayed that way
for a long time.
But when he was five
we noticed the little shape
above his eye.
Eyes.
It grew and grew.
When he was seven years old
one of his ears
became long and distended
and the other one
stained perfectly still
like the boxes
or a johnny.
Or a ditch rat.
Rottweilers often
take to the spoon this way.
And so we taught little Johnny
to learn the tricks of a dog.
By the time he was seventeen
he was working for the circuses.
Lots of work.
Lots of money.
And lots of
sycophant.
Little Johnny.
Sycophant.
Hard working little Johnny.
A sycophant?
I was a hard working
little Johnny
when I was little.
And you were exploited.
A shovel dog
dog poo for
my
keep.
Wow.
I didn't know that
Reverend Stang.
Well actually I didn't
shovel dog poo for my keep.
I shoveled dog food
dog poo
and food
for
eight millimeter
film processing money
actually.
That was what my
I spent my
money.
When I was a little
barefoot
scamp
of a little redneck
running around Fort Worth
I spent my spare money
on eight millimeter
film and processing.
Honest.
Tell us Dr.
Forster what is it like
to be a scamp?
You have different parts
by the parts
and the rest of us?
Scampishness
in those days
was so different
from today.
We didn't know
of glue sniffing
or tattoos
or shoplifting
or any
well we didn't know
shoplifting.
And we did know
glue sniffing
come to think of it.
And I guess actually
we did know
so I guess it was
just like being a scamp
nowadays.
That you don't understand.
Just one step ahead
of the law
in mom and dad.
Ah now you explain yourself.
But what you fail to realize
is there are no more
scamps today.
What killed them off
the fire ants
or pollution?
No the word itself
scamp.
It eluded
the public's memory
for long enough
for you to bring it back
and be confused by it.
There is no more scamps.
Well what
there are no more scamps.
What do they call rag
well then
what else do you call
ragamuffins?
Peter Pocky.
The Linden Squeezers.
Hum Bacchus.
Have you never heard
of these words?
You are from the past
my friend.
Where have you been?
I am from the past.
Your arms are covered
with dust.
Or the future.
I'm not sure which.
Oh well
could be either
the way you've been
crawling around
on your belly
like a snack.
I think
maybe the thing
in the middle
of your forehead
needs to be twisted a bit.
Oh no
they already did that.
It keeps growing back.
Who's they?
The doctors.
They cut that thing
off.
The doctors.
They removed it
but it keeps growing back.
What doctors?
And every time
it grows back
it's thicker
and uglier
and stiffer.
Ah yes
that will happen
you'll have lots
of that with him.
And discolored
it's a different color
from the rest of me.
Every time
it grows back
it's a little bit
more
off
different
from the original.
So it's
continuing
to replicate
itself
with a bit
Well I keep
getting it
we get it removed
which is not
fun
believe me.
They freeze it
and then they burn it
and then they cut it off
and then
it just grows back
and it grows back
and I have to wear
this mask
all the time
because of the others.
It's hideous.
There's nothing
I can do about it.
So I just keep
getting it cut off.
I've got a whole
collection
I've got jars
of them
in my
in the
basement.
That's absolutely
disgusting.
Yeah I pickle
them in
vinegar.
Oh my god.
I can't
No.
Do you pickle
them in
virtue
or in vinegar?
And a sideshow
wanted to buy
them from me
so they could
show off
what happens
when you do
too much.
But I
I really
you know
they grew on me.
I don't want to
give up my
third eyes
that easily.
And fourth eyes
and fifth eyes
but it's really
a third eye.
Each one
it's just kind of
a joke to call it.
That's my
tenth third eye
that grew in
and they had to
cut off.
God.
And it's always
warty.
Oh god.
I usually
wait until
it gets so
big that
people are
looking at it
instead of my
face when I'm
talking to them
and that's when
I go to the
doctor and get
it removed.
I know
that's like
women stare
at me all the
time because
of my
growth and stuff.
And each time
the crater is
a little bigger.
And you just
want to like
wear a button
that says
stop looking
at my
eye.
Right.
But how are
they going to
not?
You know
when you've
got something
like that
and they
laugh at me
mock me
and they
drove me
out of there.
They made
me feel
insecure.
And I'm
sensitive.
So I had
to get back
at them
somehow.
Who could
blame me
for what I
did?
It was
in the way
of a blow
for freedom.
That's the way
I look at it.
They said
it was wrong.
I did wrong.
But to me
it was
the only thing
I could do.
What else
could I do
when they
laughed at me?
They mocked
me.
They called
me
stump face.
Why there
was nothing
you could do
dear.
Nothing at
all.
You did
the only
thing you
could do.
All right
wait sit
down darling
I'll talk
to the boy.
You've been
having a bad
dream Ravel Rush.
You see
that thing
on your
forehead is
actually
device I
and your
mother Linda
here.
Linda tell
him about
it.
Yes yes
really it's
all for your
own good
dear.
Just be
patient with
it you know
you know
it'll all
be all right
in the end.
Now son
you know
it causes
hallucinations.
There's no
reason for
you to
brandish
that machete
like that.
Sit down
and have
a beer
and a
sausage
and we
can talk
things out.
Just take
a deep
breath.
Put your
feet up.
You know
it'll all
be all
right.
They make
fun of
me.
They call
me names.
Lad
sit down.
Go home
ugly normal
they say.
Die ugly
normal.
Come on
over here
and sit
on my
foot son.
Take this
bag and
just breathe
slowly into
the bag.
Watch the
bag.
Inflate and
deflate.
Just relax
darling.
It'll all
be all
right.
That's
We can
tell it's
the deflation
bag now
son.
It's just
a matter
of moments
before you're
free,
erect and
singing them
damn songs
again.
Just hang
in there a
little while
longer.
I don't
know if
we can
really work
these things
out.
Oh my
God it's
Oh God
here's a
list of
derogatory
terms for
humans and
normals.
Yeah we
can be just
like them
can't we
if we
want to
make up
derogatory
names for
the normal
people.
I mean they
make up funny
names for
anybody they
consider weird
and ethnic
slurs and
all that kind
of stuff.
What we
could do
I've got a
list of
hundreds of
them here
for normal
people.
TV monkey
planet warmer
food tube
DNA host
micro soul
back and
forther
couch bat
these are
really pretty
good I
didn't write
these myself
saucer fuel
blankety blank
Britney Spears
turned violent
late yesterday
throwing rocks
and bottles
getting a
closer look at
President Bush
shot dead
Britney Spears
used rubber
bullets
pictures show
a volcano
exploding
8 news
minute
from PR
News in
Washington
and using
canes
boxing gloves
and bare fists
to beat
educators and
secretaries
on Wall
Street 98
this is PR
News
the White House
is hosting
several incidents
of school
violence
today at
the request
of the House
Ethics Committee
lawmakers are
questioning AIDS
and former
pages about
PR news in
Washington
thanks to
lemur and
we've got news
some kind of
news here
Chicago
coming soon
brood 12
signal what
hello huh
brood 13
no brood 12
it sounds like
a bad horror movie
but actually
it's brood 13
oh I missed the one
no there's only
two eyes there
no there's three eyes
we've been talking
about the third eye
this whole time
oh that's what
confused me
XIII
it's 13
oh then no wonder
brood 13
sounds more like
I thought it was
brood 9
no
stop brooding
on it
coming soon
brood 13
it sounds like
a bad horror movie
but it's actually
the name of
billions of
sick chidas
expect to emerge
this month
in parts of the
midwest and the east
after spending
17 years
underground
I imagine
they would get
sick after
17 years
underground
these are
al-qaeda
terrorists
who've been
sickened
by being
underground
they're sick
chidas
right
sick chidas
they became
sick yes
after their
investiture
into the
you're saying
there's going to
be an epidemic
of these things
I'm saying
that they're
going to probably
underground terrorists
let me see that
news report
here I better
read this as the
news reader
the red eyed
shrimp sized
flying terrorists
don't bite or
sting
but they're
known for
causing calls
and mating
calls that
can produce
a din that
can overpower
ringing telephones
lawnmowers
or power tools
these al-qidas
are real loud
right
they're not only
they're very
disruptive
is the main
thing
you can't really
get them for
most things
you'd want to
get them for
like that thing
growing out of
your head
but you can
get them for
what do they
call that
d-o-d-r-d
drunken
disturbance call
noise
d-n-o-d
they are
really loud
in fact
when I
moved to
Ohio
I didn't
realize that
I had
tinnitus
because
I always
heard the
al-qidas
the shrieking
of the
al-qidas
the sick
chidas
in the
background
that was
their
lamented
calls
of their
strange
bizarre
religion
they
worshipped
the
moth
but there
weren't
any up
here
I thought
I was
hearing
them
but it
turned out
that it
was just
an ear
disease
tinnitus
or something
no no no
it was not
an ear
disease
you've
imagined
so these
terrorists
have been
hovering
underground
in the
larval
state
yes
burrowing
underground
you can't
hover
underground
they've
been
delayed
and
hibernating
cowering
I think
is what
a terrorist
the sick
black
they will
emerge
into
the following
states
will be
affected
brood
13 is
expected
to cross
northern
British
Columbia
banana
republics
and many
parts of
Iowa
Wisconsin
Michigan
and Indiana
sick
kites
live only
about
30 to
95 days
as adults
and then
their
main goal
is feeding
of course
upon each
other
or those
non
sick
kites
nearby
what about
mating
um
well is she
what what
does this
release
to get
to that
dear
just take
a deep
breath
okay
it says
um
they don't
harm humans
although they
are clumsy
and might
fly into
people
birds
squirrels
and pets
especially
dogs
love to
eat them
because they're
very high
in protein
now
these
terrorists
right
does that
have to do
with sex
yet
I don't
know
okay
well
look
should I
look for
the part
where they're
no no
that's okay
okay
well yeah
of course
they they
try to
meet people
but they're
so small
you see
the size
of a flying
shrimp
which in
the first
place is
ridiculous
there are
no flying
shrimp
but as
long as
there are
every 17
years
they come
out of the
ground
sick
al-qaeda
dr.
dark
wrote that
up
so if
you
get
confused
it's his
problem
he is
quoting here
as I
believe
dr.
dark
of the
bad
film
drive-in
and
b-movie
collegiate
you know
you can
take a
course
in bad
films
from dr.
dark
right
but he
is
here in
cleveland
which
university
is it
which
triple c
cuyahoga
community
college
we hear
you a lot
better when
you're near
the mic
I'm sorry
I meant
to say
at
cuyahoga
community
college
and you
can get
you can
actually
take a
course
in bad
or b-movies
they call
them b-movies
they're really
z-movies
in this
case
there are
several
courses
dr.
dark
teaches
I think
one is
in
covers
roger
corman
edwood
and who
else
herschel
gordon
lewis
maybe
I can't
remember
one of
the
greats
giants
the
greats
of the
bumblers
I should
teach
one
larry
buchanan
course
he
was the
director
of
mars
needs
women
down
on us
which is
a great
film
about
how
the
cia
killed
hendrix
joplin
and
zappa
maryland
died
in
ninety
one
six
five
when
did
zappa
die
in
ninety
six
five
he died
from
drinking
too much
coffee
I think
no
that's
the
methadone
treatment
lab
center
he
died
from
cigarettes
and coffee
yes
you're
right
from
prostitus
of the
smoke
so
anyway
we can
expect
these
alkyd
is to
come
out
of
hibernation
and
attack
our
pets
ourselves
they will
try to
attack
they will
fly
fly into
people
is that
what they
do
they will
try
attempt
to
attack
our
people
or
ourselves
as you
like to
call them
in your
ritualistic
religious
way
meaning
the higher
self
I suppose
but they
will
actually
be
eaten
because
of
their
let's
just
quote
here
on
this
one
quote
about
being
eaten
by
dogs
and
other
animals
they're
going to
have
quite
a
meal
it's
going
to
be
like
thanksgiving
for
them
said
tom
tell
dins
which
is
I'm
wish
that's
not
the
guy's
real
name
because
if I
said
that
I'd
be
sued
tom
didn't
supervisor
of
for
plant
health
safety
at
the
Chicago
Botanical
Gardens
he's
saying
these
sick
chidens
are
going
to
be
a
meal
for
almost
everyone
and
everything
as
flying
shrimp
they'll
be
marketed
sold
in the
malls
and
given
out
as
holiday
gifts
and
friends
you
too
can
be
part
of
this
exciting
new
trend
in
cuisine
and
for
more
information
you
can
look
into
the
church
of
the
subgenius
home
of
the
sick
chidens
and
the
whole
zoo
that
website
if
you
wanted
to
check
that
out
would
be
www.subgenius.com
there's
also a
post office
box
which
you
can
write
to
but
I'm
not
going
to
tell
you
that
because
you
don't
have
your
tape
recorder
running
do
you
it's
box
Cleveland
Heights
Ohio
and
with
that
friends
I
think
we
have
to
start
close
down
was
there
any
last
injections
we
are
also
going
to
exterminate
the
gypsy
moths
although
there
will
be
sick
chidens
exterminated
in the
state
along
with
Illinois
and
so
we
are
going
to
exterminate
the
gypsy
moths
here's
from
the
section
on
the
conspiracy
friends
I
think
is
deteriorated
on
schedule
we
know
the
enemy
far
better
than
we
did
when
the
church
started
in
the
enemy
here's
how
you
recognize
him
it's
anybody
who
says
that
you
must
be
part
of
their
clique
or
their
clench
or
their
church
or
their
country
or
their
species
or
their
planet
in
order
to
have
slack
anybody
that
is
I
that's
their
job
it's
what
the
conspiracy
is
it's
not
really
so
much
that
they
rule
over
us
it's
that
we
live
breathe
and
eat
the
conspiracy
it's
what
we
live
in
the
conspiracy
is
the
fish
bowl
and
the
water
that
we
swim
in
they
don't
consciously
take
away
our
slack
they
don't
even
know
what
slack
is
they
trample
it
without
knowing
of
its
existence
and
this
very
fact
shall
lead
them
to
their
downfall
even
the
unthinking
10,000
year
war
on
slack
must
grind
to a
halt
when
thanks
to
their
slack
ignorance
the
world
economy
finally
caves
in
on
itself
friends
the
free
world
is
grossly
overpriced
there's
only
one
airline
left
but
that's
okay
with
them
because
they
own
it
there's
only
one
really
publisher
left
but
that's
okay
because
they
own
it
only
one
TV
network
left
only
one
internet
provider
only
one
actual
political
party
but
that's
all
okay
because
they
own
it
everything
is
under
control
and
that's
just
the
problem
friends
it's
under
the
control
of
the
craziest
steam
engine
train
engineer
and
I
don't
mean
Casey
Jones
or
Dennis
Murphy
friends
and
this
planet
is
careening
out
of
control
with
drunken
madmen
at
the
wheel
and
none
of
them
are
Bob