The program you are about to hear, Bob's Slack Time Funhouse, is parody, satire, and comedy.
Any reference to Bob, the Church of the Subgenius, religion, politics, or any other touchy subjects
is intended only as humor and should cast no reflection on the high standards of WREK Atlanta,
its staff, or that of Georgia Tech.
Star Date 2434.2.
First officer's log.
On a routine patrol flight in the Milky Way galaxy, I discovered on our space sensors
an unidentified planet greening white.
Wildly, in an eccentric solar orbit, I ordered an immediate investigation and with much difficulty
maneuvered our ship for a temporary orbit.
Upon beaming down to the planet's surface, all I could see were ruins.
Ruins of some type of civilization.
Crumbled buildings.
Deserted streets.
Charred vegetation.
All covered with a thick layer of dust.
Existing
I heard a sound.
It came from a cellar in one of the nearby buildings.
Carefully and slowly, I found my way to the source
and discovered a human being,
or rather what once was a human being,
a scarred, disfigured man lying in the rubble.
When I questioned him,
he told me that this had once been a great world.
They had abundance and plenty.
Abundance and plenty.
Intelligence, beauty, love.
There was enough for everyone who lived there.
But the inhabitants were never satisfied.
They wanted more.
They wanted everything.
They started to quarrel amongst themselves.
They could not live in peace,
and they tried to destroy each other.
In doing this, they destroyed everything.
Their abundance.
Their plenty.
Their own intelligence.
Their beauty.
Their love.
He told me that so far as he knew,
he was the only living thing left,
but that he knew he was dying.
When I asked him the name of the planet,
he replied,
we called it Earth.
Oh my God, you blew it up!
Dad, I'm so sorry.
Theyriebu Ta- held me with a sword...
Let's bury him here.
Then re-instructed current president.
Okay, so...
Are all there any people still sleeping?
Going to bed and awake,
you happy stuff.
It's a haven.
I can't believe it,
Hey, aren't you going to turn that damn clock radio off?
It's been flashing 7 a.m. for two freaking weeks now.
Oh, I have to do everything for you.
Here, let me put on some ambiance for you.
You like that, don't you?
Yeah, some nice soothing pablum to ease your troubled mind.
Poor flues, just let it soak into your shattered little brain.
Ah, soothing.
Ah.
Ah, wait a minute.
You evil witch.
That isn't funny at all.
Ah, ease up.
You were flat out kooking on that song a couple weeks ago.
So what's up?
It's with a long face, Puddin'.
Oh, like you don't know?
Ah, yeah.
I like to experience the pain I cause through your perspective.
Mmm, this is so sweet.
So, you went up to Ranch Apocalypse with hundreds of other drooling bobbies
looking to get off planet with them hair pie in the sky sex goddesses, huh?
And, ooh, you wound up getting royally reamed for your bright and shining face, didn't you?
Surprise!
Ooh, and what did you get for your trouble?
Cuts, bruises, blisters, sunstroke, and, ha, one hell of a chest cold.
Ooh, and on top of that, you really burned your bridges behind you when you flipped that
final end of the world bird at all your co-hosts and both of your listeners.
But, but you did that!
Did I?
Really?
Hey, who's to know?
Who can tell where I am?
Rats!
Yes, there!
The sagt, ooh, Spock would turn Armys Porco into sahafanas.
No, I know I was wrong, you stupid!
Well, spare my sl breaking, Îahu."
care. Yeah, you don't care
that that surf music maniac
Rex Reverb spent a whole hour
of church time playing Measerloo
over and over and over.
And tonight
he's planning to play 25
versions of Surfer Joe
the vocal.
No, no,
no, no.
No,
no, it doesn't
matter anymore.
There is no show.
There is no church.
There is no...
Bob?
There is no Bob, is there?
Yeah, you've been on a loser's
treadmill for years now and for
nothing. It's all over
flus. Little Ivan's house of
cards got blown down.
Hey, wake up and smell the mail
fraud. Yeah, the Federal
Trade Commission and the IRS
and the National Council of Churches are
closing in on that little weasel.
He's gonna be sharing
a cell with Glenn Turner.
Yep, looks like you've been
humping the wrong leg, Sugarplum.
All your subgenius
boyfriends are gonna be taking the fall
for this. Oh, a hard
rain's a-coming from this shakedown
and I for one ain't sticking around
to take it on the chin. Oh, jeez.
Why don't you just wrap those
poisonous lips of yours around another
cliche?
Hey, consider the source,
baby. Everything in me
comes from you. Oh,
great. But unlike you,
I'm looking out for our future.
Look at it this way.
You could use this opportunity to change
directions. And your ministry
has been steadily declining ever since
you started this fiasco.
Mmm, but hey,
up isn't exactly an option
with you. Maybe you could just
go down at a steeper angle.
Oh, or
hey, you and that
co-host of yours could do, uh,
one of those drive-time things.
Like those, you know, those local radio
idiots. Stink and Sticky or
whatever their names are.
Yeah, think of the billboards.
You could take collars.
Hey, you got a natural
flair for comedy.
Except for that.
Look, this miserable
little dog and prairie squid show
of yours could be made to turn a profit.
That insipid Bob stuff
has been keeping you out of the big-time flus.
You could be straddling a
success rocket to the moon.
Oh, but I like straddling
WREK Atlanta
just fine.
Oh, right. The Mindless
Loyalty Card.
You know, they keep you and the
big band show guy around just so
they can get senior citizens kicked back
from the federal government.
And what do you think they put you
on at this hour? You know
this town closes down at 10 o'clock.
And look at this equipment
here. It's all held together.
It's spitting scotch tape.
Oh, but they have hearts.
Oh, yeah. Well, I got a heart, too,
and it's bleeding for you. Got a tampon?
No, but I do
have a wooden stake, bitch.
Take that!
Ow!
Oh, damn you!
Well.
Well, it's one less Susie to worry
about.
Ow!
It smells like summer's
Eve in here.
Bless.
I'm
sweetness and light, Susie.
And you freed me from my
earthly prison.
At last I'm
free to spread my message of love
and joy and peace throughout
the world.
Give me back that stake, sister.
Hey,
I'm pretty good
at this.
Oh, my left
boob.
Oh, why'd you have to go and do
that?
Jeez, Flues, you sure can't take
criticism.
Look, you bitch.
I only have one stake, and I hate
her more than I hate you.
So just shut your stinking trap and
crawl back in my cortex and just do your
friggin' job, okay?
Whatever you say.
I have a show to do.
I usually play it should I
wh a
%u
d
you
Porsche
san
. . . . . tet
Sunkin' higher, but I can't get a grip on all the little things
When the night comes, I cannot sit still, you see
And the years, they have not been so kind to me
Got a gallery of figures standing all in a row
Every single figure has a soul of its own
Never look back, never look back
Gone to the back of me
Hey, yeah, my life has come a-ravelling in
Like so many threads
Hey, yeah, my life has begun a-ponying
In so many pieces
Hey, yeah, my life has come a-ravelling in
Like so many threads
And I went to do it today
Hey, yeah, hey, hey
Hey, yeah, hey, hey?
In so many ways
There's a time and a place for understanding
And there's a time when a witness
Is louder than words
And I don't seem to get no implications
And I don't know how to get指 stones
Through to you
And time left the pyramids is forever
away
The mountains and the valleys
and the woods that we say
We have got to make sure
that something remains
If we lose each other
we've got no one to blame
Never look back
Come on, put your back on me
Hey, am I dying?
Is the world
where we begin?
I'm so big and close
Hey, am I dying?
Is the world
where we begin?
Hey, am I dying?
Has come our gravity
and let's set it
back to the way
we want to be
Hey
Hey, am I dying?
Has come our gravity
and let's set it back to the way
Hey, am I dying?
Is the world
where we begin?
We've got to make sure
that something remains
Hey, am I dying?
Is the world
where we begin?
Is it what we've been
told to do?
So let me say
Hey
You're coming back again
You better give me
Hey
You're coming back again
another chance
Just one more time
When you're waking from a bad dream
Don't you sometimes, sometimes think it's real
But it's only all emotion
That you feel
As painful as it is to contemplate,
I guess we should really begin at the beginning.
July 5th, 1998.
Dawn, just like every other day in Dallas.
You can't do this, Bob.
Shut up around that night!
This community is going to learn
to obey the law.
Why should we obey laws that are twisted
to fit the needs of thieves and liars?
Take it easy, Bob.
Arrest him!
He's a deputy marshal.
Don't let that stop you, Sheriff.
I'm fed up with the law around here.
This court can accept my resignation right now.
Where am I to, Bob?
Come on, get going, boys.
Bob, come on.
Sorry about this.
I'll get in touch with you.
Thanks for trying, Todd.
Hey!
It's X Day right here.
A ship that will take you anywhere
you want to go in the universe.
That's the...
kind of flying saucer I mean.
No kidding.
Yes, no kidding.
And if it doesn't turn out to be true,
you can have your worm back.
Whoa.
I don't know about that.
Oh, all right.
Sounds all right to me, I suppose.
I didn't catch your name, mister.
Dogs.
Once again, Superman concentrates.
Like a laser, his mind beams
the exact course they must take
to the silver creatures
who wait,
shivering just a foot above
the Earth's surface.
The first thing he says is,
watch out for religious deception.
Sincerity is not enough.
The devil's sincere,
but he's not saved.
Adolf Hitler was sincere,
but he's in hell.
Sincerity is not enough.
You've got to be sincerely right.
You can be sincerely wrong.
Yes, that's right.
Everything you know is wrong.
Then, like a plague of locusts,
the alien creatures rise up,
up into the sky,
up until they become once again
a tiny, tiny dark cloud
above the highest mountaintop.
And then, finally,
can be seen no more.
As the screen fell,
Dorothy and her pals
saw a most unusual sight.
Behind the screen was a tiny,
little, old man
with a bald head and wrinkled face.
Who...who are you?
I, uh, I am the Wizard of Oz.
But I thought the Wizard of Oz
was a huge head or an invisible man.
No, no, no, I'm not really
the great Wizard of Oz.
I'm just a pony.
I'm a...I'm a humpug.
All that.
Well, Mr. Strang,
it was an almost foolproof plan.
I should have stayed with the promise keepers.
No redemption, no redemption,
no redemption, no redemption
from evil and sin.
No redemption, no redemption,
no redemption, no redemption.
No redemption, no redemption.
This is a long story.
You see,
I was born in Nebraska.
That may have been the way it happened, Mr. Strang,
but I suppose it wasn't.
Oh, I'm nuts.
Hello.
Hang on here.
Who's this?
My name is, uh, Bobby Dobbs.
You come in or take our jobs!
You're dead!
You owe it to your skin!
All right.
That's a second line!
You're dead!
I mean it!
Dead!
But you did call it,
a simply-dressed Mr. Strang.
The jury has already heard the testimony about the phone call.
And I told you, Mr. Strang, that's not the best thing you could do.
There's no use trying to pull the wool over my eyes.
The damage is done.
Don't apologize.
It's much too late now
to forgive you for your lies.
Oh, my heart and soul
now with such a bitter feel
to find you only wanted
the taste of a grand new thrill.
The damage is done.
I've been such a fool.
I never dreamed that
you could ever be so cruel.
Oh, you were playing with my love.
It was all a little game.
But you'd point my hopes
and dreams.
Now I'll never know
I'll never be the same.
The damage is done.
My lesson is learned.
This is the last time
that I ever will be burned
because the damage is done.
Damage is done.
And you've had your fun.
Now you're free to go.
You've had your fun.
Now the damage is done.
The wizard turned away.
And Dorothy whispered to the lion
how the people didn't want the wizard anymore.
Oh, we were fools to trust any man.
Have you been such a fool, such an idiot, such an idiot, such a dum-dum,
as to give away my pinky, the best stuff and maker in the neighborhood?
And most quieter than most worms as well for a saucer without a matching cup?
Take that!
Oh, I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No!
Now, Bob, I think I got a little problem.
Then me, I'd just stick it up and get it over with.
Oh, Brad?
Bob generally knows what he's doing.
He does everything for the...
Bob what are we gonna do I don't know that's great go home they hang it stay
here we start today all right you don't the other way now dogs come back tonight
don't wait for me I'll meet you in Denver Mountain Hotel
wait a minute Bob me and their boys have been talking how about taking over the
bank of town before we split up nothing to it Bob I told you we were through
tonight I'll get out of here the way we planned all of it Bob says we're through
but why shame to leave all that money down there yeah that town owes us plenty
it sure does sounds good but what about Bob's order you won't even know about it
till we give him his share yeah right Bob couldn't we take our fight to
another county where we could get a fair trial that's a good idea then but it
takes money we haven't got it right hey I got what I owe you with interest
get better everyone come on come on the other officers quickly take up the
slag
thanks Bob you got me out there just in time
this ain't right Bob nothing's right anymore go on go on get going
it won't be like before
there just won't be anymore
well I walk out of here like a fool
well I think maybe I should have gone with the slugger
why did I quit because after you've been taking aboard a UFO it's kind of hard to
top that all right they have alcoholics Anonymous they don't have alien
anonymous I lost my wife I lost an alien culture who wanted to take me to the
Planet Ark tourist and I don't know if I've gotten the resentment you know
forgiveness part down in the purpose I turned to a colt for mindless happiness
when I had beer all along.
You taking it?
No, I'm letting go.
I'm letting go.
Okay, let go.
Okay, fine.
Stop.
Dad, Bob broke your beer!
No, I didn't. Doug broke it.
It was you.
Clean up the mess, boys.
Ridiculous.
Perhaps, Mr. Stang.
In the middle of the room
was a big, green, marble throne.
Something on the throne?
Well, it wasn't exactly something,
because it was nothing but a big head.
No body.
Just a head.
As Dorothy stared,
wide-eyed,
the big, bald head said,
Dobbs, go get the dynamite.
Oh, sacred head, now.
Oh, my God!
God, I hope they're stoned.
Attention, attention, attention!
The bleeding head of Oral Palmer
has been destroyed!
Oh, my God!
It was not supposed to be like that.
A premature head-launching,
but nonetheless, a lead-launching.
And now, because of the
exactly what we know, men,
we're going to have Jader
launch the head!
If anybody has any flashlights,
we need some flashlights over here.
We need a superstar needs some lights.
Flashlights, flashlights.
I know you guys have them.
Where are they?
Break them out.
Break out the flashlights.
There's a little bitty one.
Here's some lights.
Let's launch the bleeding head of Tiger Woods!
Ladies and gentlemen,
state Jader Heger's lead.
Ladies and gentlemen, we have just seen
the destruction of the bleeding head of Oral Palmer.
I think this shows everyone
just how bad the conspiracy is.
We need to go and try to stop the X's landing,
because it's the Palmer head,
which is the perfect golfer who has the golf plan,
who's actually working with the Y's
to try to stop the X's.
The conspiracy is trying to connect with the Y's,
which is connecting with things that have 7-11s for heads,
which isn't exactly the same thing as a thing with a
U-totem for a head,
which is different actually from a thing with an 8-12 store for a head.
Who?
A witness who can prove you are lying, Mr. Stang.
Now there's our third witness.
I think I'll start by reading you one that isn't terribly serious,
but it explains what his views were when people asked.
My answer is, you know, he's a liar.
He really did not believe in a serious way in UFOs,
and this might be an indication of that.
UFOs is a bucket of .
What else?
Mr. Stang, that...
Is a bucket of .
Hey, come on!
Get in!
I just come up behind him with a knife and a sling,
broke real quick like that.
So I grabbed him by the collar and I jerked him out of the car,
said, buddy, I ain't never seen nobody like you are.
How come you pull these kind of jokes?
He said, well, sometimes it works, sometimes it don't.
Now, for what kind of deal is this?
It's a bad joke.
That's great.
Your words, your words don't mean
What they used to mean
They were once inspired
Now they're just, they're just routine
I'm afraid the masquerade
Is over
And so is love
Bob, you've been through so darn much lately.
What do you think's gonna happen to you now?
I don't know.
Gotta nuke something.
Touché.
Have you thought about one of the other major religions?
They're all pretty much the same.
What if we pick the wrong religion?
Every week we're just making God madder and madder.
Testify!
You just gotta learn not to expect nothing out of life.
Were you fixin' to say a little something about how life don't seem too fair?
Don't even start
Were you lookin' to get a little disappointed?
Teardrop goin' there, don't make me laugh
Please don't touch my heart
Who said life was a rollercoaster?
Who said life was sweet surprise?
Who said life was a circus poster?
Not me, not me
So ask me no questions, give me no answers
And I'll tell you no lies
Were you gettin' yourself a little moody?
Cause some folks are downright mean
Oh me, oh my
Oh yeah
Ain't that a shame, shame?
Were you startin' to make a little speech about the troubles that you've seen?
Please spare me, that's
That's a pity game, oh yeah
Now who said life was a ball of berries?
Who said life was peach ice cream?
Who said life was a box of cherries?
Not me, not me
So ask me no questions, give me no answers
And I'll tell you no dreams
Who said life was a ball of berries?
Were you thinkin' that you were gonna maybe have to leave this lovely town again, again?
Hit one more spot
Were you feelin' a little like a baby who just got itself knocked down?
You say you were
I say, well, so what?
Who said life was a song for singin'?
Who said life was such a snap?
Who said life was a bell for ringin'?
Not me, not me
So ask me no questions, give me no answers
And I'll hand you no crap
Who said life was a song for singin'?
Who said life was such a snap?
Who said life was a bell for ringin'?
Not me, not me
So ask me no questions, give me no answers
And I'll hand you no crap
And I'll tell you no dreams
And I'll tell you no lies
Nooooooo!
Nooooooooooo!
If I couldn't, Bob, I'd be a low-down door count witness, innit?
You heard when Bob's coming home?
No
What are you lookin' at?
Ah, God, lose your skank!
If I were Bob, I'd show for you!
I'm unconscious!
It wasn't me!
Wait, you're making a mistake!
Put me down!
It's the villager!
It's a clerical error!
It's... it's staying tall!
The party's over
It's time to call it a day
They've burst your pretty balloon
And taken the moon away
It's time to wind up
The masquerade
Just make your mind up
The piper must be paid
The party's over
The candles flicker and dim
You danced and dreamed through the night
It seemed to be right
Just being with him
Now you must wake up
All dreams must end
Take off your makeup
The party's over
It's all over
My friend
Hey заглянув
Take off your makeup
The party's over
It's all over
My friend
Well, I think
I'm gonna break down
And cry
I've been hurt
Hurt, hurt, hurt, hurt
Yes, I've been hurt
I've been hurt
Like I've never been hurt before
Cause you cheated
Cheated, cheated, cheated, cheated, cheated, cheated on me
Yes, you told me
Not a lie
And you lied
You lied to me
Oh, little girl
And I've been hurt
Hurt, hurt, hurt, hurt
Till I can't hold
Not you anymore
Look, lady, I really had nothing to do with this
My name
Do you know how
I feel
There must be some sort of mistake
And a thing
Oh, no, no, no, no
When you left
No
No, I don't
A little more a kid
Oh, great
Cause I've had
New
Needs
And you
Left
For good
To die before
And I've been hurt
Hurt
Till I can't
Anymore
Well, at least it sounds like there's a limit
I'm so happy
So happy
Well, I've been hurt
Oh great, where'd she come from?
To think that you, you lied to me
Hey, I'm in the same boat
I'm hurt
Way down deep inside of me
Try to look at it from my perspective
I mean
You said your love was true
And we'd never, never, ever part
Hey, look
Now you want someone new
And it breaks my heart
Whoa
I'm so hurt
Much more
Oh, than you'll ever know
Staying in all of his goons, they just, they keep me in the dark
Yes, darling
I
I'm so hurt
I feel as wronged as you
Because I still love you so
Oh
But
How many buts do you have?
Even though you hurt me
Like nobody else
Oh man, I am out of here
I ain't fueled no class action lawsuit for this
I would never
Ever
Oh
This year I may lead You to a different course
But suchizations owered you a fear
Of abandonment
ット
leaves nothing for frat for the rest of the whole damn summer. Oh, thanks a lot, Bob.
Oh, why, Bob, why? What did I ever do to you? What's the idea of leaving me bereft upon that
misty hilltop in New York? Oh, how I tried. I was a dupe of the first water for you, Bob.
Oh, I believed, Bob. I believed in your message. I gladly lived a life without thanks, without
reward, seeking only that slackful relief which is paramount to my continued existence.
Oh, that's what hooked me from the first, Bob. The fact that you alone understood my pain,
the agony of living on this life-sapping planet, and you told me what I longed
to hear. That, yes, there was a place in the stars where the slack flowed like hot lava and
the sex codices were even hotter. Yes, yes, it didn't matter how much I suffered here because
I would be rewarded there. So, oh, how I debased myself for you, Bob. I prostitutelized for you,
serving you on my knees night and day in the trenches of the
inconspiracy world, spreading the message of your divine withering grace among the slack-starved
masses. Oh, and then, come your prophecy next day, I awaited your coming in the fearsome light
of early dawn with hundreds of believers, arms spread, mouths wide open for the first barrage
of face-raping bats, and it didn't come. Desperately,
I looked to the skies for those gleaming iridescent escape vessels under the glory of sex codices within
them, but they didn't come. I was looking for that ultimate good time that you promised us, Bob, and
Bob, I didn't come. Oh, oh, what does this mean, Bob? Is your word false, even to your true
believers? Are our sacred pre-scriptures nothing but lies? What else is there you're lying about, Bob?
What about the sex? What about the salvation? Oh Bob, if you were wrong about X-Day, were you wrong about the
slack too, Bob? Oh no, no! I can't go on if it means living in a world where I don't know God, and I can't go on if I'm not living in a world that is Godly.
world without slack. Oh Bob, I can't take this pain. Why? Why?
Friends, they turn away. I keep moving on, but I never find out why. I keep pushing so hard
that maybe I keep trying to make it right to another lonely day.
25 years, coming just one night. Oh yeah. Well, I'm 25 years old tonight, so I know
it can't be right. And I'm no better, babe, and I can't help you no more than I did
with you.
I'm just a girl.
But it don't make no difference, babe. No, no. And I know that I could always try.
It don't make no difference, babe. I better hold it now. I better need it, yeah.
I better use it till the day I die.
Why?
I don't know.
I don't expect any answers, dear. Oh, I know that they don't come with age. No, no.
I ain't never gonna love you any better, babe. And they're never gonna love you right.
So you better take it now, right now.
But I'm day-dipping.
I said, yeah, it don't make no difference, babe. And I know that I could always try.
There's a fire inside of every one of us.
You better need it now. I'm getting to hold it.
I better use it till the day I die.
It don't make no difference, babe. No, no, no. And it never ever will.
We needed it no more.
I wanna talk to you, and I'll say nothing but, hey, goodbye.
I'm gonna live in it and love in it
I get to hold it, babe
I'm gonna need it now
I'm gonna use it
Say, oh
Don't make no difference to me
Oh, honey, I hate to be the one
I said, you better live your life
And you better love your life
Love me
Or someday you're gonna have to cry
Yes, indeed
Oh, baby, yes, indeed
I said, you're almost gonna hurt me
I said, you're almost gonna let me down
I said, everywhere, every day
In the day
And everywhere
Everywhere
Oh, honey, what you hold on to, it's gonna move
I said, it's gonna disappear when you turn it back
I said, you know it ain't gonna be that way
You wanna reach out and grab on
Oh, baby
Oh, but keep on looking up
Oh, yeah
Oh, oh
I came
I saw
And I fell
Little fool I am
Now I'm in an awful jam
I love him
But oh
I guess I'll have to change my plan
I should have known
That he'd be somebody else's man
I overlooked that point
Completely
But I'm still
Until the big affair
Began
Before I knew
Where I was at
I found myself
Up on the shelf
And that was that
I tried to reach the moon
But when I got there
All that I could get
Was the air
My feet are back upon
The ground
I've lost the one man
I've found
I guess I'll have to change my plan
I should have realized
I'd be an awful ram
Why?
Why did I buy
Those black pajamas
Before the big affair
Began
My boiling point
Is much too low
For me to cope
With that illo
For Romeo
I think I'll crawl
Right back
And into my shell
Dwelling in my personal
I have to change my plan
Around
I've lost the one man
The one man I've found
I can never forget
Always have in my entire life
I cannot tell you
That I've become
Like a son
To myself
I'll count to you
I won't
If you earned
I fell in love
With a new sweet
—
And a little
The cold
I've known
For so many years
Life has been spent preparing for a day that just didn't happen.
Or did it?
Did it not happen, Seekers?
I was there at Brushwood, and I know what I saw.
Or I think I know what I saw, but...
Oh, whatever it was, it was truly apocalyptic.
I went not knowing what to expect, but...
with a background sensation that we would all somehow be ripped off.
Though, as I put it, one way or another, we're all gonna finally get porked real good by Bob!
Woo-hoo!
Oh, but, you know, Seekers,
I never expected to be feeling such righteous afterglow from the spiritual mugging we all suffered.
Sure, staying in Jesus or brazen charlatans who took advantage of our willing gods
was a great deal of unparallelability, and sure, the chance of actual redemption from the skies
was about zilch point nada.
Oh, but still, I tried to keep that wool pulled over my eyes
and to be a starry-eyed little Seeker for the cause, and...
although deep inside there was a feeling that we were about to get the big burn of all time,
I tried to deny it.
Oh, but, Seekers, something mystical happened out there in that subgenious sweat lodge,
and...
I know I'm not the only one who saw it.
The night of X-Day Eve, after all the rituals started to peter out,
I took my boombox full of apocalyptic, easy-listening music
out into the middle of the big-ass brushwood field and stood out there,
naked and alone in the dewy grass beneath a sky that was screaming with stars.
And there I danced an end-times dance,
alone in the dark.
And as I swirled, everywhere I looked was alive with our people.
The night air pulsed with subgenious life.
All around me was a ring of their glowing campfires,
and the sounds of their last night on Earth revelry carried through the cold night air
and blended with the atmospheric schmaltz.
And suddenly, I was moved to tears of absolute bliss.
Absolute joy by it all.
Because this was no longer a raggedy-ass convocation of bitter misfits and screwed-up loners.
No.
Suddenly, we were a great subgenious nation.
And at that point of Satori, alone there in that field,
I sobbed like a damn baby over it.
And in that crystal and perfect moment,
I knew what it was really like.
What it was really all about.
Waiting for the saucers to arrive was a lot of kicks, sure.
But that wasn't the be-all and end-all of the game.
Yeah, we got burned.
But at the same time, something stronger in us all got forged in those same fires.
We are all in this church from the start because of our mutually shared pain and discontent.
And at the risk of sounding just too damn sweet and light,
we have each other.
That's where our power and our true menace to them has always lain.
Oh, but by the same token,
we can draw the solace and the strength that we need for our basic survival
from the fact that we are a solid, cohesive subgenius family.
Yes.
Every one of us has a part around Bob's big dinner table,
passing that steaming tureen of slack to the yeti next to you,
and happily digging into the soul-satisfying feast of Dobbs with our brethren.
Sure, we're a dysfunctional family,
but we're made of superior material to start with.
And our version of the home game has much more amusing and fascinating characters,
like our oily daddy, Stang,
and our badass uncle, Katahdin Lagume.
And our sweet little brother, Onan.
And our silken sister, Lilith.
And our crusty old grandpa, G. Gordon Gordon.
Ha ha!
Oh, and you can just think of me as your slutty sister, Susie,
who laughs it off when you walk in on me when I'm douching in the tub.
Yeah, because out there in the woods, Seekers,
I got more bang for my membership buck than I ever thought possible.
This church has given me,
and I know it has given me,
many others,
something immeasurable,
and I am absolutely shining from it all.
With lovely subgenius friends like I have,
I can glibly chortle out of hell the sex goddesses,
and maybe I can laugh off the sting of brutal disappointment that much more easily.
Because we didn't exactly get off this planet,
but for some weird-ass damn reason,
I don't exactly mind living on
this crap ball earth as much as I did just two weeks ago.
And that in itself is a miracle of the first degree, baby.
Oh sure, this cult is founded on a big damn joke,
but our dedication to our own is totally serious,
and any lame-ass butt-stain who doubts that we're a family
can just look at the outpouring of support for poor stricken pea kitty.
A subgenius so strong
that not even diabetes could fell him.
Oh, maybe we didn't get off this planet, Seekers,
but we can use our new solidarity
to create a subgenius paradise for the utensin here on earth.
And by the way, yes,
that was a huge damn X in the clouds
in the pink light of early dawn on X-Day morning.
And it was truly a beautiful thing
to see the tangible sign
of Dobbs' covenant with his people,
a fire in the skies over our great subgenius nation.
Oh, brave new world that has such creatures in it.
Snap out of it.
Ow!
I think that pagan living softened your brain.
How do you feel?
Do I ever need a frickin' cigarette?
After that emotional display, I need a douche.
Oh, yeah.
Ah!
I've done a lot.
God knows I've tried to find the truth.
I've even lied.
But all I know is down inside I'm bleeding.
I'm superhero.
Come to feast.
To taste the flesh.
Not yet deceased.
And all I know is still the business.
In me.
I've come to feast.
The barn WOW.
The barn wow.
The barn, wow.
Camp HISCUP in my honor.
And crawling
On the planet's face
Some insects
Called the human race
Lost in time
Lost in space
And in meaning
Meaning
Ah
Smithers, I'm so happy.
Something amazing has happened.
I'm actually happy.
Take a note.
From now on, I'm only going to be good and kind to everyone.
I'm sorry, sir.
I don't have a pencil.
Don't worry.
I'm sure I'll remember it.
Post Office Box 807
Glen Rose, Texas 76043
And also see subgenius.com