on the floor
lying down on the floor you know just you grow up you have to grow up someday you've got to grow
up puzzling this is what i've been telling you all along i'm sorry i had the headphones on what
i'm trying to tell you babe that this marriage is important to me
uh what did you say problems in my life no silly movies make me cry hal's almost here
he's coming hal's coming hal is coming cutie little hal do you know that hal really likes
to be tickled oh really does everybody know that everyone should tickle hal when you see
when you see him he's got a tickle fetish yeah he does he really does he loves it and he doesn't
ever tell me how to tickle him he's got a tickle fetish he loves it and he doesn't ever tell me how
to tell really that many people but now everyone now everyone knows that's what i do um when i'm
falling asleep i get the tip of my hair i have long hair i start just by tickling my face with
it and it makes it all sometimes this is what i knock out that sounds nice so good sometimes my
tongue uh tickles the inside of my mouth i don't know what that's about it's hal
it's hal it's because you want to make out with hal
something
i guess we're nothing compared to hal i mean i don't even feel like i want to be here anymore
now that let's talk about how i don't want you going anywhere come on i mean you guys like how
are you twins are you twins no i'm in love with you now eve loves you phineas i love you me yes no
way no
way
yes oh my god i've been telling you to leave your husband for me i think i can i think i will i think
it's you know it's a new thing lesbianism is so sexy it's just so 2010 nothing honey go back to
sleep dear yeah there's nothing i like better than two chicks doing it i know i've heard i don't know
with hal in between them playing the accordion or something just imagine two girls with hal a little
hal threesome tickling him sure
what's happening can you guys roll over
look and then because anything you say on the radio becomes true you are now with her
rape murder it's just a shut away it's just a turn away rape murder yeah
oh my god
if you'll join us in this song i think you'll recognize it when i start it
let me get a corn
always remember
others may hate you those who hate you don't win unless you hate them
and then you destroy yourself
richard nixon died today that's just plain poppycock and then you destroy yourself
i saw it on the news they said
au revoir
oh i guess he was okay well i'm not a crook he was the president everybody hated because people
have got to know whether or not their president's a crook their president's a crook well i'm not a
crook i don't dream about the president anymore as a flower she grew and all of my friends they
say that
They don't eat her.
And as a fair young flower, she died.
Richard Nixon died today.
Copycat.
I saw it on the news, they said.
Because people have got to know.
Oh, I guess he was okay.
Their presidency.
I'm watching history remain.
He went to a special place in heaven.
I have never obstructed justice.
Call your Belinda.
We don't have a good word for English.
Copycat.
And I don't dream about the president anymore.
As a flower, she grew.
And most of my friends, they say that they don't eat her.
And as a fair young flower, she died.
Richard Nixon died today.
That's just plain copycat.
We'll see you again.
Richard Nixon died today.
Au revoir.
That's great.
That brings back memories.
You can play it if you want, babe.
It's all right.
I mean, I endure crappy music all the time.
I'm going to play some more Greek themes.
Yeah, I love it.
I love the Greek ones.
The Telly Saval is going to be a super Telly Saval.
So it makes me want to make mad love to it.
Oh, okay.
That's great, Telly.
Good.
Hal's almost here.
Ten more minutes.
Is that me nearly?
Yeah.
I'm not sure.
I'm still deciding.
It is late.
And I'm scantily glad.
Wow.
I guess I should go and edit this conversation.
Are you an edit head too?
Yeah, I edit.
Just like my husband.
Don't you guys have jobs?
Jobs?
Jobs.
J-O-B.
I can't go to a job.
Don't just want me to come back the next day and the next day and the next day.
I can't get involved in something like that.
Jam it.
What dat, darlin'?
L-L.
Well, alright.
Jam it.
Oh, yeah.
Alright, we're jammed!
Gentlemen
Ooh yeah!
Alright, alright, alright
We're jamming it
Gentlemen
Alright, we're jammed!
Ooh yeah!
Jam it!
Alright, we're jamming it
Gentlemen
Every circuit's jamming!
Jamming
There seems to be something jamming it
Sir, it appears to be...
Raspberry
There's only one man who would dare give me the raspberry
And that man is Bob
Local color did that
Raspberry jam it's called
The earlier song
Richard Nixon Died Today
Was from FegmoTactic
By Mark Hosler of NegativeLand.com
The titles and news are by Lee Murr
And the rest is puzzling evidence
It's not spring today
But it's morning
It's morning today
Three minutes and Hal will be here.
That's right.
Hal should be walking in any minute now.
I really miss him.
Hal bug, little buggy bug.
Let me know when he does.
I can howl at the moon.
Yeah, we can howl at Hal.
Hal, howl at Hal.
Whoa, baby.
Oh, it's time to get dirty.
Oh, yeah.
Uh-oh, I think Eve's losing her.
I'll leave.
From PR News in Washington, I'm easily within range.
Iran's defense minister said it'll be a strong deterrent against sex with its nuclear program.
The leading architects of Russia's economic reforms say the government grew in November by more than 10 percent,
but it was mostly due to Barack.
Obama's same-sex marriage to Russian Prime Minister Vladimir Putin.
On Wall Street, 5, 10, 4, 15, 2, 16.
Editors with the Associated Press have voted Federal Reserve Chairman Ben Bernanke athlete of the decade.
The nation's capital is the latest jurisdiction to pass legislation legalizing PR News.
Is Hal here?
Oh, no.
No.
That's what's going to happen.
The mystery now at 3 o'clock is where is Hal?
Where is Hal?
Is he all right?
He's late.
He's not here.
I'm kind of worried.
It's raining outside.
And I'm worried.
He's usually here right on time.
Do you think?
What about him?
We have to do a test.
It is right.
Show up.
I mean, what if he's sick?
What if he doesn't have a suit to wear or the shoes?
He's got different shoes.
Not enough socks.
And what if he ate something bad and he was throwing up for hours?
Or it could be if he got, like, the flu.
I mean, there's the swine flu going around.
Like, maybe he's got some kind of wart on his thumb and he can't.
Well, what if Hal showed up, like, in a pair of sweats and, like, a stained T-shirt?
All hell will break loose then.
The world is coming to an end.
That would be one of the signs of an apocalypse.
The world is coming to an end once Hal wears sweats.
He's such a dapper man.
I hope he's all right.
Do you think he's all right?
I'm kind of worried.
I mean, I don't know.
I don't know.
He never is.
It's already.
What time is it?
It's, oh, my God.
It's 3.01.
He's not here.
Maybe we should call him.
He doesn't have a cell phone.
You guys, none of you have cell phones.
Well, he probably got confused about the digital.
Now, this is the thing about having a cell phone that I've been talking to you about for years now.
You get a cell phone and we can reach you.
I've never owned a cell phone.
I'm not talking to you, Phineas.
I'm talking to my husband.
Dear, I really think it's about time you got on my plan.
I always think you're talking to me.
And then when you're talking to me, I don't notice.
I'm sorry.
I should be talking to you.
Okay.
So.
So, Phineas, what do you think about Hal?
Well, Hal's very smart and he's got a, probably a photographic memory, but he denies that he does.
But he has a psychopedic mind.
And that turns you on, doesn't it?
Well, I don't know.
I don't know.
Come on.
Tell us the truth.
Oh, come on now.
Once I get to go by the feather, too.
Hey, Eve, what are your turn ons?
Hey, you want to ask my boyfriend?
Yeah, kind of.
Do you want to ask my boyfriend?
He's shy.
Shy, huh?
He's five?
He's like my husband.
My husband's kind of shy.
The puzzling.
Yeah.
And I don't like him at five.
Sometimes I call him Puzz or Short.
I'm kind of a shy exhibitionist.
Just like we're secretly famous.
You want me to tie you up?
I like being tied up.
I can't hear you, what you're talking to.
I don't know.
I like being tied up and spanked.
Oh.
No, it's okay.
We're going farther.
Do you know my husband?
Do you like to be tied up and spanked?
And be spanked.
Oh, okay.
Spanked.
She likes to be spanked and tied up.
Oh.
Who doesn't?
It's fun.
Oh, yeah.
Deprive and then abuse.
It's good.
Well, do you like to be spanked and tied up or tied up and spanked?
Or is it like both at the same time?
I like when I'm tied up and then I'm like seized and spanked.
I like the pain.
Honey, have you seen the Ziploc bags anywhere?
I'm trying to put dinner away.
Okay.
You got that sandwich?
Wait a minute.
I told you that you should eat your green beans.
I got to talk to this girl on the phone, though, about something.
What?
Who are you talking to?
Eat your green beans.
Who the hell is that?
It's Eve.
She's waiting for her boyfriend, Adam.
I'm trying to really help her.
Oh, whatever.
You and your little stories.
Your little Guam stories.
Finally, we can get Phineas off the dime.
You know why?
Why?
Hal's here.
Is Hal really here?
Hey, Hal.
I bet he's wearing a hat.
Ding dong.
Not a hat like mine.
He is here.
He's here.
Hal is here.
Oh, my God.
He's really here.
What the hell?
He's right.
I screamed when he came in.
He's here.
I'm so happy.
I'm very happy.
Don't worry.
You haven't believed and not worried at all.
I don't know if you want me to move.
How's the chair working out for you?
His chair just fell apart.
We've been dying for you.
Have you heard?
Did you hear?
You can hear us everywhere.
All over the world.
I'm calling from Fresno.
Are you really?
Really? The frog shrouded place we used to always...
Home of Brian Kenny Fresno.
Hal, say hi to Phineas.
Hi, Hal.
Hey, Phineas.
Hey.
It sounded so full, so full of the vitality and zest of life that it seemed that you were actually present in the studio.
Wow.
And he had the same illusion about you earlier.
Well, I sent you a...
He was talking to you on the phone.
This world without illusions.
I sent you a present.
Phoning it in, eh?
Hello, this is me, Bernard.
I just want to say, you know, you and I, those of us who are members of...
Who are so-called subgeniuses, know that the Subgenius Foundation and the Church of the Subgenius is a UFO cult, a UFO church.
And if you haven't had a dream about an alien invasion taking place and that you'll be taken out of it,
that as a subgenius you might be left behind here along with the...
...I think to deal with the conspiracy that at the end time that everything's playing out and that UFOs are appearing in the skies and appearing personally to individuals,
especially individuals like me, that UFOs are appearing in the skies and they show that they know that you're here.
And with all that said...
We had to pour salt.
Giant salt crystals.
Thank you very much.
Happy New Year and Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
But my wound can never be healed.
Or marry...
Whatever deity day of rest and choice and perfection that you feel is worthy of your veneration at that time of year.
Indeed.
It could be yourself.
I hope it's just yourself personally.
Of course, you can have something direly the matter, but then you can get well from that.
Happy Mimas.
One must simply continue.
Mimas and...
Yeah, Mimas.
Momos.
I can't think much better of someone than I do of myself.
It's like...
Happy Mimas.
So have a nice big flagon of...
You guys are what?
Huh?
Sucking air chest wounds.
I think he's talking about sucking chest wounds.
No, no, no.
There's no sucking chest wound.
That's a tissue of malarkey and lice.
Why one could not breathe, let alone broadcast on the radio with a sucking chest wound.
I don't know what I was thinking.
The...
The lungs are not able to expand, you see.
You hangman rope sneak catcher.
Must have been Justin and Craig.
It's all her fault.
Well, her...
She makes my lungs expand, but I never got to expound on the fact that jellyfish are not drinkable.
So the idea that we can just drink jellyfish...
Not yet.
But once we put them in this blender, they will be...
In the future, we'll be able to drink everything.
Well, you can drink it, but I won't because of the presence of thousands of tiny stinging nematocysts.
The jello-matic.
Stinging.
That's why we put them in the blender.
Blend the manic 3000.
All the way down.
At this speed.
Incredibly painful beverage.
We'd tear these apart at the cellular level.
And even if they didn't have painful stingers, it still wouldn't be a good idea because,
although it's true that jellyfish contain about 90% water, that water has nearly the same salt content as the ocean.
So you'd be drinking salt water and going insane, as well as getting stung the beaches of South Florida.
But I heard that the most...
The most pointy jellyfish.
The very tiny one.
Well, that's by size, you see, and if there are a whole lot of them.
I heard the scariest alien is a very tiny one.
But I'll take the tiny one over the Portuguese man of war.
Jellyfish maintain the same salt to water ratio as the sea rock.
I heard the funniest...
Well, you could cook them down then, though.
You could distill them.
Or can't you just distill them?
Unlike the air jellyfish of the planet Pandora, the marine variety...
Most X-Day is not X.
If you have a lot of wood...
You could burn the wood, create a fire, put a pot of jellyfish on the fire, put some type of plastic covering on it, enclose it in an enclosed area to capture the gases, and actually distill the gases being put off, which would mostly just be water vapor.
What other kind of gases would you create by cooking down your jellyfish, Dr. Howell?
That's a question I bet you didn't get at the Dr. Howell Institute.
Let's call this one...
This is the Dr. Howell show.
I'll have a 1969.
Just present the state of the reading here.
Hey, can we talk about Michael Jackson or is it still too soon?
Last night a сообщman Called Messi Cesare started his Imperial journey to December 19.
Came to United Kingdom saying see you Do forced to254 days since 1905.
Wanted to visit Paris to film in Cinémathéon live, a
picture shot at 9 o'clock on Jan 29th.
We thought he was hyped
We'd heard it before
The PR machine dinnnst stop
At my door, the rumour was out
Sources confirmed
That in some distant studio
Alchemy burned
The DJ's acclaimed
I've heard it
Everything changed
He's heard it
Nothing's the same
We've heard it
Everything you know is wrong
Now hey, you
Have you heard
The hottest record in the world?
Hey, you
Have you heard
The hottest song in the world?
Nobody really
Knew what to do
Now everything else was just musical gruel
We packed up our instruments
Packed up our bands
Nobody could top it
The record will stand
At number one
Forever
Rest of the jar
At number one
Uniquely
Satisfied
Inspiring, every soul
Now hey, you
Have you heard
The hottest record in the world?
Hey, you
Have you heard
The hottest song in the world?
Hey, you
Have you heard
The hottest record in the world?
Hey, you
Have you heard
The hottest song in the world?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
The curious thing, it was never blasé.
Hearing the song once again and again.
Discos and films, adverts and news.
The song fitted every conceivable use.
Of melody
Perfection
Miracle
Reflection
Dream machine
Injection
Everyday we kept on singing
Now, hey you, have you heard
The hottest record in the world?
Hey you, have you heard
The hottest song in the world?
The hottest record in the world?
Hey you, have you heard
The hottest song in the world?
Our societies fail
In a global collapse
Nothing could cover all the economic gaps
Nobody cared
The song played again
With everybody singing along to their grave
In harmony
Forever
In a way
Wherever we were
In heaven
Finally we're all contented now
Hey you, have you heard
The hottest record in the world?
It's just the oath
Hey you, have you heard
The hottest song in the world?
It's not ageld
Sisteme
En pahes
Thim
A식
Dink
Just a word
As a définitive
The Attery Squash
The Attery Squash, of course.
I noticed they have been on Puzzling Evidence Show too, a bunch.
They are on Facebook as The-Attery-Squash
and Attery has two Ts, an A and an E and a Y.
And that song reminds me of the computer god.
4 billion worldwide population, all living have a computer god containment policy.
Brain bank brain, a real brain.
In the brain bank cities on the far side of the moon we never see.
Yes, Francis E. Deck.
Yes.
Well, good evening, Dr. Howell.
Oh, there's another one of your fans, Dr. Howell.
Well, you know, he's a faithful adherent of subgenius philosophy.
So he's also one of your fans.
And who is calling?
What?
Governor...
It's Ratnar.
It's a campaign manager.
It's a campaign manager for the Dr. Howell for Congress.
Can I give the web address out?
I will not, sir.
Oh, I don't know if you can give it out.
You might be able to.
Is there any rule against spouting it out on KPFA?
Or is there any money to be made on the far end of that thing?
There better not be.
There's a menace.
No money.
As long as you can't make any money.
Absolutely.
I think it may be okay, but it could crash.
It might send such a wave of people rushing to that web address that it's going to crash
that company's servers.
You know what?
I think it's time, with it being 2010, Philo, I think with it being 2010, that we should
see how many people are there listening to Dr. Howell right now who could say, you know
what?
Let's crash Facebook's servers.
Yeah, let's get rid of Nancy Pelosi.
But...
That's...
No, not so much that...
Well, yeah, yeah.
We'll get rid of Nancy Pelosi, but more fun would be to crash the Facebook...
Don't you think it'd be more fun to crash the Facebook servers?
Exactly.
And let's see how many people there are listening in San Francisco right now who will go to their
Facebook right now and go to...
...people in San Francisco...
Wait a minute.
It's tinyurl.com.
...they can vote for...
Flash.
...the people in San Francisco.
...elect Dr. Howell 2010.
All one word, Dr. Howell.
Elect Dr. Howell 2010.
All one word, dot what?
He'll fix up the government and make things better.
Dr. Howell what?
There will be no...
You know when you spell the name in elect Dr. Howell, just spell it D-R.
So vote for Dr. Howell in 2010.
2010.
And that's where my...
That's at tinyurl.com.
Tinyurl.com.
And that's where Nancy Pelosi will be.
My friend.
Dot com.
Slash.
Keep...
Select Dr. Howell D-R.
Dr. Howell 2010.
Let's go.
Elect D-R. Howell 2010.
Right.
Exactly.
You're going to get me into trouble.
It won't work.
Whether he wants it or not.
It's all one word, all one word.
Well, you know, he would get a free issue of Hustler every month.
I think we need a Congress of people that don't want to be there for a change.
Is that a campaign for...
Well, Larry Flint.
Larry Flint sends it to every member of Congress, every member of Congress.
Every month.
Oh, yes, I see.
Well, that is a good reason to gain elective office.
But, from the rock-bound coast of Maine to the sunny shores of California...
Yeah, plus you got the nice out here.
Well, maybe Larry Flint will go to Pandora and...
Unaccustomed as I am to public speech...
...
My head is humming, my wheels are buzzing, I'm out from under you.
My teeth are clicking, I'm lying licking, I'm out from under you.
Influential you, don't like the things you make me do.
You untucked my shirt and you burnt all my ties.
My head went crazy when I told you.
I live here because I was born here.
I don't know why I have always lived here.
Because I was born here.
I don't live here because I was born here.
I don't know why I have always lived here.
Now I light my waffles with a pecan nut.
Tastes so much darn better than that old pizza hut.
Yeah.
Some may call me nothing but a Waffle House kick.
But if I didn't have that franchise I would be sick.
Influential you, don't like the things you make me do.
You untucked my shirt and you burnt all my ties.
My head went crazy when I told you lies.
And that was also Thigbo Tactic from NegativeLand.com.
And now, the blues.
When I went back to the river.
You could do it and it could be pretty good.
I had a banjo on my knee.
Yes, going to Louisiana.
I had a played a rocker.
I had a fiddle-a-fiddler.
And I diddled a chicken.
The buckwheat cake was in her mouth.
The chicken diddler.
The deer was in her eye.
Well I was playing my fiddle like a guitar.
Driving home.
Did you ever see the devil with his iron spade and shuffle?
I run. When I see the devil I'll run the other way.
Do you ever dance with the devil in the day on my mind?
I see the devil coming and I run.
I run. When I see the devil I'll run the other way.
How then was the devil dressed?
Why he was in his Sunday best?
His coat was green and his breeches was blue.
And there was a little hot hotel coming through.
So, Rocknar, are you going to X Day?
Me?
Rocknar.
Rocknar didn't go to the last two X Days, but he'll probably reappear there.
Rocknar ran.
Me?
She had such problems with her husband.
I never finished in that chapter.
How did you do that?
Well, he really won't win by doing that.
He won two games in two rounds.
Luke Hρεv.
Luke Hρεv's suis乾acter.
1947, and the universal number signifying the meeting of a tetrahedron with a sphere,
appears in relationship with 21,600, the Earth's circumference.
6.480, one-fourth of the total years it takes Earth to complete one circuit through the
signs of the zodiac, and the duration between historic global cataclysms, and 33.33, the
latitude point, again, of Mount Hermon, where the prophet Enoch said that the mighty ones
ascended down to Mount Hermon.
Well, 33, point 33, is the relationship that is positioned to 2012.
And, ladies and gentlemen, this is the boiling point of water because zero has no value,
no value.
So, if you take out the zero of 20 and 12, you have 212, which is the boiling point of
this magnificent mystery on Earth, which is water.
Remember, it was water that destroyed the Earth, and it was water that saved the Earth.
Well, with the combination of water and fire, fire is going to be the destroying factor
in the second event, as it was in the days of Noah, destroyed the water, it saved the
righteous, and it is the sign of the earth.
So, if you take out the zero of 20, you have the same scenario, and the last days will
be destroyed by fire.
The Earth is going to melt.
Now, how do we do that?
Well, it's very easy for dimensional shifts.
If the vibration intensifies, and then everything that's not geared to this dimensional shift
that I've talked about, if you're not one of the chosen ones, then you could literally
melt down into a composite of chemicals.
You could just be a little pile.
You could be a little pile of ash laid somewhere, and then be ashes for the righteous feet to
come back later on.
You could be fertilizer for the ground if you're the wicked, and that's basically what
the wicked are made for.
They're made to be destroyed.
It's that simple, and yet they rule, and they reign, and they have the authority, and they
rule over us with a rod of iron.
Now, how could they do that?
Because Satan loves evil.
But Bob loves money.
Thanks to Lee Murr for the crazy number guy.
And...
Did you know that there's a special subgenius crazy number, like 23 is for the Discordians?
Well, the subgenius number is 273, and St. Byron Werner discovered it, and he wrote a
song about it.
This is his band, Rural War Room, doing Turn Left at 273.
Turn Left at 273.
273.
My wife hates it.
Is that normal?
273.
Oh, no.
No, thanks.
I'm not here to dance.
All right, sir.
Let's switch over to D.
Okay.
Let's have a drink.
Switch over to D.
Oh, no.
This is Phil Proctor.
And David Osmond.
I'm David Osmond of The Fire Sign.
And we're enjoying listening to the hour of slack.
I'm slacking off myself.
Dr. Hume had quintuple bypass surgery.
He did, did he?
Well, he's an excitable fellow.
He needs to slow down.
There's a fan club out there that has all of the Francis E. Decc fans transcribed.
You can go to Francis E. Decc band camp?
It's actually, I'm not...
Let's see, it's...
Francis E. Decc fan club, it says.
Well, I gotta have...
Just do a search for the Francis E. Decc...
Finger on the pulse.
Fan club.
At the original X-Day, I was getting ready to go.
It was at night, you know, and...
Yes, X-Day is at night, yeah.
...and Dr. Hume comes up and he has his arms covered in what looks like blood.
Yeah.
Blood will have blood, they say.
Trees have been known to move in stone.
It was blood.
And you were correct to be scared.
I was.
I was scared.
I'm scared.
Anyway.
Well, he told you then about the computerized brain-thinking sealed robot operating arm surgery.
Now it's time for the show to mow your mind down like lawnmower boys.
Oh, no!
Sonic 임팬
I'll be your winkie!
I'll be a wankie!
Be cameoing out now!
Pus excuse me.
Deah.
Oh!
It列実 is watch!
alted Comrey!
I'm hungry, overdose
Now I'm overdos-a
Overdose-a
Hungry, overdose
Now you're overdose-a
Overdose
Overdose-a
Hungry, overdose
Overdocile
is the name of that song by Pilgrim Speakeasy.
Somebody new to us, but he's been around for a while, I think.
More on that upcoming album at pilgrimspeakeasy.net.
And now, let us breathe.
I want to breathe.
A little light over time.
Who wants to breathe?
You want to breathe?
Huh?
What kind of bread do you say?
I just want to break some glass.
Phineas wants wonder bread, ma'am.
I want to do some...
You want to breathe?
You want bread, and I want to break glass.
With fly-eye TV cameras watching your whole body,
every part of you is monitored,
even through your Frankenstein controls.
Synthetic blood, synthetic instant sealing flesh and skin,
even synthetic electrical heartbeat to keep you alive.
A brabble.
Some of the unbelievable computer god instant plastic surgery secrets.
There was no show out there on the front here, eh?
No.
Well, doctors, I'll bid you adieu.
Oh, you mean that night when I was going to call?
What was that there, Sonny?
No, no.
Are you taking off, Phineas?
I'm not so sure I'm...
I have to go.
...talking to you now.
It's an old-timers disease.
I want to take off.
Oh, good night, Phineas.
Good night, Phineas.
Check your email, Phineas.
I need you to call me.
Okay.
I didn't think he was leaving, but...
Or send me your phone number.
I have to relieve myself, so I have to go.
Relieve yourself of the burden of the disease of mortality.
Everyone needs to know about that.
Are you feeling kind of grumpy?
Are you in a bad mood?
I'm going to reevaluate my terrible diet for every day of the week.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Is it on?
Yes.
It's a record, feeling really tired...
And no shikiboku?
On today's video, we're doing a bit of a punishment most common that is a decided
Yeah!
I remember when I met you, you were wearing a different shirt.
And you're playing with your hair by taking a breath.
I'm about to hurt.
That's getting the bagel on my head.
Let me take a lick at it.
Ouch, I bit my toe.
That's getting the bagel on my head.
Ow.
Let me take a lick at my head.
You sell more pairs of slacks than anyone I know.
You step on tiny shark contacts and have a bleeding toe.
How long has each organ been in a cell?
There was a separate cell to compose your head.
I wonder if there's a way to cheer you up.
Maybe.
Feeling kind of grumpy.
Are you in a bad mood?
Got an upset stomach.
Think you ate some bad food.
From Thigmo Tactic by Mark Hosler and friends at
www.thigmotactic.com
But Gesundheit to me, because I did anyway,
Charmed by the beauty of this particular specimen.
Yeah, well you should not be probably putting your hands on that in an unseemly way.
I already did.
She seems to be appreciating it.
Yes, well that's a mutual benefit.
Dr. Harnik.
Fyla is watching
like a flying her own egg or her model
really likes books.
Four years ago.
Dr. Harnik and his little Freas
Entre Prut,
she didn't want to get involved with Jelly beans,
just wanted to see how kind she was.
O-oh.
The young virgin once feeling
under four on one
that's probably nothing more than six.
So they had to find that baby
and said this was me.
Players only have a few seconds to select what to do next.
Madison ends up going to the sexy moan route,
and the guy decides to give his boss some privacy.
She then crushes Philo's groin in a vice-like grip
until he gives up the info.
That's some good intel.
Dr. Howell then escapes shaking but unharmed.
It was a close thing.
Is that on tonight?
Yes, that's showing tonight on the E3 channel.
On the Ether channel, on the Ether network.
And suddenly one of Philo's bodyguards knocks on the door and asks,
Is everything okay?
He really wants to be paid.
If you just pay him, you'll get rid of him.
Gotcha, okay, right. Here's some money.
I'm just going to go Google myself.
You know, you can't get away with giving that Dick Gregory money away forever.
That noticed him.
Dr. Howell heads to the ladies' room to see what he can do
about his life.
He's not sure about his conservative appearance.
No, there's just no room for me.
Using more button prompts, players help him apply makeup,
undo a couple of blouse buttons,
and tear off the lower edge of his skirt.
What's this?
I don't have a matching handbag,
and these pumps are so out of style.
Back outside, his dancing combined with his new appearance
get Philo's attention.
He invites him over.
Hey, Philo, get a load of this.
I learned this step while I was in the Catskills.
Very nice.
Nice, Dr. Howell.
Thanks.
It was, uh...
Don't step in that water, though.
It ends up in the water.
That is...
It ends up in the water, and then your game shorts out,
and you can't have any fun anymore...
Oh, I've got another pair of shorts.
That's not the problem.
The problem is...
But just take a look at that sunset.
It seems to be flickering.
What's the deal with that flickering sunset?
It's an atmospheric condition, Philo, that we call...
Are you sure it's just not LED?
No, it's no drug.
What it is, is...
It's a combination of atmospheric...
Wait a minute, my pen stopped writing.
I can't...
Hold on.
Wait.
What was that third thing you said, Dr. Howell?
...found in the troposphere of Earth's turbulent atmosphere.
Here, the upper atmosphere squids extend their long, filmy tentacles
through the windows of passing aircrafts to sample the contents.
If your aircraft is equipped with a rear observation platform,
you might wish...
...to close the curtains, as these...
...can be invasive and spoil your vacation in the sky.
They can spoil a vacation in the sky.
This has been a public service message from the Are You Ready Foundation.
And now we'll be taking Jesus for a ride.
The minister at our local clinch, according to an old subgenius war story, wasn't happy.
The reason was that it has happened again.
It was that the baby Jesus had disappeared again from the nativity scene
out in front of his clench.
It came from outer space.
And had been replaced with a baby Bob.
It rose on trees.
The minister's patience was wearing thin.
He'd had enough of this vandalism.
And he didn't find it amusing any longer.
Although Jesus never disappeared, he went up to his father's house.
Get the terror from beyond.
The little red wagon was covered with a moth-eaten sort of blanket.
The kid ran down the street with his teeny-weeny wagon.
The sidewalk was no longer recognizable as a walking place.
An undifferentiated mass of unrecognizable protoplasm.
Loads of indetestable putrescence as M. Waldemar slouched forward, disintegrating before our eyes.
A pinata of stench as his rotting body exploded all over the carpet.
What a fetid fever of freedom.
...his house and dollars.
The soul ascended to the plaintive wail of a funeral violin.
I had never felt so trapped in my life as I had been that time I was trapped inside that time.
Oh no, not Mr. Parizzi.
Yes, Mr. Parizzi.
Oh no.
Mamma mia.
He was just trying to protect himself.
That's what they all say.
It's been years since I had taken public transportation.
I'd never lower myself.
It's just a deadly weapon.
To that level again.
Just get a reprimand, like for shoplifting when you've killed another person with an automobile.
Don't misunderstand me. I'm not ashamed of the gospel of Bob.
Uh, just, uh, get into the witness stand, please.
I do.
This chair squeaks.
How's this?
Squeak, Mrs. Dean.
Oh.
Good. Very good indeed.
Uh, you may tell the jury what you saw happen.
Well, I was just searching my squishy.
Oh, which one?
Uh, that one there. Um.
I see. Uh, continue, please. Go ahead.
Well, I went in the B's, opened my ring, got to the knife, six down the door.
Then I spread out, just get one open.
How's that front?
The old foot.
Uh.
Uh-huh.
Well, um, go on.
Well, um.
That's what I heard.
And now, once again.
Once again.
That's all.
Thank you, Leemurr.
And coming up from Local Color, the music of the spheres.
Hit it.
You're welcome.
Base music.
.
Ici in Why Not?
Noise.
It is the music of the spheres.
Bass music.
Bass music?
Well, that's what the robot calls electromagnetic space static.
And it does sound kind of like music.
So we were all listening to it.
Noise is noise.
It is the music of the spheres.
Bass music.
Bass music?
Noise is noise, not music.
It's quite obvious you were never programmed for music appreciation.
Well, it does have a nice beat to it.
Noise is noise, not music.
Bass music.
The next thing I know, you two will be turning this place into the galaxy of Google or something else.
Electromagnetic space static.
It is the music of the spheres.
Bass music.
The next thing I know, you two will be turning this place into the galaxy of Google or something else.
Electromagnetic space static.
Yes, sir.
I understand that.
I understand.
So, here, that's what these pills are for.
Now, listen.
You're pleased to be old, guys.
He's not shy.
Go ahead.
Give him the pills.
Take a pill.
Remind him, you know, he's going to be a good kid.
I just think it's a cool idea.
Take half a pill, half a pill, another half a pill.
Take these.
Here, take some water.
Get another half a pill, yes.
Half a pill, half a pill, half a pill.
Now, ask him some complicated question or some verse from the Bible,
something that will make him have to process.
A foolish son is the heaviness of his mother.
Foolishness is bound in the heart of a child,
but the rod of correction shall drive it from him.
But he's an atheist, so that's not going to do any good.
Man is born unto trouble as the sparks fly upward.
He thinks that's just a throwback to man has actually gone farther than that.
He's asked the question.
Science has disproved it.
The heavens declare the glory of God, and the thing which shall be shown.
And so we're just like fooling around in this zone we know is a waste of time.
What do we do?
Are we going to eschew all these external encumbrances
and move forward with a new approach, a new ethic?
Let's get out of this religious mumbo-jumbo.
Somehow we've got to get back to metaphysics without religion.
How can we do that?
I mean, what's the approach?
How can we keep that and find that new value, that new moral,
that new truth?
A new ethic.
Making wise.
In a post.
The statutes of the Lord are right.
Delighting.
Post-religious.
The commandments of the Lord.
Commercial world.
Are pure.
Enlightening the eyes.
The fear of the Lord is clean.
How can we do that?
Enduring forever.
Or should we?
The judgments of the Lord.
Isn't even worth the trip.
Are true and righteous.
Speaking of trip.
More to be desired are they than gold.
Yea, than much fine gold.
I just spent seven dollars like it was three dollars.
But i 지금까지ения что.
stal incredible leicht fifty percent get in spite of calm down
killed
Thank you.
That does it, Mike. You want them held?
Nah, send them back to their coffee cups.
Alright, that'll be all.
Thanks.
The Void by Rural War Room
from their CD Flaming Universe.
They're at RuralWarRoom.com.
This has been the Hour of Slack from Subgenius.com.
Praise Bob.