Welcome to Difficult Listening Hour.
SHOW ME, TELL ME, TELL ME!
And now, the subgenius.
Oh, what?
Oh, God, it makes sense.
And it's so repulsive if...
Atomic batteries to power.
Reminds us of me.
You're ready to move us.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
Tonight's show would be Hour of Slack,
numbered FSC99,
but we're so far behind
and have been doing so many live devivals and things
that putting all that together
would be a waste of time.
It's going to have to be put off.
And so, to now,
to now, we're running Hour of Slack number 360,
the Pobucker special show
from around somewhere in 1991, I guess,
featuring the incredible prank call tapes
of Arnie and Barney to the late Benny.
I hear people talking bad about the way
they have to live here in this country.
Harping on the wars they fight,
laughing about the way things ought to be.
I don't mind them switching sides
and standing up for things they believe in.
When they're in the middle of the night,
they're running down a country man.
They're walking on the back and side of me.
Hello, I'm older.
Benny.
What?
I told you to quit bothering me.
Well, I want to ask you something.
What?
What's that big old green truck doing out there
in front of the showroom?
Well, right, that ain't none of your business either, is it?
You don't supposed to be parking on the street like that.
That ain't none of your business.
Don't worry about it, Captain.
Yeah, I'm older.
Benny, I'm going to tell the police
to have them move that old truck.
You tell them, and please do, will you?
Please, don't leave me.
How about the other...
Come see my new house this week, Ethan.
Ain't you got nothing else to do?
Where's your new house at?
You lied to me the other day, too, about something.
What?
You said you had tomatoes out of your garden.
You ain't done it.
I have.
What'd you lie to me for?
This fruit stand's my garden.
Huh?
Fruit stand's my garden.
Well, you got one on me there, then.
Yeah, goodbye.
Benny?
How I'm older.
Benny, you said yesterday...
I asked you to go out there not to bother me.
I won't ask you something.
That's what you say every time you call.
You said yesterday...
No, it ain't none of your business.
It's both of us.
Well, Barney wanted me to keep an eye out for you.
What?
Barney was not just...
How I'm older.
Barney wanted me to look out...
Look, quit bothering me.
Listen, why don't you quit bothering me?
What are you going to eat today?
None of your business.
I saw you the other day out there across the hospital.
Cut the little cafe.
Yeah, well, why don't you let me know who you are and so forth?
You eat out there a lot.
None of your business.
Well, I saw you eating out there today.
Yeah.
I was just at the little cafe.
Listen, listen.
Now, why in the hell can't you leave me alone?
They got pretty good food in there.
I don't know.
Why don't you go try it?
Well, I've eaten in there a time or two, but it's been a long time ago.
Well, listen, quit bothering me, will you?
Benny?
I don't want to hear from you, and I don't give a damn about you.
I want to tell you something.
What?
I hope I can see you.
You shouldn't have been drinking a beer out there, Danny.
You're not supposed to drink beer.
I drink beer when I get ready or anything else.
You don't want to drink beer.
I do whatever I damn please.
It's nobody's business of mine.
Boston.
Damn, the Boston, you too.
Well, I wouldn't want to see you get fired, Benny.
Tell me that I'm getting fired.
But Barney told me.
It ain't none of your business if I do.
I work when I please.
I don't have to work all the time.
Well, you drink beer every day at that.
No, hell no.
Well, you don't need to be drinking beer.
I don't need to be drinking beer.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
Oh, I love to hear that recording of poor old Benny getting harassed by Arnie.
And we'll be hearing other excerpts from that famous tape.
Because tonight we're going to, on the hour of slack,
on this religious broadcast,
we'll be listening to some of the subgenius preaching
from the Subgenius World Convention in Chicago about three weeks ago.
But also tonight I thought we would indulge in a short study
in poebuckers through song and prank call.
The word poebucker may need some explaining to some of you people new.
To our religion.
A poebucker generally means a person with very low values.
Usually an ignorant type of person.
The common image is of a person in a pickup truck.
Or a person, the kind of person with a pickup truck up on blocks in their front yard for five years.
I mean, it doesn't always mean poor, but it just means trash.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not saying anybody with a pickup truck.
You see, there's a lot of subgeniuses with pickup trucks.
There are many rich poebuckers for that matter.
A lot of subgeniuses are part poebucker.
I probably wouldn't talk the way I do if I wasn't that way somewhat myself, dear friends.
The term, actually, many people figured what it meant.
Oh, that means a subgenius who's poor in bucks.
It's not.
It's a term.
That's a corruption of an African language word, booker or bookra,
which meant boogeyman or demon.
And the African slaves brought to America, some of them called white people bookers or buckra.
And white trash, therefore, were called poor buckra or poebuckers,
which is how my dad's family used to pronounce it.
Mm-hmm.
And these famous telephone experiments would have to be a big part of any study of the rich texture of poebucker life.
The tapes of Arnie, his many calls to Benny, Benny Garrick, at Al White Motors.
Now, and Al White Motors is in Tallahoma, Tennessee, I believe, near Nashville.
And Benny was harassed by these calls for like three years.
And he recently died.
In fact, Benny died just in July.
We have a copy of his obituary from the newspaper.
Now, why would we know so much about the people on this prank call tape?
Well, we were that curious.
And one who was even more curious was your fellow subgenius minister.
And scientist, Reverend Lou Minotti, who recently moved to Nashville and discovered a lot about these prank calls.
For one thing, Arnie worked in the same building as Al White Motors.
In the Al White Motors building, he worked in the parts room.
And Benny worked in the showroom.
When Arnie was making these calls to Benny, he could see Benny.
And Benny knew.
He knew the person who was playing Arnie.
Arnie was one of several aliases.
Another one was Roscoe.
And the, it's just, I think we should get back into these tapes.
And I'll tell you a little bit more that's even more frightening about the incredible Arnie and Barney and Benny tapes.
After this message.
Friends between us.
This is not very far.
Oh Lord!
I'm giving my love to you.
Cause I only want to see you smile.
You've got nothing to lose but the failure to choose.
And you're turning into somebody you've been wanting.
Oh no!
You're a dog of bone.
Don't come thinking through the door.
You're one of the few us who's we will all let you go.
You're the big, the bold, the bold.
Oh!
Due to today's modern recording techniques, you may play these hits with true stereo reproduction.
Say hallelujah!
Seen it all on TV.
Lee Harvey got gunned down.
Murdered by Jack Ruby.
Ruby, the biggest sleaze in town.
He stuck that gun into his ribs and said, here's looking at you, kid.
Ruby killed Lee Harvey.
TV proved he did.
And the old lady was a friend of mine.
A very good friend.
Leave me alone.
How about it?
Danny?
Yeah?
Where's your car at?
None of your business.
You know it's raining this morning?
No, is it?
Sure is.
Well, I've been down.
I can't see that.
You can't see.
You have to tell me that.
I didn't know.
You knew it was raining.
No, I didn't know it.
Well, guess what happened?
Well, I don't care what happened.
What?
Mondale picked a woman for his running mate.
Who?
Mondale.
That's good.
He picked a woman for his running mate.
Guess what else happened?
What?
The boss man went up on my house.
I'm going to have to move out.
Well, good.
I've been wondering.
Move out in the damn world.
I wondered if you could find me a place up there close to the fourth place I can rent.
Get out of the state.
Excuse me.
Goodbye.
Danny?
How about it?
Why don't you leave me alone?
I'm busy.
Barnett said you used to have some rental money.
Leave me alone.
I'm busy.
Bye.
Shoot up.
Kill them.
Bang.
Stab them.
Crush.
Slash.
Kill.
Eat.
Boil in oil with catapults.
Throwing rocks and grenades.
I say that I want to see knife cutting.
Slicing and chopping and cutting.
Blowing up.
Well, yeah.
You can kind of see it, man.
We're going to solve all these problems.
I say give our clubs and give our guns and give our knives and grenades.
Bazooka and tank anti-aircraft.
aircraft instructions. I say there's free instructions for everybody on karate,
sabotage, anarchism, everything there could be. I say there's free lessons from the time of year
two on how to do everything that is potentially to kill another person. There's no hope for
humanity anyway. I'm just going to watch the world end. We're going to make a million dollars.
I want to help! I want to help me!
Now what, Motors? Listen, buzzard breath, why don't you talk to me a minute? Why don't you go to hell?
What's my brother been telling me? Is that true? Well, listen, I don't even believe you got a brother.
You got... Well, he said he used to be lovers over here. Go ahead, go to hell.
Hello? Baby, what you talking about? What?
I work up next to the building for... Why don't you tell me you're on business?
Hey, Benny. What? Benny, I'm on the phone, too. I'm Arnie.
Well, I'm... I'm Arnie, too. I'm Arnie, Benny. Yeah.
We're all together. Good. Let's get together tonight, Benny. I can't. Why?
Because I said I can't. We'll have a good time. I'll do the cooking, Benny.
Yeah, you'll do what? I'll do the cooking.
I won't eat any of this. Oh, Benny, you'd like it if you ever got it.
You'll do it? Yeah.
Yeah. I wish you would do something.
You'll do something for me? What's that?
I wish you wouldn't worry my brother about his boy got killed over in Vietnam.
Well, I can't hear it, Benny. But he told me you aggravated him.
I wish you'd quit worrying me. We ain't trying to worry you.
Yes, you are, too. We won't be your friends.
Well, come on up down and meet me and let me see if I can be a friend to you.
Well, I don't care to meet you, but Barney says he don't want nothing to do with you.
Well, I don't care. I don't want nothing to do with him, then.
Benny, you hit me in the head. You hit me in the head, Benny.
Well, you asked for it, didn't you? No, Benny, I was riding on my own business.
You told me you asked for it. You was asking my woman.
Oh, boo. Yeah, you was.
I know that's a lie.
But, Benny, it still hurts.
Well, I can't hit you.
Benny was bad after women back in them days.
I know it.
Back during Count Forrest's ducky.
Now, who are you?
Benny, you was like a little old rooster.
I asked you, who are you?
I'm Arnie.
I'm Barney.
Yeah?
I'm Arnie, and he's Barney.
Well, both of you.
And you're Benny.
Now, isn't that funny?
Isn't that funny?
Yeah.
I'm glad you get a kick out of that.
Oh, dear friends.
Just an amazing, unusually long segment there.
Although, after three years of calls like that,
Benny got to where he would get into long, sad discussions with Arnie.
Arnie started claiming to be Benny's son.
The bold surrealist, dear friends.
Arnie Swenson.
Praise Arnie Swenson.
Now, what makes the whole thing even more surreal is that everyone at Al White Motors
knew who was pestering Benny.
Everyone in town knew.
The DA knew.
The sheriff knew.
Everybody but Benny knew.
And people all over town served as Arnie's eyes.
They could follow.
They could.
Arnie could.
They could follow Benny around and know what he'd been doing at odd times of his life.
And just as Lois Lane never caught on about Clark Kent,
somehow Benny never made the connection.
Arnie did some spectacular things that aren't on tape.
At one point, he bought a broadcast microphone
and set Benny's radio, before he came into work,
to the frequency that that little mic would broadcast on.
And so when Benny sat down with his cup,
a cup of coffee and his cigarette,
to start the day,
he turned on the radio and there was Arnie going,
Benny!
Benny, how come you parked your green truck over there by the fire hydrant?
And Benny, Arnie could, as I said, could see Benny when this was going on.
And Benny, when he did that, just reached over and turned it off.
That was all.
He didn't express any surprise that Arnie had even invaded the airwaves.
Because at that point, friends,
uh,
let's see, uh,
there was this network of spies,
you see, who, for instance, uh,
Arnie would keep tabs on Benny's movement, it says here,
and would call him at the barber shop and the liquor store,
among other places.
Imagine, it would be as if,
well, as, as Lou explained to me,
this, this sort of like a crazed Andy of Mayberry scene.
It's like, what if Andy was secretly
tormenting Barney Fife?
And everyone in town knew about it.
Floyd knew about it.
Goober knew.
Everybody knew.
Everyone except Barney.
It was like everyone had an evil side.
Anyway, I got a letter from Lou,
who has some newly revealed background data pertinent to the Al White Motors saga.
And I know that many of my listeners wish they had this tape, but a lot of my listeners do have it.
It's, it was a pledge giveaway in years past, and I know that we're going to have to do it again.
We sent out dozens of them.
Uh, as Lou says here,
I have spoken to the individual at the firm who engaged in the protracted phone debate with Benny Garrick.
He actually spoke to Arnie.
I found him to be a warm-hearted, seemingly sincere soul,
who frankly spoke of his unique contribution to telephone research history.
Among the key findings,
Benny and Arnie were good friends before the calls commenced.
Before the calls commenced,
and even while the calls were going on,
Arnie and Benny used to go fishing together.
Arnie speaks favorably of Benny today in the wake of his passing,
though he does admit that Benny had a stubborn streak and disliked anyone getting the best of it.
Arnie would make his calls early in the morning when both began work at Al White Motors.
Arnie would usually knock off by late morning,
then immediately walk across the showroom and ask Benny who it was he'd been cussing out on the phone.
And he would say,
Can you imagine the gall to do that?
Approximately five hours of calls survive on tape.
We should be getting the complete series soon, but we won't play them all on this show.
Arnie reports that Garth Brooks, Clint Black, Chet Atkins, the governor of Tennessee, are among his fans.
Rumor has it that Senator Al Gore is a big Arnie fan as well.
And Clint Black tried to give a copy to George Bush several years ago.
Now imagine how much better the country would be now if those bold surrealists had indeed gotten through to them.
Dear friends.
A waitress asked me what we'd like to have.
And I said, I don't know really.
What would you suggest?
And she stood still.
She just kept staring at me.
And I started getting very nervous.
At the time, I had a beard and I lost a few pounds.
And I thought it would be very hard for anyone to recognize me.
This song is dedicated to Jesse Presley,
the aborted fetus twin brother of Elvis.
You can't arrest me, officer.
I'm not drunk.
I might be half-ass drunk though.
Whee!
The music is playing.
Half-ass drunk.
Well, you know who you are.
When you gotta hang over,
and it's all hung over back,
so do your girlfriends carves.
Half-ass drunk.
Just you and me.
Sgt. Carter haircut, Gomer Pyle hookup, living off a LSD
Have a ass drunk, and I'm feeling blue
Well a flood come in and it washed away my den
And my water bill's still past due
Have a ass drunk
Called my boss, I ain't feeling quite right
Well it can't be Monday cause I don't remember Sunday
And my hands are sitting Saturday night
We love songs
Have a ass drunk
And I'm drunk yet
Well I used to have a job but I'm sick of getting robbed
So I finally do a band quit
Mama had a fit
Have a ass drunk
Now my head feels odd
Well baby needs food, but his daddy needs a lude
Well the baby better find himself a job
Have a ass drunk
Santa have a best thing to do
Sadly my house got broken so big
Santa rapper andRP-op
Have a ass drunk
I'm half-ass drunk and I'm having fun
Stopped on a hill cause I had to take a pill
But I couldn't quite find my tongue
Half-ass drunk, hell I can see
Well they said the light was red now a couple of folks
Well there was 22 mangled and there was one guy that was gimped up pretty good
He had to sort of walk like this for the rest of his life
And there was one guy, it was pretty neat, he was hurt pretty good I guess
They had like this machine that was like hooked up where he had this tube running up through his nose, you know
And that was the only way he could breathe
And well there was this one dude, it was like a blade he chopped straight down on his toes
And I heard he still couldn't walk
There was one guy, well this is what's weird
They found parts of him on the front of the car and other parts of him on the back of the same car
I mean it sort of defies the mind, doesn't it, how you could find pieces of the same person on the front and back of the same car
I mean it, I just don't understand, they ought to run some kind of scientific test
I don't even see how that could even happen
And a couple folks dead
Well it, well it sure looked green to me
Half-ass drunk
Hell I wish I was
Turned a brand new Trans Am into an old tin can
Trying to outrun the fuzz
Half-ass drunk
I'm a victim of lies
Well there's nothing wrong with me, your honor
I can see hell I got this
You damn de-dug your eyes
Half-ass drunk
Oh woe is me
Well I don't really pay, but it's steady every day
Breaking rocks till they're broke as me
Half-ass drunk
Hell I'm half-ass drunk
Lord I'm half-ass drunk
Just sorry, oh I'm half-ass drunk
Oh man, friends, that was Jane or Hypercleets
Doing half-ass drunk is part of our study of the world of the po-bucker
Here on the subgenius radio ministry hour of slack
Hello
Sherry?
Yeah
This is Tom
Listen, before it gets too late, I just thought I'd tell you to, uh, you know, not with anybody knowing
You sneak out
Sure
Who is that?
Sneak out your window tonight
When you ever call three o'clock?
Hello?
Hi, is, uh, Max in?
Uh, no, he's in bed, who is this?
This is Jerry Topher, uh, I'd like to talk with him for a minute, please
Oh, okay, just a minute
This is from another prank call tape called Calls to Okies
Yes, this is Max
Oh, hello?
Okay, Max, this is, uh, Jerry Topher, uh, HNA, uh, you're living over there on Westbrook, aren't you?
Yeah
Okay, uh, HNA, that's, uh, I know it's late, but I want to talk to you about your house a little bit
Okay
Yeah
So you're over there on Westbrook in that
Well, that HNA is, is the Home Owners, uh, Neighborhood Association
Uh-huh
Okay, and we'd like to talk to you a little bit about your house, see?
You know, there's little things like, uh, you know, parking a car on the street
Uh-huh
Uh, the lawn too long
Yeah
Uh, the trash can sitting out there, uh, you're gonna have to start picking them up, okay?
Well, I don't know, I back my trash cans up just when the drugs come along, I pick them up
Well, there's none of that except in that lawn, too
Uh-huh
Your lawn, it's, needs serious mowing, that's the problem, you know?
I think you got the wrong place
No, uh, you know, I just wanted to let you know that we want to have a nice atmosphere around here and you're gonna have to take better care of it
Well, I think you got the wrong place, cause my lawn doesn't, is not in bad shape
Well, you know, you just need to mow it a little bit more, you know, we're not too picky about it
Well, I keep my lawn mowed
Okay
I don't, you sure you got the right place?
Your Mac's so green, aren't you?
Right
Okay, 1214 Westbrook
1214 Westbrook
Well, you know, we don't want to, you know, you just
Where do you get a roof?
I'm right down here, about four doors down, they kinda elected me, uh, chairman of this here, so
Thought I'd give you a call and be real, you know, manly about it
1214 Westbrook
Cause, uh, it's getting out of hand, that Mac's
Well, what's, what's getting out of hand?
Well, you just need to take better care of your house and your, your things, you know, we got that
Stings
Huh?
It was stings
I didn't understand you
What'd you say?
I said you have to take better care of your, uh, possessions, you know, if you want to stay in this neighborhood
We'll blackball you, you never, you never get another house in this neighborhood again
So what, I don't, I thought my house looked as good as anybody else's on here
Well, you know, just
Consider this here a fair warning, we, we'll just, uh, give you a couple chances, you know, and then
Things don't work out, we'll make an arrangement for you, Mac's
Well, I own my home, I don't know how you made your name
Yeah, we, we ain't no small time organization, we take care of that
I don't wanna get into that, you know, that's, we don't even wanna talk about that, just take care of the lawn a little better, we'll check back with you and check the progress on that
What'd you say your name was?
My name's Jerry Tofer
Jerry?
Jerry Tofer
H-N-A, chairman
T-O, how do you spell it last name?
T-O-L-F-E-R
Now, we'll, we'll give you a call back here in about a month or so, and we'll, we'll talk to you later then
See you later, Mac's
Better beware, Mac's
I wanna tickle your love offerings
Sir?
Hey, that's fantastic
Is it? I'm coming over too
Good!
I'm gonna bathe your entire family tonight
You're gonna what?
How's that?
You know, in the tub with the sponges and the water
Well, you sound like just the right kind of guy
Hey, you betcha I'll do it too
You don't know us, we get drunk
We like to go canoeing and bathing
Well, I tell you what
I got a whole bunch of friends that do it exactly the same way
Well, maybe we can get together
Have one of them fleas he owes or something
Are you living in Cali-Paw?
Huh?
I could be
I wanna live in that canoe you got
Oh
Look pretty good
Cor barrier
Gotta put a, gotta anyhow
No African
I can't stand her
My girlfriend is a
What's up
¶¶
Whoa, swinging love corpses.
They're live at the Chicago Subgenius Convention
with that lovely old hymn,
My Girlfriend is a Poe Bucker.
And we'll be playing more material from the subcon there.
You'll hear some Sister Mary Squared,
some Sister Velveteen Sly, actually.
I think we played most of Mary Squared's formal ranting,
but also some informal material
from the conspiracy panel discussion
with Mary Squared.
With G. Gordon Gordon
and those aforementioned lady preachers
and dominatrixes.
And, uh, yes.
Boy, we got a call.
We could tell a rumor on the air.
Ah, it would be so fun.
But I think we better be safe than sorry
because I would hate to have the Secret Service
call the station up and subpoena somebody,
make them go,
where'd you hear this?
You know, where was the leak?
Oh, well.
The eternal conundrum of Connie
as Cleavage Quinn.
Connie knows that a cucumber isn't better than a man
because cucumbers can't cry for clemency.
Oh, unbelievers,
that Connie can castrate and cripple.
Johnny comes and craters crash.
Crash.
And it's Kareem from Connie's
Connie's kiss cascades from her lips.
Lester Fern, leave a tip.
Yeah, Connie.
Can you confront the candle of Connie?
Now this chick, I'm a chick with a Y.
Of course.
This chick has to cruise.
But the chronicles of Connie will continue
as I keep on co-opting the conspiracy.
And cracking cliches.
Brian Connie, the ultimate con.
Praise Connie!
Hooray!
Oh, I love it!
I love all the Connie worshippers we have here.
Yes!
I don't know what Reverend Stang has been doing lately,
but I remember he used to talk about makeup of the church,
uh, being just, um,
Oh, I don't know.
A whole bunch of computer nerd types,
uh, people who just spend all their time indoors,
you know, never getting out of talking to women
or being friendly.
They just didn't know how to please the Connie.
And I'm so glad to see this new young crap of subgeniality.
Yes!
Wherever one or more are gathered together,
in the name of greed,
mean,
confusion,
control,
and censorship,
there is the conspiracy.
But I want to know,
all you out there,
after hearing all this stuff that should have got you riled up tonight,
how big is your hate on?
You know what's gonna happen?
In 30 years,
X day.
And our revenge will come on X day.
Our revenge will come because,
what's gonna happen to those pinks and those normals?
They're gonna go through the worst experience
of their entire lives.
They are going to be forced, all of a sudden,
to be obsessed with sex.
And enjoy it.
And Arabs are going to enjoy it.
But, you know what else they'll feel?
Because they're those pinks and those normals,
they will feel guilt.
They won't be able to help it.
You'll see those nice little ladies that you saw typing into Office.
They'll be like, ripping their clothes apart.
They can't help it.
They'll be like,
Oh my God!
I'm so horny!
This is so bad!
For weeks!
I must go.
I cannot.
For three!
And it'll seem like thousands of years!
That is what they will be doing on X day.
While we are up,
laughing,
Losing us-morty.
They will show up today.
Ah, yes dear friends.
Some, uh,
new prophecies about X day,
the end of the world,
as understood in our church.
The pinks will suddenly start having sex.
They'll be having fun,
but they'll feel so guilty,
it'll be like hell.
They'll be ravishing each other in those offices,
but they'll,
they'll hate it.
They won't be able to stop themselves,
but they'll hate it.
Speaking of X day,
Reverend Zaphod left a message on the church headquarters phone last night,
with the most outrageous request.
He said,
Can't you call Bob up and change the end of the world to,
like,
I mean,
you got it set up for 7 o'clock in the morning,
July 5th, 1998.
At 7 o'clock in the morning,
everybody's gonna be hung over.
It's gonna be horrible.
They're not gonna get up.
They'd rather burn with the pinks than get up in the morning,
get up that early in the morning.
So,
I'm sorry Reverend Zaphod,
but even if I did call Bob up about that,
somehow I don't think that the X's are going to change their schedule,
just because you don't wanna,
but the idea is you don't fall asleep the night before.
Okay?
You just stay up.
That way you don't have the hangover.
It'll,
of course,
sooner or later it's gonna catch up with you.
But,
you know,
I'm just sorry.
These godlike creatures from Planet X just are not gonna set their alarm clock.
They're not gonna be,
I mean,
you're just gonna have to put up with their wake up call.
All right?
I mean,
there's only so much that you can get for that 20 bucks.
eternal salvation is a lot to ask right now.
I'm gonna be right there.
You oughta be satisfied with that.
Okay?
The difference is,
when a,
somebody in a,
when a pink,
a human sees something that shocks them,
they run away.
They don't like it.
When a subgenius sees something that shocks them,
that offends them,
they go,
what?
This is,
I'm shocked.
I'm offended.
I want to know more.
If they still don't like it,
then they might lynch it.
But,
they're just gonna,
they're gonna lynch it.
But the,
but the,
that conspiracy,
that confederacy of dunces,
you know,
the horrifying thing is,
it's not that they're stupid.
The individual pink may be much more intelligent than a given subgenius,
because,
look at the word,
subgenius.
It's not the intelligence that counts,
it's what you do with it.
It's power,
common sense,
sense of humor,
and dollars and cents.
But yeah,
these pinks,
these,
these mindless bovine stereotypes,
and that's all they are,
they're walking stereotypes.
Come on.
Sometimes generic slurs do apply,
in the case of pinks.
This is Lee Edwards,
commonly known as the Christian con man,
because I have total confidence in the Lord Jesus Christ as my savior.
And now this,
this being my first album in Hawaii,
I want to dedicate this album new to you,
my loving wife,
for all the inspiration you have given me in life.
And they're choking on their captains on the squad.
Also happy to stretch Levi.
Etcetera.
I wonder,
wonder,
Squeeze your little finger, ease your little finger back.
You can change the world, whatever else is true.
You trust your little finger.
Just a single little finger can change the world.
Is that justice? Is that proper? I'm talking to you.
Life's so cruel. Why not end it all?
Oh, man.
Happy birthday.
Hey, G, thanks, man. I'm glad you went through all that trouble to write that for me.
Take a job!
And if you can't whoop it, go down.
Go down!
That's a lesser known slogan of Bob's.
No, go down is kind.
I just want to tell you, don't pay no attention to my brother.
I ain't no paying no attention to neither one of you.
He ain't got a good sense.
Yeah?
I don't want to pay no attention to him.
I wish y'all wouldn't be worrying me.
You can't mention my brother.
He's driving me crazy.
Oh, no!
Yeah, and I mean, now listen, I've been trying to be nice to you.
He's driving me crazy since last week at Duke.
Well?
Don't call me no more, I said.
They're getting aggravated about it.
Don't pay no attention to my brother here.
Don't call me up there no more either.
They're getting peed off about it.
Who is?
The company.
Oh, is that right?
Yeah.
Well, they don't know who we are.
No, and I don't either.
Oh.
Well, I wish you wouldn't bring it up to my brother.
But his boy, he tears him all to pieces.
I ain't brought it up.
He starts crying.
I didn't bring it up.
He says you called.
I ain't done with it no more.
I ain't done brought it up to him.
Hell, you the one who's calling me.
He says you called him, but his brother's behind the...
Well, you know, the hour of slack really is made for those who tuned in by accident.
That's right.
Those who scanned the dial.
That's what the show is for.
Leave me alone, will you?
Leave me alone.
You've got a half-dreaded...
No, I haven't.
Don't call this number no more.
What's wrong with your car?
Now, I've noticed.
The authority told me you had some rental property.
Have you got anything else to do?
As long as I can sit and visualize world peace.
Boy, that's better than folk.
Boy, that's better.
Because it's magic.
And think of the ant.
Oh, the ones you poison and step on.
They have rights, too.
Think of the lice that inhabit people.
What about the bees?
That's right.
Nature is a good thing.
Nature is an open ditch latrine in mid-summer.
Do not deny your evolutionary destiny.
Which involves lots more sweating and being stinky and killing and stuff like that.
And frapping.
We try to keep the killing down and the frapping up.
That's right.
But realize if you can visualize the nuclear winter, you can save in your air conditioning
bills.
If you believe.
But only if you believe.
And nuclear winter sports.
The nuclear winter olympics.
If you believe in the winter, it's hot and it's cool.
He's going down the slope now.
Look, his hair blowing off in little tufts in the breeze.
Chunks of radiated flesh flying out.
It's so poetic.
Dangerous sex on skis.
Backwards.
But you see, the things like abortion and pro-life and contra-life, or whatever you
want to put it, those are all issues that have been designed to keep you busy.
And I think we need to do that.
To keep you stirred up.
To keep you worrying about this and keep you worrying about that.
The war on drugs has eroded your civil liberties to the point where they can kick your door
in any time they want to.
All they've got to do is say drugs and your wife is in jail.
You're in jail.
Your children are far back.
Your Cadillac's taken away.
They can walk up to you in any airport in the United States of America and say, excuse
me, did you pay for that ticket in cash?
Yes, I did.
Can we see your wallet, please?
Here it is.
Sir, you have cash money on you.
We're going to have to confiscate it because you fit the profile of someone going somewhere
probably to buy drugs.
This exists right now.
The war on drugs is probably the single most divisive and single-minded effort to erode
every little bit of freedom that we've managed to wring out of these sons of bitches in the
last 200 years.
We've spent 200 years trying to spread that we the people to include someone else besides
landowning aristocracy.
And now that we're finally beginning to do that, they're going over to the other end
of the Constitution and gradually saying, you don't have the right to do this.
You don't have the right to do that.
Everything that is not forbidden is prescribed.
And if you don't watch it, we're going to get you.
And that's what you've got to remember.
Nobody up there is a friend of yours.
Nobody up there wants to see you have what you would call freedom.
The whole purpose of this government in this country right now is to produce consumers
and workers who will keep the cost of labor down, the profits high for the earning people.
I'm not a communist or anything like that.
I'm just simply saying that if you believe that any of these people that are running
for office are going to do anything for you as a subgenius, if you believe any of these
people who proclaim to be on the side of the people who are running for office are going
to be on the side of liberty and freedom, give us what you want, then you have bought
the conspiracy lie.
Fascism back for the people!
Fascism for the people!
Subgenius Church is behind people's fascism!
The individual fascism!
Don't visualize world peace, visualize armed insurrection.
Every dad a duche.
That's right.
Every mom an evita.
So what are you guys going to do at this revival meeting?
You're going to...
Make fun of religion stuff, right?
We never make fun of religion.
Never make fun.
Make money.
You must understand we're making money off religion, but not fun off religion.
No.
No fun.
We hope to erase the slack area in this part of the country.
We are missionaries.
This is hard work.
It's brutal and gruesome work.
And hopefully...
I've loomed the position.
Yes, sir.
These are called cribbage crotch figurines and they're wanted in every home across America.
Cribbage crotch figurines.
That's right, young man, and you've won one.
Oh, when do I get it?
Well, as soon as you sign out the...
The jewel form for the lettuce leaf kids.
At Jewelco.
At where?
We have to put up with these guys because they know the right people.
But you can trust me, Ivan Sting.
Yes, you can trust me.
I'm Dr. Ivan Sting.
And I'm prepared to take your money and give you back your slack.
And I'll be at the revival, the great subgenius revival on the 20th and the 21st at the Victoria
Theatre.
So you can believe in me.
I'm Ivan Sting.
I'm the man who's always saying, I never lie and I'm always right.
It extends throughout the rules and has to do with the dying of Bolivians.
It has to do with glass canes.
It has to do with the Pummeling of Heavens.
It has to do with Gilligan's Island.
It has to do with...
You go ahead, you son of a bitch.
You're so sick minded.
Why don't you meet me?
I'm going to show you what sick human beings deserve in this world.
Yeah, what do we deserve, my friend?
We deserve your wife's swampy.
Yeah, how would you like to be mutilated?
I don't believe you, you sleazy, slimy, dripping...
Hold it down!
I'm talking.
Okay.
I have gone low on you today.
Do you think I don't know what the hell is going on?
Do you think, for instance, that I don't know that Bill Broden is going out seeing Irene,
Irene Hargreeves?
Yeah.
The Bolivians have been there?
Sure I know it.
Don't you?
What is it?
What the hell's the matter with you?
Why you yell a rat bastard, you mother...
You know, fire.
You come once or twice a year.
That don't cut no ass with me.
See?
My ass, I'll tell you.
I'm gonna get on some asses today.
You listen.
I mean business.
I'm putting it down, isn't I?
There's no way it means that I ain't wanting any.
No.
Hell, father.
All right.
Okay.
There's something else, too.
I noticed last Sunday
that one of you put a quarter
in my offering plate, see?
Yeah, Raymond Welch.
You're the one.
You put a quarter in there.
You tight son of a...
I see all that, see?
I'm up here right and see it.
Y'all don't...
Even...
I don't look or nothing.
I can see it.
See?
Some of you are doing pretty good.
And others, you ain't doing for...
All right.
I'm gonna maybe go to another church.
I don't know.
I don't give a...
I've just about come to the end of the road.
Here, I've just about lost patience with you people.
You know we need a Sunday school space out there.
You say, oh, amen.
Praise the Lord.
No.
You know, I'm not gonna do all that
when I'm saying something that you like.
But when I'm trying to get something done,
that's something else.
You get your ass out to the mountains
or someplace or hide in there
and watch that damn tube.
That's what you do.
Listen, that ain't gonna get it.
The horse and the horses,
it ain't gonna do it.
Uh-uh.
Now listen, I tell you,
this was determined today.
I know...
I know you're in doubt
whether I will be your pastor or not.
But I tell you, if so, fine.
That's what I want to do.
But if not, I'm done.
In fact, my sermon is done.
Don't give me no more.
Brother Woodrow,
lead us in the closing prayer.
Whether you gonna do it or not,
I'm assuming...
You're dismissed.
How come you hit my brother so hard back here
to go to that old state?
Well, I don't know.
I told you to do it.
I'm Arnie.
You hit my brother.
Oh, I did.
Fair enough.
Well, he said it deserved it.
He said you knocked him loose in his shoestrings.
I did.
You hit him so hard.
Well, that's good.
I'll do it.
I'm gonna hit him harder than that next time
if I ever get a chance to.
This is potentially five and a half hours of calls.
This will test whether you're hardcore or not.
Yeah, yeah.
But I can truthfully say
that these calls probably mean more to me
than any other calls I've ever heard,
including ones that I've been somewhat involved in.
These are, I think, the great...
In fact, speaking of folklore,
he actually...
Somebody tried to contact Arnie
from the University of Virginia
that was doing a folklore project.
They wanted to talk to him.
It's an example of southern folklore.
Wow.
Hey, so what is Arnie like?
Very interesting.
He's kind of like a Mayberry character.
He's alike.
He's on something else.
He's like a likable guy.
In fact, the weekend that I called him,
he was parking cars on his lawn for the county fair.
He's just a working guy
that works in the parts department.
He was friends with Benny for years.
He says that Benny was his friend.
He was a good guy.
Used to go fishing together.
He was just like what you would call a poe-bucker,
a bored poe-bucker
who had been a prankster for years,
but this was the first telephone prank he had engaged in.
And he says he meant no malice from it.
He meant no...
He meant no harm.
But interestingly, he told me why the calls ended.
Benny got a brain aneurysm.
He gets his own church out.
Yeah, well, it's cold out here.
Cold and lonely.
Nobody can understand what's going on
until the effects are turned down
and your brain's turned up
because it's 4.35 in the morning
and the president's inside your head.
I know.
What happened?
But it's so quiet here in the station.
We're picking up dead vibrations.
Here's to dead vibrations.
Dear friends,
so the KPFA show fades off into their dawn
there in Berkeley, California.
We don't have to worry about that dawn
for it's the dawn of a new age here
at the Dallas Subgenius.
Hour of Slack.
And dear friends, I feel that I should give you a chance
to write for free information
about the Church of the Subgenius.
If this is the first time you've ever tuned in
and listened to this show,
well, there's a lot of other things involved
in our faith here
besides prank calls
and seditious ranting about sexual freedom
and how bad the normal people are.
And you can get that free information,
by dropping us a self-addressed stamped envelope.
It would be the best thing you could,
just send us a postcard.
Shoot.
You'll get a lot more with the self-addressed stamped envelope.
And the place to send that is, of course,
Bob at Post Office Box.
807 Glen Rose, Texas 76043.
You know, my Sunday night just doesn't seem complete.
Unless I say that twice.
That's Bob at Post Office Box.
181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
I am through.
In fact, my sermon is through.
Will, you wanna lead us in the closing head-launching?
Well, are you gonna do it or what?
Oh!
Oh, one last thing.
Enough!
Oh yeah!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Hee hee hee hee hee hee!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Come on baby, don't you be late.
I want your old head, I want it tonight.
Cut your old head off,
a hot pass ain't it?
Now have you know my wall,
but a hot pass did, yeah!
Come on baby, I want that head.
Come on baby, you want that head.
I want your old head to hang on my wall tonight.
My sun!
My sand!
My surf!
Oh!
Go a first round!
U, na, ka, io, n'ail mal mouth!
Ain't no tamama oh, la la
Nah, nah, nah, na awfully.
Ah, ho!
Hey!
Bonus!
E taught a lesson!
Come on!
That's a real broken man!
Well, it's hard.
Well, it's cool.
Whoa.
Before I go too much further into this tape, which ain't going to be far because we've
only got about one minute left, I should mention that I don't know who sent us this tape.
Boy, people send us such wonderful tapes and then they don't put their own name on it.
This says, look out Miami and list the 10 zillion cuts of music and records that were
on it.
But I can't remember which envelope it came out of.
If anybody knows, tell us.
Let's have another drink.
Oh, stop it.
You're killing me.
Gee, it makes me feel much better just talking to you.
Anytime, baby.
Every time.
Whoa.
I'll play it and tell you what it is later.
Sing that Billy Sweet William now
Married life done changed him somehow
He's the man the town used to fear
Now they all call him Sweet Papa Willie dear
Stronger than Samson I declare
Till the brown-skinned woman's bobbed his hair
Excuse me
No wearing out my twa-da-bee
www.subgenius
www.subgenius.com