A slacker.
You know what I'm saying?
Thank you.
I don't have a taste of the boys I narrow
Surely with the force of my years of education
I can fend off the needs of the flesh
The blood of the yak on my lips I scream out
And I know that the face of my headthroat
Is a metal mask like the acid
of the blood
The face of my headline
The face of my lanoturnum
Haring down like a horrible machine
Crashing my fragile skull
La la la la la
I don't have a taste of the boys I narrow
Surely with the force of my years of education
I narrow
And I know that the flesh of my headthroat
Is a metal mask like the acid of the blood
The blood of my headthroat
Haring down like a horrible machine
La la la la la
Crashing my fragile skull
Haring down like a horrible machine
La la la la la
Thank you.
Reagan's Pollock, dear friends.
Reagan's Pollock from Trash Fish Entertainment.
Got that pencil ready?
P.O. Box
That's Box 56497
Little Rock, Arkansas
or
www.trashfish.com
That's the amino acids in the background, friends.
But now
Einstein's Secret Outlaws
covered various different classic songs
over their recent concerts wonderfully
and I recorded them
horribly.
Friends, we need new gear
and we can't get it on a preacher's salary
so anyway, check our website.
So friends, because I have crappy recordings
of Einstein's Secret Orchestra's great covers
here are the originals
and here
The Highwaymen.
I was a highwayman
Along the coach roads I did ride
With sword and pistol by my side
Many a young maid lost her baubles to my trade
Many a soldier shed his lifeblood on my blade
The bastards hung me in the string of 25
But I am still alive
I am still alive
I was a sailor
I was born upon the tide
With a sea I did abide
I sailed a schooner around the horn to Mexico
I went aloft to pearl the mainsail in a blow
And when the yards broke off
They said that I got out of the boat
I'd kill
But I'm living still
I was a dam building
Across a river deep and wide
Where steel and water didn't collide
A place called Boulder on the wild Colorado
I slipped and fell into the wet concrete below
They buried me in that great tomb that knows no sound
But I am still around
I'll always be around
And around and around and around and around
I'll fly a starship
Across the universe
I'll find a place to rest my spirit if I can.
Perhaps I may become a highwayman again.
Or I may simply be a single drop of rain.
But I will remain.
And I'll be back again and again and again and again and again and again.
You can't count on God for Jack.
He pretty much told me so himself.
They call you Lady Luck.
But there is room for doubt.
At times you have a very unladylike way of running out.
You're on a date with me.
The pickings have been lush.
And yet before this evening is over you might give me the brush.
You might forget your manners.
You might refuse to stay.
And so the best that I can do.
Is pray.
Luck be a Lady Tonight.
Luck – if you've ever been a Lady to begin with.
Luck – let a gentleman see…
How nice a dame you can be.
I know the way you treated other guys you've been with.
Let luck be a lady with me
A lady doesn't leave her escort
It isn't fair, it isn't nice
A lady doesn't wander all over the room
And blow on some other guy's dice
So let's keep the party polite
Never get out of my sight
Stick with me, baby
I'm the fella you came in with
Let luck be a lady
Luck be a lady
Luck be a lady tonight
Luck, if you've ever been a lady to begin with
Luck, let a gentleman see
How nice a dame you can be
I know the way you've treated other guys who've been with
Luck be a lady with me
A lady wouldn't flirt with strangers
She'd have a heart, she'd have a soul
A lady wouldn't make little snake eyes at me
When I've spent my life on this floor
So let's keep the party polite
Never get out of my sight
Stick with me, baby
I'm the fella you came in with
Let luck be a lady
Luck be a lady
Roll the dice
Rub it up, rub it up, rub it up, rub it up
Right, ha!
Robert Alda and the Guys
From Guys and Dolls
The 1950s
Robert Alda and the Guys
From Guys and Dolls
The 1950s
About the Year
Well, it's really great to have you on the show tonight, Bob.
The Great Groovy Neptune, friends from his new album, Turpentine Anima.
And you can get more about The Great Groovy Neptune from www.neptune.itgo.
Itgo.com. That's itgo.com.
www.neptune.itgo.com.
More from them coming up.
And now, Occupant, friends.
Occupant is really Onan Canobite, the great subgenius, and his friend Mitch.
And this song coming up is an old, it's actually a song by Devo, which you won't recognize unless you're a real spaz like me.
Occupant.
We'll be right back.
Theodore!
The great little Theodore!
And friends,
there is new old little
Theodore available.
A new old album,
actually an old album we've done on
CD called Beneath
the Uber Putts
by little Theodore
at Yahoo.com
I should spell Theodore
spelled F as in
Frank. Y-O-D
O-R
little Theodore
at, here's another address
Raleigh
Street
R-A-L-E-I-G-H
3277 Raleigh Street
Denver, Colorado
or
little Theodore at Yahoo.com
And now, friends,
well, you're hearing in the background the
Amino Acids who played at our
Akron Revival.
You can hear more of them at
TheAminoAcids.com
That's www.
And now, friends, a song with
for some reason deep personal meaning
to me. I'm not sure why.
The King, Elvis.
I won't get any older now the angels wanna wear my red shoes
Oh, I was watching while you're dancing away
Our love got fractured in an echo and sway
How come everybody wants to be your friend?
You know that it still hurts me just to say it
Oh, I know she's disgusted
Oh, why's that?
Cause she's feeling so abused
Oh, that's too bad
She gets tired of the lust
Oh, I'm so sad
But it's so hard to refuse
Can you say that I'm too old when the angels have stolen my red shoes?
Oh, I said I'm so happy I could die
She said, drop dead, then left with another guy
But that's what you get if you go chasing out the vengeance
Ever since you got me
The punch that does is defend my sentence
Oh, I used to be disgusted
When I tried to be amused
Since the winter got rusted
You know the angels wanna wear my red shoes
But when they told me about the sign of the bargain
That's when I knew that I could not refuse
And I won't get any older now the angels wanna wear my red shoes
I won't get any older now the angels wanna wear my red shoes
Red shoes, the angels wanna wear my red shoes
Red shoes, the angels want to wear my red shoes.
I'm walking in a wonder wonderland
All I got was saying
There's a nine pound hammer beating in my skull
Laying down tracks on the road to hell
Yeah!
Thank you.
The mathematics of the equation just don't add up.
It's a paradoxical situation.
And while my cock is in elation, my soul is in purgatory.
And praying to the demon god at Radio Shack to give me peace and make the neighbor's dog stop telling me to murder the innocents in the cracks of the sidewalks in New York City.
The Great Groovy Neptune, dear friends.
www.neptune.com
www.itgo.com
A new CD from the Great Groovy Neptune called Turpentine Enema.
Proof that there's still hope in Texas.
And friends, stay tuned for yet another killer remix of a classic tune by Dr. Onan's Wotan Band.
Followed by a new, a traditional Celtic song about computer online affairs by Sister Mora.
Melodious.
A chop spin out.
Onan's Wotan Band.
Onan.
When you use your mutant powers.
Think abob
Onan.
When your blood is low and sugar.
When you're picking up a b novels.
When You shoot him with a Lự.
Think abob
Onan.
When you're outside exercising, think about
When you're using sex devices, think about
When you're walking through the woods
When you make out with the girls
When you beat up two little hoods, think about
Think it's bad, think it's bad, think it's bad, think it's bad
Here it comes
He's coming, bud
Go to come
Go to come and take your slack away
He's back
When you see a flock of birds, think about
When you just run out of words, think about
When a ring falls from your collar
When you hear a given holler
When you write checks for one dollar, think about
When you write to the subgenius, think about
B.O. Box 1403-06, think about
When you cast your mojo hexes
When you ride through Dallas, Texas
When you're out of the woods
Come on, come on, let's just think about
The four of us, think about
Outro
Here it comes
Big Mac
Slack
He's coming to take your slack away
He'll take it too
That Big Mac Bob
Heaven in the sky
That's right
Just send us your
One dollar
You get a lot more for your money
Heck one dollar
You get Bob
Think about
Yeah think about
Bob
Yeah he makes us
Think about
Everybody thinks about Bob
Everybody wants to think about
Yeah
We're thinking
About Bob
We're thinking about Bob
Yeah we're thinking
About Bob
Everybody thinks about Bob
I'm Bob
No I'm Bob
Listen here, Malachi.
Time for a religious donation.
Hand over your wallet.
But Lord, we are a poor and simple folk.
Poor?
Oh, crap.
Well, some maids like to tend the fields.
Others will tend their children.
Some will buy a DSL to find a man who's willing.
There's something about the online world that makes me want to care.
And I will go with flags unfurled to meet my Charlie there.
Well, some will wear their sexy things and turn the lights down low.
Some will grab a brew or two and drink them as they go.
But me, I'm not the kind of girl to go for a motor party.
But you won't, or if you will, I'm going online for Charlie.
Well, some will fly to Cameroon to quench their loving flame.
Me, I'll sit inside my room and summon up your name.
So get your fingers ready, dear.
And light a candle.
Two.
And if I'm old, you may not hear what I'm coming online for you.
He sends me streams of thrilling thought.
He opens up my gate.
He touches me where he should not.
And I can hardly wait.
Some like fear the strains of heart.
Others the beat of a party.
You reckon, oh.
But I don't care.
Just let me start.
Going online for Charlie.
Charlie.
That was Victoria Ganger and Revelry.
Also known as Sister Melodious Chops
with a song about online love affairs via the internet.
From ancient Ireland.
their website with samples is www.revelrychicks.com
from a new album called Highly Irreverent
my dear consor, the princess to which I am consor
Princess Wee Ardo
is one of the two backup babes singing in Revelry
and friends, I'm bird-dogging that stuff
I am bird-dogging that Princess Wee
you know, cause there's some dirty dogs out there, my friends
there are some, my male, my buddies, my man friends
if you got it, bird-dog it
cause there's some dogs out there
here's Johnny Cash
Wanted man in California
Wanted man in Buffalo
Wanted man in Kansas City
Wanted man in Ohio
Wanted man in Mississippi
Wanted man in Oceania
Wherever you might look tonight
you might see this wanted man
I might be in Colorado
or Georgia by the sea
Working for some man who may not know who I might be
And if you ever see me come back
I'll be coming
And if you know who I am
Don't you breathe it to nobody
Cause you know I'm on the lam
Wanted man by Lucy Watson
Wanted man by Jeannie Brown
Wanted man by Nellie Johnson
Wanted man in this next town
Well, I've had all that I've wanted
Of a lot of things I've had
And a lot more than I needed
Of some things that turned out bad
I got sidetracked in El Paso
Stopped to get myself a map
Went the wrong way in the Juarez
With Juanita on my lap
Then I went to sleep in Shreveport
Woke up in Abilene
Wondering why I'm wanted
I'm a man in California
Some town headway between
Wanted man in Albuquerque
Wanted man in Syracuse
Wanted man in Tallahassee
Wanted man in Baton Rouge
There's somebody set to grab me
Anywhere that I might be
And wherever you might look tonight
You might get a glimpse of me
Wanted man in California
Wanted man in Buffalo
Wanted man in Kansas City
Wanted man in Ohio
Wanted man in Mississippi
Wanted man in Old Cheyenne
Wherever you might look tonight
You might see this wanted man
And worse awaits you
At the Church of the Subgenius
Got that pencil ready for an address?
That's www.subgenius.com
Or our new Austin Post Office Box
Box 204-206
In lovely Austin, Texas
And we'll see you next time
Again, that's Box 204-206
Austin, Texas
The next hour of Slack, friends
Next week will be
The Devo Special
Every year after the devotional
We cover the great devos
And so we shall this time again
With the greatest
Devo special
And the best covers ever
Ever, ever
Praise Bob
Heaven and hell
Yes
I tried to get a
Right, right, right
And big brain
Heads are
That's fascinating
No, no
And
That's
Jesus Christ
Hmm
And
Jack
Not even the
I've had strength
Because I
Uh
Mm hmm
Jesus Christ
Thank you
Christ
Mm
Very
Well, that was fun
That was a
capt
Haha
Sure right
Right
Well, that was fun
Now for Eons of Loneliness.
Huh?