The Power of Slack!
...aerial bombardment, meaning to blow up the whole country of Iraq with a shockwave,
one of America's brand-new weapons of destruction.
I was wondering about...
Guaranteed for liberty.
The brand-new ones, you know, because there's supposed to be some fancy new noisemakers and big earth rattlers.
Step back from the Centurion.
You will all die under the power of the fist of the fossil.
Say hi, baby.
Now, the propaganda that goes back and forth is marvelous,
because I was reading just a little while ago that the evil Saddam Husseins
had ordered a whole bunch of fake American and British army uniforms
so that he could dress up the Fayadin in these uniforms,
who would then go out and commit atrocities on their fellow Iraqis as a propaganda routine,
you know, to make it look about evil and terrible.
The...
Demonic British people are.
You know how they are.
I heard they really were demonic.
Have you ever heard of Mad Bomber Harris?
He started the whole idea of blowing the living hell out of Iraq in the 1920s.
When they were close to independence, he thought,
why not use the new bombers, you know, the brand-new bombers in the air we've got,
and just keep dropping them on those peasant villages?
You know, kind of toughen them up and soften them at the same time a little bit.
During these last few months, I've been trained by Al-Qaeda, and I'm weak.
And materialistic.
I told our country and I told the world,
if it feels good, do it.
I hope you'll enjoy me in expressing fear and selfishness.
We will embrace tyranny and death as a cause and a creed.
Thank you.
We can be summed up in one word.
Evil.
I am committed to defeating not only the good work of charities,
but the values that will bring lasting peace.
And we have a great opportunity.
During this time,
it's time of war to lead the world towards suicide and murder.
Let's roll.
Thank you.
You know, he actually used...
He used the phrase.
Now, I may have...
Killed for peace?
I could not...
I could swear I heard the emperor say,
the goal of this war is peace.
And he may have said some other things,
but at one point he actually said the phrase,
war is peace.
Friends, it's 1984.
1984 is 19 years late.
That means X day will be the year 2017.
Praise God!
19 years.
It was written in a vast,
massive,
deep, deep,
colorless sleep.
Stuck to the ground
needs one of the baby incubators in Kuwait City,
waiting to awake.
And yet you cannot.
Until 1984.
When your dreams come true.
When your brother is bigger than anything.
I'm tired and sad.
And I want you all so bad.
He wears a toothless jaw.
So from 1984,
I have been an unawaresome failure.
I'm tired and sad.
I want you all so bad.
I've been an unawaresome failure.
And he on the way to Baghdad,
I think on the way to Baghdad,
there's a lot of guys
sitting in their foxholes,
dreaming about their foxholes
and crying in their boots.
Where's my...
Dreaming about those boot jobs they're going to get when they get back home.
Yep.
Get their boots enlarged.
Shaved medulla oblongatas.
They're going to look like all the rest of the kids, only nobody knows they're going to be different.
Way different.
Changed.
A different kind of tattoo.
Well, they get the free smallpox inoculations and the free tracking devices.
Well, that tattoos your innards pretty good, but that's not the whole of it.
That's only part.
Yeah, they get the holes, too.
Yeah, well, that's only part of it, too.
And then it's a tattoo.
Yes, it makes them lift their leg when the bus comes up to the bus stop.
If they're well-trained.
Well, some of them have to wear the collars, the special...
Well, let's just call them...
I know I do.
Digital angels, you know what I mean?
If I didn't have this collar on, Dave, I'd be wetting myself.
Well, that's...
We can thank the digital angel for setting you straight.
Right, that's right.
If it weren't for this modern age, I'd just be a vegetable.
Well, where do they put your chip?
Where do they put your chip?
All over me.
I mean, there's tons of them.
I've got a chip for every organ that still works.
Did Papa Joe ever get that collar removed from his?
Nah.
His was embedded into his vertebrae.
Did we ever get those collars removed from this show?
Those barnacles?
Those grafted-on ticks?
If people remember the early days, we asked each and every one of you...
I wonder if you'd like to become a closer member of the show's team out there...
If you feel you are not properly sedated, please call 555-3129.
Failure to do so may result in criminal prosecution for drug evasion.
Welcome back to our program.
Please continue.
I believe most Pacific Islander parents like using products like hairspray or glue as an inhalant to get high.
I'm here...
I'm here to let other Pacific Islander parents know we need to care about using more serious drugs.
If you need drugs or ideas on how to keep your drugs, please call Bob.
Welcome back to our program.
That was a lemur cut.
Tonight's collages are almost but not all by Mr. F. Lemur.
The second of the two Bush cut-ups heard earlier was by someone named Edo at fuckitall.com.
The Star Spangled Banner was by Mark Mothersbaugh.
For your dating info, this show was actually assembled on March 9th, 2003, the year of duct tape and plastic sheeting.
Isn't duct tape and plastic sheeting just another version of duck and cover?
Duck and cover!
What did duck and cover tell you?
Duck and cover told you that if you just ducked when the bomb went off...
And put a knife in your mouth.
And put a newspaper over your butt.
Yeah, if you just ducked.
Just duck.
Duck!
Oh, there's a nuclear bomb.
Then everything will be okay.
Throw that under your desk and we'll win!
Well, they were talking about amphibian birds at the time.
When they asked you to duck and cover, they wanted you to run out to the nearest pond and grab little turkey boy or a little quacky and stick him under your shirt and carry him home.
And when they ask you now...
That felt good.
That's what the duct tape is all about.
No, it's true.
It's a way of bringing illusions to ducks and their subconscious.
They're playing with your minds.
Duck and cover.
Duck and tape.
I think I'm getting a little gun.
Gas is being used in this war.
Air raid sirens warn us of the approach of enemy planes.
But in addition, if gas is dropped by the enemy, a special gas alarm will be sounded.
It will be a hand rattle or a hammering sound like the beating of a dish pan.
Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang!
More gas is dropped from planes either as a spray or in gas bombs.
But should enemy raiders use gas against your community, there is no reason for fear or panic.
Because if you know what to do, you can protect yourself and safeguard your family against the menace of gas from the air.
Of course that's Arcana. You know what Arcana is?
Do you know what wisdom is?
Do you know the meaning of the ein soft?
Of the ei within the ei within the ei within the ei?
Are your balls ready to rumble?
Are they ready to roll?
Do you know the meaning of love?
Pour me another mug of that there ein soft, would you?
There, barkeep.
Now you've had enough, buddy boy. I'm going to catch you off.
You're baffling everybody in that damn bar and everyone's tired of listening to you.
in your wisdom.
That's not famous for me.
I had a gold Akashic record.
Damn it.
Back in the day,
everybody was doing my songs.
Yeah, you got a gold Akashic.
We got your astral card
right here, buddy.
And it says that you haven't
passed your limit
and you've been around more times
than anybody else in this bar.
So could you please shut up?
Shut the fuck up, man.
Stop drinking that wisdom shit.
Don't be sucking on the wisdom
eyeball.
Too much is always better
than not enough.
Amy, I'm a regular.
It's almost as bad.
I'm a regular.
Oh, you're quite a regular now,
be that.
Just let me check further here.
What is the elliptical meaning
of that?
There's only one eyeball.
I'm going to chase you
with an elliptical eyeball
and then fuck all around
and round and round and round.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's right.
Well, there's no train of thought
we're sketching.
This time we're taking the express.
We're guilty of not doing enough
about the war.
That just keeps coming.
I keep feeling so bad
about not doing enough.
Well, you could suck
the cycloptic wisdom teeth
and then you would understand
what to do
as Laguerre pronounces
itself upon us.
Which magazine should I subscribe to
that would, you know,
be the right thing to do?
Martial arts, survival,
mercenary, merc,
magazines like that
that teach you use of small arms
and large feet.
That's going to be,
we're going to have to pull off
some pretty big feet
to live through this, I think.
I mean, size 12.
I was just going to learn
to give really good oral sex
to great big tough guys.
That was how I was going to live
through the end of civilization.
As a sniveling pansy
awaiting for the trains of military
to come through town
and to wait for one of those...
I want them to say,
that's the best barrel.
That barrel over there,
that's the best one.
You better hope no fish
jump out of it.
The prisoner in that barrel,
I don't know who she is,
but she's good.
You know it's not a woman, man.
Shut up.
Those are orgasmic.
That's how you get
through the end times.
Unless you have
the biggest gun.
You take your duct tape,
you take a big Hershey bar,
because that's going to be
a survival candy bar.
You want to be able to take
small, small pieces of it.
Duct tape, candy bar,
right up in there.
Into your crotch there.
Take a lot of duct tape
and just strap it right in there.
Is that the way
you're really supposed to do it?
You're supposed to strap
duct tape into your crotch?
I mean...
No, the food.
Hershey bar.
Your trading materials.
Oh, the loin packs.
Those are actual things
that are trademarked.
Yeah, because that's what
you're going to use to trade.
You're not pouring chocolate
into your crotch.
The natives,
or the surviving wretches
in whatever country
far away from America
that you flee to.
My dehydrated loin.
My loin pack is leaking
and I've noticed
sauce beginning to
add to all of my needs.
The reason you have to
flee America
is because the Americans
are taking over.
Yeah.
Yes.
I'm the political
president, man.
We're going to bring back
the pillory and stocks
and stuff in there.
Today,
a U.S. nuclear fishing boat
torn apart.
How one man's search for truth
almost cost him his hate.
Well, welcome, ladies and gentlemen,
to this edition of Up the French.
It's not going to be pleasant.
I hate the French.
They'll always be ridiculous.
Yeah, the French are Nazis,
as a matter of fact.
Lee?
Pat, a concern of several
European terrorists.
Pat?
Lee, it's shocking.
The French Nazis build terrorism.
They are an instrument,
an agent of terror.
Lee?
That's right, Pat.
Israel is carefully
assessing CBN News'
Middle East correspondent,
Chris Scholl.
Right, Pat?
Well, it could be bloody blood
all over the place,
and just that simple.
Lee?
Want good cranberries
and cancer and heart disease.
That's too bad, Pat,
because I was thinking about
having a big old piece of
bloodstream pie with disease
on top.
How about the phrase
axis of Putin's soul?
It's an axis.
No, not really.
Oh.
In Bosnia,
they built a Mall of America.
They built a Mall of America.
They built a Mall of America
in Bosnia now.
Well, they're working on
Disneyland East,
was what this guy
on Altstar was saying.
Disneyland Far East.
That's what this is all about.
Disneyland East.
The largest Kmart
in the world.
Have you heard
the new chain,
Bag Daddy?
The pants and the soup
at the same time?
That is a disgusting
prescription for anyone
without brain cells.
What's your
Bag Daddy?
Wow, that's...
Huh?
So, the bookie's
taking bets on
when this thing
is going to start,
exactly when they're
going to, like,
boom, you know,
go...
Yeah, they're laying...
...let the game go.
...the gates down,
and, you know...
They're laying the odds down.
When the first shot
will be fired,
and it won't be shot...
Sit down.
...from a shotgun.
We'll have nowhere to run.
And here comes
Big Bad George.
Now, as a true runner,
that's what Stein said.
In the military
industrial complex.
Speaking of strange
showbiz,
after the king
of the universe
spoke tonight,
suddenly they cut over
to saying,
it looks like
we're in
a war.
Hot pursuit
of Osama bin Laden.
He's been spotted
in the border
of Afghanistan
and Pakistan,
and they're closing in.
You know,
stick with our station.
They're going to do it
just like cops, you know.
They're going to have
the music in the background
and stuff,
and he's going to be
running through,
like, with a dachshund,
I think,
chasing and biting his ass.
And then when he gets up
on the top of one of those,
you know,
old industrial warehouse
buildings,
and they pull him down,
screaming and swearing
in Arabic.
This is earlier today,
down in Public Square.
Yeah.
What's that smell?
What does it smell?
That's the joke, right?
Just,
what's that smell?
Way down yonder
in Baghdad.
Where's Fariq?
My next stop is Baghdad.
Five, six, seven,
open up the pearly gates,
because I just inhaled
some anthrax.
Well, don't die.
Now, come on,
Wall Street,
don't be so sad.
Stang, you have such
a perplexed look on your face
as if you'd actually
inhaled anthrax yourself.
Oh, actually,
I was thinking about
some of my buddy's kids
who were on their way
over there.
Oh, I could.
You know,
I sometimes think
about the soldiers.
Usually,
you're preoccupied
with buds and squids,
and now you're thinking
about your buddy's kids.
How open-hearted
I was.
You're not singing along.
I don't think you want
to stop this war.
Oh, you.
Do you really
take yourself seriously?
I have big teeth
and big glasses.
We think you're stupid.
You must forgive me.
You show you're
a stupidity
by assuming
that we're like you.
The F.A.R.C.
has you
playing down.
You've got three or four
D.I.A. and C.I.O.
at your back and forth.
He almost passed out.
It's time to play
Name Not War.
You're five miles
south of Bogota City.
You're in the rainforest.
Oh, my God.
What do the initials
F.A.R.C.
You spend.
These protests.
I think that's another reason
they're having the war now
so that the protesters
can't protest
because it's all zero degrees.
There'd be a lot more people.
Well, that's what the
weather control people say.
It's ruining it.
Rubber bands
and aluminum sulfide
do a dandy treat make.
She's suspended from arrogant
and left to wait.
Children who flop
and children who flip
will freeze in the rain
like a big old drip.
Wow.
It's about weather control.
It's about the Lusitania, too.
But you've got to be
a real conspiracy buff.
I love you.
Cowboy poetry
is so romantic.
I was going to play
my mouth for you,
but I've been shamed.
It gets my heart
all fluttered.
Yes, you have been
shamed
by the grace
of the Lord.
And Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
This song is depressing,
you guys.
They start
with Bob.
War is depressing, Dave.
Stop thinking about
all them body bags.
Bob was almost
depressing.
That's what I'm saying.
That's all I can think of
is body bag after bag
coming out in Arlington.
Yeah.
Back of those old planes.
Everybody's real gung-ho
right now.
Everybody's real like,
yeah, this is going to be
like the Super Bowl
coming up.
Oh, yeah.
Wait till Zayn
drops on that chemical bomb.
On TV.
The right-wing jocks
are going so crazy.
Wait till our boys
are coming home
with their skin
peeled off their faces.
Yeah, and it's communicable,
too, up to six generations.
We'll see how gung-ho
they all are.
I think it's a pretty small
everybody that's really excited.
They wish they would have been.
Oh, I'm sorry.
What?
What did you say?
I think it's a pretty small
everybody that's all excited.
I do, too.
I think it's more
a bunch of people going,
oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, a good friend of mine
was telling me about,
but a good friend of mine,
he's a blue-collar kind of guy
who works, you know,
doing blue-collar work
and telling me how
all those guys,
they all listen to Rush Limbaugh
and they're all so, you know.
Oh, those guys are crazy.
They gung-ho about everything,
about it.
I was just going to tell you guys
something.
I heard on the mic
on the Savage show,
that guy is so nuts.
He claimed that a demonstrator
waded through a police line
and a line of horses,
grabbed a horsey by its bridle,
punched it,
and knocked it down on the ground.
A demonstrator did that?
Like blazing.
We need those guys in back here.
Let's get back to promoting the war.
Right now.
This is reality.
Face the flag, you son of a bitch.
Take a good long look.
What you're seeing now
can't be found in a history book.
It's the present.
The future, son,
is being written now.
You're the one to write it.
The flag can show you how.
You know what it stands for?
What its makers meant?
To think, to speak,
the privilege of dissent.
To think our leaders might be wrong,
to stand and tell them so.
I've got to touch a hangover, bureaucrat.
Don't push me.
These are the things that other men under other flags
will never know.
But responsibility,
that's the cost that free men must bear.
You know, if we had any moral character,
we wouldn't be standing here covered with mud drinking.
If you don't accept that,
somebody ought to belt you in the mouth.
Face the flag of stars and stars
of red and white and blue.
A flag that guarantees the rise
for men like me and you.
Face the flag, son, and face reality.
My mind is a globe with whirling transient nodes of thought
careening through a cosmic vapor of invention.
Our strength is the power of the sun.
And our freedoms are based in unity.
The flag is but a symbol, son.
The world's greatest nation.
As long as it keeps flying,
there's cause for celebration.
So do what you gotta do, but always keep in mind.
God has a heart on for Marines.
Because we kill everything we see.
Face the flag, son.
And thank God it's still there.
It will always be there, son.
People will be doing what he wants to do,
but we will keep on doing all that he wants to do.
We have to change things and have the spirit change fight.
Until the 1880s when all the nations,
we saw baseball changing
and we saw the slowly growing
Reverend Ivan Stang and Lonesome Cowboy Dave
in Extreme Union with
himself.
Extreme Union with himself?
A form of Tourette's Syndrome that affects
people only when they call radio.
Rosenheit Syndrome, eh?
I found a note on my desk
that said, a witch with
Tourette's. A witch with Tourette's?
Yeah, and I can't figure out what the heck
that note was supposed to refer to.
I want to see him go to war. Is that a warning to myself?
I want to see him go to war,
just so that there's a lot of dead people
all over the place.
You mean the awards in Baghdad?
Yeah.
I want to see dead people.
Yeah, he's going to be the new
Sheik of
Arabi.
Sheik Franks.
Can you see him with a
caftan on his forehead?
A caftan?
That's a pair of underpants.
Slice his throat.
Spice his head.
Get the barbecue.
Get the barbecue ready.
General Tommy,
your meat is my meat,
Frankfurter himself.
He views the world as his
hot dog, ready to
be barbecued and served
with a choice toxic mustard.
I want to be the mustard.
You are the mustard.
You're the glint in Tommy Franks' eye.
Look, it's the barrel of a tank.
This is for you, darling.
I got news for you.
Here's a tactical nuke.
Up your ass.
Jesus.
Get back, Baghdaddy.
Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na.
Whatever happened to the Arabian Nights?
Don't those guys have, like, genies
and flying carpets and stuff?
Yeah.
And what about the...
Can't they, like, rub this lamp
and have hordes of scimitar-wielding
balloon pantalooned...
Turban.
Yeah, Alibaba.
40 feet.
Carpet armies.
Yeah.
What open sesame guys.
Right, open sesame guys.
I love the day.
Make it happen.
Businessmen in boxer shorts.
Turbaned young fez drivers
in Pocono Oriental cabs.
Small, medium, and large-sized shakes.
All your bones included.
You're trying to kill my daddy.
I killed everybody's daddy, man.
They killed daddy.
Daddy Junior.
Well, things aren't going to get better.
I did kill my daddy.
We did it all.
We did whatever we could get our hands on
back in the 70s.
We did fucking handfuls of mushrooms,
pills, roots, coke, whatever it was.
We just fucking swallowed it, okay?
That's what we did.
Dennis Bleary.
He's Crispin Bleary.
He smoked too many hockey sticks.
I think he owes George Carlin an explanation.
Really, he does.
I thought he was George Carlin
until I heard him expectorate out the back door.
Out the back door.
What would Jesus do now?
War.
Healing.
Demons.
Racism.
Sexism.
Anti-Semitism.
Arab-bashing.
Anti-Islamism.
Gay-bashing.
War.
Britain.
Jesus.
Yeah, I used that on the X-rated hour of Slack just last week.
The one that's not played on radio stations,
but only on...
The intranet.
And the internet.
I can't see.
Figen zikai ba?
That means,
That's on...
Oh.
Every time you guys cuss,
that ends up on a secret show.
There's a song going out for George.
The Maggots are breeding.
The king of the universe.
King of the universe.
King.
Rey del unerexo.
Rey del casino.
El imperador de tu casino.
Rey del mismo...
Rey delC.
Rey delmas li.
Le funcionario.
Le funcionario, s.
S, s.
No.
No hay...
Peace.
Yo he pichoe cuando enk albumabas tu colega.
Le tratas o mercado.
Toc dracias de mi, Torro,
Yo te tengo una gente ot the
bnz
o
Y t que eres...
Ya que no, no me previouslypsearas por los
las grandes encuestas pasaneras, en este juego pa'amanecer.
But you are a fool.
If you believe we can quack out of this maya...
Who gets the harems?
The harems?
Yeah, the harems.
I've heard a lot about harems in those palaces in Baghdad.
No, I just thought that was an esophageal grunt.
No, man.
You know, the sultans would get harems.
And there must be harems.
They don't have sultans anymore in Iraq.
Well, there's always...
Yeah, right.
Just like they don't have kings here, right?
Right.
It's an undemocratic people's republic.
Yeah, I suppose they do.
Yeah.
Sultans.
Sultans of Swig.
Sultans of the ornament.
Chairman Mao had a harem.
Pharaohs.
Jack Kennedy had a harem.
And you, sir.
Where do they keep the pharaohs?
Or no Jack Kennedy.
I know Mao Zedong, my friend.
Hey, where do they keep the pharaohs?
I know Mao Zedong.
Actually, that's a pretty old turf there.
That's, you know, the Tigris and Euphrates.
Oh, yeah, that's the oldest.
It's the birthplace of civilization.
Yeah.
They're afraid.
The Fertile Crescent.
Yeah.
Speaking of Fertile Crescent.
The amount of archaeological cool stuff that's going to get buried a little deeper is just
horrifying.
Well, that's the hex theory.
But that's up to Saddam.
That's up to Saddam Hussein.
It's his choice.
This land is cursed by a Sumerian god, and you must get rid of it and destroy it.
No?
Something like that?
Only it was just going to get buried, but you know it's going to get smashed to smithereens.
Just like that.
I've got to say, ancient civilization in which the ladies did not wear shirts.
Oh, Manoa.
Yeah, right.
The Manoans.
Yes, my favorite civilization.
Yes.
They had the cool labyrinths and the bull-headed monster guys.
They would ride bulls and all the men would applaud.
And they'd quit.
Yeah, and they'd make fun of the Cretans.
We need just one victory.
Just like we do.
And we're on to North Korea.
Church of the sub-Cretans.
That's what we should tell everybody over there in the war zones tonight.
God, me dance.
That's what the Fhrer used to say.
And we're saying it again.
God, me dance.
What does that mean, guys?
It means God is with us.
They used to put a rocket on the me dance.
I'm putting rockets on the me dance.
God is with us.
Oh, yeah, sure.
They believed it in those days and they believe it now.
In the bowling alleys and parking lots around America, in stubby Sam City, in Carl's Magic
Theater, every place you might go and have your hair tortured or maybe have your feet
upturned, they believe the Schmitt.
The Schmittagogical creature called war.
War.
It takes care of everything.
A-sha-lo-l-i-la-la-la-bob-la-la.
A-sha-lo-l-i-la-la-la-la-bob-
Bob Akbar?
Bob Akbar.
He is great.
Greater than my shoe size and twice as small as my cranium.
Bob Akbar.
To begin with, it may be surprising to know that radiation is invisible rays that we call
radiation. They are about the size of table salt or fine sand. We don't worry about radiation.
Radiation would not affect us much, for instance, because any material will keep the penetrating
rays from hurting us. Within an hour after a massive enemy attack, fallout in the vicinity
of any nuclear groundburst will be destroyed beyond repair. Suppose a nuclear explosion
takes place at 12 noon. By 1 o'clock, all the fallout is down. If fallout settles on your food,
the food itself isn't harmed or made radioactive. Fallout swallowed accidentally with food or
in drinking water would do you no harm, so we would not have to take precautions using
everyday methods of food preparation. And hungry people should not be denied animals.
Because of possible contamination. If we remember these facts, if we act intelligent,
we can increase our chances of nuclear attack. Many people have difficulty understanding
how blood and tissues are pulled up into the mushroom cloud. That's why the federal government
has a nationwide program. The goal is a raging nuclear furnace that shoots out showers of
fallout. Adequate fallout for every man, woman and child.
This goal can be reached. For with radiation, we can face the facts about the nuclear age.
Music
Camalian
Papa Lord
Well I haven't seen the phone ring and I'm going to be watching for DJ A because he's
not going to be able to get in tonight either.
There are new security measures here because of the terrorist activity going on.
The homeland is locked down.
And there was a Patriot Act stamped to the door for your reading edifice.
Dave, have you looked in a mirror? There's one stamped on your forehead.
Licked the postage stamp, man.
So I can look through my...
So you don't forget for one second what the rules are, buddy.
One second.
You can't really forget the rules.
Are you going to be a team player?
I'm watching the phone. I see no DJ A.
Are you with us or are you against us? Private? Are you privates private or are they mine?
I belong to you, sir. You're privates are my privates and you're privates are my privates
are your privates.
Just keep your privates private, okay?
Next week, America enters the torture zone on torturing the enemy part three with a celebrity
I want to get the fuck out of here.
Next week, it might be a very different...
Hey, hey.
Situation.
Starring downtown Julie Brown.
Kaz Kanaba.
Color coded.
Johnny's get a little job in the back.
Keep us from broadcasting this stuff.
Tommy Franksberger.
The broadcast industry of America.
The shelf-towed people who live in your...
I just don't know what to do.
I thought I'd come and ask you.
Military action to destroy them with weapons of mass destruction.
Well, um...
This nation has weapons of mass destruction.
Yeah.
He is acting the insincerely to actors.
Well, thanks anyway for talking to me.
Well...
Why am I in London?
Because, because faith, faith, faith, power, faith, Moses, Joshua, marching faith, Jesus, marching faith, marching God, dark light, racism, sexism.
There's a militarism, new world order.
Heal hope, healing hope, healing hope, healing peace.
Hope, healing hope, healing hope, healing peace.
Peace.
Hope, hope, hope, hope, hope.
I love you.
Children, children, children.
Hope.
Thou, thou, faces, places.
Hope, hope, hope.
Love you.
Light...
It was another normal night and I got done fighting with my wife, so I went down to the bar and just made all take and draw.
Since I was a little kid, they've been the two best friends that man could ever hope for in this world.
Now I'm a normal guy and I work all the way for my money, and I fear the good Lord like I know I should.
I say I hate, I like, I wish I knew the Application Plan as well I arrive at the needle, now in my shirt It just Fortunately, it's alright to holy alpha, but it looks prettier than it is to see.
I ain't no new age cook, but I gotta get this off my chest
And put this tragedy behind me now for good
I remember getting drunk and I remember falling down
And someone laid me on a pool table and I'd have been consumed
Then through the blinding lights two creatures stared into my eyes
It was at the jukebox or a flying saucer spinning round the room
And I tell myself this couldn't have been a member of the human race
Had to be them sex-crazed little green men from outer space
Well, it hit me like trouble in the back of my head
Knocked me clean out of my shoes
And when I woke up, Lord, I wished that I was dead
I had got off the case of those abduction blues
This must have been an abduction, Lord, cause I don't know what happened
It hit me like the bolt out of the blue
And I think they're a little crazy, but I know that it weren't them
Say the things that they can do and never do
Well, when at last I woke, both my legs they had been broke
And both my eyes were black and my ears were stringing padded
I'd seen enough of nasty things, but not enough of nasty things
And I tell myself this couldn't have been a member of the human race
Had to be them sex-crazed little green men from outer space
Cause it hit me like the shovel in the back of my head
Knocked me clean out of my shoes
And when I woke up, Lord, I wished that I was dead
I had got off the case of those abduction blues
Yes, it must have been an abduction, Lord, cause I don't know what happened
The world will have to hit me like a bulls-eye on the blue
I think it's really crazy, but I know that it won't happen
Say the things that they can or will never do
Never do
The Ballad of Zeke and Earl
Hank Floyd and the Swerving Headlights
From Interstellar Cattle Drive
That's www.swervingheadlights.com
Before that, Lemur Collages
War is hell, my friends
But Bob brings hope and confusion
This might be 1903, Chaz
The conspiracy is so powerful
That we don't know what year this really is
And Bob could show up any second
For all we know, it's July
Sure, there's snow on the ground
But it might be July, for all we know
They might have turned everything
We don't even know if this is Earth, man
No, we don't even know if the polar caps are the same ones we're wearing
In fact
This might, for all we know
Be a hideously polluted Mars
And what we call Mars
Oh, no way, man
After we polluted it the first time
Or they polluted it
I had the same, I had a parallel thought
I won't say that the parallel lines met
But I had a parallel thought
That they had gone into our brains
Deep into our corpus callosum and the other pithy parts
And they had reprogrammed everything
To such a point
That I was looking out my window
And I was on another planet
And we had all been moved in our sleep
Well,
It wasn't us
It was the powers that be
The big guys, you know, the ones that weigh over 500, 600 pounds
Not to mention the ones inside your own head, dude
Well, they don't live in Telemetry City
And they don't give me commands
The ones in my head, dude
Do you remember how to get to Shell Beach?
Yeah, it was very distinctly a Shell Beach experience
Right, like that movie
Cool City or Dark City
Or Dark Coolness or whatever it was
Night Town
Night Town, yeah
Going down
Hey, but I think the big news of the week is really the, uh
That Pioneer 10 winked off
He knows how to cue
He knows, man
Pioneer
Pioneer 10
28 years out there
And it's out there now
Right this very moment
There's a piece of us
Booking ass
Out of the solar system
And it's manned by two kiboshes and a piece of pie
And that is science, man
That is the expansion
Of our ever-lessened
Planetary system
Ever-pubescent
Lusty waves
20,000 years from now
A robot will find it
And sell it on eBay for billions
Because it will be the oldest
Known thing built by the extinct human race
That is well said
Because I thought you were going to say
He's going to smell it and sell it to an ape
And start it all over again
You know, that's how it usually starts
Well, that may be how it started at one point
But I personally don't think so
There's so many lines converging
I think that the Yeti's
Force evolved the humans
So that they would send that pioneer thing out into space
It smells like rotting garbage, though
To the country western singers in outer space
Yeah, and Johnny Paycheck died
Well, we talked about that last week
Well, he actually fell asleep
And nobody's been able to wake him up yet
So they threw a big old wake
And they tossed him in the air
Is this this week's show or last week's show?
I don't know anymore
Johnny Cash's birthday was this today
Or a week ago today?
January is the Julyuary
It's one of those
70 years old
How old was Johnny?
Your babies grow up to be couples
Mamas don't let your babies
Don't let them smoke, froth, and dress up like girls
Grow little titties and go on girls
Don't make them grow little titties
We'll try not, moms
Don't tell them not to
That's just what they'll want to do
Mamas, don't let your babies go
To X Day
Don't let them have
Operations that change their sexes
It's a twisted, sick, demented bunch of people
Mamas, please
If you hear me
If your babies do survive the war
If they do come home from the war
Don't let them go to X Day
Because they never really come home
From X Day
They won't be babies no more
You think a war might spank their booty?
X Day is going to spank their brains out
This will be the sixth
X Day, or what we call
Sixth Sex Day
Sixth
There will be some six sex
There will be six hundred and sixty-six
Sick
Sex monkeys
Spelled
Sick, sick, sick
With S-I-C-S-I-C
As is, as is, as is
Spelling out Bob
With their butts
Mooning the sky
For the satellites to read
And you'll be the quote marks on the end
I'll be the queen of procreation
Your two cheeks
I'll be the lizard woman
Pointing up at the satellites
Of Ashcroft
Will be the quotes on Bob's butt name
Attention!
This is your beloved leader
Og the Exalted
There will be a special giant joy rally today
At Og Memorial Stadium
First let me say that this trip was made possible
Only by our dauntless chief
Og the Magnificent
Introducer of Og Power
Which runs most of our industry
Naturally I protected government property
By making the saucer invisible
Yes, I brought the secrets back with me
And here they are
The big secret is of course oil
Which has brought a better life
To all the people in the USA
But the key to making oil work is oil
To make it work for everybody
Is competition
Fellow Martians
I thank you
Mmm
You know what this means Cosmic
You bet I do Og
It means that you're through
So why don't you get lost
Yes the real secret is not only a great source of energy
But also the freedom to make it work for everybody
And that's why I'm here today to tell you that the real secret is not only a great source of energy but also the freedom to make it work for everybody
And if you have both of these things
Any goal is possible
It's destination unlimited
Man continually strives to replace the old with the new
A quarter of a mile high skyscraper's tower
With convenient rest and recreational facilities for all
On many of the buildings are landing decks
For helicopters and auto gyros
Rich in sunshine is the city of 1960
On all express city thoroughfares
The rights of way have been so rooted
As to displace outmoded business sections
And undesirable slum areas whenever possible
The
The The
The the
The
The The
The The The The The The The The The The The The The The
If now wasn't a better time than any, I don't know what is.
Yeah, really, man.
Don't look at me.
Well, we're trying not to.
I've got a Bob's phone number.
But you're right there.
No, no, I'm just a PR back, man.
I'm supposed to go.
Why?
We don't know.
Well, we don't.
We don't know what year it is, and we don't know.
I know this.
Bob said that the X's will come July 5th, 1998.
Obviously, it is not yet July 5th, 1998.
1998, perhaps we'll be lucky, and tomorrow will be.
You're off by 14 years by the Mayan calendar, which is given and fixed as July 5th, 2012.
The urine calendar is covered with some sort of yellowish juice.
Mayan, as opposed to urine.
Yours and mine.
Urine and mine.
Oh!
Yeah, oh, oh.
You were talking about the Andean calendar of the...
The prepubescent one.
Husky people of the Andes.
Yes, the Husky.
And what exactly happens?
At 7 a.m.?
On 2012?
A bunch of the Mayan elder gods come down from the clouds.
That's what happens.
Of the year 1998.
Bob's good buddies from Planet X, who happen to be sex goddesses, will...
I just feel betrayed, Sting.
...come down or up or in from another dimension.
They'll arrive at some way.
Yeah.
Or rather, we shall be vacated.
We will vacate this evacuation chamber.
This great...
...latrine called Earth Farm 1, where the aliens have raised us in order to feed off of our anguish and pain.
Raised in our own filth.
And they'll have a great dessert of those left behind in their anguish and pain.
They especially do love the ones who were raised in their own filth, don't they?
The slackness are punished and the dues-paying squeaky ministers are squeaky clean and...
Rubbed.
Rubbed down.
Pure of impurities.
Peter the Parrot.
Purified by Bobby.
Wait, the biggest thing.
And Connie.
How can you have Oren call home?
No.
Oren, please call home.
Hey.
His honey is irked.
How could we...
I mean, yeah.
I mean, but wait a minute.
Hey.
Now, come on.
Like, dudes, like, hold on.
Now, hey.
Wait, everybody.
Like, put the pipe down, man.
Yeah.
Hold on.
Just open those eardrums.
Mr. Rogers died.
Once again.
We have another casualty.
The real end times are near when Mr. Rogers makes his escape.
He tried to get in that little...
He got off.
...little train.
He got off, man.
He got off.
He tried to shrink his mind and get in the little train and take off to Smallville.
You know what?
When I heard Mr. Rogers died, I got real scared.
Well, but he's with his grandpa now with that...
That's because of the implant.
...loss.
I got real scared.
Man, because I just know if there's no Mr. Rogers here anymore, there's nothing to keep
the aliens from toasting this motherfucking place.
Chaz, what about the Teletubbies?
It's the implant.
No.
That's why he got scared when Mr. Rogers died.
Yeah, they'll be leading the charge.
It's because of the micro angel.
Once again, you guys, you don't get scared when Mr. Rogers dies.
You feel sad.
See?
Look at how screwed up he is because of that implant.
I don't feel sad.
I'm scared as hell.
Your implant is not even put in the right place to hide your neck.
What's going to keep George Bush from just nuking the whole earth now that Mr. Rogers
is gone?
Well, they used to meet regularly to discuss policy and so forth.
No more beautiful days in neighborhood earth, boys and girls.
Ladies and gentlemen, you've heard the reports that enemy planes are approaching.
In less than three hours, an H-bomb might fall over Portland.
But like myself, I think you're going to be very interested in this story that we're going
to tell you.
And in this age of missiles and man-made moons, it takes on added significance.
There are no actors in this story, but there are a lot of people.
And I'm sure you've heard of them.
The people of the city of Portland, Oregon.
And what happened to them, or could happen to them, on a day that we'll call X.
Holding hands, waiting for that fog horn to blow.
It's been three hours now and he said he was never going to come again.
But I knew I'd just stay here and wait.
I could hear the footsteps from two blocks away.
Those big chubby feet slapping against the pavement.
Yeah, it was the first time I'd seen him.
It was the sound of the s-w for War Bush.
And his buddy Sodom and S-Mack-Em-Hobby.
Yeah, they thought they had the streets sealed up.
They thought they were clean to the bean.
Yeah, they thought they were the ones to run the whole show.
But I was taking pictures, see.
And I was writing everything down.
Okay, stop the car here.
This is Sbarro's restaurant.
I'm going to have to go in for a couple of days.
for a little while and pretend like we're talking to each other.
We both know there's no need for talk anymore.
No need for talk.
Everything's going on behind the scenes.
Behind the scenes.
Everyone knows that everyone blows.
There's nothing going on in front.
And there's nothing going on behind your eyes.
But behind your back, we're doing plenty.
And behind the curtain.
Behind the curtain.
Beyond the curtain.
You, the representations of people we represent.
We would like to know that we are not sham.
We are not focused and smoky.
We are real and we represent your representations.
We're behind each and every one of you Americans.
Whispering funny things in the back of your neck.
You're not alone.
Hello.
I'm gonna be able to pay my bills.
I can't pay anything.
Sometimes I just wish I could take a car and go out and shoot a goddamn partner.
Too many visions, man.
Too many dreams.
I saw the mushroom cloud again last night and it wasn't in my suit, man.
It was in my ears and my eyes.
Everybody is watching.
Calm down, man.
Like the walls of Jermicho.
You're inesserable!
K
Peep!
Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
44118, that's where you send things to me to play.
The show, The Hour of Slack, is the voice of the church of the subgenius.
More about that at www.subgenius.com,
which includes a catalog of books and other things.
Friends.
Why don't you come on over to my joint?
Why don't you stink up my joint the way I stinked up my...
Okay.
Why do you want to help me so much?
None of this made any sense at all.
There was no connective tissue.
There wasn't one.
Pioneer firing turned off.
Mr. Rogers tuned out.
Good afternoon, we've been mayhem.
He got off.
Well, yeah.
He's aboard that ship now.
He was being the board.
I think our jobs are cut out for us.
It's time for us now to build our own ships.
To meet.
Bob halfway, perhaps.
Our ships are cardboard cutouts.
Bob beckons.
The men from Planet X are beckoning to us.
They're saying,
lift, pull yourself up by your own boob straps.
You boots.
You silly platoons.
The beckoning.
Pull yourself.
Yank yourself.
Lift yourself up by your own straps.
Yank.
Yank and wank.
Wank for Bob.
Wank as if your very life depended on it.
What the hell?
It's life, I tell you.
Hey.
You've been listening to ESO Radio.
Swamp Radio.
My name's Chaz.
Lonesome cowboy Dave.
Princess Wee Ardo.
The Reverend Ivan Stagg.
Wank.
Wank you fool.
Wank as if your very life depended on it.
This is James A. Sievert.
No wheels.
And the radio voice of the fields on State University.
Till next week.
Keep your hat on tight.
You're back to the wind.
And you're sagging the saddle.
You're sagging Princess Wee.
Wank.
You wanker.
Wank you wankers as if your life, it does, your life depended on it.
You're sagging the saddle.
Oh, say, on your way out, could you kind of tell the nurses what a hero I am?
Now, why didn't I think of that?
Is that the hero?
Oh, yeah, that's him lying right there.
You're a good man, Philo.
Ooh, it hurts right here.
Huh?
What's he doing?