Our friends, this is Hour of Slack number 1,447, a rerun of Hour of Slack number 753 from the year of 2000.
We know now that in the early years of the 20th century, this world was being watched closely by intelligences greater than man's, and yet as mortal as his own.
We know now that as human beings busied themselves about their various concerns, they were scrutinized and studied, perhaps almost as narrowly as a man with a microscope might scrutinize the transient creatures that swarm and multiply in a drop of water.
Mob?
And now, the subgenius!
Hour of Slack!
Slack!
The subgenius Hour of Slack that you are about to listen to is specially designed only to be played on radio station and only in the city of...
Should any other shows be heard from or contacted in the course of this show, the listener is advised to remain calm and only contact listed or unlisted officials in the event of any material from this radio or other listening device being inhaled during broadcast.
Small animals or other children becoming exposed to the ultra-high or ultra-low shocks and brain frequencies constantly scanned throughout our program should seek shelter in an approved safety unit only.
This is Walter Teasdale reminding you that it's often a photon that light releases, but truth is, not everyone gets the...
...picture.
Hoping your time is all time and all your unpremissible truths are happy truths.
Here's your host, the Reverend Pippi Stinks.
Well, to usher in this brand new month with a brand new disclaimer, here's the Reverend Pippi Stinks.
Today is the last day of the end of your life.
Pippi...
Look at it that way... Tomorrow...
and, you know, there won't even be a tomorrow.
So what you gonna do about it?
Might as well just lay back and enjoy it.
It's like bad weather.
Get back down.
Slide into it.
If you hit it hard,
it's hard as a rock.
But if you touch it gently,
it talks.
Caress it like a dog.
It accepts you.
Oh, thank you so very much.
It is like a fluid.
You are truly, truly.
Through which you can float.
My one-eyed guru.
And if you run into it,
I have worshiped other one-eyed gurus.
But as you snuggle up.
Through aeons by,
I have wasted my spiritual juices.
It's like a warm, fuzzy,
bathtub full of
hot material.
But now,
when I see you rising in the eastern horizon,
fuzzy and red,
and made and built for my sexual pleasures,
I can only offer up my squanderances
in what meager supplies of vestal surges are.
Dave's talking to his dog again.
Oh puppy.
Salutations.
Today I feel a sense of urgency as I speak to you for Devo Incorporated.
Salutations. Today I feel a sense of urgency as I speak to you for Devo Incorporated.
There is a direct connection between Devo's work in the music field
and a big wiggly world around us.
You may not be aware of this, but we are in the middle of World War III.
It is not nuclear bombs that we must fear.
The weapon is the human mind or lack of it on this planet.
That will determine our fate.
Capital punishment for airline passengers who attempt to save money.
Spud men in gas lines who forgot that guns don't work.
And tourists attempting to catch some rays at Three Mile Island
add up to a major attack of corkscrews in the brain.
We must fight back.
We must know what we want.
We must want what we need.
And what we need is duty now for the future.
They make me say things.
We're all here tonight to praise Bob.
He's kind of...
He's shown us that Devo works in parallel ways
with other pockets of humans on this planet.
Where we thought we were alone,
we know there are now other human forms
that believe in conscious mutation.
As he knows, Bob is merely an enema for a constipated society.
These people here are here to help a constipated society blow it out their ass.
Have you ever met Bob?
Well, like I said, Bob would appear in my bedroom
and chase me around, making me do jumping jacks.
Peek-a-boo!
I know what you do.
Cause I do it too.
Intelligence.
No.
Am I as smart as I think?
Probably not.
That's good.
Daily disease cannot feel pain.
No.
There will always be time for DeVoe.
Where we were raised, we were taught this is the way that music should be played.
Thank you.
From little snails, I say it's all just for themselves.
Are we not men?
We are DeVoe.
Working heads held, we are not whole.
Working heads all, can't go home.
Are we not men?
We are DeVoe.
In business, teachers and critics all dance the blues.
Are we not men?
We are DeVoe.
DeVoe.
Are we not men?
We are DeVoe.
DeVoe.
hear us shout in the thighs that assigned by irony,
You order by the collection,
Light supporters,
So arise that zeros are persons,
I've got a rhyme that starts with a riddle
Ohio
What's round in the ends and high in the middle?
God made man, but he used to want you to do it
Makes it a plan, but wants to ruin it
Can one thing, one thing, do what I want you to do?
God made man, but I want you to supply the deal
Norma, Norma, let go of the sofa. It's time to go now.
Oh, Carol, I am having second thoughts.
Now we've discussed this, Norma, so just let go of the curtains.
When you think of inviting a friend to church or synagogue,
you probably imagine meeting some resistance.
Norma, let go of the emergency brake.
No, no, really, Carol, I think I changed my mind.
Please, the steering wheel, huh?
The more you think about it, the more you think about it.
The more you worry about it, the more you imagine how difficult it will be.
Please, Norma, let go of the door.
Oh, I just can't go through with it.
But it's probably just your imagination, and your friend will actually thank you in the end.
Carol, the service was wonderful. I feel so good, I almost hate to leave.
Well, maybe we'll come back next week.
Come on, Norma, let go of the pew.
If religion enriches your life, share the wealth.
This week, invite a friend.
A service of the Advertising Council and Religion in American Life.
Bob?
Hey, you might be sitting there looking around at yourself going,
well, now, so this is the Church of the Subgenius.
Well, there's all kinds of people here.
I was...
And I'm trying to understand these people.
I'd like to understand a little bit more about this Church of the Subgenius.
Well, friends, these ones around here that seem to be sort of fanatic,
like they really believe this stuff.
Friends, those are the ones who have given their brains to Bob!
And I'm not going to try to get everybody here to give their brains to Bob for good, like I did.
But you just tried giving your brain to Bob temporarily.
And you may find you like it.
You may find that you didn't need that brain all that much.
Why do you think we call it Church of the Subgenius?
Jesus Christ!
As I crossed the desert, pulling myself along by my stumps,
and it's very hard to pull oneself with using stumps,
I would just wrap my handless limb around the cactuses to pull myself forward.
But I knew that it would be worth it.
For I had heard the call, and I had smelt the smoke of the pipe of the piper.
He was... I knew...
And what a horrible liar he was.
He was the one to follow.
To follow!
No matter that I had blinded myself blundering after him in his path.
Like a bumbling, sickening Christ.
No wonder that I had chopped my own hands off in devotion.
And was crawling, pulling myself along the desert.
A shiny visage in the dark.
Nothing to drink but Helium Monster Blood.
But my love for Bob.
My guru, my savior, my sweet, sweet...
Bob.
Surely this, the quest for Bob alone, was slack.
I thought as I wrapped my arms around yet another prickly pair of cactus
to drag myself forward as the ants and the rattlesnakes crawled over me.
My only friend.
I crossed my promise to四-o-оры and Champions.
Mis одesser
gesch empowering me to
And once again, chief!
over there.
Q-top,
square off,
eight corners,
nine new triangles,
black top,
straight ahead,
straight guys,
walking!
Never
over,
stands alone,
he is
up ahead,
making man go
broke, he comes
with the pants,
Q-top,
square off,
eight corners,
nine new triangles,
black top,
straight ahead,
start hot,
walking!
énormite.com
waar
thitions
Utah, square one, eight corners, nine to be hanged,
no, we're flat out, stay straight ahead,
not much left here.
Black hands, black hands, hey,
don't give me, don't give me black hands.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Oh, yes, dear friends, Blockhead by the Doguloids.
I wonder if they're any relation to my old friend, the Mongreloids.
And before that, friends, lots of subgenius preaching
with Einstein's Secret Orchestra on WCSB in Cleveland
and at the Blind Lemon in Cleveland.
Before that,
the Jocko Homo version was by the band called C.D. Truth.
C.D. Truth, who we just saw live at the Devotional Day of Atonement, friends,
an international Devo spud harvest held here in Cleveland
by Michael Comer, Toth Wilder, and Ace, and Devo,
and we heard Mark Mothersbaugh,
your fellow reverend Mark Mothersbaugh,
on TV.
Bob and General Boy, progenitor of the Devos,
who was live at the Devo Day of Atonement.
Also, we heard, friends, puzzling evidence,
the original puzzling evidence,
and our original live, dead, live announcer,
Bleepo Abernathy.
Friends, the Devo convention was great.
There were wonderful bands,
many fellow subgenius.
Alan Meyer's shoes,
the whip from Whippet, friends,
but the DevoCon is not the same as the con,
as in conspiracy.
Well, what is the conspiracy?
It's 20th century traditions.
It's the old traditions.
It's all the things that got us where we are now.
It's the old traditions. It's all the things that got us where we are now.
It's Christ without a penis.
He's part of the conspiracy.
It's presidents that don't look like they're capable of getting erections anymore.
That's the conspiracy.
Hey, Benz, you've just been had.
Do Daddy want
baby, baby, baby
baby want
We're pinheads all home
We are not home
Jot the hormone
Are we not men?
We are devils
God created man
But he needed the monkey to do it
Monkey man
In business suits
Teachers and critics
All dance the flute
Are we not men?
We are devils
Well, are we not men?
Yes, are we not men?
Extremely interesting and extremely worthwhile artistic performances.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Mongrel lord, it was a mongrel lord
Who was happy with you
Who was happy with you and me
Hm municipality, including you
Hm municipality Mountainанию
Mongrel lord who was happy with me
That's all right with me
Mongrel lord, it was a mongrel lord
Mongrel lord who was happy with you and me
It's all right with me
You may portray that you are not too low
But you are a special
I don't believe!
Oh my god!
Yes, one.
What are you guys doing?
What is this?
What kind of...
With infinite complacence,
people went to and fro over the earth
about their little affairs.
Serene in the assurance of their dominion
over this small, spinning
fragment of solar driftwood,
which by chance or design,
man has inherited
out of the dark mystery of time and space.
Yet across an immense, ethereal
gulf, minds
that are to our minds
as ours are to the beasts in the
jungle, intellects
vast,
cool and unsympathetic
regarded this earth
with envious eyes
and slowly and surely drew their plans
against us.
It was a thing I had to do.
It was a message from below.
It was a message situation.
It was desire for approval.
I'm not a wanker or a banker.
I'm not afraid to take a risk.
It's the thing females ask for when they can taste opposite.
Before I die.
I'll get another piece of pie.
I have to die.
Ha!
It was a thing I had to do.
It was a message from below.
It was a messy situation.
It was a triumph of the will.
And the people just started to say.
When I die, before I die.
Before I die.
I'll get another piece of pie
Get another piece of pie
If I have to lie
And when the well cries out for water
It is a need that must be filled
It goes beyond the laws of nature
It takes a triumph of the will
And now, CD Truth!
Freedom of choice
An ancient poem
There was a poem
About a dog
Who found two bones
He kicked the one
He licked the other
He went in circles
He drowned dead
Freedom of choice
Is what you've got
Then you got it
But you don't want it
Seems to be the rule of thumb
Don't be tricked
By what you see
You've got two ways to go
Just say it again
And we'll let it hum anew
Freedom of choice
We'll be right back.
plague.
take in one tiny pill.
Every afternoon at around
6 o'clock, Mom and Dad get awfully
sleepy, but with one shot of
God's Opaque, you'll be back
in Boozness again.
I can't believe it.
She's just a girl. She's just a girl.
The girl you want.
You're in a corner
and we're waiting
for the day you turn.
You know you're headed for the pattern of burn.
When the words get stuck on the tip of your tongue.
She's the real thing
that you knew in our lives.
She's just a girl. She's just a girl.
The girl you want.
She's out of your mind.
Come on, you.
Come on, You're радиot.
All right. Praise Connie.
I'm kidding.
Don't.
wan tooo yaaaa pag.
This is me.
What all you
thing you play
and it asleep, but I'm using
the Tesla even voice because it
stays on Batteries while I think
with your brains.
I've seen that so-called
vehicle.
the accelerator.
evidence before and maybe puzzling where it comes from, but as far as I'm concerned, it's just a lot
of the same hoopla that they've been feeding us all these years. Somebody ought to do something
about this business before it gets completely out of hand. Well, if that kind of thing doesn't
bother me, what I want to know is, when I talk to somebody, is he real when I'm talking to him?
Only when you're talking to him is he real. When he tries to answer, he becomes tape again.
Oh my God. Is this for real? No, no, no. This is just a tape. Relax. It is not the day before
or the week between. It's just the show. The show that, yes, was thrown into the bay three
weeks ago and struggled free of its chains and floated up, swam back to the studio here,
climbed up the antenna, and is now running all the way down those little air wires right into
your ears. You never know when you're here or not on this show because there's so many doctors.
Just a few dugs, sprinkle a few Gary's, drop a few bobs over here. Yes, I'm sorry, listener.
You've got a real problem now. They're alive all the time.
A puzzling evidence did it. Puzzling evidence did that. And this music in the background,
and all of my credits background music is from Mark Mothersbaugh's Christmas album,
Joyo Mutato. Girl You Want, that kick, kill, amazing version of Girl You Want was by
Robert Palmer and from Einstein's Secret Radio Show on, or Einstein's Secret Orchestra Radio
Show on WCSB. Lonesome, Cowboy Dave, Chaz Smith, yours truly, which is also heard strangely in the
insane music.
Mixed by TODCRA now.
Königschau knows whatcha time is gen 3
Always kept your distance when you built my friends near you
Love keeps on rolling over
Flying in between our four wheeled ships
The ship was supposed to take a leap to the plane
To be had and rehired in the thick of a feeling
Now it's strange
It's a strange first to be
I come running like a fat boy
In a suit like a fat boy
I don't come for nothing, yo
It's hopeless, I hope for the one thing I want
I got a strange
It's a strange first to be
I'm a little dazzled, but you don't have to
I'm a strange first to be
Taking my mind apart, I'm lost for a few seconds
It's a strange first to be
Never get stuck when you get to where you're at
Time you can't stop, but you never turn the head forward
It's a strange first to be
Taking my mind apart, I'm lost for a few seconds
Never get stuck when you get to where you're at
It's a strange first to be
You just can't stop, nobody can stop, no one can stop you
I won't stop, will run do what I want
You couldn't stop me once I told you
After I'm all dried up, dragon the dude
Fluged along on his way
No more inhabitants to two-one me
It's a strange first to be
and is coursing
like the love
of Bob.
The blood and the love
shall defeat their weak
god
with the power
of the blood
of Bob.
It devour the
weak and the unfit.
The dwarfish.
The stunted.
Oh, wait, no, that's us.
The handsome, the large,
the successful, yes, those we will bring
down and we will
raise up the dwarfish,
the stunted, the criminal,
the evil,
the bad,
the pug-nosed,
the pig people, yes.
Those shall become our
beautiful gods
and the
modern movie
stars and politicians,
they,
they shall become
our tongue-beaters
upon the face of society.
I'm trying, I only wanted to
check your underwear.
Because the revolution
is close at hand.
Mark my words, all the signs are there.
The conspiracy
is a running
whipped dog.
You can just tell
they think they're fooling us with their
silly elections and things.
Nobody,
and as soon
we will all
band together and
leap up and say
I'm mad as hell
and, uh,
I'm falling asleep.
Yes, yes,
that sounds like a better idea.
Let's forget this revolution
and have our own
spiritual revolution
in our navels.
A life
free from worry.
Free from cares.
In a condom condominium.
Hermetically sealed.
And kept from all trauma.
Mother Mary comes for me.
Whipping
words of wisdom.
Let it be.
I'm in a wheelchair.
He's in a wheelchair.
But I want to know
and let it be with you.
I can breathe in the wild
I can't help but love this love
And I'm coming to the wind
I don't care
Coming to the wind
celulose
I don't care, could it be a joke or a piece of cake?
We've got a plan in place, and we're flying high.
But we've got a plan in place, and we're flying high.
And we're flying high.
Now, could it be a joke or a piece of cake?
I don't care, could it be a joke or a piece of cake?
I don't care.
Could it be a joke or a piece of cake?
Just a joke, dude.
Just a joke.
He wasn't there, too.
I don't care.
I don't care either.
I don't care making jokes all day.
I don't care, neither.
Thanks, guys.
Thanks for doing a good job.
And thanks for doing a good job.
Thanks, guys.
Oh, wow, dude.
Hey, man.
You have your license?
Turn the radio down, sir.
What?
I can't hear you.
Please step out of the car.
Step out of the car.
I can't hear you.
Wake up, my friend.
It's just a show.
Einstein's Secret Orchestra Radio and Jimmy.
Jimmy's in a wheelchair.
That Devo song by Crapper Keeper.
Michael Pilmer's band.
He used to do Silica Jelly.
And we also heard Strange Pursuits as performed by Gajito
with our oldest, youngest friend, Dr. Onan Canobite.
And now, the touch tones.
They tell us that we lost our tails.
It was enough from the first note.
I say it's tough.
Just wind and sail.
Are we not meant?
We are Devo.
Okay, here's the story.
But aren't you going to molest me some more?
Dr. Piper Pop?
All right, climb right up here on my...
That's right, that's a good boy.
Climb right up here on my lap.
Now bend over.
I'm going to have to give you...
Oh, boy!
Can I have my spanking?
We're all Devo.
Come on, boys.
Come on all over here.
And the doctor's going to give you a good spanking
and teach you about Planet X.
We're just cannibal eggs.
Huh?
And so,
the poor little children were abused and abandoned
by the evil doctor.
Left to their own devices,
there wasn't much left to eat
but rat meat and sundaes for the week.
Some of the little boys resorted to crying,
but they knew they had to be bigger than that.
They had to stand tough and swallow back their tears.
This is the end of the show.
This is the story of Cry Baby Duck.
They said he cried too much.
Then he cried some more.
Poor little duck.
What could he do now?
Then he began to cry.
And again, he began to cry.
Cry Baby Duck.
More tears.
So, drip, drip came the tears.
Cry Baby Duck cried harder than ever.
He did not want to go away.
This was his home.
And he wanted to stay.
Cry Baby Duck drank and drank.
He was happy.
He was glad.
He was happy day after day.
So, Cry Baby Duck cried again.
I remember when I had that harmful, and they removed both of my hands,
they removed my feet, and they showed them back on.
So I don't really see...
Seven times a night.
Well, actually, they cut them off seven times, but only sew them back on six.
Six times?
And you have to learn, by the seventh time, you have to learn how to do it yourself.
That's how the aliens really work.
I don't know if actual learning is involved.
It's more of a rote task, isn't it?
Well, we'll be back next week.
Till then...
We'll be back next week.
Keep your hat on tight.
You're back to the wind, and your sack firmly seated in the saddle.
Keep the caps on your feces bottles at all times.
Make sure the sunstroke medicine is correctly prepared and hermetically quarmed.
And make sure that Mom and Dad have restructured the DNA groups for both you and yourself.
And don't forget to pray.
Pray for Dave here.
I need not your prayers.
I worship not your false god.
I worship the bright shining star.
I worship the evening star.
Please.
Adios, muchachos.
Please keep those cards and letters coming.
Please spread our song to all wherever you are or whatever area you live.
Stay in touch with us wherever you might be.
Thanks, Dave.
And friends, to learn more about The Devos,
just try www.spud2.nz.
SubgeniusTalk.com.
They seem to be in touch with everybody that I was.
And friends, the Church of the Subgenius can always be reached at, you've got that pencil ready?
After you remember to check the website at www.subgenius.com, I want you to write down Bob's address.
Yes, Hour of Slacker or Subgenius at P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 4417.
118.
Ah, yes, praise Bob.
I can see now from the drool perv, the material pouring out of his ears, that Dr. Stang, the lovely Dr. Reverend Ivan Stang, must mention his shoes tonight are just spectacular.
Speaking of the last words from the formication amulet of Dr. Pinky,
and the other...
...tracks from the liturgy already spoken by,
Dr. Stang will be making his next appearance at the Cow Arena in downtown Sundersburg,
brought to you by the Kiwanis and the people of Original Duskent.
Also this week on the forum for formulators, it's the...
Well, it's the Reverend Ivan Stang again, speaking this time at Willie's Tavern on the corner of Barkmere and Handerbury.
This...
This evening's broadcast was brought to you by the manufacturers of sex-sexual subsensual...
Did I get this right?
I can't read the way...
I can't read this damn stuff.
Are you a bit of an audio nut?
You like to record stuff and find it to be somewhat of a hobby?
Yeah!
Want to subject other unfortunate souls to your eccentricities?
Just leave a cassette recording of your stuff anywhere.
Be it concerts, bars, or other public places, you can expose yourself to the public in a private and anonymous way.
And leave a message on a tape to encourage the listener to do the same, if he or she wishes to.
You heard of the internet? Get in on the cassette net.
Thank you.
Gosh, I don't even know the guy.
Bye.
Our boss.
Hey, what's the matter, kid?
No good?
Ah, it's a lot of baloney.
Not for me.
Yeah, that's what I figured.
Well, good night.
Don't let the bed bugs bite.
Good night.
I'm a man of few words
Is the band ready to play now?
Ready?
Play!
And now
As a bonus
Cut
Mongoloid
By
Occupant
Praise
Onan
Move
He was a Michael Lloyd, and it determined what he could see.
Michael Lloyd, Michael Lloyd, not here.
Michael Lloyd.
Let's go.
You say you've heard it all before
Songs about my nuts
A song about a whore
I know a place where MCs get crushed
We can smash
And that ain't much
I got late
And paid
Had it made in the drug trade
Fuck minimum wage
I just got a page
Need a nickel
A dime
A twenty
I know
I'm a slinger
Motherfucker's got money
On my asshole
Going under
And I'm drunk as a skunk
Don't fuck with me, punk
Going under
I'm high as hell
The evolution is real
Can't you tell?
Going under
And I'm getting fucked up
And I'm with my boy Chuck
Going under
We're smoking blunts
And we're pulling stunts
Nine a.m.
Going under
And you motherfucking dig it
Give me a forty, I'll swing it
Going under
And I'm getting lit
I don't give a shit
Going under
Why you wanna step?
Hey, I'm gonna put you in check
Yo
Hi, this is C-Dawg from Crackers
And I'd like to cordially invite the entire town of Springfield, Illinois
To check my motherfucking NU's
That's right, my nuts
That's right, I'm King Lit, a.k.a. Swap G
On the motherfucking cracker tip
That's right, I cordially invite you
Guess what?
I'm D.N.A.
And that's dick, nuts, and ass
For all you buster-ass motherfuckers
That just don't know
See, yo
I'm gonna fucking float
Here we go
Fuck you
lungz
Kuckagg
All you fucks
Go all hell
Go
uh
We ain't no pumper
Hey, what was that in it, dude?
The
See
S
Vaccin
Come on
Golf
BRIAN
Come on
A
another couple of months. Not just this show, but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob and want some of that slack back to rebound to you, you should go to
subgenius.com front page or especially the radio page or the catalog store pages and help out
financially as best you can. Now, we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty,
and we don't want any subgeniuses to make their own situations worse. But some of you still have
jobs. Even five bucks makes a big difference, even if it's only once a month from enough of you.
50 bucks makes an even bigger difference. All we're saying is that glow jobs could go the way
of Steve jobs if you don't pay dogs. We also take checks and money orders to
subgenius.com.
P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Thanks for anything you can do to help let there be slack.
We'll see you next time.