This is your last chance.
After this, there is no turning back.
You take the blue pill.
The story ends.
You wake up in your bed and believe whatever you want to believe.
You take the red pill.
You stay in Wonderland.
And I show you how deep the rabbit hole goes.
Remember,
all I'm offering is the truth.
Nothing more.
Time for show.
Live show for you now.
This is Doug Smith, radio operator.
I'm going to bring you a piece of that green cheese for sure.
Welcome to the subgenius radio ministry.
Hour of Slap.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
Laughter
Music
Samuel Bruce.
Text to Uncle Dan, meeting with the Ku Klux Klan.
Tell him there's a change of plans, the South won't rise again.
Yammering with the Southern drawl.
Bless your heart.
Howdy y'all.
President Trump won't build that wall and the South won't rise again.
General Sherman came to town riding on a horsey.
Stuck his boot inside your ass and burned your town of carsey.
Corpulent, seditious scum pining for a donkey's bum.
Yodel, stomping, clapping, strum, but the South won't rise again.
Let's see what's going on in the cornfield.
Hey, Clarabelle, where'd you get that pretty Q-9 baseball cap?
Oh, Rufus gave it to me.
He got it at that riot up in Washington, D.C.
Well, as pretty as you are, Clarabelle, I bet he gives you lots of nice gifts.
Well, he ain't given me nothing since he went to prison.
Hey!
Jimmy Bob, what's the difference between President Trump and President Obama?
I don't know, Clem, you tell me.
What's the difference between President Trump and President Obama?
Well, I want President Trump to f*** my dog.
Oh, f*** him!
I don't know, Clem.
Football-watching tubs of lard
Likes for General Beauregard
Arithmetic is pretty hard
And the South won't rise again
Knife-siege thugs with rebel flags
From our buffers
We will drag, ship them home in body bags
But the South won't rise again
Racist fucks in Alabama
Bombed a church in Birmingham
Then they rotted in the slammer
When you fuck your next of kin
Go and tell your white trash friends
You lost before and you'll lose again
The South won't ever win
The South won't rise, the South won't rise
The South won't rise again
Oh, Frabjous Day, Kaloo Kalay, friends.
Not one, but two Rudy Schwartz Project albums came out today.
Saving this show and my mood.
One is an album of songs called
Adjacent to the Latex Gerbil.
And the one we just heard,
The South,
The South Won't Rise Again, is from that one.
We'll be hearing more of those later on in the show.
The other album is called Frop Music.
And it's all instrumentals.
The one in the background right now
is called Devil Horns on the Forehead of Broderick Crawford.
Ahead.
We'll also be listening to some
uh, uh,
old synesthesia radio
with Dr. Hal
and Lonesome Cowboy Dave
and some puzzling evidence
show from KPFA Berkeley
from the old days.
The synesthesia show is from WCSB Cleveland.
And, uh,
and some ancient fire sign theater.
But now this.
Ah, if only we could bring this
special,
special understanding to so many of our citizens
who unknowing are searching in the dark
and thirsting for it.
But these early days,
Stang,
is Stang counseled for us
as he used it to bring them the message.
I don't know if this is still valid
in today's world of modern times.
Well, the first Stangian orthodox fist temple
of whatever it is,
is standing by to leech away your vital essence
and turn it into solid blocks of subgenius understanding.
Slack, come.
Slug guns from the barrel of a gun, Dave.
The slug gun.
Looks like one of these.
I bet you wish you had one of these.
Slug guns like this one, see?
Yeah.
Pretty sharp, huh?
I can smell your guys' pineal glands
all the way from out here, 50 miles away.
Oh, I guess that's me.
I can smell crackling and burning
like a big forest fire out there in the west.
I'm slightly embarrassed.
I'm not, I'm just in such an awe
because I wanted you guys to explain Dobbs Town
and the good works.
And it faded out as I began to transflux.
Transflux.
Well, you know, we practice acubiting
and opening of the third nostril to all inductees,
but that's just at the first few weeks of big boot camp.
Afterwards comes hell month.
Now, the legends and rumors
about the balls and vice grips and the hazings,
that's a bunch of propaganda for me.
That's right.
It's not nearly so hard.
Benny, enjoy it.
And they come back again and again
to retake our slinky subgenius seminars.
Well, sadly, some of the propaganda is being recirculated
by various sectors of the Church of the Subgenius itself.
They are conspiracy dupes.
But I wouldn't ask you to direct yourself to that.
They're in the pockets of Time Warner,
Clear Channel and the Saturday Evening Post.
They're everywhere.
That's right.
Just like the carpet under your feet
or the nails at the end of your fingers.
Your little tinfoil helmet ain't gonna keep them out.
Yes, pyramids won't do it.
But my tinfoil helmet has worked out.
For an awful lot of the evil things you've tried to do,
you know, playing with my mind and stuff,
it has helped.
You have to remember that.
It doesn't have a self-destruct button
like our helmets do.
Well, that's another thing in the hierarchy.
How come you guys got better technology
than the rest of us?
Well, we were there when they passed out the beans.
Hmm.
The what?
You mean the multicolored beans?
Well, you plant them in the backyard
at the full of the moon.
Should we be giving away this information?
I think...
Nobody's listening.
All right.
Well, it doesn't matter.
You cast your beans on the fertile earth,
and the next day, there's a humongous big piece
of crabgrass out there with your name on it.
Now, I wouldn't give these special things to you.
Go see my new movie, Terminator 3,
and please go vote for me, please.
Now we see we're listener-censored radio
and still being interrupted by public service announcements.
That was...
...NPR affiliate.
Oh, that's very annoying.
...that itches out the inside of your ears.
Here we go.
But I think it's a form of cosmic relief
for the whole rest of the evacuation, you know,
you guys have been sputin' out.
I mean, some of it's right on the money,
but the rest of it is just to take your money.
Well, you know, you don't know what to say about that.
Well, you're like cracking stones, buddy.
We can't control every aspect of the way this has developed
and promulgated?
I'm with you 100%.
It's just that, you know, I...
I have the eyes to see and the ears to hear, you know, like they used to say in the old company.
And now you're looking through a glass darkly.
Get some Windex and get a better view.
I've got 360 vision, man.
That's the best part of these helmets.
I mean, I'm not saying it's keeping out all the bad vibes you guys are sending right now or anything,
but I can still see behind my head.
And you can see in the dark without searching blindly in the dark.
That's correct.
And it's been very, very valuable for so many members of my family who keep losing me daily,
especially, you know, after the sun goes down.
They should let their fingers do the walking up your spine.
Yeah, I knew you were going to talk about doing that stuff to my spine again.
Don't, you know, don't.
I'm not going to forget it.
Let's just put it that way.
You've got to release the Kundalini energy, see?
There are 33 little bumps here, and after each one is tweaked, you'll feel like a new being.
Yeah.
I have felt like a new...
It hasn't done me any good.
Well, you just don't have faith.
You've got to have faith, and faith will move mountains and molehills, too.
Every day, a new personality.
Every time I wake up, a completely new, different history.
You contain really, really, you know...
Your name is Legion.
You have a hundred zip codes.
Have faith and eat more prunes, Dave.
Well, I'll give that a try, but no more of the Satanist hobo stuff.
You know, my name is Legion and everything.
My name's not Legion.
That challenge, you know...
Well, not most of the time.
Let's take that other call there.
Oh.
The L stands for lumbar.
Vertebrae.
Hey, Dan, Jack, and Jim, go over to see Tim.
Dan, Jack, and Jim, go over to see Tim.
Can I borrow a toothbrush to clean my shoes?
Wouldn't you guys like to buy a bottle of long water?
This isn't a lending library.
Hello?
No.
Special privileges.
They all do.
You know, and after all the years that I've been sucking up to you guys and stuff,
how many have I got?
Three.
Well, you see, those who do don't receive the benefits,
and this is very ironic of those who simply lap up the cream.
See, back to perplexation again.
This Buddhist-type stuff, if I seek it, I will not find it.
If I sit down and I take a nap, maybe it'll happen and et cetera.
You know, I don't know.
I do lose my faith once in a while.
I sit under that fig tree and concentrate on the eternal infinite.
Okay.
But what does that really mean?
Well, it means that there is a universe of emptiness inside you.
Oh, man.
Now, that's not what I feel when I'm sticking my hand down there.
Well, what?
You've got an amusement park inside?
What?
No, but I have a lot of misdirected hairs and calloused parts.
College radio.
My name is actually Lesion, not Legion.
I've got scars the size of the San Diego Freeway.
Why don't you put a Band-Aid on that sucker?
That's unsightly.
Our listeners aren't interested in your wounds.
He needs to drink lots and lots and lots of aloe vera juice, Dave.
I've suffered these wounds for Bob Dobbs.
Much in the same way.
To heal the inside of you.
You know, I'll tell you one thing, Dave, as long as we're talking here, man to man.
Chicks dig scars.
You know what I'm talking about?
Yeah.
So those lumps and wounds, lesions, things that you're talking about,
they help you along in life.
They're chick magnets.
Yeah, exactly.
Just like on your refrigerator.
So buck up and pull yourself together.
Things aren't as bad as they seem,
and it's always darkest just before it goes completely pitch black.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
It seems like it was somehow easier to do shows
back when we had a radio station to do them in.
That's from Dr. Sinister's show on WCSB Cleveland.
It still follows the Hour of Slack after like 20 years.
I should call that show.
It's just that I'm usually asleep or half asleep by then on Sundays.
I've been doing this weekly show for 36 years, friends.
Almost 2,000 episodes.
And I was about to write up a report on how I've been slowing down
because I have the malaise from my advancing arthritis
and I'm not feeling well.
And declining motivation and this dang chest cold,
which you may be able to hear in my voice.
It's been clinging on.
But then I looked at my email,
and there was the weekly flat-out donation
from listener Reverend John Flanagan
with the phrase,
Thanks for Hour of Slack.
Pray, Bob.
And it's things like that that motivate me
to go ahead and try to throw together a new show.
Even if it's made of old parts, largely.
Instead of sitting on the bed staring into space,
which has been getting easier and easier to do.
There's another guy that sends $130.13 every month.
And another guy that sends $50 every month.
And about 10 subscribers who actually pay $5 an episode for each show.
Otherwise, I think I might be too tired of this
to even bother to put out a rerun.
But knowing there are at least 20 listeners
that care that much,
well, now I'd be a real wuss to quit now.
Plus, X-Day is in a month,
and after that I won't have to worry about anything, right?
I'm going to go to Reverend Zanthea's campground
in Florida, Land O'Lakes, Florida,
and see lots of buddies.
And that'll be my first trip past Granbury, Texas
in over a year.
The Granbury's only 20 miles away,
but they have doctors,
and even a movie theater there.
Heck, they even have an opera house.
Where I live, in Glen Rose,
there are two grocery stores,
two drug stores,
three banks,
a dollar store,
and about 100 churches.
However, I like it here
because there's a half mile of unspoiled woods and creeks
around my house in every direction,
and a few houses occupied by my siblings and nephews,
and a big herd of goats.
But I think during the last year and a half,
we've had a grand total of five visitors.
Luckily, almost all of them were beautiful ladies.
So there's that.
Also, we've been seeing subgenius friends on Zoom
and other weekly or monthly internet meetups
like the Subgenius Diaspora every Saturday,
and Ask Dr. Hal once a month.
And I'm in daily touch with Philo,
Philo,
Onan,
Sterno,
Sphinxo,
and Puzlo Evido
via a secret channel.
Now, Onan's helping me get some new and old books out.
Now, nobody in Glen Rose, Texas,
knows who Bob is,
except for one subgenius who isn't related to me,
and she's one of the beautiful ladies that visits.
Because I don't wear Bob shirts around.
My car has no bumper stickers.
I don't want to get into that conversation.
Nobody knows about the movie.
Which reminds me,
I haven't played the rest of the soundtrack
of Sandy Boone's excellent 2019 documentary about us
on the show yet.
So I'm about to.
Incidentally, it's no longer on Amazon.com
or Prime or whatever,
but it's still on Apple TV
and I think Hulu.
Several, a whole bunch of other ones.
You can look at dobstown.org
and that explains all of that stuff.
Anyway, here's some
hopefully not too dated stuff
from near the end of the subgenius movie
by Sandy Boone,
J.R. Bob Dobbs,
and the Church of the Subgenius.
The world never did know about Church of the Subgenius.
We never were that,
that big.
It is kind of obscure.
That keeps it special.
If everybody knew about it,
it would be normal.
We were just too lazy.
We didn't want to be responsible
for our own cult members.
We just wanted to tap them on the forehead
and say, wake up.
And of course,
some people you have to hit with a sledgehammer.
And even then, that doesn't do the trick.
Or you can get them to wake for a second or two.
And then they doze off again
as soon as they see a cat picture on the internet.
Today's secret ingredient is...
How am I doing? Am I doing okay?
I'm present.
Hey, I'm president.
Do you believe me?
I believe.
Donald Trump's probably
the most subgenius world leader there's ever been.
He's completely caught up in his own world,
does what he wants,
makes up his own reality.
I'm not going to give you a question.
Can you stay cataclysmic?
You are fake news.
Sean Spicer, our press secretary,
gave alternative facts.
Facts and lies have no meaning to him.
Subgenius.
Genius, but not in a good way.
Trump's stakes.
Where are the stakes?
Do we have stakes?
Do I?
We've been friends for a long time.
We're living in a world that's upside down.
Trump is the perfect example now of a world turned upside down.
He's the Joker.
This is a special year.
Our country is doing great.
We've got surreal, unbelievable, shocking, psychedelic,
covered with reality.
It's not a good place for any party to end up with a cult-like situation.
I mean, Bob Dobbs is not in any way weirder than Donald Trump.
I mean, Donald Trump wins.
I could stand in the middle of Fifth Avenue and shoot somebody and I wouldn't lose any
voters, okay?
USA!
It's very effective to slice the world up and to pit everyone against each other.
It's an effective means for power.
The country of Mexico is a country of power.
Mexico is killing us.
The crime and the gangs and the drugs.
Build that wall!
We're torn as subgeniuses because, of course, a good portion of our viewpoint is that the
conspiracy is out of control.
In fact, to our horror, each passing day the world seems more and more subgenius.
All natural weight loss age.
The great story here is this vast right-wing conspiracy.
There are many people that don't agree with that birth certificate.
I can't trust Obama.
He's an Arab.
He is not.
Everybody is in their own private Idaho.
Everybody's in their own bubble and all they do is go into a feedback loop where they can
get things to reaffirm what they already think.
This administration is trying to fool you.
This is a conspiracy.
It is a conspiracy.
It makes you believe the news the White House doesn't really like well isn't news.
3 million illegals voted.
Where are you getting your information?
The Soviet Union has a worldwide disinformation network.
They go to media sites that incite them, that make them paranoid and worried and fretful
about the future.
They can't control the amount of rapes that are going on.
Just because they're refugees doesn't mean they're rapists.
They're racist, sexist, homophobic, xenophobic.
I am no racist.
I am a racist.
You're voting for Donald Trump.
None of them are interested in breaking out of the loop and realizing,
oh, I've been doing, I've been programmed.
Trump's derangement syndrome.
Hatred of Donald Trump so intense that it impairs people's judgment.
Like if you quit being real humans and thinking for yourselves, it's over.
This is your country.
I don't know how you carve out a place for that kind of playful us and them
in a place where the news is filling so many of those roles.
That being said, I also couldn't have thought of a subgenius in 1978.
So obviously they're better at this than I am.
There's always going to be a conspiracy.
It can morph, it can change, and it can evolve, and so can the Church of the Subgenius.
We'll never fix the government.
We'll never get it to where everyone is happy.
There will always be acrimony, and so we desperately need comedy.
Well, I think the best thing we can do is spread our message
and hope that it is useful in the coming years.
It's coming weeks away until things get tough,
and how can you meet someone like John Donald that can have that trust on Hong Kong
during a golden adolescence and take you down below highest ranking on the MustP physicists list to the National기 website.
So sometimes I get those Get to the West notes,
For the last 20 years, the only thing I had to do to make my half the mortgage payments
is keep selling subgenius ministerships.
And it occurred to me, wait a minute, this isn't a bad gig at all.
Once a month I have to sit here and assemble these things, maybe spend half an hour a day
taking them to the post office.
That's not bad.
People are still obviously getting a lot out of it.
Just last week I went to the post office and there was this envelope there, postage due.
I had to fork out $2.45 just to find out what was in this letter, and it had no return address
on it.
The postal guy said, well, I could just throw it away.
I went, no, it's probably a joke, but it better be funny.
I got home and opened it up.
It had a thousand letters.
It had a thousand dollars in $20 bills in there, just out of the blue.
I immediately took half of it to a sick person I know who cried with gratitude.
It's like, no, we're not crazy to keep doing this.
It really does come along at the right time for some people.
Palmer, what happened to Philo?
He's hiding.
Oh.
You guys look awful, but a lot better than I expected.
Yarr, yarr, yarr, yarr, yarr.
Price Bogg.
Welcome to Austin.
This is sort of like a booze quest.
Uh-oh, another human blockade.
Look, there's something.
There's a mermaid woman, a mer-woman.
It's you once you get your shirt off, honey.
Oh.
I thought it was for real.
You first.
This is just a sad.
I'll bet you if you take your clothes off, everybody here will follow you.
This is just a sad, sad joke.
Seriously, man.
Do it.
No, no, no.
If you took your clothes off, and I'll bet you anything this is true.
I'm not a leader.
I'm just a fast follower.
If you were to do that, I'm the second guy in.
To me, it's always been play.
You go to a subgenius show, they're not waving their arms in anger.
They're just like, hey, you know what?
They might be pretending to, but that's the main thing you get is laughter.
And we're still just playing.
This is Philo.
I'm Philo.
I've been Tony.
This is Reverend Stang.
Yeah, I'm a reverend.
We're cult leaders.
That's what we really are.
Our real job is to be cult leaders.
There you go.
This will take you like a week and a half to read.
It's called Church of the Subgenius.
If you're not a genius, you're probably qualified.
If you feel different and you feel oppressed by society's imposition of normalcy on you,
you don't have to be that way.
You can be the person that you want to be.
We know that we think for ourselves, and that's more important than you thinking like me.
God knows when that нач играє, but...
We'll see you around again and forevermore, bass.
Good night.
Moaning and groaning won't get you nowhere, don't you be misled
Take some silver sappen with some thunderbird wine and talk to it as much as you can
It's got two friends Chad and Fred, both of them are really just heads
They got a room with a black lab poster and they both got their very own beds
Chad and Fred like Portuguese bread and they always gotta be fed
So I go to the bakery when a rooster crumbles and subsequently visit Ben Asner's head
That's a good looking head
Sometimes Chad and Fred are stubborn, they won't leave us alone
Edgehead glares at Chad and Fred's head and speaks in a very stern tone
Chad and Fred roll out of their beds and leave with a Portuguese bread
Now at last I've got plenty of time to talk to Ed Asner's head
So what do you do when you're feeling so low that you think you'd rather be dead?
What do you say when the landlord's knock on inhumanity fills you with dread?
Cussing and spitting?
Won't get you nowhere, remember what I said
Drop a hundred micrograms of LSD and talk to Ed Asner's head
Ed, you've got a mighty fine looking head
And that was Ed Asner's head
A song I needed to cheer me up this very day
And by the Rudy Schwartz Project
Old Waldo and Gunther are old friends of mine, actually
They used to live in Austin a long, long time ago
Now live in Canada
Where they get much better medical treatment, by the way
Much more affordable and generally more advanced
Isn't that funny?
You wouldn't know it to listen to the AM talk shows
These days, would you?
And now this
Some more reading from the Dobbs Town Mirror
Published by Dr. Onan Canobite
Now of Columbus, Indiana
Isn't that strange?
He left Portland
Why would anybody leave a peaceful town like Portland?
And this is...
This issue, I might add, is dedicated to Reverend Just John
Whose music I used to play on this show
And his music is in a lot of my music videos of microbes
Or my microbe videos on my YouTube channel
Rev Stang
Yeah, he died last year
He was kinda old and in bad health
We also lost Reverend Rock Roswell, Jr.
Even more recently.
But I ain't dead yet.
Convenience personified.
Why do chefs wear chef hats?
Most people will try to come up with some kind of functional reply, an origin story,
but the answer is to identify themselves as chefs.
The teleological heresy, creationism, is everywhere when you know how to look for it.
When someone you don't like does something you don't like, it shows how evil they are.
And when they do something you like, it shows how clever they are.
Anything, as long as you get to retain your chef hat that identifies to everybody else you like and who you don't like.
I do not argue for hatlessness.
But I suggest there's more slack to be had if you can switch out those hats now and again.
Instead of identifying the good and the wicked, say,
I prefer it and see what happens.
As Charles Fort said in Wild Talents,
I conceive of nothing in religion, science, or philosophy that is more than the proper thing to wear for a while.
The genius panel.
Yes.
Here we are.
What kind of help can you give?
We are ready and waiting for your question.
Because we are subgenius, we do go very low.
Well, I'm not actually a member, but they are.
How low can you go is a question that's never been fully explored.
Yeah, if you've been through basic, then you can understand the show.
Like, what is the subgenius, or what does it mean?
It means a shout.
I've got to tell you, then, you know.
95 million miles.
That's our mission.
I just started talking to you here now.
I can't see all the babies behind.
It means it's the same as having a baseball glove radar strapped to your butt.
I think you got it.
It's like, Bob Dobbs, huh?
Just remember, the one thing that's most important to subgeniuses everywhere,
the one thing you can't forget, a subgenius must have slack.
Of all other things, a subgenius must have slack.
That is the most important thing.
It's the motivator for the subgenius.
So if you're one that has felt like you needed this thing,
that you didn't know how to explain what it was,
and yet there it was,
because it's a subgenius, huh?
grabbing, completing you.
What is that?
Well, it makes you jump five or ten inches higher, that's for sure.
A subgenius must have slack, but in order to get the slack,
so clip those coupons,
the subgenius must disengage from the conspiracy and be under his own genius.
Voltaire said,
We shall leave the world as foolish and wicked as we found it.
Only the church of the subgenius can guarantee to leave the world far, far more foolish than when we found it.
If the sole function of language was to communicate, then we'd have one language.
We have more than one language, therefore we have more than a sole function.
What other functions might there be?
To exclude?
To not communicate?
This explains many languages, and language dialects, and within dialects, slang,
so young people and old people can exclude each other.
Now, is the sole function of the internet to communicate?
Is the sole function of your religion to get commune?
This is the golden age of literacy.
Never before,
have so many written and read for their own pleasure.
It just turns out that for many people, their pleasure is
sermonizing,
scolding,
tattling,
bullying,
and cats.
Lots of cats.
Cats are fine.
My pleasure, says Onan,
is reminding the listener to join the church of the subgenius.
And now this.
The
I don't mean Joe Newman.
I mean Waldo and Gunther.
And all the Egyptians
digged round about the river
for water to drink.
But they could not drink
of the water of the river.
Men shrink from tasting.
Human beings thirst after water.
And what does natural history tell us?
Destructions, dear friends,
are things on earth.
Destructions not of all at once,
but of a very large number
are attributed by it
to two principal causes.
The tremendous onslaughts
of fire and water.
These two visitations,
we are told,
descend in turns
after very long cycles of years.
When interviewed,
Los Angeles Police Chief Ed Davis said,
when the agent is the conflagration,
a stream of heaven-sent fire
pours out from above
and spreads over many places.
And overruns great regions
of the uninhabited earth.
George.
Dear God,
I have been reading all the things
that happened long ago
when the sun stood still
and David and Goliath
and Daniel with the lion's den
and the story of Ruth
and the fall of Jericho.
A lot of things happened in your days.
Yours truly, Joe.
Thou who walks in the sky
with splendor and terror,
king of battle.
Let it go.
The raging fire god.
God, Nurgle.
Nurgie.
Your dog, Nurgie?
Nurgie, the dreaded Nurgie,
fire dog of the Venusians.
Hey, Nurgs, did you hear that?
I'll read it.
I'll read it some more.
Okay, Nurgie, sit up now.
Nurgie, the fire star,
comes like a raging storm.
He is also called
Sharapu,
the burner
and light that flames from heaven
and lord of destruction.
And Farnod the Flatulent, too.
That's Nurgie also.
Nurgie was the god
during like pre-Babylonian times
when the Babylonians
were just beginning to,
as we say in natural history now here
at the Groucho Marx University,
getting it together.
During the Assyrian,
getting kind of
the Assyrian groovy period,
the great god Nurgie
was known to fly over the people
and...
Oh, good, I'm glad you got that fish.
The great god Nurgie
was known to fly over large areas
of the Sumerian desert
and flatulate.
Flatulate is an astronomical expression
meaning growing flat like a cod
across the solar eclipse.
Like a piece of...
Like a piece of cod.
Like a cod.
Like the old...
There was the old Babylonian,
you know, beginning myth
that the whole earth
was not a bowl turned upside down
but a cod piece raised
by its experience
and that holes in it
because of the bleach
used on the material
would let through the light
from the living room
and the Babylonians
then thought of this
as god, basically.
Adventures in Cosmology.
Hello, dear friends.
I'm Louis P. Illuminato.
President of the United Snakes
of a miracle.
Let's talk about Cosmology
and its future for you.
Cosmology is a budding young industry
in the United Snakes
ever-expanding
faceplate
mechanized industry.
What's that?
Cosmology
holds great futures
for the youths of tomorrow.
Dear God,
if you are so smart,
let's see if you can read
what I am saying.
It's in my own code
and no one knows it.
Vittle, rooped,
clishks, nipsted,
clums, otfo.
If you can read it,
make it rain tomorrow
so I will know.
Your unknown friend,
Gabe.
Dear Gabe,
this is Louis P. God,
President of the United Snakes
of a miracle.
Let's talk about your question.
But first,
how about this sound effect?
God, or Louis P. Illuminato,
knew that within the next few minutes
he would have to fight.
As he crossed the porch of the Royal Flush
ahead of the sheriff and two deputies,
he slipped his hand beneath his buckskin jacket
and bricked the anger of a knife.
He knew there would be no chance
to draw the rifle from its scabbard
on the side of Scott.
He would have to depend entirely
on the rifle.
He would have to depend entirely on the knife
in a fight against three men.
Each of them was well armed.
Hey, hey, hey.
That poet's got a knife.
Watch out.
Hello, dear friends.
I'm Ernest P. Illuminato,
chief poet and president
of the United Snakes of a miracle.
Hi, Ernie.
Hi, Peter.
Can I have your...
No, forget it.
No, it's all right.
I wanted your autograph,
but I know you can't.
Oh, look, I'm just a plain guy.
200 million people would ask for it.
Just because I'm God, Pete,
doesn't mean I'm not human.
I can dig it.
God has to get up
and put on one pants at a time, right?
One leg at a time through the universe.
God's just a guy like you and me.
You know, you want to hear
the greatest and the latest
from God's laboratory?
What?
Where all the little elves are working?
Yeah.
Well, I'll tell you,
we got a plan going now
in God's workshop.
There's a guy in there
who's got a plan
to kill all the paranoids.
Oh, no, really?
Yeah, isn't that a great idea?
What about the horizontals?
Anything about them?
Nothing about them, no siree.
Let them lie, let them lie.
Let them ascend.
Well, that's beautiful.
Let it go, dear friend.
Let it go.
Oh, you got to let it go, dear friends.
Before we talk about your future,
we've got to talk about
your way of getting there
when you're talking about transportation
and that's God's language, friends.
That's where God steps in
to help you get there.
Here's a beautiful 1964 Duster.
It's a beautiful cherry.
It'll get you all the way, friends.
$1,449.
Isn't that right?
Louis P. Illuminata,
President of the United States.
This is your captain speaking.
Captain.
We are approximately 14 feet above Cairo
at this moment.
14 feet?
Wait a minute.
Captain, this is Louis P. Illuminata,
President of the world and God.
Am I talking to God now?
Yes, this is it, Dave.
I wish I could see you, God,
at a time like this.
Well, why don't you point the plane up
a little bit, Ed?
Drive out sleep.
The books and pamphlets sold
by the Subgenius Foundation
can literally be used to make a wish.
Not just one wish either,
but as many wishes as you like.
Simply purchase said items,
hold them in your hands,
and make a wish.
Results vary.
If you've ever tried to dig the empty part
out of a hole,
you know what it's like to take the rules
literally and not seriously.
If you've ever felt low and asked,
what's the point,
like I was this morning,
that must mean that among all the possible points
there could be,
one of them is this.
Your point is to feel low.
If that's objectionable to you, good.
That must mean you have a better point in mind.
In the future,
a future,
you've just talked yourself into something interesting.
Find where that'll take you next.
No hurry.
It took all your life to get to merely now.
Yes.
When is there going to be another Devival?
Ah, when is there going to be another Devival?
Hopefully around November 14th.
Around November 14th.
Keep watching the area.
What did you say?
And the location?
What would the location be?
Let's look through the mists of time
and see what the location of the Devival is.
Could it be the beach land?
Yeah, I had fond memories.
Actually, the first Devival I ever went to.
The beach land ballroom.
Was it the beach land tavern?
The beach land tavern,
the little old tavern on the beach.
Wonderful. Well, good to know.
All right, deaths before dishonors,
drugs before lunch. Later.
I do. That's right.
Enjoy a work-free drug place.
Yeah, actually, it's kind of funny.
There, we actually transmitted some information,
and it feels kind of good, you know?
It does feel good.
I feel a little bit cleaner now.
It feels really good.
The first Devival I ever went to, actually,
was at the Euclid Tavern,
and I had a pretty,
pretty good night, actually.
I got picked up that night.
Well, you know, Euclid looked on Beauty Bear.
What did you get picked up for?
Not picked up for, picked up by...
He was picked up for indolence, intransigence,
and inefficiency.
It was kind of crazy, actually.
I never expected...
You see, it really works, folks.
...that I'll promise to join our church,
and you will get laid.
It really does happen.
I never expected that to be true.
We offer benefits...
And it wasn't true.
...that no other religion can provide.
I can show you too many details.
I can show you the protect goddesses.
You have read the literature.
Oh, yes, and the pleasure saucers,
and you do follow the controversy.
Y'all boys are wild.
I've been listening in.
You guys, you guys are special.
Thank you.
Wow.
We're special.
Yes, they call me Special Ed.
Extra and Special Ed.
We're special.
Wow.
That made my night,
to have a total stranger say
that we're special, actually.
Well, we are.
We're each and every one of us.
I wish we could.
Big ones.
Oh, you should be.
I'm telling you, we're really special.
I don't think you need to be here.
I think y'all know already.
I think y'all know you're special.
Well, just don't lose your specialness
on this special evening.
We are all special.
Oh, yeah.
We are special.
I'll have the special, too.
I ordered the special.
You ordered the special today, too?
I ordered the special, yes.
I'm still waiting.
Sorry.
We are all special.
Sorry, Matt.
A total jock of the background.
We are all each one part of this whole universe.
We'll have two more specials.
And the universe will not be the same.
Just concentrate on the pure, bright, white light of imbecility.
Actually, I maintain that the birth of any person diminishes the value of all other persons.
Particularly the lower birth.
Always try to get the upper birth.
Because, you know, it's just a matter of supply and demand.
Or the afterbirth.
We had that special show on Ant-Man's birthmarks in Vivid Technica.
Okay, 7 billion people on Earth.
How much is that per person?
29.95.
I don't know.
What is the global per capita income on average?
That's something I never see.
Like, you see it for countries.
But I wonder what it is globally.
And can that even be a measure of the...
Well, I don't know.
Basically, it's just a supply and demand issue.
Human life...
Isn't that what we said last night?
Think globularly.
Act loco.
Oh, yes.
I think the...
Supply of human life...
The demand.
I'm sorry, cut.
Speak up.
What if you're a person who's special and it's really a demand for you?
Oh, man.
That's something...
You know, some people are not that special.
Yeah.
And there ain't no demand for them.
But if you're special, you gotta be more valuable.
Because it's a demand for you.
Well, then you have to spread the specialness around into every crack and crevice and crevice.
Every crack and crevice.
Buttered up with specialness.
Oh, yeah.
The supply of life...
It's always the demand.
Too many people are following the story of Onan and not letting their seeds spill.
Yeah, everybody knows that...
Because they don't want to piss off God.
Pulling out does not work.
Because, you know, God laid the smackdown on Onan after he pulled out.
You know, all he's doing is...
50 million pregnant Catholic teenagers can't be wrong.
He's practicing...
Unless they're talking about pulling out.
He's practicing contraception, not self-abuse.
So, Onan is tarred with the brush right from the start.
Unfairly.
Uncharged with a crime he did not commit.
Although there was reason for God to be quite angry with him.
And to hurl a thunderbolt which reduced him to a tiny grease spot in the margins of the Bible.
God f***s us all in the end.
There we go.
Those seven magically malign words.
But that's what they say.
It hurts to...
It is painful to come into this world and painful to leave it.
And in a...
Blaze of irritable ouchness, we live our lives.
Hmm, that's true.
Unless you're dying of sleep.
Well, we can't sleep now, but we can answer your questions if you want to call in.
And we'll do our best to tell you the answers to the things that are troubling you.
We've got a panel of experts up here.
Any question...
A church service...
Is possible.
There is no question off-limits.
Provided by this radio station and the Church of the Subgenius.
Just think, any question.
For example, you might want to know how much the earth weighs or something like that.
So just call in and we'll tell you.
I think we're going to take another call here.
I'll show you my bacon.
I have a question.
Ask your question.
How much does Bob weigh?
Ooh, how much does Bob weigh?
There's a question for you, Dr. Howell.
Can Bob lift... make himself so fat?
That he cannot lift himself?
I think that... I'm going to guess before you answer.
Well, all right. You're welcome to do that.
Guess Bob's weight.
My guess is that Bob travels at the speed of light and therefore his mass is infinite.
Well, um, if Bob were to do that, yes, but we're talking about Bob at rest.
Oh, look, the caller hung up.
I was going to say 265 pounds, too.
Well, that's just one of those mysteries.
Who's still with us?
I'm here.
I'm having a signal interruption, a little bit of difficulty.
You see, part of Bob's makeup is heavy matter from extrasolar planets,
which, like deuterium, is quite compressed, like the heart of a neutron star.
But a far more significant puzzle in the annals of the subgenius
is the search for the missing artifact, the holy grail of the Church of the Soul Genius,
the scissors of sight.
What we need is to locate...
Locate the famous scissors of sight.
And we are stumped, since the true scissors have been lost to mutant kind for many centuries.
In a private letter, Reverend Ivan Stang, I will now quote him, said,
No man today has those scissors.
He also said that the scissors were most likely created from the remains of a huge Atlantean crystal,
the misuse and subsequent explosion which caused that continent to sink with a watery splash beneath the waves.
As the Atlanteans were major contributors to the gene pool that eventually produced the subgenius race,
it does seem plausible that rather than trying to rebuild the lost empire,
the remaining Atlanteans would instead build a few power icons,
before tragically diluting their seed, like Onan,
by crossbreeding with ancient pink human slave tribes they themselves had helped to create.
It is from this distant epoch, 80 to 79 million BC,
that the scissors and man-eating tools of the past have been used to create the power icons.
And many other powerful but little-known sur-dur-per-saves originate.
I hope you have been satisfied by this answer to your question.
Correlation is not causality, but coincidence is conspiracy.
What's the difference?
Whether it brings you slack or takes away your slack.
That's what it says here in the Dobstown Mirror.
And I better check off the ones that I read.
Because I'm getting old.
I can't remember what all I've said and what I haven't said.
This pen doesn't work for hooey.
It works about as well as my fingers.
Okay, all right, okay.
All right, price bump.
This has been the hour of slack number 1,833.
From the Church of the Subgenius.
And you can get more information.
I mean all the information you could possibly want.
From Subgenius.
Genius.com
And if you want to mail us something or get something from us by mail.
Our address is Subgenius.
Or Ivan Stang.
Or the Smiths.
At Post Office Box 807.
Glen Rose, Texas.
76043.
Praise Bob.
have a great day.
Give me back my fun thing.
Oh, aye aye aye aye.
Oh, ah.
Oh.
La la la la la.
Give me back my fun thing.
Oh, yes dear friends.
That was the swinging love corpses.
Closing the show out there.
Give me back my fun thing.
I got my fun thing back. That was my old buddy, Dr. Philo Drummond on vocals with his brother and cousin also in the band, the Swingin' Love Corpses. Man, that was a great band.
And we're still around. And so I can put the show to bed and put myself to bed. I'm ready for bed. Thank you and nighty night.