Ladies and gentlemen, this is for our Slack.
Before the sermon, a message concerning Bob Dobbs, Living Avatar of Slack, and Saint of Saints.
You have to love Bob.
He loves you, but you love Bob. You have to.
Or else what happens if you don't love Bob?
He'll kill you. He'll bob you out.
Though Christ was not our Savior, nor born on Christmas Day,
to save us all from atom bombs when we have gone astray.
Oh, tidings of trembling and fear, trembling and fear.
Oh, tidings of trembling and fear.
God love ye weary citizens, for it is such a shame
to think of cruel injustices all done in Jesus' name.
Remember when you go to church, believers,
what you blame.
Oh, tidings of trembling and fear, trembling and fear.
Oh, tidings of trembling and fear.
God help ye weary citizens, you've all been taken in
by priesthood's waxing rich and fat upon your fear of sin.
Though you may knock at heaven's door, they will not let you in.
Oh, tidings of trembling and fear, trembling and fear.
Oh, tidings of trembling and fear.
God save ye weary citizens, for this will make ye sick.
That Christ was just another Jew they nailed upon a stick.
He couldn't save himself, you know religion is a trick.
Oh, tidings of trembling and fear, trembling and fear.
Oh, tidings of trembling and fear.
God save ye weary citizens, you've all been taken in by priesthood's waxing rich and fat upon your fear of sin.
Was the St. Baphomet Neo-Pagan Reform-
no I'm sorry.
Something like that-
Let me say this right.
St. Baphomet Neo-Pagan Reformed Choir of Miskatonic University.
How young I sound, Friend-
It was gonna be an official Christmas show.
Yeah, God, I sound like a little child back then in the, back in them days.
Well.
When the promise was my show, when the atoms were placed up in a衣
friends, I, you know, I was, I was so depressed yesterday. And when I came out of it, I wrote a
wonderful rant about being depressed. And I was going to, I was going to read it to today on the
show, but then I got too depressed again. But then I remembered it's Christmas and everybody's
supposed to be depressed. And, um, and on top of that, I, it, it kind of got me off the hook
because that means that I could run the old Christmas special. Huh? Suddenly without warning.
Yes, dear friends, I'm saved because, um, because we do have, uh, a Christmas special that I can
always use chunks of, uh, like that last song. And we have this new wonderful Christmas music
from Ray Brunel and the Jethro's, an entire, uh, album of,
uh, nothing but insane Christmas music like this heard in the background. And, uh,
oh, let's just listen because it hurts so good.
Lundering through a winter fun land, dear friends. And, um, you know, what the heck,
what the heck? So it's Christmas time. It's, uh, we can, we all,
we can celebrate a religion that we don't believe in and, uh, and give presents to people we have
to give presents to. Uh, yes, isn't it? And we get to get together with our families and all our
family members, even those ones and all pretend to be happy and praise the birth of, uh, that first
Jesus guy.
What really went wrong? You know, cause you always have that thing in the back of your mind. Well,
gee, maybe did I screw up someplace along the line to cause this all to happen? I mean, you have to
bring home some evidence saying, Hey, folks, it wasn't my fault. Take a look at this picture.
You know, something happened back there.
I wasn't back there.
I am not responsible. Not for your problem, buddy. Your problem that causes you to tell me what all
my problems are. I'm not responsible. And if you try to make me feel like I am, then you can take
it and shove it where Bob Dobbs and his family don't care to look. Cause I didn't do it. I didn't
have anything to do with it. And I'm not going to feel guilty about it just cause you decided
somebody had to be blamed for something. No, sir, ma'am I'm on vacation. You know what I do when I'm
on vacation?
I work cause I'm tired of trying to work. I'm going to just work this time. I'm going to just say no to
play. I don't care who wants to play. If they've been my friend for 15 years, if I've been married
to him for 25 years, I don't care. I'm going to work cause that's my slack. And I just about had
a nervous breakdown over feeling guilty because I didn't play with everybody else enough.
I don't feel like you were the bad guy cause you wanted to work. Well, ironically enough, that may be
because you are a subgenius and the rest are pinks or else conspiracy dupes. It's the conspiracy that
said that work was supposed to be unpleasant and bad, but necessary because of the money. And it's
the conspiracy that said, oh, you aren't having fun or playing if you're working at what you were
born to do. No, you're only having fun if you're drinking and smoking dope or else at the very least
spending money and eating, uh,
whatever you want to call it.
I don't care if other people wait on you and laugh and real loud about all those other dumb people.
You're only having fun when you're wasting your time. Well, Bob, that stuff. And not only that,
but I'm going to do exactly whatever work I think needs to be done. How about them apples, huh?
I'm not going to do the work that you think will be good and sell and make the world better in
some small way. Or even what Bob says I do or what A&M says I do. No, I'm going to do exactly what I
think is going to be good and sell.
And make the world better in some small way or not. Or not. I have suffered way too many fools.
Way too gladly for way too long. And as a result of being such a sweet, nice guy,
I ended up with a whole buttload of critics whining that I didn't do enough for them.
And with myself all balled up in a corner of the garage this morning, all by myself screaming,
leave me alone. I hate you. I hate you. Leave me alone. Let me flee at the top of my lungs and
with only a few words left. I'm going to do exactly what I think is right. I'm going to do exactly what I think is right.
only the puzzled new guard dog to hear me.
And I, friends, I happened to have had an appointment
with a shrink in the afternoon
because several people who are definitely crazy
think I'm crazy and it takes one to know one.
And I told the shrink about how I was starting to feel
like I was in an airless box
with all six sides closing in at once.
And she said, well, maybe you're just going to have to say no
to some of these people.
And guess what?
I'm going to do just what the doctor said.
And I suggest you do too, my friend.
You really do know what's best for you.
And all those hundreds of nagging weenies and widgets
don't know Bob crap.
In fact, most of them don't even know what they want.
And that's why they're telling you what all you want.
And that's most people, I'm afraid.
Most people have not the slightest idea
of what they want to do next
and are probably better off letting the boss
and the shrink know what they want.
And they're not going to let the boss
and the spouse and the church
and the society run their lives for them.
But some of us not only have such a long list of things
that we want very much to do
so long that we know we can't possibly ever do them.
But we're also, believe it or not,
smart enough to make our own decisions.
I'm smart enough to decide right now
whether or not I'm going to go get drunk.
I could go get drunk right now.
And I might.
I could also decide not to.
but screw anybody who tries to tell me.
And that especially includes the Miller Beer Company
and the Reynolds Tobacco Company
and all those Republican drug cartels
with their damn so-called war on drugs.
If I want to OD on heroin, I will.
If I want to become a cop and beat up junkies, then I will.
If I want to screw some willing babe in the closet,
then perhaps I damn well will.
And if I get caught, then I'll take my lumps.
But no, I won't.
I shouldn't have to take any lumps.
The only people who are going to care
whether some willing babe and I go do it in the closet
are the ones that can't.
And because, friends, as crazy as I might be
and as dumb as I might be,
and I often feel like the dumbest, most naive,
redneck, unsophisticated, just-got-in-town, clumsy subgenius,
the most horrible, horrible aspect of all this is,
as screwed up as I am,
I really am still saner and smarter
than any of the humans,
and you may be, too.
Now, that is a really chilling thought, friends.
But not only must we stop trying to ignore that thought,
we have to start acting on it.
Or at least I do, or I really will go off my rocker.
So enough is enough.
Enough trying to be some armchair amateur's idea of good.
I went to the mental health professionals,
and they themselves agreed
that I am...
not insane,
everybody else is,
I am right to be ticked off,
and thousands of buttheads really are out to get me.
So once again, I say,
with as much feeling as I have ever said it in my life,
I can't say this on the radio,
but it's, you know, if they can't take a joke,
you know what to do, friends.
So I'm sure you'll understand if I don't happen to
respond to your email this vacation,
or do that thing with you that you wanted to do or whatever,
don't take it personally,
I did, and it doesn't pay.
Build your own ship.
We're now deep inside the brain cavity of Doug Smith.
As you can see all around you, they're sparking.
There was a short circuit.
The brain seems to have recovered.
There are sparking energy thoughts all around us.
Far more than the normal human brain.
But as we know...
Another misfire there.
We know Doug Smith is not a normal human.
No, and here inside the brain of Doug Smith,
we can observe some of the differences that make this man
a unique leader among humans.
And we can see that he's a very strong man.
Over here in this corner are the memory bands.
And over here is the main printout area.
This is the South Canada Radio Ministry.
Power of Land and Oil FX.
Praise Bob.
To be a good man.
Your source is not in the tank.
Your source is not in the bank.
Your source is above you.
In another dimension, sex, in another world.
Oh, my, how far it can go.
Well, that's a good long, long time.
Oh, sex, well, I had no intention.
Sex, not with nobody, girl.
Oh, I tried and I tried.
I will, I tried.
Oh, it's not with crazy men.
Oh, sex, well, I had no intention.
Sex, now in another dimension.
Oh, sex, well, I tried and I tried.
about
Don't look at me.
I put a down payment on a small red dwarf.
You've got suckered, man.
No, it's a really small one.
It's just like, you know, the size of a car.
So I was going to put it in the backyard.
Look, right.
Still, it's going to draw your entire house and most of your neighborhood right into it.
It's just going to be a slightly bigger red dwarf in a much smaller neighborhood.
Yeah, right.
Your neighborhood will essentially become the paint on the outside of that red dwarf.
And some of this will eventually suck the whole planet up.
Would it?
Or would it eventually?
I mean, it's only the size of a car.
I mean, we're not talking about a whole neutron star, right?
You're talking about it would still be hot.
A red dwarf is almost a little bit bigger than, like, you know, mass-wise than Jupiter.
It's like the smallest star you can create.
But one ounce of it weighs.
A ton.
No, no, that's a neutron.
Oh.
A neutron star.
One tablespoon weighs as much as the largest mountain on the Earth.
One tablespoon of neutron matter.
I've got, like, a gram of that hanging from my...
Well, I don't want to...
It's a trendy piercing thing.
Well, yeah, we used to snort it back in the disco days.
Snorting neutron star matter?
Yeah.
Oh, God, how could you see in the next day?
It seems like you'd be, you know, in the bathroom.
It would just be...
It would be so hard to keep.
Yeah, you'd almost have to wear lead diapers or something.
Yeah, very reinforced.
Well, it'd only take a little bit.
It's just like not even a match head full.
But a match head full weighs as much as, you know, a couple of semis.
Oh, yeah, at least.
Yeah, people don't...
We're not just jabbering inanely.
There are neutrons.
There are really such things as neutron stars out there in space that are collapsed.
Right.
Old stars that have all the...
Massive stars collapsing the size of, like, New York City.
Yeah, there's no...
What is it?
I guess they're...
All the forces.
They're all neutron, right?
They're just the energyless atom core.
Right.
They're all in together.
And the only thing keeping them from just collapsing down to nothing...
Nothing.
I think they're down to the last force there.
The weak nuclear force.
Yeah, they're just so tight.
They're so tight-packed.
Can't get nothing in there.
Add just a little more matter to it and it'll disappear.
Oh, yeah.
Dear friends, well, I bet if there...
I bet you could get in there if there was hair around it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Friends, I almost forgot it was Christmas.
But I have to give credit there for that ESO.
Wonderful Einstein Secret Orchestra song, sax.
Chaz Smith on keyboards.
Michelle George is the Hendrixian violin player.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave on guitar.
And Bob Mosick on drums.
Here is the address of Einstein Secret Orchestra,
who we also heard on that little radio clip afterwards.
ESO P.O. Box.
81555.
That's P.O. Box 81555.
Cleveland, Ohio.
Backwards, that's...
Y-hole DNA level C.
Zip code 44181.
44181.
And this in the background, of course, is the Jethro's from their Christmas album,
The Dark Side of the Christmas Tree.
And you can reach them at 212 and a half,
which looks sort of funny on paper.
212 and a half, Miller Avenue,
Hort's Mouth,
New Hampshire,
030,
3801.
I think that's right.
It's hard to read.
Jesus scribbled all over this CD.
And I don't know...
Merry Christmas, dear friends.
It's deep inside of all of our black holes and our black hearts.
We wish you happy holidays and Hanukkahs and Christmases and Kwanzas and, you know, whatever the heck you do.
Uh...
We might qualify.
The
story was rooted
in the
dyso
Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas...
I'm home for Christmas.
Walking in the winter wonderland.
Jingle bells, jingle bells, jingle bells, jingle bells, jingle bells.
What do you think?
Two, Santa's coming for you.
Three, four, you better lock your door.
Five, six, grab a crucifix.
Seven, eight, better stay up late.
Nine, ten, Santa's coming again!
Daddy, when's Santa be showing with his big red sack?
Five, six, jingle bells, jingle bells, jingle bells, jingle bells.
Way up north where the cold wind blows.
There's a little old man that you all know.
He's been busting his nuts the whole damn year.
Stamping on tools, riding his deer.
Come prance up, open it, say, oh, what a great book.
It's that time of year, guess I've got all the luck.
And you, Mrs. Claus, are you?
You ready at last?
I know the pole is ready.
I'm bumped up with gas.
It's Christmas time, it's my time of year.
It's your sweet boys cooking, let's get into gear.
Santa's red sack is packed and he's ready to roll.
The long-darned women's from their heads to their toes.
Time to pack up the sled, make that be trick.
No time to complain, don't give me no less.
They're counting on me.
It's Christmas time, deliver my load.
If I don't, it's a crime.
Do the corn on the field.
I'm flying my sled.
Don't need no radar, I'm using my head.
To direct my nose to your shoes.
From my ticket to your fancy till the morning come.
Christmas time, it's my time of year.
It's your sweet boys cooking, let's get into gear.
It's Christmas time, it's my time of year.
I come down to Cheapman just once a year with my big red sack.
It's not a full up year, I'm gonna bring all the women lots of Christmas cheer.
Load it in, ready, say, it's Christmas here.
This is the story of old Saint Nick.
With his big red sack and his candy stick.
Flying back home with his beard so white.
He's licking that boom tang all Christmas.
Christmas time, it's my time of year.
It's your sweet boys cooking, let's get into gear.
Said his red sack is back in hisensitive form.
Gonna love them women from the head to the toe.
Christmas time, it's my time of year.
It's Christmas time, it's my time of year.
guitar solo
Dear friends, I don't know who this is.
I guess it sounds like Ventures.
It's from whatever old Christmas subgenius show.
The old Christmas subgenius show.
I guess this is the only new one in forever.
Forever?
For ever?
For ever and a day.
There's some more Jethro's in the background.
Frosty the Snowplow.
This is called.
Oh, I was going to give credit.
Santa's Big Red Sack was the swinging erudites.
Brother Cleve Duncan and the great Dr. Cruel on vocals there.
Before that, Zandy and Civet with their little Santa Claus thing.
And let's just listen.
препят nailurgy
yell
ballroom
string
drum
vocal
a groovy little song
loud będziemy
Holsters, Mithras won his fight.
From now on, the days are longer than the nights.
¶¶
Of the battle of the roses and the war
Of the broken home
I got busted for drinking while begging
Carrying a weapon under my coat
And I trusted for all the people
And now I am a pirate on the bad dream coast
I'm alone
And now I'm not a starlet
Cause I am a man
Without a country
I'm a boy
Without a home
I'm a casualty of the battle of the roses and the war
Of the broken home
guitar solo
Oh, I see land
Oh, divided down the middle
And the sides are divided and divided again
I see so
Many people lonely
Love or hate
And love is all I see
Love or friend against friend
Now I'm alone
I'm alone
And now I'm never going home
I am a man
Without a country
And I'm a boy
Without a home
I'm a casualty of the battle of the roses and the war
Of the broken home
I believe you ​​reck in my heart
Of all of the troubles
So far for all nights
To me with God
I love you
Afrid
acompaña
Asmilan
As faço
In this life
Gujarat
Thank you.
Merry Christmas.
I don't usually do that.
Play rock and roll DJ.
I don't feel like that little children ought to be,
have to be exposed to all that.
Then was the Rainmakers.
Battle of the Roses from Good News and the Bad News.
And in my ways, Frank Marino, Mahogany Rush.
Little drummer boy.
No dang sign.
Jimi Hendrix.
And I believe Joe Satriani.
Merry Christmas.
You're spending an evening at home with your family.
Suddenly, without warning...
a сожалению.
Thank you for watchinginger.gsm
We'll talk soon.
¶¶
Well, I said I wasn't going to sing,
but I have to give the post office box of Bob, friends.
Sometimes we forget what Christmas is all about.
It's about Bob, of course.
I mean, did Santa?
Blow X day for your sins, and God only knows what else.
That's Bob, friends, at post office box 140306
in beautiful Dallas, Texas.
75214.
I'm going to give that number again.
That's Bob at post office box.
140306, Dallas, Texas.
75214.
Ah, yes.
And this is the Jethro's in the background.
We gave their address earlier.
212 and a half Miller Avenue, Portsmouth, New Hampshire.
03801.
And, uh, it's the holiday times.
Well, I guess I've probably got an old hour of slack
full of holiday music.
I'm going to have to get out of here to raise us up
out of this sad, sad, happy, wonderful situation.
So let's have at it, I guess.
It's He-Bomb.
Hey, kids, you can help the mighty subgenius race
overthrow the evil normals with new Bob Dobbs action figure
with rocket pilot.
What I wouldn't do.
From Bob Dobbs.
Get new more chocolatey pebbles from you.
No, ooh.
I'm a chocolate space cadet.
Life support system down to zero. Cocoa.
Feeling spacey.
I have some of my new cocoa pebbles.
Now so chocolatey.
Mm, smells cocoa-licious.
Basically collectible.
Hey!
Smell that.
Oh, my God.
That's serious.
That's delicious.
Well, friends, what do you think?
Is it the nativity of Santa Claus that we're trying to celebrate here,
or is it...
Go, but so what?
The horrible death of the Santa Bob, the Santai Bob,
as he's been referred to in some early pre-scriptures.
So separate.
New.
R2-D2, we wish you a merry Christmas.
R2-D2, we love you, it's true.
We hope our little message gets to you.
We look up at the winter star.
We know that's where you are.
Our chimney's big and round, so you can come right down.
And if our wish comes true, we'll spend Christmas Eve with you.
Our hearts will sing with glee as we decorate the Christmas tree.
R2-D2, we wish you a merry Christmas.
R2-D2, we love you, it's true.
R2-
So separate.
New from Tonka.
Now, you are in my evil clutches, Bob.
I'll use this MTV bombardment to turn you normal.
Shut up, pink boy.
No way.
I'll never sell out to the conspiracy.
Taste a little of my rocket pipe, alien tool.
I want to dance.
Bob Dobbs comes with rockets, pipe, head launcher,
Janeer device, all Yaka-tisma, fighting Jesus,
and other action figures sold separately.
Some assembly required, batteries not included.
This toy falls apart in three days.
He-Bob!
And the bastards of the universe.
Too much is always better than not enough.
From Bob Dobbs.
Gorgeous.
We girls can blow from head to toe.
Like Barbie.
From Star Wars.
Story of my crazy life.
And casual dra awful!
Huh?
What's that?
Is thiske.
Make my pursing friends, all of you.
I bet that firms havin' tell ya!
She's pefect.
Bye.
I'm sure driving is hard.
Keep walking all out.
Say hi!
I need mean days so I can get some broad time.
What?
Say goodbye!
Why?!
We go signin' up at your house.
We'll be right back.