How'd he turn you on?
We were talking about tea.
How the kick wore off.
And he said there was something else.
Something that had a real jolt.
The Self-Genius Power of Swag.
Never got so sick in my life.
Thought I was gonna die.
You're a big talker, aren't you, son?
When you're just taking a little drop, kid.
They receive punishment as prescribed by law.
Putin said PR news would be excessive.
Putin says he's holding the remains of people earning over a million dollars a year.
A federal judge released dozens of wild animals from his personal menagerie to protect the public.
U.S. District George said there's no constitutional right to own dangerous PR news.
The
I'll try to mile so as not to walk on foot.
I am a human being of the first goddamn order.
I am too intense to die.
For I speak only the fucking truth.
I am a human being of the first goddamn order.
My imagination is a fucking cancer.
And I'll park it before it parks me.
I think backwards.
I do it for fun.
I cook and eat my dead.
I swam up a human triangle and didn't get wet.
I kidnap the future.
I'm ransomed into the past.
I wait time.
Wait up for me.
I'll live forever and remember it afterwards.
Yes, I am the power of the future.
I am the flower of hell county.
Gimme one word.
I'm a man.
Man of a million.
They say a godzillion is the highest.
Well, there is.
Well, by god.
I count to a godzillion and one.
I weigh six hundred and sixty six pounds.
Zero gravity
Come and get me
I told Jesus I wouldn't go to church
And he shook my head
I have my own personal saviors
I change them every hour
I don't give a fuck if there's laugh after death
I don't wanna know if there's even any fucking slack after death
I am a goddamn visionary
I see the future and the past
In comic books and wine bottles
I paint my jeans
I riddle my DNA
With the force of my mighty will
I steer my own goddamn adventure
Give me slack
That was The Brag of the Subgenius by yours truly
performed by mythical burrowing animals
who I suspect might go by other names.
They may even be famous.
It's from one of our Bob Songs CDs of yore.
Before that, collages by Mr. Fernandanende.
The more.
And this is Hour of Slack number 1403.
And I'm recording this part of the credits
in my son's garage in Los Angeles.
But, friends, this is an Hour of Slack
that's really a puzzling evidence show.
Yeah, but we're gonna pretend like it's not, right?
No, it's really, it's obviously a puzzling evidence show.
There's no way you could fake that.
True.
Except that it's all fake to begin with.
But, yeah, this is the only part
that's really the Hour of Slack.
This is the intro for the puzzling evidence show
that's gonna replace some Hour of Slack
somewhere in the...
Hour of Slack number...
Yeah, this is Hour of Slack number 14...
Brought to you on station...
We've got unexpected special guest here,
Pope S. Lilith.
Hi!
In from Seattle.
Yeah.
And, uh...
And who else?
Dr. Howland puzzling and...
Dr. Drummond and that's...
And the sound effects and...
And that old...
K-Rob, okay, if we...
And if this is the intro for the last week's show...
Oh, no, we can't.
K-Rob was last week.
Yeah.
So I've already said Lil, so I can't...
420 guy is here, but he's always here.
It's that 420 guy.
Yeah, that's him.
I thought 420 guy was just a caller.
No, no.
Oh, okay.
I gotta sit down.
Okay.
I'm gonna go sit down.
I gotta get warm.
I'm gonna go get some water first.
Please stand on the retinal scan imaging security pad.
Eyes forward, please.
RSI security scan in progress.
Don't move.
Retinal scan imaging for access.
RSI system engaged.
Scanning.
Your authorization code...
Verified.
Access granted.
Everything is complete.
There is more than one kind of freedom.
In the days of anarchy, it was freedom.
Now you're being given freedom from...
Bustard!
Whatever you imagined has made Ryu before you.
I'm going to give you...
All the games that you need.
One in a million.
Come on.
That's it.
What are you doing here anyway?
What good is all this equipment?
I thought you reported lots of information.
Discretion is advised for this feature presentation.
We are dealing in an area of uncertainty.
An area where there are no rules, contradictory laws, and no clear social conditions.
There are no common sense as to what should be done.
Decisions about life and death.
I will kill you now.
Luke, I am your father.
Now!
Luke.
I am your father.
Luke, you must join me.
Help me, help me.
What is too bad you can't smoke and hear?
I know good health and insight.
You will die!
Wanna help me with black chocolate milk resultados?
Here we are.
What?
Are you looking at the fire?
Get an amplifier into my car.
I was just losing it.
Need more protection.
From the ꞎz discipline?
Yes.
I know that Mr. Knifeman.
Yes, That's my man.
Now, I will get this out of the loop.
Yep. It is the show again.
It's all different this time.
That's how the things used to be in the church in the 70s.
Not anymore. Now that we got Dr. Howell,
we got the Oberman, we got Ivan Stang,
and we got...
From up in Seattle.
The Popus of Seattle.
Lilith and yourself.
Yes, Lilith is here.
Puzzling evidence.
Did you really just play half an hour
of some old talk tape from me to you?
Because that's why I don't do Facebook.
I have no idea what that means,
but we're talking about loss of Facebook.
That's what he did on Facebook.
It won't be on an hour of Slack.
I'm sorry about that.
It'll be on the larger arc of Puzzling Evidence.
But that's the Puzzling Evidence show archive.
And that's a great piece of history.
That's right.
That's wonderful stuff.
You're not supposed to like it.
Oh, well, good.
The people who study subgenius.
What was so terrible about it, Reverend Stang?
It was baby Reverend Stang
back when I cared about everything,
back when I cared about Bob.
I think I heard myself on there.
They don't care about Bob.
Don't care, don't care, don't care, don't care.
How right they were.
They don't care about Bob.
But Reverend Stang,
all the little secrets,
the little secrets,
Bob, bless him,
ought to have a chance
to get in touch with the friendly Stang
as well as the scolding, stormy Stang.
Oh, I'm sure I'll go into character at some point.
But by gobs, you know...
You don't have to do it anymore.
Just use these priceless archival tapes.
They'll never know the difference.
That's right.
I went on this vacation
and I was free from Bob, per force,
sort of involuntary slack.
And why it feels good.
Damn it.
Yes, it does.
It feels good to be free of Bob.
Why, I've...
I've been answering...
I've been filling orders dutifully.
Luckily, there've hardly been any at all.
And I even cranked out
an edited all X-rated internet show
earlier today
over the last several weeks.
And really, it went out for broadcast?
No.
It's an internet-only hour of slack
number 1,000, 4,000, 0.5.
Only on the internet.
X, X, X.
Yes, now that makes it more clear.
It has a lot of dirty words in it.
Thanks to you, Dr. Philodromo.
Seven dirty words.
For man first degree.
The seven deadliest words of Christ,
plus a few more.
It has the seven seals.
The seals on Dave's car,
that sports team called the seals.
The seals that are brutally murdered.
Oh, that was last week.
The seals that you blew out.
The San Francisco seals
on Seal Rock.
That wasn't my show.
That was Chaz's show on this show.
It gets confusing.
Have you ever noticed that?
Yeah.
That it gets confusing?
It does.
Confusion to your enemies.
Confound their politics.
Frustrate their knavish tricks.
It certainly does.
Yeah, but it's confusing to me.
Not my enemy.
But that's okay.
Well, maybe then they'll be even more confused.
Because you've been
reacting to that confusion
since about the sixth grade.
His success is passion,
joy, and blowing his own horn.
I haven't forgotten a single slight
from sixth grade.
All those times your young, proud spirit
was slapped down
by an uncaring world.
Mrs. Reed from first grade?
She'll face me on next day.
Mrs. Darden from fifth grade?
Oh, yeah.
She'll be at the judge's meeting.
What did these women do, Reverend Stang?
Mrs. Reed made me...
made me eat a pimento cheese sandwich
in front of everyone in the cafeteria
because I wasn't eating my government-issued
pimento cheese sandwich.
And to this day, I cannot eat them.
Being forced to eat that jelly donut
while the rest of the platoon exercise.
Mrs. Reed was fired the next year.
Not for that infraction.
And I'm sure she's dead now,
but that won't stop me from resurrecting her
and torturing her and making her eat
something like a pimento cheese sandwich.
Just as in the case of...
Right in front of everybody.
Charlie made her.
I foam.
I certainly would.
Yeah, the foam pimento.
If you can collect all her ashes...
And oddly enough...
...in certain thaumaturgic practices
affect the palingenesis.
Due to Stockholm syndrome,
I remembered Mrs. Reed as a wonderful teacher.
Restore her from her ashes.
Yeah, she was married to Oliver Reed.
She was...
Well, that was short-lived.
Yeah.
Ran off to England.
She realized...
They went to Reed College.
She realized he liked sex and that was that.
All she likes is pimento.
Reed Richards.
Pimento.
That's like the worst thing in the world.
Yes, they...
They read Richards, uh, day and night.
Baked the trap with nice cheese.
Only this time, the bait's going to be fat cheese.
Only this time, the bait's going to be gone.
Mmm.
We return in just a moment.
A big morning's work in the defense classroom
certainly does whet up a fella's appetite.
Yes, mother, dad, and you young buckaroos,
you'll put your...
party okay on your sandwiches with delicious North Dorf bread.
And on top of that, more delicious North Dorf bread
made with pure dextrous energy foods.
Oh, boy.
Believe me, North Dorf bread has such grand, smooth, delicious nerves
and fresh cornrows.
Yes, North Dorf bread is made with special lunch food.
So, ladies, make North Dorf bread.
Yes, for goodness sake, make delicious North Dorf bread.
Yes, make fresh and tasty North Dorf bread.
Tomorrow, tomorrow, sure.
Oh, boy, you'll like it.
And don't forget it's been judged by baking experts.
Yes.
I can handle this.
Well, maybe you can handle this too.
Bye, that green-tailed bobcat.
Mmm.
Oh.
Oh, little beaver, I...
I don't know how to thank you.
Oh.
Now, then I've had other teachers that I remember that will be made into queens when X-Day comes.
Like Mrs. Neendorf, my fourth grade teacher.
Oh, yeah, she was the nice one with hair on her chest.
Man, she was everything a little weirdo could ask for in a teacher.
That's Mrs. Dennis for me.
She had a thatch sweater woven into her chest hair.
Not only did she not take away my comic books,
she encouraged me to draw them,
and she even showed me how to make a ditto copy of them.
The only reason I have any comic books from elementary school
is because Mrs. Neendorf mailed them to me about ten years ago.
She had kept a few.
She wrote to me and said,
I saw you in the newspaper.
I'm so glad to see that you've done well.
And I'm a crazy weirdo myself.
I'm a big Star Trek nut, and I go to Star Trek conventions all dressed up all the time.
That's very cool.
And she sent you your comic books?
She sent me my comic books.
I have them.
I had not seen any of that derivative crappy artwork since fourth grade.
Wow.
That's a true teacher.
I threw away my own comics when I was 12.
I threw away everything I'd drawn because I had vowed to become normal when we moved to Dallas.
Boy, did that not work.
Isn't that sad?
I threw away my comics.
I burned them.
I went out in the alley.
As soon as we got to Dallas, the kids here in Dallas,
they don't know I'm a weirdo like the kids in Fort Worth.
So I'm going to burn my comic books symbolically,
and I'm going to be normal and get laid.
I was 12.
I was born in Dallas.
That's cool.
He was 12 when he started thinking about getting laid.
Well, but see, you moved to Seattle where you could say,
they don't know me.
In Seattle, I can be normal.
Oh, wait.
No, it's the other way around for you.
More like just to be me, and that was actually kind of awesome.
Because I would have to remain.
I would have to remain Reverend Sheldon if I stayed in Dallas.
Right.
As it appears in the first subgenius video.
My kids.
Reverend Sheldon?
Yeah, with all of the pamphlets filling the house.
By the way, by the way, I found out that 22 years ago,
last Saturday night was the anniversary of me first doing a subgenius revival,
preaching at a subgenius revival.
Where was that?
It was called the Big Slack Attack.
It was an anniversary.
It was an anti-stang revival.
Really?
Yes.
Yeah.
Actually, it was an intentional anti-stang revival.
No stang, you're not allowed.
Well, I had dumped Buck Naked.
He actually didn't talk that much trash about you or anything like that.
I had dumped Buck.
I told Buck Naked I didn't want to do shows with him.
He could do whatever he wanted.
As far as minus stang divivals, it wasn't all that terrible.
It was probably 1980.
It would have been 86 or so.
Uh-huh.
87 maybe.
When was the Chicago Divival?
Which one?
There was one in 83.
The one where, yeah, where Sternow was bonked in the head.
Oh, are you talking about the World Subgenius Convention?
World Subcon.
Oh, right.
Yeah, that was 83 in Chicago.
The only reason that Pope Florist didn't lose his behind on that was because the Radisson Hotel,
changed owners right after that, and they never billed him.
Wow.
Otherwise, he would have been, you know, financially ruined.
That's how slack works, folks.
Uh-huh.
I drew a drawing of a tree that had faces and hands all over it.
I guess I was influenced by the Poultry Guys series.
Poultry Guys.
Yeah, I remember this.
The second or third one had that tree-looking, weird-looking thing made out of all those people and those arms and whatnot.
So I drew this drawing of a tree with these faces, arms.
Philo guys.
Scary one.
Poultry Guys make very good fertilizer for trees.
It's expensive.
Poultry Guys make up the principal type of spontaneous material manifestation.
Wow.
Yes, and it was really cool.
She said, remember this?
And that's all it said.
She died in a car accident, actually.
Just after that?
What's that?
It was nice of her to give you the thing back before that happened.
Yeah, you could say I was a teacher's pet.
I was one of her favorites.
I used to go after long-
Never pet the teacher.
I used to go out of the way to say hi to her and stuff at the school, so.
So the other kids didn't like you?
No, it was all that ectoplasm.
All that ectoplasm.
Oh, there's that music again.
Yeah.
All I can say is, can you guys help me find my scanner?
Although it's awfully dark in here.
Scanner's a living thing.
Nope.
Is it a flatbed or is it for eggs or slides?
We cannot help you find your scanner.
I just had that, too.
I just had that movie for sound bites and I turned it back in at Netflix.
If you call Homeland Security, they'll be able to help you.
Hey, you guys.
They know where your scanner is.
I think I know where your scanner is.
This is kind of a historic show to me because Homeland Security is now all over the station.
Yeah.
Everywhere you go in this station, there's little domes.
Now, I'm sure they're all props that don't really work.
Yeah, probably so.
Yeah, we went through a sea change of adaptation tonight.
That's right.
Once again.
Yeah.
It happens many times.
Instead of rocking away, we had to shuffle away.
Yeah, we shuffled away.
We had to cringe and hide and firmly cringe and hid.
Because we're of the generation now that said, let's be free.
Right.
Then that was that.
Yeah, let's be free.
And then they invented Homeland Security.
Yeah, let's be free, Rose.
Hey, not only that, but international postage rates went up almost 50%.
Yeah, it's 46 cents for a first class stamp now.
That's not a big deal.
How about U.S. postcard rates?
33 cents.
33 is a postcard now?
Yeah.
Mailing a Salvation from the United States to anywhere overseas went from $10.14 to $14.90.
$15.
Holy cow.
Alexander the Great had conquered the Nobel world when he was 33.
I've got two orders from Australia.
I'm going to either lose money on or have to beg them to send me another.
He sat down and wept.
Five bucks.
They're trying to get us to the moon.
I've done it all.
It's a conspiracy.
We'll stop it.
Nothing.
Nothing, I tell you.
They will raise the postage rates just to foil the sub-geniuses.
And then what do they do once you get all smoked out?
What happens?
Well, they don't smoke you out when they throw the smoke bomb in.
Your house catches on fire and you burn up.
That's called Koreshin you.
I mean, if they upped the postal rates, I took a course in that.
Koreshin.
The post office department, which is one of the more abysmal houses in the world, was
functions of the U.S. government,
ups their rates, and that smokes out all the cults?
Well, the cults
can't absorb it, that kind of cost
anymore. They're going to have to cut some workers out.
So the cults become like the little potato people in
dissent? They're little potato
people. Well, a lot of them were already
like the little potato people.
They're little potato families.
They're the
tiny spud men.
We call them tater heads.
Ireland and elves in England.
They're kids we call tater toms.
Some smirkers in Australia.
When Stang is on the show.
Oh, no!
Why, when Stang
is on the show, it's just the same
as if some utterly insignificant
negligible person were on the show.
We're so democratic
that we treat Ivan
Stang like we
treat Joe Lunchpain.
Would you please get some better toilet
paper, boys?
It's really rough.
Right away, Chief.
Wobbly, bring him back.
Yeah, bring Wobbly back.
He's asleep.
You mean the industrial workers of the world, son?
Yeah, these are very, this is KPFA
and they're very, people are very, very,
very, very, very, very...
They're pro-labour.
Why don't you come out and say it?
They support the union.
It gives you two hours...
We taste like blueberry and strawberry.
I'll have a blueberry and strawberry.
...energy suppository,
which will make me fly through the rest
of the evening. That's what they do at the first part
of the show. We're very, very...
They do it on camera now. You have to. They see
everything.
We're all watching you now.
We're doing it now.
Who's this we?
Do you have a mouse in your pocket
or something?
The horrible thing is the new photographer.
What is this we?
We, we.
She's not here right now.
No, no, no.
We is me.
We is...
We is not thee.
We is Princess We.
We is...
Many moons ago
In a far-off land
Called Ohio
A space princess
Roamed the grounds
Of a campground
Called Wisteria
Spreading light and love
Wherever she goes
She's the one
Who's going to be
The queen of the world
Because everybody knows how
And loves her
Sweetness of night
All that is good
All that is right
A space princess
The birds they sang
When she was born
A space princess
And the fairies rang out
With laughter when she landed
A space princess
A blessing on this planet
You know, I was wondering, Rev Stang, what happens when all the bobbies go to Ex Day and they go to the Saucers and who gets all their stuff they left behind?
Who cares?
You can get anything.
You might get their stuff.
Their stuff isn't worth a dollar.
The key thing to X-Day is that you don't have to leave it behind.
You can take it with you.
Not only can you take all your stuff, you can take all the pink stuff.
And, indeed, I say it again, I've got dibs on the Grand Canyon, boys.
But you don't have to take it with you because just think,
when you get on the ships, there'll be comic book collections
that are much better than the one that you had.
Right, you can have your real one and your pink rival's real ones,
plus better ones.
All waiting for you in your cabin when you get on the ship.
Every issue of Famous Monsters, not on disc.
Pristine copies.
The smelling like they just came off the rack at Mason's Hobby Lobby.
I've got them, but not in that good condition.
Same here.
Well, you won't need them anymore, Dr. Howell.
You can burn those Famous Monsters.
Never.
You're burned.
You're waiting next to your bed in your pleasure saucer control room.
You'll have your own stack of pristine Famous Monsters of film.
Now, you know, some people would be fantasizing in terms of fast cars
and beautiful, beloved things of the other sex or whatever desire.
Don't forget, even though this...
And here we're talking about comic books and monster magazines.
Well, even though the spaceship is large...
But those are wholly object.
There's only a three-quarter mile racetrack inside.
You won't be able to really open up like you would in the NASCAR arena.
Must you really run your infernal internal combustion engines on the spaceship?
The evidence's saucer will be completely filled with battleships and...
Oh, he's got helicopters and things in there.
Yeah, every kind of military hardware.
That's true.
I'm going to go get Oswald's body, JFK's body, Goldwater's body, Nixon's body, all the presidents from...
What about Mr. Body?
How about Houdini?
Mr. Body's going to fix my UFO, the dents and the paint jobs.
You mean?
Fred Houdini.
Yeah, Mr. Body.
And Mr. Peabody.
Tink, tink, tink, tink.
And the mermaid.
And Mr. Peabody.
Actually, it's one of the things I'd like to do while I'm here is I've got a UFO that I want to take a picture of.
The queen of UFOs.
UFO.
And the big UFO will be in the foreground in the fake picture.
And the little...
From outer space.
We'll just see about that.
We'll just see about outer space.
Outer space.
We will.
Yeah, we.
Sure.
We will.
Did you hear about the big asteroid crash in the Soviet, I mean, in Russia?
No.
It blew it right out of the sky.
It came in near Moscow.
It was destroyed in an airburst, but it broke windows and knocked down spaces.
It broke wind?
Therefore...
In the sky?
No, it broke windows eight.
Or they shot down the UFO.
Ruined the whole software pattern.
Those are the only two options being given by the news media so far.
And what about that asteroid that's not going to destroy the Earth?
It's coming incredibly.
It's incredibly close.
22,000 kilometers.
It's very, very near.
But it's nothing to worry about.
They just thought they'd mention it.
Just, you know, sniff it.
I thought you guys were working the line that because people bought enough memberships,
that's why it's not smashing into Earth.
Well, we'll say that right up to the time it does.
No, no.
If they buy enough memberships, it will smash into Earth.
So, spend, spend, spend.
Help bring on the interview.
This is not a call to action.
This is a satirical statement.
Yes, not to be given credence in the final court.
And that phone number we can't bring in is completely fake.
Theoretically, how much money would it take to make the comet hit Earth?
Well, you know, we won't find out until we get there.
Well, no.
We could, theoretically, we could calculate.
Hang on.
I'm going to get my calculator out.
I'm going to make some projections.
I'm going to extrapolate some of these algorithms out into the future.
Make sure to carry the one.
I'm going to carry the one.
I'm going to multiply infinity times this special subgenius algorithm.
And he's going to do it.
To get the answer.
All the way to the other side of the...
Hang on a minute.
I wish I had...
You can't jerry-rig this.
I wish I had my calculator sounds that you could hear right now.
My calculator won't even work.
Instead, you just have to listen to pocket protector sounds.
I'm going to pull...
This calculator is so old, it still has a one-armed bandit on it.
I have to crank the stamp.
He's the operator with his pocket calculator.
To blow up like it's supposed to.
Yes, cramp.
Yes, tramp.
Me, I'm cramping.
Me.
Well, I...
Hang on a minute.
Hang on.
I'm carrying my one.
It's really a heavy one, though.
It's a heavy load.
And listen, we're calculating how much money the church needs to raise
to cause the asteroid to smash into the planet Earth and...
Recalculating.
...replicate what happened.
Okay, just a second.
The answer is going to...
We'll be here in about three...
Less than two minutes now.
Only $35?
We only need one more $35 membership?
Recalculating.
Quiet.
That means if one person...
One person out there were to fall for it...
In one half mile.
I'm pushing the button.
My golly, we could destroy the Earth.
Uh-oh.
The calculator is not responding.
It's not responding to...
Although, if it was one person in China, that doesn't really help you, right?
I think it's going to go...
$150 to send them anything.
The calculator is going into cardiac arrest.
I'm going to have to perform...
That explains that hostage, right?
I'm going to have to perform cardiac pulmonary resuscitation.
In one quarter mile...
Turn.
Turn left on Red Rock Road.
Uh-oh.
It's flatlining.
The calculator has flatlined.
The calculator is...
Dr. Hal, have you turned?
No.
Wait a minute.
Here it is.
No, wait.
It's come back.
It's come back with an answer.
Oh, much better.
Here it is.
At Red Rock Road...
We have the answer.
This is how much money it's going to take to bring about the end of the world.
All we need is a few more contributions to make up the one zillion dollars.
Recalculating.
One zillion.
One zillion is just past a trillion.
One zillion dollars and 53 cents.
That's with inflation?
At Washington Boulevard...
That is with inflation.
I'm going to round up and just say one zillion and one dollars.
And point to the left.
Breakout marker rejoin Red Rock Road and turn left.
And it just pumps it up.
And point to the left.
Yeah, we'll round up that last dollar.
At 53 mile marker.
But I've only got a couple million and I need the world to end.
And now...
Then donate to the...
Are you sad because the world won't end and you only have a couple million to help bring it about?
Well, you should send $35 somewhere fast now.
And just throw it somewhere.
If you can't get it out of your hands, just force it.
Take your pockets off.
Make sure that you don't have a special place to put that $35.
That's all right.
You're going to have some money soon.
Perhaps an envelope would help.
With a stamp.
That big envelope will come.
Just make sure it's a 46 cent stamp now.
Watch for our prize patrol and our annoying flashing neon sign in your neighborhood.
We could have a forever more stamp.
I'm Ralph Snell of the Super Sweepstakes Prize Patrol.
And this February 28th, I and the rest of the prize patrol goons could be rolling up your driveway
with a bunch of balloons and a giant check that says,
Jane Q. Summers.
Somebody, you've just won $500,000 every day for the rest of your life.
How do we do it?
Wait, you know what?
Getting away these valuable magazines and premiums.
Yes, what is it, my boy?
I think Jane Q. Somebody actually is a real person.
Well, I think so.
And she's going to win unless you fill in yours and send it in.
Then you just wouldn't have to taste the bitter cup of reading that Jane Q. Somebody won the fortune.
Which, by rights, should have been yours.
Should have been mine. Was mine.
Yes, it was destined from the beginning of the world.
By God, I'm going to make sure she doesn't get it.
Yes, you can make sure that she spends every day in appalling agony.
I want her to spend the rest of her life in an iron lung.
A red hot iron lung.
A red hot steaming iron lung.
Yes, all this can be arranged.
But what we're going to do first is give you a full psychiatric and physical examination.
And a rubdown, right?
Make sure you're in fighting trip for subgenius.
Exercise number four.
Big fuzzy postage stamp like the kind a clown wears.
33 cents.
Point those sticking out.
Turn communist.
You lick the fuzzy stamp and you paste it into the...
Great calculating.
Into the stamp calculator where you wash it with gasoline and soap suds.
Foolish humans.
None can go against the might of Calculon.
The shoe starts hopping around and kicks over a large glass bowl filled with goldfish.
These are talented shoes.
Hey, hey, you guys.
I have a new terrorist thing we can do for the church to get a bunch of PR.
A terrorist?
I've just been thinking.
A better one to go.
A foolish ranger at Carlsbad Caverns showed Princess Wee and me how to turn the lights off in there from one switch.
We were the last people there and they were shooing us out.
It'll be so dark you'll terrify the people trapped in the cave.
It's the thing.
We could go in there in the middle of the night.
In the middle of the day, plunge the entire two mile...
Well, the whole time it's miles and miles of caverns on a busy holiday.
Plunge it into darkness and then run around in, I don't know, glowing bob masks.
Wait, wait, wait a second.
My pencil broke.
Good rehearsal for when we plunge the entire civilization.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'm an impressionable youth.
What's a pencil?
Well, you don't know where the Carlsbad Caverns light switch is.
But I do.
Technically it's not a pencil.
It's just a piece of charcoal.
It's in Canaan.
Oh, okay.
Wrapped with a tree.
Wrapped with bark.
And you know those caverns communicate with the lost land of Turak, son of stone.
Hey, what if we took these...
Careful, Hal.
These pieces of charcoal wrapped in bark and we actually manufactured them?
They communicate with an Indian that's supposed to be a Mandan but looks like Cochise on a bad TV show?
We could make a zillion dollars.
A zillion and one.
Well, a zillion...
I thought it was a zillion and 53 cents.
Well, I'll round it up.
It's a godzillion.
I don't work for anything less than a zillion.
A zillion and one dollar.
I don't want to deal with these little sins.
Well, aren't you already a zillionaire?
Only in my mind.
But your mind is not your mind.
I know.
See, that's the problem.
Your mind...
I don't know where I put it.
I wish I could use it.
But I don't know how to plug it in when it's gone.
Relax.
Unzip your mind and float down the street.
It's not even my mind.
I lost the adapter for mine.
You're on autopilot?
My mind is.
Yeah.
Only from the mind of me.
I don't know.
It's the recharger for mine.
Yeah, that's right.
The mind of Minolta.
Like a company can have my mind.
Get out of my mind.
Speaking of out of your mind, Dr. Howell, that's a good cue for me to cut to an instrumental
by the Psychoskeletons called The Space Between Your Ears.
Because I know your ears need a space break.
First, I should mention that the song Space...
Space Princess was part of a seven-minute epic jam song from 50 Next Day with Reverend
Hazel of the Windmills on flute, Reverend Suds Pichon guitar, Princess Pisces singing,
and I don't know who else, Reverend Angry Larry on bass probably.
The Dorf Dorf bread commercial preceding my discussion of my great fourth grade teacher,
Mrs. Anita Neendorf, was by Leemur, as are all of the other collages this show.
Anyway, here's The Space Between Your Ears from the Psychoskeletons, who are on SoundClick.com.
Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
Milo Meillender.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
It looks like Michael Pepe's trying to get in.
What a rowdy fellow he is.
I don't know why we tolerate this kind of thing.
Such an unco TVs Joshiwaga- comedy type cookie that doesn't exist anywhere.
Don't let him eat that burrito.
He is an oaf.
Why?
Why I ought to...
Swear an oath.
I'm going to swear an oath.
Didn't he swear an oath of office?
We're all going to swear an oath on KPFA 94.1.
Are you planning to release a video of the show last Friday that you sent the still pictures of the...
Up on YouTube now.
The bride girl embracing an ecstatic Michael.
And the end of the fancy space people are already up on YouTube.
Oh, great.
The problem is the sound.
It was so awful.
But I am going to take your three cat poems and mix them with the beautiful little kitties that were running around the edge of the stage.
Those weren't kitties, Doug.
Those were young women dressed in cat suits.
And what they were doing was not just running around.
Reverend Stang, what did you make of that show?
Did it seem to be culturally valid to you?
My favorite part of it was sitting in Philo's car for the last two hours of it.
Looking at...
Movies of Harry the Hipster.
And listening to Acid Car from X-Day 2006.
Yeah, it's cool when you carry your own videos.
The sound was better.
Yeah, the sound was better.
I think if the sound had been better and we'd been sitting down, there was no chairs for people with old bad knees.
And it was like lounging on the floor was just...
In Philo's car, there were only two posers.
Yeah.
I don't know when my X-Day is.
There were extreme posers.
July 5th.
No, that's a subgenius X-Day.
She's talking about the personal X-Day.
But isn't your personal X-Day the same as...
Darling?
You mean Bob?
That's between you and Bob.
Between...
You can't get to Bob until that X-Day comes.
It is literally blocking you from Bob.
And you should thank your lucky stars that that's still true.
Because you just don't know what's going to happen when X-Day comes down.
That wall comes down and suddenly there's Bob.
Rushing towards you.
Embracing you.
Enveloping you with that pipe smoke.
Might be good.
Might be bad.
It actually smells good, though.
But it won't be just a little good.
Or just a little bad.
It'll be the extremes of both.
Or one or the other.
We just can't know.
And that's...
Isn't that the wonderful mystery of it?
The unknowable...
That's what keeps us interested.
Or at least it kept me interested until earlier.
It's the wonderful mystery of it.
But what happened a couple of weeks ago to dampen your interest?
I started...
I finally got into video games.
I started playing video games for the first time a few months ago.
I don't care about Bob or Church's subgenius.
But you were playing those a year ago.
No, not really.
I was just...
You can play video games and Bob at the same time.
You know what I did?
I was so mad because I couldn't play video games,
I went out and bought a brand new computer.
That's actually true.
Philo...
Yesterday...
Was it yesterday?
Yeah, it was like yesterday.
It seems like a million years ago.
It was yesterday.
I just went out and said,
I'm going to have that one.
He had a stack.
An hour later, I was setting it up.
He had this giant stack of games
that he had never really been able to play for years.
He kept buying them,
knowing he couldn't play them.
Finally, he buys the machine that'll play them.
And for the first time,
I got to see Dr. Hal's performance in Half-Life.
Yeah.
You had lost a lot of weight for that part.
When you were playing...
Well, which Half-Life was it?
Half-Life 2.
Ah.
But you're familiar with Half-Life 1, I suppose.
I never got to play it
because I never got...
I never played any video game
between 1982 or so and this year.
But I finally discovered why people do that
because it's extremely addictive escape from the real world.
In the video game world,
I'm a rich, rich, powerful,
powerful, tall, strong warrior.
I have a question about the Egyptians.
And Half-Life Hal has a whole giant laboratory in that world.
Yes, I do.
And I try to keep it in some order.
In Grand Theft Auto,
Philo gets to just run around killing everybody.
God mode.
If the...
I don't think of it as killing, really.
I think of it as putting them out of their misery.
You know what's missing from that game,
Grand Theft Auto,
this show on the car radio.
They give you a lot of channels
that are pretty well put together
just for the purpose of the game.
You can make this show be on the radio.
I've actually done that
where I've listened to the Puzzling Evidence show
while playing Grand Theft Auto
through the Grand Theft Auto play.
Oh, that's right.
You told me you had a mod.
It was one of those mod...
No, it comes with the game.
You can make a reference in the game
in one of the control files
so that it will play a directory of MP3 files
that you've set up.
That's mysterious.
The lost children of Babylon.
What'll they think of next?
Man, if I was playing Grand Theft Auto
and listening to this show,
I'd feel even more like I was on Kweli.
Would you feel like you were alienated from society
if you did that?
No, actually, I'd feel more integrated.
Like an alien.
Like I was a normal person.
I'd be sitting there playing video games
or watching TV instead of what I normally do.
Would you hold hands with...
Which is order padded envelopes
and compare prices for CDs.
That's what I do for Bob.
And that's enough.
More than anyone should ever be asked to do.
Yeah, tell me about it.
Mm-hmm.
I'm looking at a picture of Bob right now.
Oh, she's looking at the picture.
Where's your other hand?
Are you genuflecting?
Are you breaking eye contact?
I hope you genuflect.
I can't.
And it's sort of...
I think it's an overload of being on show
and looking at Bob.
You can mentally genuflect.
Holler, I understand.
Last time I was on this show,
I was on a show.
I did show, too.
And it was very, very disastrous.
I'm actually, believe it or not,
saying no to show this time around.
At least that particular administration method.
And hedonic twaddle.
So, yeah.
Maybe you just simply need to have it properly injected.
And that's really between you
and your version of the deity.
It needs to be properly packed.
Maybe your medical professionals...
The contents may settle.
It's that old do-do.
But I'll give you a better dictionary.
Anyway.
Should I put down this picture of Bob and inject it?
Inject an image of Bob?
There's a good type of people who've injected themselves with Bob.
Now, you need to be injected by a senior doctor
in a special fashion, which can be explained by an examination.
I think you did.
A caller?
Do I know you?
You do know me.
I've called you many times before.
Say that again.
I used to call in all the time.
Oh.
I just wondered if I knew you from X days or something.
Or from another life.
I thought you might be a friend that I know named Reverend Baby Bear.
I'm Reverend Baby Bear.
You are?
So it is.
I'm a girl talking.
Oh, okay.
There's two girls talking.
I'm confusing.
Yeah, this is the show where there's always two girls talking.
Well, Reverend Baby Bear is often calling.
Two girls in one show.
I didn't know that.
I didn't know that Reverend Baby Bear called and watched.
She's very active.
She's active on Scrub Genius.
I normally don't get up in time to call because it's six in the morning here.
Yeah, me too.
That's when I go to bed.
How do you happen to be up this morning?
I didn't have to work today, so I decided to wake up and do it.
That's pretty much my excuse to wake up.
Wake up and do it.
That's what we all do here.
It's hard to stay up.
Well, do the show.
It is hard to stay up.
It's hard to do it.
It's hard to wake up.
I literally woke up for a show.
That's why I haven't called in in a long time.
I'm sleepy.
You've got to get some sleep every now and then.
So, wait a minute.
Are there three girls on the show now?
Yes.
Awesome.
And they're freaking out.
Reverend Baby Bear is heard at the end of almost every, all the new hours of Slack,
usually right after a cut with G. Gordon Gordon,
because she does the URL and address in this young girl voice.
And that sounds so nice juxtaposed with G. Gordon Gordon's,
mechanical, cancer-ravelling.
Gravelly.
I agree.
Haven't you ever heard a man with cancer before?
I remember that.
You guys sounded like a...
Oh, yeah.
He went around and loaded up the sampler with all these different church slogans.
The junior sampler.
Most of the ones that he could think of.
Some of which, of course, I think quite...
And then he would lip sync to them, holding the little sampler up to his throat like it was a voice.
Yeah.
People thought that he really had throat cancer and had to talk through the box.
Nonsense.
He just had a case of terminal crustiness.
One of the precepts he had was his own voice saying,
What's the matter?
Haven't you ever heard a man with throat cancer before?
And he would push the button on the lip sync to it.
I know.
It's in a scary place.
And I later had people say...
I never saw it before.
What?
Has G. Gordon Gordon died of his throat cancer yet?
But it doesn't have a color to it.
I've read it ten times, but I've died of some kind of cancer.
Every week I read that I'm dead from some horrible illness.
Thank God.
Wishful thinking on an old alt-slack form.
Yeah, liquids around electronics, not a good idea.
Try new clean tobacco.
New because the tobacco is green.
And the clean tobacco tastes clean.
Yes, the clean tobacco tastes clean and clean.
The result is...
New clean tobacco.
Authorities have exhausted all leads in the apparent heavyset female in western Minnesota.
The Swift County Sheriff's Office says a young heavy female was wearing a black hooded sweatshirt and dark pants in an SUV in Appleton about 8 o'clock.
The BCA says a white heavyset female wearing a black hooded sweatshirt got out of the SUV last night.
Investigators say a heavy female was last seen wearing dark pants on Highway 7.
The Swift County Sheriff's Office says it has not identified 20-year-old Melvin Jr. of Brooklyn Park.
Two officers wearing black hooded pants had run out of the store through a rear entrance.
At least one of the officers shot American Crystal Sugar workers.
Dan Gunderson reports.
1,300 workers for about 18 months.
Wouldn't you like to be a pepper too, though?
I was a pepper.
I like coffee.
I was a pepper for the FBI.
Dr. Pepper.
Yes.
I like to chew.
I was a pepper.
I'm a pepper.
You're a pepper.
If I was a pepper, I'd have a mobile living room that I could drive around in the desert.
Yeah, that's a great idea.
Actually, Pepper just put up a picture of himself in like 75 or 72 on the mobile living room.
No, long before that.
He has some kind of a VW camper.
And he has very, very long hair.
I'm figuring the baby Pepper probably had real long hair.
That's what I figured.
Yeah.
Now we're swimming around in your mind.
It feels gross, don't it?
More of that puzzling evidence show from February 15th next week.
Thanks, Puz and Hal and Phyla and callers, including Reverend Baby Bear.
What I'm going to play to close out the show may seem old to the young, but it's new to the old.
A rapper that my son told me about by the name of Macklemore.
Macklemore.
It's really old if you're especially young.
Obviously, to me, 2001 is still the future.
Anyway, here's a song by Macklemore called American.
How y'all doing there, folks?
My name is Aberdeen, Washington.
And I'm a proud American and a terrorist fighter.
That's right.
Hey, give me another beer, bitch.
Now with the day been light and it comes to town,
I'ma drop a deuce, wipe it up with this towel
I'm on my lawn, sit on the couch
I'ma watch some football
I pray to the Lord the cowboys win
Beat the hell out of them damn redskins
Call up the boys, get drunk as shit
Goddamn right, I'm American
That's right, I'm American
Got a picture of Reagan above my fire
Next to the deer, I shot with my rifle
An RA, hell yeah, I support him
No pro choice, no abortion
Mexicans, send em back over the border
Right on home to Samoa
Wherever they come from, they takin' our jobs
Eatin' our hamburgers, takin' our jobs
They takin' our jobs
I see em in the field, I'm takin' their head off
I hate my job and I hate my boss
But I love my country
And I pray to God that the cowboys win
Fuck yeah, Romo
And the cowboys win
That's right, that's right, that's right, come on
Everybody, just clap your hands
If you love our country
If you love our land, that's right
And if you're not clapping your hands
You're a terrorist and you eat sand
Sandwiches
The day be loud and comes to town
I'ma drop a deuce, wipe my poop with a staff
Roll my lawn, sit on the couch
And I'ma watch some football
And I pray to the Lord the cowboys win
And beat the hell out of them damn redskins
Cause the boys can drunk as shit
Goddamn right, I'm a marathon
I'm a can
I'm a marathon can
I'm John McCain and Sarah Palin
I know you lost out there
It was a tough one
There's still two Mavericks in my book, don't worry about it
Now listen, paper
I heard you like beer
Me too
I don't have a six pack, but I got a beer bong on my pants
What do you say we go get shit-faced in a helicopter and kill a moose?
America, the chosen
Guns, explosions
McDonald's, bowling
You'll see
You don't like it?
We exploit shit
Pop a pill
Get a boner
Hell yeah
Tony Romo
And a guy so damn cute
I wanna sack his boner
And ride him broke back
All the way to Wyoming
No homo
Psych
Hey, I said no homo
Hey, fuck terrorists
I mean like
I don't wanna fuck a terrorist
Guys, I'm kidding
I like Romo
I don't like Romo
I said fuck terrorists
Fuck terrorists
Not I wanna fuck a terrorist
You wouldn't
If you caught Bin Laden
You wouldn't give him one in the butt
For America
If you said no homo
Right after you did it
It doesn't count if it's terrorists
Hey, little Aberdeen
Come in here
Hey, come see the National Family Anthem
Come on
USA
Hey hey
That's right
I'm an American citizen
Aberdeen, Washington
This is my country
And just because Barack Obama won the presidential election
Does not mean colors are supposed to be the same
That half the country doesn't feel the same way I do
And I came to America, yeah
And I live in America, come on
And I live in America
I did too, Dad, let me get up
And I live in America, Dad
And I live in America
Shut up!
Little Abbey, shut the fuck up!
My bad
Let me tell them
That's right, I'm American
You've been listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack
For free information, write to
P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118
Or see www.p.o.box.com
Subgenius.com
Praise Bob
For Sire, there is no more money
We gotta get some money
That dirty Turkish harker back
Flackin' Wharton
Phillip Buckaburton
Perkaluma Burton
Don't you watch tonight
Friends, we're glad you listened to this show
And we're even more glad that some listeners
Have donated enough to help us
Keep going
For another couple of months
Not just this show
But Subgenius.com
And all the other archive sites
But if you truly love Bob
And want some of that Slack back
To rebound to you
You should go to
Subgenius.com
Front page, or especially the radio page
Or the catalog store pages
And help out financially
As best you can
Now, we know what it's like
To be on the brink of total poverty
And we don't care about it
We just want any subgeniuses
To make their own situations worse
But some of you still have jobs
Even five bucks makes a big difference
Even if it's only once a month
From enough of you
Fifty bucks makes an even bigger difference
All we're saying is that
Blow jobs could go the way of Steve jobs
If you don't pay Dobbs
We also take checks and money orders
To Subgenius Foundation
P.O. Box 181417
Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118
Thanks for anything you can do
To help let there be Slack
We just invite you to subscribe
It's a deep grind
It's just five clicks
And I'm rid 난
arrive
Please subscribe
But there's more
And everyone is spending
Quite a little money
It's ahyun
In front of theó
Please, click there
You'll be all dressed up
I'm running out of
blasted
A Burada
See you around
I'll see ya
See ya
Bye
Hasta Can issue
Next и
See you
Zoomло
There you go
Got my things
Just gone
Got it
I've been gone