At the moment I'm thinking about my reputation.
You're going to marry me, Bob.
Listen, I've told you how it's going to be and you might as well get used to the idea.
Because if I have to, I'll smear you, Bob.
I'll ruin you for...
The Hour of Swag.
THE HOUR OF SWAGGER
Yeah, let's start from the top.
Turkeys and hams.
You'll also need to be aware of moving things, electrical critters and contaminant things,
radioactive sources, and even loud objects, loud sounds.
Turkeys.
For more information, visit subgenius.com.
What a good idea.
And thank you, Reverend DU8, for another steaming sack of slack.
And before that, we heard a song from somebody new to Hour of Slack.
I got a letter and a link from a band called Hombres del Mar.
Hombres del Mar.
With a song called Uberman.
And that was the clean version.
The internet version will be very different from the one heard on our beloved broadcast stations.
Yeah, Uberman.
The lyrics of Uberman are borrowed from the brag of the subgenius,
which I will admit to having written myself when I was 22, I think, and I'm 61 now.
And that's like the...
Fourth?
No, more like the sixth or seventh musical version of that old rant of mine.
It just resonates all over the place, dude.
It's a resonating food.
But I have a little rant here, but not by me.
Written by Reverend Fid Chooley.
And it was posted on the Scrub Genius Forum.
I'm going to read it.
People had been asking,
What's going to happen to the church in the future?
Meaning the church of the subgenius.
And Fid Chooley says,
Humbug.
The question at hand should be one that we all answer for ourselves.
What am I going to do with the influence I have drawn from the church of the subgenius?
This is a better question because it's one we can answer now,
as opposed to the previously quoted question,
which is a wait and see type deal.
Buddha said something to the effect that a man shot by a stranger with an arrow
should first ask how to take the arrow out
instead of doing what most people do,
which is bleed to death with the arrow still in them
while they frantically try to figure out who shot him and why.
To that end, if every one of us put all our energy into figuring out the fate of the church down the road,
then the church would, in fact,
already be over at that moment.
Similarly, if there were to be some kind of power struggle,
a tug of war as to which schism was the rightful inheritors of Bob,
then both sides would have missed the point, no?
We who are here are all here right now.
Are you going to wait until the flood starts before you build your ark?
Are you going to wait?
Till X-Day, the real X-Day,
before you build your saucer?
If you're hearing these words here on Hour of Slack,
then you've probably been exposed to the church of the subgenius
long enough to have the manual for building your own saucer.
But there are still a lot of others out there
who will mistake the manual itself for the building materials.
A saucer cannot be built using the building instruction manual itself
as the only building materials.
Toilet paper, however, can.
And once you've memorized the manual,
toilet paper is all the manual's good for.
And after getting it,
toilet paper is really the only thing it's good for
other than helping others to get out of the bathroom.
Getting it is not the goal, but the first step.
Toilet paper does get you out of the bathroom,
but if you don't leave the bathroom to engage in something more than pooping,
then what difference does it really make in the end?
Pun intended, as you're still a poopy butt either way.
Look, I know I'm pretty much preaching to the choir
by saying this on the show,
but the point had to be made.
It's been said that
beep them if they can't take a joke
is the greatest or only truth told by the church,
but I'll take build your own saucer
over beep them if they can't take a joke.
I'll take a joke any day,
because building your own saucer isn't just saying beep them,
it's actually doing it.
And I'd rather be counted among those who are doing the beeping
than those who are talking about it, right?
Bottom line, the topic of what happens to the church
after its founders are no longer with us is a red herring.
When it comes to the church and the subgenius right now and always,
we should be infinitely more concerned with inspiration
rather than expiration.
Otherwise, we are truly doing a great disservice
to said founders and ourselves
and most importantly, Bob.
May Bob awaken your latent emergentilianism
and if it is awakened,
may you draw slack in sustaining it.
Yours truly, Fid.
Reverend Fid Chooley,
who last week,
we quoted with his shorter rant,
less terrorism, more care-or-ism.
And, uh...
And...
Yes, yes, yes.
I do have some, um...
a great old recording of Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
I think it's a rehearsal
recorded in the late Chesmith's basement
with you and me and Dave
and...
And it was before a show.
The rehearsal was probably better than the show.
But I'm gonna play that in a minute.
I do have yet another rant
I'd like to whip out here.
It's not...
Again, this one's not by me.
I wonder if I should put different music on for this.
Sure, why not?
They're all from the same basic source.
Uh...
Well, this is one...
Believe it or not, I got this off the CNN website.
It was an editorial.
But it's about Texas, and it's by a Texan.
And I used to be almost a Texan.
So...
And I thought it was really funny.
And I'm gonna go ahead and read it
because it's gonna tick off a bunch more Texans.
Praise Bob.
And it's titled,
We Texans Are Brave Enough to Resist the Pentagon.
By James C. Moore.
And it's a letter.
Dear America,
I write to you from behind the lines
in the last free state of Texas
as we prepare to resist the invasion of Jade Helm 15.
While General Travis laid in a supply of extra beeves
in advance of the Mexican assault at the Alamo,
we are fearful of running low on Slim Jims and Moon Pies
as the Walmarts are turned into detention centers
for citizens robbed of their constitutional rights.
As POWs, or prisoners of Walmart,
we expect to be put to work in the sporting goods department
against our will while earning below minimum wage.
We've had one encounter with the commander of the invading force
during a hearing in Bastrop, Texas.
Lieutenant Colonel Mark Lastoria was deceptively polite and informative,
but Texans don't fall for those characteristics.
We don't need facts.
In Chuck Norris, we trust,
and he has informed us that this is an attempt
by the Kenyan socialist in the White House
to surrender our country to the United Nations.
We've heard the talk that this is a training exercise
in seven southwestern states to prepare U.S. troops
for new types of war fighting,
but Chuck Norris said,
quote,
it's not crazy to think that we're going to be able to do this.
It's not crazy to think Obama would invade Texas.
So that's what we believe.
Our brave governor, Greg Abbott,
has ordered the Texas State Guard
to establish listening posts
to monitor Jade Helm exercises
in case America's soldiers come to take our guns,
Duck Dynasty paraphernalia,
Lone Star beer pickup trucks, and bass boats.
His command has left only a few of us confused.
The governor says,
he honors the military at the same time he sends a message
that he distrusts their activities.
We're concerned that our previous governor, Rick Perry,
has transcended Abbott's intellect.
Perry can't remember three things at once,
but he thinks paranoia over Jade Helm is not warranted.
We expect the Jade Helm troops
to seduce our population with the profits
from selling gas, food, and lodging,
but we will be vigilant.
We have our radios tuned
to technology,
such as wheat,
and we watch the
utos'
frantic
glasses
twinkle
when
our
waters
tell
around
that
the
Todd Smith, a Republican, wrote the governor to tell him that his, quote, pandering to idiots, unquote, had made him livid.
Although Smith served 16 years in the Texas House, he seems to have salvaged a troubling intelligence.
He told Governor Abbott, quote, I'm horrified that I have to choose between the possibility that my governor actually believes this stuff and the possibility that my governor doesn't have the backbone to stand up to those who do.
I'm not sure which is worse.
But be not afraid, America.
We are Texans.
We will resist logic and intelligence to the very bitter end.
And we will keep up our traditions from the Alamo to the Buckeye.
The Battle of Goliad.
The Confederacy.
LBJ's Vietnam.
George W. Bush's Iraq War.
And even Jerry Jones' Dallas Cowboys.
We have a long legacy of losing.
And the odds are also against us in the coming battle of Jade Helm.
But we expect to prevail against the invaders.
And we will not give up our rights.
Or our air conditioning, cold beer, and Slim Jims.
Signed,
a patriotic Texan.
James C. Moore.
Not to be confused with James Seymour.
And now, back in time to something recorded by us and Chaz and Dave and Einstein's secret orchestra.
These phobias can be countered.
.
No, but those insects were there the night Harry went over the edge.
And how can we surmise that from this incident,
the head of J.R. Bob Dobbs did emerge into the illustrious as a numinous being?
I don't know, but you can find out by coming to the X-Day Drill
on July 5th through 7th this year
and every year from now to X-Day!
That's right, Ivan, that's right!
Remember to call for free information about the amazing X-Day Drill.
Yes, it's like the legendary Dockstock Gathering.
That's right, Ivan, that's right, Ivan!
Oh, you'll see the most hated preachers of the subgenius church.
You'll camp out on a lovely, fully developed campground
surrounded by geeks you'd rather not ever spend much time with.
But by God, you'll know more about the church of the subgenius
because, friends, you will have...
practiced for that fatal day,
that glorious day, X-Day!
Yes, only two years from now, in 1998,
the sex goddesses from Planet X shall come
in their space vessels
and rupture up the news playing
fully Dobbs-approved subgenius ministers.
That's right, Ivan!
All 4,000 of us,
and destroy the rest of the planet.
That's right, Ivan!
Well, not destroy it,
but turn it back into the stinking swamp
that it was before the filthy,
the humans came along and muddied everything up.
But, friends, you can come along and muddy everything up.
You can wallow in the filth.
You can dance all night.
You can pull your clothes off
and county law doesn't care
because we are having the first X-Day drill
this July 5th through 7th.
Sunday, Sunday!
Sunday!
You'll see the pill.
You'll see the bleeding head of Arnold Palmer.
It lives, it bleeds for you.
If you...
You don't vomit your money back,
friends, you will see things you wouldn't dare believe,
things you never wanted to believe
and things you'll wish you never saw.
That's right, Ivan.
Yetis will be copulating in the bushes.
Oh, dude!
The Loch Ness Monster will rise up from the little pond.
The crazed pagan drummers will drum all night long
and keep you from sleeping.
Mosquitoes the size of Dobson flies
will devour you, but you won't care!
You won't care!
Because you spent your money and came to the X-Day drill
July 5th through 7th in Brushwood, New York.
Brushwood, New York.
Only three hours from Cleveland.
And friends, you can call for information
216-0060338
I'll give that number again.
Write that number down.
It's the free information divinable hotline
at the Church of the Subgenius here in Cleveland.
0060338
That's 0060338.
What do those numbers add up to?
Aha! Now you know the secret.
Now you know what we're really trying to tell you about.
The froth. Yes, the froth.
There's no end to it.
I have a bucket of froth.
Back tubs full of froth.
Three months tired.
That's why I have a froth.
A different ancient Tibetan ocean full of froth.
Oh, dude!
Ancient Tibetan herbs
growing right up under your feet.
You won't be able to sleep.
There'll be so much froth growing
at high speed underneath your sleeping bag.
0060338
I'm tossing you around.
It's like a giant funhouse.
Yes, it's insane.
It's crazy.
But ain't it always been the crazy people
that were able to party like the new hell?
Yes, sirreebob.
Yes, sirman, sirlady.
You will finally learn what it's like to be a subgenius.
That's right.
I've been staying at the Church of the Subgenius
and so...
Oh, did I say that?
Well, then pick up on it, man.
It's said that the end of the world shall come in a great flash.
I sure hope so.
Some people might go and the other ones might last.
Will you be the one who goes?
Where will you be on next day, brother?
Where is your...
Will you be in the sausage with Bob?
There's still lots of room.
Or will you be down in the room?
You can have anything you want.
Will you be burning?
Ex-ex-ex-ex-ex-ex-ex-ex-ex...
Will it be perfect pleasure or perfect pain?
Which will it be?
It's up to you to choose.
Bob gives you free will.
But you can't give anything until you sign on the dotted line.
And the next day is coming, so you better move fast because...
Where will you be on next day?
I've got plenty of time to spend my $30 on that Bob ministership.
I've got plenty of time.
I've got two more years for next day.
Why am I in any kind of hurry?
There couldn't possibly have been some kind of a misprint in the book of the subgenius.
I mean...
Just because that first edition from McGraw-Hill actually did say that next day was on July 5th, 1996.
Well, they changed it after that.
I'm sure that...
I mean, it looked like a mistake.
Probably was a mistake.
I don't think I really have to spend that $30 quite yet.
Because that probably was just...
It's probably not that the world's going to end in this year, 1996.
Probably not.
I could probably afford to...
Take that risk.
I mean...
I've got that $30.
That's not a problem.
But there's this Hootie and the Blowfish CD I wanted to get.
And, well, you know, I wanted to go to this movie about water spouts.
And, well, I just...
I just...
You know, I mean, Bob will wait on me.
I mean, Bob's a patient man.
He ain't a wrathful God.
Now, you see, I heard Bob would love the subgeniuses, even if they never spend any money.
He's a patient man.
A patient man.
Man, he ain't no patient.
Bob is the doctor.
He ain't no patient man.
Bob is the surgeon who will excise the filthy rotting tumor that is America, that is modern
America today.
Yes, my fellow rebellious citizens and untax payers and militia members, all the citizens
of courts.
We must come together.
We must come together. Quick, they're coming. They're trying to stop me from speaking.
All of us religious nuts and crazy, bright-winged maniacs, we must bang together against the man.
Because, oh, wait, they're coming. I've got to get my message out.
The last true hope is 5560338. Call 55603. Here they come.
No, come on!
Oh, my God!
Yes!
No, please!
No!
One more day, oh, it's going to be.
I won't give your love to me.
Your love will last more than one day.
I'm going to tell you nothing at all.
I won't hold you.
Thank you.
Got a cobra snake for a necktie
Got me a church by the roadside
Made out of rattlesnake hide
Bob is gonna ask you, who do you love?
Who do you love?
Oh, Bob's bigger than a cat in my eyes
Oh, who do you love?
Oh, I tried to live with the dark, but
It's all for me, got a man around
Oh, I'm in the mountain, my
Oh, you don't know just how I feel
Huh, huh, huh
Go on
My love is real and I find the way
Hooray
Hey, hooray, hooray, hooray, wah, wah, wa phew!
And, dear friends, that was Einstein's Secret Orchestra,
plus yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang,
blabbering there along with Lonesome Cowboy Dave
and Professor Chaz.
And that was 1,000 shows ago, Princess Wee.
An even thousand shows ago.
No, not even.
But just about a thousand.
Yeah, it was number 569, and this is number 1517.
Oh, my goodness.
And I don't know what that phone number was
that I was giving out.
We've been sitting here trying to figure that out.
Maybe it wasn't recorded in the station.
There were times when Chaz would bring
his whole band in.
And Dave would have his guitar,
and Dave would actually be here.
And love is real, not fade away.
And I have some advice on mounting for you kids.
First, this is love advice.
Well, monster hunting advice, which I love.
First, make sure you're wearing your best armor.
Mix up your clothes.
Have some mega potions to make a more relaxed atmosphere.
Don't do anything to make the monster mad at you
because it's generally really hard to mount an angry monster,
with some exceptions.
Make sure the lighting is good.
Not too dark, but keep it low.
Don't rush it or be too pushy, aggressive.
That tends to just make things harder for you.
Just have fun.
Stay close.
Don't be afraid to the monster.
Be playful.
When the time comes, you'll both know it.
And the mount will just come naturally.
Make sure you're wearing plenty of protection,
even if you think you know the monster well.
Don't just go in with nothing and hope for the best.
And don't just run back to the village when your quest is over.
Stay a while.
Make sure to keep in touch.
Unless you both agree this is a very dangerous place.
This is a random, one-time mounting.
Yeah, stay, bask in the afterglow.
But this isn't a one-time mounting, is it, Lonesome Cowboy Dave?
No, it's a frequent mounting.
It's a mountain of mountains.
I knew you'd say that.
A mountaine of mountings.
A mountaine?
That's why I was wondering about the last tract we just transmitted,
and if it got to you, know who on time correctly.
Heh heh.
You know where.
You know what I mean?
The last what that was transported?
The recording from...
That's correct.
I'm not talking about that APA dissertation that Dr. Jason Sky wrote.
I'm real familiar with APA, and they always talk that makes you want to kill them.
But I was talking about a little news release, we'll call it,
that you and I, and we, we all transmitted a short while ago, subconsciously and psychogenically.
You mean that old tape of Einstein's Secret Orchestra?
I'm hoping.
Yeah, that's what it was.
Okay.
You're just guessing, aren't you?
No, I feel relieved now.
Oh, okay.
Because I thought, but did it get to you know who, you know where?
What, did it get to Chaz in hell?
I don't know.
I'm not Satan.
Or heaven, or whatever, you know.
I mean, subgenius hell, same thing as Christian heaven.
Same difference, basically.
Yeah.
And you don't have to have big feet to get in either.
I mean, a lot of these religious paintings show people with huge big toes,
and chubby, chubby little toes, and stuff like that.
And I always wondered what that really meant,
especially since the instep.
It's so perfect.
But then they had these big yeti-looking feet.
I mean, you know, size.
I'm peculiar about that, at least at a moment's notice.
Well, it is where the soul is contained.
Yeah, yeah.
I remember when we were discussing that,
and nobody could get past that except for about holes in their socks and stuff,
and their socks were holey or something.
That was it, yeah.
Is that because they have a feet fetish?
A fetish.
Yeah, well, if they're feeling fetish,
and they have a foot fetish.
A feet fetish.
Praise Marge Lambert for that expression.
Thanks, Marge.
Huh? What?
Marge Lambert is the person who coined that,
the feet fetish.
Oh, I thought I was just coining it off the top of my head.
No, no, that happened many long years ago
when she looked into my apartment,
and she saw 5,000 pairs of shoes,
and she said,
Princess Wee,
do you have a feet fetish?
Oh, right, right.
Okay, now I remember.
Yeah.
Oh, she had, Marge had great feet.
Yes, she did.
Oh, la, la.
Very yeti-like.
Yeah, I understand that, yeah.
I mean, but what about a feet fetish?
Because I heard that that's even more peculiar.
Because they're so tiny, and they're hardly formed, you know?
Some people think that's actually sexual,
but I don't think that's sexual.
See?
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't understand any of that stuff.
Me neither.
I can't even see most people's feet.
I don't know why you'd make out with them,
or whatever you do.
At least the bumper stickers are creative,
because, you know, you can only handle
so many abstruse statements on one bumper.
And they're pretty good at it, you know?
But sometimes you almost get into an accident,
slamming into people.
What the hell?
What?
Yeah, what?
No.
If you can read this, you're driving way too close.
I bought a bumper sticker.
I actually paid money for a bumper.
I looked up where to find this bumper sticker,
because I'd seen it on a car,
and I admired it.
And I found it, and I bought it.
But now I don't know what to do with it,
because I'm not going to put a bust me please on my car.
It's not a bust me please.
It's a someone get angry.
It's a, it's a key my car and break the windshield with a brick,
and leave a little note saying, God bless you.
Because the bumper sticker I bought is the word fiction
spelled out in religious symbols.
Sort of like coexist, the smarmy one.
Only this is a mean one.
So it was like the cross and F?
Or was it the X?
Or the T?
The, the, the, the F.
The F is made with like a Russian Orthodox cross,
which has extra, you know, crossbars.
The two crossbars.
And of course the little T in the middle is a regular cross.
The C is the Muslimic crescent.
And so forth.
I think there's like a Taoist and a...
The I is dotted with a Star of David.
Right, yes.
Fiction.
Humble, punky, punk.
But see, if I were to put that on...
New religions.
Huh, what?
Oh, I just, it's a plethora of related religions.
They all have to do with abstinence.
And nevermind.
Well, they don't have a pipe in them.
Because Bob just doesn't,
the church's subgenius doesn't fit into that word.
It is that word.
That word is like one tiny part of the great church.
That word is one faction of the fiction.
It's the faction.
I think it's an acronym that's real good.
A-sog, or I mean, C-sog.
I mean, C or C, sog.
Hey, are you one of those Zog kooks
that were under the Zionist occupied government?
Reading A-sop's labels?
Because I think we're really underneath
the government occupied government.
Uh-oh.
Is the government occupying the government now?
That's what I've heard.
They're about to invade America.
At least that's what the Texans seem to be afraid of.
That the government's going to invade America.
That American soldiers are going to come onto our shores,
if you can imagine that.
Because they could take over any time.
I think they try to provoke these reminiscences
because I was on a regular highway once,
a main highway, you know, not a four-laner,
but a two-lane mainer and stuff like that.
But nobody was around.
It wasn't very crowded at all.
There was nobody around.
And I was passed by this Humvee-looking war type of wagon
with the guy sticking out on top wearing kind of...
I swear this is true.
I know it sounds like...
But anyway, with this cat wearing kind of like
more NATO-ish looking clothes,
you know, kind of like Swedish Army hat,
American camouflage bottom, you know.
And I thought,
well, we never see soldiers of any kind around.
And why is he driving down this street?
It's kind of, you know, anyway.
If you lived in some places,
you'd see soldiers driving around all the time.
Sure, if you live near a base,
you know, you get on a bus
and you're surrounded by uniforms.
But mostly people try to get rid of the uniforms
so they can have fun in town.
Well, I respect our soldiers.
They, for whatever reason,
signed up for the absolute worst job in the entire world.
And, you know,
I would...
I wish I could be up there on the front lines with you men,
but they declared me 4F.
I have flat feet
and I'm just not good enough for this man's army.
That's what they told me back in Vietnam.
Vietnam, Texas.
And I heard that you had such a hard time.
And with that, you had to volunteer
for the greater day.
Plus children without homes.
Oh, I volunteered for everything.
But they all said I had flat feet.
I couldn't even do meals on wheels
because I had flat feet.
They just don't want me.
They don't care.
They don't want me.
And all the time this was going on,
you never once considered the fact
that you had misread
what is so obviously preoccupies your mind.
It's fat feet.
Not flat feet, but fat feet.
I have a fat feet fetish.
And...
And so...
So they're still looking for you.
Just like the Kent 12.
The guys that got away
and snuck around back behind the guardsmen
and threw eggs at them and stuff like that.
They're still at large.
I don't know if that's the actual term they use,
you know, about size or anything like that,
but...
No, I made that up.
I had to.
I'm a communist.
No, I'm confused right now of anything.
Poor Dave.
Poor, poor Dave.
Poor old...
Poor old Wobbly.
They haven't been...
He's the last of the living Wobblies.
The very last one.
That's the way they always have to sing it, too.
Like some...
I think it's a preacher voice
from the southern Midwest or the Southlands.
A creature voice, did you say?
Huh?
Goddamn, the creature man.
See, that's...
That's not the right tone of voice,
so you have to actually sound like you're oozing...
That's coming out of your pores.
Oh, you said preacher.
I thought you were talking about the creature
from the Black Lagoon,
which I'm much more interested in than most preachers.
They tell me about the preacher
who paints the picture of the preacher.
At least when he's still sweating.
They used to call old Dr. Lagoon
the preacher from the Black Lagoon.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ha, ha, ha.
Well, if you haven't heard it 2,000 times before,
it's kind of funny.
Right.
Kind of like that whole Church of the Subgenius thing.
If you haven't heard it 1,517 shows,
it'd be kind of funny, I guess.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
So sad.
We've got to come up with something new.
Oh, wait.
Tater came up with...
Tater Gumfrey came up with something.
It just came right out of me.
He said,
your rights end where Bob's fist begins.
And that is the stark fist of removal.
Yes, them Texans can worry all they want
about somebody coming in and taking away their gun rights,
but I'm afraid when Bob's fist enters the room,
you'd best kiss it or back out backwards, buddy.
I propose a new plan, a bold new plan,
wherein all members of the ministry
are given punching gloves,
big, fat, thick ones filled with lead.
At any moment of discourse where things cause pain,
they must chomp each other and punch each other in the face
roundly and savagely as many times as possible.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
At least that's what I was hoping for.
Hey, did you hear about those...
Okay, there was that...
the mean lady in Texas
who says that she's like Jesus
or Martin Luther King,
because she invited some radical Muslimics
to come kill somebody
at her draw cartoon of Muhammad party
for free speech.
Okay, and a couple of guys showed up
and they got themselves killed
because, you know, Texas.
Anyway, guess what?
It's a story that doesn't make any sense.
I'm sorry.
Guess what?
There was a subgenius
who had his artwork,
but I had them tomatoes when I'm eating.
So he showed him a lot of his artwork
and he said that this is a magic,
amazing show
and he literally gave this year
that's like a 50% juice to his time.
I was praying to him
that this will come to an end
and that this TV show
won't be the same,
that's really, really bad.
speak.
They hadn't invented word balloons.
His dialogue would be written
on his shirt. Anyway,
Onan drew a picture of the yellow kid saying
I am the prophet.
That was it. But
here's the problem.
When's he going to get his artwork back?
It's
sitting in this building
in Garland that's a crime scene
apparently with all the other artwork.
And I guess some chalk
somebody said my favorite
artwork in there was chalk outlines around
bodies.
But anyway, Onan was more concerned
Most of
these things go and six months
there'll be a pre-trial hearing.
They've already been arraigned I suppose.
And since it's material evidence
to the case, it'll probably take another year
for it to come to court.
And then another year after that for him to get his
artwork back.
Well, I just hope that lonesome
Onanist Onan
finally gets his
Mohammed picture back.
I do too.
That's what I'm saying. It doesn't seem likely
the way these things go.
Now we don't have to worry about that
because we don't
we're a radio station
so we can't draw pictures of anybody
not even Bob
except, you know, in our minds.
I think I just did draw
a picture of Onan's yellow kid
picture. I think you did too.
Okay, well I guess we're on the death
we're on the death of Onan.
We're on the list now to us and Salman Rushdie.
Yep, you drew it with words.
We blew it.
Can I just ask one question?
Doesn't it seem like any kind of provocative
art like, you know,
a crucifix in urine or
a dung statue of the Virgin Mary
without the explanation of what it really was
at the time and stuff
like that as well as just purposely
trying to like, you know, show
Mohammed in his underpants
and stuff like that.
And doesn't it seem like there's
a whole bunch of much cooler stuff
going on right now?
I mean, in the art world.
Well, yeah, of course.
Why are we directed towards these silly
neo-propagandistic
things?
I'm wondering.
Well, the lady who is sponsoring that thing
she kind of believes that all
Muslimics should be driven
out of America and rounded up
and put into some desert
and then
bombed.
She's obviously not a citizen.
She goes to the doctor
once in a while and there's the Islamic
doctor there who wouldn't harm a person.
Well, it's true that
you know, the neighborhood is
7-Eleven or whatever you call it,
the convenience store and stuff.
Oddly enough, it is actually
legal to be
a believer in Islam
in the United States.
Yes, Thomas Jefferson even
put him in a...
George Washington was a Muslim.
People don't know that.
Abraham Lincoln.
Abraham Lincoln was...
Well, he was a little...
He didn't always have that stuff piped out.
He had a little turban on
some of the time.
Well, you want to hear something real...
Did you ever hear about Thomas Jefferson's
flying carpet?
Now, of course, then you're getting pre-Islamic.
I'm becoming a member of...
Never mind. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
I'm sorry, three.
I interrupted.
No, I'm here.
Oh, excuse me.
No, excuse you.
Oh.
But Thomas Jefferson was
also enjoyed...
How shall we say it?
He and Benjamin Franklin
were turned on to...
Or not turned...
How would you put that?
They did little surveys
of the Middle East
and asked questions.
Huh?
Did you know that
this also was immortalized by,
of course, the Fireside Theater?
Thomas Jefferson and Ben Franklin
smoked urine.
I mean, smoked...
Yeah.
They got goodly stretched on the hemp.
On the hump.
Yeah.
And they directed the course
of this nation's affairs
for some 16 centuries now
since, oh, well,
in the Byzantine period.
Oh, they were...
They were total potheads.
They were so high
on the best skunk
from Amsterdam.
You can't even imagine.
They had the purple haze
mixed with the G13,
mixed with the Jack Harrow,
mixed with the purple kush,
the silver kush,
and the...
the couch cushions.
And they were smoking that stuff
until their wooden teeth
turned brown.
Because that's what they could do
back in those days.
That was...
Did you know the original
zeroth...
the Bill of Rights,
the zeroth amendment was
thou shalt smoke
all the damn pot you want?
And that was the one...
You don't even know about that one, right?
This first one that they sent you.
Well, no, I...
The Democrats said...
The Democrats answered it
back when they was the Republicans.
Remember those days?
Yep.
When we were really little.
When our parents were little.
When our parents were...
Very...
Grandparents.
Yeah, our grandparents were...
When our grandparents were little.
When our great-grandparents were...
After the...
Teenagers.
After the Civil War,
which was painful until removed,
but still left scars behind,
just like any war would.
Well, you'd probably say that
because you're...
I bet your parents are Yankees.
That's right.
We're proud Yankees.
Not from recent...
Not from the days of when
this was a hotbed
in this area of northeastern Ohio
where John Brown even trained
his inabilities.
And the Giddings and the Wades
were from here
who were in Congress
and were downright socialists
who wanted to divide up the South
between the poor
out-of-work white people
and the slaves.
They were going to give everybody
a plot of land and say,
hey, man,
everybody's fine.
But no.
Yeah, right.
That really would have worked.
Gosh, reconstruction.
Well, why wouldn't it have worked?
Everybody was kind of getting along
in some places.
Because my slave-owning ancestors
would have been run off
of their own plantation.
That's why.
That's another problem
they don't consider
is how many...
How many have a life?
This is Southerners
were punished
by the Confederacy.
Many, many, many.
In fact, it was a violation
of the right of pre-assembly
in which is in our
American conscience.
I never...
The American consecration.
Yeah, they started
deporting abolitionists
who were born and raised
in the South
for saying, well, you know,
it ain't in the Bible
that it's a good thing here.
We're against it.
Just...
Out of the South?
Well, I'm of mixed blood
and mixed feelings
because my pappy
is a Southerner
from South Carolina
in a long line of...
But not...
Well, some of them were...
His cousins,
his insane cousins
were plantation owners.
But my mom was a Yankee.
But her grandma
was something much worse
than a Yankee.
An immigrant
from a foreign country.
It was a foreign country.
It didn't even speak English.
It was called Ireland.
And we're surrounded
by foreign countries.
Lazy, shiftless.
You've heard about the Irish,
haven't you?
Lazy, shiftless, stealing.
Drunks.
Yeah, drunks.
They're all drunks.
They've given an Irishman
one drink
and he's just completely gone.
What's an Irish St. Patrick's
State dinner?
It's a six-pack
and a boiled potato.
They're out hard, hard.
Oh, and my...
And everyone laughs.
And my Yankee mother's
grandfather was a Yankee.
An immigrant
from another country
where they're famous
for being money-grubbing,
greedy,
and big in show business
and banking and stuff.
Yes, the Scottish.
Putman.
Yeah, that's what they said.
That's what they said.
We know what that means.
You're used to the whole culture,
so to speak,
of transgenderism.
Yeah.
Because when you wear,
you know, like a skirt
and then lift up a big,
heavy, huge log
and you're going to pump
some...
You know,
one of the forehead
with it real hard
if you possibly can
and you have to keep
worrying about what,
you know, like...
I'm an American
made of immigrants.
My right foot
is a money-grubbing,
old, miserly Scot.
And my left foot
is a drunk Irishman.
And my right hand
is an evil,
perverted Englishman.
And my left hand
is a Nazi
from Germany.
Is it your family
that invented the haggis bites?
Just bites of haggis?
You don't have to have
the whole...
Just bites?
Or slammers.
No, that was Dave's.
That was Dave's.
Oh, wait.
No, Dave was the other kind.
Dave's descended from...
Well, they aren't even
white people.
But Dave's descended from...
I am descended from
many, many groups.
But the main thing
I would say,
there's the Mediterranean area.
Pizza eaters.
Mm-hmm.
It's quite well represented.
And I'm quite proud of it
because we invented
everything we could.
in Europe
while the rest of you people
were picking your noses
in caves up there
in the north.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Yeah, I'd like to...
I'd like...
You Romans
had to go and make slaves
of my people, you know.
That's a...
Where do you think
we get the word slave?
It's because the English
were enslaved
by the Romans.
Of course,
as I understand it,
the English really wanted
the Romans to stay
because they made
such great cloth
and weapons
and pottery
and just all kinds of...
Their cloth was so...
They were so smooth
and they could make
the hair so purdy.
But the Saxons
And you know,
there's spear chuckers
in England at that time.
They're just...
It was like,
come back.
Show us how to make
that really good wine.
All we have is this grog.
with the great guys
and all that stuff, man.
They were mean.
They were nasty.
They tried to abolish
the Roman blood.
There was still a lot
of it around at the time.
And they used to go
in villages
and blind people
or, you know,
young males
they would blind them
or remove their testicles
which is a part
of the anatomy,
you know,
that everyone's familiar.
Well, you know,
it's...
If it ain't one thing,
it's another.
And every country
gets their time
in the sun
where they get to
enslave everybody
around them
or on the other side
of the world.
And then the next thing
you know,
they're the ones
that are broke
and miserable
and everybody's
laughing at them.
Really?
It's just everybody
gets their turn.
I'm waiting for the
Aborigines
to get their turn again.
I would hope so
after all these years.
What's it been like?
Somebody said
it was like 30,000 years.
Right.
Since they were...
Since they had the giant...
Since they were
enslaving people.
Well, since they had
the means to wipe out
humanity
and to destroy
their surroundings
which they didn't think
were important.
You know, they just thought
you're kind of
self-born into this world
like Bodhidharma
or something like that.
Next thing you know,
you snap on a lotus.
You know, you just pedal
and go dancing
down the beach
and try to get a pickup
on the 40,
41-year-old truck driver.
You know, some kind of
bizarre old...
Well, in those days
you could do that
because there were still
plenty of resources
and not many people.
But not on the spaceships.
Well,
on the spaceships
I guess we won't have
anything to worry about,
will we?
We're hoping.
They won't let us worry,
will they?
Yeah, that's another...
That's another thing
to try to do.
What if you're screwy, man?
What if it's like,
you know,
mind control
so you don't worry
and mind control
so you do have a good time
and you can...
What about that?
I don't know, man.
I don't know.
What would Bob do?
What wouldn't Bob do?
What would Bob not do?
Now, there's a question.
Yeah.
Bob Dobbs I'm talking about.
Not...
I mean, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Not just any old
Noah Campbell.
Those are a dime
a billion.
A dime a billion?
Yeah, a dime...
Yeah, a dime a billion.
A dime a billion.
That's how...
That's what Bob's are worth.
Playing Bob's.
Then there's the...
J.R. quote
Bob unquote
Dobbs.
And that's different.
And the listener
can gaze upon
the visage
of J.R. Bob Dobbs
if they...
If they were to look
at subgenius.com,
they could also download
1,500 hours of
quote,
slack,
unquote.
But I don't expect
him to do that.
I don't expect him
to do nothing.
I give up on him.
I don't know
what they expect,
but I just...
I just throw up my hands.
Well, they don't not only
see the visage of Bob,
they can see
10 billion thousand
trillion interpretations
of the visage of Bob.
That is true.
And unfortunately,
that also makes me sad
because now,
what am I supposed to do?
Each time I interpolate
Bob's facial feature
in his smiling face,
I start a whole new diatribe,
an internal dialogue
that pushes me
in a different direction.
It means this.
It means that.
It's pretty mean,
all right.
Yep.
Mean to me so far.
In the meantime...
How can you argue
with all those arteries
of enlightenment?
Yeah.
It's in his forehead
having a bad afternoon.
We're having arterial bleeding
of enlightenment
on this show.
We just...
Enlightenment's just pumping,
squirting out of us
with every heartbeat.
It's going to be gone soon.
We better hurry
and finish this show
before it's all gone out.
I'm running out of breath
and enlightenment
and everything.
I mean...
God, I can't do that
for very long anymore.
What a bloody mess.
Yeah.
Man, wow.
Well, that's because
we've been talking about
the major bloodshedders
on our planet right now.
The dystopians.
The...
The denisovians.
Wow, man.
We just invited...
Didn't we do something
during the last half hour
to get ourselves
targeted by fanatics?
Oh, probably several things,
not just one thing.
Right, but how many...
Which fanatics
are going to come after us?
The T-Buckers.
The Muslamics.
The Christ Punchers.
Remember that band
in Detroit?
Yep.
The Putin Thumpers.
The car keyers.
Right.
The fiction haters.
The fiction lovers.
They were the worst, man.
Both of them.
The feet fetishists.
The popular cowboys.
You know, the popular cowboys
are so jealous of you,
Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
They wish they could be
as lonesome as you.
Yes.
I corresponded with those folks
and I found them to be
just as good as stumps in the rain.
There were no artificial mistreatment
or any kind of miscalculation.
That's just how they felt.
Did you say they were as good
as stumps in the rain?
Yeah.
Did I?
Yeah, I don't know,
but that's what it sounded like to me.
Does it resonate
with adamantine hardness?
Adamantine hardness?
a stump in the red.
You know, like...
Adamantium.
That was a great band.
Yeah.
Adamantium.
I'm just saying that
I never actually...
I wouldn't know a song
by that band.
I wouldn't know
anything about it.
I remember them,
unfortunately.
Well,
did I already say
subgenius.com
and people can
check it out?
And what other news?
What's coming up?
Well, another show.
No, that's the best news.
And...
Well, I guess that's
about it.
Well, there's lots of things
coming up.
There's X Day coming up.
There's Starwood coming up.
There's millions of things
coming up.
Well, we've already...
It's going to be
a hot, hot summer.
Yeah.
Let's hope it's
not that hot.
We'll see.
Friends,
I'm going to
have to sign off here.
And I'm going to
have to say praise Bob
because I know
Bob will kill me.
He'll kill you too, buddy.
He'll kill us.
If we don't play
our cards right.
So,
it's Dave fading time.
Dave, you can start
into your lecture now.
I'll start.
Bye, Dave.
There he went.
He's gone.
And we're going to be gone,
thankfully,
very soon.
I guess I'll just
leave this music on.
And I'll let
somebody else say
what this is.
Praise Bob.