Meanwhile, gaseous rhetoric and stupid, bombastic, empty speechifying.
The subgenius power of Slack.
They need Jesus.
Thank you, Lee Murr, and this is Hour of Slack number 1229,
which is a rerun of number 344 from 1992, 17 years ago.
Because we're really busy on other subgenius projects.
This one is a mix of recordings from various subgenius shows at various stations,
including Cleveland's WCSB from long before we moved to Cleveland.
You'll hear people who've long since been unpersoned
and much younger voices of people you now think of as old.
Hopefully, you'll also be inspired to donate to the WCSB pledge drive coming up next week.
A week at all.
Use a donation, actually.
Did I mention that there's a subgenius revival with the amino acids in Detroit this November 28th?
And weekly revivals in Chicago all through December?
No?
Well, see subgenius.com events for details.
And with that, we hop into the Wayback Machine and vanish backwards!
Backwards!
And for our own part, we see very clearly that unless justice be done to others,
it will not be done to us.
The program for the world's peace, as we see it, is this.
The Church of the Subgenius in the name of J.R. Bob Dole.
Yes.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
So good, so good to be back.
Back.
On the airwaves with tonight's hour of Slack show,
which, by the way, will be a collision of subgenius shows.
It's been a while since we've let all the shows that are the original shows done out there in subgenius land
just collide in the time warp of the church, the bosom of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
We have a special guest here tonight, the Tevinator,
who, uh...
Tevinator?
Are you, uh, prepared with your statement?
You may proceed.
We are the future, the children of a new era.
We have been born from the mistakes of the past
and are expected to pick up the pieces of the future.
We are shackled by a dysfunctional system
that is unable to keep pace with our hyper-accelerated culture.
We have been told what to think by fundamentalist demons
masquerading as leaders and saints.
We are expected to ignore the damages
inflicted by a dismal...
We are forced to watch our rights being whittled to death.
Our time is now!
We must use all the tools in our power.
We must utilize our brains as primary weapons.
We must harness the power of chaos.
We must forcibly occupy cyberspace.
We must assimilate.
We must subvert.
We must pave a new leadership for a new millennium.
We must regain control of our destiny.
Our lives are meaningless.
Pray.
Please, follow me.
Ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay.
And now, dear friends,
the show you've been waiting for,
the subgenius radio ministry hour of...
Slacker, yes.
It's worthless because it's merely the work
of a few unbridled individualists.
Artistic value is achieved collectively
by each man subordinating himself
to the standards of the majority.
I read that in your column yesterday.
You did? Thank you.
Now, the greatness of Peter Keating's personality
lies in the fact that there is no personality
stamped upon his building.
Quite true.
Thus he represents not himself,
but the multitude of all men together.
And produces great big marble bromides.
I believe I'm failing to sell you, Peter Keating.
Why, no.
You're succeeding.
Your Keating is worthless.
So he's probably the right choice for that building.
He's sure to be popular.
You wouldn't expect me to pick a man of merit, would you?
We are told we are weak,
incapable of grasping scale,
afraid of ourselves,
and desperate to push responsibility
for all events in our lives onto them.
We are insistently trained to accept
our corporal existence.
As hopeless in itself.
To become subservient to the greater good.
We are perpetually conditioned,
encouraged, and blackmailed
into self-restriction,
into narrower and narrower perceptions of ourselves,
our own importance,
our own potential, and our own experience.
We are trained to ignore the evidence
of our senses and experiences,
and to feel guilt when we glimpse
the subgenius.
Our
world.
What?
All personnel, please leave the area.
We are starting the final countdown.
TSC, this is Florida Control.
All power for the shields checking out at 100 percent.
All systems are go.
Please run final checks on all shield power elements.
All personnel, please leave the area.
We are starting the final countdown.
Hello? Hello?
We're recording. Everything's going fine.
...
... back through that back door on this platform.
Don't you think it's time we let them have a glimpse of what it's like?
Don't you think it's time that you sat down and, uh,
came face to face with your destiny?
... glimpses of the auditorium and the sanctuary.
...
Uh, isn't it about time you came face to face with...
... it's easy enough to do?
...
... Jesus...
... you ever...
... see?
... face to face with my destiny.
Now, this famous curtain rod depository was on the site of Adelie Plaza.
Yes, right here at Let's Make Adelie Plaza, we're going to begin the quiz show of all quiz shows,
the...
... Let That President...
... 1963 election giveaway.
...
And our first gag guest is Jiro, the monkey that's been trained to act like George Bush.
Let's give him a big hand.
...
Jiro can walk on stilts, dance jigs on his hands, and somersault through hoops like any ordinary circus monk.
But he can also mimic the president's actions and emotions with uncanny accuracy.
...
He is an actor, not just an animal doing tricks said Taro Murasaki, 30 move on of Jiro's trainer.
That is the art of Suroma Washi.
In the Stomach Medicine ad, Jiro parodies the pain of overindulgence in booze
in the very human ritual of vowing never ever again.
...
Jiro's most recent skit is equally sharp-egged.
Bush-san coked Morisaki.
Bush-san, the monkey, gags, pretends to vomit,
then closes his eyes and swoons in the manner of flu-stricken President George Herbert Walker Bush
during the state dinner with Prime Minister Kiichi Miyazawa last month.
Poor taste, sure, but it elicits guffaws from both Japanese and listeners of KPFA.
At the time of the shooting,
there seemed to be some commotion.
I just am unable to describe a flash of light or smoke or something,
which caused me to feel that something out of the ordinary had occurred there on the embankment.
The Church of the Subgeniuses in the name of J.R. Baldos.
And the
Enough.
My victim.
Tribune.
Who in the world...
regrette the loaf...
...I am?
How long have you been here?
Peace, peace in the Middle East
Everlasting, loving peace
Joy, joy in the Middle East
Peace, peace
Everlasting, loving peace
Whoever said the subgeniuses were not politically correct?
Can't go wrong
Urgent peace
Peace, everlasting peace
Peace, peace
Everlasting peace
And please don't get me wrong
I'm not accusing
What I'm trying to say is
If you have to lose your self-respect
In order to be popular
Is it worth it?
Go! Go!
You know, we tried every kind of treatment, and it just failed.
She wanted to be cremated. Would that make a difference?
No, that makes no difference. If she wants to be cremated, that's what you do.
So, in other words...
And that's more reasonable.
If I wanted to bring the lighter fluid and the matches...
No, you can't do a lighter fluid and match. You have to have her cremated at the crematory.
Well, she wanted me to do it.
No, you can't cremate her.
So, it has to be done at a crematory.
Would that cost extra?
No, no. The cremation is less reasonable. It's less than the burial, of course.
Okay, well, that sounds very good.
And one more thing. She wanted me to cut a piece of her off.
Cut a piece of her off?
Just to save to remember her. Her ring finger.
You can't cut a piece of her off.
You can't do that either.
Because she said that I should. I didn't want to do it.
No, you can't cut a piece of her off unless you take a piece of her hair.
But not her finger.
Huh?
Her finger. I couldn't...
Oh, no. You couldn't keep her finger. No way.
No.
I couldn't eat her flesh.
Huh?
No, you can't.
She wanted me to eat her flesh.
You can't do that. I'm sorry.
I'm not a cannibal, ordinarily.
Well, I don't know.
What time can you come down to see me tomorrow?
Now, I have a funeral here at one o'clock.
So, can you come down in the morning?
Well, who...
I guess I can.
I'd like to see you at ten o'clock tomorrow morning here at the funeral home.
Okay. And one more question.
The man who's... Is it a man or a woman?
It's a woman or a woman at the funeral. Could I eat their flesh?
You want to eat their flesh?
I'm a ghoul.
I'm a real cool ghoul.
I don't know about you, but before the election, I'm gonna have to get well-earned at least...
Make sure that you...
Ow! Hey!
to demonstrate.
I enter the air
and screech as the words
again and again.
Screech!
It's commercial.
It makes me more and more desperate.
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
These dedicated television viewers.
Oh, my, I just don't know.
It's been difficult
to take the president seriously
every time.
I never knew you.
Oh, you stupid idiot!
This stuff costs money!
I'm sorry.
I spoke a little out of turn,
but boy, what a skullbuster
of a headache I've got.
Doing this show this early
in the morning is no picnic,
I tell you.
It's at a time like this
that I want to kick back
and relax with a silly chocolate bar.
Yeah, they say this isn't
a funny show,
it's just a silly show,
and it's at that time
I want a silly chocolate bar.
The powerhouse bar
that knocks you silly.
Covered with creamy milk chocolate,
it's zesty, tangy, tasty, yeasty,
with caramel nougat,
crunchy walnuts,
and a rich butter taste.
It contains sugar,
cocoa butter,
milk, chocolate,
and lecithin added as an emulsifier.
Salt, artificially
flavored with cough syrup,
vanillin,
a vanilla substitute,
and 27 milligrams
of millivanillin,
an artificial,
phony sugar substitute,
butter, almonds,
with salt,
artificial flavor,
more sugar,
more lecithin,
more everything
in a silly chocolate bar.
Enjoy a silly chocolate bar,
and you can be cool,
like me.
I'm a real cool ghoul.
Oh, they say.
Ooh, they say.
We have spoken now,
surely in terms too concrete
to admit of any further doubt or question.
An evident principle runs through
the whole program I have outlined.
I'm a real cool ghoul.
Very in that area,
so it would behoove you
to use a funeral home
in that particular locale.
Hmm.
Well,
what if we, like,
had them cremated?
Uh, you still would probably use
a funeral home in your own locale
rather than come way down here into Neptune.
What hospital is the body in?
Paul Kimball.
Oh, it's in Paul Kimball.
Hmm.
Uh-huh.
Well, it would do you better to go to one of them local funeral homes
rather than to try to come down here.
Um, well, what if we decided to, like,
chop him up and eat him?
Eat his flesh?
That would be fine.
Y'all go ahead and get him and chop him up and eat him.
Because that would do you good.
We're a real cool ghoul.
Yeah, that would do you just right to chop him up and eat him.
Why don't you get some lye and put him in a pot of lye,
and then it'll all dissolve in the lye.
Wow, thanks, man.
That's a good idea, isn't it?
Woo-hoo!
All right, whore.
What?
I said do your thing, whore.
Is this any way for a funeral director to be talking?
Hey, yo, you there?
You know, she's like, I'm responsible.
I'll just go here.
And why would you wait till 1225 at night to call a funeral director?
Because I get—
You should be calling one tomorrow morning early.
Because—
And it's one of your choice.
Well, let me tell you, I've got an inheritance coming.
I've got money, all right?
You know, it's just—I don't have to explain every yard.
No, you really don't have to explain none of it to me,
because I'm not going to have the body.
Well, you won't do it?
I'm not going to have it.
This is the third prank call I've had tonight about dead people,
and I'm not going to have anybody that's dead,
so I don't need to listen to your—
But you're a funeral home.
No, what are you saying?
What, are you insane?
Yes, I'm very much insane.
Do you know Jerry Lewis?
I'm Jerry Lewis.
You know what?
Yeah, Jerry Lewis?
I'm Jerry Lewis.
Oh, that's cute.
That's—no, I really am.
Listen to me.
You know, I love to talk to an idiot once in a while.
You know what?
It makes me laugh.
Now, am I in communication with some sort of—
Is this supposed to be your collar here?
Is this supposed to be your little collar?
Is this what you call a little collar?
Hey, let's lose the background.
Yeah, thanks.
Now, caller, I want you to tell me your most embarrassing moment.
My most embarrassing moment?
That's right.
Well, go ahead.
We're all ears.
Well, I creeped myself into the church and nailed myself to their cross
and was standing there above the altar when all of a sudden my loincloth came down.
They all thought I was Jesus Christ until they saw that I was—
I'm like a subgenius.
It is the time to go public with the war on Satan.
We must go public because when the government made ease to wipe out drug users and homosexuals, it was not enough.
Yes, we need more.
They have developed terms that will mark people who take drugs and listen to loud music.
It discards the skin of people who listen to certain vibrations of music.
It discards drug users also.
They have terms to kill all major sinners who kill the Christians.
Satan kills.
God will kill him.
How many bodies die?
Children of God dying.
We will say a prayer.
God help us cast out the infidels.
We welcome Satan's plundering, pillaging, and killing.
For Satan kills only the depraved and wretched.
God, let the gargoyles loose from the gates of hell.
You said that you're a weapon against wretchedness.
Let them cast out their feces.
Let them cast out the faces of earth into the quagmire of human filth and wickedness.
God will stamp his heel into the sinner's face.
Then Satan will judge and beat them down again.
Then they will be cast into hell.
Their insides will come out from within.
And all sinners who don't die will be old and decrepit.
Who died? Christ? Why? Your sins?
God only son died.
He died for you.
Okay, ma'am. He's going to talk to you.
Okay? Okay.
He'd rather do it himself.
Okay.
Hey.
Yeah?
Now, listen here.
It was a dreadful day when everything happened.
Be quiet.
I don't know how long ago. Don't ask him. He's drunk.
Well, listen, guys.
I'd like to say, and we know that you have drank too much,
but do you have a mother and a father?
Hell no. I'm 21. He's 18.
And you don't have a mother?
No.
So she's dead.
Is she dead?
She's dead.
Is your dad dead?
My daddy got ran over by a car.
Oh? How long ago?
Two years ago.
Oh? The clock's not working.
Really? Wil, do you work?
Do I work?
Yes, ma'am.
Do you work at Philip's?
Do I work?
Hers does?
She works at Philip's.
Okay, so here it is.
Does your brother work?
Yes.
Well, it looks like you guys don't have enough to do.
I don't understand, mom.
Well, to be getting on the phone this time of night and be drunk and talking out of your mind, it sort of sounds ridiculous now, doesn't it, really?
Well, I mean, I'm sorry, ma'am.
No, I don't have a daughter named Glenda. I have to.
Well, you know, I tried to tell you, Mary, because I'm sorry.
Well, I know.
And I don't know how in the hell this all came about. I really don't.
Well, I don't either, but you know what? I don't think it's an accident you called me.
Now, your name is Johnson.
Yes.
And what's your first name, did you say?
David.
David Johnson.
Well, anyway, what I was going to tell you, David, it isn't an accident that you called me.
Is it not?
Let me tell you why.
Because I know I used to be a real miserable person, and I done things that I knew that I shouldn't do.
But I was running, and I was looking for something to fill a void that I had in my heart.
And like you, you're not happy, are you?
No, ma'am, not really.
I hate my job.
I hate my wife.
I hate both my kids.
I hate my brother.
I hate myself.
All I ever do is get drunk.
That's all I ever do.
I hate myself.
Well, that's what it all boils down to, David.
And really, you know, we're not supposed to hate ourselves.
And it's not that you hate yourself.
You have just made such a mess of your life.
My daddy did that before he died.
He probably did that.
He didn't help you any if he was a mean person.
He was.
He used to beat me up and my brother.
He beat you both up.
Was your mother a good person?
No.
Do what?
Was your mother a good person?
My mother was a saint.
She was a saint.
Do you think she was a Christian?
I know for a fact she was.
She used to make me go to church and I didn't like her because of that.
But you really now wish that you had a...
I wish my mama was here so she could take me to church today.
Are there any questions?
Please ask your questions so that all the members may hear.
Yes, John?
What are you doing quite this early in the morning?
I just wanna stick to my ways.
You think cup d después a lot of people?
Have you been shooting these ads a lot of times?
Hello.
Almost.
What should I do now?
She's only one over there.
Shouldn't she be ready?
Honestly, you and I are just having fun.
Also,
Oh, feel the energy.
There's the grounding and self-centering.
We need to do a grounding and self-centering right now.
Oh, I can feel the change coming on right now.
Joe, speak it, Joe.
Now, we want you to clear your mind and think only of yourself.
Only of you.
In the name of Jesus.
There's no place like my ego.
There's no place.
Boy, that was refreshing, wasn't it?
Bring me back to John Lennon and I'm me mine.
I'm me mine.
Hey, Stang, thanks again for clarifying again this thing about the Trevino-ist, you know,
making sure that...
It can't be said enough.
No.
As long as the secular Trevino-ists are still launching Trevino heads on Thursdays, Easter,
or any other time, that we cannot rest.
Our vigilance can never cease.
We have the mighty bleeding head.
The mighty bleeding head.
The mighty bleeding Trevino head.
There's one right here in the station frame.
Just stop.
It's a head sort of manifestation.
Bleeding head good.
Heel head bad.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, you can't do that.
You can't deliver a plug on this show.
Shameless advertising there.
Food plugging.
Time to crank the preacher.
Immediately cover over with obfuscation.
Yeah, we're going to have to bleep that out in the...
We'll have to adjust that all later so none of you heard that.
I don't know who you think you are.
You can't come on the air and do a plug on our show.
Mr. That is Lord.
That is Lord.
I'm not doing that on this show.
Oh, who's plugging?
I'm just asking you to prank him.
Well, now look, you can stop scratching that squirrel and get back to basics as you
study your subgenius doctrine in the book of pre-scriptures.
Okay, and here it is now.
Doctrine one.
As we walk down the path way of life, do you ever turn to yourself and say, damn it,
where do my left socks go?
Now, you know, Women and Children's listens to this show.
Women and Children's.
Women and Children's come into my laundry room and steal my socks.
I can't get up.
I'm falling.
And I can't get up.
Oh, my God.
You can't get up.
Well, you'd better buy some of that senior home security stuff, Missy, or else you'll
get all out of control.
Yes, join a support group for senior support socks.
Oh, that was too much.
Well, now we're back in the tunnel of love, trickling along at a pleasantly slow pace.
And not much more can happen to us.
I tell you, this evening has been one of those times.
It's what you call a Maalox moment.
Well, look, that's what it says here.
You know, we've got to get better writers.
That's all I have to say.
Well, anyway, off the record, it's been fun.
But, you know, it kind of gets, it wears you down after a while.
You come on out here.
You do these shows.
It gets so that, you know, it's just not fun anymore.
And that's when you need a little bit of new blood.
And what we call the time control effect.
I thought he was running away.
Dr. Fred is here.
I'm here!
He's with us.
And Sister Clone's back.
And the flow, the show, it's floating down around you right now.
Golden baubles floating through the air.
Dr. Should we have a little epitaph for Dr. St. Bogumil?
Dr. He's not dead yet.
Here we are, high over Humboldt Bay, looking out on the beautiful lights and the rain.
It's a pleasant sight.
Dr. We're drifting gently with the radio show.
Dr. Drifting down.
Dr. High above the stratosphere.
Dr. Drifting down into your headphones.
Dr. Out there.
Dr. Below us, we see the lights of Arcata Eureka.
Dr. It's all so beautiful.
Dr. The special little lights.
Dr. The light of Bob's country bumpers.
Dr. And we have no telephones up here where we're at, so we're not taking any calls.
Dr.
Juggle, juggle, juggle.
Dr. KHSU with Dr. Fred and Sister Cline,
St. Dogzomatic from Arcata there,
as well as some prank call reenactments.
Submitted by some anonymous friends of James Blanchard, I think.
Dr. You also heard, dear friends, of course, WCSB in Cleveland,
Dr. Reverend Cole's show, on which I was lucky enough to appear with
Dr. St. Stymie de Bergerac and Reverend Mary Squared, au contraire,
Dr. and of course, also the most recognizable voices in subgenius radio,
Dr. Howell and puzzling evidence there on KPFA in Berkeley.
Dr. Ah, yes, what a lovely, horrible thing.
Dr. Putting a little rain seed here, a little rain seed there.
Ha, ha, ha.
We're a little short of oxygen, but that doesn't hurt us.
We don't need it.
Dr. Fortunately, due to these gills I got at Bobstown,
Bobstown, I can breathe almost any kind of thing.
Absolutely. Acid rain doesn't bother us either.
We're impervious.
Dr.
Dr. Looking down below the lights of Arcata and Eureka,
Dr. in Bob's country bunker, a special little light shining off in
Dr. We ought, California. It's so nice to be here.
These guys, flaming inverted cross.
Dr. It looks like, yes, a flaming inverted cross on somebody's lawn in Manila.
I don't understand it.
Dr. Manila?
There appears to be a dead baby at the same house.
Dr. Perhaps it too is suspended from the light.
Dr. Do you think you could zero the show in a little closer to this cross burning on the lawn in Manila?
Uh, standby.
Dr. Hold on, Fred, hold on. We're looking.
Dr. Twenty-six Americans.
Dr. Here we go, here we go. Hold on.
Dr. Oh, yeah, that is an inverted cross.
Dr. P-L-O-T. P-L-O-T.
Dr. Oh, oh, I'm kind of dizzy. Did we have to go so low so quickly?
Dr.
Dr. Ah!
Dr. Quality, quality, quality.
Dr. Ten eight.
Dr. On the air and standing by.
It's a success
You know what?
Like I say, it's not an accident you called me
Why not?
Because, did you know that God loves you so much?
He loves you so much
Even no matter what all you do
Even that you're drunk as a dog
He still loves you
Now, he doesn't like your sins
He doesn't like things you've done
And he knows you've made a mess of your life
But he realizes that you're just weak
You know, you're just a person, a human
That makes no sense
But he loves you
And I'd like to be your mother
I'd like for you to go to church with me
I'd take the place of your mother
Really
Ma'am, this is so touching
I just, I know my brother's drunk too
But you tell him the same thing you just told me
We may feel better, hang on
Hello
Yeah
Now, your name is David?
And you really are her brother?
His brother?
Uh-huh
Are you drunk?
Uh, yeah
Well, how come you guys, how come you guys get drunk?
Well
You all right?
Hey
Cheers
Just a second
Hey, Bob
Don't hang up, will you?
I won't hang up
The voluntary relinquishing of responsibility for our lives and actions
Is one of the greatest enemies of our time
Oswald was a radar operator
He'd have about as much use for Russian as a cat has for pajamas
These books have gotten to your mind, Mr. Gerson
Here's Johnny
Ask not what your country can do for you
Ask what you can do for your country
Here is a bulletin
But there are certain things that we can all agree on
There is a right and a left
Uh-huh
Let me hear you say uh-huh
There is a dark and a light
Uh-huh
There's a good and a bad
A wrong and a right
Now, to the pagan
Uh-huh
There's a lord versus lady
There was a yin versus yang
But the subgenius
Yang man
Well
Well, Bob might have had a lot of yin
Take it from me, folks
Connie had a lot of yang
It may take a subgenius to make all that money
But, honey
It took a Connie to spend it
Charming, charming Irene
My heart is filled with joy
Your love, you said, is mine
And all of very good
You're good, you're good, Irene
Heaven sent you to me
Charming, charming Irene
I'm in love with you
You'll be imploding with joy before you know it
Oh, happy, happy joy
Did you notice how
When I
When I was in love with you
Launched the head in the name of Ren and Stimpy
How the audience just went nuts
Absolutely went wild
Truly, Ren and Stimpy cuts across all
Almost all cultural and whatever kind of borders
Oh, it brings me back to those days of my childhood
In front of the television with that audiovisual
Pouring into my eyes
Eating those highly sugared cereals
And taking a couple of hits off that whipped cream bottle
That's where it all started
Good, this is Ren Huat
And this is Stimson J. Cat
Of the Ren and Stimson J. Cat
of the Ren and Stimson J. Cat
And you're listening to the Hour of Flack on K-N-O-N
Keep listening, you idiot
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Else I shall damn you
Good job
In the name of Ren and Stimpy
Yeah!
Hang on, hang on
The secondary launching
The secondary launching is incredible
Hang on, hang on, hang on
Bleeding head good, healed head bad
Connie is the true goddess of the sub-genius church. You can't con Connie.
God's a ghost for great ideas. When I'm good, I'm very, very good. But baby, when I'm slack, I'm better.
Testify.
Yes, Lord. Amen. Amen.
Well, before you go getting in all this dogmatic stuff, we just want to welcome you back. You've been gone so long, Sister Clone.
Yeah, where the hell have you been?
It's been a difficult absence.
You know, I've been out here for a while.
I know. I'm really still not sure what happened. I...
Were you off studying the ways of Bob?
No, I...
She was studying the ways of Hobie.
I don't know if it was a dream or if it really happened, but I think that I was...
Studying the ways of Akira.
I was kidnapped.
So, I do know Akira.
Oh, go ahead. Go ahead.
I was kidnapped by a...
Don't let us big, powerful sub-genius doctors frighten you, Sister Clone. Go ahead. Speak. Speak.
Oh, well, it's so... I'm still so shaken up by my experiences.
I can imagine.
I was kidnapped by someone who attempted to deprogram me.
Force-fed me Pepsi and aspirin as an antidote to what they said.
What was a deep... I was having a problem.
408.
And, you know...
Yes, yes.
It was actually working. I was attempting to invoke the power of Bob.
Straight out of Brooklyn, boy!
Yo, boy! Straight out of Brooklyn!
And you invoked that power of Bob, and what happened?
Well, I don't know, but I woke up lying in the parking lot next to a 7-Eleven.
Clutching a Pepsi, wondering if it had all been just a dream.
Whether they had actually deprogrammed me and learned some of the secrets...
Oh, it's them sub-genius people taking your voice away!
And they're giving you nothing but this parking little howl, and all you can do is just kinda yop, yop and yop and...
Scientists announced today that time travel is theoretically possible.
An article on page two of the San Francisco Examiner postulated that a gravitational field...
could, in theory, and in accordance with the beliefs of modern physics, influence time within a controlled area.
Ah...
The problem is total disorientation and confusion of all elements of life by the renegade rogue device.
Wait, wait, wait. There's two of you over there.
Wait, who's she? What's happening?
We could turn him into space and now...
The problem is it...
Don't take that! How about you?
Oh, Gesundheit.
It's real hard to try to fix this thing when it's going haywire and...
Here we go.
The effects could be disastrous to our own continuum.
There we go.
Oh! They're shooting at us...
Okay, we're climbing to the top now, over the hill. The sub-geniuses are all around me.
How do we get out of this?
I've only got a few bullets left. I'm gonna have to...
Oh, the cops! Wait a minute. I didn't have anything to do with this.
Okay, you're under arrest now.
Wow, I'm passing out.
And you're in the sub-genius gym.
I'm going crazy.
You hear the water dripping and the interrogator's voice.
Hey, who's that? Oh, holy moly!
All right, stand launch.
One, two, three.
Ignition.
Oh, my God.
Lift off.
Oh, oh, I'll get it.
All right, if I could just shear this bolt, I could...
Okay, here we go.
Project on bad.
Yeah, well, you see, um...
They said that the problem is that instead of influencing the external continuum, the Crononaut, or Time Traveler, might, uh, reduce his, uh...
How would this one put it?
It's not even in the English language.
That's what he likes.
You like it, huh?
What do you want?
No, that's not it.
You're wicked here somewhere else, and you're stupid now.
Is this where S87 hit him?
I'm just talking to myself.
Oh, Nicole, I'm sorry, you know?
любой становится сущеerweiseembresстран.
It's not before my death that there should have been a new square tidy universimum.
Right, there's a GED written up there today.
or too deep baking?
I mean, is this what happens?
Well, you know, this was an oral use of prairie squid,
which I cannot recommend to any subgenius.
It's definitely out.
I got a shot of street sepia right down my gullet,
and things have not been the same since.
I hate it when that happens.
Oh, Lord.
I don't know if I will recover.
However, I have been using snake oil.
I mean, not the Dobbs brand snake oil,
but something's going to get me going again, I'm sure.
Will you be well enough to attend
special anniversary celebrations
of the Day of Infamy
occurring tomorrow throughout Humboldt County?
The Day of Infamy, of course, yeah.
Boy, how destructive this thing is.
You know, it's damaging the fabric of the universe
and the space-time continuum
all through all time.
Well, that's what happens
when you use that excess technology
without a reason.
It's what we call forbidden science.
It's the incredible excess technology
that we all have in the show.
Hmm.
Yes, it's Edgar Allan Poe once again,
and I think...
I'm afraid not.
Well, you know, we've got other things.
We've got lots of stuff for you.
We've got gags, cosmic truth stories.
We have 28 minutes left in the show.
It's the meaning of life.
It's the meaning of life,
that little carrot in your backyard
that you thought was so unimportant.
Life and life's effluence,
clouded walls and shadow.
Joy, color is the spirit
and the power which wedded nature
gives to us in dower.
A new earth and a new heaven.
Undreamt of by the sensual and the proud.
Slack is the soft voice.
Slack the luminous cloud.
We in ourselves rejoice.
Reverend Cole tried to shoot me last night.
You know, the funny thing is
I really don't...
I wasn't that upset because...
Well, I missed.
I don't fear death.
I don't fear death at all.
I know that I will never be allowed
into the Christian heaven.
Praise Bob.
None of your friends would be there.
Who would want to go?
And the Christian hell is only
for those who believe in it.
It's only there to, like,
scare Muslims and Christians and people.
Trevinoists.
Right.
For those who are afraid
that if they don't believe in it,
they'll go there.
They'll go there.
That's right.
Those are the ones that are on the lowest...
Get the lowest rung.
And everyone knows...
Everyone knows how hard it is
to get a good corned beef sandwich
in heaven, too.
Yeah.
But subgenius hell...
White.
Valhalla.
It's just...
It's the kind of classical hell,
the subgenius hell.
It's called Helle.
With two L's and an E.
Helle.
It's...
Probably...
It's the more organic,
spiritual version
of the escape vessels
of the sex goddesses,
which...
So, like, on X day,
no matter what happens,
if you die as a subgenius
or if you are ruptured up
into the escape vessels,
you either get the spiritual hell
or the techno hell,
which are the...
Which, of course, by the hell,
we mean these are like heaven.
But you have to go through
subgenius hell
in order to be ready
for the pleasure,
in order to be able
to withstand
the increased pleasure
of the subgenius heaven.
It's like a cleansing purgatory
that prepares you
for the true, true slack.
Ah.
Come on.
Over here.
You have to call.
Get out of here.
Back this way,
ladies and gentlemen.
You'll see two-ton Tessie,
the ugliest thing
on the Midwest.
And if you step into this tent,
gentlemen,
no children or...
You will see the most sickening sight.
Your eyes have ever seen
its caution, ladies and gentlemen,
against doing that terrible drug, LSD.
Inside this tent,
my good friends,
is a young man
who experimented
with this deadly drug
and you can see for yourself
the effect it had,
not only on his mind
and his soul,
but on his very body,
right down to his toenails.
And...
here is that young man now.
Hey, Hal.
What is it, my boy?
It's Gary.
Can you guys stop by here
on the way home?
Well, I suppose so.
What's going on over there?
Well, I can't talk about it right now,
but I, uh...
Uh, you'll like it,
whatever it is.
I hope you're not mad at me
for giving you that, uh,
hoot and holler
earlier on in the evening.
No, I'm not.
Um...
But if you guys could stop by,
I'd appreciate it.
You betcha, you bet.
Well, uh...
Hey.
Uh, you have to ask Dr. Brough
because he's, uh,
piloting the space module.
Well, I'm sure he'll be amenable
when he finds out
about the free-frop program.
Oh, wow.
Amenable, abominable, adorable.
Uh, we'll do it.
Sure.
We've got another two and a half weeks,
so see you later.
Okay, uh, we'll be right over
to dip our wicks
in the fountain of eternal pleasure.
That's located right off
Cajunga Boulevard
in beautiful Oak Town, California.
And we'll stop by
and pick up some ice cream, too.
Is that all right, Auntie May?
Wait a minute.
Who am I talking to now?
This is the phony caller.
You know, it's so strange
to be disembodied
right at the moment.
You seem rather disembodied.
Floating, floating here.
I might be mistaken.
That girl ain't got her pants on.
Uh, I hear zippers here and there.
Yeah, well, that's a check
we'll see right here.
The boys are here.
I want boysied out, boys!
The boys is here.
Straight out of Brooklyn
and boysie all over again!
Talk to me, number three.
Talk to me.
Uh-oh.
Yes, yes.
So, so, are you,
are you deathly ill?
Can we send a care basket, perhaps,
so we can get you out of here?
I'm gonna go get my chocolate-covered son.
Here goes my wish!
Actually, it's just,
it's just a voice, you know.
I, I, I'm, it hurts to talk,
but I'm doing it.
I'm doing it.
He's doing it for Bob, damn it!
I give testimony.
I mean, there's a reward.
There's a bounty out for my voice.
If you should find it,
I will give you...
I'm gonna hit you on the head
and give you the healing power of Bob!
Get a witness.
I will give you my seat
on the Exorcist.
If you can find my voice,
children, there is a quest
in Arcata tonight.
I have given a secret treasure
to the boy.
Your map is buried in,
it's on the plaza,
at the foot of President McKinley's feet.
The Lord has blessed this quest.
Exactly.
You follow the map
and you find my voice.
I want every waking subgenius
to head down to the plaza right now
and find that map.
Right now, right now.
Bob, when we find your voice,
we will cage it
and return it to you,
or would you prefer that we fleet it
in some, uh, wild area
so that it could roam,
roam the area?
Actually, just,
just let it watch the antics
with a little bit of prairie squid action,
you know.
Just let it sit
and do the voyeur thing
that it's so fond of.
Special prize
for all you subgeniuses.
We're going to make it down
to that plaza right now.
Constable Bob
will be waiting there for you.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Hey.
When boys around
food fights with the gods
and you're listening
The Subgenius.
Our
House
What else caught your eye at the show, at the devival, Reverend Stang?
Well, I got snagged on a coat hanger at one point when we were trying to...
In your eye?
Yeah, but, you know, I'm on a lot of healing herbs at any given time.
Well, I was going to say, what good would a bleeding Stang head do us?
And launch it.
Well, couldn't you?
Well, not in its presence.
That was one industrial-strength catapult.
I think it could have actually launched it.
Yeah, we could have found out.
Oh, friends, the launching catapult, we hadn't even mentioned that.
It was the most obscene...
All I can say is, if the legs had been spread a little bit more,
the head probably would have flown farther.
Had the legs been spread more, there wouldn't have been any changes in the ladder between them.
Oh, the alabaster legs.
There would have been more head either way.
But the head did squirt around.
You could feel the electricity.
You could feel the electricity in the air from that head launching.
It was a thing.
A thing to behold.
Now we know why she ain't got no legs.
As Jayner, the crazy preacher, Jayner of Little Rock,
he punctuates his every other sentence with,
Help me, somebody.
She ain't got no legs.
My legs are on fire.
Pull the lever down and you go.
We pulled the lever down.
The she ain't got no legs is from the unfortunate incidents of people losing their legs at Doctors for Bob concerts.
We often wondered where those legs went.
And there they were up on stage.
That's true.
With lascivious.
And then they were obviously spread-eagled, mounted on this sort of framework, religious-looking framework.
It was a big platform of cherubim.
Yeah.
It was like, oh, God.
Frightening-looking thing.
But it was a great launching.
And it had a secondary launching.
And the first launching, it landed in somebody's lap.
And they screamed and threw the head up into the air further back into the audience.
People kissing it?
They really responded to the head launching.
Oh, incredible.
Which was the climax of it.
Well, it was way above.
The very first audience to the show.
Dear friends, and before it gets too much later, I think I should at least fill some of you in on what's going on.
In a way, we hate to do that.
But I should explain that you're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
Sponsored by, yes, the Church of the Subgenius.
Tonight's show in particular has been a cross-section of the other subgenius shows from around the country.
There's only two or three other original ones, of which this one is off to compose.
And while you can learn more about our outreach in the name of J.R. Bob Dobbs,
the living avatar of Slack, by writing for free.
And for free.
For free information.
And I'm about to give you that post office box number to write to.
Just drop us a line.
Say, Bob, I don't know if I'm with you yet or not, but I'm willing to hear what you have to say.
I'm willing to try Slack on for size.
One size fits all, dear friends.
Just write to Bob at post office box.
181-417-Cleveland Heights, Ohio 4411.
And also see subgenius.com.
And I know that the way I say that, the way all this sounds, like, it sounds like it's just a joke just to put on.
There's probably nothing at that address.
Well, that's not true.
You're just going to have to drop us a line and you'll find out for free just how much is at that address.
You may find yourself surprised.
There's things to see, say, and do.
Things to think and know.
And you'll pay to know what you really think, won't you?
Yeah, well, we'll find out.
Praise Bob.
Oh, speaking of Bob, last night was the beginning, not only of the first rant and rave and the little extra dribble of Hurricane Bob,
but in that town, Avon, Colorado, where they named their bridge Bob.
A true omen.
They're holding the Bob Festival.
And apparently there's, there's, it's like just this Bob out.
Of course, this is the way the conspiracy tries to water down Bob.
They are basically, it's like the Nissan commercial and all those other ways the conspiracy uses to make.
The pleasant Bob.
The mellow Bob.
The friendly Bob.
Bob beer.
Bob book.
Do you think Bob, well, actually Bob did market a type of beer.
It was called Beer God.
It was a little series of liquor stores in Tennessee called Beer God.
Thirst, beep, er.
I can't, I can't say what it was an er of, but it was like thirst, er.
And, uh, yeah, Beer God.
He also had Burger God, hunger, er.
It was kind of a little chain.
He later, uh, moved, it became very successful in Brazil.
Uh, there are Bob's Burgers, like the McDonald's of Brazil, uh, in, in the competition.
A country well respected for its culinary tastes and skills.
Oh, yeah, it is, actually.
Absolutely.
They're wonderful.
And, uh, they're very American style.
But, you know, I understand the rumor has it that it's Connie that's pulling the strings
behind all of those, uh, huge, uh, businesses.
Oh, you could, you better believe it.
Any of those extra little, those kind of things, that's, Connie, uh, definitely is, it's like
with the Jimmy Swagger.
He was the sort of crazy preacher, but his wife was the one who made the ministers of
beer.
She focused him.
Well, no one knows meat like Connie.
She focused him and whipped him into shape.
She made the bad Bob's say, please and thank you.
I'm telling you, last night.
Oh, no kidding.
That probably ain't all she did.
Remember the guy who had never been put on before?
It was at the sales table after all the preaching and dancing and killing had happened.
Uh, and, and there.
Attempted killing.
The ace and subgenius type people had already, you know, they were, they'd seen the show,
they bought their stuff and they were gone.
So it was only the regular smart bar crowd that were coming down to where the, they encountered
these bookstores.
It was like an ACE store with all these underground comics and amazing sort of, I don't know what
kind of philosophy books.
And if you Leary and happy, yeah, all those sort of rare things that you need, uh, this,
this guy came down and it was like, he, he, uh, was looking at.
At the subgenius table.
I was about to pack up and quit.
And so it worked.
He, but he gave us hard time about the dollar.
He was going, well, what is this all about?
He wanted us to tell him what the church of the subgenius was all about.
Get this.
He goes, would you explain briefly what this was all brief and rough.
Okay.
And we said, look really honestly, this little pamphlet here is the best thing that that's
the only way to really get you to understand this.
It's only a buck.
I mean, he had.
God only knows what he passed.
He didn't pay to get in.
He probably had $40 worth of ecstasy in his pocket or whatever.
And but they didn't know these people wanted to spit out a dollar.
That's you just, that's probably just what you want me to do.
Give you a dollar as if we weren't giving him a 16 page book in return.
I mean, that takes a week to read, but he wouldn't do it.
So at that point I went, he goes, I don't even know who Bob is.
And uh, go be.
And I just kind of went, oh, uh, you don't know who he is.
You can't read this.
Oh, good.
Oh man.
There's state.
Whatever you do, don't buy it.
You don't want it.
And I started grabbing, not just the pamphlet, but all of the stuff off the table.
It's too dangerous.
I was like, stay away.
Whatever you do, don't end up like us.
He got a little angry at first, but to his credit, he did.
He wandered away and I think he realized that we had been challenging him somewhat and he
came back and he bought the pamphlet.
It was a true subgenius.
He did buy it.
He did buy the pamphlet and uh, and then he, but, but he.
Yeah.
He went around and got to talking to, to different people.
Uh, and it became obvious to us that the poor guy, I mean the, the church of the subgenius
is a serious religion, but we love to put each other on and we put, we, you know, it
was like, this guy took everything anybody said at face value.
I feel such pity for this man.
It's like he's ripe for Scientology.
Well, he, he already is.
Fortunately.
He has some of the sacred documents.
He has some of the sacred documents in his hand now.
And so he may well be saved from Scientology.
And he'll learn that until your first dollar is going to Bob, you will never really understand
Bob Dobbs.
You will never understand that man until at least one dollar.
You have to make that breakthrough.
And I mean, what's a dollar?
That's really a token amount.
A dollar is what we used to consider a penny back when I was a kid.
You can get a piece of gum for a dollar.
Ron Hubbard.
Did you ever order anything?
Um, as a matter of fact, and this is a true story.
Um, uh, this, this old gal.
Reverend.
Reverend Betsy Curtis in Pennsylvania set, uh, happened to be an old friend of L Ron
Hubbard's from back when he was a science fiction writer and they'd stayed in touch
and she had his for real address.
It was a post office box in Florida and people would take his mail to him out on his yacht
and she, she gave it to me and I said, you know, you ought to send him some of the subgenius
stuff that slightly based on Scientology, like our questionnaire.
And I sent him the pamphlet and the questionnaire and all that and thought he might get a kick
out of it.
And he sent it to me a week later.
Yeah.
He died a week after I mailed it.
Fancy.
The same thing happened to the science fiction writer, Philip K Dick.
Yeah.
Uh, I, I, we got his address and sent him a subgenius pamphlet and, and within a week
he was dead.
The last person, the second to last person who saw Dick alive was, uh, Reverend Jay Condom,
the author of P-Dog comics who had just met him and gone over and they discussed it a
little bit.
Well, there are some people who are uncertain about the Philip K Dick's that whether that
was really staged or not.
So, uh, you never know maybe an L Ron Hubbard, the after the, after Dick.
Hmm.
I like to think that
cruising with Elvis in Bigfoot's UFM.
That's right.
The Elvis, Elvis Presley of course is alive.
I mean, there's no question about that.
What could kill him?
Bob, Elvis, Kennedy, uh, the, the, uh, they try to make it seem like partying could cure,
could kill Elvis.
I, it's impossible.
They're all in Dobstown.
They're gambling, man.
They're having a great time.
We'll never die as long as that Hydra is out there trying to take our slack away.
No, no, no, no, no.
They cannot die.
No, there are some, the Kings and the Queens of, of true slackdomness shall ne'er die.
Now, Jimi Hendrix really did die, but he was reincarnated as an entire tribe of exes.
And so we know everything's going to be okay.
Come on.
You're putting us on.
No, that's in book of the subgenius, man.
It wasn't in there when I read it.
Right.
It may not have been.
I'm sure the next time I get by, it'll be back in there.
Yeah.
That's funny.
Have, have you all ever noticed how your book of the subgenius will change you?
Absolutely.
Yes, I've noticed that.
It kind of ticks me off though, because I, you know, I've read the thing about 14, 15
times and I still don't know a damn thing to say.
Uh, mine moves all the time.
I leave it in my chamber of extra meditation.
I go to find it and it's not there.
It's gone.
And the Bob's heads are on different pages.
Each time you look, it's, you know, there's one on the corner here, but it's another corner
now.
Different languages.
All kinds of things twisted and turned.
And you know, sometimes I'll find it laying right next to my frap table and my frap will
be consumed more.
More so than I thought it had been before.
And, and then I'll pick up the book and I'll start reading it.
And, and the words seem to, to speak more, more spacely.
They seem to penetrate between my, my nostrils into that third, third nostril.
And I get that psychic stench, that stench where, where somebody's been smoking.
Oh, whiff it, whiff it.
Whiff that stench.
Woo!
But it sure hasn't been me.
But my book's looking on that table, looking up at me.
And I'm like, I'm going to die.
Well that's my book.
And that man sitting there smiling with that pop in his face.
And he is going, oh yeah.
Woo!
And he's got bloodshot eyes.
It's in my book.
Oh, I don't even know.
Oh, he's got bloodshot eyes.
Bloodshot eyes.
Tell it.
Woo!
Testify.