I keep feeling and I hear shuffling noises all about me.
Shuffling?
Well, not exactly.
More like little sucking noises.
You know, a...
Well, that's great.
All right.
Praise time.
Thank you.
You missed it, people.
If you missed it, this is what you missed.
There was dancing, naked, crazy women wearing nothing but neon.
There was a giant 20-foot-tall neon man staggering around,
a huge robot from outer space, an incredible live show, and this!
Nature.
Nature has a way sometimes of reminding man of just how small he is.
She occasionally throws up the terrible offsprings of our pride and carelessness
to remind us of how puny we really are in the face of a tornado,
an earthquake,
or a Godzilla.
The reckless ambitions of man are often dwarfed by their dangerous consequences.
For now, Godzilla,
that's all.
The strangely innocent and tragic monster has gone to Earth.
Whether he returns or not, or is never again seen by human eyes,
the things he has taught us remain.
But back here at the duplication hall,
the muffled sounds were driving me.
Driving us.
No more.
Driving us mad.
They were driving us mad.
The input.
It goes into analog.
That's exactly what it's for.
That's what it's for.
And now,
here at the Victory Theater,
on Buena Vista Court,
in beautiful Chamfrom Rock in Cisco,
the night of Clarabelle,
the dingweasel people,
and the shouting,
the dancing wizards,
singing in perfect unison
for your indecent delays
and your artistic miscreants.
You know, I can't tell if you're being very simple or very complex.
The Eloi have all we need.
We have no use for your questions.
But how long have you had all this?
And don't you have to work for it?
I don't know.
Work?
Work.
Toil.
Doing things you don't want to do in order to do the things you do want to do.
I don't understand.
Well, you know, somehow I don't either.
This was a land and time of plenty.
And yet,
we're still here.
Yet they had no appreciation for it.
They knew nothing of labor, tension, or war.
The very food they ate was provided by nature's bounty.
Fruit, by the way, seemed to be the Eloi's only diet.
The people of the remote future
will be strict vegetarians.
But what else of our future was I to glimpse,
as the days passed?
Yeah, Becky?
I've been staring out this porthole for the last 25,000.
Creepy Clown also lives in Mojo World now.
Creepy Clown managed to get into my wedding.
Did you see that he appeared briefly on stage?
No.
Yeah, there's a photograph of our lovely wedding.
It's Princess Wee and the preacher and me and those two little boys standing there.
And Creepy Clown's back in the shadows waiting.
I took many photos and I saw no Creepy Clown.
I got confused because the wedding was down on Deck 4 and I went to Deck 3.
Well, that's where they were having the planters.
Got stuck there in the seminars.
Well, once they get you inside, you can't really get out,
especially when they're trying the new material on your cerebral cortex.
I'm sorry, what?
Can you tell by the gravity, though, the difference in the gravity between the two decks?
We were looking for a place that had a lot of light and happy type stuff coming out of it.
There were so many concourses.
We were blistered one place.
We got through and the spinal monkeys actually ripped all of our hair and set us on fire.
And so then it was another half an hour trying to get to Level C.
What was it again?
Three?
C.
DNA Level C.
DNA Level C for the consummation of your zygote there.
Yeah, Deck C.
And what a decked out affair it was, too.
I remember the pumpkin spread.
I stole some and took it home to my dog.
And I remember the one.
What was his name?
His name was Father Flagelist, who tried to beat the onions out of you before the beginning of the display.
Those guys in the suits have been out there, like, for a long time.
I think they're working on something.
I think they're just, I think they fropped up and they're just floating around.
Well, look, yeah, that's what that one guy's got in his hand.
It's not a tool.
It's like a little Dobbs pipe.
So they just wanted to get away from the rest of the people near the concourse.
Man, I can't believe this place just goes on and on and on.
It's, you know, from one different...
It never does stop, no.
It's a room that, you know, has colors that you never saw before.
And then suddenly you're smelling the band, unfortunately.
Most of them haven't shaved in a couple years.
And they can keep adding on to the thing indefinitely.
The constructions out here can eventually...
Oh, look, he is.
He's going too fast.
He's going to hit the side of the ship.
Hey, I heard there's parts of the ship where, like, that really can hurt.
Their own civilization.
That can hurt, man.
Oh, man.
You think he's going to make it now?
Yeah, he's all right.
I hope it doesn't make him.
Oh, is that Roger out there?
Who, Roger?
Yeah, they keep...
They keep saying his name over and over.
Yeah, they're looking for him, I guess.
A lot of people wonder what happened to Roger Haley, and here he is.
Is it true that there's...
He's been with us all along, too.
That there's parts of the ship that, you know, like, other...
Nobody knows about, and the people have lived there so long,
they don't know of other parts of the ship.
It's like lost worlds within the ship itself.
Have you heard those rumors?
There were some experimental zygotes implanted in some areas,
just to see if life could form in that kind of environment,
and I don't know.
Like the walking bowling ball pins or the arguing trees?
Are you talking about those places?
Well, the ones they implanted down by the engine housing and stuff.
Oh, man.
I didn't know they had something going down there.
Like, life can't even...
If you walk down there, you'll get destroyed.
You know, you would be dead in a couple of seconds from the radiation.
But they've implanted them zygotes down there to see if they would survive.
And apparently a few of them have.
I don't... I guess.
So, like, they are radiation resistant, or they're actually radioactive now?
They don't even...
I don't know. I don't...
They're growing some great chronic down there. I know that.
Yeah.
They're supposed to do that.
I mean, isn't that part of the contract?
Or does it...
No, they're not supposed to.
You're supposed to have to buy that from the conspiracy.
They're not supposed to be there.
No, you're not supposed to urinate there.
Yeah.
Big Brother is getting very, very, very big.
Can you hear?
Shut in the radiation chambers down now.
All the plants are going sleepy.
Thank God they don't have, like, you know, like...
Like they had back on Earth, you know, the place with those heat detection sensors.
They can go by your house and tell if you're going in the bathroom too long on a cold night.
That was crazy.
Creepy clown.
Just called me.
That was a creepy man.
If it was a man.
In any sense that we might call him human.
I bring you light in a rice pudding made for a new human with extra appendages.
This is...
Aranceha of Maverick.
Yes, it's true that the machines came from Heaven
in a first shipment in the rockets.
And if you think they're used too much, you can complain elsewhere.
They are holy instruments of instruction.
From here in the headquarters.
We could be what we really are.
Humans together, subject to the trauma of birth and the fear of death,
to pain and loneliness, disease and loss, ecstasy and terror.
We could accept our vulnerability, which would allow us to feel it,
and that in turn would help us to feel all of what we have to deny
when we try to be invulnerable, impregnable, consider the root of that word.
THE END
My fiery friend, are you feeling better?
I think a plutonium injection and a shot of steam in the right place will wake you up.
Hey, we're on our way. We're only three and one half blocks.
Right now, from the Ericksonian Glass High Security Art Compound,
they have not found me yet. Thank goodness.
I'm still just a nameless building with a cow skull and cross glass cutters over the front door,
as far as the local art police are concerned.
Oh, there's one of their cars.
You heard that young girl scream?
She was...
thought to be an artist, also.
The moth that flies into a flame and instantly frizzles into a heap of protoplasmic sludge,
so the collars are burned and seared by the blistering truth revealed over the air
by the doctors of precision.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
I'm not a doctor.
I'm a doctor.
And let me tell you, friends,
it's not just the swelling coffers of the elder bankers.
It's not just the truncated detention spans of the conspiracy glorks,
scrambling to get that ever-elusive status symbol.
It's not just the vapid shells of the chicken-like models
posing on cue.
It's not just the puppet rock idols playing into the hands of the Hellspawned image consultants.
It's not just the cannibal zombies gorging themselves on self-interest.
It's not just the video pigs wallowing in visual sludge.
It's not just the mellow morons stuck in a time zone from the good old days, mon.
It's not just the aerobic airheads working themselves into a cardiac arrest.
It's not just the talentless pigs,
the tanks hooked into a groove devoid of style.
It's not just the fuzzy dice brains rampaging like the Visigoths.
It's not just the misguided gummy space creatures.
It's not just the oppression of the raging slavs of the lame leftists.
It's not just the frothy mouths of the reactionaries.
It's not just the blank food tubes slamming their craniums against the walls of their own creation.
It's not just the empty youth culture
borrowing from the ABC computerized format of possible personas.
It's that and a whole lot more.
Thank you, Sister Chris. We love you.
I saw one of those TV shows that has America's most fascist, home-hilarious cop abuses.
Oh, those are great.
And it was, I gotta admit, it was pretty funny.
This cop had pulled over this sort of a buck-toothed hayseed poe-bucker,
just got in town, jacked.
He was a little bit of a gasper, sort of a feller talk, kind of like me.
They love them newcomers.
And on the vid, there was a cop and a video cameraman talking to this guy.
And the cop's going, sir, I suspect that you've been smoking marijuana.
Now, do you know why I would suspect that?
And the guy's going, I don't know.
The whole time he's got this joint in his ear, right behind his ear.
The cameraman, of course, zooms in on it.
And, you know,
uh, uh,
it embarrassed me, you know, to see that pot smoker look so very, very dumb.
Because I know it was the beers he had.
And he admitted to the beers.
He said, well, I did just have a couple of beers before I came out here.
But I don't know why you'd think I'd be smoking dope.
And the cop finally points to the joint behind the guy's ear.
And he goes, well, now, when I didn't even smoke it,
now I ain't gonna get a chance to smoke it.
If I'd have been smoking it, why would it be?
Well, darn.
That's right, too.
Wasn't it?
Yes, friends.
The idea.
Right.
Right, right, right.
The next time you eat a hamburger, don't just eat the hamburger.
Pull the damn joint out from under your ears and smoke him in remembrance of you.
Ah, yes.
And then when you have truly remembered you, pick pieces off of yourself, pull yourself into little tiny bits and let the seeds roll away.
And then kind of fluff yourself over into that huge bowl of Bob's giant pipe and let him smoke you.
And as you become the molecules coursing down and hitting you.
And as little airy viola bubbles in his lungs.
And as you enter Bob's bloodstream.
And as the essence of you becomes that which is interfering with Bob's rational thought.
Don't forget.
Don't forget what you owe Bob at that moment.
You owe Bob more than the air you breathe.
You owe Bob the liquid you reconvert into spatial D-cells and brain signals like this.
Like those shown in Mom's Decembered head.
She wanted to be Miss January, but look at her now.
Frozen.
Under a three-foot sheet of ice.
That was a very lackluster performance on your part, Larry.
I think we can cure that easily.
Ha!
Here we go.
Look at the monkeys and the...
Dwarves and midgets.
And the bears.
And the pigs.
And the normals.
And the subgeniuses all running around.
I can see them now.
As if they were right in front of me sweating and farting like the other circus animals.
God almighty, I love the circus.
The smell of the peanuts.
The quaint, piquant aroma of the dead chef.
God, I love the circus.
If I could just make cattle perhaps live one wish, it would be to have a circus.
That would be to be in the circus always, front row, center, and what?
A mass ceremony.
I'm afraid, Monsieur, you have failed.
You have failed the test miserably.
You have taken a very, very detailed log of your activities and your motor responses.
You are what we might call a spud animal.
Hey, you little spud man.
You little silly spud people.
You would do no of the roots of ice.
How can he see in any one direction?
Dirty, dirty little animal.
He's like a swollen piece of flesh that has no use.
A fudger.
Dirty, dirty, dirty.
Steve, Dr. Dog, we're ready to tee off now.
Those of you who haven't watched are going to have to go back and hit the...
.
Once again I call on you, Vellmavia
Come one more time, my trusted aide
Join me and my beloved
For we have work to do
To bring her back to life
Vellmavia
May we hear our song.
Let's hear it.
I already know your name
All your nonsense to your heart
But for your mouth you slay
There's no time to understand
Your mind is much too late
So bow your head
Bow your head
The music in the air
These
is the music you see
Don't try to change your mind
It's much too hard to understand
I will lift you up
With all my strength
With everything
I'll take us right away
For your song
I will lift you up
With all my strength
I'll take you right away
For your song
You're small Н European
It's so sweet
I'll take you right away
With all my strength
With everything
For your song
Thank you.
Huge and beautiful colors, pink and blue and yellow.
The ex-president erects ears are going, look, they're becoming pointy like the horns are his.
For three years now since my discharge from the army, I have prospered little.
Man, he's pretty old.
Oh, look, his discharge is just going on.
Up and down the land, we linger in a depression.
Talk about his discharge.
We must compromise or we flounder.
Compromise or flounder.
Shall we flounder together on the slippery slopes of flounderhood?
Or these we bow down before J.R. Bob Dobbs.
In search of slack and in faith.
In ex-day.
That is the psychic command.
I messed it up.
It is.
Sing praises of Satan.
We, the people of the United States, in order to form a more perfect union, establish justice,
ensure domestic tranquility, provide for the common defense,
promote the general welfare, and secure the blessings of liberty to ourselves and our prosperity,
we kiss general warfare and support the party of racers that your mom and dad gave us.
Thank you, Mr. President.
Wonderful.
It's really glad.
I mean, we're so glad to see that you're still pulling air, as we'd like to say.
If we could say anything, this is all a psychic conversation.
He remembers doing that?
New York.
He probably remembers doing grander things than he ever really did.
Thirteen years ago.
Someday, on the concourse near the White House,
we will step up to Ronald Reagan.
He will be a great leader.
A gigantic, frozen palace, a mortuary,
dedicated, consecrated to the man who saved us from the communist threat.
With one bold Argyle sock thrust forward,
and one hand on a lathered-up breast,
he sang the praises of America.
Are you talking about Mr. T?
I'm talking about Ronald Reagan.
Ooh, five dollars a pair.
Have you been to Reagan's tomb?
Ah, Jesus Christ, yeah.
Yeah.
Hot dogs down there.
The Chabrette hot dogs.
Any Pasoini hot burns.
It's a pyramid, right?
Reagan's pyramid?
Well, I guess they've just finished the last part now.
...the confederate...
I like the Raygun shot they got there, man.
How can a gun depend on the collective will of its states?
I'm stuck in Ronald Reagan's mortuary underwear suit.
I do not see how it can work.
I can't get the wrinkles out.
Do not see how it can work.
Do you hear that?
I can feel these little swastikas.
I can't see.
20 years.
August.
Reinforcement.
Old Granny Gate.
The artists are the evil ones.
Subliminal Command 45.
Gentleman Johnny Burgoyne has taken Fort Ticonderoga.
Well, I think a Jerry Springer-ish episode of the West Wankers would be perhaps to have the two daughters,
much beyond that's here's my hair bush.
Well, you think they're doing it with George W.?
That the girls are doing it with George W.?
Yeah, there's a big incest.
In the old Southern tradition of keeping it all in family.
Family taboo website being launched from the White House now.
I just thought that that'd be pretty hot.
Like Twin Peaks inside the White House right now.
They both have a pair of shalogies on them that will not quit.
They put up solid.
They will not come down.
He is George, eager for fun.
Hockey or imaginary guitar.
Get a good job.
Joe did.
Happy.
I know.
On the day shift at the utility muffin research kitchen.
Arrogantly twisting the sterile canvas snoot of a fully charged icing anointment utensil.
And every time a nice little muffin comes by on the belt, he boots forth.
Jazz, you're confusing the issue.
That music.
Big trouble.
They thought that either you or I or the Reverend Stagg was somehow the erudite and the gooprious Franco Zappa.
A man for all seasonings and well concealed in his own apologies.
New York.
City of doom.
What a bloody mess of Freeman's Farm.
What a bloody mess.
New York.
New Sherman, New York.
What a bloody mess.
Eight days away.
Nine, seven, six, five, four, three, two.
Hey, hey.
Give me a piece of that.
Rockets away.
Hey, I was a war veteran.
Come on.
Hey, hey.
Come back here.
I was in the non-main.
I was in R3.
Where were you?
You were playing with your ass.
Why you were smoking that shit?
Hey, come back here.
What are you going to do?
I don't like life.
I've been able to move my leg for the last 32 years.
Thinks it's a joke.
I could use my mind, though, to make my foot move.
And someday I'm going to be able to fly.
I'm going to pick this wheelchair up.
That's what I'm going to do.
I'm going to fly right over the East River.
And I'm going to drop a few bombs.
On that old lady's house.
Yeah.
30 years, but I still remember that bitch.
Hey, hey.
Who you calling a bitch?
I hate Bob.
My Bob made my daddy go crazy.
My daddy used to make money, but now he just sits around all day.
Huh.
I hate Bob.
He's a bad man.
I wish he would die.
He's probably the most terrible guy.
My kid's name's Slap, too.
Mike.
A classroom is something you know.
I wish wand were the only bad funny story on Earth, which chance I got to blackmail a
Go to bed like another child who just got their
sets straightened out, mi amor...
... grind people.
Do you want to know how long I
went to sleep?
이
It wasn't hot, right?
That's right.
Why don't we grow all the might all together
and protect ourselves?
I mean, I don't think I can keep up with it.
I mean, it's like there's two sections.
These are celebrities coming to me.
These weird magazines.
These characters that show up at the door.
These take your medication.
And they want to know things.
They want to know what's going on in their lives.
What should I do?
What should I do about this?
What about my girlfriend?
My girlfriend, they wouldn't know what we were talking about.
What should I do, man?
I don't know.
Relax.
I'll tell you what you should do.
It's like doctoring yourself.
Do this.
No head-launching, doctor.
Oh, take the pills.
Light the fire.
Oh, try some of this false slack.
But we can't talk about that because it would leave this station open to libel and slander.
That's our lawyer now.
Oh, my God, he's in.
I feel much better now.
Oh, man.
That's because Bob sent this for you.
We should live in cities on our own filth.
Oh, we tried that.
That's so 14th century, Dave.
That's so 1400.
Man, I'm so pashay.
You know, living like back in the 14th, like the 15th century, man.
Yeah, right.
Well, the plane walked out half the humans.
You have that going for it.
Cans and pieces of plastic.
Half the humans.
This was the sound of it.
We got it on tape.
Feel the drill.
The nose drill.
It hurts more.
It just keeps getting louder.
Oh, my ears.
My ears.
Thanks, Bob.
Oh, my ears.
I'm looking at you.
Thanks, Bob.
Oh, I can't stand it.
Another second.
More, more, more.
Oh, I see it's back.
I'm being ruptured.
Almost done there.
And it feels so good.
Now spit out of your ears.
And you turn it off.
Let your ears drill in the cup now.
Just when you get a breath.
My ears are beating.
I'll tell you anything you want to know.
Killing me.
Don't stop, Bob.
I hate this.
Don't stop.
Oh, I can't.
Hey, I'm losing it.
I'm losing it.
I've got to look well.
I'm going to go to bed.
Oh!
Don't bring it up.
Don't let yourself go.
Don't worry about it.
This is the worst thing that's ever happened.
God is fair.
God.
Bob, I want to pay extra for that.
And for those of you who want to know what I was playing tonight,
it was all on tape, so I wasn't cutting in and telling you.
You're just going to have to write for information from the Church of the Subgenius.
That's right.
You, friend, are going to have to dare having your address on our mailing list.
Do you know what sort of government agencies get hold of our mailing list, whether we know it or not?
A? I don't either.
But anyway, you need to write to Bob, friends.
Write to Bob at the Church of the Subgenius.
And here comes that P.O. Box number, friends.
P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
Huh!
Oh, yes, friends.
Yes, and you can also check out, in the more modern day than that ancient post office box show, www.subgenius.com.
Or you can write to me.
It's staying at subgenius.com.
For those stuck on Earth, friends, for lack of $30, I hope you've enjoyed this show.
I'm sure I'm off planet by now.
Thanks for listening, though, all these years.
And special thanks, friends, special thanks to Reverend David Bauchner for MP3-ing these shows
and for forcing them onto the Internet the right way.
And to Prostata Cantata for helping to make that possible, as well as Sensory Research, friends.
Sensory Research, who makes the real audio versions of the show possible.
For those listeners and those co-producers, I don't know how to repay you.
I really don't, except to just keep on trying to spread that mighty...
Wheelbarrow full of Bob across the barren plains of America.
Yes, Doctor.
Do-do.
My name is Vivian Spud, and I've got something I'd like to ask you, Doctor.
Well, don't just stand there, boy.
Ask away, and we'll try to answer your question.
Well, something has always puzzled me ever since I was a beast back in Indiana, Doctor.
Why does the porcupine where its eggs are?
Because Hoosier boys oughtn't to get off their home soil.
I think I'm traipsing out where they're trying.
You know, Phil used to ask us that, too, but...
It's not the kind of answer we can put on the air, that's the problem.
More pressure.
I'm taking it over.
More breath area.
See here, the clamoring masses here below us are sub-demies wishing for church air.
Ho-ho, mister.
Air.
They're looking for spiritual guidance.
In a time of confusion.
A time of worse things than that.
You know what I mean?
We're back here at the studio, trying to clean up the mess after the explosion.
But we did get Bob all over two billboards, right by Tower Records,
and we did take an authenticating photograph, which, if it comes out, I will send to you.
And you can see Bob spread out all over Berkeley.
And I was relating to you on the tape.
It may come later.
I'm going to put him all over California.
And see those stars so clearly.
It's not at all like on Earth.
Look at that cloudy planet go by.
Gee, it is really inspiring, and I'm glad to be talking to you here.
Air.
here on this escape vessel.
And of course, pouring the liquids
into the fugitives' heads can be
very dangerous, and so she always
makes sure to wear the rubber gloves
provided her by Dad.
She's not about to make the same
mistake Little Sis made last January
when she lost an eye
somewhere in the backyard.
Have you found
that mystic eye?
Have you found it yet?
Have you found
that mystic
eye?
What you're looking for,
friend and seeker and peeker
and peeker?
What do you want
in your true self?
Why have you been
standing on the sidelines
when you could be standing on the
front lines with your foot
planted firmly in your own
ass?
Praise me, Bob!
Thanks for watching!
If you like this video, please heavily
subscribe to my channel!
verbal matching with
tiny Chamberlain
unasitized
marshal
poltergeist
10% of trainers who care many times from their top 1 only support group.
Thank you.
Don't tell me.