Now, would you get your nose out of my amoeba?
Before we begin today's lessons, I think there's one thing we should straighten out in regard to our relations with each other.
Uh-oh.
Oh!
Some of you seem to think there's something shameful about a little boy and a little girl liking one another.
Mm-hmm.
Now, let's think about it for a minute.
I want the reason.
All of us are rather like one big family.
Oh, that's not good enough.
And I think our family could be a lot happier...
None of your business.
...if we were kind, considerate, and friendly toward one another.
I am not.
Well, you don't have to be.
I wanted to hit somebody.
But I do think you should have mutual respect and learn to get along together.
You're a smelly old ape.
You really told him.
You know, if you do that...
For two days.
You'll be taking a big step toward...
The Self-Genius.
Power of...
Science.
The kind of men and women we want.
Yeah, because you're dirty.
All right, fellas, let's get going.
The following is copyright 1981 by the Subgenius Foundation.
Should you have comments, criticisms, or suggestions regarding the cassette book program,
please forward them directly to...
The Technical Staff.
Division for the Blind and Physically Handicapped.
Library of Congress.
Washington, D.C.
205-42.
Over 21 years...
This concludes the instruction.
Perhaps this is as good a time as any to take a few minutes to repeat a message
that seems frequently lost in the hustle and bustle of our daily activity.
This won't make too much sense, but it's not intended to.
It's intended to strengthen the lips.
Bring your lips far forward now.
Now with woo.
Woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo.
For variation, emphasize every third or fourth woo.
Woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo, woo.
And I have so much I would like to say, but I don't know how to say it.
So please bear with me if sometimes this doesn't make much sense.
It's realistic.
The second question is what?
What's happening?
Is this a miracle?
What kind of a miracle?
Is this a parable?
What's the point?
Is this a letter?
What's the big idea?
What's he trying to communicate?
Because people like you are helping us stay on the radio.
You can't buy a miracle.
But you can certainly stand behind a miracle ministry.
Like a bunch of...
Oh, I like to go to the lake.
I like to go to the stage and walk around.
You're going to be introduced.
And people will have a number in their hand and in their forehead.
Someone with a lot of energy.
They'll be given a...
Okay, your code number once more.
237.
237, you're calling from Dallas.
Okay, thank you.
And I'm going to continue to do business in this world.
And without it, you can starve.
I guess my code number is two.
You can let it out.
Amen.
We're living in terrible perilous.
Chaotic times.
Praise the Lord.
And these times are not going to get any better, my friend.
Amen.
They're going to get worse and worse.
Opium is still the primary plan that the United States has for dealing with its people in the event of a nuclear attack.
There has been six cases of breast cancer, one bladder cancer, and one throat cancer.
There is a God who is a God of love, and there is a God who is a God of judgment.
Two sides.
Mockery of everything that's decent and wholesome.
And I challenge you to point out national talk shows that do not belittle sexual fidelity, purity.
That they do not belittle the marriage union and the family lifestyle.
That they don't literally flaunt illicit lifestyles.
I mean, I challenge you to show me a picture.
Talk show that doesn't make light of God.
The Subgenius Foundation, the Reverend Ivan Stang and Dr. Philo Drummond.
And they are, as we mentioned before, the dual heads of the Subgenius Foundation.
You don't know about the schoolbook suppositories.
Watch out for all the leads.
Because I'm number 6,742 witnesses.
And they're coming after me.
So go there, come in.
Hello there, follow through.
We're picking up all your transmission.
With us, the leader and the idea are one.
And every party leader must do what the leader orders.
Subgenius culture, subgenius legend.
Mr. Chairman, gentlemen, I must admit, I know very little of this time.
It doesn't make fun of godly laws.
They laugh at us.
They make a mockery of us.
Now, we don't have to watch it.
We can turn it off.
Who will pay to clean up the contaminated land?
And because of the equal time provision in the law, we can't show you the taped interviews.
787-1270 is the number.
Call us and talk about what you'd wish.
Go ahead.
I'm going to point out that a lot of people worry about the one world government that the conspiracy is trying to get across on us.
And we suspect that the only...
The only thing that can fight a one world government is going to be a one world religion.
And of course, that's what the subgenius...
The church of the subgenius is here for.
I'm telling you, all other gods besides Jehovah and his son Jesus Christ are strange gods.
Question number two.
Do you believe in the virgin birth of Jesus Christ and the death and burial and resurrection of him?
Answer damaged door now starts ringing in the radio
Sir, we absolutely believe in everything
Sir, we absolutely believe in everything.
We believe in it.
Wholeheartedly.
We believe in it wholeheartedly.
They remain at the final 자주
Oh, Bob's my friend
and he's taking me somewhere
This book isn't an Elton John table.
No.
The voice analyzer was designed by our guru, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
We have to make clear from the beginning that we are not really the founders.
We were just hired to promote the word of Bob.
Okay, that then brings me to this.
It is that the Subgenius Foundation is the publishing and PR firm of the Church of the Subgenius.
So would you tell me then what is the Church of the Subgenius?
It was founded by Bob.
Bob founded the church mainly to help unmask the conspiracy.
And we're talking about the conspiracy, the one behind the other conspiracy.
Oh, that's the one.
To unmask the conspiracy and to get us all a little bit of slack.
Slack through any means we can make do with.
Time control is one of the most spectacular and hard to achieve ones.
We're going to go into some depth before the evening is over.
We're defining and, as I say deeply, the terms, slack and what was the other, time control.
Time control, right, absolutely.
Those are things that I, of course, think we need to deal with.
Subgenius
Now we must vote to know
Grandfather, all the whites aren't crazy
I'm glad to hear that, my son
I thought they were
Oh, no
I know of one
Who is as brave as any human being
I'd like to meet this man and smoke with him
Bob started the church about, oh, 20 or 30 years ago
And we've got a picture of him here
We'll hold it up so everybody on the radio can see him
Hold it up to the left part of the radio there, yes
Can you see that?
You can see that he's a really handsome guy
He looks a lot like George Noll
Has a pipe
Very handsome
And smiling
He's got a
What some people call a sinister grin
Jack Armstrong, all-American boy
He looks like a man
He lives
I can't say
But it's just
A sin
And you just can't call it anything else
Many of you in this stadium have been deceived
Perhaps you've been deceived by
Evangelists masquerading as angels of light
Hanuman Lakova, the ninth seed
The only cult they want to talk about is the subgenius foundation
The church of the subgenius
And the only reason they talk about it is for the money
We're going to go to the phones right now
Good evening, you're on KFJZ with Mr. Opinion and Dr. Philo Drummond
And the Reverend Arnold Stang, Ivan Stang
I have a question for Mr. Drummond
Yes
Go ahead
Are you Mr. Drummond?
That's right
I'm calling from Dallas
What's your question?
Well, um, do you know how ...
Do you work on spiritual problems or do you just work on wallets?
We will help you out spiritually.
Of course, it helps if we can have some financial assistance.
We sell $10 memberships.
And once you start getting our newsletter,
you start receiving lessons on how to conduct your life
in the most beneficial way for both you and us.
And regardless of what you're looking for...
Doug Smith says we're different.
Doug's right, Virgil.
We are different, thanks to Jesus,
the genetic engineering corporation of American states.
Mommy, too?
Yep, the whole family.
Is everybody like us?
No, son, but we're working on it.
Round the clock.
Soon everyone will be a superior biospecies.
Wowee.
I want to be a genetic engineer just like you, Pop.
You will, Virg, if you don't baggy.
It can lead to photon confusion.
Don't baggy.
For a healthier, happier biosuperior.
Hi.
You say you're looking for excitement, adventure, business opportunities,
and a real nice place to raise the kids?
Well, explore no more.
We're there already.
Let's visit the world of the future.
World of the future.
Yes, this bustling world of a thousand moods
reflects the dreams of its ambitious inhabitants,
dreams already realized of man's triumph over nature.
Where humans no longer suffer self-inflicted pains.
Where one is made to enjoy life.
Hallelujah.
All the signs point to serious health damage.
There are no winners in a nuclear war.
The minute you have another war, there's not going to be any world left, I don't think.
Because we're going to blow one another to pieces.
Because in this day and time, we don't know what we're going to come to.
There's not going to be anything left for the kids.
I mean, there's not going to be a world left.
And we're all going to end up digging our own holes.
As soon as we dig them, they're going to fall in on us.
I don't think anybody would know what to do.
Even possibly the president.
The only true religion is guns.
The guns.
Guns create your own reality.
If I had a gun, I'd create my own reality.
Crude to the loom.
Simple.
You have a gun, you point it at their head, and you're in control.
I would listen to television and watch it.
I'd listen to the radio.
Put your hands, put your hands on the radio.
Those are the Pink Boys from right here in Dallas.
And put your hand on the radio.
Before that, the B-52s in private Idaho.
And of course, Devo.
And one of the earlier, more primitive versions of Mongoloid.
This is the Pink Boys.
This is the Rock and Roll Alternative.
My name is George.
And tonight, on the subject of the Pink Boys and all that, we have in the studio with us
Ivan Stang and Philo Drummond from the Church of the Subgenius.
Hi, guys.
How you doing, George?
Oh, just fine.
Say, a lot of people have been wondering, just what is the Church of the Subgenius?
Well, George, if we could describe the Church of the Subgenius in one sentence, we'd be rich by now.
As it is, we're explaining it in long-winded terms.
We're explaining it in short sentences, and we're getting rich kind of half-fast.
It's kind of a scam, religious cult company, whatever you want to get into.
It's the first industrial church.
That's right.
We're hoping to make a lot of money real fast.
And if we can wake up ten more people out there in the listening audience tonight, we will have achieved our goal for the evening.
What is the church's priorities?
What's important to you guys?
Mainly the quest for slack.
The casting out of false prophets.
And controlling time.
Those are our three main goals, I guess.
Slack.
Slack is something we all need.
And I know that lots of people out there listening right now are feeling a terrible shortage of slack.
Slack is something you can't get enough of.
That's right.
And we can help them to get slack, George.
Man, the world is filled with a bunch of kooky ideas and concepts about the Bible.
And I can't believe it.
I can't believe the weird things that people get in their heads and start teaching.
Why do you think that these people, aside from that rather vague reference in the Bible, why do you think these fallen angels have stayed around to do us in, so to speak?
Well, they figure that this planet is theirs to loot and that the people of Earth, we Earth people, are their slaves.
And I think the past history of all the records of the wars and the wars of the world, they're all the same.
I mean, we've got the Bible in the Bible, and we've got the Old Testament, and we've got the Holy Bible, and we've got the New Testament, and we've got the Old Testament.
by our families and things that were created deliberately by them, I think bears it out.
Now, not only that, Joe, besides the Bible, there's also other ancient works.
That's what I like about the Word of God.
There's nothing fake-y about this thing, man.
You talk about telling it like it is.
See, it hangs the dirty wash right out the front bay window for everybody to see.
And, ladies and gentlemen, this is the transmission that we've picked up.
You probably noticed it was a lot bigger than what we were talking about last time.
obviously from space beings.
That's right.
And we want, when 1998 comes,
we want subgeniuses to be in positions of power
so that this alien technology is not abused.
And Bob tells us what we need to know
to get into that position.
One year ago, we were obscure nobodies,
and now we're secretly famous.
That's right.
And we've got hundreds of dollars at our disposal.
And close to thousands upon dozens of members.
That's exactly right.
We are international now.
Every state in the Union is represented
on our mailing list in 12 foreign countries.
That is strictly incredible.
And what are the various ranks in the Church?
Well, of course, Bob is our high-E poppin' guru.
He's the saint of sales.
That's right.
Ultimate businessman.
Very few people are able to meet Bob.
He is pretty hard to get hold of.
He's like most cult leaders.
Dr. Drummond here is the...
He communicates with me via telepathic transmissions
beamed into my skull.
And so what we get from him is usually secondhand information.
He in turn is like a shortwave radio picking up signals
from famous dead holy men, living holy men,
creatures from outer space, advanced supersonic Nazi hell creatures
from within the hollow earth.
Waiting for the UFO.
When they use the latest components, I feel like a new machine.
Go now. Quickly.
The survival of our galaxy is in your hands.
Thanks, and I'll try to live up to that.
Jeez.
Well, the Church is going pretty good.
How has your life changed since dogs came into your life?
Crowds?
I realized that the exes are a reality and that my life is geared towards their arrival.
I redefined my own space and was able to center my being.
I was really able to integrate all my anti-societal.
I'm gonna kill everybody here!
When I first heard Bob on the radio, he said that he could heal and told me to put my hand
on the radio so that the Bob energy could come out through the airwaves.
Death to the fascist earthworms!
Many of you in this stadium have been deceived.
Well, let me ask you, sir, are you having some type of problem in your life now?
If I have a dreadful spirit, I'm gonna go to hell.
I'm having a spiritual problem right now.
Okay, give us some idea of the nature of the problem.
Well, I'm afraid of God.
Oh, you are?
Yeah.
Well, there's a lot of people out there just like you.
I tell you what, if you would, put your hands on the radio right now.
I think we're being sold a bill, a big bill of goods.
Uh, really now, are you guys in this, uh, cult business just for the bucks or do you have
...
Mr. Wilsey, isn't it a fact, really, that you've invented this whole thing, that you've
thought up all these little gimmicks and you're taking advantage of a lot of ignorant people
by getting money out of them, people who, uh, believe in you and your silly preachings?
No, it isn't, Joe.
I don't have ...
Uh, the Illuminati will be unmasked and the subgenius cult will have a lot to do with
that.
Bob is gonna, gonna see that the whole conspiracy, the Illuminati, the trilaterals, the, you
name it, the guys that drive up and down the streets selling ice cream, that all, all of
that will be exposed.
That's what America needs.
They have their brains washed.
Clean out all that filth and all that garbage and all that fear and all that sickness and
perversion and all that junk that comes from the pit of hell and the ...
I'm completely ...
Multi-reverend.
I'm about as ... I can perform marriages.
I can legally perform marriages.
And I can also ordain people.
And that's what we've been doing.
When you, uh, become a $10 member, we send you a little card that says you're a minister.
That loosely explains that.
Then, uh, Dr. Drummond, could you explain your, uh, your, uh, doctorate?
I'm not really a, uh, a medical doctor, but more a, a PhD-type doctor.
I obtained my PhD at Dobbstown Community College.
Yeah.
And, uh, my PhD was in journalism.
We sell doctorates, too.
Um, sell $6.00 ...
What's that?
What's a good doctorate going for now?
Six, six bucks?
Yeah, six bucks.
That's a ... we sell about the cheapest doctorates on the market.
Most of them are $20 to $30.
But, uh, the, uh, diploma gilt-edged or plain?
Um, it's plain, but it's got more content on it than you can imagine.
Not a thrill.
Okay, that's good.
Yeah.
It takes about three hours to read, and it tells you in great detail what sort of a
subgenius you are.
It's ...
Praise doctors for Bob!
Here's a Doctorsners for Bob album.
What is subgenius?
It's Doctorsners for Bob!
Here's a Doctorsners for Bob album.
What's the first?
You think you can know the subgenius without knowing Doctorsners for Bob?
Well, you're wrong!
What is Doctorsners for Bob?
Doctorsners for Bob!
Only we know what we don't know, and when we do know it, we shall find out later just
exactly what it was that we didn't know.
But!
In the meantime, we shall experiment further and delve into the deeper recesses of the
human mind to find out exactly what causes this device not to function properly.
Could it be a malfunction of the foot gland or the nose gland?
Yes, possibly you did not know that the nose and the feet are true glands of the human
body.
And only after permanent foot and nose contact can you know that the nose and the feet are
true glands.
And only after the nose gland escaping can you know how to make your feet smell and your
nose run, which would mean possibly that you were backwards or built upside down.
But we'll delve further into that at the end of the broadcast when you and I cannot hear
each other.
And we can get into this too.
This psychoneurotic masto-synesthesia.
What are we doing?
See, even in Da bore.
His outfit is backed up for the abuses, it's just got turned over now.
And you tell your sitten, do you remember this thing that you guys soem?
I don't recall seeing it that closely.
I remember I think I think you saw a video on this before it started.
What?
The voice about it.
at doctors and here hyper cleats here it is doctors for Bob doctors for Bob and
everything real in my life doctors and Bob and everything really my life Oh really my life damn
pickup truck come out blue done run over my wife he's got the blues cuz they run over his wife
ain't in the church
don't turn the radio off keep it on and I wouldn't infer that that our secondary
state that is that our Christ but I'm telling you that preparations are being made and that
the very of the very door of the day of the wrath of God is at hand and that if you plan
to get saved you're better good now there will be a day not in the too far distant future in
which you will be saved and you will be saved and you will be saved and you will be saved and
the Christ will be revealed and the mark of the beast will be introduced and people will have a
number in their hands and in their forehead number if you please
we have a lot to do in a very short time boy you are kidding
and that's the way I felt for quite a while
get ready to ease out of orbit
you bet honey that's what we're gonna try to do I have never flown a city before well
many of you in this stadium have been to see I think they'll they'll pass the ten
dollars bridge the original concept was that throughout history all great geniuses
are considered geniuses and you have not there this means there was
nothing we you know does no complete sense of the human spirit no one you
know I've got now go on that third remember when Christ used to answer our
prayers is later we have 10 further on to say never lets say they're they addressed
on family life as two normal objects for my idea was nothing but a Libra and I was to make a 71.2% protected R.B in a larger number than 20.0 million in natal bills an hour before I was measured only 40.46 educating them after 10 years afterbels one was a sub-genius in good court his proper messages but con jetastrhans inflated pride the right reason was being missed vir Hel senate & it was frightened off the basis of subgenius now was the sub genius for the straight
know i'd never seen before but the lord was talking to me god was talking and i was walking
listen to a little of this right now my sister i don't know anything about you i haven't talked
with you as far as i know you haven't told him have you told him my staff anything about yourself
you haven't then if i know anything about you it would be because the spirit of the lord has led me
to you today am i right you're in dire financial
things that you possess if you don't go for some money pretty soon
and you have come to the end of your road
starting to affect your nerves
sleepless nights
we're going to put this in the hand of god in the bible in two different places
a handful of meal brought a miracle i want you to hold that envelope open
i'm going to pour it in this envelope
now amen pastor don't fart anymore tell the truth i know you're telling the truth
that's what's bad from now on every new addition to our demand for energy will be met
from our own production and our own conservation
you have
people
have a white
person just taking over the world
that's weird
there's nothing to be afraid of we're not going to hurt you but once you
understand you'll be grateful let us go look we're laid down we
won't come back we can't let you go you're dangerous to us
don't fight it miles it's no use slowly understand that.
Sooner or later you'll have to go to sleep.
Subgeniuses strike out on their own, too.
There's rogue subgeniuses, in fact, that have gone.
They were originally subgeniuses that went off the deep end,
like Howard Hughes, Jack the Ripper, Adolf Hitler,
Richard Nixon, for sure, would be one.
And not just crazy people like that.
Muhammad Ali, yeah, renegades, Muhammad Ali.
He's a renegade subgenius, I guess you'd call him.
But these people don't know they're subgeniuses.
No, they don't know.
Well, they haven't, you know, they haven't declared it yet.
It wouldn't even help a lot of them.
They may know.
They may know, and for all we know, they're out there reading stuff.
The 5th Temple Lodge of the Church of the Subgenius of Little Rock,
and before we begin this sacred spouting,
I think that we should all bow our heads
and let's all have a minute of noise.
Ah!
First, we have a schisming member of the church here.
This is, uh...
Did you introduce yourself?
No!
Holy Master.
Do not listen to this man.
This man is a retrogrunt.
This is an anti-Dobbs speaking to you here.
We've got stereo here.
This, that is a lie.
This is the anti-Dobbs.
this note this one here this one okay the true dobbs is in the right channel now true dobbs
all dobbs followers to the right uh hello hello reverend doug this is edwin better known as savage
pencil speaking to you from you in a little room in belsaise park london where i live anyway i'd
just like to thank you very much for sending me all those really great uh subgenius things including
the absolutely work of art stock fist brochure and all the other things i've got them all plastered
up everywhere i've been telling everybody about them i've been mumbling about subgenius and
everything to many people and with your permission the reverend bob and your good
selves may be popping up in a future rock and roll zoo this man has something when i come up
these stairs
morning i knew that bob was straight but you know something i serve a miracle working god
higher than a star highest of style you can't ever get higher than a star
god bless you and a little children that's a hell of a testimonial i say friends
enterprises explore the depths of the 23rd century for the federation
of our household have you dedicated your own to the
lord sensitive
ミ наказップ
the um
is
female
leave please
be
of God here.
Say something, Farideh.
Bob.
And Bob.
All right,
that's the youngest member
of the church.
Channel 7's still the one.
Ben, Ben,
I'm Snavely and Eklund.
I'm over-repped.
You will not be.
I'm over-repped
Snavely and Eklund.
And we were at
the Hall High School
Library today
and we put lots
of subgenius literature
in all of the books
all around.
We have Dobbs hit
miniature Dobbs hit
uploading everywhere.
Miniature Dobbs hit
everywhere you go.
There's a miniature
Dobbs hit.
Begin by
settling back
comfortably.
Get as comfortable
as you can.
Well,
we're getting
comfortable now.
Hey,
I feel better already,
Paul.
You know that we're here
until the next afternoon
and the music's cool.
Oh, wow.
I can feel it coming on.
Must be a whole trip here.
It's like being on
acid ice.
Yeah.
Doing our inflated
work.
The post office.
We're going to park
here very carefully
and very quickly
so we can run
across the street
and plaster Bob's
little face
all over the billboard.
We're back here
at the studio
trying to clean up
the mess after the explosion.
But we did get Bob
all over two billboards
right by Tower Records
and we did take
an authenticating photograph
which if it comes out
I will send to you.
And you can see
Bob spread out
all over Berkeley.
And I was relating
to you on the tape
it may come up later
anyway that I'm
I've been putting Bob
all over California.
You can see those stars
so clearly
it's not at all
like on Earth.
Look at that
cloudy planet go by.
Gee, this is really
inspiring and I'm
I'm glad to be talking
to you here
from Star Deck One.
My Lord.
Yes?
Yes, Elric.
A floating ship
is about to land.
It's about to crash
into us.
Oh, pay no attention
to it.
So, John!
Yes, my Lord.
These droids
get so upset
when the least
little thing
goes wrong.
But anyway,
it's a...
Wow.
That is pretty awesome.
Look, it's...
Oh, God damn it!
Shoot.
All systems
prepare for full power.
Okay.
Give me Mach 1,
2, 3.
Charlie Baker
says,
749.
Ooh!
I think we maintained
a hit there on starboard.
Ooh!
Put up full force phasers.
Call Bob!
Very few needy.
I need you.
Let's lock in
these controls.
Move it out.
Okay, Bob.
Okay.
Let's go.
Bob.
Bob flies us.
Bob flies standing up.
That's incredible.
I'm not worried
because I know
all the force field
wasn't on there.
Now it's on.
It's okay.
Come back, you fools!
You cowards!
Come back, I'm sorry!
Listen to him.
Come on, you'll be destroyed!
Let's go!
Well, Doug,
we found Bob.
Uh,
do you want to say
anything to Doug?
He's really appreciated.
I think he'll be
really, really great.
Hi there, Doug.
I'm Bob.
I'm better than you've
ever heard of.
Believe me, I am.
I'm a native.
Thank you.
I'm...
He isn't here.
Yes, he is.
Probably not for a few days.
No, right now.
Try Madison, Wisconsin.
No, try Dallas, Texas.
Victor Street.
Bob will kick their asses
and take their money
and drive them to drink
and steal their honeys.
Excuse me...
He says
he'll come at us
It wheel you out!
If Rick's gonna give
a stunning wages
fly out and get enormous
a little
the
Hart she News
Don
Doves x8
Duh-duhs, duh-duhs, duh-duhs, duh-duhs, duh-duhs, duh-duhs, duh-duhs, duh-duhs, duh-duhs.
Since he came through my life, I've quit selling wrenches.
And I've got a micro-encapsulated feeling about things now to you.
I'm trying to tell you about dogs, dogs, dogs who know what's going on.
And this time you know.
Ah, hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm.
I've got to get some slack in case you couldn't tell.
And that's what I'm doing.
I'm trying to tell you about dogs, dogs, dogs who know what's going on.
And this time you know.
I lack, you know, maybe this subgenius stuff that we've been getting involved in.
Maybe.
Listen, Bob.
Bob, are you in here?
No.
Bob.
Where's Bob?
Are you here, Bob?
No, I don't think Bob's here.
Where else, Bob?
I can't find Bob anywhere.
Can you hear me?
Oh, Bob.
Dr. Drummond, can you hear me?
Dr. Drummond's in a special room.
Oh, the great stinking Bob-o.
Oh, Bob.
I need some money.
I need some slack.
Oh, Bob.
Bob, I need some money.
Give me food.
Give me some money, Bob.
Oh, Bob.
Bob.
Bob's my friend.
Thanks for being my friend, Bob.
Bob's my friend and he's leading me somewhere.
Where are we going, Bob?
Bob.
Is he waiting there for me?
Oh, he's not waiting anymore.
Did he go up and go home?
Bob went to vote.
He went to vote?
He'll be back shortly.
Oh, okay.
In the white form.
A donut.
Bob left you a donut, Bob.
That's what's waiting for you, is a donut.
Bob can stop the aliens from killing me.
Yeah.
I...
Bob can save me, but will he?
Well, no problem.
Don't count on it, Bob.
Well, I mean, yeah, any problem.
Bobby, Bobby, Bobby, Bobby, Bobby.
He can have some money or not.
Bobby, Bobby, Bobby, Bobby.
Bobby, Bobby, Bobby, Bobby, Bobby.
Bob's $15.
Well, okay.
He'll save you, Bob.
Don't worry.
What is waiting there for me?
Bye.
Oh, the Bobmobile.
Okay, the Bobmobile, the Bobmobile.
Let's all go riding in the Bobmobile.
You don't need gas in the Bobmobile.
Oh, the wonderful, wonderful Bobmobile.
You don't need no gas.
You don't need no...
You don't need no money when you're in the Bobmobile.
When you're in...
Hey.
Look, up over the car.
They're back again.
Oh, Bob.
Hey, Bob.
Bob, Bob.
I'm ready.
Oh.
Oh, I'm starting to get slack in my feet.
Oh, they're shuffling out from underneath me.
Oh, Bob.
Bob, Bob.
Don't run.
Bob, don't run away.
Here's my dollar.
Come on back.
I want you to stay and stay.
Oh, Bob, Bob, Bob.
What's wrong?
What'd I do?
You mean you want two more dollars?
Two more dollars?
Okay, Bob, here's two more dollars.
Oh.
Wow.
Wow, I suddenly feel...
I feel great.
I feel like...
I can see through all the women's clothing.
I can.
Look out the window.
Them girls are all naked.
It's Bob.
Right?
We can sit here and talk about...
You know.
It's here.
He's...
It's Bob.
That's why you need to send us money.
Here at Subgenius Church.
It's Bob.
He can work miracles in your life.
He can bring...
And money.
Send us money.
He can bring you love.
He can...
And, of course, the molecular dispensation,
which comes from the spewing diodes
embalmed in our brain cells
through the Bob's cell.
Surgery and Dob's tan,
of which we've all gone through.
Kill Bob.
Braise the lard.
Kill me.
Shoot Bob.
I don't believe there is a Bob.
Sometimes we...
If there was, he wouldn't be so cool.
Dob is...
Dob's 80.
If there's not a Bob, then...
Then, why are you here?
I can explain life if there's no Bob.
Ha ha ha ha!
Can I ask you...
Pick a symbol, any symbol.
How about Bob?
I'm starting.
It's Bobby.
Bobby Dodds?
Bobby Dodds.
I remember Bobby Dob...
Bob's, Dob's.
Bobby Dob's when he was a boy.
Bobby Dobbs.
Little Bobby Dobbs.
Where did he grow up?
Right here on the main street.
Where's Bobby Dobbs?
I knew Bobby Dobbs when he used to cut the grass off.
in front of the drugstore, and he had a part-time job in Vietnam
long before any of us even knew how to say the word.
Oh, well, that's just the way Bobby Downs grew up.
Of course, he grew up in a small town in the Shenandoah Valley in Virginia.
Nobody knows that, actually, but it was Stanton, Virginia,
that Bobby Downs grew up in,
where his father owned an antique store
and sold half-burned uniforms and ancient rusty farm implements
as tourist attractions.
Hi, Daddy.
Here's Bobby now.
What's happening today?
There's Bobby Downs.
How'd he get so hit?
We have these ancient holograms of Bobby Downs, the way he was,
asking how the things are the way they is now.
What did you do in the war, Daddy?
Bobby Downs!
There are no answers.
So he thought for himself.
Bobby Downs.
Bobby Downs was looking for a drug, some kind of transformation.
I think I understand.
Yeah, sure.
Well, no, maybe not.
Bobby Downs figured it out for himself.
Oh, his budget is sitting around.
Yeah, that's it.
Thinking.
Bobby Downs.
Yeah, sure.
He's sitting around.
I got it.
Hey, I know.
No.
He got it.
No, he didn't get it.
That's it.
Bobby Downs is sitting around thinking.
It's not that.
It must be.
As he got a little older, he decided his name was too long.
He wanted to have some dignity.
He knew his character and personality, so he named himself Bob.
He said, he said, we understand.
We know what's going on.
And he convinced people.
And then a voice came to Bobby Downs one day.
Bobby.
He said, you really think you know what's going on?
Yeah.
Hey, Art.
Art.
Oh, here you go.
Oh.
He said.
Who is that?
What?
Hello?
Oh.
Bobby Downs.
What do you know?
Hey, it's dark in here.
I don't see anything.
I don't hear anything.
Oh.
Bobby Downs.
But I think.
I understand.
Bobby Downs.
He's getting his voice right now.
I know what it's all about.
This is where his voice sounded like.
Bobby Downs.
This is where it's getting light.
Here it's happening now.
It's the universe out there.
That's what it is.
Bobby Downs.
And here I am.
Sitting in the middle of it.
To you.
Yes.
Yes, folks.
He's really.
Bobby Downs.
To you.
Now.
Bobby Downs.
Yes.
Three.
Bobby Downs.
Where were you during the war, Daddy?
It's time to wake up, Bob.
It's time to get up.
Bobby Dobbs, this is your wake-up service.
That's right.
Bobby Dobbs.
Are you asleep under there?
Hey, your hair's on fire.
Hey.
Hey, police are coming.
Better get up right now.
The cops are coming, man.
They're going to beat you up with brass knuckles and baseball bats.
Hey, your hair's on fire.
Friends, I want to talk to you today about something that I'm sure is close
to everyone.
It's hard to mind.
You might not be living up to or be the man or lady, woman you should be.
And that subject, you might have guessed it by now, but that subject is Bob.
A man came to me.
He said, my life is empty.
I said, why?
Why is it?
It's not because my wife left me.
No, it's not because my car broke down.
It's not because I'm fixing to be evicted.
It's not because I'm getting fired from my job.
It's because I don't have Bob in my life.
And I talked to that man.
And I saved that man that night.
I showed him the way of Bob.
Oh, Mr. Bob Dobbs.
Where are you in this dark hole?
This dark hole of humanity.
Oh, Bob.
Somewhere back here in the attitude.
The secrets of the...
The universe.
Somewhere in this slimy, slimy hole that we call the top of the subgenius conclave meeting hall.
This is the pink boys.
This is the battleground.
Oh, Bob.
Oh, who are you on your organ, Bob?
And what a big organ you got.
But friends, I get up in the morning and there's just like this electricity that just shoots through me.
And I say, praise Bob.
And you can feel it, man.
You can feel that.
Was that him running around over there?
Did anyone want to see Bob?
I just want to say, praise Bob.
Don't you think he's the greatest sterno?
Bob? Praise Bob.
Sterno said praise Bob. I don't know if you hear. But everything comes
from Bob and it's just so beautiful. I just want to
turn everyone in the world on to Bob. And I'm not
sure, ma'am. I don't know, ma'am. I seen the pretty pictures
one time. But you think Bob might give me those
pretty pictures if I vaporize Smith and Jones?
I don't know, man.
No, it's not here. Look at me. Do you live on a farm?
Come here. Something wrong.
Seem like I see you on a farm.
Now, don't worry. I mean, I always, I feel my way through sometimes.
When God starts, when it's the Holy Ghost, you don't have to worry about it. Just relax.
I know I'll get tired after. I know I'll get tired.
No, I know what I'm doing. Praise God. I may stumble around
and feel around, but I'll come out all right.
I'm a girl about the gift of the Spirit.
But I see something about a farm, Woody.
I'm on a farm.
You was what?
Praise God.
Farm.
But you don't live on one now?
Still something about a farm. What's a farm?
Huh?
Because you look like a farmer to me.
What?
The name what? What does it mean?
Farmer is your name.
What is your name?
May Farmer.
May Farmer. Farmer. Oh, hallelujah.
Oh, God.
He knew her name.
May Farmer.
Oh, thank you, Jesus.
Jesus stole her life.
He knew her life.
I know Jesus.
I know Jesus is alive.
He tells me her name.
Like I say, I'll talk to Bob on the phone about your problems.
If you have any special needs, we can always supply you with anointing oils.
Yes, we have special anointing oils.
And we can...
You can...
Just for a few dollars more, friends, only a few dollars more to that miracle box number,
we can let you come to visit us at the special retreat.
At Dobbs Town and where you can get landscapes.
And Dr. Drummond and all his little friends from the special places will open up your third nostril
and make it where you can pick up on the strange liquid vibrations that are all around us in the air.
I think I can get a whiff of them now, friend.
Yes, I can tell there's...
Oh, Pastor Naked.
No one knows what happened to him.
He just disappeared in a burst of smoke a little while ago.
But people didn't even get excited.
They didn't even jump up and down because they're so used to seeing it happen in front of the tape recorders
and all the microphones that we have here at the foundation.
Hallelujah, friend.
Oh, can you say anything about what Bob has done for you, my dear sister?
That's Bob.
I can say, I can say, baby.
Oh, Bob's working miracles night and day.
I can say, baby.
Baby.
They call him Bob.
And I think, I think I can try to, I can pick up what your name is.
Yes.
You've never met me before, right?
And you've never been into this temple, right?
That's right.
And this is true, friend.
This woman has never met me.
And she doesn't know any of my employees or any of the other people at the foundation.
And I think I'm getting a picture.
I'm getting an image in my head.
I see a, I see a farm.
Yes, I see a farm, a little, little rooster on top of a house.
And what is it?
Wait, the farm.
Are you a farmer?
Close.
Close?
What, what, what, what, what, what, what is your name?
Farm?
She said yes.
Friend, her name is Farm.
God, you know what I'm talking about.
I'm telling you.
God.
I've got an analyst now.
Yeah, that's Becky Box.
You can't steal that.
I think so.
But you know what I think we ought to do?
Is just rent.
We ought to have our open.
We ought to open a damn lab of subgenius analysis shop back here and do counseling.
You know, we can get a license to counsel in a subgenius fashion.
Can you do that?
Uh, I don't know.
Well, we can do, hell, they do palm reading.
Here.
They do, you know, astrology readings.
We can come back here and do mental life transfer readings.
Do them really.
Spectacularly.
So it's worth people's $10 that we charge.
Yeah.
Even if they.
I mean, we flop around on the floor.
We speak in tongues.
The voice of their good relatives comes through.
This is granny.
I hope you did well.
It's beautiful here.
There's music and soft clothing and tight shoes.
This is a place where all of us live together.
Happy and free.
I just spoke to Sigmund Freud about your problem.
And he says, you can quit.
If you're.
I think.
In order to change you or give you a meal or acutally'elate the devil, just try.
Or just try.
prudently because it's me on cake rock.
And in Friday night, fame.
Well.
Rottenamental pourления malolен Bur 240.
We got this film call it,Tsign Up, made fun of you.
Take me if u need it.
Put me in a box with a good little phone
Pink boy, never gonna grow up
Pink boy, think I'm gonna grow up
Pink boy, you're the kind of guy
You can bring it down, but you gotta find the man
Oh boy, you are the man
You're the man who knows the all, the answer
So it seems at least that's what Doug and Follow keep telling us
Well, maybe I could be
If the string is right here
And I'm not, can't fall