Vomit and then retchings.
At first that seemed like soul fun.
The self genius power of smirk.
The agony will continue for one hour.
Oh, who would have believed it?
Who would have dreamed that the aliens live right next door in the next trailer?
What will they be talking about?
What plans for the future of mankind?
Will it be conspiracy or brotherhood?
Well, seeker, we're about to find out.
This is the weirdest thing I've ever seen.
Oh, my God.
They've gone into the bedroom.
They've been screwing us for a long time.
Hey, look, I'm a super intelligent being.
My understanding is I have an IQ of 1600.
And I can't even understand what you expected from that relationship.
I'm so young.
Not from around.
Here, but a real square little fella.
Oh, come now.
We've been through so much together.
Just call me Bob.
Bob!
On July 12th, I took a trip in a flying saucer, which I am pointing right here.
The saucer was well equipped with rooms, bedrooms, bathroom, toilets.
And this saucer.
This saucer.
I went up into Mars, over the moon, Venus, Clarion, and Orion.
When I say Orion, I do not mean Orion.
It is a planet outside of our galaxy.
So I thought I saw a UFO once.
Really?
Yeah, but I had taken a lot of mescal at the time, so I don't know.
Well, that will do it to you.
Yeah, I was down in Mexico.
I was with my English professor.
We were having an affair and he was married.
It was really terrible.
You thought you saw a UFO?
Yeah, we both, we really thought we did.
Well, I mean, it's just, it's a delusion.
Well, I won't go into any further details, but she had a very interesting experience
that she'd never remembered before.
The numbers who have had contacts with these aliens, how has it affected their lives?
They very often have a religious kind of conversion, although not of a formal sort.
They're good people and they've generally been influenced in good ways, maybe.
So naive.
And there are some people who've got glimpses of it, perhaps.
And they yin for something like that.
They're looking for the family that maybe in some vague way they've known about.
They join cult groups.
Friends, there's a force that runs through the universe.
We used to call that force God.
We now call it the Church of the Subgenius.
And Bob.
They check the systems through and they read the books.
And they find
It's got some really crazy dividends, shut-eye readings, like, text messages.
Some days it takes a week, a week, five days and not long enough to call the police.
Like, stick your teeth to it and see that cow.
When one takes a step back, another takes another.
You see things have happened several times.
There's this idea of gravity helping you.
You see it taking turns and jumping around.
You can hear vision, worried as the range of the expected people with you cannot turn
forward, not only your memory, seeing welcome's like the spectrum's likes, this kind of
system economy. Excuse me? I'm an occult nutritionist.
I think mind control has been over-emphasized.
See, if you were a truly benevolent alien and didn't want to invade Earth,
you'd also hold off delving into a person and making them do things that
they're supposed to do.
Sort of like the crime directors in Star Trek. Stupid!
Stupid! You humans. You've mentioned that there are many people who have been influenced
by the extraterrestrials and are not even aware
of it, but some things like the movies we see, the TV shows,
you think there may be some influences there?
I have a friend who's a writer in Hollywood. He told me when he was 21 years old,
he was crossing an outed desert, and a UFO swooped down over his car and saw it zooming
away into the sky and kept on driving. Nothing happened.
After that, his life took a different turn.
He became more serious, and he had a goal in life.
And that little boy, whom nobody liked,
grew up to be Roy Cohn.
Wow!
And now you know the rest of the story.
You've identified at least two distinct groups of aliens.
There's not more than two groups, but you could put them in two camps.
Okay.
Now, Camp One have just recently arrived, doing their investigations from Square One.
So, Camp Two have been around a long time.
They're also the ones that induce a feeling of friendliness in the part of the people they pick up.
Mm-hmm.
We were picked up on a desert, in California desert, and I was taken to the mothership,
and they were flowing around, not too close to the moon, but with instruments.
Similarly, you might say, except it wasn't a camera, it was really sort of a telescopic instrument,
that we were able to see what was on the moon on the other side of us. See?
It looked like this.
Burn it! Get it to hell!
The people think of themselves as being picked up by old friends.
Came crawling out of a well, wearing ladies shoes.
Didn't know what milk was.
Real little, smooth like baby's feet, with big friendly eyes.
He sounds like a real nice guy.
Took him to the Swiss picnic for a good time, and he choked to death on a piece of cheese.
Yeah.
Right.
Now, of course, this may be a psychological manipulation, but so what?
It's nice to have them do that kind of psychological manipulation.
Yeah.
There are three extraterrestrials of humanoid Caucasian appearance.
The leader is male, about 31, 62.
Ooh!
190 pounds, pallid complexion, lank, greasy hair.
The second is of indeterminate sex, 28, 5'10, 145 pounds, short, dark hair, pale skin.
The female is 26, looks younger.
She has a delicate complexion and excellent bone structure.
Her eyes are hazel, flecked with gray, and sometimes a little sag.
Her voice is throaty, hands exquisite, and she's said to have a certain indefinable something.
Ah!
They were highly intelligent.
Highly intelligent and potentially dangerous.
Highly intelligent!
We'll be going back to England for on-the-spot interviews.
And continuous...
You've got it wrong!
Throughout the night.
They've got it wrong!
They have been dealing with the, what you would call, the real smart aliens, not the ones who have just been here recently and are kind of bum-dling.
Here comes something.
Remember the story when newlyweds on our way to Earth capital...
No, Shazbut.
I don't wish to dwell on technical matters.
But these visitors from outer space, they are what we scientists call brainless.
Brainless?
Brainless.
They're thick, stupid, dumb-dumbs, crubs, twits, morons...
...who don't invoke a very good amnesia.
Graduate students from Alpha Centauri on their first mission, isn't it?
That's right.
They're still doing their PhD thesis on planet Earth.
Uh-huh.
No one could have guessed what was inside.
Hey, look, they're drinking tea.
Hey, look, it's on TV.
Turn on and see, two worlds collide.
We're morons.
Welcome to our pressure dome.
Welcome to our mobile home.
Up in the sky.
We're morons.
People say we've gone too far.
But we don't know where we are and we don't know why.
We're not far away.
The really smart ones, you'll never know.
They dreaded anything to do with them.
Perhaps there are some people who've heard them.
They have this kind of contact themselves and may or may not know about it.
What would be some of the characteristics?
Well, a person who has been fascinated with no particularly good reason.
Been fascinated with UFOs, science fiction, Star Trek.
Has a psychic streak in him.
And has fallen in love absolutely without any good reason with someone.
And then finds afterwards he has also had an interest in UFOs and psychic things.
Now, not any one of these things, or not all of them are necessary.
But you can find a little profile there.
Vwing, vwing, vwing.
Stateless wonders.
UFO and its followers, perverts, monomaniacs, dipsomaniacs, artists of the fast buck.
True believers, objective believers, new age believers, kiho believers.
Shushed by the three men or masturbated by spacemen.
UFO is a bucket of shit.
That's the title.
And I sit here writing while it drips down my face in great rivulet.
I'm going to be very disappointed if UFOs turn out to be nothing more than visitors from another planet.
Because I think they could be something much more interesting.
Something from another dimension of space or time.
I think what the UFO phenomenon is teaching us is that we don't understand time and space.
I think we have to call them objects that are physical, that interact with the environment,
that cause effects on the witnesses, on the psychology and the physiology of the witnesses,
and leave traces on the ground, and yet are capable of, appear to be capable of manipulating
time and space in ways that go beyond what our physics understands today.
The Air Force investigated UFOs and issued a report, couched in polite language, which translated,
means...
Now, let's have no more curiosity about this bizarre cover-up.
We'd like to ask you some questions, if that's all right.
Be my guest.
Good.
Let's start with this idea of light travel, shall we?
What can you tell us about that?
Absolutely nothing.
If I told you you'd blow yourselves up, or worse, someone else, you'd be surprised how
much energy is in a beam of light.
Well then, maybe you could show us how this light travel works.
You humans.
I travel light.
Don't believe it?
Well, listen to this.
Come here, now.
Right now.
Watch the lights here.
Well, first I thought it was a big old dog, of course, the way it howled and how it had
them big friendly eyes.
But I had to ask myself what the hell it was doing up in the graveyard, digging up the
ground with a shovel.
I thought I was crazy.
I'm not a drinking man, I'm not a drinker.
I'm a man on duty, Mr. Cox, not me.
You know, I figured it was one of them werewolves or something, so I slipped a wooden load in
my shotgun, and then all of a sudden, now this is going to sound crazy, a big dark thing
with flashing lights come up over the top of the hill.
That one right over there.
It was about 100 miles an hour.
This dog or wolf or whatever it was, it took off like a bug wrap in that dry hump over
there.
Hey, just a minute, will you?
I'm not a drinking man, Mr. Cox.
I swear to hell I saw it.
That was no crazy thing.
I'm not a crazy, raised sterno bum, but a respected law enforcement officer, Sheriff
Luger, axe handle of Heater County, California.
Crumbling remnant of the old west, or could it be the final resting place of a little
guy from outer space?
Could be, could be.
All I know is everything you know is wrong.
Oh, Christ.
God, you're dumb.
Dumb, dumb, dumb.
Enough of this deception and trickery.
I admit it.
I was taken in too by clever fakes like this.
My name is Dr. Onan Kenowight.
I am great at interpreting the languages and words of subgeniuses to others.
I am a smart guy and very friendly to most everyone I meet.
Spadoinkle.
Uh, what's your name?
My name is Dr. Kenowight.
I am a good friend of Reverend Onan.
Could you come back here for a moment, please?
You can continue to keep talking, but Reverend Onan and I, we need to translate this into
sign language for Hindu gods.
Should I read from the book again?
Please do.
Children of the Chronotron.
The trail of the captives led them gradually upward toward the summit of the mountain.
They were on the edge of the low range of hills.
They soon discovered that the nature of the jungle near the seashore was much less spectacular
than the aspect of it inland.
It began to appear as though nature had dumped all her experiments into one bottle and mixed
them together.
They passed through groves of trees that were mostly roots, all intertwined like some giant
vine.
Their bark was like shaggy hair, and their fine, web-like branches sprouted foliage that
looked like feathers.
Among these feathered branches crawled brilliant orange and red land crabs, some of them as
much as two feet in diameter, emerging from the tent of Reverend Pease.
That's a nice flourish that you did at the end.
It's good.
Yeah, that's improv.
I ad-libbed.
That was a really nice story.
It was beautiful.
No.
I'm swapping out.
I've read.
Here, add them all.
Take a book.
I'm not going to read.
Oh, I don't read books.
All right, who's tagging out with Dr. Fox?
Dr. Fox, I think Shaga.
Shaga.
Are they receiving Reverend Dr. Miller?
You need to come up and do some stuff.
What am I going to say?
I have no idea about running things to say myself.
All right, I'll sit there and laugh.
I hope we're going to make it really funny now, because as we've all said in the past,
every lady subgenius is worth 12 of us.
And now I'm going to have two of them up here, and we'll get some balance.
Bring it.
The ladies in the house.
The ladies are in the house.
Oh my God, welcome to the show.
It's so good to see you.
You look fabulous.
Oh my God, that ensemble with the lights and the bells that you have on, it's amazing.
What type of music do we have loaded into the CD player?
I have no idea.
It's some rare selection that's still in the works.
I think Robot Stang might have had, but apparently Robot Stang prefers this German trance music.
I think we should change that.
I think we need some music.
Oh yes, I've known Space Ghosts.
Now I'll be one.
All right, I see something called iGasm Stang tunes.
I see the amino acids, and then something called Great Songs 1, beginning with Go Monkey Go.
Put that on.
All right.
Heh heh.
We're going to do a little bit of a
I'm linking the satellite in now.
And as we're working to get the technical difficulties done, now we seem to have got the uplink,
and we are communicating with sub-satellite 4.
And disk inserted.
Oh those long nights in Purgatory, I tell ya.
But I'm not.
And yeah, I'm not sure if that's a good thing to say.
You're a good reader.
I'm not irreprochably damned.
There's still gold you see.
You talk good words.
Gold pour.
Oh those are actual song songs.
Those will have lyrics.
Oh is this something bad?
Oh, Reload!
All right, what do we have that's just noisy?
The show is moving along very smoothly.
No one should be disturbed by the iceberg in front of us.
It is a normal feature of the show.
Sorry, I just tossed Stang's cookies.
I'm so sorry.
Can the orchestra continue to play?
Wow, this has been an epic.
Next day of surprises.
Bad, bad Dr. Reverend Miller Miller.
What madcap are you going to read to us now, Anna Mama?
I can't explain it either.
Look at that figure.
Okay.
What one?
How about monster movie soundtracks?
I hate you so much.
Perfect.
Why are you stuck on reading the book?
That was just, that was Argus messing with you.
Reverend Stang will tell us what we're about to hear.
You got to jump in.
Okay.
Yes, yes.
Stay back.
Curse of the, it does have Conan the Destroyer, which we've heard every hour this year.
Curse of the Werewolf, Dark City, Dark Man, Dracula, Dracula, Elephant Man, Fly, Frankenstein,
Godzilla, Golden Voyage of Sinbad, Hannibal, Hollow Man, Horror of Dracula.
What track is the Golden Voyage of Sinbad?
Can we queue it up?
15.
We have technology.
We can do whatever we want.
We are, after all, subgeniuses.
Literally.
All right.
You want to go to Golden Voyage?
I have the whole soundtrack of Golden Voyage.
The entire soundtrack is available to us for a minimum price.
You two could own it.
Oh, well.
Yeah.
Oh, remote control.
Yeah, and the listeners heard it five weeks ago.
Unchain him.
He's my friend.
Why is this?
No, he's to remain my captain.
What are you reading?
Please proceed during the intermission.
You better crawl.
You better crawl back in that bunk, boy.
You're raving.
I had the fever.
Let me be, ma.
Let's just let it play.
Thank you.
It's aliens in the background.
Thank you, sir.
Yes.
But it's quiet.
It could be hard to hear.
Oh.
Aliens.
So just some of this ambience in the background.
Here is just a mythical place.
Yeah.
You can't.
In an alternate dimension.
I've heard that about London, too.
Thank you, sir.
Yes, I can.
No.
Jesus.
Yes.
Oh, wait.
There's a level four biohazard in the studio.
Just a little checkup.
Dr. Howell, this would never happen under the stern guidance of Pete Goldie, I think.
This would not happen.
It would be foreboughten.
In order to maintain this process on an automatic level, the special people, those persons who
could read silky minds, were maneuvering into being in charge of it.
Blenders are $9.18 on sale this week only.
Blenders?
Here, I just made one.
I'll give it to you.
$9.
And how much was that?
An 18?
18 cents.
All right.
Here you go.
It's quite the bargain.
God, highway robbery.
Highway robbery?
I think it's a very economical entry point for a subgenius blender.
Yes.
Truth be told, man, because when we blunder, we blunder well.
Right?
You got to mash the bones and the gruel and apparently Argus Fox's man stuff into some
kind of paste.
That takes a lot of work.
It's a high quality blender to do that.
The mortar and pestle process.
It's disgusting.
Now, Princess Wee is picking the rare beer plant that has just sprung from the ground.
Apparently, some beer has grown in her feet.
I thought there were weeds.
I pulled three of them from the table earlier today.
We planted two beers here three weeks ago and all the beers that you see are from those
two beers.
I'm sorry, guys.
I salted the earth.
I thought we were done with this place.
Do you have any pepper?
I do.
Praise.
Mr. Animal for salting the earth because the men were previously seeding the earth
and bragging and rather boastful about it.
It is a medical necessity to avoid government interference.
No, but we can salt.
We can salt.
Salting the earth, I think, is better than seeding the earth.
Salt, piss, and vinegar.
In this case, absolutely so.
What's that?
I don't know.
You tell me.
Well, if the alien women are all plain in human form and look like one person, then
I'm not going to.
Don't worry.
That sounds like you've got a good plan.
Don't worry, the happy man.
They all look the same, huh?
Can we get 15 or 20 of them in here?
Oh my god, I'm dying.
As Fat B drone cast, bumbled ineffectually into a flower and hunted nearsightedly for
a drop of honey.
I love it when you read erotic poems.
Is this turning into bug porn, Sister Animal?
I mean, nearsighted bumblebees, that's starting to get a little steamy for me.
I had to get all close and feely with it.
Animal is very wavy today.
Is he going to use his stamen?
Did my father look like this?
Many times, but only after drinking.
This is supposed to be science fiction.
It's science facts.
That's right.
Of course it is.
And only the uber femme has got it really figured out.
I did like the whole uber concert.
Except for just you and uber for a bunch of parasites in your body.
Sister Animal.
I make the homage to you.
You're whispering.
Am I?
I have lost my voice.
It's your turn.
Oh, it's a search.
Stop mumbling.
Get that dick out of your mouth.
It's a search.
The chimp will raise the trapped leg clear of the ground and dash me down.
He's hurt.
I'm hurt.
Man down.
We need another comic on the stage.
It's all he can do to hold on.
Man down.
I'm so sorry.
That was a harsh embrace of roasting.
Danny Chagat.
Danny Chagat to save the peas, man.
As least his teeth aren't hurting.
Come up to the stage.
Thank you, my brother.
Did he just say a shout out to hamburger buns?
If you don't got buns, hon, I don't want none.
So, do you have hamburger buns?
We need hamburger buns over there.
All right.
Less peas.
For the listeners at home.
More hamburger buns.
I'm pointing that way.
Well, I'll stay on unless Barat.
That's right.
A third voice is necessary for the continuation of this sort of auditory torture experience
that we're going to inflict on all you poor little so-and-sos right now.
Let's begin to organize for a fantastic future.
I'm ready.
Come on, Susie.
It'll be great.
The future's bright because it's only destruction.
There's nothing left.
There's nothing left but fire.
Yeah!
Destruction.
We have sewn the cigarette butts and we shall reap the win.
Do all of your drugs today because tomorrow will not come.
The frog sticks are a little fatter here at X-Day on the last day as people prepare to
board their airplanes and go through security measures enforced by the Frankenstein monster
computer government.
Yes, sir, but it's the only thing they listen to.
Well, let them listen because it's the last chance they're going to get.
Enjoy.
Here have a drink.
Carol J. Clems, the historian.
Oh.
Are these books from the Bull Data auction there?
Is that what's...
Books purchased by some geniuses
that just left up on stage
because they don't really care.
May I recite a passage from this book?
Would that be all right?
No, but please continue.
I don't do it anyway.
This is something from December 1952.
Imaginations, stories of science and fantasy.
Children of the chronotron.
It was decided that to trek aimlessly through the jungle
unaware of what they were looking for would be futile.
Instead, they chose to follow
the well-delineated trail of the captives
in order to determine where the alien was taking them.
I always follow that trail.
We all want to know where the aliens are going to take us,
but we're going to find out tomorrow.
They all looked at each other in shocked silence,
except for Henry.
He merely experimented.
Henry's a scientist.
We all experimented in college.
With some of the drugs.
Especially that.
Last day.
All your drugs.
Bring them.
Bring them down here.
Them big ol' fat frop sticks you all rolling up.
Them big boys ain't going down without a fight.
Bring them up in the suboxone, thorazine, urine, blood, piss, pod crust.
We'll do our best to help you fight those frop demons.
That's the royal we, right?
Mmm.
And it was at that moment that fate cut the cord.
An eye-searing light filled the cabin,
and Kennedy shrieked,
The reaction sphere!
The planet once known as Earth burst into a minor nova,
blasting its quick-fling into spiraling shreds
and tatters of celestial tinsel.
Hell yeah, read that part again.
And we'll do it again, and then we'll continue,
because it's even hotter after that.
This is just Earth destruction, peak porn.
Start over.
We're in space.
Yes.
The planet once known as Earth burst into a minor nova,
blasting its great ring into spiraling shreds and tatters of celestial tinsel.
Shaggith, get your hand out of your pants.
Oh.
In the face of that.
I prefer not to.
All right, keep them there, all three of them.
In the face of that swiftly advancing flame,
the starships that had survived the rocket's first onslaught
flicked safely into hyperspace, which was us,
and came to the surface of the planet.
Kennedy tried to stand enough Gs of acceleration to keep up ahead of it.
Oh yeah, how much Gs did he get on him?
Not enough.
He had no sub-Gs, and he, along with the rest of the pinks, perished.
And so it was.
An airlock sealed the gun compartments off from the rocket's cabin,
but the remains of the two gunners drifted into the turbulent ethers.
And so it was.
You know, I'm a little concerned, because I don't think that the space would be so hyper if it was just medicated.
Right?
Properly medicated.
Oh, you're just coming here from Big Pharma.
You know, this is again part of the Disneyfication of the church.
Now the sponsors are coming in, and you're gonna try and push your conspiracy pills on us.
Yeah.
No, no, no, more them kind pills.
They aren't even trying to hide it anymore, folks.
The robot Stang walks around glitching and malfunctioning inside the animals up here.
I can hear him squeaking and whirring and clicking, clicks and beeps.
Making an advertisement for some kind of anti-herpes medication.
Now he's pressing buttons.
He's probably got experience in the matter, though, and I take her advice.
He's some type of android scribe.
I mean, robots can type faster than hippies.
Oh, well then for sure he's a hippie.
I mean, he's not even typing. He's just standing there like some kind of an ape, you know, holy...
What kind of madman would build a hippie robot?
Stumbling like a mummy.
You know, that's a good question.
It's not.
Because I'd like to meet that person.
Oh, you know what? It must have been J.R. Bob Dobbs himself.
He's trying to sell shit.
And he suckered me in. My wallet belongs to Bob.
I'm just a little concerned that my money's going to robots now.
Hal, I'm wearing headphones. I can't hear you. Don't talk to me.
Your money is going to robots. And there's nothing to do but wait for the aliens. Tomorrow, 7 AM.
But think about what pinks do when you send them things.
I don't want to think about pinks.
Wouldn't you rather send it to a robot? One thing I know about robots...
They ain't pink.
How do you know? You been inside one? Don't answer that question.
Eggplant.
Never mind.
For those listening at home, never mind.
I'm running out of breath telling all of you...
For those listening at home, enjoy what little time you have left, suckers.
Because it ends tomorrow.
And you may die.
Less than 24 hours to get here.
I have one thing I have to say.
The sales table will close at the end of time, which is pretty soon.
He was built by a robot.
Considering today's date, July 4th.
So friends, everything must go by 1998.
Hit that sales table.
And when you are eating the food and fishes and loaves, we shall do the final auction of the final bulldada for the final time.
That is all.
Bring your money, bring your money.
Open your wallets to Bob.
Open your wallets.
Open them wide because you ain't spending any money after 7 a.m. tomorrow.
Thanks, Janebot5000, with your salesmanship upgrade.
I told you he was built by Bob.
Sales swag.
Reverend Eggplant, would you like to represent the mitten state?
The mitten state?
Yeah.
A whole state based on not being able to use all your fingers.
That's absolutely correct.
We hail from the...
A fine thing to call yourself.
Little nipper claw shaped.
Peninsular.
With all their appendages exposed.
That's probably true.
They do have big, weird looking fingers.
I like this song.
We're changing out staff here.
We have to...
Hang on.
We're inserting Eggplant into the Tarzan radio station console.
We might have to take him out and blow on him first.
Give me a minute for my meat.
But he's going to have to pay us for that.
I'm going to power up my kazoo.
I took the battery out of your kazoo.
I noticed.
I was just looking for the batteries.
I need to recharge them.
Yeah, these are stupid little watch batteries that you can't find anywhere.
They use like four different names.
I dropped one and it's gone.
They were impossible.
Gone forever in the grass.
We'd also like to note that we need hamburger buns.
If you want to eat hamburgers, bring any buns you got left.
Because you can't take those buns on the plane with you back.
Can't take those with you actually.
Can't take them on the bus.
And if the cops pull you over, you don't want them to see you with those buns.
So bring all of your buns up to the stage here and we'll help you dispose.
Keep all of your appendages within view of the arresting officer.
Pease isn't the only one with problems.
Hey eggplant, I'm glad you could join us.
Hi.
I was wondering, what's your favorite kind of apocalypse?
My favorite kind of apocalypse would be where we just totally incinerate the whole god damn planet from orbit and say, yeah, we're done.
I like the way this guy thinks.
What are we orbiting?
Incinerate them.
Yes, it's still counting.
We actually do orbit a giant incinerator called the sun.
The counting.
And one day, like the trash it is.
The earth is going to be a mess.
The earth will be thrown into it.
The countdown has begun.
We are watching the clocks.
Hoping that the calendars do sync up.
The two subgeniuses who actually wear watches are watching the clocks here at Wisteria where you can't really get reception.
Mine's just drawn on.
That or masturbate furiously.
We don't know what we want to do.
Masturbate furiously.
Or watch the clocks.
Masturbate furiously or else.
You don't actually know how to work a digital clock.
You don't have to be a digital watch.
That's before your time.
No, it has three buttons and they're, as far as I'm concerned, it's written in, there
are three buttons written in Egyptian.
There are three buttons.
No, five?
Written in the secret tongues of the exes.
What happens if I push this one?
I have no idea.
Oh, that's not the right number.
Did you make different numbers show up on my watch?
Different numbers?
You might have.
Oh, RoboStang would love that.
It's going to happen sooner than we thought.
Different numbers, alternate facts.
Ow.
Oh man.
You got a time machine on your wrist?
Yeah.
How does it work?
I'm not, I don't know.
The instructions was like six, giant page and half of it was written in Japanese.
Stop it.
It only goes in one direction.
You cannot go back.
Oh, that's not good.
Stop.
I'm just going to touch this other button over here.
He's not trying to play side two.
Listeners at home, animals being really obnoxious.
I'm just touching the buttons on the one of the three.
Almost as obnoxious as evil genius, man.
Mastermind to the stars, Fid Shuley.
That man is missing.
I'm so glad he's here.
We need to find him.
I mean, missing.
Why are you glad he's missing?
Nothing.
Because it means something.
Because it means eventually he's going to show up.
Because I don't have a cover under the stage here.
Uh huh.
There's not a space under the stage.
There is a door under this stage actually.
There is a door.
It leads to his commands.
Not anymore.
I threw a rug on top of it.
I'm sorry.
Oh, that fixed it.
Great job, you sub genius.
I want to give you this penny.
You seem like the kind of person who'd pay $35 to a bit mapped image you can print off
the internet.
It's a dirty penny.
It's a dirty, dirty penny.
What do you got?
Stop laundering money in front of my face without paying me to watch.
I'm going to put batteries back in them.
Hey, watch all you like, son.
You know, that's what gets your rocks off.
You know?
These are double A. I need triple A for the kazoo.
Dude, I don't have any rocks left to get off.
Not after this.
You have the third rock to get off.
Nope.
It's gone too.
I'm going to have to wait at least six weeks after I get back to recuperate and regrow
my lizard parts.
1932.
I'm so glad I'm not the only lizard person here.
I was so alone.
Actually, it was misread.
It's 1923.
Oh no.
That number.
That other religion's stupid number.
Read the numbers on this one.
I've just been handed some counterfeited currency and I'm going to examine it.
We only counterfeit pennies here.
Yeah, it's...
Easier to pass.
The margins are more difficult.
Okay, I'm holding a highly oxidized 1972.
Is it 1972?
1972.
Okay.
Common currency.
Common.
Nothing special about it.
Legal tender for all debts, public and private, for approximately...
Three, two, one.
Fourteen hours.
Less than 14 hours.
Less than.
Indeed.
The end approaches quickly, friends.
And we couldn't be more glad for it.
You never know when it will come up and bite you right in the behind.
I know it's going to come and bite you right in the behind because I paid it $20 to do
so.
Why would you do that?
Fuck you.
Fuck you if you can't take a joke.
Well, I'm right here in the joke.
It's even better when they're in on the joke.
We're in on the joke at this point.
We're all in on the joke.
It's hysteria.
When you walk up to another subgenius and you punch them right in the face, it's because
you know they're in on the joke.
A cigar shoved deep into his mouth.
Mm-hmm.
Keep going.
Lit on fire and explode.
Don't tease our listeners.
You don't do something like that, that would be the equivalent of saying that you're in
on the joke.
But still, allhhh...
Do you sleep on these casse etc where you're thinking, holy shit what's going on
I don't know.
I don't see it, bet you do.
I'm not sure what the exact answer is.
story about bureaucracy.
Okay. It's layers deep.
Yeah. You know, that's
the thing about science fiction. You take something boring
and then you put it in space.
Nope. Not in space. It's
on a planet that is...
Where our planet's animal.
Here's the science fiction
to read. Yeah.
But this guy's having to request
If you like the concept of taking something
boring and turning it into
a fantastic concept, what
you need to do is get on the
internet and look up, probably
on subgenius.com, how to purchase
Neighbor World by lonesome cowboy
Dave
DeLuca.
It's a great book.
You know, they asked
me to write a blurb for the cover, but I
didn't want to sound unrealistic in my
praise, so I said, why don't you get
somebody else to do it,
you big dummy.
But I
read it. I received a preview copy.
It was so good, I threw it
against the wall twice.
Fantastic universe. And then I put it in a blender
because I said, if I'm gonna... I've got
some new ideas about this cut-up technique thing,
I'm gonna put a book in a blender
and then just make...
Imagination.
That's what it's all about here.
He stuck out a large bony
hand. Why did he stick out?
A large bony hand.
Mm-hmm.
No, this was about
a tall man with a lean, almost skeletal
face, framed by a check.
Big bony hand. He stuck right out.
Would I be
able to pick him out in the crowd?
He's a salesman. He's a salesman
with a big bony hand that he sticks right
out. Who could this be talking about?
Smiling face.
I wonder if he's been a long ponytail.
We don't really know what Bob looks like
before he puts his hair product on, because clearly
that thing's slicked back or he just doesn't take a shower
so much that he's created a natural grease,
a natural promod that he
produces from
his own scalp. Oh, wait, there...
It's getting exciting, guys. They're asking to be
taken into a private office to have
a chat. Oh.
Dang, what's that gonna be all about?
Read the rest in Amazing
by some dead
people.
Published by a company that
probably doesn't exist anymore.
Available at a
garage. Original price, 35 cents.
Resale price,
49 cents. But don't be
paying those kind of rip-off prices
to original retailers. You gotta,
you gotta get the second-hand market going.
You can probably find this for
five cents.
Maybe they'll pay you to take it.
Free on Craigslist. Now.
See the
man who had no brains.
Carousel.
Alright, right now we're gonna...
What we want you to do right now is
we need to...
Get your butts up here. Come from
your camps!
Wake up!
And come over here.
And buy this
fantastic object that I've just
been presented by Dr. Cosmec.
And I'll allow you to describe this
thing that we have right now available
for you for a limited time here on
the stage.
So many molded jellies from ancient
lands. This here, it looks
like a small cake, but it's not
a cake. It's an off-white
plastic device, possibly
with lights. And it's got
one, two, three carousels.
Cell horses on it. How much should we
trust that? I can confirm that it's
not a cake. I tried to eat it last night.
One horse is brown. The other
two are a violet
color. And if I
turn it on... Dare I turn
it on? Dare you turn it on.
I'm sure it wouldn't go spinning about.
It plays the voices of angels.
Why don't you play that
on the microphone for about five minutes.
Hang on. How do I turn this
up really loud so everybody can know what they're doing?
They're purchasing. Oh, it's being
heard very well.
That's great.
I can't wait
for it to be over so I can listen to it again.
I wonder what
else it does. So, uh,
we've got an asking price.
Oh, you're going to
auction this guy off. Yeah.
Oh, crap. It's mobile.
So if you want this hot item
right now,
it moves around. It will try to
escape you. It doesn't want
you around. It will try to run away, but it's
bad at it. It's like, hey guys, you need to listen to this
song. You need to come here and get this
right now for the lowest price that
you can bid. And it's going to be spicy
too, let me tell you. Honestly, all you gotta do
is put a couple of those, uh,
dust cloths stuck to the bottom of it.
You've got a musical room
thing. You've got like this.
You could just sweep up after yourself.
He's coming up here fascinated with Childlike
Wonder staring at this device.
Maybe I want to re-inhabit this planet.
And you need to sweep up the scorched
ashes. You can do so using this device.
You just put a little paper towel on the
bottom of it and let it go.
This will be a document to take into space
with us on the pleasure saucers as a reminder
that Earth existed. Pease, how much would
you like to pay for this device?
People should bring plates.
And when you come up here to get this device,
you should bring great things too.
He wants plates. Bring your plates. He wants
He wants buns. He wants
He wants plates. He wants buns. He wants
hot dog buns. Which one is it?
Bring your hot dog buns.
People have plates.
Bring the remains of your gear.
Bring your plates. Bring everything over.
If you want your slop, then bring some buns, you pigs.
You want to stuff your faces on this red meat?
You want to sweat it out later tonight?
By providing us the goodies and tools
we need to consume it with.
I'm talking to all of you.
Pease is going on a bicycle right now
to extort buns from every one of you with threats of violence,
which will be followed
up later tonight after we see your camp get dark.
Where are the fuck with us?
Bring your buns.
Where are the buns?
I know where they are.
They're all out there and they need to be in here.
And that's all your responsibility.
For those listening at home, bring your buns.
The robot wants to feed you meat sacks.
We will take your buns now.
One time, Argus Fox was like, I'm going to make some buns.
I'm going to make some hamburgers.
And some geniuses.
And they were like, you don't have enough buns, Argus Fox.
But he fed it through the hypercube and lo,
there were plenty of hamburgers and everyone could have had one,
but they didn't have any buns.
So we saw plates, mustard, ketchup, mayonnaise.
The bloodless laws.
Let there be.
Taste fucking bad antidote pudding for dessert.
Butterscotch flavor.
Make them appear.
I don't like the butterscotch flavored one.
I like the natural taste.
The strength of 10.
It's basically kombucha and pudding for them.
It's disgusting.
We need your spice rack.
Bring your spice rack and bring your racks.
Bring your bring your big old racks down here and we'll put some spices on them.
Where's the beef?
Naturally.
The beef is accounted for.
It's the buns that are the problem.
So if you hear me, you.
Chairs.
Knuckle dragging subgenius, inhuman, here sweet, ugly weirdos who are my favorite people in the world.
I do everything you do at home, but better.
Bring your buns down here and bring your asses for delicious burgers provided by hypercube laboratories.
I don't have to worry about chopping wood or growing or cooking food.
You're not going to have to worry about chopping your own wood while you're eating.
Or playing a natural one. If you're chopping.
your wood out in the TARDIS because
you can't get hard without the smell.
Then stop.
Get your hands off
your dick, grab some hot dog buns
and get down to Caffeinas.
Just don't play with your phone.
You can play with your phone
if you're playing with something else.
If you can get a signal to get on those dirty
websites you go to.
We have no survival problems
out here. We got all we need.
All we want.
Except for buns and plates. Please bring those.
How many subgeniuses come to
X-State just because they have a
Port-A-John fetish and this is like
number one spot in the world.
A plus material over there.
The Jacob Capital. This is like
San Francisco in the 60s but
for shithouses in the woods.
Speaking of which, don't forget
to close the doors
for you. Close the lids.
That way the flies get to stay.
Peas is returned and
probably not with buns because why
would you expect them to do anything wrong?
If you like
the smell of the fudge. He brought bowls.
Just what we asked for. What else did you bring?
Peas. Is that bread?
Not buns? You want to see hot
hamburgers off of plain
white bread? You...
How'd you do that? He asked.
Now watch. How'd I do it?
I just thought about peas and said
what was the truth.
Let there be meat.
But bring buns or
no meat for anybody. How could
you eat your pudding if you don't bring
us hot dog buns in the words of
an old song? Nine.
Nine is the answer. The number
nine. Bullshit.
Stop. See the numbers
again. The numbers. Nine!
You're probably
programming the robot's next direction
slowly by speaking these codes.
These numbers. He's slowly
ticking them off. John Lennon
was part of this too. John Lennon was another
agent of Fid Truly sent back into
the past. I think I needed to talk to you.
Do some more.
You know if you play Revolution Number Nine
backwards. Number Nine?
It says send $35 to P.O. Box
181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio
44118. Box.
The murmuring voice is
fed into indistinct... I practice at home
in the mirror, Stang. Then the wind grows
covering everything in such a rich
hum.
Where's my fucking kazoo?
Number Nine? Rich hum.
If you
play Revolver backwards,
if you play Sgt. Pep, I was gonna make
fun of Revolver, but that's a good album.
If you play Sgt. Pepper's backwards,
you hear a good album.
Thick, needly pine branches
rubbed together
in a dull crunch.
Oh, wow. Is that
a haiku? Oak,
hickory, maple,
and elm limb screeched
with the clattering of
dead leaves. The sound swelled.
That's not a very good haiku.
The zoom faded, leaving
faint, deeply overcones. I heard a good haiku once.
And this isn't it.
And Francis disappeared.
I bet. Where's Pease?
Where's Pease?
He has to answer for his
typical behavior.
Every time.
Do you hear that sound,
hungry people? That's the
sound calling. That's the bread bell.
Bring us
your buns.
Your buns.
Not your hot dog buns.
We've had enough hot dog bun related
content from enough people
this week. All the wrong
people all about the hot dog buns.
Hey, kiddo, he oozed.
How about some breakfast?
He oozed?
I got some new Agri-Corp W, bagels, fruit,
you name it, a feast.
Climbers need fuel. It's right over there
next to the plates.
We need fuel to send the hill
to the Port-A-John.
Looks like dinner time.
Pod crust eats last.
So fine. We're too
scrummed out to...
I don't need it. I got all the scrum I need.
You don't get to eat, animal.
I just absorb nutrients through the air.
Good.
I know I don't get to eat. You didn't bring me any food.
You left me out here
in the middle of the woods to fight for myself.
I brought you food and you were
very rude about it.
I showed you how to use a stick.
And I brought you ass.
No skills to find the things that you need
to make your way through the forest.
He doesn't even know how to use a stick properly.
Do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do.
I'm a kazoo.
Didn't even know how to use a stick properly.
They didn't teach you shit at homeschool.
That's right.
There were other ways a stick was applied.
Upside your head?
No.
Can't you tell by looking at this million dollar face?
They never touch that.
Never.
That's my money maker.
Sure. What the hell?
It's not my wit.
My dulcet tones.
I'm just reading this fantastic book
Neighbor World by Dave DeLuca.
And I'm always really getting off on this book
Neighbor World every year.
The floor on the stage
has got a weird color
discoloration on it right under her
as she reads Neighbor World.
There in clear sight.
By lonesome cowboy Dave DeLuca.
Available from Subgenius Press
for a low, low price of insert price here.
A very camera looking
Neighbor World source
pre-processing.
Sitting here next to the book, I can tell you
it looks nicely formatted.
Looks like I'm going to go with Times New Roman
though it could be Palantino font.
I can't tell exactly from here.
The margins are nice and even.
I'd say that's a
10.5 or 11 point font
though definitely not a full
font.
That's fine.
It is not a sans serif font.
It clearly has serifs.
Holy shit.
Just saying words.
Another robot.
But aren't we all?
I love watching these subgeniuses
eat their hamburgers that I'm not eating.
There's something nice
about it, you know.
Apologies again, dear neighbors, for such
unpro-focus.
This orgy of
BS.
This book is prophecy.
This book is fucked up.
I know, that's why it's prophecy.
That's how you know it's real.
Find another passage.
Don't sign anything before reading it, P's.
At the...
Oh, you would.
Wisdom that you find inside.
I looked inside for wisdom and all I found was a crumpled up bazooka joke comic in the bottom of my soul.
I found wild berries. Can you believe it?
Let's try one.
That's not as good as what I got.
Don't eat the red berries.
It was one of the really funny ones.
You can tell it is I'm making this up because there are no funny bazooka joke comics.
I don't even know why they put them in there.
It's disgusting gum.
The comic nobody likes.
I wonder if their brand's even still alive.
Did you ever want bubble gum but didn't want to have all your teeth left?
Bazooka joke.
Uh...
The worst gum.
The best gum for the record is that bubble gum one that's green on the outside and red on the inside.
No unfunny comics involved. Just delicious gum.
Sorry, I can't... My A material is vanishing as I just watch all this food.
Just think Halloween.
It's gone.
Listen to that.
You know what...
The Hour of Slack sponsored by Stamps.com will return in a moment.
Stamps.com.
Do you not use Stamps.com? Look how stupid you are. Go to Stamps.com and type...
... into the search bar for a special discount from the Thorazine Urine Suboxone Recovery Clinic.
Not open on Mondays or Tuesdays.
In Ohio, right next to scenic Illinois.
Stamps.com.
USA.
You need about 5 more minutes of that.
Just keep it the same spot. We want them to hear all of it.
That's better.
That's my jam.
La la la la la la la.
No kidding.
La la la la la la la la.
Do you not know the name of this song?
That's Help by Led Zeppelin.
La la la la la la la la la la.
No, it's Dr. Feelgood by Frank Zappa.
Oh.
Maybe it's Alice Cooper's Rock the Casbah.
I don't know.
I'm going to take this 5 minutes.
I request that extended to 5 more.
I have like 5 minutes.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
I don't know how long 5 minutes is.
My watch is drawn on.
Here comes Lagoon with the sacrificial poisons.
The final nudge into the diabetic coma that every subgenius will be suffering tomorrow
after their beautiful night of restful sleep that's coming right up, you know.
You've got to be bright, like I said before.
You've got to be ready for the saucers.
Well rested.
7 a.m.
Just a little after blue 30.
Don't forget to wake me up this time, guys.
That's why they didn't show up last year.
Why would they?
Never.
Everybody's asleep like a baby.
And you're going to be the only one out there in the field.
Mm-hmm.
And they're going to be like, pfft, screw this.
And that's why they left last year?
Masturbation.
That's why they're like, out of here?
Yeah.
The X's came down.
They smelled my shirt and they left.
It's a binary masturbation.
I'm so glad that you're happy.
I have bear-scented deodorant now.
It's real.
Arrr.
Have you shown anybody else?
Have you let anybody else know?
No, it's not something that I would talk.
It's a personal issue.
I did have to buy.
It's a personal matter.
I don't want to discuss it out loud with people.
He's like, why did you want to go in town so bad?
Why did you want to go into town?
What's so important about town?
I was like, to buy you deodorant.
If I knew that's why you wanted to go to town, I would have bought you deodorant.
If I knew that's why you wanted to go to town, I would have refused.
And I would have buried you in the woods.
You did refuse.
Some place that's familiar.
I did.
Oh yeah.
I should have taken you in the car I rented.
And well lighted.
And secure.
On my way to the clinic.
I'm never buying you a plane ticket ever again.
That's good because you haven't yet.
Remember, it's all for your safety.
I took the bus.
For your safety.
I don't know what you did with your GoFundMe money.
Actually, I do know what you did with your GoFundMe money.
About every other subgenius here knows because they smoked it.
Yeah.
That settles it.
Didn't waste any of that on camping supplies.
I just been sleeping on the stage.
You're not sleeping at all.
Yes, but they won't let me leave.
Bring me food or kill me.
But I'm going to rebel.
Want a hamburger?
Nah.
Give me slack or kill me food or kill me.
And uh, fuck all your friends.
Give me slack or give me food or kill me.
Or why not all three?
Do me now, baby.
Why not both?
Oh, I'm taking an extra letter.
Okay, it's a true Thorazine you're in Podcrust.
We got somebody eating food.
Podcrust Theater continues now on a different frequency and channel.
Does anybody have a shop dog?
We need a shop dog to bark into the background.
Can you bring your dog down here?
It's very important.
I want him.
Oh, no thank you, doctor.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
Oh, it looks so good, but I am absolutely...
This is the first hamburger I've had since January.
Stan gets to eat his new hamburger.
How lovely.
From NPR News in Washington.
I'm known to have information that I want to share with you.
As far as grams.
Yeah.
So far, in the last four or seven years at some point that I've sat in the middle of
No, no, don't say that.
Well, you have to share your life together.
There's Congress here today.
I've heard the word, and they should have told me.
And I think I know what I'm talking about as well.
I'm busy, so I've got no time to be sitting here with anybody else.
PR news.
This show, the hour of slack.
If you need more information, please see subjeetunius.com on the internet.
And you can write to P.O. Box 807 Glen Rose, Texas 76043.
Praise Bob.
I'm hoping now I can give out your phone number.
Your own phone number.
And now we'll copy the Fireside Theater again for those of you on drugs.