I'm serious, Mr. Jammet. I'm certain something's wrong. I'm sure it is.
Calm yourself, madam. It's just a signal to stop the hour of slack.
Because we're so geniuses.
Oh, it's lovely. Oh, it's so beautiful.
Well, Dr. Watson, that was certainly a case of never the one for a man was that.
On the contrary, we were both in the same position.
Oh, no.
Jesus Christ, come on down!
Come on!
If you ever wondered how you get triangles from a cow you need
But a milk and cheese and an equilateral chainsaw
In debt I owe someone a fiver
Maybe I should try my hand at slack
James Dean was just a careless driver
And Marilyn Monroe was just a drag
Makeup室
9.99% of gargoyles look likelov attracted
And you may have got one too
depending on how you're bigger than that
This has been Theсти
!
© All rights reserved
Senhor
Duest
Obej Waqar
рем temporary
pico
Mary had a little lamb
The doctors were astounded
Everywhere she went
Gynecologists surrounded
They've been cooking on Blue Peter now
They're sampling the dishes
I don't normally like tomatoes, John
But this is delicious
99% of gardeners look like Bob Tart
Take me home
The son of Jimmy Clitherow is shouting out
Where's my Perucci?
The son of Jimmy Clitherow
I don't do their little helped
You can see there's a town
Did you honestly think that they would?
And if eight out of ten catch or prefer
Whiskers to the other to prepare Leslie Judd
99% of gargoyles love light fleck cars
99% of gargoyles look like hot dogs
99% of gargoyles look
like
From PR News in Washington, I'm bottoming out.
After 11 straight weeks of declines, I should soon be going back up again.
PR's report is causing headaches for companies trying to prepare next month's victims.
Taxpayers could see an average two-tax increase next year.
PR News.
PR's reports show shoppers say shoppers saw stores spending stocks shot in snow shop states.
Syria's president told reporters, this is PR News from Washington.
It's being described as another insider attack.
PR News has stirred outrage across the country.
Forecasters moving across the middle of the country say police staged PR News with a pistol in Washington.
Thanks to Lee Murr for that and the titles.
I have to do these credits quietly and quickly because I'm in a motel room and we have to get up early to go to Death Valley.
The song 99% of Gargoyles Look Like Bob Dobbs was by Half Man, Half Biscuit and is on the Bob Songs 5 CD.
Most of this show came about while we were in California.
First, we went to KPFA in Berkeley.
And did a puzzling evidence show.
And now we're swimming around in your mind.
I'm just splashing my feet.
I just pushed her cough sensor.
I just took my socks off.
What's this crud floating on the surface?
Old Sequa will nibble your toes.
Well, I took my socks off in her brain there.
Yes, the secret of old Sequa is that he doesn't so much live within the pit of the wisteria pond, but deep within the pit of your own mind.
I have to admit.
It's really terrible.
The waters are actually rather warm.
But there is a prehistoric turtle down in the depths.
A snapper.
Ready to shoot up and drag you down instantly in one gulp.
It's like everything in John's panorama ever right now.
Giant birds all over the place.
That's true.
It smells fishy.
I think old Sequa will shake your body around to soften the bones up and then stashes you under a shelf underwater.
I don't know if he shakes.
He stashes you, yes, but I don't think he shakes you.
He just drags you down.
Live at some place.
Live at somewhere con.
Yeah, live at some place.
Crocodilians and alligators shake their prey, but the snapping turtle, an opportunity feeder, just grabs it and drags it down.
Eating animal and vegetable indiscriminately.
An omnivore in the turtle family.
Do you know of any mermaids existing to this day?
No.
They're all organic.
When I'm feeling bad, I just throw some money at something.
Over this way.
There it goes.
I feel better all the time.
No, you overshot, damn it.
That's a lot of money.
I missed it, too.
We could have had the asteroid hit the planet for that much, and you guys just threw it away.
I could have had a V8 for a cheap laugh.
There you go.
We had a good time.
He's on the air.
He sent the meteorite.
Now that meteorite exploded in the air.
Isn't it?
In an airburst, fortunately, instead of striking on land, which would have been quite a problem.
Cheap pops and bad puns.
That's what we do here on the Puzzling Evidence Show.
Just keep it down to a dull roar and confine your shenanigans to the rumpus room.
I don't want to hear one peep out of your kids, and don't make me come up there.
Oh, yeah?
Well, what if?
I beg your pardon?
Yeah.
What if we don't want to listen to you?
Well, I...
I can hear him jumping on the bed.
He's up there right now.
That's right.
Yeah, what are you going to do about it?
Who's going to fight next?
What if...
Yeah, what if we don't want to listen to you?
Oh, that could never be.
What are we going to do?
If we don't...
If you don't want to listen to the Puzzling Evidence Show right now...
Wait, wait, wait.
Well, what...
Well, there are other things...
What kind of person are you talking about?
Who would not want to listen to this?
Oh, wait.
McAfee's over.
A suicide call.
It's a sad man.
Suicide call's over.
Who would not want to listen to this?
this. This stuff, this
dreck, this drivel, this pile of
stink. Not as sad as it is.
People don't want to listen to this show.
No, surely
not. This is a distempered
dream of Dr. Drummond.
Well, ever since Homeland Security came in, they make
you do everything. They force you to
listen to the show even now.
We didn't want to have to. We wanted people to do it
voluntarily. And we'd rather
be at home on the auto, man.
Stretched out, eating grapes.
But instead, we have to be here and
do this show.
And there's 11 or more cameras
just focused in on us right now.
11 time zones.
And there's 7 safeties
on the 45 and 18
cameras in the building. 18?
You counted them, huh?
No, that's what they said. They sent out a little email
to warn everybody.
But outside, they're also...
I'm going to start wearing a mask to the show.
That'll make me invisible.
They might know it was you
just the same. Shane's going to wear one of those
kind you wear when you're in front of a green screen.
Yeah, one of those dark, standard
darkly ones. They'll just shop me out
of it. Well, we can
always take you out. They'll shop
me. They'll just shop you out, too, whenever
they... Just take a still...
They'll shop you.
They'll shop you into the picture.
You'll feel the air rise.
Just take a still picture of the room and put it in front of the camera.
Yeah, there you go. Yeah, that's right.
No one would ever cut none of that.
Like the little... Oh, they do it in
a... Mad Magazine.
And Mad Magazine. Right.
It worked there. Yeah.
It worked with Stang. I put a
still picture of 1977 in front
of him. He never noticed.
You are bobsolete.
Sounds evil. That's terrible.
I protest.
You are bobsolete.
My attorney let me place
in the record...
You are no longer
of use to the society.
You are bobsolete.
Isn't there any young
person that will speak for me
or must I be... No, go
throw him into the lake of Soylent Green.
Don't take Halloway. I like
house. Don't take Halloway. There you
go. She's supporting me in my
last pathetic... Everybody
loves Hab Halloway.
That great jazz singer.
Hab Halloway.
He was ripped off by another guy.
Hoity ho, hoity ho.
There was a cigarette
dance that said, don't take
Halloway.
Don't take Halloway.
Hab Halloway
smokes Chesterfields.
They are mild.
The cigarettes?
Chesterfields, yes.
Named after Lord Chesterfield.
Who wrote such excellent letters
of advice to his son.
Yeah, Chesterfields
I guess would be the official cigarette
of the Church of the Septuagint.
As opposed to Raleigh,
which were smoked by Sir Walter.
Although Lucky Strikes were a real
runner up.
It's luck to catch one of those,
but nobody can.
What about Camel?
Which? What? What about...
Camel.
Now the thing you have to understand
is that the reason why Chesterfields
are important is because that's the
brand that Jesus smoked.
Yes, we've been through this all
before. Jesus smoked Chesterfields.
But once the Camel gets its nose
under the tank, then, uh,
it's a little bit of a
one must give up.
The rest of the beast will soon follow.
But Satan smoked Lucky Strikes.
All the way through the eye of the needle.
No, no, what about Camel Crust?
LSMFT.
Crust.
Lucky Strikes means fine tobacco.
Says Satan.
It has to be some sort of satanic.
Loose straps mean floppy.
A little too hard on Satan's head.
I think you called the wrong show.
You can get cigarettes in hell
unless you're a smoker.
Even in a distant city?
They are inventing machines down there.
Yeah, that would be hell in itself
if you're a smoker but you can't
get cigarettes in hell.
That's your punishment.
Distant city on the steps
like Chelyabinsk.
Fine tobacco.
Still has all those cameras.
I'm taking notes of everything
you're saying here.
All these cameras that can
record something remarkable.
Yeah.
Even in that far corner of the
civilized world.
Right.
We now have dozens of videos
of the civilized world.
Among which,
are the most incredible footage
of such a natural event
that ever occurred.
Incredible.
Unbelievable.
Pretty possible.
One in particular has the sound
of the shock wave arriving.
Shock wave.
And shattering windows.
You hear this cascade of breaking glass.
That was the astronaut,
the air burst of the asteroid.
Hold on.
I'm going to write this down.
Yes.
That's right.
That's happening right now.
Or is it?
Over the Pacific Ocean.
The skies of Russia.
Several hours ago,
they had the most remarkable
video ever obtained of a close
cup of Mirage Junior,
which was obtained.
They shot that?
They have it on video?
There are dozens of them now.
Dozens of videos?
You won't going to believe it.
Some of them looks like surveillance
cameras of an office,
and all of a sudden,
you see the window blown open
and the door on the opposite
side.
Same thing.
The paper is simultaneously
shoved the same direction,
and the papers are flying across the room.
It's like nuclear test films,
but within a modern living context.
There's a room with a door that was blown open,
and you can see the brilliant outdoors.
That's right here.
Smoke kind of going into the room.
But did you ever see the movie
Is that on YouTube now?
Day of the Trip?
Yes, yes.
Meteor, Russian explosion.
I wish I could give you URLs,
but I'll put something on the,
on Philo's Facebook page.
There's something weird going on here.
You know this is for a reference.
What is, what would you Google for that?
I'll give you the word Russia.
Why do you want the meteor?
It's always by the Russian meteor.
Russia is so big,
the chances mathematically are increased
that they would hit great big Russia.
But that's still,
you're talking about not just Russia,
you're talking about the entire surface
of the world.
Well, then they should follow the Pacific,
shouldn't they?
Exactly.
And maybe they do.
And in the US.
And in the Atlantic.
And everywhere.
But instead,
they always fall in Russia.
This is the world so far.
But,
this is the world so far.
Maybe Russians deserve it.
Anyway,
if you could put,
you probably don't have a computer there,
you could put something online,
but the audio of this one thing,
I'll reference it,
which is well worth listening to,
just for the,
the immensity of the sound.
You can hear the sound waves
slamming in the cascade of glass,
and then you hear the secondary explosions
from the,
the pieces that were trailing
each leading air shock wave.
It's terrible rotten smell
of burning flesh.
A horrible rotten smell.
The Siberian Tate is
the worst.
This is real.
Even the rogues of the church.
The rogues of the church
have nothing to do with it.
Well,
I heard that the Russians
don't love their children.
They're just making money.
They're not like us.
They're all rich like us.
They have no respect
for the sanctity of human beings.
I heard that on a
Seafrist for Communism movie.
Really?
But,
who,
seriously,
who else saw the movie
The Day of the Triffids?
I did.
I did teach her.
Who didn't see the movie?
I saw it a whole bunch of times,
teacher.
I saw it recently.
I saw it when I was a kid,
but remember,
I read the book.
it starts with a gorgeous
meteor shower
that everybody watches
and they say,
ooh and ah.
Everybody in the world
watches it.
Except one guy
who's got bandages
on his eyes
because he's in the hospital.
The next day,
everybody in the world
except that one guy
is blind.
No.
Because those meteors
that everyone was looking at
burned out their eyeballs.
Don't be scared.
Nobody else in the world
had a blind eye.
There's a whole crew
in a submarine.
There are people in mines.
There are people
in train cars.
They all get there
of course.
What's going on down there
at that station anyway?
We're trying to figure out
when to go to Gary's house.
We're having a party.
Culler,
can you suggest
when to go to Gary's house?
We're thinking Sunday night.
No,
come to my house.
Come to my house.
Okay, Culler,
that's what I'm saying.
We're all going
to little Big Bear's house.
We're going to go
to Gary's house
and then Baby Bear's house.
Because Baby Bear
is hiding the cop gun gun.
Baby Bear's hiding
the cop gun gun.
where is your house?
Well,
my house is at the corner
from the auction.
Not yours.
Not yours,
Baby Bear.
What was that?
Not yours, Gary.
Not yours, I was asking
Baby Bear.
Yeah, not yours, Gary.
Not yours, Gary.
I'm really getting tired
of this year after year.
This is not
your Gary business.
Not Baby Gary.
It's little Baby Gary.
I want to believe
I'm important, you know?
Well,
then you have to buy the band.
Oh, God.
You know, again.
All over again, yeah.
I thought he owned the band.
He did,
he had the best deal.
So how do I get
this surfboard
out of my butt
and why?
That's what I want to know.
It feels good there.
You need to weaponize
your surfboard.
Install some
automatic weapons.
Yeah, and also,
I thought that's
the name of the band.
Surfboard up my butt?
Something about
butthole...
I was always afraid
to say the name
of that band.
It's called
the Butthole Smurfs
or something like that.
Yeah, something like that.
Yeah.
Yeah, well, you know,
that's the thing.
It turns everything blue.
Stick a pencil
in your ear.
Oh, that's a different
album cover.
Never stick anything
smaller than your elbow
in your ear.
Wasn't that an album cover?
Yeah, it was.
It was.
It was a giant billboard
in Los Angeles, copyright
Paul McCready.
Oh, yeah.
Yes, it was.
And then after they
take down the billboard,
they give you the giant
piece of paper
that it's printed on.
You have to take care of it.
Oh, gosh, I would have...
But you'll never have
to buy toilet paper again.
Well, so I guess
we should all come down
and troop through
your museum wing.
The museum's wing.
Curiosities,
anomalies,
and oddities.
I was hoping...
Of weird protests
of nature and sports.
Grotesques in the grottos.
I was hoping all my
rich subgenius friends
would buy paintings
and then donate them
to the museum
like 30 seconds later
because they hate them.
Museum of pathetic mutations.
You were hoping, right?
Hoping against hope.
That's grotesque
monstrosities of...
Holding off
on destroying the art?
Well, he doesn't
destroy the art anymore
because now it goes
into the giant
Gary Hughes wing.
That's right.
Is it because
he can't collect
on the art?
No, sure.
Seriously,
there's a
Ghebregfran art wing
of the Santa Cruz
Museum.
Insects,
too late now.
Yeah, but it's
the broken wing.
Snakes,
moles,
birds.
It's limping around.
But now,
I presume it's
the left wing, right?
Name and piece.
It's the left wing.
And his enameled,
jeweled snuff box.
Your Philo's art
is in the other wing.
Philo's art is
in the other wing.
It's in the right wing
of the Peoria Museum.
I refuse to be
on any wing.
I'm not a winger.
I'm a wingless man.
I don't have no wings.
Wingless man.
He's a flightless
bird of a man.
I do.
Now, just sit down
in the chair.
An emu of a man.
We'll have those wings
off in no time.
I've performed this
operation a hundred times.
There's nothing to fear.
Why do I want them all?
Why?
I got a email
yesterday from Sterno.
Wow.
Why?
And he said none
of you guys ever call him
or write him anymore.
He told me that he
only comes to me.
I tried to write him.
I said that about him
the other day.
He never calls
or writes or comes by anymore.
Okay.
Doesn't everyone
email?
We're all reactionaries.
We react.
I think I smell a scum.
Let's all just
letter bombs Sterno.
And by letter bomb
I don't mean like...
What a letter bomb?
He's not on the internet.
What letter bomb
do you mean by text bomb?
He only communicates
by text, he told me.
You know, I knew
a Jewish doctor
who was a terrible
letter bomber
when he was a kid.
Yeah, he only does
sex speech.
He sexts and texts.
Right.
Letter bomber?
Yeah.
Is that the person?
Hey, hey, is this
where I'm supposed
to say something
about Frank Zappa?
Sucks.
I'm gonna send some...
There you go.
Oh, I feel so liberated.
I'm gonna sext a message
to Sterno right now.
You've really caused
the Christmas tree
to light up like a board
with your last remark.
Oh, I know.
I do that on purpose.
It's just to drag out
the Zappa cultists.
It's a drag out,
knock down Zappa
I'm gonna take a picture
of something sexy.
All right, throw it
in the towel over it.
Yeah.
Um, let's, uh...
He was gonna visit
everybody in Santa Fe.
...growing roses
in sedate floral gardens
where perfumes wafted
upon summery daisies
are idly fanned
by the wings of huge
hovering butterflies
and lunar moths.
Hmm, deep fried wings
of huge hovering butterflies.
Don't you guys get
better stock footage
to go with that narration?
...of hanging grapes,
We have one of those
butterfly wings
that are like
a allegations.
I am очie...
That's a native
Man with wings...
That's a monster
that's make the most
sound in the thành
õ...
...crie...
This is a true anecdote.
My father's dog ate my father's teeth.
My father had, Pappy, had all false teeth.
And he left them out.
And the dog just loved the taste of his master's slobber.
So he chewed on those dentures.
Hence, I can say the dog ate Pappy's teeth.
That'll teach your dad to slobber on his dentures.
Yeah, right.
How disquietingly distasteful.
If he'd brush once in a while, he wouldn't have those problems.
Yeah, he could scare the hell out of little kids by popping those things out.
Don't slobber on your dentures.
I used to be that little kid.
An indentured servant.
No, please, no.
When I grow up and get some dentures, I'm not going to slobber all over them.
Brave words now, Philo.
Let's see if when it gets right down to the rough and tumble, you're able not to eat them.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, well, I turned down some the other night.
Somebody offered me a plate of dentures and, you know, like...
Turn down the top sheet and put a mint on the pillow.
Was it a variety?
Pull down the top sheet and pull the hell you're in, Hal.
You're going to sink the boat if you...
Hal sunk the boat.
I did not.
I piloted her truly to where she should have been.
Hal sunk the boat and Bob screwed the pooch.
Ever last time.
It's the same...
As ever.
It's the same, you know.
You flew the coop when you...
After you sunk the boat.
I know that.
Sink the boat.
That's how you realize that you now have several million...
He hit the...
Because the pilot...
He sunk the boat, hit the road, and flew the coop.
All at the same time.
Fans are fans.
Yes.
I'm sure you can...
I think Baby Bear did the same thing.
First of all, I'm sure it's...
I'm sure it's...
An uphill battle against...
The sound effects now.
And now...
I can't breathe.
If only we could hear you...
So it's just all there?
Must reach volume switch.
Yeah, it's just guys talking real loud about how they can't hear anything.
I can't hear a thing.
Well, I can hear it all.
Of course you can.
Every last word.
They just can't hear it.
That's what I've been waiting for is the last word.
Now, where is it?
Around like two in the morning.
I think you're sitting on it.
It was at 420.
Oh, the princess is there too.
Yeah.
Everyone's there.
Where's Michael Pepe?
Right here.
Is this the one about the lady that was at the side of the road?
Yeah.
There is no princess.
It is not.
Right.
Can you hurry this up?
It's the same old story that lots of people tell.
She's a magical person.
In Navajo country, it's a guy's uncle.
In the Appalachians, it's their aunt.
The wailing woman.
In Slovakia, it's a grandmother.
La Iona.
Is she a grandmother?
No, it's not Slovakia.
She was old and she was giant and she was in the pitch black with a staff and it was 2.25 in the morning in the mountain.
You don't want to mess around with her.
No, ma'am.
No, you don't.
I know.
Was she there when you came back?
She was walking.
She's there now.
She's still there because you didn't give her a ride.
Don't.
Don't give her a ride.
Don't feed the ghost women.
You might make the offer just to be polite.
Hey, do you guys have any kept women down there I can use?
You know, what they do is they want to drink some blood.
Ghosts always want that.
If you put out a bowl of blood for them, they'll be very happy.
You know, after a couple of days, it becomes a gap.
I think she's a vampire.
You can see the level of the blood go down when they drink it.
Well, it's just a courtesy to them.
They want to.
You should sip off the bottom of the bowl.
The blood doesn't get as.
Why do you think she's a vampire?
What do you mean?
They want what they can never have.
Well, and it takes all day for the ghost to drink the.
I don't know.
I just sounded good at the minute.
Sometimes you can see the level dropping down rather swiftly.
Oh, really?
It's really easy.
If you centrifuge the blood before you drink it, then you can have the antibodies one by
one, and then all the blood solids, and then at the last, you can just top it off with
a big drink of plastic.
And then you can have asthma.
By Jove, that's the key.
Much better that way.
I think we should do an experiment.
Which is current cancer.
The red cells of courage.
The red cells of green courage.
That's right.
They may be red as it were said.
All aboard the razor train.
But their money is green.
With this razor.
So I'm going to be in San Francisco for an hour tomorrow.
Slice away error.
Oh, you are.
Are you?
An hour?
What time?
I'm coming up to sell my car.
Sell your car?
Well, how are you planning to get a better job?
I'm going to drive out with a new car.
Well, I'm still on my truck.
A truck, eh?
You can drive one with each hand.
There's plenty of room.
There's plenty of room in it, pal.
We'll take you to Arkansas in the back.
Oh, okay.
We'll strap you down.
We'll give you a couple shots of Nemutol and...
The Arkenstone of Thrain.
Dr. Gubrog, friend, is this the car that you scared me to death in last year?
Whoa.
The hot rod sports car?
Yeah, it's being sold tomorrow.
It's a gold...
Oh, thank God.
...car.
You know, it's just filled up with ghouls and I can't get them out now, so I've got
a...
I've got a...
And plates of blood spilled all over...
Igor, you fool.
Be a little more cool.
I brought my mummy with me.
I love this guy.
Oh.
Gary took me for a ride in the hills in that...
He took him for a ride.
...fancy car of his and...
I gave him a concrete...
...heal my soul...
Well, that's one of the problems.
I was never able to get rid of the smell after that.
I think that you're not supposed to be scared.
I'm not supposed to.
We're on the way.
Oh, the smell of it goes on.
Well, we design and create and manufacture an outrageous line of products to handle
problems just like this.
All out of the oil of the common polecat or skunk.
We call it piggy on the potty.
It's great stuff.
Our pot on the piggy on the...
Is it true that somebody, some visitors might be on our planet as soon as Sunday?
Well, it might be.
It would be Sunday night if I think.
Sunday night.
We're the sleeping air.
Bob has not told us what to do fully yet.
We're awaiting his instructions.
Would you have a place on your floor for a stang to lie?
Well, we have a...
...weary head.
Yeah, we do.
We do.
There would not be a Princess Wee with me, unfortunately.
She's helping the Queen Mum of...
The Queen Bee Mother is again filled with honey to the brim and has a lot of...
...she has to be bled again with...
She's laying eggs again.
...meeting bubbles.
She's...
...beating bubbles.
Her pulsating abdomen is...
...winking at the brim.
...is heaving out those...
...and purple stangers...
And we're thinking about driving to the Pinnacles.
We'll be in the camper and then coming to your place that evening.
Home of the giant California cumber.
...that spreads its wings and blackens the sky.
We're hoping puzzling evidence would be with us as well.
Okay, well, we have enough floor for you.
Under the unrushing wings of darkness...
...we're hoping puzzling evidence would be with us as well.
And we have a comforter for you, too.
A monstrous crow.
It's a monstrous comforter.
She's a little furry, but she's warm.
Oh, look at that.
And you can stretch her out over...
How cute.
Oh, my.
Well, all right, I...
Very crazy.
We were thinking about going to Pinnacles National Monument, which last two days ago
became Pinnacles National Park.
Just listen to Pinnacle Pete over there.
What's funny is they...
It was like front-page news.
There was a beautiful photograph of the pinnacle-shaped phallic rocks.
I'm telling you, there's a...
And I swear to God, there were people on Yahoo!
Comments going, see, they're programming our mind.
They could have shown any photograph of rocks, and instead they showed that one.
That, you know, implying that...
The pinnacles.
Now, as far as I know, everywhere you look at pinnacles, you see rocks that look
like, well, pebbles.
They're swinging federal...
Well, you do.
And you also...
You also see the giant condors living there in the trees.
Right, and you do a butt.
Some of us also see the rocks that look like butts or bosoms or faces.
Rocks that look like butts, and there's also a cave full of giant spiders that you
have to go through.
But these paranoids...
Oh, yeah, yeah, that's the whole idea.
The path leads through there, and after that, it gets even harder.
It's one of the toughest paths ever.
Oh, great.
I nearly died on it.
What are you talking about?
Yeah, the path at the pinnacle that goes up over the saddle.
Which trail did you take?
The one that goes over the saddle of the mountains.
There are six trails.
Well, the one that goes through the cave of the outsized arachnids.
Oh, yeah.
You counted them?
Yeah, that's a strenuous trail.
I never had trouble on that trail.
Oh, it's...
I almost did.
I'm just exaggerating.
I did fine.
I did just fine.
Well, anyway, the point is the conspiracy built those rocks to look like phallic symbols
because they're messing with our mind.
That was the point of the Yahoo comment.
I thought they were just doing it to get comments.
They're just doing it to get comments on YouTube or something.
Well, they got it mentioned on the show.
Learn how to use the internet or get off.
I don't speak their lingo.
I don't know why you want to follow a series into a sick place so they can be in peace.
I'd kill that caller, would you?
I don't think it's that I'm deaf.
I think it's that cell phones are getting worse.
I'm far off, I'm lost.
I'm sorry.
I got nuts.
I don't think that's it.
You guys make me want to cry and remember the people that I once was.
Why hidest thou thyself in time of trouble?
Yeah, they're trying hard to be on show.
Be with show.
Be in show.
The wicked in his pride doth persecute the poor.
Let them be taken in the devices which they have imagined.
All those other mattress guys, are they not there tonight?
Mattress?
Pookie and the mattress folks aren't here.
The Plecto mattress company?
Mookie and the mattress people are...
I think they're playing down at Bob's Pub or somewhere.
The wicked through the pride of his countenance will not seek after God.
Oh, Mookie and the mattress backs, though.
They're down there at the other place.
God is not at all in his thoughts.
His ways are always grievous.
His judgments are far above and out in the sun.
Dookie and the dumpster divers.
As for all his enemies, he puffeth at them.
You puff.
Puff.
Bob is the box.
Bob is the box you have to think outside of.
He hath said in his heart.
Huh?
I shall not be moved, for I shall never be in adversity.
His mouth is full of cursing and deceit and fraud.
You guys can't be cursing on that nice, pretty radio show of y'all.
Under his tongue lieth deceit and vanity.
We don't say the seven deadly words of Christ, but we say the rest of them freely and openly.
Like poo-poo, you say that.
We say poo-poo.
You say left nut.
You ever say that?
Yeah.
It depends on the context, Dr. Gibbard-Fran.
We say arse town from time to time.
Oh, wow.
It's more context than the word itself.
Yeah, well, I don't have to use context anymore since I went through menopause.
He sitteth in the lurking places of the villages.
In the secret places doth he murder the innocent.
Those are pretty castanets, too.
Do you know of any medication that helps with the woes of menopause?
Well, you know...
Because I think I'm starting to catch that.
He's a man who's being put on pause.
That's right.
That's why they make Cialis, Reverend Stang.
Just go see Alice.
She'll treat you fine.
Menopause.
Hand effect.
Gland effect.
That's it.
Transplant usually is the best thing.
Total body transplant.
And try a steel wool rubdown at S&M-Olin Recreational Park.
And not to mention a good power buffing helps.
True.
You can't be too buff here in California.
No.
Be a buffster like everybody else and you'll prosper and flourish.
Also, we recommend a full exfoliating scrub genius.
Well, around here we just peel ourselves.
We don't peel our skins off like the little reptiles.
We don't have eczema or pandouty or any of those other diseases.
Because we're just able to cut our entire skin at once.
We whip our skin back.
We clip the claws on our menopause.
Yeah.
Yeah, what he said.
Now, I'm going to stop the show until I sell just one.
I'm going to sell just one of these magnificent watches.
Everyone ought to have a watch like this.
It's one that will probably make that girl.
You've got your eyes on.
Sit up and take notice of you.
And she'll say, say, what a handsome watch that young buck is.
I never noticed how cute you were.
He must be a good provider.
He has a handsome watch.
Now, I'm going to tell you, you can expect to pay at least $12 for a fine watch like this with a nickel steel casing.
But you don't even have to pay $12.
You don't have to pay $11.
You can pay $5 and $12.
You can pay $37.8.
Now, wait a minute. Where are you getting that?
That's kind of wild.
We're making an incredible offer with these fabulous steel watches.
We're cutting out the middle man.
We're cutting out the top man, the under man, the low man on the totem pole.
We're going straight to the manufacturer.
This has a high tensile mainspring of Toledo steel.
We're even going to cut out the manufacturer to get this price down to nothing for you.
But who watches the watch salesman?
Robin numerals that roam all over the dial.
This watch is so tiny you can't even see it on your arm.
It's so lightweight. It won't cause any stress.
It's crystal starts fires and tortures grasshoppers.
And it's stately, saintly case clicks firmly in place.
But do you have an under-putting watch that works down to 300 feet of footing?
Yeah, this special compartment holds, well, your medicine.
It's a very well-known watch.
It's so dark down there the light on the watch has to be really bright to even see it.
No problem. Built-in LED light shows the way.
So when you get to the bottom of the pudding, you can still see at least one nano-inch in front of you.
Clockwork mechanism plays Annie Laurie as ringtone.
Annie Laurie or just a specific one?
Annie Laurie, the song Annie Laurie.
Oh, yes.
Some people were raised in a barnyard.
You guys ought to be on the home shopping channel.
Only 27 shopping days till Axe Max.
Oh, no.
But how many... What day is Cuthbert?
Counting down the calendar to St. Swithin's Day.
And at the end of St. Cuthbert's Festival, all readily available mails will be in bowels.
I always loved St. Cuthbert.
St. Cuthbert was a fine saint.
You know, one weird thing about him was his body never corrupted.
Centuries after centuries, they kept opening his coffin just to give him a haircut and a nail clipping.
Really?
Yes, and finally...
It didn't do any good, though.
Well, finally, the last time they opened it, he was looking kind of mummified and skeletal.
And now he's just a skeleton surrounded by holy relics.
If they hadn't been opening his grave up and opening the closed...
Open and close, open and close...
He's probably saying, keep that damn door shut!
These holy relics include fragments of the true cross, water from the fountain of Gethsemane, and a small Japanese transistor radio.
You kids must have been raised in a bar!
I told you kids not to bother me when I'm broadcasting!
A small Japanese transistor radio...
Don't you know what rest in peace means?
That's no kitty cat, that's a skunk! It's a skunk!
I've been growing that hair for a long time now!
January and February are the times of year when most dogs, cats, people, and sometimes even passing cars get sprayed by old rare skunk.
Don't you be trimming my nails if you used to grow that little one out just so I could pick my nose!
Your average skunk can shoot an oily mixture out of two specialized glands in their anuses...
Ah!
...and cause severe pinpoint accuracy from ten feet away!
Get that pin out of there!
My mouth is watering!
This pale yellow fluid can cause temporary blindness and severe nasal and mucous membrane inflammation.
Why, that's so tight you couldn't drive a pin up there with a ball-peen hammer!
The hideous combination smell of this santorum of garlic, rotten egg, and burned rubber is so powerful that it can ward off bears...
Don't forget the burning flash.
...and be detected at least a mile away.
You can wash it off with X-T-D flush.
Yes, the reeking stench is nearly impossible to get off and can linger for months. That's why we recommend...
You just can't wash them out.
Yes.
And how come it isn't the best pot smells exactly like what you're describing?
It's one of the mysteries.
Here is Jehovah One in his senility...
That's not a coincidence!
Jehovah One in his senility got a few bio details mixed up in his...
...and wires crossed as so often it does.
So where are we having breakfast this morning?
At Dream Fluff Girl Donuts.
Donut-uh-uh-teria.
Godfud, you mean?
The only successful skunk predator is...
We go to Dream Fluff Girl.
...the great horned owl...
You know, I just thought we could break into my old house in Oakland and we could go to breakfast there.
...which flies silently down, expanding its huge wings...
...and it sticks its talons right into the struggling, squealing skunk...
...and flaps off into the night sky with its odorous prey.
A great horned owl has no sense of smell...
...and it can swoop silently undetected from above.
It's easy for its giant eyes to spot the tell-tale stripes of a skunk...
...pumping along bent on mischief.
Gary, it's 75 miles from your house after we leave the pinnacles.
After you leave the pinnacles, it's only 75 miles?
Well, that's if we go...
We need to go up to the 101 side entrance.
Why? Oh, okay.
Because it would be quicker to come back to Gary's.
Don't we get to use the secret underground tunnel?
Yeah, I'm going to use the secret Gloria Road, but you're right.
What about the submarine?
It's Purdy. Either one's Purdy. But I go up Gloria Road because...
If you are confronted by a skunk, remember the seven safety signals to disarm when skunk attacks.
I'm not sure if the motorhome... I mean, it's a one-lane old silly road.
...striped skunks lift their tails and stamp their feet before turning around, lifting their tails, and letting fly.
It's not one of the two parking lots. It's a different entrance than one of the...
No, it comes out onto...
Spotted skunks not found in this bioregion actually stand on their hands to squirt you.
They stand on their hands to squirt you?
Now that is cool.
Oh, yeah, okay. I know what you're talking about.
That's the first interesting thing I've heard on this show.
But we're not going to go in on the east side where you come down out of Hollister.
Well, those are the skunks in your vicinity, Reverend Stang.
Where you come down out of Hollister.
In California, they don't do that.
Oh, yeah, yeah. There you're right.
But where you live, right next to that giant gorilla statue in your front yard, they will stand on their hands and do their business.
Yes, quick movements are never a good idea around the easily irritated animals who startle easily.
Yes, if you see skunks, you just let them know you're there.
You make some noise and just sort of stand up for yourself.
And they generally run away.
You can't blame them for spraying every now and then.
It's part of their defense mechanism.
Surely you wouldn't deny them this one simple pleasure.
It wouldn't be so cold and inhuman as to force Br'er Skunk never more to release his effuvium upon the lambent breezes.
Dr. Howell, I've heard a theory.
I've heard the theory advanced that our animals are not as good as they used to be.
Our ancestors, the Primo Anthropocus, despite being weak and without claws or sharp teeth, smelled so bad that carnivores avoided them.
They did because they were without the ability to groom themselves.
And they didn't bathe.
Evolutionary oversight.
But we, in our days of microchips and microchips, we were able to do it.
And moon rockets have evolved many caustic soaps which will scrub the sin from the quivering flesh.
But a skunk meat chimichanga is better than almost anything, wouldn't you say, Doctor?
Well, as long as it's been deodorized, the skunk flesh is savory.
And the Skunkawatomi Indians used to make it part of the staple of their diet.
You gonna make that skunk dinner, Benny?
Covered with cheese and skunkalotta sauce.
Mmm.
Bring that fresh skunk in there. It tastes pretty good after you de-stinkify him.
Skunks have good hearing and a good sense of smell, but terrible eyesight.
Which is why they can't read newspaper articles and may get hit by cars more frequently.
The skunks and the ducks have a very similar family ethic, which makes me love both of them.
The male walks proudly in front, followed by the female and the little skunk.
Well, skunks are not related closely to ducks.
Skunks, which are sometimes called stink badgers or polecats, are members of the mephitidae family.
A unique group of m-m-m-m-mammals.
Where we go, they're called civicae.
They're similar to, but genetically different from, ferrets, weasels, otters, badgers, wolverines, and African bull elephants.
Skunks in France are known... male skunks in France often mistake commonest animals for male.
They're called house cats for female skunks.
They are called les peuves.
Yes, if they happen to walk under a ladder with white paint on it or something.
A common misfortune to house cats in France.
Causing the amorous skunk to fixate upon the feline victim.
And not to mention the horrid French stinky cat.
Oh, worst of all.
So you see...
They don't, those cats don't shave their arms, it's more anything.
They are slinky and most appealing.
Philo's brother had a one-eyed cat that loved to have you insert your pinky into its furry little eye socket and rub it back and forth.
Oh, how that cat would purr.
I once saw a gotch-eyed cat in a green grocer's window in Idaho.
That cat was the fightingest cat there ever was.
And what happened eventually, he got in another fight and lost his other eye.
No way!
Walked into a blind tank and fell in.
He eventually became a totally blind cat, wandering around the house by sense of smell and hearing and habit.
I told the barkeep I hadn't had a bite in weeks, so he bit me.
But no kidding.
It didn't seem to bother him that much.
He just used his other senses and just managed to get around.
And at these prices, you're not likely to. No, but seriously.
That was an orange tabby named Slick.
Slick?
Slick.
Yeah, my friends had a blind horse that...
He had a younger female horse that led him around.
It was a little nursemaid. It was pretty scary.
I could do somebody that had a goat, had a horse that had a friend that was a goat.
An old horse and a goat were like best friends in the pasture.
Don't pay any attention to that old goat.
Out on Stang Ranch, we had a goat that thought he was a cow and would follow the cattle around.
What a moo-ving story.
Yep.
It was...
I love the female address they have.
Pus Ev.
You love the female what?
The Pus Ev they have.
Have you seen on KPFA it says, Pus Ev?
Pus Ev.
Oh, come on now.
It's the wrong email address.
Are you sure?
Pussy Ev.
I'm looking at it right now.
The email that showed that they have on the KPFA page is the wrong address for Pussy Ev.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
Unless you have Pus Ev.
Are you sure?
The Pussy Evidence Show brought to you by Walsporn.
These young people get so confused by the internet, but it's okay.
It'll take a generation to kind of settle into how this works.
The Pus Ev Show.
That was my favorite story when I was a child.
Hey, young man.
Who is it?
Yeah.
Hey, is this show going to be over soon?
I'm getting really tired.
Yeah, it's almost over.
It's almost over, and we can get a donut when it's over.
Yeah, we are rewarded with sugar and dough and grease when it's over, and vitamin salt
and vitamin...
I want scrambled egg soup or de-booper de-booper.
Yeah, vitamin grease.
Vitamin grease is the best.
Vitamin G.
I want a bagel waffle.
Vitamin S.
Vitamin G.
Vitamin S is salt.
I'll give you some vitamin G right now.
Sugar and grease.
Vitamin G.
Yeah, grease.
Or garlic.
I've got a sack full of vitamin G. Let me squeeze it out for you.
It's got vitamin A and vitamin B.
Vitamin D stands for vitamin Dough.
Vitamin Dough.
Vitamin J is jalapeno.
It's the only vitamin that's really high in protein.
If you're fat, it's for that.
It's within packaging.
Well, I know you're going to have to package to show up and get rid of all those clowns
you've got and Bishop Joey and Freedies and...
Bishop Joey is just sleeping like a little baby right now.
Aww.
For some reason, Freedies are sleeping.
Freedies never accepts a ride or...
No, he doesn't like shows.
He doesn't like...
He thinks shows are stinky.
He thinks all calls.
He thinks shows are bad.
He thinks that the people that do the show is bad.
Well, it's really fun once a year for 10 minutes.
I think it's the greatest fun once a year for 10 minutes.
People who do the show is bad.
People that come down here every week are nuts.
They're just completely bad.
I don't think there's anybody down there.
That's stupid.
We'll get up at 3 a.m.
Now, boy.
This is the tape they make at 10 o'clock in the morning.
Exactly.
Well, they're drinking coffee and looking out over the ocean.
And laughing and laughing.
And there are huge picture windows.
Wow.
And they just laugh and laugh and say...
They're going to be so cool.
Who's going to listen to this?
They're even going to think the callers are real.
So, you know about the other park they're going to build down there with all the tapered
holes in the ground, the Punicles?
Yeah.
Oh, no.
Well, they're going to think that Lonnie is real and Sarah is real and Suicide Man is
real and Michael Pepe is real.
I'll just act like I'm really down at the station at 4 a.m., 5 a.m.
You sit in the lurking places.
Yeah.
That I really woke up in the middle of the night.
Vitamin H. Hey, man.
What about Vitamin H?
Vitamin H. What about Vitamin H?
Did you take enough today?
No.
Did you have 120% of your rural requirement?
I don't know.
That's why I said I'd talk to somebody about that.
Okay.
Well, this whole show is set up just to talk to you.
If it's Vitamin B12, it's good.
If you have any questions, we'll be happy to answer them.
If you have answers, we will definitely question them.
Okay.
And you've only got like five minutes, caller.
But only in the order in which they've been received.
It's important.
You'd better get yourself up in a hurry because your time is running out.
Calling number 43, caller.
I'll ask this question.
Where can I find Habifrop's Ritulox?
That's Vitamin H.
We've got plenty right here.
Right here.
But unfortunately, it only grows upon the droppings of certain Tibetan holy men.
You have to go to...
I can tell you this.
Like the Marifosa Luminesa.
You must go to Radio Valencia tonight at the Ask Dr. Howell show and I'm sure you'll find
plenty there.
Well, yes, but...
Oh, I see.
Yes, but...
That's what kind of deal it is.
If you bring plenty there, you will find plenty there.
For he who brings plenty receiveth plenty.
Will I receive the mission, the preaching of Ivan Stang as well?
That is so.
And seed bearing flowers and fruits of every kind.
But not all of them.
And they're all going to go to the whole plant.
That sounds like my kind of place.
The tiny Tom tit-wren shall circle and sing in the bosky bowers of the golden bough.
The tiny tit-wren.
The Tom tit-wren, yes.
While the chaffing sings of the orchard bough.
Are they as tufted as the tiny...
Are they as tiny as the tufted tit-mouse?
Well, I...
They're tiny.
They're...
You know, they're not that tall.
You have a tiny tit-wren and a tiny tit-mouse together.
They're tiny.
Which one has the tiniest tits?
They're tiny finches.
They're fluttering little finches.
This is not doing a thing for us.
That's all.
Oh, yeah?
Their tiny hearts beat pitter-pat.
The part where the show goes away?
Go away.
The tiny tit-mouse and the tiny tufted tit-mouse.
Out of my weakness and my melancholy.
And the tiny tits to the show is when you built a tit-wren.
You see the show's butt going through the door away from you.
The butt, butt, butt.
Exits at high speed.
Man is born to be a tit-wren.
You let the show slam on your butt as you leave.
You let the smoke fly upward.
Yeah, you.
What were you born in a barn?
What were you born in the show?
Forever.
Yeah, you're born in a show and you left a barn door open to the show.
All the animals got out.
All the animals had to leave because the show got too hot for them.
You know how it is on the show.
You can't touch the show when it's that hot.
It's like a smoking the end of a recently discharged pistol.
Don't give up, folks.
We'll get this over with.
We're going to do it right one of these days.
Keep listening.
All these errors will get straightened out.
Yeah, yeah.
We're just practicing.
If you shoot the show's bullets for the next edition.
We're going to do it right eventually.
You shoot the show's bullets, all the show's bullets at the same time the show's pistol
barrel gets really hot.
You'll be there.
We'll be sweating bullets.
You can burn yourself on the show's barrel.
Don't grab the show like that.
Our eyeballs will be dripping blood with the effort.
Hey, by the way, the big question is what's on your radio?
What's on your playlist?
If you don't bring the show, then reach around, give you a look at the show.
Show us what you're listening to right now.
If you're going to reach around, you need the show can do that.
Well, it's been great to have Ivan Stang.
Yes, and congratulations to each and every one of you.
Dr. Howell and Philo the Oberman all here on the Buzz and Evan Show.
Subgenius.com.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's right.
Subgenius.com.
Goodbye.
Bye.
Where do you want to go?
What do you want to know?
What's on your radio?
Radio.
Take the stage, put the fans on the stage.
Radio, radio.
What's on the radio?
Thank you.
What's on your radio?
Radio
Thank you, the Puzzling Evidence Show of February 15, 2013, Part 2.
And Doug and Philo and Hal and Gary and Lil and Baby Bear and Michael Pepe and other caller.
2 and 3.
That show was duplicated to form this hour of slack number 1,404.
Except for the following by the Psychoskeletons.
Psychoskeletons.
Jump and laugh for a while, yeah, yeah
We live on clouds up in the air
With hearts and rainbows everywhere
So clap your hands and sing along
To the Care Bears song
Share one, two, three
Care a lot's the place to be
We are the Care Bears
La, la, la, la, la
Show your love, hug someone
Caring fills the world with so much fun
And fun, and we are the Care Bears
We are the Care Bears
La, la, la, la, la
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la
You've been listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
For free information, write to P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
Or call 1-877-44118
Or see www.subgenius.com
Praise Bob!