From PR News in Washington, I'm committed to laying down PR News.
President Bush is wrong.
I disagree.
The president said he's cracked down on dissidents.
The president also said he's violent if they contact PR News.
The U.N. Refugee Agency warns of PR outbreaks in Pennsylvania.
The U.N. says former unsanitary president Bill Clinton is reading PR News in Washington.
Oh, please stop.
This is genius.
Oh, sick.
Mom.
Yeah.
Ladies and gentlemen, we take pride in presenting a thoughtful address by...
Adequated.
Badass.
Giant.
Wizards.
And dwarves.
And we're all on a diet.
They're ignorant.
Fanatics.
Fools.
A giant, a wizard, or a dwarf.
Hello, boys and girls.
Overthrow the government and seize all private property.
Now.
Birth of a nation treacherous and filled with obstacles.
Rebell now.
Now.
Now is the time.
The new world begins.
Hello, boys and girls.
Overthrow the government.
Alien force invade.
Infest in government.
Call on the gym.
Bob.
Yes.
Bob.com.
He has now been f-indicted, indicted, indicted, indicted, binning, binning, binning, binning,
blunderings, Bob.
He faces Bob Tom DeLay.
Hurt, hurt, hurt, hurt himself.
Finger.
Pain.
Release.
Irregularity.
Blunderings.
Bob.
Move on.
Blunderings.
Crazy.
S-s-s-s-move on.
Violate.
That's insane.
Time.
Why not let Fidel Castro dream?
Gone in less than 30 minutes.
nutty funneling $10,000 why don't you give it to the Nazi corporate donations
it's ridiculous Bob yep yep to help support a child's healthy breast milk
good hello and facilitations I'm Izzy isn't your wacky
host for the how radio isn't done series on what used to be this program over the edge
however tonight we either suspend the how radio isn't done series or we end up incorporating
this program anomaly the one you are about to hear if you don't turn away to make this
how radio isn't done part 10 that's up to you here at UMN's KPFA outlet UMN's only outlet
you're listening to the how radio isn't done podcast and I'm Izzy and I'll see you next time.
you the listener will decide according to your own personal community standards
whether this concept makes any sense on the other hand it has already made a great deal of sense
c-e-n-t-s no show in the history of radio has ever been detected attracting a longer
listener attention span than last year's or was it oh two anyway the past mergings of over
the edge and the subgenius puzzling evidence show into five hours spectacular radio fillers have
proven to be with specific reservations among the highest audience ratings traps since gun smoke in
all of radio history therefore and with special reservations over the edge once again merges with
puzzling evidence and the whole subgenius directors of the board for this five-hour holiday earthcast
of the subgenius show
the subgenius executive banquet
live from the palm palms in the middle regions of the new world sector center downtown berkeley california with special reservations we are broadcasting the subgenius executive boards thanksgiving banquet as a public service designed to enhance your perception of their reality just a moment while I put the cd player on continuous
is
that's better
we published and
you can the
hospital
team
here
up
that's easy that of yours truly izzy isn't the banquet facilitator a psychological deflective
diversion which i spent six years training for so that now as a professional banquet facilitator
i am able to ease the way across any direction the twisted tables of such a confoundingly
contentious sit-down organization such as the subgenius church foundation of america
may take whenever they gather for this annual thanksgiving business like banquet
and right off the bat like a left field vampire let's go down now to the main banquet pit from my
broadcast booth high above them down to what this five-hour show is really all about
i see uh dr howe over by the asparagus cooler professor of esoteria at estonian u eating up a
storm
and now reverend ivan staying as risen to his feet from the head table of potheads about to attempt a
banquet opening remark
let's listen in as one of the disputed founders of the church of the subgenius addresses his near
equal fellow executives in the worldwide subgenius semi organized cult
let's talk a little bit about ivan and again right smack dab in the center and very very healthy looking
again you can see very symmetric good outflow here
center of circulation very evident i've been pummel grenade a
flattening homes in cutting power at least fifteen desks are being blamed on
ivan we need you to watch it all along with us
right now i've in its head and forge and make up and then cuba with the latest
details i got your gel
vial leveraging g invented a monster sized everywhere than more banć
we have a new concern
with us Paper Man
online streaming app umm printing app an alarm device props dvmрах online traffic lights mayors on
By then, Carl will be watching Ivan.
But here's a closer view of Ivan.
And you can see that right here, and you notice it is in the middle of the central dent.
That's an indication that this is a very, very organized Ivan.
And they know that our one-world religion is the only antidote for the one-world advertiser.
Ivan, here is Ivan right now.
Down with the quote-less Bob, and up with Bob, and up with Bob.
We'll be watching Ivan.
We know we're here, and we'll keep you posted every day on the progress of Ivan.
Ivan struck the Windward Islands with deadly force yesterday.
Ivan tore off roofs, knocked trees into power lines, and blew down streetlights.
At this point in time, is it more likely than not that Ivan will affect the U.S.?
Actually, what time is it?
But at that point...
Oh, yeah.
That time is...
It's pledge time.
Oh, that's Doug Wellman.
It's a tape.
It is a tape.
But now, consider another fact.
I mean, the mob worked as assassin mechanics.
That's what they're called for the CIA.
Under the CIA's William Harvey, who hated Kennedy.
And while they had a motive, they had, of course, no means to cover up the crime.
Unlike Alan Dulles and the CIA.
And, of course...
And, of course, Hoover and his FBI.
And, you know, by the way, George DeMoren Shield once dated Jackie's mother.
He could have been her stepfather.
And Ruth Payne were both handlers of Oswald with their obvious right...
Well, not so obvious, perhaps, but with right-wing intelligence connections.
Oswald himself, of course, was an intelligence informant
who we had sent to Russia as a double agent.
And, you know, after we trained him in the Russian language,
which came out in the Warren Commission hearings.
Yes, let me tell you something, man.
The CIA tried to kill me, like, must have been 11 team minutes ago.
You know what I'm saying?
But I'll tell you what, the CIA did nothing.
I'm coming for the CIA and I'm coming for Bob Dobbs.
You heard it first.
News at 11.
And I think the best assessment of the JFK hit was probably that presented by...
Oliver Stone in this movie, JFK, was the former chief of staff for Special Operations,
Colonel L. Fletcher Prouty's input.
He was, of course, Mr. X in that movie.
That was his view.
And Ruth Patterson's North Carolina macaroni and cheese.
I gotta tell you, man, I love church.
I just love church.
Bye.
Bob.
Love church.
Totally.
Yes, giving.
Bob.
I love this guy.
Come join the fun.
All of you have heard of...
Bob.
Love church.
I gotta tell you, it makes you feel real big.
Go, go, go.
Love church.
Bob.
Yes, giving.
Love church.
Bob.
Come join the fun.
All of you have heard of...
Bob.
Love church.
It makes you feel real big.
Yes, giving.
Bob.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
We all thought you were dead.
No, no, still here.
How are you Bob?
Why this sudden concernure?
And the facts, you hear, this obscenity traffic conflated,
news dance literature has become increasingly worse not only
in countries like Rome, but in Europe and America.
enfim
so do they understand what's happening does anybody know what's happening well
I know I know we'll be celebrating the death of yeah the guy that's on one coin
and the guy that will never make it to a point Bob I've been staying here tonight
the overman phylo drumming members of negative land members of this church and
the subgenius all once again gathered inside the secret hideout and we'll be
discussing certain church secrets here as we always do before the end of the
year every two years we gather it used to be in Arkansas now it's here in our
scene shifts now to onion opalus
ring very easy capital of the United Socialist Republic of leeks and onions
it's a
a hurricane of lies you're living in every day
personally I don't think so I don't think it's true
I think the critical documentation is probably gone if there ever was any
documentation the people who really knew I believe all dead all we can do at this
point is piece together this puzzle and kind of see a picture if we step back
from it a little bit we can kind of see the picture from a distance and be able
to put it together I think that whether or not you believe it can in a
conspiracy and some people still don't as you know there a lot of people who
believe the Warren Commission
yeah I got something to say here it is right now check this out Bob Dobbs
I know Bob this is baby Rick I'm gonna kill you
yeah that's right Dobbs hear that one of two here's the next voice
hello I'm Bob Dobbs look at me you look at me I'm cool
all right here's another voice hey look at me I'm Bob Dobbs
take that
oh
Oh
the corporations themselves receive corporate welfare for free television
corporate money they're corporate fascists it's all true George feel good
that's playing out oh pages the piece that's
lights flyin out a bug does that play that we go down to vip simplesmente
lie around. George, will you tell me
what to do? It comes naturally.
From PR News in Washington,
I'm firing tear gas and pushing back the crowd.
But Pennsylvania Governor
Edwin Dell announced that the
34-nation summit of the Americas and Argentina
failed to revive PR News
in Washington.
Who are the overlords of the UFO?
UFO. You serve them
chilled on food picks. Canned mushroom
caps can be marinated also.
And so can tiny canned
shrimp in the same oil and lemon juice
dressing.
Which controls
half of the planet Venus.
We are in the office of the Secretary
General of the Party, a large
fat white onion named
Odor.
This traffic
continues to increase
and flourish
for
one
, one reason.
It is big business.
And
that bit about the secret service
driver who was a
Protestant from Ireland, by the way, who
lived on Henry Cabot Lodge's estate
who Kennedy defeated twice.
He turned around to
watch Kennedy get hit.
But the brutal frames
of that are missing.
We know they should be there.
There's too many of them.
Too many.
There are too many.
And you're forced to look for alternate explanations.
I mean, we don't have this many coincidences
in normal life under normal circumstances.
A
a
a a a a.
For some reason, for the assassination,
they multiply like crazy.
I think you still have to look at it that there might be something deeper underlying the assassination,
a deeper kind of force that was at work that brought all of these coincidences together,
all of these people together to create this addition.
My only pleasure is tormenting those people who work for me.
All your memories about your past are just a memory.
like your wife and your daughter are false and are more like a dream.
Gonads are useful for their purpose.
Good luck with your layoffs. All right. I hope your firings go really well.
Can your heart stand the shocking facts about grave robbers from outer space?
I like the team. Juice me. I'm a shiver boy. I got secret needles in my
poke globe.
Hello, Americans. This is Paul Harvey. Stand by for news.
Hi, man. Drugs are bad because if you do drugs, you're a hippie and hippies suck.
Fuck.
We take you back now just for a moment to look at these pictures that we're seeing.
We have to finish the security of the United States of America.
John Kerry defended a fellow terrorist.
Jack Murther was a counterterrorist.
He's a coward in Vietnam and he deserves to be vilified, not respected.
And the saying just said, do you think?
No, I'm not thinking.
The fuck up back there in California.
Now, man, all we need to talk about is detergent, deodorant.
A little people know of a few occasions where Andre the Giant actually did meet Bob Dobbs.
This show is the enema for society.
And unlike the...
Unlike that fall, he had a...
Had to take for a whole...
Become clogged up with media sexual...
Andre the Giant really did get his ass kicked by Bob Dobbs.
Look at that.
Just got his ass kicked when Bob ran behind him and kicked it real hard and then ran off real quick.
But Andre the Giant eventually caught up with him and...
Yeah.
He made some sounds.
Made a bunch of painful sounds.
Made a bunch of sounds.
Well, you know, I wanted to talk about that bunch of pills.
Yeah.
And I wanted to talk about Naughty Dallas.
That night where he drank the bucket of pills.
That was so amazing.
With the pill sauce...
The pill chainsaw.
Sauce pudding.
Topping.
Condiment juice.
It's a floor wax.
Where are any of those pills left?
Yeah, we've got...
Got a pill here.
And there's a bucket of pills over there.
And there's a big...
Pill over here.
Four-foot pill over there.
It's a giant pill.
It's a pill too big to swallow.
Now...
In keeping with the...
Questions that...
And a pill over here.
The caller has asked...
Yes.
Can the drug company make a pill that's too big for a human to swallow?
Or God to swallow.
One of the two.
And here on the show, we can answer those questions.
We can tell you what the pool of blood was.
We can tell you why it's called Six Floors Over Dallas now.
Yeah.
Can you tell us about the shaded relief behind the grassy knoll?
We can tell you why K-Rob is here but quiet.
Which led to the assassination.
Now, do you know the degree of slope facing the grassy knoll?
There you go.
Or say you're in the Daltex building on the second floor.
What's the degree of declination as the car moves away from you?
Well, I think you have to take a four...
I think it's 22.9 times 20,000 divided by 1 to the 50th.
There we go.
And we'll work that out.
And in one hour and a half, we'll have our answer.
Because we're only allowed to use computers that were available in 1963 on this portion of the show.
Degree of slope.
Yeah.
And you can see on this topographic map of...
By the way, I meant to say...
I meant to ask you, Mr. Overman.
Yes, sir.
Where were you on that morning?
It would have been morning then.
Or just afternoon.
Where was I?
Yeah.
Half an hour into the afternoon there.
Well, I was having breakfast on that morning, that fateful morning.
Where was...
Oh, in reality.
In reality.
Oh, yeah.
This is for the audience, not the real thing.
I was in my little schoolyard suit, dusting off my little culture browns.
Right.
Your little Serge wool shorts.
Soon to be having, you know...
And CPO jacket and camel hair.
Right.
And a little bit of a...
That's right.
That's exactly right.
Meanwhile, up north, Ramsey Clark, the Attorney General, is walking into his office.
Major General Clifton, Chester V. Ted Clifton.
Our president had been shot.
Yep.
Everybody in those days had a three-name nickname with quotes around it.
In Clifton's case, it was Ted.
In Dobbs' case, it was Bob.
And that's one thing we've never, ever talked about.
And maybe the public is ready to know what happened.
Where was Bob when Kennedy was shown?
He benefited from it till today.
Thanks.
He did?
Yeah.
Bob has benefited from just about everything till today.
But on tonight's show, we'll reveal church secrets that have never been revealed before.
No, we won't.
I knew Tim Garrison.
I met him in 1969.
He's a madman.
We won't?
My Xerox, my smudgy 13-page Xerox here says...
I can see...
My Xerox is only 12 pages.
Now, what's the missing page that I have?
Oh, a machine.
I don't know.
I think that's the one about the pool of blood.
Let's go.
And wait a minute.
I'm confused.
There was a pool of blood and a bucket of pills.
Now, which one of those is...
Where's the bucket?
The pool of blood may be connected to the headless golf player.
All right.
Doing dumb stuff.
Kind of dumb.
We don't like to talk about it, but we do it.
Dumb things I do.
But we do dumb stuff, don't we?
We don't like to admit it.
Really dumb stuff.
Hold out his gun.
This is a wannabe criminals.
Okay, okay, okay.
Dumb things we do.
Dumb.
Do it.
For some immediate gratification, do it.
Go ahead.
Do it.
Evil desires.
Did you hear that?
Flirt with a great disaster.
Meetings alone with the opposite.
It's sex.
I can handle it.
I want to sleep with you.
But, did you hear that?
It was art.
It was modern art.
The minute I think beautiful woman in a bikini.
Grow.
Go off.
I like watching pornography on the internet.
I like it.
How close can I come flirting with you?
Whatever.
Come on.
Don't worry.
I want to sleep with you.
And you have to do it.
Hey, listen.
Sud in the hole.
So let us come get pooped.
Flintstones.
Get pooped out.
Dumb songs or commercials that we'd like to forget.
Thought.
I mean, you know, you got to take a break here.
Pooped out.
Drastic measure.
Flirt a little bit with.
Why would he do that?
So let us come.
He came and he did it.
Do the dumb stuff.
Did you hear that?
Dumbs, dumbs, dumbs, dumbs, dumbs, dumbs, dumbs, dumbs.
We've blown it.
There.
Let me tell you something.
Dumb stuff.
I've done a lot of dumb things.
Thank you for dying.
What happened to the executive retreat we were supposed to.
I thought we were supposed to get a meal tonight here.
Well, we're playing.
Yeah, well, all that's down the drain.
Really?
What happened with the meal issue?
I mean, I thought.
I don't know.
The turkey.
The dressing.
I was up in the booth and I introduced Stang and lo and behold, he wasn't here.
And so we had to play a tape of him.
And now he's here.
And he sounds.
Well, are we still going to have to go over the budget?
He is here.
Just like a tape.
God.
White five.
Look.
I mean, that's a joke.
White five?
Stang, would you like to make some opening remarks to this banquet celebration?
I guess so.
I mean, how would you introduce the subgenius to, say, the complete neophyte?
Well, your doom has finally come.
And in the long run, it'll do you a lot of good if your existence ends now.
But is there any money in it?
That's actually our message to those who refuse to believe in the word of Bob as represented
by the Church of the Subgenius, which is the world's first industrial religion founded
in the 1950s by the.
Mystic super salesman, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
But is there any money in it?
But there's tons.
What do you mean?
Is there money in it?
It is of money.
It is composed entirely.
It is an edifice made of coins and dollar bills, you might say.
Then why am I paying for everything?
Pardon me?
Why am I paying for all this food?
Where is the food?
I mean, if you're paying for it, why aren't we eating it?
It's upstairs, man.
It's upstairs.
It's cool.
It's being prepared.
Okay.
So we are going to eat before we leave, right?
Oh, yeah.
Now, will that be after or before the budget seminar?
After.
What happens is the bobbies are watching the entire time.
They're sitting right over there at that big table.
Now, they can't hear me, but the deal is they have to figure out that they, too, can come
over and share the meal with the lower arpy.
If they don't figure it out, they get a...
Especially the she-bobbies.
The she-bobbies.
As far as I'm concerned.
Now, will that include the second portal of entry that can be utilized for biological
agent employment in this game?
Get the continue-alternative lunch.
What?
Oh, no.
Bob's here.
Run!
Let's have those spacemen, General.
Oh, that's not him.
Oh, God.
It sounded just like him for a second there.
Bob!
From PR News in Washington, I'm extremely dangerous.
The U.S. military says about 3,500 troops are meeting to discuss economic issues.
Their objective is to set fire to a street.
In advance of the December 15th explosion, you're listening to PR News.
The U.S. military escaped from a Texas jail after being sentenced to PR News in Washington.
I see people acting so cool.
Sometimes they don't notice.
Other people don't.
People see it right through.
There's a guy with purple hair.
I see him in a coffee shop.
And when he talks, he's always talking loud.
When he talks, he looks around.
You see who's watching while he's talking.
Think he wants to stand out in the crowd.
Notice me, notice me, notice, notice me, notice me, notice, notice me, notice me.
No, no, notice me.
Notice me, notice me, notice, notice me, notice me, notice me.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Notice me.
There's a girl with braces and she's standing by the punch bowl.
She's making funny faces at the boys.
She's sweating and she's fretting and she's sighing and she's trying.
She ain't talking, but she's making a lot of noise.
Notice me, notice me, notice, notice me, notice me.
No, no, notice me.
Notice me, notice me, notice, notice me, notice me, notice me, notice me, notice me, no, no.
Notice me.
Same old high school bullshit.
Dressed up in the style of today.
Don't matter what you call it.
Make it happen with your wallet.
Use a doctor, use your tongue, shoot a gun.
Now, now.
Now, now now.
Outro Music
The Bean Weevils did that song, friends.
Notice me from their one album, The Bean Weevils.
See, beanweevils.com.
Which we bought from Bean.
Bean, CD that is, when we saw his band in San Francisco
at the Ask Dr. Howell show at Café du Monde
just before we did this five-hour Thanksgiving subgenius business banquet
on the Over the Edge and Puzzling Evidence shows on KPFA in Berkeley
with Don Joyce of Negative Land and Doug Wellman, Puzzling Evidence,
mixing up us guests.
Dr. Philo Drummond, the original Overman,
Pope Michael Pepe, Dr. Howell Robbins,
Princess Wee Ardo, and the callers,
and yours, truly, Reverend Ivan Stang.
And that's mostly what this particular Hour of Slack number 1023
and several future ones will be.
Except for all of the remixed collage musical cut-ups
by Reverend Ivan Stang.
And for the PR news, and the collages shorter than or equal to 33 seconds,
which are mostly by Mr. Fernandez Leamer.
And don't try this at home, which is by Lemp Grey Systems.
Friends, the background music is by the Flying Ryan Brothers
from Blue Marble right now.
That's their CD.
That's Ryanetics.com.
Praise the guitar tech skills of Reverend Jimmy Ryan
and his brother, Johnny.
We must have their technical skill before the carrots get it
or we will be in the soup.
Penetration of the skin can be accomplished
by the bite of an arthropod vector.
These insects and insect-like organisms
are capable of transferring pathogens.
The man who breaks in the skin.
For the purposes of this seminar,
this definition of vector is limited to subgeni.
What the hell are you talking about?
I'm talking about drafting principles for overlay preparation.
What do you think I'm talking about?
I thought we were going to talk about the budget for this conference.
We're talking about the budget tonight.
And I do mean literally God forsaken.
Well, I hope you're ready to go through line item after line item.
He seems to have ignored us completely.
I hate that.
You know, I mean, it was bad enough when he ignored our prayers.
But to ignore our declaration of outright war,
it's an insult.
It is an insult.
It really is.
And let me tell you something, Bob, real quick.
Let me tell you something.
Bob?
Yes.
Okay, let me break that down.
Philo?
Bob?
Okay, Don?
All right, here we go.
Here's the point.
Bob?
I'm going to come down there.
Bob!
Anyway.
Aye, aye, aye, aye.
I'm going to take two flapjacks.
I'm going to take a piece of sausage and a bacon.
I'm going to breakfast you.
Okay, is this some kind of party?
What's Reverend Stans?
Reverend Stans, what is this?
I mean, what kind of church is this?
Come on, Doctor.
Where's the old preaching?
If you want to find out what kind of church this is,
meet us behind the Linwood Library at 730.
You'll find out.
Bring all your boys.
Bring the Johnson boys.
Any pro you want to take.
We're ready.
Bring Jerry Falwell.
Yeah.
Bring Pat Robertson.
Bring on Jimmy Slater.
Actually, it's been a long time since I've...
I've had a party with Jimmy Swagger.
You know, he's on back...
It's a shame what happened to him and he was both.
He is back on television, too.
He's back in the news.
He's back on TV.
Jimmy Swagger's back in the news?
Yeah.
Yeah, join in on the...
Actually, I'm so far behind.
I haven't been keeping up with my rival cult news.
Yeah.
You don't need to anymore.
Now that you're an ascended master of your own church, you don't need to worry about that.
No.
I'm the top clerk of Bob Dobbs cult.
Oh, I'm sorry.
So I haven't had time to enjoy any of the goose...
Juicy gossip or goosey jossip, we call it in cult jargon.
Yeah, goosey jossip.
About our rival religious nuts.
Yeah, and the jossip part is really the best part.
We're not...
The Church of the Subgenius is not really in competition with any of the other major world religions or fringe cults.
You can...
We have a lot of overlap with almost all of them as it is.
You're hearing it real time.
We scratch your hindbrain and you scratch ours or however that works.
As long as we're the picture.
What about this one?
No, it's the same thing.
It is the same thing.
Yes, comrade.
We are a number of churches and a number of influences right here, right now, because I actually went out to Dallas the first time to go see the Dealey Plaza.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
To breathe in the air of the scene back when nobody cared about it.
Back before yogurt was in America.
Before yogurt?
Well, in the sense that Danone had started shipping about two years before and it was slowly coming across the U.S.
And I'm thinking, I've eaten yogurt.
No American's going to eat yogurt.
Though I didn't realize they dumped so much sugar in our version that everybody was going to eat it.
Yes, Bob Dog's invented yogurt and the Church of the Subgenius.
And how to evaluate it.
One day I will kill you.
I will kill you.
I kill you.
I will do that one of these days.
Talk is deep.
If you don't shut up, I'll kill you, little evil one.
Trying to drive me out of my mind.
I will kill you.
Now get out of here.
Get out or I'll kill you.
I did kill again.
I'll kill you.
No, I'm happy.
Well, that's something I hope we can cover tonight.
You've got to think about that methodology.
You've got to get back in there.
You've got to think about which process you're going to use.
There's a certain amount of business we should be covering this evening.
Boring I know, but it's important to cover.
Yeah.
Or how are you going to interpret the written and the actual information.
information. As opposed to the data. We're trying to replace the written information
with pit codes. Instead of using English, we're trying to switch over to the subgenius
hieroglyphs, which take up a lot less space and have so many... You mean those little
icons in the Bobco font? It has almost no nuances. It's the opposite of the English
language. It puts things bluntly, perhaps a little too bluntly for the polished ears
of the modernist, the liberal, the conservative, the human.
Why don't you answer the phone, Rims? Phone!
You no longer need to answer the phone, Rims. It's a religion, not a hair shop.
I don't see what I see here, so I'll miss the caller.
And just who did kill Kennedy, caller?
I killed Kennedy. You did.
Well, can you confess now?
I'm going to put the phone down on the air and tell us why.
No, I didn't actually kill Kennedy.
Put us all out of our misery.
Okay, why don't you guys...
Why don't they call him Robert Kennedy?
No, we're just going to cover the ones you and me...
Why are we talking about the death of Robert Kennedy?
Well, that one, we can't talk about that until April, obviously.
Quick question real quick.
All right, we got two Bobcops.
This one has to be talked about on its anniversary.
And today is not only Thanksgiving, but it's the...
Okay.
It's the reason I met these guys when I went to Dallas.
Okay, I agree, but let me tell you something.
Well, okay.
Bobcops are not going to be quite as safe.
If I was any younger, I'd come down there and I would take a flapjack with a minecart.
And I would take some maple syrup.
It would be pretty good.
And these pancakes I sell are about $3.50, $4.
I'm having a gas attack.
I'm having an ass attack.
I mean, a donkey is attacking me.
Sex on the streets in every major city from coast to coast.
That's in front.
What a dumb thing to do.
I bet you wouldn't have done anything like this if Mom and Dad were here.
Hi, Mom.
I'm pregnant.
Do what you want to the girl, but leave me alone.
Emotions are for ethnic people.
From PR News in Washington, I'm Dresta Today on human rights and corruption charges, including alleged support of a paramilitary death squad.
On Wall Street 5-6, the U.S. military says it's abusing PR laws.
The photos show U.S. soldiers humiliating and otherwise mistreating PR News.
Former Peruvian President Alberto Fujimori set fire to a bus and held a police with PR News.
Washington.
Speaking of the Kennedy assassination, friends, the ultimate sacrifice can now be yours.
Actually, the book, Ultimate Sacrifice, by Lamar Waldron and Tom Hartman, is out now.
and I have been waiting for this book for, well, I've known Lamar Waldron for about 17 years
and that's how long he's been working on Ultimate Sacrifice.
It was finally published in hardback by Carroll and Graff Publishers
and you can find out all you need to know at a website called ultimatesacrificethebook.com
One word, ultimatesacrificethebook.
Ultimatesacrifice, John and Robert Kennedy, the plan for a coup in Cuba and the murder of JFK.
Friends, it's a whole different look at the Kennedy assassination than what you may be used to.
I can't even begin to go into the depths of the research and all of that
because this is the hour of slack and the Kennedy assassination isn't slackful for everybody.
But I've been around it for a long time and this is, you know, if you're really seriously looking for answers,
you should definitely check out Ultimatesacrifice.
Ultimatesacrifice, the case is not closed, but this one comes close.
Ultimatesacrifice, thebook.com
And by the good Lamar Waldron and Thomas Hartman.
Praise God.
I just say, Rev Stang, it's so wonderful to have you here in our precincts
and I just need to recuperate what you said about...
I'm sorry.
We are being ready for Lee Hazel...
What's his name?
Jimmy Swagger.
Hey, all I know is I'll never forget that bath I took yesterday.
Swagger, Falwell, bring him on.
That was a good one.
We got more holiness in the church alone than they have all there.
And, you know, as far as it...
As Pat Robertson goes, hey, why didn't somebody take him out?
Somebody in the church of the subgenius.
Take him out.
You can do that, can't you?
You can just say...
You know...
You know, Doug Wellman does that subgenius.
Take him out.
You know...
Buy him dinner, drinks, go dancing with him.
I don't get it.
And meet with him in a restaurant.
We're in the baby boomer generation.
I don't think...
You work with these people...
I don't want to take out Pat Robertson.
I know.
I think this would require infiltration.
I think we should, like, join Pat Robertson's cult.
Work our way up from the inside until we can infiltrate the properties of our organization.
Pat Robertson.
That way, that's the only way we're going to meet these budget commitments we have here today.
Dr. Drummond, is that all you can think about?
Money, money, money.
I have to bring us back to the matter in hand, which is going over these line items.
I know.
What are we going to do?
We're way over budget on man traffic, Spence.
What are we going to do about that?
Bob, it's not going to make a difference.
Let's just do like we do every year.
Put a bunch of big numbers over the final report and say it's going through.
What about...
The destruction, harassment, ambush, forearm teams that we have to get out there right now.
I mean, how are we going to do that?
Yeah, you've been saying that for 25 years, Dr. Drummond.
We've got to get those ambush teams out there.
What about our destroyer?
Our search and destroy troops?
Destroy all the monsters.
What about all the budget, the $3 billion a year that we contribute to Malaysia?
How come there's so many guys talking at once?
We're happy with that money.
Yeah.
From PR News in Washington, I'm stronger than expected sales.
Weather for a few minutes.
Forecasters say PR's bad.
PR's bad.
This is PR News.
The federal government has committed more than 300 million PR News in Washington.
The atomic bomb and the bicycle.
The photo mosaic patterns are minuscule compared to the impact the subgenius church has on America.
Wow, the beautiful trails.
Bend over and, you know, kiss, you know what, goodbye.
It's so well.
So, Michael Pepe, when are we going to shoot that movie?
We're going to shoot it very soon, as soon as I get through living in it.
No.
That doesn't work.
I'll tell you what.
Because then we get your mummified body in the kitchen like this.
That's what I want, like Titan, the mouse whose remains are in a little.
You still have?
Yeah, he's still, but you know what?
He's, his liquefaction.
I had a liquefied mouse that actually solidified, coagulated.
You said it on the air.
Reverend Strang, remember, whatever you say on the radio becomes true.
What?
In real life.
Wait.
Have intercourse with a beautiful live girl.
Okay.
Wait.
Or anything else.
We, yeah, we'll do that.
Well, yeah, no, that didn't, no, but what I have is better.
I brought, I brought a minute and 46 seconds of me doing Shakespeare.
There will now be four hours, five minutes of show left in your tank.
There are exactly four hours and five minutes left of show in your tank.
It's so little.
Oh, and I didn't get to say everything in my heart.
I didn't get to say, I didn't get to say anything.
I didn't get to say anything from my heart.
Oh.
But this is the show where any, any question you want to ask about something is true.
I didn't realize that Michael Pepe was in the same actual building with us.
And the funny is, I thought that was Sonny Bono.
Hi.
The smell came in.
I'm able to, I am continually, at this moment, I am continually hanging up on Hal's cell phone.
As he tries to call the show.
Hello.
Kim wants to talk to you.
Can I talk to you?
Jim.
At any date.
Sometimes the show becomes a little too color-driven.
Oh, wow.
Um, any, uh, man, uh, he's echoing bad.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
It's hurting you?
It's hurting me bad.
Okay, okay.
Sit down.
Sit down and, and let the show drain out of your ears.
You can't be responsible.
Come to my house.
You don't have a house.
Did you watch The Matrix?
Is it good?
You're, you're a guy in a little bathtub.
A battery.
Wait.
He's barbecuing us to death.
Yeah.
Shut up.
All science fiction movies have the truth.
Listen.
Don't barbecue cheese.
Get back in line, coppertop.
We've got to resist the, uh, lengthening of daylight savings time.
Yeah, take Red Pill, Blue Pill.
You're not free.
Go back to your bird hole.
It was June 23rd, I think.
There'll be no time for slack.
The first show, 1982.
More and more daylight.
And, uh, we had coppertops again.
We all took coppertops.
Hey.
And yet we're most excited.
Slack.
We have the great Slack batteries.
Okay, man.
The great dynamos.
And Dobstown must be charged.
With your slack.
You must give it up.
To Bob.
No.
That we may store it.
For later.
We'll give it back to you.
Amplified.
Oh, this is better when you get it back.
Only bad radio will suck the evil poison of good culture.
Why, a preacher wouldn't lie or be wrong, would he?
And replace them with, uh, $20 a month.
Just send it to 400, never mind.
And is there a more?
There's a mortgage payment on it.
There's a, a mortuary what?
A mortuary payment.
Oh, uh, yeah.
We will, if you send us $600 now, we will, uh, keep you in, in urns for 2,000 years.
Not stored in any soul.
But, don't you have to be burned to be put in an urn?
That's right.
This is an outrage, a national insult.
No.
Yes.
We're gonna burn you down into ash.
Put you in the urn and keep you for 2,000, our descendants have, uh, pre-humanized.
Signed.
But I want speakers inside, you know, and a radio.
You got it.
So I get to show broadcasts inside my urn.
Yeah.
That's right.
That's the kind of thing.
Really?
That's, you've got it.
We can arrange this for your ancestors or your descendants.
We can do anything.
That's right.
But I wanna be put in orbit.
Your ancestors can be saved.
Okay.
Orbit?
You want, but that's gonna be a different.
Even Bob.
I want the Moonraker planet.
Posthumously.
Okay.
All right.
But, you know, now you're changing plans.
We're gonna have to switch you off to someone, another person in charge of plans.
No.
I like talking to you.
Cause I figure I can maybe like, you know, work you out of it.
You can trust me.
Yeah.
Salesman Pepe has a very trustworthy sounding voice.
I just sound like one of these dweeby dumb guys that is really.
Well, not be here tonight.
I'm trying to take advantage of your naive.
Yeah.
Exactly.
He's supposed to be listening.
We will promise to do this.
And I'll tell you, if I have to get fired by my boss.
You're gonna just rock.
I will give you this deal, man.
Oh, what about your car too?
All right.
Okay.
But after you're dead.
Yeah.
I'm gonna give you this deal.
Okay.
But you gotta carry me around in your trunk though.
Yeah.
But I mean, you have to, then you have to die before I do.
That's the thing.
And so, no, this probably won't happen.
I'll probably die first.
I like the, the way it sounds.
You have to die before I do.
Yeah.
That has a nice ring to it.
I think it'll work.
Just generally as a statement.
You know, it worked on a couple of the leads that Philo gave me.
And he, and yeah, it just kind of like taking you into my confidence and saying, you know,
uh, you know, I killed my mother and father too.
And I said, I know where you're coming from.
And I can feel your pain.
It's talk of death and dying and pain and such.
It all leads to heaven sooner or later.
We're all gonna meet, meet in heaven.
We all just get along.
But at the same time we need insurance.
I just wanna let people know that we're there as a church to help.
That's right.
It's a form of insurance.
It's, yeah.
Don't you worry about what's gonna happen.
I just worry.
I just, I just stay up all night worrying about what's gonna happen to my body after
I die.
We only worry about how much money you've sent in.
Really?
So we can keep track of how many lifetimes you're going to be allowed after this one.
Yeah, right.
Exactly.
That's right.
Bean counters, really.
The more you pay, the more lifetimes you are given.
Bean counters of soul.
Soul counters.
How many lifetimes do you want?
We can make your soul bigger too.
That's the whole idea.
Yeah.
That is exactly what it's all about.
Thank you.
But how?
Make that soul bigger.
March your soul.
You know, it's working on you at the moment.
It's like a prostate.
Already working.
We're already working in your mind.
It's near the prostate.
In your body.
Work it out.
This music is already playing.
It's already been pre-played.
It's been all pre-played.
Everything has been predetermined beforehand by the church.
The forehead expands first.
Then the body follows.
That's right.
You can feel the hairs growing.
You can feel the...
Wow.
You know, you float off away a little bit.
They get bigger and bigger.
Yeah.
And you've got to try to hold down.
Don't allow the air in your brain to lift you off the surface.
Another bowl of finely chopped green onions.
And...
Another of commercial sour cream.
And for all time, we will play...
The soul of the soul.
The soul is expanding.
And Bob knows how many times it's gonna come and go.
How much time it's gonna take.
And go, go, go.
To your urn.
Give the know-how.
Keep all the ashes in the right urns.
We don't want to mix any of the souls.
Bob may become confused.
We do not mix your urn.
You've earned an urn.
You?
About an urn?
No, you're yearning to earn a human.
Determine the size of your soul.
It's not like you're a human.
Your soul is enlarged.
Your urn's right.
Well, the amount of your earnings that you send to the church.
If you have a big soul, you're gonna need a big urn.
That's right.
Appropriately.
It's gonna be huge by the time we get through.
If you want a bigger soul, you're gonna have to earn more.
Yeah.
I mean, this could cost millions.
Everything's in the church.
Stay away.
Sending the money.
Why are you...
Cast out me.
Stay away.
Sending the money.
Cast out me.
It's as simple as that.
You're a fool.
Fight the conspiracy by doing those things.
Stay away.
Number one, you have to do that.
Don't say it.
No.
My eye is in the blood of a gorilla.
As the great Comartie said.
I was making my boo-boo.
Number two.
Send in the money.
Right.
Number three.
What was it?
Oh, yeah.
Cast out the evil one.
From your own gut.
And the money.
There is an evil demon of the conspiracy living in your liver.
And you have got to vomit that vomit.
That's right.
You have to drive that thing out.
No, you've got to kill it with alcohol.
The only way to do that is to study Bob's work.
Yeah.
Well, the only way to do that is to keep earning.
Stay away.
If it's in your liver, then we'll just kill it with alcohol.
Cast out the evil one.
That's right.
Drive it out using whatever poison you can.
I understand some types of mushrooms will drive a demon life out of your liver.
Drive the evil one out of your liver.
The so-called liver.
Electronics.
Certain bad health plans will be...
You can't do the same thing.
And alcohol.
Drive it out.
Karma.
Perfect.
Yeah, it's like churches.
And taint.
You want to get rid of that soul taint.
Yeah.
You want to cleanse it.
It's like a river.
Slack is like a river coursing through your body.
Wild.
Like a Kundalini snake dragon.
That bottle.
That's Slack.
Remove the karmic energy of death from your body.
What do you call that, Reverend Stang?
That river of Slack.
I call that Slack.
What do you call that, Stang?
What's it?
The orniferos.
The world river.
Sprinkle some of the green onions.
The Ouroboros.
Thank you.
This whole reprintable.
That's right.
The Ouroboros.
It's the world river of Slack, which you can join and dive into.
It's the endlessly...
This room is a thing.
Not just everyone.
Sex speed.
This room is a thing.
The ouroboros has a...
You're always climaxing constantly.
Your mind is constantly...
True Slack is like that.
It's like in that movie Brainstorm when that man made a loop of the orgasm.
They really want to.
That is Slack.
That's continuous orgasm.
That's like one million times better than that endless orgasm loop.
Some of the greatest of them, monks, have not achieved complete Slack.
Don't you want a little bit of that, friend?
Don't you want to just get a cut of that?
Yeah.
Just a little tiny cut.
Possibly.
Undoubtedly, but we will change that point of view once...
That's subgenius.com.
There's no O in subgenius, but there is in com.
It is a C in com.
Is there an O in com?
Is there an I in denial?
What was it?
It is a time and place of com.
In the same place there's one in bob.
Right in the middle.
Dot piece and dot com.
Yeah.
Synthetic piece, synthetic com.
Church is actually the only church that is a church.
It's a dot com, isn't it?
Isn't that with the number change?
That's a fraction of a con.
It's a fraction of the conspiracy itself.
But, you know, that's the way why we're saying.
You're tainted with the conspiracy.
The church is tainted.
Everything is tainted except for Bob's pipe.
That's the one clean place.
And if you can throw yourself into that pipe and let Bob smoke you.
That's right.
You're not smoking Bob.
You're not going, let's get into Bob.
Get high.
Here.
Yeah.
No!
It's the other way around.
And, you know, the thing is, the pipe is actually the thing doing the smoking.
It's sucking Bob's brain and inhaling it in a smoke-like form into the universe.
Yeah.
It's a reversed pipe.
It's a reversed time pipe as well.
That's proof there, Reverend Simon.
It's both a slack river and a time river.
And it goes backwards through Bob's head.
Upwards after his lungs like an ever-vomiting, perfect pureness of love.
Perpetual motion.
It's a perpetual motion of vomited love coming forth from Bob's pipe.
And it's made of pure brain being smoked in that thing.
You have got to get real.
This is not some game.
This isn't some metaphor, some performance art.
This is real.
This is your soul we're talking about.
This is happening.
It's your income we're talking about.
And it's the savings you know we're talking about.
You will.
Have you willed these conversations with your church?
Have you thought about it?
I have a question for you.
Look at that breathing down your neck right now.
He's there.
He's behind you.
The structure of this room is hovering.
It's about ready to grab you up on a scruff of the neck.
No!
I have a statement.
And that is you're not Bob.
You're lost.
You are lost San Francisco.
You saw what happened to some of the other great cities in this country.
San Francisco you better pay attention.
Berkeley.
You hear me?
You hear me now?
San Francisco on line one wants to know what can they do to save their sorry, sorry asses now.
Thank you for your tribute to this marvelous radio station.
Here is the word of Bob.
Golden Bridge.
Golden.
The next thing they can do is tuck their head between their knees and kiss their fanny goodbye.
After the world.
They join the church of the subgenius for real.
And show Bob they really believe.
By signing their name on that dotted line on that check.
And would that entitle them to the.
To subgenius.com.
Would that entitle them to all of the privileges that other subgeniuses would derive.
No.
As well as the microorganisms.
No because each subgenius has its own type of privileges and slap.
It's different for each one.
For some it's a terrible rip off.
For some it's an endless pit of bad feelings.
By the way.
By the way we missed the ID again.
Oh.
No.
The ID.
We missed the ID.
From PR news in Washington.
I'm Tom.
That's awful what happened here in an unusual,
started by a discarded cigarette.
Catholic Archbishop Sean O'Malley is calling for an end to homosexuals.
He says he doesn't want homosexuals.
Personally O'Malley's hostile to homosexuals,
but views ban and gay men as important for children from Madrid.
The Dow Jones 666 the Spanish government says it is ignoring PR news in Washington.
So out people come over this Bob,
this Bob,
this Bob is the president of the.
Uh.
Bob. No doubt we'll have an interesting hour there. That's Bob. But now I've got a little
joke for you, Bob. Get you, Bob. I've got another joke here for you, Bob. Active Bob. You're free
to go. So help me, Bob. From PR News in Washington, I'm both at the same time. The huge storm system
that produced the past few days, National Weather Service forecaster Peter says, you've got a cold
front moving eastward and northward. And snowplows try to restore electricity to hundreds of thousands
of miles of interstate highways. Vice President Dickey advocates the use of PR News in Washington.