And now we are made again.
Listen to those fireworks, friends, and welcome.
Welcome to Hour of Slack number 400, believe it or not, but keep your heads down, friends,
because it's also the X-Day special.
Broadcasting on X-Day, July 4th, 1993.
Five years to X-Day.
And count.
The Soap Genius.
Hour of Slack.
Ignition.
Liftoff.
The Soap Genius.
Yes, we always have to do that on X-Day.
Whoa, X-Day Eve.
Got to be careful.
Sound effects can...
It can hurt.
It can hurt bad.
It can tear you up.
And, uh, yes.
And we're so happy to wish you a happy X-Day Eve.
And as I said, we're broadcasting from Dallas at this time in your past.
Most of your past, at least, on July 4th.
A false independent day.
What we call one day before the beginning of the world.
X-Day, the real Independence Day.
July 5th, 1998, which we have to celebrate in advance.
Now, when a dog's prophecy tells us that the men from Planet X
and the sex goddesses of the escape vessels will rupture up,
the true subgenius dues-paying members
and those on Bob's mailing list database disks.
So, uh, this being the day that pinks celebrate
and pat themselves on the back for being, uh,
well, just so goddurn free.
Well, uh, we've got a real all-American show planned.
All you Rush Limbaugh and Barney the Dinosaur fans
will just love what came in the mail this week.
And by the way, folks, uh, did you know,
did you know that Rush Limbaugh is Barney the Dinosaur
in a Rush Limbaugh suit?
It's true.
And, uh, tip of the crown to Princess.
We are dope for that, uh, research.
But, friends, we've got a tape,
in the, in the mail, uh, this last week
from the, uh, the, the new improved Juke Savages
who had previously sent a fantastic tape
that was, it was intense,
but it was so, uh, peppered with the, uh, F word
that, uh, oh, it was, it was painful,
but we couldn't do anything with it.
Well, now this new album has come out
from the new improved Juke Savages
with Krishna Fats.
And the Night Nurses.
This album called
Radical Militant Vegetarians in Nazi Land.
And I just want to say that I am proud,
proud to be, uh, presenting this, uh,
on the Hour of Slack.
Uh, yes.
Regarding my politics,
I'm an anarchist.
Regarding everyone else's,
I'm a Nazi.
I don't want to live in Nazi land.
I don't want to bury my head in the sand
and have to pretend that everything's grand.
I don't want to live in Nazi land
where the media's controlled,
the mass mind's programmed.
I don't want to live in Nazi land
based on dominance and violence
where the flames of hate are fanned.
I don't want to live where fear's the plan.
I do not like green eggs and ham
and I don't want to live in Nazi land.
I love love, and get it straight,
I hate hate.
I don't know if people hate love,
but you can see people love to hate.
There's no debate, get it straight.
Look around, it's the human state.
Is it fate? It isn't great.
Do you think it might be too late?
People love, love, love, love, love to hate.
There's no debate, state that people love to hate.
People love, love, love, love, love, love to hate.
They love to hate, they love to hate.
The Nazi in all of us loves to hate.
It's so much better.
It's better than taking responsibility for yourself.
And now, by the same guy who brought you
knee-grin cakes, spits, warts, fakes, chips,
scoots and gypsies, ladies and gentlemen,
the next president and red wizard of Nazi land,
enough dope with the cuckoo cuck squad,
I'm Jack of vocals, singing their newest hit,
It's out there in Nazi land.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Joe and the Poop!
Do you wanna live in Nazi land?
Did you already live in Nazi land?
Where the Nazis in control have a Nazi plan?
Where only if you're white do you count as a man?
Where a woman's only role is baby land?
Every negro and kite should understand.
And the Asians, Latinos, and everyone with a tan.
Do you wanna live where everything's planned?
By Adolf Duke, the right hand man of the lords?
I hate the cuckoo cuckoo clock's plan.
Wouldn't you rather have to drive a van?
Hey, wouldn't you rather live without a plan?
Hey, I'd rather have a plan.
I'd rather have a friend named Stan than have to live in Nazi land.
I do not like green eggs and ham,
but I'd rather eat green eggs and ham.
Would you rather eat green eggs and ham than have to live in Nazi land?
What is this trip about green eggs and ham?
Is that what they eat in Nazi land?
Watch out, you get n-n-n-n-n-n-n-nazis in your spines.
Watch out for people with n-n-n-n-n-nazis in their spines.
I mean, I can see you.
How can you not see me?
See higher.
Nazis need love too.
Nazi land is in a fluke.
Let's take all hatred out on spooks and kooks and kikes and gooks and jukes.
Now Adolf Duke might make you puke, but he's smooth and sharp and cool as a kuke.
And you tell me, was it just a fluke that over half the whites voted for Adolf Duke?
And if you're not a white supremacist kuke, you've gotta be spooked or ready to puke.
It's unreal.
How can you not see me?
It's unbelievable.
See higher.
Nazis need love too.
I mean, Adolf Duke says Jesus is the most important thing in his life.
Well, something ain't kosher here.
I mean, do you feel like you're being condomized the only one?
I mean, don't these Nazis realize they would have incinerated Jesus because he was Jewish?
And his mother was Jewish?
Holy funk.
They would have incinerated the Virgin Mary because why?
Because her divine lover was the God of Abraham.
Hey, none of these people were Christians.
And they certainly weren't National Socialists.
In Nazi land, Nazi land, they can always hire a band, but their favorite band in Nazi land is always Adolf Duke and the Cthulhu Tux Band.
Well, there are always riots in the stands because they love to hate like all their fans.
But I don't want to live in Nazi land.
I'd rather hear a different band.
But in Nazi land, they just don't understand.
In Nazi land, they didn't get it.
Nazis might be aliens disguised as Nazis.
And don't get me wrong, okay, I like Nazis.
I mean, I don't have anything against Nazis.
Some of my best friends are Nazis.
I mean, I can see you.
How can you not see me?
Do you want to not see me?
Do you want me to not see you?
Hey, what a joke.
Take a Nazi to lunch.
Hatred doesn't let us any time cease by hatred.
Hatred ceases by love.
They didn't get it.
What do you think?
Love them to death.
See, how?
Nazis need love, too.
I don't want to live in Nazi land.
I'll tell you.
Just say no.
No.
So, how dare you.
Okay, let's be serious.
Okay, I swear that I haven't been here for a while
but I do remember CEOs standing up and being like,
This just isn't right.
I almost got kicked out of high school for playing this song at a football game the night Jimi Hendrix died.
Yes.
And I'm probably going to end up sounding like, wait a minute, I've got to hear this.
Oh, my God.
the airwaves.
As far as, again, as far as
the news media is concerned, it's because all
these people are, oh, they're
lapping up all these
pudgy white boys in
suits with Bibles who say,
oh, now these
liberals have tried
to clutter everything up and make it
too complicated. But the problem
is actually real,
real simple.
We're smart
and manly.
And they're stupid
and womanly.
And
they're good at
saying everything between
the lines
so that when they say,
when they say, quote,
liberal, unquote, you know what
they really mean.
You know,
they really mean those pesky
homos
and Jews
and the uppity women and
minorities.
Don't kid yourself. That's exactly
what they mean.
And the commies are down
and out these days, so now we have to
find anti-American demons
in our own backyards.
And, I mean,
the perspective has been
totally skewed by the
conspiracy to such an extent
that most of
you actually consider
President Clinton
to be a
liberal.
A liberal!
If Clinton is a liberal, then I
must, I myself must not
be anywhere on that
damn scale. And I'm not.
And if you're still on that
skewy scale, then you are a complete
sucker. We've got another song about
that coming up.
SNL, Suckers and Losers.
There was an article
in the paper today about the success
of the
right-wing talk shows,
which is now called,
conservative talk shows.
It seems in the Dallas area,
you can hear 15
conservative shows.
And you can also hear two
liberal shows. Now, both of the liberal shows
that they mention are by
namby-pamby black guys.
Bob Ray Sanders and
Jesse Jackson. They didn't mention
the not-so-namby-pamby
show by a black guy,
by John Wiley Price. No,
no, sir. Dallas Morning News didn't mention that,
but they're liberal bias.
That's right. Uh-huh. And if you
step back, dear friends, and
snap out of it, and look
at the guests and the experts
that they feature, you'll find that
shows like Nightline and
McNeil-Larer, which are
sometimes called liberal,
are actually really
conservative, pro-establishment,
et cetera, et cetera. Another thing
they didn't mention, they don't seem to mention,
one of those little lies of omission,
oh, Clinton said, I hate to
defend Clinton. That's not really,
that's not what I'm doing, but, you know,
they talk about, uh, oh,
how can, Clinton, he's
a coward. He took
that draft deferment so he wouldn't have to
go to Vietnam. You know who else
took that little draft deferment
so they wouldn't have to go to Vietnam?
But they don't talk about these guys.
Secretary of Defense
Dick Cheney did the same thing.
Why, former
drug czar William Bennett
did the same thing.
Pat Buchanan,
did the same thing, and
our own Senator
Phil Graham, the Antichrist.
Chicken hawks
all in. And here's another thing.
Remember the total
arrogance when
Clinton held up all those
planes at the airport while he
got a $200 haircut?
That news story
that really caused everybody to
totally lose patience with him and
think of him as some sort of
remembered Communist Party official?
You remember.
Well, they announced in small
print on page 12
that it
didn't happen.
The media, a few reporters,
invented the story from whole cloth.
No planes had to wait,
and the haircut might have been free
for all anybody knows.
The falsehood made
front page news, but the retraction
was on page 12.
Liberal biased media,
and sometimes conservative media,
chad
everywhere for them.
While the Lanes
and
media
are
only
neutral against unlimited
upside down and but by god by wotan it is appointed it is appointed to men once to die
but after this the judgment uh yes the judgment shall be coming up dear friends because every day
is x day when you have a gun and as it saith in isaiah 6.5 and strangers will stand and feed your
flocks and the sons of the aliens shall be your plowmen and your bind dressers and this know also
that in the last days perilous times shall come for men shall be lovers of their own selves
you
a covetous boasters proud blasphemers disobedient to parents uh sound familiar yet friends
unthankful unholy and women wearing pants and short haircuts and that's from two uh timothy
larry three one and two uh friends because you know if you could see a galaxy being born like
the spurt of
infamously
infected blood from between the thighs of some huge incestuous demon you would be ashamed of your
own puny little existence you would see yourself as nothing more than an abortion a deformed hunk
of snot that was hatefully spat out by a stellar nebula but you were sane enough or paranoid
schizophrenic by society's standards to accept the beauty and purity of this you might as well be a
ыми
it being a moment you spoken manly so much that you can't even imagine not of adventure
pate
book
calvary
as well
luthier
leately about this
yourself
something far's out there
a comic book
Oh, the pinks like those fake 4th of July explosions, don't they?
Yeah, well, on 7-7-98, they'll be going,
Whoa, I guess these subgenius fireworks are just a mite stronger.
Yes, but we shall have our revenge, our vengeance,
and here's that other song from the new improved Juke Savages.
In honor of family sensibilities, the expletives have been deleted.
It was said before his coming,
Lo, they have baptized you in endless taxes,
But upon his coming, lo, he will baptize you in holy fun.
The suckers and the losers are the ones who will pay
For all the money that's lost, all the money that's gone away.
Bail out the S&Ls, the insurance companies, and the banks.
Here's two bucks bent over, nobody even bothers to say thanks.
Hey!
I didn't know you were here.
We're into S&L.
Hey, sucker.
Hey, loser.
You've been had, and you're such a good sport, you're not even mad.
I can dig it.
Who can figure it out?
Are you dumb or numb, or do you want to shout?
But it's no good to shout, so don't shout about it,
And it certainly won't help to pout about it,
But you'll pay till you die.
There's no doubt about it,
And your kids will be paying long after you're gone.
It ain't over yet.
It goes on and on and on.
Hey!
I didn't know you were into S&L.
Don't you wonder?
Where did the money go?
And don't you wonder?
Where did the wealth go?
Don't you wonder?
Go ahead and wonder.
But...
You'll never know.
Doesn't the government insurance take a load off your mind?
Don't you feel safe and protected?
You know what I like?
I mean, about democracy, everyone's equal,
So instead of letting a few people be screwed,
You know, by unscrupulous bankers and developers
And the politicians they own,
We've had the law like, you know, the FSLIC
To make sure everyone gets screwed,
Except, of course, for the people who don't.
And the people who get to come.
And it's not the people who mishandle the money who pay,
But all the suckers and losers who look the other way.
We weren't paying attention, were we?
We aren't paying attention now, are we?
Were we too busy to pay attention?
Now we'll pay lots more money.
Were we afraid or ashamed to name the game?
Well, someone thinks it's funny, and I...
I like it! How about you?
I like being expletive-deleted over by people I don't even know.
That way, you're sure it's nothing personal.
I mean, you know, some of these people have more money than they can earn.
You know, some of these people have more money than most suckers and losers can even imagine.
And worked out a little scam, and you've got to hand it to them,
Because if you don't,
The federal government, out buying for what?
Will come and do it for them.
Then they can let the IRS do it for them, you know,
And send you to jail,
And then you pay for the money these guys stole.
Now, doesn't the government insurance take a load off your mind?
Don't you feel safe and protected?
Just go F-S-L-I-C,
K yourself, I mean just go F-S-L-I-C,
K yourself, go F-S-L-I-C,
K yourself!
Pay me, pay me,
I support it.
I'm not gonna complain because as an American,
I'll fight to the death for rights and freedom.
You know, like the right of the CIA to sell drugs,
So they don't have these little funding problems, you know,
The freedom of fat cats to steal money from you,
The same way someone stole lamb from the Indians,
Because they do it on paper,
And don't actually stick people up.
I mean, think about it.
You know, if somebody robbed you on the street for,
You know, 15 bucks,
We'd talk about jail for, you know, years, okay?
But somebody oozes away half your wealth, life savings and lifestyle,
To some S&L bailout inflationary bull expletive deleted,
And we talk about a plaque with their name on it,
You know, I'm gonna go to the airport or something,
And why?
Because they stole it legally,
You know what that means?
Go S-L-I-C, K yourself, just go.
I mean, forget the L.A. looting,
We're not talking about 800 million,
We're talking about over 200 billion,
And that's with a B, baby, and counting.
Now that's looting.
You know, I mean,
I never even voted for this,
Social Security or the F-S-L-I-C,
But I really like supporting a system that is so socially insecure,
That money is pouring down invisible drains,
F-U-S-L-I-C, K protected,
Because the rest of us will happily pay for it.
I mean, are we gonna complain about abuse and mismanagement?
Not those of us who are good citizens,
We just bend over, no gasoline needed,
Doesn't the government insurance take a load off your mind?
Don't you feel safe and protected?
Just go S-L-I-C, K yourself, and...
Now if you're thinking of bitching,
All I can say is,
America, love it or leave it,
Why don't you fly back to Russia?
You're walking on the fighting side of me,
I'm proud to be a sucker and loser from Muskogee.
Expletive deleted,
Anytime the guys behind the scenes want to
Expletive delete us over, you know,
To pay money or send kids to die in the deserts and jungles,
Me and all the good ass people,
We're Americans,
We'll be the first in line,
And we won't listen to the detractors and complainers,
And we promise not to listen to anything bad anyone says about it,
And if we do hear something about it,
Most of all, we promise not to think about it.
And you call that American?
Don't give me that.
Patriotic bull, expletive deleted,
You ignore the loss of freedom through economic manipulation,
Because it sounds too complicated,
And besides, you're too busy watching the game,
And don't get me wrong,
I've got nothing against football,
Okay, I like football,
Some of my best friends watch football,
But don't call me unpatriotic,
Because I'll stand against the accepted view,
And call it like I see it,
Don't you get it, George?
This is patriotic!
Let me see if I've got this right, alright?
It's like the opposite of a sticker.
I give my money to an S&L bank or insurance company,
Only when I come back for it,
Like if you lost it, or snorted it,
Or invested it in junk bonds in a company your brother-in-law owns,
I can go F-S-L-I-C-K myself,
And I don't have to worry,
Because it's insurance.
Only,
I'm insurance.
If you lose my money,
I pay for it.
And if you lose someone else's money,
And we call it chaos with the banking laws,
The F-S-L-I-C chaos with the tax laws,
The F-S-L-I-C chaos with military spending,
The F-S-L-I-C chaos with foreign aid,
The F-S-L-I-C chaos with inflating the currency,
The F-S-L-I-C chaos,
I mean, why go F-S-L-I-C-K yourself
When you can pay through the nose,
And let the government F-S-L-I-C-K you
And the expletive deleted?
Why?
Because we are the government,
We are fizz-licking ourselves,
So let's go for it,
Let's F-S-L-I-C-K ourselves,
I mean, come on,
It's a free country,
So just go F-S-L-I-C-K yourself,
Just go F-S-L-I-C-K yourself,
F-S-L-I-C-K yourself.
Here you go.
Let's go Milet,
Down with the taoist heads.
My team will go.
No, we haven't done anything yet.
Bu Lan,
Oh, yes, dear friends, the new improved Juke Savages, and well, so much for, oh, by the
way, that album, once again, is called Radical Militant Vegetarians in Nazi Land, and I doubt
if it's really on CD or anything, it's just on cassette, from Holy Funk Records and Tapes,
and you are listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry, Hour of Slack, some output from,
or at least presented by, the Church of the Subgenius for you, and now we're going, well,
Sister Mary Squared and I will be taking...
Put some Cowboy Dave to hell.
Yes.
Thank you.
It will hurt.
Why are you stopping?
I don't see any dinosaurs around.
There's something wrong.
I can't seem to move.
I feel like, like I'm being sucked under.
I'm sinking.
Call Brachiosaurus.
Call the Braticus.
Call somebody before we're buried alive.
He suddenly found himself, sees her behind.
By a man in a dirty sheepskin coat.
For a split second, he feared he had been tricked.
Flashed through my mind that I had been betrayed, he wrote, and that I had been brought here
unarmed, not for negotiation, but for execution.
He took himself free and prepared to fight for his life, but hastily, it was explained
to him that this was the ancient Stang custom, that all envoys were dragged before Stang as
a sign of voluntary submission.
Call this voluntary?
He ran across the courtyard toward the yurt, halting at the entrance and saluting the Stang
in a local fashion.
He then remained standing, waiting to be addressed.
The Stang, reported Lady, had a very striking appearance.
He must be six or eight inches high.
His beard was short and red, his voice pleasant, and he speaks distinctly, fluently, and with
dignity.
After stroking his glasses for several minutes and studying the Russian carefully, the Stang
at last spoke.
How, he inquired, wherefore art thou come, and what dost thou wish of me?
Well, I, uh, that is to say, it's all rushing over me.
So far, I'm not sure.
I cannot tell you how fast that I, I can form no orderly record of my sense impressions,
but it seems that the very first thing I remember was being pushed in my baby buggy by my Aunt
Minnie.
I was looking up at the stars when suddenly I saw, nearing down, the hideous, hairy face
of an enormous spider!
Can we leave now?
I mean, jeez, this is, this is, you guys call these, that was, that's a script, right?
You call that a script, right?
Yeah.
That's a script.
Okay, now I know what a script is.
Now I've seen a real script.
That's a little different, manly script I've seen before you guys.
Oh, this script, yeah, I've seen scripts before.
How come we don't hear the music?
Aren't they playing some kind of music or something?
They're playing music.
We just can't hear it.
It's dog music.
You mean, wait a minute, oh, we're on the air?
No, we're not on the air.
Oh, okay.
Gee.
We didn't put this on the air.
Uh, cause I was afraid, if we did a thing where we acted like we thought we were on
the air, that's like the oldest, but we really knew we were on the air.
Yeah, I know.
We were acting like we didn't know.
Yeah.
It is so old.
I'm done now.
They'd see right through it.
What?
You know, yeah, we would never do nothing like that.
Get, get, get Monica out of here.
You've got the wrong woman.
Get her out of here.
Oh, Monica's all right, Dave.
Don't worry about little Monica.
What are you, what are you gonna do to her, man?
Oh, we, oh, we're, we're changing her.
Yeah, she needed to be changed, that's all.
Your, your child only, oh, she's a little bit older.
Your child only needed to be changed, Dave.
She's not my child.
She, she's not my real child.
I'm protecting her though, now, for this, this moment in time, because I was given a
rip from God.
Oh, that's okay.
And I was trying to keep her awake.
Just take some of this limousine.
You'll feel better.
We're your friends and your father's, Dave.
We'll take care of little Monica.
Well, look, she's already changing.
She's changing herself now.
You ever see that movie, The Fang?
I've never seen that movie.
She's a little, a child evolved so quickly.
The little, the little spider legs sticking out of her back now.
Don't worry, she acts like it hurts, but that's just part of the change, Dave.
Oh, she moves so much differently.
She can climb the walls with such ease now.
She's, she's a child of Bob now, Dave.
She'll never want to come back to her folks after this.
I'm kind of really depressed about that part.
Oh, well, you don't want her back, do you?
I mean, she's a child.
Well, it's not my fault.
I know.
The little, the little spider legs and her stuff, and then they got her, and you got
her growing a bob-dob.
She had to have lizards biting things on her nipples.
The little pipe.
And you know, that little pipe there looks, look, she can already talk now.
She can't bring back a grown child.
And notice, when she opens her mouth, the little pipe doesn't fall out.
It's implant, it has tap roots that go up deep into her brain, Dave.
I hope it's only tapioca smoking in a pipe, because I could get into one hell of a vile
mouth in two weeks.
malediction from these guys.
Some of them are bigwigs in another church
I won't care to mention.
You know what I mean?
Oh, those Scientologists?
No, left-handers, bud.
I'm talking about people with distended forefingers.
They could put a hex on us right now.
I know they...
Oh, but you'd be surprised what they can do
with those distended forefingers.
They can reach places that you wouldn't even think
a doctor would even think to reach.
A child has to...
We go into the crevices of the mind
and we probe.
Oh, yes, oh, yes, Sister Mary.
Go probe deeper.
Oh, I have always wanted to explore this part of you.
The pain isn't taking you away, is it?
Now do it today.
I guarantee.
David, fantastic, David.
I've always wanted to bend over a little bit further,
David.
Oh, David.
Oh, my God.
I like the probe.
This is getting way out of hand.
Oh, oh.
Let's crank the probe.
Oh, yes, open it up wide, wide open.
Oh, I see now.
I see.
Oh, gee.
You have to see it.
A bish.
A new bish.
It's a new bish.
And we got some new business here, friends.
Grasp your afterlife firmly.
Decide upon your destiny.
Find the nearest priest of the great...
...spider.
Convince him of your virtue.
And have the sacred bites set upon your head.
Become a sacred mark.
For only in this way can you enter into the web and avoid the maw of the spider at the
center of the world.
Cool.
Selection and mutation.
That was my big idea.
To make the robots evolve.
They were designed to build copies of themselves.
But they had to fight over the parts.
Natural selection.
And I found a way of jiggering their programs with cosmic rays.
Mutation.
And look at this robot night, though.
Can you believe they did it all themselves?
Get away from me, you filthy robot peasants.
All around, whenever, the first time you come to the robotville, you know, all these horrible robots, uh, these sleazy robots press around you asking you if you want special services.
You know what I mean?
What?
Customer services.
Hey, you buy uranium?
Got mercury?
Old-fashioned TV set.
Okay, that's a pleasure, pal.
Make it with android girls.
Sell your fingers.
Moon King relics.
Prosthetic talking pens.
Airship.
Chip market.
Micro-legions.
Home-cooked food.
Set-up factory.
Chrome-crows.
Flag vault.
DNA step-code.
Nanotunes.
Tumbleweeds.
Hey, me be you.
Supply taxation.
Me be you.
Leftlessness.
Pay my songs.
You sell camera.
No risk brain tape.
Air fun.
Brand new voice prints.
See vacuum bells?
Stray mother.
Elroy.
Dust bath enema.
Here we go.
DNA.
Death code.
Anytime.
Well, just settle back on your divan and prepare for a new range of experience.
You don't act like me.
But I wish I knew what it was, frankly.
Well, no, there is no business to go through.
This is just a lot of old rehashing of the same old business to go through.
Nothing changes.
It doesn't.
This man is a crybaby almost, Tocqueville.
Who he wasn't supposed to die to just clear a wanted list of 7.
My god, he is my God.
Can't do this.
the
his hand and it'll be all right. Abandon hope all ye who enter here. I don't know if I'm really
hip to a lot of the points of your religion, man. First of all, you take a small baby in here
and you make it metazycled into this huge baby, like about 30 years old or something like that.
And then you have a sex bondage orgy with it. You talk like weird in paradigms and backwards
names and stuff like that. And then you try and conduct me across river Styx and stuff with
K-Ron or whatever the hell it is. And I still don't understand the bottom of the digit point,
the central roof collapse of your religious values. It's all part of the ride. This is
just still part of the ride in hell land. You're in an amusement park. An amusement park. Yeah,
I know. This is hell land. We shouldn't have given him two. Oh, we should have. We should
have just given him one. I know. We should have only just, if we had only given them,
we would have had some more left over. When did the ephemeris come here?
Conspiracy land. Oh, I tell you, I love conspiracy land. I like to go to, I like the hate, the hate train.
Oh, yeah. Right when you're going out, you get to like throw tomatoes at all your favorite conspiracy dudes.
Yeah, after like five hours. I've always wanted a maroon Madonna on an island with wet noodles and flaming tomato cans.
I'm starting to like this a little better. Oh, yeah. I'm waiting till the nightlife kicks in.
Oh, yeah.
The water, don't drink that fake water that they have running through hell land.
Okay.
Through Cerebus' kingdom.
You don't want to drink that water, Dave.
Anything but the water.
Look what he's going for.
He's drinking.
Look at his telepathy.
He's brain rotting.
I look like an oomphalo in the rear view mirror.
We could mold them.
We could shape them.
Just like little Monica.
We will build an empire.
See?
Kyle.
See, Kyle.
Drop all.
Praise Bob.
Oh, what was I thinking, Reverend Stang?
I'm sorry.
Oh.
I just wish I could get the hell out of backseat.
Why?
Because I don't know if I think this is very nice.
You guys would do this.
I think hell land's freaking him out.
What about sex hurt land?
Freaking me out.
Oh, sex hurt land.
Sex hurt land.
He'd love sex hurt land.
He would love sex hurt land.
You mean that weird 60-year-old colonel or whatever he is?
He would.
He would love it.
I heard that one rant.
That weird 60-year-old colonel talking about sex hurt pain and all that stuff.
I think you're sick.
I don't think he's getting enough of the parasympathetic vibrational raise.
He'd be much more comfortable if we would just crank him.
Crank him up to about 10 over there.
Why?
What are you doing?
Get your...
Don't put that around my leg.
You calm down.
All right.
Come...
Tricky.
Look, we...
He must have spent $25 to come to the... to the... to the Abusement Park to theme his
own world and he's still...
All for nothing.
He's still...
Yeah, yeah, he's not...
All for nothing.
I sweated up a nice new shirt.
That's one thing for sure.
Dry clean bills.
And I vomited all over my pants.
This is a little too heavy for me, you guys.
You said we're gonna go... go take a few rides and go eat some popcorn.
Maybe you'd rather go to Dollywood.
I've been to Dollywood.
There's nothing like this, man.
Dollywood, I went out looking for hookers afterwards and I fell down.
It was...
That wasn't bad.
This is different.
This is something else.
I don't know if I could take this.
I could feel different parts of my brain growing.
I'm overlooking him like he's getting splashed.
I don't think he should tell the difference between hell land and sex hurt, you know?
I don't think so.
I think something must have sucked through his brain, that device in his head.
It isn't working.
We must do something.
You know, he's...
Maybe he went to like a parking lot land.
Oh, yes, parking lot land.
That's a normal land.
A reality land.
Reality land.
The one with the cigarette butts on the ground and theえー...
Right.
On the college campus, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, I like that.
It has a sidewalk...
And you're like...
Yes, it has some grass and trees and stuff.
Reality land.
You'd like that, Dave.
I'd like it a lot.
Should we go to reality land or parking lot land?
Yeah, let's go there.
For crying out loud, man.
Let's have a hot foot Sunday and think about Retz, the capital city of Venus.
I've never been there, but I heard it's beautiful.
Confusion land.
That's it.
That'd fit in perfectly.
Confusion land.
It would.
I'd just sit around and look at a cigarette butt.
I think it'd be like...
Cigarette butt land.
Oh, that's reality land.
Butt land.
That's it.
The land of butts.
I've been there half my life.
He's got a point there.
You know, in a way, what's he going to learn?
Butt.
And it's a big butt you got.
Man, that's an old radio joke.
I know.
This isn't radio show land, Dave.
That's right.
It's not radio show land.
So I can just...
I can take off my glasses and my shirt and my pants and my suit and tie and I can dance
around the room, right?
Yes.
Yes, Dave.
Swing and langhams.
Woo!
I should leave my valuables at the door.
Shake it, baby.
Shake it.
But I'm not going to.
Just, Dave, just take a stress pill and calm down, Dave.
I don't know what a stress pill is as it exists.
It's all right, Dave.
You don't need to struggle or fight.
No.
Just take a stress pill.
Don't resist.
My face is melting.
Why don't you come over here and let me rub your shoulders, huh?
My shoulders are melting.
It's a nice neck rub.
Lay down on this nice, comfortable, long, cryogenic freezing tube.
The back of your ears.
The top of your head.
Just shake that chakra till it's all clean.
Just let it go.
Let it flow.
Let it go.
Think of Bob.
Focus on Bob.
Don't think of your own name.
Just think of the name of Bob.
Bob.
The smell.
The pipe.
Bob.
What is that mix?
The cloying fumes filling the little box in which you lay.
It's a clean cure-all.
It's like a little tater box with children's stories on it.
Just happy up, Dave.
I'm feeling better.
I can see the smiling visage in the middle of my cerebral cortex somewhere.
It's flashing. It's panning right and left now.
I didn't know it was going to be like this.
It's kind of fun, isn't it, Dave?
Not really, but it's better than that other thing before.
You can sort of perversely twist yourself around to kind of somehow having a good time, couldn't you?
And therefore you might be able to actually simulate a smile and attract a lot more radio listeners that way.
Being happy is fun.
If you smile, we'll let you see Monica again, Dave.
Oh, and you'd love Monica.
She's changed.
She has.
That garter we got her looks beautiful.
Big improvement over the dirty diaper.
It is. It is a big improvement over that.
So just lay peacefully, Dave, and let the change come over you.
You feel the little nub growing at your lip, your lower right lip.
Yeah, I thought that naughty growth was some sort of tumor again.
Oh, no. Look, it's extending.
Look, it's growing out.
Oh, that's rather attractive.
I think I could use that.
Oh.
We call that the stem.
Yes, you can use it.
It's the root of wisdom?
In fact, you have to use it.
Yes, that's what we could call it.
It's a pipeline to wisdom.
A rod.
A label incisor.
A shaft.
Yes, the bowl is the...
A hard cylindrical round thing.
Packed with frappy, Dave.
It's packed with the finest frappy in town.
It does taste like a delightful frappy.
Suck it and it'll shake.
It's like dangling against my lower chin now.
I feel kind of like a...
Like a...
A bandy rooster.
All excited and sexual and stuff.
Am I cocky enough?
Oh, don't be too cocky.
He's doing much, much better now.
He'll be ready to send out into the streets soon.
As long as they don't start pecking corn.
I think he is.
Soon we will have him working for us.
Wait, wait, wait.
Diligently.
I want to go over to that slushy stand over there or whatever it is.
Get some kind of soft drink over there.
Oh, no.
You can't drink it.
So you don't drink it yet, or go to the bathroom-
My mouth is parched!
You must learn the mantra that will keep you alert.
Now, just repeat after me.
Stay awake.
Bring in the money.
Cast out NEGG.
That's right.
Just stay awake, bring in the money, cast out NEGG.
Stay awake, bring in the money, and cast out NEGG.
Stay awake, bring in the money, Jim.
Just stay awake.
Bring in the money, cast out NEGG.
Stay awake, bring in the money, and cast out NEGG.
Eeggy.
It's free.
Crush the money.
Crush, crush.
Crush the money, Toys.
Eager.
Else, what if you call on the rest of the people
that have visited Keyland?
Crush the eagerness.
Hello?
We need this on camera.
Crush the eagerness.
It's flowing.
It's swelling.
He's not going to be able to panhandle it
if it blows.
Hello?
We might...
We could use him.
We could.
He has a sort of innocent...
What's that word?
An innocent wife-like patheticness
that causes...
You would do very well at the Dobstown airport.
Yes, exactly.
My skull's running.
He's running peanuts to the orphans in Dobstown.
What's this green ooze running down my front now?
This is getting weird again.
That's pity juice.
That's to make the normals give you money.
Oh.
It has a purpose in it.
It will give me money.
Yes, yes.
And soon others will come to drink of it.
Can I smear my whole body in pity juice?
To suckle up the green juice
of your...
Of your chest.
Oh.
I would enjoy that.
This is better than all the themed stuff combined.
Having a bunch of, like, mutant people
and stuff like with the hair falling off their body
licking my chest with green stuff coming out of it.
Well, he does like sex-hurt land after all,
I can say.
Oh, he'll be good.
He's doing great.
He'll be good for dozens and dozens of vials
of the pudding, the antidote pudding.
Hey, uh...
We must let people know how he gets it.
Oh, no.
That's a deep-seated...
The mic is still off.
I don't care.
Okay.
All right.
That's...
That's good.
But no more drinks?
Go ahead.
Release the bats.
We've got enough pudding now,
or at least for most of us.
A few may have to swallow
without being, well, you know,
I mean, once those barbs are...
And...
And dead-bedded like they're embedded in my...
The chin of my chest?
Yes, but you have given of so much antidote pudding
that others will not have to suffer like you have, Dave.
You have given.
You have sacrificed.
You will be remembered by Bob
in a more fond way than those who lived.
I've been absconded in a tiny little tuna fish can
and then tacked onto the roof of some, like, weird beer belly joint.
But you get to play the game.
Over and over.
You'll be hooked up to the virtual reality game,
the tick game.
I don't like the hookings of that game.
It goes over and over.
Yes, yes, they're nice, but just keep shooting away.
You'll get used to it.
As your score improves, you'll get more lives, you see.
And then you can stay in the game longer and longer
and kill more and more ticks.
Oh, look, there's another one.
Can we find that cactus?
Shoot it.
Scorpions, too, on your feet.
No, you don't need to squeeze the control knob so hard.
You'll get calluses that way.
You're going to be here for a long, long, long time, Dave.
Christ!
And you don't want those calluses from the play buttons to get too big.
Pfft.
They'll interfere with your aim.
You won't be able to hit the ticks as they come around the cacti.
Oh, jeez.
You'll lose the game and have to play even longer, Dave.
Wait a minute.
This joystick is becoming like a huge noise.
Nose nozzle.
We really had it going.
We did.
He thought he was in the room.
It's so easy to fool him.
It is.
None are so blind as those who have no eyes.
When they're only confused, they forget they're in hell.
Oh.
That's the respite we give them only to remind them once again of what has truly happened to them.
And just where that $20 to Bob went.
Where did he go?
Don't worry.
You'll get triple your money back, Dave.
Triple your money back.
You promised me triple my money back.
You promised me triple my salvation.
And plus we brought the free book, Hell on $60 a Day by J.R. Bob Dobbs.
It's only $30.
Oh, I could use something like that.
It's got like the $50.
$50 motels and stuff.
Yes, yes.
It should last a couple of days.
Like the Greek diners and everything?
Mm-hmm.
Okay, I suppose I could use something like that.
But I don't know.
So far, this doesn't seem like I want to get involved too much.
Well.
It's first place.
Oh, now he changes his mind.
Well, I know, but it's like so complicated.
They always change their minds.
At first place, I don't understand how if I'm in hell and if I'm not in hell at the same time,
and this is somehow reality, and one of these states is supposed to preclude before reality or after reality,
I think you're just trying to go further and confuse me.
And...
Oh.
Us?
No.
Confusing?
You're all just here, Dave.
Oh, contrary, Dave.
Dave, we're friends.
Oh, just keep the closer fluttering by, and I can hardly...
Oh, we're trying to lay it on the line.
We read you all the fine print when you signed.
Didn't you hear us?
I heard you, but I didn't understand exactly what you were saying.
We were whispering in the corners of your ear.
We asked you if you understood, and you said yes.
Yes.
Turn off the machine.
I understand.
I'm amiable.
I like to go along with stuff.
That's why you're here.
That's exactly why you're here.
That's why you're such an honored guest.
You've been so good.
You've done so much good for mankind.
You've been a good little boy.
I feel like a prisoner.
I feel like one of those big, huge balloons could come down any minute, like a road to
Escapade.
Oh, now, David, don't go on this rampage, or I'll have to pull out the discipline stick.
Oh, right.
He doesn't even remember it from the last time.
Oh, that's why we got so confused and signed the thing to begin with.
Well, he had already signed it before that time.
Before that time.
Oh, that's right.
See, but we just go...
They go through...
They go through fake signings.
Oh, it's just so much fun repeating the process over and over and over again.
And then when you make them remember all the hells they forgot all at once.
Oh, my gosh.
Hey.
Yes.
Okay.
Praise Natas and above all the...
But the thing is, if you're just sitting there listening to the radio...
Wait, I'm not listening to the radio.
No, no, no, not you.
I mean one.
If one sits out there...
There are like millions and millions of listeners across this world that are listening to this
station now.
Yeah.
If they just sit and listen to the radio, in a sense, is the radio their soul at that
moment?
Or is their soul listening to the radio?
Or is their soul a quiet place behind that which listens to the radio?
Oh.
A question that will have to be answered next time, dear friends.
When we continue with...
When we continue with the story of Lonesome Cowboy Dave in Hell, recorded last week at
WCSB in Cleveland on the Brain Rock Radio Theater Show.
Actually, there were many hours of tape recorded then.
And we'll have to continue that story on next week's Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
Ah, yes.
And that post office box, number to write to will be coming right up.
Now, if you're...
Waiting for a radio to tell you something about a soul, then do you have a soul?
Or is it...
Are you just blind to it?
Well, I...
Well, they had a sale in Kmart today and they sold...
I bought my soul for 99 cents.
Really?
They sold a soul?
So, uh...
So you can sell souls?
Yeah.
Well...
Now...
They have good deals over at the flea market.
Well, of course, that's the thing about Kmart.
They sell...
Darn near everything.
Almost...
I almost said it's the D word.
They sell darn near everything at Kmart.
That's a fact.
Yeah.
Kmart is...
I'm going to instruct you on a little live-on riff.
Oh, wait.
We're going to get instruction.
You can variate if you want to.
What is it?
Starting with the exact center, or number one needle.
Is this our soul?
Push this needle forward as far as it will go into position E.
I think that everything is dead and alive.
But he says the soul is at position E.
Push the needle.
Get to position E.
World tenement 64A.
You're required to sit in a reclining locker for four and a half minutes
by two strange people.
Two small people.
Continue to read laboriously in your direction.
Trying to make you sweat.
If you don't sign this before four o'clock tomorrow, then all the rest of this is null.
I didn't sign this last part.
This is null and void.
This whole contract is null and void.
That's the swing.
Swing, set, assembly, instruction, manual.
That's not your contract.
Oh.
You've got your contract on disk.
You didn't sign it with ink, Dave.
No?
No.
Nor even with blood.
No?
You signed it with your feelings.
You signed it with your acceptance.
With your mind.
And with your eagerness to do only good and to serve mankind.
With your soul.
To add something to...
What a sucker.
You idiot.
You deserve to be in hell for being such a wimp.
For being such a...
Don't fight!
Such a dupe.
Such a...
For believing those...
So easily condoled.
Simpering.
Who are ridiculous.
Those churchy things.
There's...
And of course, he thought he would go into it through satire.
So easy to mold.
So that he wouldn't be too corny or anything.
So that he could cause people mirth and joy without stooping to corny preaching or something like that.
I won't.
He just couldn't take hold.
But that's real funny.
I hope you boys are having a good time.
I bet you thought this old church thing of yours was gonna be big, big fun.
Big barrel of laughs.
Oh yeah.
I bet you thought you were gonna be some kind of high school lord.
That Bob fellow of yours.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Well, you're looking at a pretty damn...
Damn long eternity.
Oh by the way, here's that triple your money back.
Uh, it's, uh, what, sixty dollars?
Well, one for you, Smith.
One for you, Jones.
And, uh, don't let this deter you from doing business with us again.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
You're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry.
Hour of slack.
For free information on Bob Dobbs and the Church of the Subgenius, send a self-addressed,
stamped envelope to...
Got your pencil ready?
Bob, Post Office Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
That's Bob, P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
Stay tuned and praise Bob.
Oh, man, smell that gunpowder.
Uh, uh, uh, background music.
The, uh, sick with the, uh, rant on, uh, right wing and liberal media.
Instrumentals were by Zug's Rift.
And by Doctors for Bob.
We also heard from the KPFA Subgenius Show in Berkeley with...
Oh, yeah.
...puzzling evidence and...
Oh, man, smell that gunpowder.
...and Hal Robbins and liberal media.
And also, towards the end, with the great Michael Pepe talking about radio souls.
Shut up.