We interrupt this program to activate the emergency subgenius power of SWAT.
We don't party like a subgenius party because a subgenius party got crushed.
News on the march.
In the news here, I'm looking at the 19X Day page.
Look, some Reverend Mother Miller is on her way.
I just got a phone call from her asking if women really were free or admitted free.
So the...
Jim.
It looks like fun.
The free women are coming.
That's right.
But let's see now.
Where are we here?
There was some actual real news here.
Okay.
Well, for one thing, Pease is delayed.
Pease Doug says...
That's one way to put it.
...got screwed on a flight.
Now standby.
Called AA.
Oh, poor guy.
I guess he's got a drinking problem.
Said standby.
Those airport bars are going to kill him.
Means I...
I won't get there.
They changed to real tickets about four hours later.
And that Mother Miller said to him, have a drink and a Cinnabon.
Okay.
And you can pay for it.
So he's...
Actually, I heard I got a message.
Pease won't be in until late tonight.
Here's one from Sinfaltimus.
I'm here.
We're hoping it'll be late later.
Hey, here's Reverend Andrews.
He says...
Hey, guys.
Don't tell Heathen, but I used his spoon without asking him first.
Andrea Volkerding says...
Grr.
I am bear.
I'm here for your beer.
And it's a news article about a bear downs 36 beers and passes out at a campground.
Okay.
Is that why that spoon smelled so funny?
What about the bears stealing the spoons?
Well, there was a raccoon at Brushwood that used to steal Playboys.
Heidi Mintz says, I'll be down tomorrow with the chicken pox.
And this Reverend Miller is very excited about coming here.
And Cara says...
As I settle into heavy drinking in this town, I have named lower bunghole after my old Nissan broke down.
I am reminded that being stuck here overnight isn't totally awful because there's lots of vodka and scotch in the world.
Also, I think this town has only one cop.
I bet I could take him.
Is he on the way here?
Here's a picture of Reverend Annie, who I consider to be the best.
This is the second prettiest girl in the whole world.
And she's forlorn.
She had a selfie saying, someone please remember to fly by and pick me up on the fifth.
Shows a little bit of cleavage there.
Cleavage for Bob, as always.
She's so beautiful.
Oh, I posted the video of the kazoo duet by APO Stacy.
And Anna Mall last night, which was really a good shot, by the way.
And it says, G. Gordon Gordon says...
I'm enjoying all this without being here.
There.
But I'm with you in spirit.
I do hope the weather is better than the last time I was in Ohio.
And he was here during the terrible duray show that killed everybody.
Oh, here.
Pease has a report on X Day.
Sha-na-na.
Has reunited to open the show tonight.
People are being told, no more glass bottles.
The freeway is pretty backed up.
It's going nuts.
Hopefully you can make it through all the crowds.
And there's some pictures I posted of just a minute ago.
Oh, that's it.
Okay, that's the news.
Ah, yes, dear friends.
About this Reverend Pease fella.
He snuck into the Church of the Subgenius from Facebook, I think, about four years ago.
And at first...
We didn't know what to do with him.
On the internet, he was so charming and childlike and...
A seemingly brain-damaged way of it.
But he was just so lovable.
The bastard.
After a while, he was everybody's pal.
And he asked every newcomer to be his friend of it, too.
Well, when you have a whole bunch of subgenius friends, they do things like make up songs about you.
Special subgenius songs.
And when Pease finally got to Wisteria, there were old subgeniuses on stage.
Reverend Sinfaltmus, Reverend Angry Larry and them.
And they were playing this song of it.
He ran up to the stage and grabbed a mic and joined in.
Now, cutting out the cuss words from this song for the broadcast radio version is going to be quite a challenge.
Because the entire lyrical content is the phrase,
Fuck Pease.
What?
That was the pedal working, that wasn't me.
Fuck Pease.
That wasn't me, that was all prerecorded.
This is me.
Fuck Pease.
alguma coisa.
Fuck you.
Putt.
We came down from the top.
And did everything just fine at the stage.
We pulled out our shots.
The terms were good.
Good.
It did.
Hey, just for the quote-unquote record, we plan to do that song wrong.
Fuck Pease.
Just for the sake of it.
Everybody give it up for the fuck Pease.
And then, much to my surprise, Pease picked up one of the dozens of bass guitars lying around
and started jamming like crazy on jazz versions of old hippie songs.
¦
¦ ¦
The dog that'll never die will have the above design, but the fox that will never die.
Poor old Peasy came to Wisteria looking for Bob, but got some dizzy.
The wolf came out and bit poor Peasy, the spiders came out and bit poor Peasy, the dogs came out and bit poor Peasy, Bob came out and bit poor Peasy.
Poor Peasy! He got lost, he drove to Wisteria, but it was in Alaska.
Poor Peasy! Poor old Peasy!
Today is his last day there.
When I went back to work, my mind says, my dad taught me how to drive, and now I've become a horse driver.
This man is д outbreak of his train is Cass.
é
What's the hun 관?'
What are you? What are you?
I was a little late because you guys may not realize this in the throngs of people here, but the freeway is backed up for like 100 miles.
There's 6,000 people just waiting at the gate for registration to reopen.
.
Pretty sure what he's trying to say is fuck peace and fuck peace.
That was pretty much it.
I hated fucking up that song.
I felt sorry for it.
I would turn off it and kept singing.
It would not die!
It still won't die!
It will die!
The poor lost Reverend Pease finally found his way after terrible travails and a big fight with the airport people.
I captured that rant, by the way.
The airport people gave you some problems, Pease?
Oh, that's terrible.
He handed it right back to them, too.
He called up his friend Barack Obama and Bill Clinton and had them.
Hey, you got some action going there.
Those fascist pigs were hassling a righteous dude.
Yeah, man.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I mean, yeah, dude.
But they didn't know.
Yeah, bruh.
Is that it?
What are...
Spiritual guidance from afar.
A magnetic line of force emanating from the wisteria campground.
Calling, beckoning, irresistibly forward.
So, I don't travel a lot.
But when I do, I like to make sure I'm surrounded by clean people.
So I can remember just what it's like to be a Yeti.
My day started out at 5.30.
I was full of slack.
You guys saw my picture.
I was posed to strike out the next day and framed by Sopher!
But no!
I was immediately spoiled.
Immediately.
I got to the ticket counter.
And a lady took one look at my Bob shirt.
And she decided to help me.
Oh, she helped me.
Here's what you need to do, sonny.
It's not a ticket.
But if you run real fast.
And you get through security.
You get an X-Day.
Four hours earlier!
Now.
Here was my mistake.
I'm a master of time and space!
I didn't need her pink four hours.
I couldn't stand with those four hours in my spare time experimenting.
But no!
I trusted her.
So I went to the pink security.
And I didn't put my laptop in the bin right.
So I was pulled into a secondary inspection area.
Think about it.
Peace.
Is God's like peas in a secondary security area?
It doesn't make any sense.
And so before they can deal with my terrorist problem.
They have to make sure the mouth reader in front of me.
Isn't bringing on some kind of nefarious liquid over a ounce and a half in capacity.
Or perhaps.
He has some pornography.
Perhaps saying something to the great state of Ohio.
But regardless of all these functions.
It took these two gentlemen.
These fine agents of the TSA.
These pink agents of the conspiracy.
Over fifteen minutes.
And when they finally found the thumb sized non-bomb.
I was able to go on my way.
Needless to say I missed my flight.
And I could have lost it then.
But I have learned over the years my Yeti friends.
When she told me I was standby.
I said no.
You're on standby.
And I called Bob.
I called Bob!
Bob answered the phone.
Yeah Frank.
Peace.
What's up?
Bob!
I'm going next day.
Yeah.
They took a long drive.
Of course you're going next day.
Peace.
I'm going to be there in three days.
Guaranteed.
Well Bob they got me going standby.
They're huffed up in me.
Bob said this won't stand.
So I was on hold.
I was on hold.
But it was okay.
It was worth it.
Because the pinkest pink of them all.
Barack Obama.
Barack Obama came on the phone.
Obama.
He said Frank.
And he sounded just like Bill Clinton.
I want you to know Frank.
I got you on the very next flight out.
And I said thank you Elvis.
Barack Obama.
And now I'm here to tell you my story.
Except for one strange thing and I don't know if this guy was a sub genius or just the most
obnoxious.
his pink ever. But I watched
a man for four and a half hours
bite his fingernails
and pick the dead
flesh from his fingers and
spit it on his young
skateboard-holding son.
And that was my
trip to Hexgate.
Oh, Reverend Pease dropped his big
camera into the pond, and now he's getting
bobtied. In for a dollar,
in for a dollar. Doug!
Reverend Pease, first bobtism.
So it is.
Reverend Pease,
I know that you have been beset
by the conspiracy, and you're probably harboring
conspiracy parasites,
demons, devils, and angels,
and guardian angels, and all kinds
of supernatural things, as well as
brain-eating amoebas, who are going
very hungry right now.
Do you accept, Bob?
One second.
Oh, it's a lot warmer now.
Yeah, sure, let's do it.
Okay, go!
That's it!
Woo-hoo!
And we are out!
We're done here.
So,
this is my first
Hexgate, Hexgate,
ready for such reason.
With it comes a few observations
and
slactations to
enthrall you and
hopefully enlighten you
on your last, final hours
on this
cloudy, muddy,
dirtball, we've all heard.
Okay.
Let's get it.
Slag.
You can't chase it.
You can't find it.
It has to come to you.
You can't covet it,
although if you try, you'll get
loaded up with empty slag.
Slag.
You hear him talk about it.
You hear him trying to find it.
But here's the thing.
It's different
for you. It's different
for me. And it's different
for that guy with that weird thing.
Slag.
Talking about
Bob's Slag.
A lot of people are concerned.
They say we all know
next day is gonna be a going concern.
As we go on and on.
What should we do?
Who the fuck knows?
Slag.
Let it flow. Let it come.
Let it be. Let it run.
Slag.
Bob taught us one thing.
Maybe a few more.
He never defined
what it was. And that's how you know
it's the greatest thing he ever sold us.
Slag.
It was theirs all along.
Taken by the con.
Slag.
It's there for you.
Just let it flow.
Slag.
Thank you, brothers and sisters.
I'd like to take a moment of silence.
For silence.
See, that's what happens when you ask us to do just anything.
We'll do the opposite of whatever you tell us.
So what you should have said is, I want you to make a shit ton of noise.
Say, Doug.
Doug.
Just look at all these Dougs.
Awesome, Doug.
That's the thing.
It's everyone here tonight.
Thank you, Doug.
Somebody can make it.
I do not.
I do not understand how a guy who's been doing this.
For over 75 years.
Can write on the internet.
Don't call me Doug.
Okay.
I mean, you think that he would have some sense.
You think he would know that if you tell some geniuses to not call you Doug.
That's the first thing you're going to do.
Yes.
Look at that.
Dumbest thing I ever did.
What is that?
Because I'm pretty sure that's high ranking.
I'm sorry.
I said, don't call me Doug.
And now everyone is called Doug.
Yeah, everyone except for you.
How does it feel?
I'm sorry.
It's Doug three.
When we refer to you, you're Doug.
Well, they're.
If you don't want to be Doug, we'll be Doug.
Fine.
Well, it's funny.
The very first subgenius is when there was only ten subgeniuses.
About half of them were named Doug.
We had numbers.
I was Doug three.
I think Doug one was some guy in Houston.
We have some numbers puzzling.
Puzzling evidence isn't right.
Are you Doug the second?
I'm Doug.
Dr. Reverend Doug Esquire the second.
Then there's a Dr. Reverend Doug Esquire the senior.
Oh, God.
Why did I do that?
I don't know.
We all asked ourselves.
Since you did it, we've all been asking ourselves what you were thinking.
Not to do a thing.
Why?
We looked at you for guidance and wisdom and you were like, what the hell was he thinking?
More echoes of him asking himself, what the fuck did I just do?
What?
What did I do?
I told subgeniuses not to do something.
I asked them politely not to do something.
That's the worst.
Hey, call me Doug, everybody.
And call yourselves Doug.
That's an order.
That should work.
Too late.
No.
That one goes out to Fuck Peas.
For the tribute band, Fuck Peas.
And the Dugs.
We are the Dugs.
We're the Dugs.
We'll be here all weekend.
I thought it again.
Dave.
It's Dave.
We're on the air.
We're on the air right now?
Yeah, we're on the ear.
We're in the ether right now.
We're in the convulsing ether implementing plans against the .
Never mind.
We'll see you guys.
what Dave said.
Yeah.
That's all you gotta do.
That's all you gotta remember
is what Dave said.
Yeah.
So can you hear us okay
this time, Dave?
I can hear you okay this time.
Can you hear me okay this time?
Oh, we can hear you
loud and clear, man.
Loud and clear.
It's exciting.
It's beautiful.
It's wonderful.
Yeah, it's like
a little tummy grabber.
It gets you a little
baby boner
thinking about it
or not.
So how's the new
incoming administration
treating you, Dave?
I've been receiving
these blue letters.
They're typed on blue paper.
And they're warning me
about something.
They say if I don't shut up,
if you don't shut up,
we're gonna have to go
to some place
to learn how to concentrate
or something.
They call them
patriot camps, I told you.
Yeah, patriot camps.
We're gonna have to go
to a patriotic camp
and wave flags around
and stuff like that.
Yeah, they're...
Well, I got one of those
blue letters,
but since the ink
was also the same color blue,
I couldn't read any of it.
Yeah.
Well, it's not funny
if it's really a summons
to the patriot camps.
I thought they understood.
We're just kidding.
This is just a comedy show.
It's not like they're trying
to shut down
the complete freedom
of the press
and the First Amendment.
No.
That would be unpatriotic,
un-American.
Yeah, they wouldn't
want to do that.
I mean...
What the hell?
Why?
Just because a newspaper
or a website
might say something critical?
I thought that was
what it was all about.
what America is all about.
That's not what it's
about anymore.
What it's about now
is sucking up.
Dave, you can't talk
that way on the radio.
It's like high school
rah-rahs
cheerleading.
Inappropriate.
Red light.
That's what they say
where I work.
They say if you start...
If you use a dirty language
or something like that,
like frown thing,
or something,
they go,
red light, red light.
Because we had to watch
a film and we had to
watch a lady
go through all kinds
of weird nervous agitations.
Oh, because...
Because the bad talk
triggered the lady?
Yeah.
Because somebody
was talking bad talk
so she had to come
from corporate.
We had a big meeting.
She put an erectoral
thermometer in her ear.
And she started babbling
all the time.
She had a...
A soup's on carriage
or whatever they call it
when they bring out
numerous video cameras
and numerous TVs.
And they were running
all these things
back and forth.
And remember,
if anyone swears
an awful lot in the room,
say red light
to remind them
to keep their mouth shut
and stuff like that.
Well, Dave,
it's tough
being a special snowflake
and everyone having
to talk special
just around you.
I mean,
I don't mean you.
special snowflakes.
Yeah.
You know,
back in the day,
they used to insist
that you talk dirty
and tell race jokes
and smoke
and spit
and drink.
And pray.
And drink at lunch
and also pray.
And now you're not allowed
to do any of those things
pretty much anywhere.
Except everybody still does.
If you look behind
any successful company
or unsuccessful...
Well, there'll be
a whole lot of people
out back smoking.
Mm-hmm.
Tanned.
Yeah.
Healthy looking people.
And or drinking.
Yeah.
And or stuffing things
in their desks
that don't belong there.
Like those weird
little rabbit heads.
Rabbit heads.
Yeah.
Is that what the kids
are doing now?
Rabbit heads?
Rabbit heads.
Yeah.
That's expensive.
God.
Well, I guess rabbits
are the only animals
that aren't about
to become extinct.
Rabbits and pink boys.
Yeah.
There's a rabbit track
near my house in the snow.
And I'm glad to know
that there are still
a few of these.
Yes.
I'm glad to know
that there are still
a few of those little
fuzzy-tailed guys, too.
I'm glad there's a jackdaw
flying over my roof.
A jackdaw?
Arr.
The only true artist
is the jackdaw artist.
Say, Dave,
what do you know
about this new thing
called virtual reality?
I know you slap
a big old...
thing on your head
and you're suddenly
in an environment,
feely-weely,
I call it in the book,
where you...
you...
spatially experience
things that can't
be spatially experienced
because it's stimulating
a certain part
of your brain
past your...
past your optic nerves.
Is it safe?
Do I think...
Do you think it's safe?
No, do you think it's safe?
I think it's fun.
I just got a set.
I got a real cheap VR...
Yeah, my...
Well, get this.
I found out
I was ignorant and wrong
because I saw
the Christmas list
for my grandsons
and one of them
wanted this VR headset
and it was only 40 bucks.
And I thought,
no, virtual reality sets
cost like 500 to 1,000.
The Oculus cost 500 bucks
and a person like me
would have to buy
a whole new computer.
for 500 more
just to run it.
And I thought,
well, that's got to be
a rip-off
if it's 40 bucks
and you do it.
How do you do it?
And then I did some research.
It's like,
it works with your phone?
And then I was like,
oh, yeah,
my son tried to tell me this
about this a year ago.
It was called
Google Cardboard
and it actually did work,
but you had to build
your own headset.
Well, this Christmas,
suddenly there's
every company
on the planet
is making
a cheap VR headset
for 15 bucks.
And when I realized that,
well, I read up on it
and realized,
oh, they actually can do VR
because it makes
a little split screen
on your phone
and then the headset
just makes your phone
look big
on each eye separately.
Yeah, everybody needs
to have a big-looking phone,
you know.
I have the biggest phone
in town.
I have a bigger phone
than you do.
No, I don't.
no, I don't.
I promise I have
a bigger phone.
Mine's got more RAM
and ROM
and readout in it, too.
But I only have
one port.
There's only one plug-in.
Yeah, you probably
have more ports than me.
Anyway,
let's get on with this.
Yeah, I tried to,
I found that
I could download
these VR apps,
they call them,
and most of them
are free.
Of course,
then they,
they're free.
You're bombarded
with ads
until you give them
a dollar.
That's where they
make their money.
But it completely
controlled my mind
and made me think
it was fun
and creative
and that a lot of people
had done some real
interesting stuff with it.
So, obviously,
I have already succumbed.
And that was only
the first night.
Obviously.
So, you strapped it on
and what did it do?
I instantly wanted
to fall down on my knees
and worship
an orange-haired,
baboon.
I lost almost all
of my ability
to spell or punctuate.
I decided that I preferred
simple explanations
to anything complex.
And I realized that
the only real science book
is the Bible.
But yeah,
aside from that,
the VR stuff is really fun.
And I think it's safe
and I don't think
it changes you into,
you know,
I don't think it does
anything to your brain.
I mean,
right?
How would I know now?
Now that I've already
been defected,
I'm not going to...
That's the question.
Yeah, I'm not going to
know the difference.
My friends will have
to tell me.
You could have a deviated
septum by now, too.
Another one of the false...
No, they fixed that.
I had that.
Yeah, they fixed it.
Hear that?
Yeah.
Yeah, man.
That's not deviated at all.
I can suck snot
through both holes
in my nostrils.
Yeah, but if you continue
to go VR,
as you have...
You just discover
that you're feeling
wildly aloof
and full of painful
miscreants
and stuff like that,
it's going to be
pretty easy for you
to all of a sudden
develop a new kind of...
What I just said there.
Addiction.
To the next gimmick.
Yeah, and...
To the Trump glasses
and the Trump hearing aids.
Everything you hear
sounds like the worship
of that great, great man.
That scientist.
Scientific American
Donald Trump.
Yeah.
He knows more than
all the scientists
put together in the world.
He knows what's in every book,
in every laboratory,
in every library
in the whole world.
And I'll tell you what it is.
Words.
But they don't write good.
They don't write good anymore.
No, they don't write good.
They don't write good.
Well, you kind of
slipped into his persona
just accidentally
on purpose.
I told you,
I've been playing VR games.
Do you have an orange wig
as well?
I don't need one.
All my hair fell out
what there was of it.
And these new little
orange wispy feathers
are growing in.
Yes, and when he takes on
that persona,
he gets a virtual orange wig.
It just pops right out.
The only thing is
my hands,
they're getting tiny and weak.
I can barely
jack the car up anymore
with those tiny hands.
It's making me frustrated
and it makes me insecure.
And when I get insecure
and angry,
then I want to dominate everybody.
And insist on everything
being my way
and acting like a big,
stupid, fat baby.
But it's okay.
I've heard,
I've been told
on the VR TV
that it's okay now.
Oh, you watch the VR TV now?
Yeah, yeah.
I watch the VR TV.
So you're a Breitbart fat baby?
No, I actually,
actually they don't,
they don't offer VR.
The New York Times,
of all things,
has a really good collection
of virtual reality news
shows.
In fact,
the first one I looked at,
it was as if
I was standing
in the middle
of a celebration
at Standing Rock
and there was a bunch
of Ogallala people
singing a big song.
I was to swivel my head
around to the back
and they were behind me.
I swiveled my way
to the front
and they were in front of me.
And I looked down
and there was a great big hole
where the camera tripod
probably was.
And everything was fuzzy
and kind of blurry
and ill-defined
because it was,
yeah,
it was a,
it wasn't a,
I guess,
I guess it wasn't
the top-notch camera.
But there you were
standing at Standing Rock.
Yeah, I know.
But when I stood,
I,
and started spinning
my head around
while wearing
these blinders
and seeing something
I wasn't really,
that wasn't really around me.
Yes.
I fell over.
I was no longer
standing at Standing Rock.
I was falling
in my living room.
You really fell right over?
No, I didn't.
But that,
I'm making it,
I'm making a gag
because I think
that there is this,
I think the danger
of VR
is that you,
after you've been
fighting dinosaurs
and gang members
in VR
and driving through walls,
you get in your real car
and you,
you might drive
into a wall
because you think
you can just
turn off the headphones
or rewind.
And the reason I say that
is because
as a video editor
for a hundred years,
I would go drive home
from a long day at work
thinking that way
that I could just rewind
because I spent
a lot of my life
in a kind of
virtual reality
editing video.
Then,
about 30 years ago,
maybe only 25,
I met this guy
at a big computer convention
named Jaron Lanier
or Lanier.
And geeks will know
that that's the guy
who was trying to
trying like hell
to invent VR back then.
He and Reverend David Leavitt,
who was a subgenius,
was the guy
who's developing
the way the audio
worked in VR.
And the problem is
the audio worked,
but the video didn't
until a couple of years ago.
Well, that's a real
steak and beans idea,
but you know,
you know what the corporate
heads are going to do.
I mean, not the bodies
connected to them,
but just the heads
with the VR devices
snapped in there.
They're going to
produce a video
to produce a band
of which we've never seen
the likes of
in the last 4,000 years.
They're going to
snap down hard on it.
Or, you know.
A band?
A band.
B-A-N.
Not a band.
A band of what?
Yeah, a band of what?
What would they ban?
A band of free materials
to interact
and interlace
with the constant
billions of ideas.
I think you need
to restate that.
I think they're going
to put a band
on coach and thought.
Well, Dave,
television was invented
decades ago.
They didn't have to
put a band on it.
They know when you're
not thinking.
When the television's on, man.
So 90% of the time
they don't have to worry
about anybody.
There's nothing to ban
because they're all
on their butts
staring into the VR space
of a TV set
or their phone
or the TV set.
Or the radio set
that they're looking at
right now
as if they could see us talk.
Thank God they can't.
I didn't shave.
I'm like,
you wore the same dress
I did, Dave.
We can't be on TV
together anymore.
On one side,
so I would look
extra special
for the ladies
who are waiting here
on the show.
Well, you know,
sometimes we do have
an audience on the show.
It's rare,
but it does happen
once in a while.
At X Day.
It is rare
because most of them
know they're going to hear
the playback later
so they go do something else.
They go fornicate
with each other in the woods
while Hal and me
and whoever else
goes rattling on and on
with our brilliant
smarty pants stuff
that nobody cares about.
Well, a lot of people
come for that
and they have to get up
at 6.30 in the morning
to be able to hear it.
That's what bothers them.
No.
They only have to get up
at 6.30 in the morning
to see the saucers
not show up.
The shows are
early.
No, the shows are...
We...
Dave,
you haven't been to an X Day
in a long time,
but we don't schedule
anything before 1 o'clock
for the simple reason
that I don't get up
before 12 o'clock.
Jase,
things have changed
at X Day.
Yeah, no more bosses, man.
It's kind of late now.
It's late.
It's kind of like,
oh, the baptism?
Did I say it was
going to be at 2?
Well, let's move that to 3.
I think maybe 3
would be a little bit better.
Workers of the world unite.
Yep.
But seriously, Dave,
um,
uh,
they've already,
they've banned
sensible,
rational thought
in a lot of states
of the Union.
Kansas,
Oklahoma,
Texas,
you know,
the school books,
uh,
they don't like that.
They don't, yeah,
they don't like
that science stuff anymore.
That's for the Japs
or the Arabs
or the Chinese.
We're Bible studiers here
in the South,
apparently,
and the Midwest
and the West.
And the Northeast
and the Northwest
and the Southwest
and the Southeast.
I've seen little heart designs
from children
that say,
Standing Rock,
we stand with you.
Isn't that amazing
to know that
regular school,
I'm sure that there are
many orange baboons
and we call them
taught by evil
liberal teachers.
Well, all teachers
are communists.
Didn't you know that?
Oh, of course I knew that.
That's why it's stupid.
Only stupid people
go to college
because then they,
that turns them
into communists.
And, you know,
all those engineers,
doctors, scientists,
they're all communists now.
They don't know anything.
They can't prove
any of that stuff.
Science is just a religion.
They can't prove it.
They used to think
the world was flat.
That's how smart science is.
Wait a minute.
I don't think
any scientist
ever said
the world was flat.
Come to think of it.
Hmm.
But, you know,
that's an argument
they make.
It's a completely
false argument.
It's a lie.
They make it frequently.
But it's because
I don't think
they understand
what the word
science means.
Literally,
don't understand
the meaning
of the term.
Nor do they understand
the meaning
of the word
communist
or
fascist
Bob.
Buh.
Probably,
they don't know nothing
and they
lax it that way.
Mm-hmm.
So, we'll just
march on into the future
as cheerfully as we can
considering that they're
about to remove our legs.
Starting with the little toe
and just take a little bit
away at a time.
Yeah.
Until we're marching
on our stumps
into the future.
Yeah.
And finally,
rolling on little
motorized chairs,
but that's what
half the people
are doing voluntarily.
Yeah.
Go to the supermarket
and they don't want to
walk.
Half the people
have stumps
and they're sitting
in little
electrophonic chairs.
Yeah.
And it's getting
to where
you can roll along
in your little
electronic chair
looking at your
VR phone
with a headset on
just bumping into
other people
in wheelchairs
with headsets
in the supermarket
with all the stuff
falling off the shelves
on you.
And then you
kind of drive
past the laser
uh
self-serve
checkout
and whatever
fell into your
wheelchair
you've just bought.
You mean they don't
have radar features
on them
so it like
keeps you from
They'll have to.
They'll add those
because that kind of
thing's getting cheaper.
Everything that makes
people stupid
is getting cheaper.
And lazy, yes.
Yeah.
They call it
comfort and convenience
but in actuality
it's redundancy
of movement.
Well, they're not
going to get me.
They're not going
to get me either
because I'm going to
wear my VR device
every day.
They're not going
to get me through either.
Actually, they got me
already because I tried
on that VR
that $15 VR headpiece.
And actually
what I mostly
looked at, Dave,
was cartoons.
VR cartoons.
That's understandable.
But I don't want
to hear about you
running off
crying like a little girl
into the other room
with one of those
things on your head
trying to find
a sanctum
that you can
escape from.
Escape it to.
It's too late, man.
I caught my first
Pokemon just yesterday.
I'm not lying either.
You caught it?
I caught a Pokemon.
I caught my first Pokemon.
He was sitting
in the kitchen.
Right on our kitchen
counter.
Yep.
Oh my God.
But then after that
I couldn't find
another one.
I sucked its soul
into my phone
and then the company
responsible for it
tried to get me
to buy something.
And I haven't seen
another Pokemon
since then.
But it's probably
because I don't know
what I'm doing.
And I'm going to
have to get
my grandson,
the six-year-old,
to show me.
That's not uncommon.
Dave, haven't you
had your grandsires
show you how to do
stuff that you don't
want to know how to do?
Yeah.
Quite a bit, in fact.
Come on, Grandpa.
Come into this VR room
and learn how to
eager nerdba
with me.
What?
Yeah, just put on
your granddadden
and eager nerdba
with me.
What?
Huh?
Grandpa, you're so
out of it.
Don't you know
any goblin labba?
And that's the way
it is now.
Yeah.
Yep, I've experienced
that.
Men flying around
the moon.
Yeah, they don't do
any of that stuff
like they have to move
or any of that stuff
anymore.
Oh, it's privacy.
It's privacy.
Private companies
do that nowadays.
The owners of
private companies
do that?
Yeah, private companies
are trying to get
people on Mars now.
There's people
lining up to go
die on Mars.
I think they were
going to die before
they even get inside
the atmosphere.
Well, there's not
much of an atmosphere
to get inside of.
Well, no, they can,
they can, you know,
you can get a machine
to Mars and you can
even get one back
if you're lucky.
It's just that
they haven't solved
the radio problem.
It's a radiation problem.
So you will die.
Even if you go to Mars
and come back safely,
you're going to die
a little sooner
because of the
radiation problem.
Is radiation a problem?
In outer space,
it is a severe,
severe problem
because there's nothing
that can shield you
from it except
lead and water.
And those are
kind of heavy.
And they don't
shield you completely
because it's real,
real, real, real,
real strong in outer space.
And the only reason
it's not real, real,
real, real strong here
is because of our
powerful atmosphere.
Which is being
depleted of its
radiation protective.
Yeah.
So we're,
so it's,
don't worry about
those people,
those idiots going to Mars.
Everybody's going to die.
And everybody's
going to Mars.
But all the animals
will die first.
Then all the people.
Well, we can make up
a huge stew,
a huge non-vegetarian stew.
Oh, the animals
will come back.
Before we shove off.
But it'll take
a long time.
20 million years.
Oh.
I feel so decrepit.
I'm trying to
come to an adjunct
or conjunct
with many of these
mysterious theories
you're propounding.
And I realize
that I just haven't
done my homework.
I wanted to.
But I got so darn scared
sometimes I just
want to go into a room
by myself and cry.
Apparently,
psychiatrists are
making a killing
on the animals.
On people
who are feeling that way
during the last
month and a half.
Funny how that happens.
Ha ha.
Real funny, man.
Yeah.
SADS.
Seasonal Affective Disorder.
Post-election SADS
are the saddest
SADS of all.
It's not funny
how it happens.
It's Trumpy
Trumpy?
Yeah, it's Trumpy.
Everything is so
Trumped up in this world.
I just can't stand it.
I just feel totally
Trumped.
I just want to just
Trump everything
and just jump off a bridge.
You want to
Trump off a bridge?
Yeah,
Trump off a bridge.
I'd like to give him
a head noogie
and mess up his
yellow, orange hair.
Oh,
I'm not going to be
one of those sad,
pathetic liberals
who are going,
no, it must be a lie.
How could it be?
Because I was one of those
angry liberals
that were going,
you jerks,
if you don't get off
your butts and vote,
it's going to happen.
People who never,
ever voted before,
are going to vote this time
because they've never
been so upset before
had so many lies
thrown at them
on Twitter
and Facebook
and all that.
That's where news
comes from now, man.
Yeah.
We don't just
write the news.
We make it.
Yep.
Make.
You have
points that were succinct
and right on the money.
Well, it was
William Burroughs.
It was Burroughs Clark.
I think.
Oh, was this from
Nova Express
or was it the other one?
Naked Lunch.
When you realize
what's on the end
of your fork,
that little calf
we raised
and named
a tap-tap
is on the end
of my fork.
I'm a vegetarian
from now on.
Well, till next week.
Yeah.
Till the next
burger floats by.
In your,
in your,
in your
sacrosanct
mental abilities,
which are,
far from viewable
right now.
There's a ban
on that too.
A ban on
sacrosanct
mental abilities.
Yeah.
If you fashion
something out of dirt,
spit on it a few times
and give it a name,
you've been
muted with a lifestyle
or a possible
managerial problem.
I've heard
that's how God did it.
That's how he done it.
God
done it.
Gosh
darn it.
Dad,
Will,
really darn it.
Will dad
blame it?
Dad blame it.
Yeah.
Will heck
fire it?
Heck fire.
Yeah, Dave.
It's a tough,
it's getting me
a tough world
because it's so cold
and it's so,
so wet
and so hot
and so dry.
So confusing.
We can't complain
about the weather.
Everything's so old
and so new
and it's just,
it's all,
it's all so black
and white.
Making the complex
simple.
Well,
when,
when we're recording this,
it's a week
before Christmas.
By the way,
Dave,
next,
next year,
we're going to be
a Eurasian holiday
here.
It's been
next week
will be the
annual Christmas
rerun
because that's what
Christmas is all about.
Reruns and presents.
Beloved reruns
that you,
we force them
to be beloved
by running them
every year.
So,
it's a wonderful
hour of slack.
We'll be on the marathon
next week
with the same
old,
same old
Christmas show.
It's a compilation
of dozens
of Christmas shows
but it hasn't been
changed in 15 years
and that's
a deliberate move
on my part.
I want it to be like
that Rudolph the Red Nose
reindeer stop motion special.
It's terrible
but everybody loves it
because it's there
every year.
And that's us.
It's terrible
but there every year
nonetheless.
Yeah.
Reliably bad.
Oh boy.
I'm sorry.
That's us.
Dave, you sound like
you're really sick.
I feel like
I'm really sick.
You probably are
really sick.
I'm blowing my nose.
Did you get
your news shot
so you'd be inoculated
against the fake news?
No, they said
they were all out.
Come back tomorrow.
No, they said
come back to work tomorrow
and we'll pay you
to write some more
fake news for us.
No, you don't.
You're not one of the people.
You don't get paid
to write fake news, do you?
You have the boring
real news to report on.
No, if I say something
that anybody says
something successful
or positive,
I'm accused of
politicizing an issue.
Red light.
Safe word.
Yep.
Safe light.
Red word.
Red tube.
Give him some chicken soup.
He needs some chicken soup.
Chicken soup.
Needs some what?
Dave can't hear you
as well as everyone else.
Here's where Dave's ear.
Dave's ear is over here.
Oh, I can hear
chicken soup.
Chicken soup.
And you poop.
Poop, poop, poop, poop,
chicken soup, poop.
Yang, yang, yang, yang.
Well, that's pretty ridiculous.
I hope so.
It is
ridiculous
that makes the world
go round
like a sunshiny place.
Yeah, man.
It's sunshiny.
But you know what, Dave?
You're not going to believe this.
It's the end of the
show.
Well, almost the end
of the show.
I don't believe it.
So what does that mean?
That means you don't
know.
But, uh,
there was, there was
the half hour
part dedicated
to his penis.
And then there's
the half hour part
dedicated to
to our
penis.
Well, whatever
we do.
But...
Small hands
have big penises.
Yeah.
As you know.
What?
No.
I wasn't talking about,
I wasn't talking about genitals.
I was talking about
Reverend Pease
and the qualities
of his personality
which add up
to penis.
Yeah.
Well, if more correctly
you could say
a peas-ness.
But
that's confusing
of it.
But we're going to have to do it.
We're going to have to, uh,
we're going to have to end
the horrible show now, Dave.
We really are.
Well, I'm, I'm sorry
it was so horrible today
because I'm, I'm sick.
No, you sound fine.
But you didn't sound horrible
to us.
Well, no, we like you
to be sick, Dave.
That's why we, um,
well, oh, nothing, nothing.
It's not,
you just happen
to be sick
by accident.
It's not like we,
some conspiracy
higher-up
who happens to be
my boss
said,
Dave sounds better
when he's all sick.
So, we're going to have
the boys drop by
and put some special stuff
on his toothbrush.
He'll be sick forever.
But he'll sound
a lot funnier
on your show.
Actually, I did have
a thing today
where somebody left me
some kind of
arcane cryptic message
with a bunch of
really, really
beat-up, um,
um, insulating material.
It was green.
And I, I
couldn't understand.
I wondered if somebody
went into my house
or why they did that.
What they were trying
to show me.
And what it all means,
I don't know.
Yeah, they got you
just where they want you,
Dave.
Wondering.
Fearful.
Coward.
Paranoid.
Sick.
Looking behind chairs
and under tables
to see if there's
inside pencil sharpness.
Well, you never know
when there might be
snakes copulating
under your couch.
Although that's probably
not going to happen
in winter in Ashtabula.
That would be a great way
to spend the rest
of the winter
watching a movie.
Watching snakes
copulate under our shoes.
Move to Arkansas.
That's all I can say.
Probably hop, skip,
and jump away.
No.
Yeah, we have to
end the show, Dave.
So we're going to say bye,
but we're not going
to hang up the phone.
Bye.
And I just wanted to say
for those people that,
uh, the folks at home
that couldn't make it out,
uh, to Wisteria,
to the campsite,
to the, to the landing pad,
if you will,
for X-Day here,
uh, if you couldn't
make it out with us,
to enjoy the festivities
and be on stage
with us tonight
or tomorrow night
or then, uh,
well, I mean,
that's pretty much it, really.
But if you couldn't
make it out here
because you had, like,
car troubles
or, you know,
you got shit going
on in your family,
uh, go fuck yourself
because we all did
and we were still here.
We're here!
Fuck peace.
Fuck peace!
Yeah!
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to go deep
on that one.
That was...
Didn't want to,
didn't want to get
the real feels.
I was getting close.
It's like you're getting touchy.
Touching some hearts, man.
Whoa!
And some eyes.
It just got squishy.
Oh, yes.
I almost forgot.
Uh,
friends,
are you a subgenius?
Minister yet?
Have you joined
the church of the subgenius?
And by that I mean
actually send in your
35 bucks
payable by PayPal
or credit card
uh,
on subgenius.com
where it says
become an ordained minister
or where it says stores.
And even if you have,
do you have your
well-made Bob t-shirt
from anticonformity.com?
Do you have
your,
your Arise DVD?
Sure, you could watch it
on the internet,
but
it's not the same.
And it isn't the same.
It hasn't been kissed
by the lips of Princess Wee
who kisses every copy of Arise
that goes out.
And I sign every copy of
Book of the Subgenius.
How about that?
You can still get those from us.
But yes,
the 35 bucks for the minister's pack,
you really ought to think about it, folks.
You, you,
don't have to meet
any subgeniuses ever,
but you will have that option.
You can't come to X Day
unless you're a member.
You can't go to the, uh,
members only, uh,
kind of smarty pants internet forum
called Scrub Genius.
Uh, I, I do a lot more there
than on Facebook.
Because Facebook's just a bunch of
gimme bobs, people who can't even spell
Bob's name right.
Do you know that Princess Wee?
Yeah.
They can't, they can't even spell
Bob's name right, half of them.
They leave off the quotes.
Oh, yeah, gimme bobs.
You can tell.
It's so easy to tell.
Anyway, friends, uh,
we'll be back next week
with more X Day recordings
and hopefully with the Lonesome Cowboy.
Hopefully he won't be lonesome next week.
Rotten house old Dammit
doing over there.
Dammit, the hound dog's doing fine.
Well, thank you.
Good night and praise Bob.
Ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya-ya.