Yes, dear friends.
Thank you for calling J.B. Smith.
I will be returning to this telephone number on Tuesday,
so please leave a message for me,
and I will return your call at that time.
Thank you.
Well, another very sad moment.
A message meaning that you will not be away till Tuesday.
I don't know.
These calls are getting more and more and more expensive.
Mr. Smith, it would behold you to stay in your room
until you are called either by a major studio,
Branson, Missouri, or God.
You're missing the most important,
important thing in your life.
That is your dear friend and talent,
former star, Jonathan Winters.
Righter side?
Two words, who cares?
You know, we're only visitors.
Bye-bye, and remember the Prince of Darkness
is with us 24 hours a day.
Regardless of light,
the Prince of Darkness can deal with it.
Heavy.
This is Smith.
Please leave a message for me,
and happy Easter to you.
Here comes Peter Cottontail
Up and down the dusty trail
Yeah, the bunny song
The bunny song
Cutting through the snow
Colored eggs
How do you think the bunny does that?
Hmm?
He takes dye
Yeah, colored dye and drinks it
Sometimes purple
Sometimes red
Sometimes black
Yellow
Green
Blue
Chartreuse
Indigo
And so forth and so on
The subgenius hour of swatting
Everybody must get stoned
Thanks for calling J.B. Smith.
If you would please leave your name and telephone number,
I'll return your call just as soon as possible.
Thank you.
Yes, Mr. Smith, this is Dr. Death in Indianapolis.
I've been putting people to sleep and out of their misery for a number of years now.
The government has stepped in and slapped a lot of suits against me for doing this.
However, a lot of people have been relieved by the government.
I've going to go to my own home soil now.
Dr. Ethic不能 policy
Phew...
Oh, I got to go to the room, wait a minute, maybe I have to allege a little.
Thank you.
Quit that.
Give them a chance to help me here.
Talking to age
Yeah
but women really do?
Yeah.
We've had children with disabilities.
So some people have the same,
separate mental health levels.
and I hope you'll call me, area code 617-478-1000, Dr. Death.
And I'd be only too happy to fly out there.
The only expenses you would incur would be my flight out,
which of course would be first class because you're going to have a first class death.
And that would be out and back to Indianapolis.
I'll take care of my own arrangements at some motel near you.
And I hope that you'll get back to me in all fairness and just let me know
because I've got lots of people on my agenda and my list here.
So please let me know one way or another if you decide to take your own life or just sweat it out.
I would be only too happy to be informed.
Inform me as soon as you can, would you?
In the meantime.
As Dr. Death says, even though death is knocking at your door,
it could be tomorrow or forevermore.
Thank you.
Not clever, but the best we can do with the many patients that I've been seeing
that occasionally depress me.
Have a good day.
Yes, dear friends.
As we record this at WCSB Cleveland, tomorrow is tax day.
April 15th.
And the subgenius taxes, yeah, I'm afraid there are such things,
are going to be filed late thanks to Jonathan Winters dying.
It's tribute time.
And I've got an hour of rare, secret, unreleased, uncensored special recordings ready to go.
For you see, friends, St. Jonathan Harshman Winters III,
born on Kennedy Day, 1925, an Ohio boy,
was a huge influence on many of us older subgenius spouters and blabbermouths,
even before the Firesign Theater.
Some of you might remember Jonathan Winters only for his roles on various live TV sitcoms,
but I never saw those.
As a child, I was educated by his comedy albums, thanks to my parents.
And later, I was blown away by the stuff I'll be playing tonight,
which is mostly ad-libbed outtakes from various commercials,
and also some of the special recording sessions,
recordings which I obtained as a young assistant sound man.
Actually, friends, I found most of these recordings on the internet today,
although mine are better versions, I must say.
And thanks to Philo and Jonathan Winters' agent, Jim Smith,
heh, Agent Smith,
we also have a string of phone messages that Winters left on his agent's phone.
Now, Reverend Baby Bear did our titles,
but everything else tonight will be Jonathan Winters,
not performing in front of crowds,
but just for his old buddy or his fellow actors in various recording sessions.
And so, dear friends, please settle in for a long Winters night.
Well, the other fellas are wonderful.
The warden's a nice guy.
Here comes Mel. Hi, warden.
Hi, listen, boys.
Now, you've got to shape up.
A lot of us in our dramatic classes and clay and our fun times on Sunday,
Father Duffy.
Yes, I know, boys.
Father Duffy's a wonderful person, and I want you guys...
I didn't know the warden was a queer.
Listen, we're all queers, dear.
We're creative people.
We can put the fires out in your prison.
Just for that, your radio's taken away, Junkie.
You don't get to hear the prison jokes.
All right, uh...
Philo, some adventures.
I gotta... I'm trying to find this character here.
You're first.
I know. I'm sorry. I didn't... I lost my hand.
We're just gonna do it for time.
Okay.
Mr. Strasburg won't wait for you, dear. You're all over.
Henry Fonda gets the part, after all.
Straighten up, honey.
Tear your clothes off and live the part, Judas Priest.
It's Adam and Eve.
Don't come in here with some high-miller shoes and a dress on, for God's sake.
It's an Adam and Eve role.
Broadway will eat it up.
You got a great body and a voice.
Sing it out, honey.
Sure, you don't like to be naked, but you're getting $400 a week in Boston, New Haven,
and a thousand if you score.
We'll have an affair.
All right.
A salad should be tossed, not bossed.
That's why I, Fussy Piper, use only tender, well-mannered garlic in my chef salad dressing.
Folks!
Stop there and radio land.
Today, the Reverend R.D. Sopter will be brought to you.
A real down-to-earth religious fanatic who saves buildings and then the people.
How about that, boys and girls?
Get your decoder pins.
Forget letters on that.
I'm dissolving, Johnny. I'm dissolving.
I wonder why I don't have my own show.
I tell the truth.
Go ahead, honey.
Try to leave the park.
I'll tell you why.
Because I was kidding you.
I'm a Blue Jay.
It's another $25 Chatelle.
I got those guys all screwed up.
I had seven of them after me.
Are you really?
Why did you say you're from outer space?
Because I am.
Now, don't say that.
Have you been out there?
See, that's the important thing.
Nobody's been there.
They got six clowns.
One Marine officer and the rest of the Navy guys trying to get a piece of cement up in the air.
I believe in flying saucers.
I talked to a clown the other day.
He said, that's a lot of jazz.
I said, are you reading Popular Mechanics or looking out?
I said, I've never seen any, but there are 400 billion stars out there.
Is this the only hip planet?
Everybody's got to see everything.
They're all, you know, from Missouri.
I got to see it.
I don't believe anything.
It's going to happen, boy, when we land.
Not going to be like H.G. Wells or any of the clowns, you know, space after dark and all that.
Come in on Halloween so that it's a big joke anyway.
You know, trick or treat.
Charles Adams thing and say, hello, lady.
I'm from Mars.
Oh, you got a wonderful costume on.
All right, next.
What a great way.
We'd never attack on Christmas.
But Halloween is meat for us.
And all the little kids, welcome to Disney.
Oh, good.
Look at him, boy.
He looks all fuzzy and green and everything.
All right, we're ready to go.
Two to top, 14.
By the name, what is your last name, doctor?
I haven't figured that one out.
Well, Judas Priest, Doc.
I mean.
That's it.
Judas Priest.
Goodness.
Of course, I can tell by the secret ring.
Doctor, I'm in here because my wife, I'm not, I'm not able to score.
I hate to put it in that vein.
What do you suggest?
Well, just bring your wife or a friend.
I'm not going to put her in here.
I see what's the trouble.
I couldn't just.
You mean you take advantage of my wife?
No, no.
I take the couch out before she comes.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Yes.
Okay, Doc.
You're a wonderful person.
My little boy's going to take advantage of my little dog.
It's a sick family, Doc.
It's a very teddy bear with sawdust all over the floor.
Let's run this one down.
It'll be tight, huh?
All right, so, where are the sports?
Good afternoon, sports.
Thank you.
Well, let's move it there.
There's a beautiful lake and certainly is a beautiful lake.
A little lightning over there.
However, there's a snow storm and here is one of the all-time greats Chick Harburg.
Chick, what do you think about the game so far here at half time?
Well, it's hard to say.
Both teams have taken the air a lot, have been tremendous groundwork for both teams.
I enjoyed the Willerton High School band.
It gave me a feeling of warmth.
Yeah.
of seeing the youth of America
with 20 degrees below zero
blowing their little horns,
playing their instruments,
those girls in the naked legs,
letting America know that they're there.
Thank you, Chuck.
Jesus, pathetic.
Well, friends, that's it.
And in the meantime, don't forget
Carlton's Cool Shave.
When you step up in front of that mirror
in the morning or at night
or whenever you shave,
always go,
and the whole side of your face is open, Jack.
Done.
It was a pleasure.
Thank you, buddy.
Bye-bye.
Good to work with you.
Good luck, Gil.
To the women out there who are listening in
at our noontime program,
it's now 1.03,
and our next platter is
Roy Bean and the Beaneries.
Let's give it a listen.
G-B-E.
Jesus, Roy, you goofed on the bringer.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Um, friends, we don't have that record
with us this afternoon,
but a guy just stepped in here,
Tony Burlow,
one of the all-time great singers,
has a new record out called Fancy Fuzzies.
Ah.
How's it going with you?
Crazy, man.
Like, I've been pressing a lot of things,
and I've been flipping over your show, man.
It's too much.
I mean, like, how do you come on?
Like, steel balls and a steel striking pitchfork.
Ha, ha, ha.
What kind of a kick are you on?
It was right up in the paper here
that you were a narcotic.
Yeah, yeah, man, but like I take in the back,
I scratch wrists, you know.
Crazy.
Mm-hmm.
Well, you heard it, boys and girls out there.
Instead of exchanging those silly little baseball cards
or hearts for Valentine's Day,
be a poppy pal,
and this year, wear the real ones.
Huh?
Okay, kids.
And here's for all our little poppy pals
who sent in those dope letters.
Here's a little thing entitled
Swinging All the Way.
I dig my parents.
And fair as day,
we swing all the way.
Here you go.
Let's pick up the music.
Crazy.
You like it, Bob?
Yeah, man, like everybody moves.
Elvis is back.
Ha, ha.
Good boy.
Better than World War V.
Elvis, how do you feel?
Jesus, I never felt better.
That damn army boy like to beat this shit.
Watch where I'm on the air, Elvis.
Hey, come on.
Whew.
What'd you do over in Germany?
I told them crats by God
that I was one of the king rock and rollers,
and I told my lieutenant and the general and everything.
I told them to kiss my elbow.
Well, Elvis, I'm sorry.
I see your language is still limited.
That's right.
I don't care.
I got five million dollars.
Ha, ha.
Mm-hmm.
Here you go.
Well, you'll never record for Capitol.
I don't care.
I got moon killing it.
I put silver dollars in the machines in Vegas.
Silver dollars.
Don't know Roy Gene.
There's my agent.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He's an idiot.
Number three.
Hey.
Ha, ha, ha.
Number three.
And, friends, that was some of that Jonathan Winters material
from outtakes, I guess,
from some commercial recording doing an ad.
There's a bunch more for when he was doing
some hefty garbage bag coming up.
In fact, the one coming up after two phone messages
may be a fake.
I don't know.
It's offensive to some tender sensibilities
since its racial humor of the 60s
before white guys imitating black guys
became officially bad taste.
But, you know, if you're looking for taste in a religion,
try McDonald's or Waffle House.
That's my favorite.
It's the one I prefer.
Official bad taste food of the church and subgenius.
Ha, ha, ha.
In fact, I'll probably tack that.
The racially offensive,
offensive routine onto the end of the internet-only version of this show, which would be downloadable
at subgenius.com, but which I would not inflict upon all of the listeners of WCSB. Most of them
would probably be perfectly cool with it, but there's always somebody who just doesn't get it.
Now, friends, you know, in the world of Church of the Subgenius,
we have our own sort of Jonathan Winters, which would, of course, be Lonesome Cowboy Dave,
an uncontrolled eruption of spewing character voices and accents, which tend to go surreal
fairly quickly, as we'll probably be hearing any minute now.
As we'll probably be hearing any minute now.
With any luck, anyway.
Well, I guess Dave's time control is all over the place.
I guess.
Like the characters in his head. Princess Weave, did your parents have Jonathan Winters' comedy albums?
Oh, my goodness, yes. I definitely grew up with Jonathan Winters as part of my family,
as far as I was concerned.
But those were the clean ones?
The clean ones.
Yes. Yes. But he was a...
a huge presence in my young life.
He wasn't a small man.
No.
Yeah, I remember thinking, gosh, I wish I had the ability to suddenly go into characters like that
and sort of spout like as if I was somebody different from what I was or am,
if I even knew what that was going to be.
Oh, wait a minute.
I think I was just using somebody else's character.
And I think that is the truth, too.
Yeah.
Oh, well.
You are just using someone else's.
I've only got like five or six personalities, really, that I can call upon.
And I can't get all of them out just in front of everybody because, you know,
some people don't like to see that.
But Dave, on the other hand, can't stop.
In fact, let's see if we can stop him now.
Dave?
Hello?
Oh, there we go.
Yeah, what happened?
Are you still there?
That's not Dave.
This is a different Dave.
Yes, this is a different Dave.
This is a.k.a. Reverend Angry Lair.
Well, I was wondering when somebody would hijack Dave's place when we were waiting for Dave to call.
I know.
I heard that.
And that's why I was like, okay, well, I better call.
Uh-huh.
Oh, well, I think Dave's as good as another.
You know, I told Dave that he could only talk for ten minutes on this show.
Because it really is going to be all Jonathan Winters.
Well, that's fine.
Actually, when I thought of the news, I put all of my Jonathan Winters records on sale at Weirdsville Records.
Is that Weirdsville Records in Detroit?
I sold quite a few Jonathan Winters records at the store.
Oh, good.
Well, the stuff we're playing tonight is not on any records.
I don't.
I think.
No, I don't think so.
Well, I got the impression that his phone calls to his agent ended up on an audio book somehow.
I have hand-selected those.
Yeah.
Well.
I haven't heard any of that stuff that you've been playing on any of his records, though.
So we've got popular dead Dave, but we don't have lonesome live Dave.
Yeah.
It would be great to have a two-headed Dave show.
Yeah, Dool and Dave's.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, if you want, I can imitate Dave.
Go ahead.
Yeah.
I can do some of the other really, really weird voices that he does and kind of talk about things that are irrelevant.
About banana trees.
Stan, you know about banana trees, right?
Yeah, and rear elephants and manna trees falling from the sky.
Sure, sure, Dave.
And manna trees, yeah.
They grow up from the depths beyond the discos that are underneath the Earth's crust.
I don't know, man.
I think we need the lonesome Dave.
Right.
You're too popular of a Dave to really be that insane.
Because there is no other besides him.
So, yes, I do understand that.
And my apologies to the true lonesome.
Cowboy Dave.
But the Reverend Angry Larry cannot do him justice.
And that's fine.
That was a pretty good Dave, though.
I thought.
I think it was.
I give you your due.
Here's the other Dave.
You know, it's a series of errant urinations caused my head to spin.
And I forgot I was five minutes later than I was had I been staying in my yacht up on the.
It's okay, Dave.
We had a Dave stand in who I think I just accidentally cut off.
Because I've never had two callers.
Once you have to put the caller one on hold and then push it, punch in caller two.
But I kind of forgot.
Well, anyway, we only have five more minutes left now to talk about you and your good old buddy, Jonathan Winters.
So can you tell us any, you know, anecdotes from your.
Well, I use your affair with him.
I'm in my my affair from my affair, my actual affair.
Yeah.
Well, he was a rude man.
Sometimes we'd go to restaurants and we'd, you know, whatever I'd order, he'd want to order.
And I'd say, of course, well, that's two, you know, and then we can't share and stuff like that.
And he'd get very brushed.
One time he punched a waiter in the stomach.
Wow.
The main sail of his yacht completely naked.
Goodness.
As you remember.
Oh, yeah.
He kind of made the news for that in the early 60s.
He was one of the few.
He had a nervous breakdown, but he was just fed up with everything.
Like most.
Of us are.
And he decided to take a jaunt where where he could be the jauntiest on the main sail of his boat.
Completely.
You know, everybody hears a different story.
I heard that he climbed up on a on a like a theme park pirate ship rigging, saying he was a pirate or something and then was locked up.
But, of course, I don't think any of that actually happened.
I think he just had he had the bipolar.
And which may explain a lot.
And and he was locked up for a year voluntarily.
I think he's one of the few comedians that would, you know, talk about that back in the day.
I remember him referring to it on the albums that my parents played.
You say, oh, I better not talk about the UFOs anymore.
They'll lock me up again.
Stuff like that.
Maybe that.
Well, there was also that going around that he had made.
He had made first contact.
But.
But he also had some of the habits of his father.
So, you know, he may have seen them and they weren't really there.
Kind of like DTs or something.
Oh, man, I wish.
Do you have any of those DTs?
Because I've ran out.
Well, I've only got the ones with a little with a little yellow speckles on them and stuff.
And they keep you up for three weeks.
Not not awake.
They just keep you physically off the ground.
Right.
Yeah.
After an hour.
Yeah, I wouldn't want to.
I don't think I'd want to be that way for three.
The gluteus maximus goes first.
Your butt muscles.
You just you.
You're hanging from your butt in the air.
Yeah.
And it's a vicious drill for those who care to perform it.
Unless you're, you know, certified EMS by the state of Ohio and the city.
That's the way.
Boy, your phone sounds great.
This time.
It's a great phone, isn't it?
It's a wonderful phone.
As a matter of fact, for only fourteen ninety five, we're selling all of these phones right here.
The entire lawn here.
You're on me.
It seems like something's missing.
I'm going to try to provide what's missing.
Well, anyway.
Yeah.
Dave, I take it you were also exposed to Jonathan Winters comedy albums as a child.
Right.
And that's what happened to you, among other things.
Among other things.
Also, I used to watch this.
I would stay up late because my parents were not always in the same area as the television or the babysitter.
Right.
And I would watch Professor Irwin Corey, who also was a.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
And, you know, when Brother Dave Gardner died, nobody made a big deal about that.
Well, I liked Brother Dave Gardner quite a bit.
There were some people who didn't like him on account of.
The problem.
But, you know, we really.
I should go back to the Jonathan Winters stuff because this is the only time I'm going to do this.
And I really do have a lot of stuff that probably a lot of Jonathan Winters fans have never heard.
So.
Quite an archive of consequential and inconsequential drivel.
Well, we'll have our own style of drivel in the next weeks to come.
But this week.
You know, whenever somebody dies, that's when they get an hour of slack show about him.
Peter Bergman, Professor Chaz.
Who else have we killed and then done a tribute to?
Oh, wait.
I didn't say.
I can cut that.
But it didn't really happen.
Remember that one?
Oh, yeah, that's right.
The Katahdin Legume tribute.
And then we found out he was really alive.
That bastard.
Yeah.
They didn't kill Legume.
Those bastards.
OK.
Maybe he didn't kill Jonathan Winters either.
Who knows?
He may be with Jim Morrison and Hendrix and Janice.
All the people with J at the beginning of their names hanging out in heaven.
Jim, Janice, Jimmy, Jonathan.
Let's kill Jonathan Colton.
No.
I bet some of my listeners would be ready for that.
Well, anyway, Dave, let's go and listen to the St. Winters.
Of Ohio.
Yes.
An Ohio man.
Hello.
This is Jim Smith.
If you would leave a message for me and the nature of your call, I would appreciate it.
And I'll return it as soon as possible.
Thank you.
The nature of the call.
Well, it's a call of a very violent elderly person.
Someone close to your age.
You realize that just a few months.
May, June, July, August.
In August, you know what you're going to be.
Sixty-nine.
Yeah, that's a magic number, you know.
It's a sexual connotation.
Sixty-nine.
Swazanuf.
Well, my friend, it's the last time you'll be that.
Then you go into 7-0.
And just remember.
Remember.
The prince of darkness is really staring.
On the walls and the halls and the people with the white hair.
People with the bad rugs.
People bent over, crippled.
Drooling and screwling and grueling and stumbling and fumbling.
Using a cane.
Using their hands.
Be fewer and fewer sit-ups and, you know, push-ups and running.
You'll have stopped running, you see.
Maybe, maybe, maybe in your room in tight circles.
A few little things there.
But the body eventually turns to clay.
You heard the expression, feet of clay.
Well, get ready.
Yeah, this is Mitch.
I'm out of stir.
I need some heat.
I need some bread.
And I need a car.
Now, you told me you'd be around here at 9.30.
Like, what's happening, you know?
Can't you tell time?
You got no Mickey Mouse on your wrist.
I'm gonna have to get you one.
Yeah, tattoo it on your wrist.
It'll be 9.30.
Permanent tattoo.
So every time you say I'll see you, it'll have to be 9.30.
Do you get what I'm...
what I'm putting down?
You hear me?
Hello?
This is number two.
Another call.
A toilet of time.
A time toilet.
You'd be able to come along with us, sir.
A lot of the men are full of fever.
Dr. Mudd was sorry about the Lincoln thing,
but he likes actors,
and that's why he helped.
John Wilkes Booth.
Oh, here comes the president now.
Good evening, Mr. Lincoln.
Good evening, General Grant.
How's the war going, Ulysses?
Well, it's going great, eh?
God bless you.
Got that crazy beard on, eh, gang?
You bring any juice with you, eh?
Thank you.
I've asked you not to drink so heavily, Ulysses.
You know the war is going badly,
I'd hope that you would give me a direct liability answer.
What'd he say?
Liability answer?
Come on, Abe, all them pretty words.
You're sitting over there in Washington.
One minute you're for the colored folks,
and then you're for the union,
and you're kissing Jefferson Davis.
What kind of clown are you?
I happen to be the president of the United States.
Oh, sorry.
I've been drinking a lot, you know.
I'm gassed up and firing them mini-balls in the side of walls.
I'm going to get you for that.
Jesus, I don't know how the war is going.
We got 800,000 men, and the clowns are in Gettysburg.
I know.
I've got a little something here that Mary's been helping me with.
Four score and seven years ago.
What are you saying, Abe?
Well, it's going to be something, a message when the war's over.
And we haven't won it by a hell of a long shot yet.
And you're reading a peace thing already?
Is that right, Mrs. President?
I have asked Abe, God bless it, memorize past the four score.
I wrote the damn thing for you on a paper sack full of hard-boiled eggs.
Now, come on, Abe.
They ain't got no cue cards.
Read it, damn it.
Mary, I don't like you, just like Washington hated Martha,
made his face break out with all that damn candy.
You're a mean woman.
You have the quality sometime of a lesbian.
My two boys are half faggots.
And I'm President Judas Priest.
Mr. Lincoln, time off, Daddy.
You're too much.
Never mind there, Samuel.
I've told your people they'll be released.
You know, some cat earlier tonight on Cincinnati was going on the Underground Railroad
and he stopped at the damn hole.
Don't think that wasn't hard.
I come on like a catfish running into a trench mile.
All right, your people will be released.
God, I promise you that.
I love you, Mr. Abe.
You're all right.
I don't want to hang around that blue theater too much, though,
because some clown's going to shoot you.
I heard about that the other night.
I was sitting around Eddie's place.
Never mind, I'm not afraid.
Mr. President, looks like a fun show.
I'm sure it does.
Who's the headliner?
I think that's what they say in the trades.
It's John Wilkes Booth.
He's a fantastic actor.
Try to get rid of that habit.
Yes, it's going well.
Don't you think so, Mary?
Ah, hell, I got to take a dump, Abe.
Mary, I wish you wouldn't talk like that.
I don't know.
After all, we're sitting up here in the...
Oh, go ahead and take a dump.
Who's that clown behind the curtain?
You there!
I'm glad I killed him.
Man, I told you he was going to come behind the curtain with me.
Thank you, Samuel.
I'll make you my secretary of war.
Tell John Wilkes it's all over.
General Lee?
It's all over, and as Ulysses says,
he gave his word, you give the horses to the men,
and their land is back.
It's all over.
You fought one hell of a war.
Don't quote me on that, gentlemen, please.
I don't want to use a curse.
Well, I want to thank you, Mr. Lincoln.
Are them folks going to move all around me?
What do you mean, those folks?
I mean all them clowns.
Yeah, we're going to move around you.
What the hell you think you do?
You done lost the war, Whitey.
When I'd have seen the glory of the coming of the Lord.
That's been history again here on Station WMUD,
originating from New York.
An original picture of it could have happened, and almost did,
in the Civil War.
This is your announcer, John Burgerar.
Burgerar.
Bargerar.
Jesus, I can't even read it, friends.
Join us again next week when we present
The Monitor and the Merrimack.
Faggots killing faggots.
One with a box of cheese,
the other with a floating...
a floating barge.
There's another mini-ball.
Who's he?
It's a fun picture, friends, of it could have happened and almost did,
for the Monitor and Merrimack in the year 1863.
And now a special message about Rosalie's rosy bushes.
Do you use our Rosalie rosy bushes?
Try them.
You get your little stuff all torn up down here inside,
and your fingers full of little needle points, but they're fun.
And they bloom 14 times a year.
Why not die right with Rosalind's rosy bushes?
This is Station WXQR MUD.
And Hi-Fi and Nu-Fi.
Brought to you, and now, we're going to join the network with Galen Drake.
Here's something I like.
Every time you see a little boy, spit on him.
And now here's an old lady, Maude Frickert.
Maude, you been in here how long?
I came in here when I was three years old.
Really? That's an unusual age that they would catch us.
I'm erotic.
Catch you that early?
They didn't catch me. I come in on my own accord.
It was Easter time, and I was rolling some eggs,
and I rolled an egg across the road over into the sanitarium grounds,
and I've just been here ever since. It's a ball.
I have my own little jobs and chores.
I knit rugs and weave baskets.
I screw a lot of the day patients.
When I say screw, don't misunderstand. I mean I screw them financially.
And a lot of the guests that come in, we sock them for the rugs.
$14.95. And they feel sorry for us.
You know, we wander up.
Help us out. We're loonies.
You know, and they give us.
It's a ball. I ain't no more insane than some of these other cats.
We get out on the afternoons and watch hardball games.
Went down to see the Yankees last spring, the Red Cross.
Bunch of square clowns took us down to see that.
Junior league girls, you know.
How's it going? That's all they say.
We roll them before they take us back just for dark time.
You know, hit them in the shrub, pick off their uniforms, and get some jack out of them.
Terrible.
This is one of the most frightening programs I've ever witnessed.
And to hear some of these people and what they have to say.
And here's a man who's going to be released.
Uh, Lamar Jean Gumbadie.
Mr. Gumbadie, you've been in here some four years.
Well, how do you feel? What has the sanitarium done for you?
Well, I'll tell you.
I know, I, uh, when I come in here, I lost my mind.
And, uh, I regained it in four years.
I'm going out now into a new way of life.
Well, what will you be doing?
Well, my aim is I'm going to kill my brother-in-law first.
And, uh, it's a terrible thing to say, but I do.
I always wanted to kill him.
I wanted to kill him before I lost my mind.
And, uh, he never wrote me no cards or nothing.
My sister put me in there.
And I'm going to kill her after I kill him.
Uh, those are the two big projects I have on my mind now.
Third project is how I'm going to get a damn gun.
Uh, because being a man of taste, you know, they won't say nothing but a damn BB gun or no Count 22.
And that way you got to hold it up and get both of them at the same time.
Unless they're laying together, you can't do it.
Uh, what I aim to do is, if I can't get the gun, is just to burn their damn house down.
I know where they live over on, uh, Bexford Avenue.
And I'll just get a box of matches, you know.
Have some kid go in there, high school kid, get a box of matches.
And then I'll pour gasoline all around the house and cook them in there.
Well, I think that's a wonderful outlook.
Uh, I'm sorry to hear that that is your project, what you're going to do.
Would you lock him up now, please?
I don't think he's ready.
We don't lock up anybody here, fella.
We're locking you up.
Really?
Next week...
Caught my hand in there, you fool.
Next week from the Funny Farm, we bring you another inside story of It Can Be Fun to Be Crazy.
That's from our leader.
What is the top cigarette in the country?
Let me tell you, mother, something.
L&M's, L&M's, buddy, you know.
Let's go when the whistle blows.
Now, let's face it.
A lot of you folks out there, you know, another thing along with L&M's,
where these southern cats are at responses.
Why, uh, we have some northern folks.
It's a Jew fella.
His name is Mr. Goldie.
Mr. Goldie puts out this King Kong.
King Kong hair straightener.
And, uh, let's face it.
A lot of you cats have got kinky hair.
And the thing to do is jab some of that salve on, see?
And then you're free.
You're free.
This is the way to get the white chicks.
Ugh, mother.
That's pretty sick, isn't it?
Yes, sir, friends.
I don't think we got too many letters, do you?
Maybe just from the West Side or Harlem District.
I told Sammy Davis that one night, and I thought he'd die.
You know, he's broad-minded.
And I mean broad-minded.
White broad-minded.
He tells a lot of Ina White jokes.
I had a thing I wrote over Christmas about a family scene, you know,
and it was a thing about describing the members
and putting it into a wild vein.
There was Uncle Willie, who was a little odd, boys and girls,
in the fact that Uncle Willie used to always take all the presents,
a little bit after 12,
and center them in the center of the floor,
and take a bottle of maraschino cherries,
pour it all over.
We often thought Uncle Willie should have gone up to the funny farm,
but we just didn't have the heart to put him away.
Then there was Lamar Jean Lamar, my stepsister,
who had a husky voice.
And she used to ride up in a sleigh,
pulled by three teenagers in black leather jackets,
which was a gimmick of hers.
And she worked at the commissary over at the big depot for the Army.
And she'd ride up there in the late afternoon,
and then she'd stand there in her red Mackinaw,
I'll never forget it,
her hair flowing in the breeze,
boy, she had a long, mmm, man.
And then she'd stand there and she'd rip her Mackinaw off,
and she wouldn't have nothing on,
and she'd run over the snow,
hollering,
Jimmy Dean's alive, alive, alive.
Oh, that's some wild stuff.
Hello, this is Smith.
I should be returning to base about 8.30 this evening.
8.30 this evening.
Are you gone literally all day from 6 o'clock until after dark?
It's hard to believe, isn't it?
Yeah.
That's a full-time job.
24 hours of nothing, huh?
Just driving a white car around.
That's okay.
It's an exercise.
Keeps your arms,
if you don't want to jog,
you don't want to be out there running in the streets or on the sand,
you know, doing wind sprints,
best thing is to stay in the white car
and drive around until you're shot at.
Yeah, I like to get together and, you know,
see what's happening here,
see what the expression on the face is,
and what you're doing with your hair,
your body,
whether you're squeezing a soft rubber ball
to strengthen your fist or whatever's happening, you know.
Man, you've got to pull the chain on your mind
and pull,
pull the chain on your head and flush your mind.
Okay? Yeah.
Pull the chain on your head, man,
and flush your mind.
Okay, I've been using that
and it's starting to pick up momentum.
So, until next time, man,
I remain your obedient servant,
The Shadow.
Well, we're not leaving any names
or numbers.
This is a city and a country of paranoia.
It means that, you know,
they can use your name,
false pretenses,
and the number can be traced,
and your house can be blown up,
or you're murdered in it.
Well, the nature of the call is
what to do about the deficit.
I mean, I can't handle all this.
I mean, the little guy,
people like yourself are going to have to
take responsibility here.
You're going to have to be bitten into,
as it were.
And I'm sorry to see that.
I know what it's like.
I've been bitten into several times in the past.
Uh, mm-hmm.
All right.
And bye-bye for now.
In Toluca Lake.
Hello.
Well,
you see, it's late to me.
I'll be in bed in a half an hour.
It's 8.30.
And of course, to you,
it'll be 11.30 or 12.30, I guess.
You're on some kind of a magical tour,
I guess, preparing yourself for heavy taxation.
You better study all the papers now,
because one mistake and you're in prison.
Sit down there to take a nap.
You're like a dump.
You drop them Levi's,
sit down there where you're on the Twin Holder,
and maybe you're in one of them big hotels.
Anyway, you got to take your pants down, right?
Sit there on the crapper.
Just smoke up a storm.
Shit, ain't nobody going to bother you.
Just sit there on the stool and cut away, boy.
You know what they are.
Oh, yeah, occasionally now and then,
you get ahold of them bad, bad bowl of grits,
they'll go right on through you.
I've had them screaming mimics.
Called it the Green Apple Quickstep.
Move like a bandit, boy. That's it.
That's why I say you're going to have plenty of time there with the GIs.
Well, fellas, that is.
Or just the GIs. You know what them is.
Like the Green Apple Quickstep, like I say.
So, just sort of pick up a copy of Bugle,
or some funny papers, whatever is down around your feet.
Don't ever grab hold of nobody in the next stool.
Lose a buddy that way.
Take out a pack of them L&Ms.
Sit back and light up and...
Oh, you can't beat it.
Just too much.
Ain't it, Jed?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You better put your clothes on. Folks are starting to talk.
L&M draws easy.
All right, where's the fire? Where's the fire?
In your eyes, officer. In your eyes.
You're a fairy, aren't you?
Do you see any wings?
I think that's a mastinine remark on your part.
You great big Neanderthal person, you.
Yeah, it's just a hood with a badge.
That's the only difference.
What did you call me?
A hood, a hood.
You ought to have one right over your skull.
Jesus.
Now, watch your cursing.
I happen to be, uh, patrolman O'Brien.
Oh, tell us, old leader.
Where is your motorcycle?
Do you have the multicolored foxtails and the devil on the front?
What'll a Harley do?
Open it up on a snowy day, and then we'll see.
Oh, you damn fool.
You ran right into me.
Yes, yes, fairies can fly, can't they?
All right, well, lock him up, Joe.
Fag. Put it down. Number 367.
That's right. Take it in the prison.
I don't want to fool with him.
Get in the back seat with those devils and they'll tear your clothes off.
As in our report to the nation today, we have with us, uh, a number of important men here
that have been working on the Atlas and some of the other guided missiles.
Here with us, first of all, is, uh, Dr. Alan Duvers.
Uh, Dr. Duvers, that's all rhymes, excuse me for the pun.
Uh, Dr. Duvers, just what are they doing about the Atlas?
Uh, not a darn thing.
Uh, we put that aside.
A lot of them people went down to Montego Bay, and they're down there for about two or three months' rest.
It's a tremendous strain on all of us.
And, well, good Lord, the country here, this has been the problem all along, Doctor,
is the fact that there have been too many vacations and talk and, uh, very little work.
Well, look, I'm a scientist.
I mean, uh, I just knocked my ass out over this thing.
We're on the air, Doctor. We're on the air.
Oh, well, I don't know. I didn't know. I'm a scientist.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry out there.
But I have. I've just been working my ass off on it.
All right, cut. We're off now, Doctor.
Jesus, I have way to go.
All right, Ted, we're off the air.
Because of that, you can't say ass on the air.
Well, I guess not. Uh, shit.
The scene is an old farmhouse somewhere out there in Midwest land.
And, uh, it's summer.
And there's about that much dust in the road.
It's an old, run-down farmhouse.
And inside is an old lady, 87 years old, Grandma Frickert,
been confined to a wheelchair.
The term we use is shut-in.
The mister's been dead now some 20 years,
and she runs the place herself, along with the hired hand, Lenny,
which is 22, who helps out milk the cows and what have you.
And this is the scene. She's in the living room in her chair,
wheeling back and forth, rocking.
And over the fireplace is a, is a rifle.
And the beaded curtain's in the knotty pine pillow,
which says Niagara Falls, 1934.
And suddenly Lenny comes in with dung all over his Levi's,
and he's a good-looking Lenny is all he is, you know.
And he's standing there.
She says,
Good heavens, Lenny.
What are you doing in here?
You've never been allowed in the house.
Why, if the mister was alive, he'd kill you.
Now you get on out and get about your chores.
Lenny, what are you doing?
Good God.
You're exposing yourself.
Oh, no.
You're sick.
If I could just get over to that fireplace and get that gun, I'd, I...
You ain't gonna get over to that fireplace.
Oh, God in heaven.
Oh, if I could just get over to the telephone, I'd call Sheriff Bain.
You ain't gonna get over to the telephone.
Oh, Lenny, don't touch me, please.
I beg of you.
I'm church people.
Don't attack me.
Lenny, please.
Oh, Lenny.
Oh, oh, oh.
Hey, hey.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
That wasn't so bad, was it, Mom?
I'm going out there and get that dog out of the road.
Set the crapper up right.
Fix that fence and I'll be back.
Oh, God.
Oh, oh, mercy.
See that you don't stay away too long.
That's our chapter for today in Sex Can Be Fun.
Join us again tomorrow when the makers of aluminum screens brings you...
Grandma Brickert.
Chapter 365.
Book 12.
Sex Can Be Fun After 60.
Here's one for strictly fellas.
This is pantomime, see?
Pantomime.
Oh, right.
And the kid, it's a...
10-year-old boy in an attic.
He's up there in...
Oh, oh, oh.
Wellis, Wellis, are you up there again in the attic?
What the devil you done up there?
Wellis, I'm not doing anything, Mom.
I'm looking for my ball glove.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I'm coming, dammit, dammit, dammit.
That's a pretty second.
So, one can does the work of more.
Hefty, hefty trash can liners.
Use them.
Oh.
Hefty.
Hefty trash can liners.
Trish can liners. Use them. No kidding. A lot of the guys over at Bernie's Bar throw up in them.
And we cart it out. Okay?
When garbage starts piling up on you, use hefty trish can liners and wrap up the problem.
There's a dead cat in there that won't come out.
Let's do one more. Okay. Another.
Get down, you ding-dong, and get hefty trish can liners.
Big, strong, hefty trish can liners will hold all you can throw away.
They're leak-proof, odor-proof, plastic.
Help the container. Well, keep the container. Blow it.
Looks like help to me, isn't it, son?
Instead of keep.
That's why I was in the home for a year.
Now, let's see.
Holy cow, what am I going to do with all this garbage?
That's some mess.
I wish I had some hefty bags.
Hey, down there, old lady. You old beast.
You got any hefty bags?
Hefty, H-E-F-T-Y, hefty.
Hot damn you.
I can't help it. The house stinks.
Thanks.
There are a lot of people inside. I don't know. I think they're hippies or something.
And they've just let the place go.
I need hefty bags.
You got any?
Well, screw you.
Hey, Margaret.
I'm not going in the service.
I'm not kidding.
I'm going to hold up up here.
Ah, damn it.
I don't want to die in Chinlou, fool.
Or whatever it is.
And the lieutenant was right.
He should have killed them all.
I don't want to play with you, kid.
I'm stoned.
Oh.
But where to rake it to?
Hefty lawn cleanup bags solve that one.
They're extra big to hold lots.
Extra tough to hold up.
Extra easy to haul away.
Hefty.
Hefty lawn clean-up bags.
Use them.
Ah.
I did doo-doo.
I did it.
Pants are all full of music.
Oh.
See the doggie go away?
Under the rock is a...
Psh-s-s-s-s.
That's a snake.
Ah.
Ha ha.
Ha ha ha.
Okay.
We'll try it again, huh?
So we get it.
Cleanup bags.
Okay.
Jim Smith.
Hello, this is Jim Smith.
And please leave a message for me.
And I will return your call.
Thank you.
Beep.
Yeah, you should be getting up now.
It's 7 o'clock.
See, the hours are getting away from all of us.
And this thing, you're married to eternal sleep.
And you're going to have that, you see, anyway.
That's the bonus.
Yeah, just striking 7 now.
Yeah, about five minutes faster on the great clock.
I wanted to report here as to what's happened.
And you see, once again, I hear nothing.
I tell you, as far as being with intelligence, an intelligence unit or information,
I would not think that would be your following.
Because I'm responsible.
I'm responsible for getting back to a person who's concerned.
I don't know if I'm making myself clear.
Because the sick people, even the well people, I mean, I question how many times I'm understood.
Because a lot of times, most of my career, I've been too smart for the room.
And you've been in the room, of course, when I was talking.
And, of course, you were talking to someone else.
But I should be used to that.
I've seen it with my wife.
I've seen it with my father.
My mother.
And other would-be loved ones.
And while I was trying to perform and trying to capture the attention of a few,
what I would call today mudheads,
people were just gallivanting around with their humor.
I would like to know, Mr. Smith, what's going on here.
I'm coming down tomorrow.
You know?
So you, Mr. Smith, you said a nice thing about not hearing your voice.
The only thing is, really, I'm not, you know, you don't try to top me or interrupt.
The art of interruption.
This is the one time that silence prevails at the other end, which is semi-good.
But I'm not going to ramble on here too much longer because I'm not making a cent, as they say.
And you just wonder if the tape is in the machine or what is working.
If you can find one of those, I'd love to have one of those.
it in your in your pocket forget about your heart because i think that's probably a mattel reject
anyway in your in your in your mind what's left of that to call me you know it just uh if it means
calling me collect i guess i'll have to go to that because uh the spending of money on your part now
is i i realize your hand is deep in your in your pants but at any rate um please uh inform me one
way or another maybe maybe just drop me a card thank you so much and have a good day because
it's certainly sunny and beautiful up here i would imagine down there the only
reason it would be overcast would be from the smoke from the guns that are killing people thank
you
oh yes dear friends and that was the great jonathan winters the late great jonathan winters
um uncensored not performing for anybody but his friends or his co-workers there
you're listening to the subgenius radio ministry hour of slack from the church of the subgenius
and you can get more information on that worthy institution at subgenius.com
if you want that or you can write to subgenius at p.o box 181-417 cleveland heights ohio 44118
you'll have to play that back over and over again to write the number down
the music in the background is by the rudy schwartz project they have a new album coming out uh
full frontal klugman and we'll be advertising promos for the advertising for that soon
and uh
and with that we shall uh go right back to jonathan winters until next week
how are you how are you how are you you know goldie and i are out there in virginia we always
after a big fall day get a whole big bag of hefty
lawn cleanup bags you'll like them and if you really get up tight you can eat the bag
why not
and now goldie and i are gonna ride around the ring with you
and collect all them road apples in the hefty lawn
just scoop them in there they're a poor man's golf ball if you spray them all over the place you're gonna get a lot of money
wait you to market the box
wait
today
as traditional
organic
sighted
it
does
Cherry
out
going to
christmas
look around. You old beast. I don't need that kind of language. I'm gonna go to the manager.
I not only own this store, lady, I own the chain. Well, it's the last time I'm shopping here.
Guru, great. That's the best break I've had all day. Take your business elsewhere.
I don't need it. And take your kid and your dog. You made fun of my son? He's a creep. Ask the dog.
Here, boy. Come on, sport. Hold my arm. Back over. Now, pick the dog up.
Oh.
Okay.
Number one product. This is spossy hyacinth of potassium sulfate.
A lot of people come into my drugstore and say,
Holy Jesus Christ!
This is what we use.
It'll slow the person down to almost a screeching halt.
He becomes almost anesthetized in front of me.
Only $15. Think about it. $15.95.
But if you come in early, a dollar and a half.
You deal with me.
Now, a lot of the kids on the street, as you know only too well, being parents,
sniffing glue, smoking pumpkins, all kinds of weird things.
This puts an end to it. What's this?
This? Kalinau. Kalinau.
Nothing on the label. Don't ask me about that.
Inside those, these kids are...
Once they...
And our last.
The rest of these shelves, as you can see, are empty.
We've had sellouts like this.
People come in here. We used to have liquor on that side.
We got stone, you know. I didn't need that.
And a guy fell into the deep freeze and...
frozen out.
Sold him, though.
$136.
To a necrophiliac.
That's all for today from Mr. Grocery Man.
Good evening, everybody. This is Philana Philbert.
And as you know,
this is, uh,
uh,
last year on television was,
uh, Mr. Nat King Cole,
one of the all-time great, great cats.
I would like to explain this, first of all,
to get the show off to a great start.
We are, uh,
really expressing realism.
I'm certainly no phony cat,
and we're gonna come on strong,
pushing that type of theme.
As you can see and observe, I'm a nigger.
Now, right away, folks are getting up out of their chairs.
Already, our switchboard is lit up.
Like Christmas.
But I, you see, I wanna get that,
everybody knows we're niggers, boogies,
all kinds of words.
But we wanna stress that.
We wanna put our cars on the table.
The ace of spades.
That's a little funny for you.
Black is the ace of spades.
You've heard that.
Or coon.
We, uh, cloud, you know,
darky, smoky.
We get them all.
So I wanna use just one nigger,
if you don't mind.
I'll just stick to that.
A lot of you wanna use your own little cuties.
We're gonna have all kinds of folks on.
Jews,
and guineas,
and hunkies,
and poles,
and limeys,
krauts,
and, um,
we're gonna have on, uh,
spics,
and, uh,
we're gonna have on, uh,
we're gonna have on boogies, too.
I mean, I don't wanna, you know, be,
I don't wanna show that I'm anti-this,
or anti-that.
I'm anti-everything.
But, uh,
I'm mad at white girl.
A lot of folk right away,
see if the boys lit up again.
Uh, but, uh,
well, it was a thing.
We fell in love.
And, uh, society has frowned upon it,
but we live in Sutton Place just the same.
Um,
because we're making money,
you know,
and my daddy is Father Divine.
So, uh,
may the Lord be with you, Daddy.
He's gonna be on, too.
He's a religious boog.
And, uh,
right now, incidentally,
our sponsor's a Jew,
uh, Mr. Goldie.
Mr. Goldie has put out a great thing,
the King Kong hair straightener.
A lot of you cats, you know,
have the frightening wigs,
and, uh,
come on like spooks.
So, this puts it down, man.
I mean, oh, so much.
That's how you get the white sex.
And, uh,
right now,
we're gonna have the former mayor of New York on,
who's a guinea.
Um,
Mr. Impilateri.
I'd like to say I'm not a guinea.
I'm Italian.
Well, same thing.
I mean, that's one thing we're trying to stress
to make the people relax, Daddy.
You know, you're a guinea.
Let's face it,
they go a-wop.
Well, I wish you'd stop that,
Mr.,
uh, Philander,
whatever you're...
Philander, Philander,
that's it.
You know, relax, Daddy.
You're out, you know,
to beach up in the longshore.
Uh, but, uh,
it's true,
you screwed the people there
for a long while, didn't you?
I mean, you joined a lot of the hoods,
didn't you?
You swung pretty hard with the,
with the, uh, longshore group.
Well, I did have my difficulties.
Difficulties?
Hell, you're out.
That's obvious.
Um,
but, uh,
how do you feel about the Italians?
Do you feel...
Well, certainly,
well, how do I feel?
That's one of their silly questions,
and actually,
my being Italian,
they're a wonderful people.
Well, they kept them
in a certain part of the city.
I mean,
more or less put the monkeys
and the organ grinders
and all them people
and them, uh,
those, uh, guinea grinders,
those, uh, heroes and everything,
they bunched up that soup cap
and pizzas
and they jammed them in
right in town.
I mean,
they're not spread all over.
Well, I don't think
they can certainly go anyplace.
Well, now,
you see right away,
that's true about the guineas,
but the boogies, man,
we're all jammed into Harlem.
You know, you can't,
I had some folks up
in White Plains,
they kept the,
burn them up,
something terrible,
but on the highway,
it made it look like a crash.
Um,
well, I see our time
is running out,
and, uh,
remember,
uh, next week,
we're gonna,
we're stressing,
uh,
don't care packages
to, uh,
Confederate soldiers.
Uh,
well,
no, just,
I was just kidding, folks.
Two soldiers in Arkansas,
we are sending those
don't care packages, though,
and, uh,
next week will be
not Brotherhood Week,
but Anti-White Week.
So,
think about it, friends.
All my white friends,
my chalk people,
I call them,
and my blackies.
So, remember,
keep it cool,
you know,
and keep it down.
Good night,
and good night for Mr.,
thank you, Mr. Goldie.
Wonderful.
That's that.
That's all he says.
Oh, incidentally,
we hope we didn't
offend anybody.
B-O-B
Friends,
we're glad
you listened to this show,
and we're even more glad
that some listeners
have donated enough
to help us keep on going
for another couple of months.
Not just this show,
but subgenius.com
and all the other
archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob
and want some of that
slack back to rebound
to you,
you should go to
subgenius.com
front page,
or especially
the radio page,
or the catalog,
store pages,
and help out
financially as best you can.
Now, we know
what it's like
to be on the brink
of total poverty,
and we don't want
any subgeniuses
to make their own
situations worse.
But some of you
still have jobs.
Even five bucks
makes a big difference,
even if it's only
once a month
from enough of you.
Fifty bucks
makes an even
bigger difference.
All we're saying
is that
blowjobs
could go
the way of
Steve Jobs
if you don't
pay Dobbs.
We also take
checks and money
orders to
Subgenius Foundation,
P.O. Box
Cleveland Heights,
Ohio
44118.
Thanks for anything
you can do
to help
let there
be slack.