Bob and Bob and Bob and Bob!
By special order of the mayor of Springfield,
you are in my grudge and in full and complete pardon.
Bob! Bob, come in!
And by morning, the rest of the city was gone.
I'd say it was set.
It was incredible.
Coming up on the hour to the dining room level,
Bill Chappell.
Kids controlling the micro-bodies in our food.
Who is free to television set.
Free to telephone.
Into the computer.
The scabies of the core and the heart.
Morning.
Television?
Without portication is a disease.
The main cause of cancer, a lack of masturbation.
The heart is in sex.
No sex, no life.
You are not listening to the subgenius hour of slack.
The subgenius hour of slack is listening to you.
Welcome, dear friends, to the subgenius hour of slack.
Slack, slack, slack.
Slack, slack, slut.
Local Feng L慩
Black.
Black Death.
You can escape the plague.
Send one dollar to Bob.
Bob's on the other line, so let's go to Bob and see what Bob has to say.
Bob, are you there?
Yes, sir.
Is this the Bob that takes everybody out in the desert and lives in caves?
No, I'm just Bob, just regular Bob.
Oh, okay.
Well, you heard the other guy talking about Bob, and I saw your name, Bob, and you're calling from the same city,
and I just figured you're maybe the cave dweller guy or something.
That was crazy.
What's up, Bob?
No, I...
Sweet hour of slack, how great it is to become one with Bob.
So quit your job and get in line for the divine immaculation, J.R. Bob Dye.
Amen.
The divine immaculation, J.R. Bob Dye.
Thank you.
Be seated.
Amen.
Good morning.
Welcome to the First Church of Belbridge, a subdivision of the Church of Subgenius.
Amen.
This morning, we're going to talk about the Jehovah God.
Some of y'all actually believe there's an invisible man in the sky watching over your
ass every minute.
God knows when you've been sleeping with your neighbor.
Why?
Amen.
God knows when you've been sleeping with your neighbor's farm animal.
Bubba Tyrone.
I must resist temptation.
Get behind me, Satan.
There's a demon with a lance
inside of my pants.
Amen.
Please hit me, Bobby.
Please hit me, Bob.
I seen my neighbor's wife naked
and my penis got hard.
Please hit me, Bobby.
Please hit me, Bob.
I seen my neighbor's wife naked
and my penis got hard.
Amen.
Everybody.
He taught me.
Praise his name.
Amen.
Thank you.
Be seated, everybody.
Praise Bob.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
And that was, in fact,
the first church of Elvis
in Bob.
Here, they sent us a tape
from right here in Texas.
I wonder how they even hear
of this show here.
And there'll be more
from First Church of Elvis in Bob,
I'm sure, at some point.
We also heard a little bit
of the Crystal Methodist call in.
Live prank calls
done at our Austin DeVival.
And there'll be more of that
coming up.
Friends, you also heard
a little bit of Friday Jones,
a little bit of Reverend Felicia,
and a little bit of John Casual's
media barrage.
And friends, you know,
it's getting to be like
near to Christmas time.
Now, ain't it?
And normally,
that would be an excuse for me
to just rerun
the standard old Christmas show,
dear friends,
that you hear every single year.
And especially this year,
because this will be
the last Christmas.
There will be no more
Christmases on Earth
after this one.
But, I lost the tape.
I can't find the dang tape.
So, we've got so much
new material in
that there's no excuse
for reruns,
aside from my lack of time.
But that's okay, friends.
We've got, let me announce
very quickly,
if you happen to be
able to make it,
we have X Day Drill .5
New Year's DeVival
coming up in Austin, Texas.
New Year's, actually,
the weekend after,
after New Year's,
Saturday,
January 3rd,
dear friends,
this will be
one of the largest,
most insane DeVivals ever.
Austin, Texas,
January 3rd,
at a place called,
and this is the name
of the club,
Bob Popular.
Eh-heh.
For, um,
information about
subgenius DeVivals
and so forth,
you can call the DeVival
hotline,
which number,
I don't know where,
where the heck
is it?
While you try,
if you're serious,
call 1-888-669-2323.
All right.
Now, um,
and the confirmed guest
there will be
yours truly,
Jesus Christ,
I mean, me,
and also Jesus Christ.
I wouldn't want to imply
that I was Jesus Christ.
Dr. Katahdin Legume
is likely.
Pope Angus,
Nikki Deathchick,
and friend Sterno,
Kekever,
Pope Sterno,
of Doctors for Bob,
and get this,
X-Day,
1998,
July 5th,
well, actually,
let's say July 4th,
there won't be much
of a day on July 5th,
but July 4th,
X-Day,
big event in Brushwood,
New York,
where we do our
X-Day drills.
Doctors for Bob.
Well, the original
Doctors for Bob,
well, minus the guy
that died,
Drelloyd,
uh,
Jayner,
Sterno,
uh,
Dr. Snavely,
Eklund,
Gene Splice,
will be
the final performance
on X-Day.
Thank you.
And, uh,
what else?
Well, I'm gonna get back
to the tapes, friends.
We've got great stuff.
An amazing
Papa Joe Mama rant
from, uh,
Dr. Reverend Ed Strange's show.
We've got, uh,
and, uh,
the Crystal Methodist
prank calls.
They're kind of hard to hear,
but, uh,
they're, um,
but they're worth it.
And, uh,
we've been so busy lately,
friends,
uh,
the, the big hammer
came down, uh,
regarding our website,
which had been
a charity, uh,
situation, uh,
donated by
the University of North Carolina.
Well,
they've been
real great about it.
They, they defended it
as long as they could,
but one trustee
of the university,
too many,
got one too many lawsuits
from the Church of Science,
blah, blah, blah,
ye, and, uh,
the, uh,
uh, threats, rather.
And, um,
too many, uh,
calls from relatives,
uh, discussing
the pierced, uh,
blah, blah, blah,
close-ups on
www,
on the new
www.subgenius.com.
Um,
we have been in the,
by the time you hear
this show,
we will have fully moved
the website over,
and anything that
didn't work before
probably will work now.
Oh, what else?
What else did I,
before I go on,
there, there were
a couple of news items
I, I wanted to, uh,
mention.
Oh, giant rats.
This is very important,
uh, from the
Onan Canobite News Service.
These are the end times.
Santiago, Chile.
Chile.
A Chilean ecological group
has sounded an alarm
about two-foot-long
mutant rats
that have attacked
barnyard animals
in a suburb of Santiago.
The private Orbe news agency
said Mauricio Barraza,
uh, president of Ecologra,
believes that the rodents
had grown so large
because they fed
on the droppings
of hormone-fattened
poultry.
According to Barraza,
the giant rats burrow
in the banks of the Mapocho,
the filthy river
that crosses Santiago,
and have shocked farmers
in Maipu, a Santiago suburb,
with their vicious attacks
on chicken and small goats.
And friends,
those mutant rats
will soon be swimming north
on El Nino
to meet you and me.
And now, my reading
from, uh,
The Onion,
in this case.
I mean, this,
I love this newspaper so much.
The, the Onion
from, uh, Madison, Wisconsin.
This time I'm going to read
one of their editorials.
I, I hope I,
I'd rather have
Hedgelak of the Hildanes
himself read this.
He wrote this.
Um,
but I will try to do it justice.
I will lean back.
Now, from the microphone.
No, I have to pull this down
just a little bit.
Okay.
I am Hedgelak of the Hildanes,
and I have spoken.
The youth of today
have no valor,
no courage,
of kings,
t-shirts,
blue jeans.
When I was a young man,
we wore bone helmets
and horns that proclaimed
our kinship with valorous
deeds of courage.
We wore hair shirts
that ripped our flesh
even as we drank our mead,
and we fought for
great treasures
known across this middle earth.
My son,
Unferth the Spirited,
once sacked an entire mead hall
for a bloody boar's head
hanging from the door.
That was his treasure.
He wore it and became known
as Unferth the Boar's Head.
Where is such valor today?
Last week I spied a young man
exchanging money
for a Snickers candy bar.
Money?
Exchange?
Where is the honor
in such an act?
And further,
he did not even
stab the cashier
when he left.
I am Hedgerlach,
son of Hrothgar,
who wore Banlok,
the sword of the Skildings,
as a token of his valor.
I sacked for golds and jewels.
I've lost patience
with today's youth,
with their music
and their automobiles.
I demand Viking ships,
spears, swords,
and torture devices.
I recently saw a young maiden
taking part in a most
shameful exchange.
She was providing fellow citizens
coffee in return for paper currency.
What has happened?
What has this nation-state come to?
I want swords, fire!
I want sacking and burning!
Where is the courage in negotiation?
Without deeds of valor and courage,
how do we remember the name
of Wealthy Owl, the Peace Weaver?
We do not, I tell you.
This morning I saw a group of children
running around playing tag.
And who was killed?
No one!
There was no carnage,
no headless beast, nothing.
For what?
Again, I say nothing.
No head of the wicked Grendel,
no houses of kings,
no spoils at all.
You call this valor?
We need sacking and burning.
The whole of this Middle Earth
shall be destroyed without
the might of its people.
We will perish in the depths
of the dark abyss,
leaving no name behind.
The need of valor is urgent,
the time of reckoning imminent.
Nation's youth, hear me,
and hear me well.
I know all this, for I am Hedgelac,
prince of that fane known across the land.
And I have spoken.
An editorial from Community Voices,
the Onion newspaper, Madison.
Wisconsin.
And finally, I'm going to give you
the information, contact information,
for The Onion.
And it is, as we say,
well, it's www.theonion, one word, dot com.
You can email onion2, that's onion numeral 2,
at theonion, one word, dot com.
Or you can email me, at theonion, one word, dot com.
Or you can phone 1-800-695-4376.
Once again, that's subscription information
for The Onion, 1-800-695-4376.
Yes, and now to return to the valor.
Hello, friends, and welcome.
The sermon tonight is entitled,
The Bandwagon of Bob.
Now, how does one explain something as complex
and sophisticated as Bob's bandwagon?
The answer, my friends, is to begin at the beginning.
Since the dawn of time, humans have sought to know their god.
Who is he? What does he want with us?
What is his plan?
Literally hundreds, if not thousands of religions
have sprung up to exploit this instinctive desire
to know one's creator.
The real motives of most these religions
becomes painfully obvious over the course of time.
They dangle the circle of religion,
the so-called answers of the universe,
in front of their followers' faces,
like a carrot on the end of a stick.
If the faithful want a taste,
they need to hook up the church wagon
and pull it down the road to better reach their goal.
But alas, the ever-elusive carrot
seems to move forward as well.
Lifetimes come and go,
but few of the faithful feel any closer to their goal
than they were when their journey began.
And by then,
they're too tired and worn out
to try another route.
All religion.
Dear, dear friends,
it is not enough to hook up your wagon to the nearest religion
and pull with all your might.
Faith on your part is important,
but the faith you choose to have faith in
is equally important.
If your religion is wrong,
all the faith in the world won't make it right.
Only God has the power to make a world
of wrong religion right,
and he would never do that.
It would be bad for business.
It would bring down the morale of all the true believers,
because the true believers believe
that everything in their faith is true,
and that includes the part that says
there is only one true religion,
their religion, not the other guy's.
So which religion is right, my friends?
Well, ask yourself this.
If you were God,
which religion would you make right?
The fundamentalist religions of persecution and war?
The Christian religions of guilt and self-denial?
Or perhaps, just perhaps,
the subgenius religion of humor and self-sacrilege?
You see, a lot of folks out there don't stop to realize
that God has to listen to his own bullshit.
But he does, even more so than everyone else.
What you mumble at church, God has to listen to
a million times over as everyone else repeats the exact same thing.
Critics, they dismiss the subgenius religion
as being too diverse.
They say, oh, there's too many inconsistencies.
Or they holler, what you claim this week
contradicts what you said last week.
Well, maybe that's the entire point, my friends.
God's already heard last week's theology,
and he's tired of it, sick of it.
This week, he wants something new.
People conveniently forget what the purpose of religion is.
From God's perspective, it's not to entertain us.
It's to entertain him, God Almighty,
Savior of the Universe.
When it comes to heaven, conventional religions claim
God wants to save the most souls.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Now why the hell would he want to do a stupid thing like that?
He's got to spend the rest of eternity with those bozos.
God doesn't want quality of souls, my friends.
God wants quality.
Souls cool enough to hang out with him forever and ever.
Not to drive him crazy, that's why they believe him.
And they've got all these conspiracy religions out there, friends,
to distract the losers and boring people away from the one true religion.
And that's also why the subgenius religion is so hard to take seriously.
If we were easy to believe, everyone would want to jump on the bob wagon.
Remember, there is no such thing as space in space.
Avoid those pleasure saucers, come Edge.
Judgment Day.
Space is at a premium, and there is no such thing as extra space.
The fewer that climb aboard, the more room and board there is for the rest of us.
So forgive the subgenius if he doesn't come crawling to your door, wearing a coat and tie, begging you to join his religion.
Because the truth is, we'd just as soon watch you burn.
It's up to you to realize the right religion, my friends.
But believe me when I say that your choice will affect you, the rest of your short, pain-filled, puny little lives.
Unless, of course, you choose Bob.
Herein doth the word of Bob!
Praise Bob, amen!
Baby Bob! Baby Bob! Baby Bob! Baby Bob! Baby Bob! Baby Bob!
Responsibility only to oneself.
Life, liberty, and the pursuit of pleasure.
The new declaration of independence for the teenager around the world.
Then when it starts to fade, the old world returns to what it was.
Come over to a similar apartment in the village.
Smoke a joint. Burn a little grass.
Pot party. Roach party. Mainliner. Skin pop. Shoot some crystal.
The language of the narcotic and marijuana user.
The language of a large and ever-increasing number of teenagers.
Starting in high school on Benzedrine and Dexedrine pep pills, it is not long before many soon graduate to marijuana.
The teething biscuits to a whole generation.
The generation of adolescent psychics.
And if marijuana is the appetizer, the advent of the space age technology has provided the main course.
Lysergic acid diethylamine.
LSD, the crazy acid.
To use it is to take a trip.
A trip in the world of mystique, religion, and self-knowledge.
For others, it is a trip to the emergency ward of the nearest psychiatric hospital.
For some, it accentuates the beat.
For some, it quickens sexual desire.
For some, it is the release of sexual inhibitions.
But whatever it is, teenagers are going for it.
A drug that can be made in the kitchen sink is hard to stop.
And may be the forerunner of a new drug society out of some science fiction writer's imagination.
Will drugs pave the road to destruction?
Or will they be the structure for the now generation?
The End
is coming upon you. Your wealth has rotted and moths have eaten your clothes. Your gold and
silver are corroded. Their corrosion will testify against you and eat your flesh like fire. You have
hoarded wealth in the last days. Look, the wages you failed to pay the workmen who mowed your fields
are crying out against you. The cries of the harvesters have reached the ears of the almighty
dogs. You have lived on earth in luxury and self-indulgence. You have fattened yourselves in the day of
slaughter. You have condemned and murdered innocent men who are not opposing you. The subgenius church
is one small step away from becoming in full mystery Babylon, the adulterous harlot of revelation.
And we all know what a harlot is.
It does a harlot screws. And this harlot is going to screw you.
Amen, brother. Amen.
Thank you for listening to the Prozac Free Radio Show. We're almost out of here. First, let you know,
we won't be here next week. Lucky, finally get a vacation from the station.
I'm gonna jump in the car and just head south to warmer weather.
Well, I thought maybe we...
We might be incapacitated by a certain Rodney.
Oh, doubtful.
Although, I suspect I may be fleeing authorities. One never knows.
We'll be out in the parking lot cleaning our radiator with a toothbrush, taking those last chunks out.
See you, Rod.
The dog?
Oh.
Oh, why I'm at it, just to thank you for coming up here.
I'm going south. You guys need anything?
Yeah, I knew a car.
Oh, yeah. And while you're down in South Carolina, stop at south of the border for me and pick up a sombrero for me.
You know how to find it? Just make a left at that dead black and white dog.
Oh, yeah, the one we ran down last... Yeah, okay.
Mickey.
I know where you mean.
Oh, Mickey.
Also known as...
Mick Mick.
Oh, Mickey. Oh, Mickey.
You know, it's amazing to me that someone would pay a $3,000 reward on the head of a $25 dog.
So the head is exactly what we will deliver.
If you want the rest of the body, that'll cost you extra.
You'll find it on a stick in your front yard, Ronnie.
Dog head on a stick.
You know, in Mexico, that's a delicacy.
We'll even give it its special road rash free of charge.
Yeah, we thought about bringing you...
The whole dog, but it's a long trip from North Carolina, and one's ought to get a bit peckish on the way.
We dragged the head back behind from the illustrious station wagon window, but we nibbled on the rest the whole trip.
But if you're offering $3,000 for the whole dog, I mean, the head's got to be worth at least $1,500.
I mean, that's where the little doggy brain is housed, after all.
Well, you got to remember that.
So he probably doesn't really need the head so much.
It's the other end that he used the most.
We're holding that for final payment.
Oh, yeah.
Don't worry, Ron.
We're keeping it nice and warm for you.
We're using that aquarium tube light to keep it all nice and moist.
Wee doggies.
Brothers and sisters, this has been Prozac Free Radio.
Copyright 1997.
The Subgenius Foundation.
And the participants.
No animals were harmed during the taping of this show.
We now return your radio control to you until next week after next.
Or at least until somebody else shows up.
I'll never know how Ed Strange always gets the music to end just perfectly like that.
Friends, Reverend Strange, Dr. Legume, Joe Mama, some great ranting there,
and you will be able to access almost equally great ranting, perhaps even greater,
at the Oscars.
At the New Year's End of the World Drill .5,
sponsored by Fringeware in Austin, Texas,
at Bob Popular Club.
That's the name of the club, Bob Popular,
sponsored by Fringeware.
The idea is to pack as many mutants into one place
for the biggest freakout of the last year of our lives.
Be ready for slack like you've never experienced before.
There will be ranters and music all night.
In fact, we'll use time control to roll back the clock
and ring in the new year with noisemakers hats and even a ball drop.
I will provide the ball.
Witness the Earth anthem.
See the acid Jesus drop a dope beat.
Marvel at Pope Angus's coat of many colors.
Experience deaf chick's newest ritual of pain.
Dance, dance, dance, frop and die.
Get resurrected and do it all again.
Covet, lust, hate and hate because tomorrow will be.
Not come.
Dear friends, we'll see you there.
In the meantime, praise Saint Wanderer
for digitizing this show for the internet
and working so hard on the sub-site move this week.
Hail Wanderer!
Hail Legume!
Hail Joe Mama!
Hail Reverend Ed Strange!
Hail, um, hail yes!
Praise Bob!
And the...
Oh, this jazzy music here is from Schoolgirl.
A moral report.
A CD of German, 70s German softcore porno movie music.
Thank y'all.
Look into my eyes.
Don't seem right.
You can see it.
Don't seem right at all.
There's something, something unclean.
Yes, yes.
Like being in league with the...
That's it.
You got it right.
Divine simplicity.
You said it like it's got to be said.
Yes, no decision.
The devil.
That's who we'll have fighting on our side.
Yes, yes.
We're all input systems.
The devil.
The operators.
They had my mind.
You Had My Minds.
Not dead.
Not alive.
They had my mind.
We're all input systems.
And operators.
Not dead.
We're all input systems.
Not alive.
And operators.
Burit, advance!
Pass the bell.
Oh, don't run me out.
I called you for too much.
I can't.
Can't fool me.
They had my line.
Had my line.
My line.
If my unhappiness came up very suddenly, maybe it'll go away again.
We can keep you unhappy, son.
Give us a chance.
You're gonna have to handle reality with nothing added, sport.
The main cause of cancer is a lack of motivation.
The Juventus squad恐uched by sexual violence.
No sex no life.
No help, got to do, got to have
Lots of sweet bodies, licking, yammy
I believe that my heart will good start
The pigs want to take it away
They want us to crave till we die
I believe
We must jerk off with soft cars
Stick their dicks in the pig stash
From On the Necessity of Bestializing the Human Female by Margot Sims
Answers to the six most often asked questions about heterosexuality.
Question. What is heterosexuality?
Answer. Heterosexuality is a disease characterized by the desire for intimate physical connection
with a person or persons not of your gender.
Question. What causes heterosexuality?
Answer. No one knows exactly what causes heterosexuality.
There are reasons to believe that there are several different causes.
There seems to be a genetic predisposition to heterosexuality in certain families.
Environmental factors either cause or contribute to some cases of heterosexuality.
There is no evidence that heterosexuality is transmitted via public toilets.
Question. Who gets heterosexuality?
Answer.
Heterosexuality strikes nine out of ten Americans.
About ten percent of the population appears to have a natural immunity to the disease.
Heterosexuality strikes people of every socioeconomic class, race, and religion.
Heterosexuality is usually contracted in early childhood and, if untreated, lasts a lifetime.
Question. Is heterosexuality fatal?
Answer. Not usually.
The average life expectancy for heterosexuals is about one in one hundred percent.
The average life expectancy for a person is about one and a half years shorter than for homosexuals.
Childbirth used to be the most frequent cause of death directly attributable to heterosexuality,
but monster and obstetrician methods have greatly reduced this risk.
The biggest killer now is the IUD, intrauterine device, followed closely by the pill and enraged husbands.
Still, chances of survival are excellent.
Question. Can heterosexuality be prevented?
Answer. Not yet, but research on a vaccine has shown that it can.
The vaccine is promising.
It is hoped that an injectable serum manufactured from the tissues of healthy, i.e. homosexual donors,
will provide lifetime protection from heterosexuality in children under the age of six.
Question. Is there a cure for heterosexuality?
Answer. No.
Heterosexuality cannot usually be cured, but there is a very effective treatment that so completely controls the symptoms of heterosexuality
that nearly complete, permanent remission of the disease is possible.
Yes, you can be cured of heterosexuality.
Send $1 to Gay Bob, P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
Oh, and to think I was just wondering how Ed Strange manages to make those pieces of music in just when the person's talking.
Just by the divine luck of God.
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Friends, that was Irreverent Friday Jones with that rant by Margo Sims, What is Heterosexuality?
We heard a little bit of some ranting from Reverend Felicia.
And that thing that started off this side was The Bogwan Rag by Ludwig Sears, a subgenius we haven't heard from in a long time.
And we've got a lot of tape from him.
And I guess now it is time to go into that last Austin devival sponsored by Fringeware.
Praise Paco.
At which the Crystal Methodists performed some live on stage and also on the air prank calls
to some stations.
This was a national effort in that it was announced through the internet and so forth beforehand.
And there were calls coming into the station from all over the place.
It's kind of hard to hear, but it was quite a miracle that it worked as well as it did at all.
It was truly an interactive and disgusting thing.
So we shall proceed.
Thank you.
We hear in the background here this...
I think I disagree with you on this point.
I guess it may be Brother Russell calling this...
Okay, where do you disagree?
This Christian talk show.
I'm going to try to filter this as best I can.
I think that Heterism has a place in the church, and it did in the early days, but it's just when these authorities tried to come in.
Can you give me some examples?
Okay.
Like the church fathers, you know, they came and they made the Bible disciples.
They were the official version.
You can't add to it or take away from it.
I think the Bible says that itself, doesn't it?
Well, at least the book of Revelation does.
You know, Jesus sat down with the wine drinkers and the prostitutes.
Yeah.
He was cool with that.
Yeah, but he didn't get drunk and he didn't sleep with the prostitutes.
I mean, there's a difference between associating with befriending and hanging out with individuals and then also engaging in their practices.
Well, I mean, see, that's what my Aunt Melba said.
She's a pastor of a church, the Faith Tabernacle Outreach Ministry Mission Crusade Healing Deliverance Temple in Jesus' name.
I'll cut that out.
Let me see.
Jeff, an Aurora call.
You got Mark?
Yeah, as I said, from now on we're going to institute an IQ.
They cut the Aunt Melba reference, but then they get another one.
How do we make that?
I mean, I know you got to be under the age of 34, but let's say you got to have an IQ above 34 as well in order to call the program.
You think that's a good idea, Chris?
I think that's great, but how do I test it?
Do I ask them whether they worship Bob?
Yeah, I think that would be a good start.
Or if they live in a cave.
Jeff, an Aurora, Colorado. How you doing, Jeff?
Hi, Chris and Leif.
And Mark. Don't forget Mark.
Mark, Mark. Yes, of course.
Well, you know, I'm afraid, I don't know about the last few callers, but...
I hope you're on a little different level than that.
I think we are on another level here, Leif.
I think primarily I'm concerned about backsliding myself.
And I think you're right. We all risk backsliding into a hedonist position.
And I think that the culture today just makes it easier to go in that direction.
Well, I agree with you.
I think the culture, there's so much thrown in our face.
There's so many things out there that are available to us that, yeah, it's very difficult to be self-controlled.
It's very difficult to...
Before you put something on your credit card, before you sign a check, before you throw cash on the table,
it's difficult to stop for a moment and to think, you know, I wonder if God would like me to do something else with this money.
Maybe there's someone in need that could use this $50 that I'm going to spend on this new pair of shoes.
He's just stringing them along.
More than I.
Absolutely.
But, you know, we get caught up in the whole quickness of what...
Everyone who has called this session, we've heard so far is a crystal bad minister of such genius.
Well, I'm afraid that you put your finger on the point, Leif.
I mean, and I'm worried for my own salvation.
We should all be worried.
We should all pray every day that we don't get backslidden.
Now, the Internet, for instance, is an area where a lot of my great Christian friends got caught in a trap
because they go out there, they may keep their lives, you know, crystal clean,
but until...
until they go out and they experience vicarious...
and you never know how Satan is going to work.
He sneaks up on you.
I think the Internet, for instance, he fell into...
he fell into backslidden theology.
He became a crystal Methodist.
A crystal Methodist?
A crystal Methodist.
And that is after having spent years and years in the church.
Yeah.
Well, we...
Well, we got them all going on tonight here.
I hope I'm believing these things, folks.
If...
if any of you look to the...
stations, I apologize.
I've gone hitting the red button, bleeping these guys.
We got them coming out of the woodwork tonight.
The red button will not stop us!
The other two are from Colorado.
The other two are from Austin, and who knows where the next one...
Actually, that was a Chicago one, but I did ask them if you were...
No, that was Colorado, I think.
Yeah, the thing is, um...
the Lord here, Jesus, the real Jesus, who's be...
here,
here, posted on the internet that people should call in this station and so forth.
So, you know, it's not just Friends of the Crystal Methodists and people here in Austin.
There are folks all over the country, in theory, you know, probably not a hell of a lot of them,
maybe a dozen or so, calling this station and, you know, going,
well, I'd like to talk about hedonism in my church.
And then when they get on, you know, hopefully slowly working their way up to my church.
Oh, yeah, the church of the bleeding head of Arnold Palmer, Launcher's Society or something like that.
Sorry, aren't we a bunch of illiterates around here?
Ah, let's chew some gum and forget it.
Well, you know, let's not pretend.
Let's go to Louisiana and talk with Shiloh tonight, who's 18.
Hi, Shiloh.
Hi.
How are you tonight?
I'm fine.
What's going on with you and Jesus, Shiloh?
Yeah, you asked the question a while ago what to do about Jesus, something to that effect.
Yeah.
Well, I believe that you should renounce him and all the lies that he stands for.
Oh, we're having a fun night on Dawson McAllister Live.
Now, where did you get all that baloney, Shiloh?
Well, I was raised in Christianity as a child, and it basically made me miserable.
And after I got older, I decided to, you know, renounce Jesus Christ and join the Church of the Subgenius.
All right, let's start over again.
How were you raised in Jesus Christ now or in the church?
I went to Christian school, and I went to church, and I was force-fed the lie of Christianity.
You were what?
Force-fed the lie of Christianity.
What is the lie?
Christianity, Shiloh.
Virtually everything that it stands for and the hypocrisy that it stands for.
Wait a minute.
I mean, I can't say that I've ever run across hypocrisy in the Church of the Subgenius.
The Church of the Subgenius?
Yeah.
What is that, Shiloh?
It's basically like a cross between almost like a UFO cult and the Church of Satan.
It's a church out of Dallas.
Oh, bless your heart.
You've gotten into some demons.
You are into demons, Shiloh.
Oh, Dawson.
I am a demon.
That's what I thought.
I have all authority in Jesus Christ over you, Shiloh,
and you need to give your life back to Jesus Christ and get rid of those demons, how many there are.
You need to give those up.
Demons, let go of Shiloh in the name of Jesus Christ.
I prefer to keep my demons.
Yeah, well, you and your demons will spend eternity in hell, Shiloh.
Well, I don't believe in hell.
Well, it doesn't matter whether you believe in hell.
Jesus Christ, who is the truth, says there is a hell.
And you are...
You have been told the truth, and you know the truth,
and you have chosen in your rage to turn away from the truth.
I'm not enraged, Dawson.
In your enragement towards the Holy God, Shiloh.
I have nothing against Jesus.
It's basically his fan club that I'm against.
You said it was hypocrisy.
Yes, his fan club.
You said he was a liar, Shiloh.
Yeah, he is, but there's nothing wrong with a liar.
Shiloh, I'm going to say to you real quick here,
because I refuse to let Satan get in the way of kids.
Well, I'm all for your demonic laugh, but let me finish.
I am not going to let Satan get on the air here and sabotage this show.
When you are not open to Christ, you don't want Christ at this point,
you've turned away from Christ, you've taken on demons,
you've called yourself a demon,
I am here to tell you that the hottest place in hell
are reserved for people who had Christianity all around them
and yet refused to...
I know the hottest place in hell.
The hottest place in hell is for people who listen to Marilyn Manson.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
A hotter place in hell will be for someone like you
who heard the truth over and over again and turned away, Shiloh.
Yes, but I don't drink and I don't smoke and I don't sleep around.
I don't know a lot of Christians who do that.
I'll tell you the greatest sin there is.
The greatest sin there is, Shiloh, is rejecting Jesus Christ,
and you flat out have.
That is the greatest sin.
That is the unpardonable sin.
Mm-hmm.
The Holy Spirit says to you, Shiloh,
come to Christ, come to Christ, come to Christ,
come back to Christ, which he has done.
And I say, no, no, go away.
That's right.
That is the unpardonable sin,
and that is the sin that will take you and your demon to hell forever.
Well, at least I'll have company then.
No, you won't have company because hell is totally dark
and you're going to be totally in pain
and you will not be able to see anybody
and you will be in such agony there will be no party there.
Kind of like being in church.
Mm-hmm.
I've had enough with her.
Hang her up right now.
Do you hear that demonic laugh as she went,
I'm not going to let Satan take over these airways tonight, folks.
I refuse to.
Let's stop and pray for her, though.
When I sense there are demons, like I did the last two calls,
I'm not going to mess around.
Thank you very much.
Let's see if we can get back to hedonism.
Danny in Colorado Springs.
Hi, Danny.
Oh, hi.
Let's get back to some hedonism.
Hedonism.
Yeah.
Boy, I was listening with my girlfriend,
my girlfriend Connie,
and she is of the opinion that anything you want to do is okay.
And I'm going to an Assembly of God church,
and I feel totally fine with my denomination,
and I don't think that we can do just anything we want to do.
What do you mean?
Is she a Christian?
She says she's a Christian,
but she says that, you know, anything she wants to do is the will of God.
The will of God?
And I don't understand.
Just sit here, Danny.
The will of God?
Yeah.
Who's God?
No, the will of God.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
Anything she wants to do is the will of God.
God.
You just said God's again.
No, I said Bob.
Bob?
I said it's the will of God.
I think you're all messed up, man.
No, but...
But try to call in again and try to speak by us again, Danny, okay?
It was a good try this time.
What?
It was a good try.
God.
Okay, Bob.
Bob.
Bye.
We've got some really weird ones tonight.
That's what happens with live radio, you know.
I mean, we don't screen any of our calls.
We let everybody on, and then I kind of got to deal with them.
You know, they seem to be getting smarter.
They're catching on.
I guess maybe they finally decided to evolve.
Oh, they won't like it.
Believe me.
They won't like it.
Hey, we got a drawing real quick.
I don't believe any of these.
Drawing.
Hmm?
I don't believe any of these.
I don't believe in evolution, so I'm not going to.
I'm ready for what is rightfully mine.
I'm God, people.
You know, I deserve more than what I'm getting right now.
I own everything.
I own you.
You say, yeah, all right.
Sure you want me.
Well, we'll just see.
We'll see, man.
You ain't got to help me.
You don't have to.
You know, you can blow it off.
But you're no friend of mine.
Once I find out that you didn't help me,
and once I find out that you did not try to,
that you did not send me a letter,
and you did not do it immediately,
then I'll use that as a curse.
I'll use that to curse you with.
And I may very well send you to hell for it.
You know?
Don't think that you can't do one simple thing and go to hell.
Don't think that, because you can't.
Matter of fact,
let me explain to you the way Satan becomes Satan.
Satan used to be a holy angel, too.
Okay?
Me and Satan, me and my brother Mike,
we walked into this room where God Almighty was sitting.
And God Almighty, who was our Father,
he said, look, hey, I'll tell you all what.
Let me explain to you all what I'm going to do.
We're going to go, and we're going to live another life,
and we're going to learn the difference between bad and good.
On this planet, I'm going to make it where absolutely anything you can imagine,
anything you can comprehend,
and anything you can think about can come true.
And my brother goes, whoa, wait a second, God.
Don't do that, man.
Don't do that, because if you do that,
then they won't need you anymore.
And he said, boom, for that, you're Satan,
and you'll be Christ.
What's, what's, what's turning heads
in subgenius fashion today?
Why, it's the lonesome cowboy Dave look,
complete with all the finery.
That stylish, rakish hat with the bloody hole
from the recent suicide attempt.
That little hospital number there
with the urine and vomit stains on the front.
I mean, now that's turning heads or turning something.
Lonesome cowboy Dave, friends.
You know, I heard this song many times,
before, it's a wonderful life.
But we all know, don't we?
It ain't a wonderful life.
It's a pile of shit.
And we're all, yeah, yeah, right.
That's right, too.
And we're all living in this steaming, hunking,
holy, holy, holy, holy, holy pile of shit.
And we're trying to eke our way out.
I eke my way out with Bob Dobbs at least three or four times.
I was a mental patient in a Sebring State mental institution.
I didn't have nothing going for me.
And I was staring into the john one day,
doing my extra medications, looking at the plash of waters,
trying to do my breathing exercises.
I am somebody.
I am something.
I am going somewhere someday.
I ain't shit.
My life ain't nothing.
And then I discovered J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Somehow.
I saw him on the freeways as I was going down Route 90.
The Russians masturbating in the car with those little weird Indian shields dangling
from the rear view mirrors.
I saw him at a hot dog stand.
Newton Nathans in New York.
I saw him in a bad dream.
In a bad dream.
.
This is not a ploy to get your money.
This is a ploy to get your soul.
It's not much of a ploy.
It's gonna take work, to squeeze the juices out of each and every one of you.
Much in the same way the juices have been squeezed out of me.
I'm hardly standing.
I'm hardly alive, but I got faith in J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And I know that this force, this form of power has been little in a million years and I get
On next day, most of you are going to be dog meat.
And I'm going to be a big puppy chomping down on that cattle ration.
Yeah, you could say things are going to go from bad to worse.
There's people doing experiments out there on your mind.
They have these little prathral worms that can go through the air.
They're like remote viewers.
And when they work their way into your brain, they start eating your brains right out.
And telling you what to do.
I've been getting signals for a long time.
In fact, doctors at Sebring State had to put me on nivane to stop the voices.
I hear voices like this.
I hear hollow, hollow, hollow, hollow, hollow cries in the night.
I hear people trying to chew at my intestines.
But still I live on.
And then I hear voices like this.
Hello, David. How are you today?
How are the minerals and the trinifons?
What's doing with you and the ice baths?
Are the ice baths working today?
Voices.
Hollow voices in the dark.
Everyone in here is infected with the same kind of madness.
You all got them things growing out of the side of your heads.
You all got them weird like things that come out of your ears in the middle of the night.
And whisper commands.
You're getting them commands.
Aren't you?
And there's only one way to stop them guys.
Military intelligence.
And in the spaceships too.
See, because when they built them guys, them gray things, you know, they're clones.
They took the matter right out of our skulls.
And they stuck them right in the cockpits to fly around.
It doesn't make any sense to you. It doesn't happen.
But it's only gonna keep getting worse.
Until each and every one of you got to give up the ghost.
Just a little bit.
Jesus ain't funny.
This is...
This is horrific.
And stupid.
So what can you do?
Well, you can give the Reverend Ivan Stang your money.
Or better yet, you can give me your money.
Because I ain't promise you anything in return.
What could be better than that?
You just give me your money and I'll be as happy as shit.
And I don't know how you'll feel about it.
But I'll do it.
What?
And next Friday you have to go to the hospital once for everything.
Some shit.
Cause the
Come on.
What the fuck?
The
You fucking stop right now.
Unfortunately your memory isn't full.
This these Together.
You've got to let go of all of it.
Like a moist evacuation.
Yeah.
Like your sphincters have been treated with morphine.
Just spoot it out.
Yeah.
Release it on.
And them hammers won't come down anymore.
No more life in the factory.
No more of them hard crystal bitter tears.
Some of you are waiting for the testifiers to come down.
And them suborbital skull crystals that are going around the planet.
I don't know if you know about them or not.
But that's another thing our government is doing to us.
And it's sapping all the juices right out of us.
I don't know how much longer I can take it.
So if we were to communicate in that way, you'd all scream out praise Bob.
And I could go release this moist evacuation.
And clear my mind again.
On the count of six and a half.
One, two, three, four, five, six and a half.
Praise Bob!
Thanks.
The following broadcast is brought to you by the forces of darkness.
Makers of the world's great religions, governments, and corporations.
And when you're in the moon, have a hunkering hankering for alien smegma pie.
For a taste that's out of this world.
Try an alien smegma pie.
When the X ships come.
I mean on X day.
When the ships come down.
Each and every one of you will be led off to your own private.
Excuse me.
Little area.
Where anything you desire will be crystallized immediately for you.
Except for in case of people like me.
Who will be led into smaller rooms to be confined until the rest of it's over.
But you'll see.
Your favorite girl or your favorite guy.
And you're right in front of him.
And like a Cadillac car.
Anything you want.
Anything your heart desires.
At least this is the bullshit I've been sold on.
At least so I've been told.
By the reverie.
Oink the stinks.
Well.
I uh.
I spewed my last sputum.
It's dry.
It's very very dry.
So goodnight.
Goodnight.
Oh.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave
live at the Euclid Tavern.
Subgenius D Vival with Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
Dear friends and for more information about the church of the Subgenius
As always you can Run it.
Or send a self-addressed stamped envelope.
To Bob at post office box 140306.
Dallas Texas 752.
You can also email me personally, stang at subgenius.com.
Or you can email the church in general for faster results, slack at subgenius.com.
Jesus and the WOM unit will catch it that way.
Or check our website at www.subgenius.com.
The Crystal Methodists can be had by emailing melba at fringewear.com.
Praise Fringewear. Praise Melba.
That's melba at fringewear.com.
And what else? I've got so many cuss words to cut out of this show after I send it to the Canadian and pirate stations and the internet.
Praise Juan Derer. Praise Jesus. Praise Ugly Shiloh.
The Crystal Methodists. Chris Peterman. That crazy coot.
Reverend Felicia. Ludwig Sears. John Casual.
Friday Jones. Papa Joe Mama.
Dr. Katahdin Legume.
Reverend Edward Strange.
And everyone else involved.
And Owen, of course, here in the background.
The Flying Ryan.
The brothers.
Jimmy Ryan and his brother.
Having at it, and good night.
Oh, oh, oh, oh
You have held the same as I
Then you know what I mean
Just keep on going, don't you cry
It won't solve anything
Don't take my words to life
I'll take what I know is right
Stick to your guns and fight
Oh yeah
See I'm stuck in my ways
In my ways