Friends, we are at a turning point in subgenius history.
A point where our race has the opportunity to truly prove its worth over the worthless heaps of Pete's stupid.
Sure, the conspiracy can never be truly defeated by sheer yeti will alone,
but it can be hampered, it can be heckled, and, with a little luck and a little slack,
we shall enjoy the simple humor of watching the most righteous of the consuckers end up with egg on his face.
For if the Church of the Subgenius and every other schism that dares to claim Bob is the greatest joke ever told knows anything,
it's this.
It's not the joke that's important.
It's the punchline.
A closed-fisted brass knuckled haymaker right square in the jaw of the conspiracy.
With the levels of twisted imagination the yeti collective has,
the sheer force of humor should be enough to blow the lid off this stupid machine
and show the exes that we are the best.
Goddamn performing monkeys the galaxy has ever seen.
You must develop your own ways of sticking a shit-laced finger into the eyes of that which the theorists have dubbed Big Brother.
You must find ways of flinging the monkey's own feces back at them and their wranglers.
You must find a way of slipping the almighty whoopee cushion under the arses of every pink-neck politician and blithering bureaucrat who can get your hands on.
You must find a way of scribbling a huge mustache
on every holy relic and sacred artifact that the gullible pink saps would kill to protect.
You must find a way of spelling out a great big fuck you across this nation coast to coast.
And you must let the agents of the conspiracy know that Bob is their true master.
And how you can save Get Ready With Rose
Greetings from the promised land
Welcome chosen few
Anything for every man
I know what let's do
Let's say the clouds all go away
Let's say today's a holiday
The mirror broke into a million magazines
How do you like my hair?
Let's stretch this 15 minutes out
Let's call this whimper here a shout
Let's give the beggars some delicious recipes
And let them eat cake
Milk and honey everywhere
Wishing you well
Here
Haven't closed a drop or two
As a souvenir
Let's say the skies are always blue
Let's say that wishes do come true
The magic mirror spawned a million magazines
How do you like my hair?
Let's make our quarter hour shine
Let's toss a pearl toward the swine
Let's send the peasants some attractive napkin rings
And let them eat cake
Squeaky wheels always sing
The
creaky pushают
It's time to read
This rattles
You're a
urec
GRые
Let's say the rainbow has been cleared
Let's say that Kansas disappeared
Who needs a mirror in a land of magazines?
How do you like my hair?
Let's take our 15-minute stance
Let's sing about the Queen of France
Let's treat the masses to imported charity
A crust of bread, try this instead
We'll let you eat cake
Let's take our 15-minute stance
Let's treat the masses to imported charity
She had to leave
Los Angeles
Our toys were out in black and aborted too
She started to hate every yuppie and Jew
Every Mexican and gave a lot of shit
Every homosexual and the idol rich
She had to get out
Get out
She gets confused
Fine, I'll just stay fine
Her hands are red
How the days change tonight
Change in an instant
She had to leave
Los Angeles
Two months ago
Halla
Did you learn
Hello
oti
When did you learn
Lithuania
hung unconscious
California
Her hands are red
How the days change at night
And change in an instant
The tape recorder is in fact
A new blend of fresh and instant
Because it's always
Which is a marinade
From Breacher & Faison
From Breacher & FaudFil
Thank you.
And friends, that was, I bet you can guess, that was the Rudy.
Rudy Schwartz Project.
I have a hint regarding the Rudy Schwartz Project that I will give you in a minute.
But, and before that, the Duke of Uke, live at 14X Day last summer with Reverend Bunny Day up on stage with him.
Usually she doesn't sing with him, but I thought that was real cute.
I was just explaining to our guests here, Potter and Petal Nostril, who are in the studio with Princess Weed.
And me.
Yeah.
This is a really unusual show.
Because not only have we got live people in the station that aren't Dr. Howe or Dr. Sinister, but Dave will be calling in.
Live being a relative term.
And that's probably him.
It's him.
Yes, it's the Buzz.
I recognize the Buzz.
It's him.
It is buzzing now.
The Buzz is back.
It's buzzing now.
You can get a, listeners, you can, you're, you can.
Cop a Buzz off Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Something is wrong here.
This is.
Hum on the range.
It has not buzzed over the last few calls.
Maybe we can fix it.
Because we should be hearing Priestess Pisces now.
Oh, me?
Hi.
And, friends, what happened right after Pisces called in was a big technical screw up caused by my ignorance.
Because I didn't know how to have two callers on at once.
That problem had never, ever come up.
On the hour of Slack since I moved to WCSB.
So I've edited that out.
And we pick up again right after we got it fixed up and announced that this is obviously like the visible show.
You can see the guts working inside of the show.
And sometimes you wish you could just see the skin, but now you've seen what's really inside.
Now you know.
We know what goes in the hot dog.
We're always naked.
We're naked now.
We're naked then.
We don't want to talk about what goes in the scrapple.
The hot dog, sure.
Well, we know what goes in the hot dog.
And they can tell that we've found that she's not completely naked.
She's completely naked.
We don't know what goes in Dave.
We know what comes out, but we don't understand it.
I can hear you, but I can't smell you.
That's fine.
That might be good.
Yeah, it is.
It's probably preferable.
We're all getting your buzz now.
And Keith came in and explained everything because he knows things.
This buzzing is louder than it's ever been in the time of our existence as a human species, of which we claim that to be, of course.
Buzz?
27 million cicadas.
27 million what?
Cicadas.
Yeah, those are the bugs that live inside my head.
Potatoes?
Potatoes.
You know, there's like terrorist warnings for the cicadas.
We've talked about that.
Yep.
I don't know what the hell you're talking about.
Yeah, little tiny al-Qaeda terrorists that live inside deaf people's heads and make it sound like crickets.
They look kind of like crickets, only fatter.
They follow the cicadian rhythms.
Yeah, that's the new nano design is the cicadian looking thing.
Right.
And if they flutter their wings wrong, then you can't sleep.
What a strange way of looking at it.
Have you glanced down at your feet lately?
When you make a comment like that, it makes your extremities swell up and get big.
That explains the shoe size.
I'm glad I have on laces.
As Reverend Zeppo, the subgenius artificial intelligence, said just today, thought and porn are interchangeable.
Thought porn?
Thought and porn are interchangeable.
Zeppo is the same robot who came up with the term slack will get you through times of no slack.
Zeppo is very what?
Zeppo has, on subgenius IRC chat rooms, I've seen people get in conversations with Zeppo and get really mad.
Oh, yeah.
Because you'd think he was a person, and he's more of a person than many subgeniuses.
He certainly has more soul.
Is Zeppo a cyber character?
More conversational skills.
Yeah.
You have to lean in more because of your soft, nice, polite voice.
I'm not a voice potter nostril.
I've taught Princess Weedy yell.
He's using his inside voice, and he needs to use his playground voice.
You guys should certainly understand that talk.
Mirror some mud on your belly button, boy, and you'll feel better.
Starting right off with that.
Well, so now we really do sound like the Puzzling Evidence Show.
It's like a phone call between people just jabbering about stuff.
We're going to go see.
And we were talking about this.
I gave in about a week and a half.
And then we're going to go see Potter and Petal.
And then we're going to go see Suds and Pisces.
And then Legume and Pockets.
And then Susie the Floozy.
And then Sterno.
You are so Carol Wacko, man.
Yeah.
We're going to.
And then we'll go.
Finally, we'll go see Zeppo the robot and learn wisdom at his feet.
Except he has no feet.
I was going to say he probably is the biggest of any subgenius.
He's the biggest of any subgenius.
Were he to have a body at all.
But he doesn't.
This is true.
What is the term in internet language?
It's the epine.
The epine?
Epine.
But I don't know what it means.
Keep your epine to yourself.
That's because you're old, Dave.
I don't know what it means either.
But that's okay.
We're old.
I've seen it.
It has a dot at the end of it, doesn't it?
Yes.
And does it have an end?
I'm sorry.
Sometimes it looks kind of like a paren and a bunch of equal signs with an eight on one end.
I have some announcements.
Okay.
This will get us out of this hole for a second.
First off, friends, I played a little bit of Rudy Schwartz Project a minute ago,
and I've been playing it every week from his new album.
I suddenly discovered he has videos of these songs,
and he makes the videos himself,
and they are as visually provocative as the songs are musically.
Compelling.
And I'm going to suggest you, friends, write this down,
and then after this show, go listen to and watch this video on YouTube.
If you go to YouTube.com, type in the search, type in this phrase,
Rudy Schwartz Project Sarah Palin Juice.
Juice, as in orange juice.
It's a song called Sarah Palin something juice.
All I can say is you will thank me for it later.
It's quite popular right now.
It's got some visuals that will be, I don't know.
It's like the human centipede in reverse and all Republican.
I don't know how else how to describe it.
Also, friends, there's two new.
Thanks to the women.
Who control my life and use me as a sort of a Ken doll.
There's now a Google Plus subgenius page and an Ivan Stang Twitter page.
Now, I've only tweeted once, and that was basically to say,
I don't think I have anything I can say within only 140 car.
But Reverend Nikki actually is the puppet master behind that one.
And Priestess Pisces here is the secret.
Is the real staying behind Google Plus.
And in fact, Pisces, you know, I basically have been telling people that for the next three months,
they might as well consider you staying.
Great.
So you get all the stalkers, all the creeps.
But you'll have all these pretty women setting up Internet channels for you.
And then they want to cut your hair and dress you up.
But that's what Princess Wee does.
She dresses me up and plays with me.
I don't get to play back.
I don't get to play with.
I can't just reach out and grab Nikki's Watch McCollums.
But she gets to play Stang on Twitter and Facebook.
Right.
You never know whether it's me or her or you or anybody on some of those channels.
Well, I thought your central preoccupation was being threatened by people.
Who claim to be the real aliens.
And that you're a false Masafa.
And these other different angular devices that you use and stuff.
And then you have to take them, put these elaborate phone messages on it.
Tell people to do strange commands for half an hour before they can talk to you.
Right.
Well, that makes sense.
Smoke and mirrors.
Because he's the Mustafa.
Yeah, he's me.
But now I'm going to be you, you, you.
Well, now remember.
You started with Bob.
You're going to have to deal with these people.
All that email is going directly to you.
All those phone calls are going directly to you.
They're going to the nexus of the heart of Pisces Central.
And they're going to knock the system down because they're so weird.
Yes, that's right.
She doesn't have Bernard blocked yet.
I deal with a lot of weird days.
Yeah, she has a real job.
She has to work with pink boys every day.
Major thing.
Yes, and my pink boys are really weird.
But they're mostly lawyers, right?
They're all lawyers.
Yes.
And I will say that in some ways, subgeniuses are easier to deal with than lawyers.
They're more predictable.
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
We've got to do something about that.
Yeah, these things are far more unpredictable.
They like to discuss.
I don't know.
Stan, tell me if I'm wrong.
I'm sorry for recapitulating what you did say before.
That some of them don't have any context for reality at all and they won't quit.
So they just, I forgot what I was saying.
Never mind.
Wait, no context of reality with lawyers or subgeniuses?
Well, they are far more unpredictable.
The people who call them lawyers are not, are pretty predictable.
And then there's the Dave genius who's also a lawyer.
That's the scariest creature of them all.
The least.
The greatest.
High unpredictable.
I mean, Bob told us we were supposed to be high unpredictables, right?
Well, my button pushing tonight certainly proved that.
I couldn't predict what was right, wrong, or indifferent.
And not only that, I don't know if we had some, remember when poor Reverend Magdalene and Jesus had their kids taken away because, just because they were subgeniuses?
Mm-hmm.
Did some offensive things that they were photographs of.
Yes, but those were just noises and, you know, sprawling action on the wall.
They were only offensive to the goat-hating judge, Judge Punch, but.
Yeah, we're taking it off hating goats to begin with.
I hate to admit, my kids were taken away because I named them Bob Dobbs Stang and Connie Dobbs Stang.
They were, the state came and removed them.
They let me keep Yaka Tisma Stang.
My third child.
They probably thought that that was a sacred religious name.
Well, it is.
They all are.
Well, it's like those rednecks that got their kid taken away because they named him Adolf Hitler and John Lean Aryan Nation Campbell.
Would you furthermore.
They should have named him after suits.
If you named your kid Jesus Hitler, would you furthermore be rescinded from the radio waves by a group of irate citizens or what?
Hmm.
I don't think.
It was just the fact that they named the kids that that got the kids taken away.
In fact, the state people said it wasn't just naming.
The naming of the kids was a clue, but there was other reasons besides being politically incorrect that the kids were taken away.
You know, sometimes CPS does get hit with a clue by four and they take those clue by fours and they nail them together with the.
The nails of righteous indignation and build a case.
And they've they've crucified quite a few scientists that way.
Wouldn't you say, Paisley?
I mean.
Yeah.
I mean, that's a clue by fours are everywhere.
And and that's the problem is you have to be aware of the incoming clue by four.
Well, I can't get I can't get spare parts for my cloud buster or my organ box.
Oh, you can't find your organ going.
I've got the box.
I just I don't have any spare parts for it.
Well, I.
All that stuff.
You can get them in Russia.
Filled with orange juice.
Yeah.
Russia still has them.
I mean, they have all those Reich.
The third day.
Even the third Reich part.
Wilhelm Reich.
Yeah.
Well, you know, the thing is that the Russians are still the only people making vacuum tubes.
And an analog.
You know, you have to start there.
Our vacuum cleaner doesn't work either.
We need to go to Russia and get vacuum tubes.
Yeah.
Well, that's the way you could get old fender tubes.
They sound as good as the old.
You know, the 1960s ones, because that's the ones they were copying.
So rather than, you know, they're not available anymore.
If you have an antique instrument or something.
And the real reason the Russians are still making that stuff is that they are immune to EMPs.
Electromagnetic.
They won't blow up.
Well, the Russians always took that nuclear war stuff a little more seriously than we did.
I've talked to Russians of my own generation who said they were a lot more scared than we were.
Their propaganda.
Propaganda said that we were, well, basically just what our propaganda said the Russians were.
But the difference was they thought a nuclear war would be survivable.
And they really did have a lot more fallout shelters and so forth set up for that.
Whereas, as I understand it, the main stash the U.S. government had was morphine in case of a nuclear war.
You know, you had to build your own fallout shelter and so forth.
Hide under your dust.
And, you know, the threat hasn't gone away.
They don't make as many.
The monsters don't come from atomic radiation anymore.
They come from quantum foam or something.
But those bombs are still there.
Genetically modified food.
When the X's come, you hide under your dust.
Put your hands above your head.
Yeah.
And kiss your teacher goodbye.
Really, try not to urinate yourself.
Not this teacher.
And you go for the, you find the shelters and then you crawl around in the subways and wait for, you know, the rest of the subgeniuses to show up.
Because you didn't actually go.
Yeah.
Instead of meeting other subgenies, soon you become one of the creatures that live in the vast subways and the tunnels of the bowels of the earth.
And you become like in that science fiction thing that, I forget, I think it was Ray Bradbury when he was real hip and cool and stuff.
And it was a radio show.
Oh, the 1930s.
The tall beneath the earth.
And the guy didn't know he was actually a dead robot because there was a tunnel.
Never mind.
Oh, you always find out you're one of the dead robots, too, or you're one of the department store dummies.
You're one of the dead Civil War ghosts marching back.
I know how those stories all end.
Well, then, if that's the way all stories end.
They end in a dead end tunnel that we call the Twilight Zone.
The Twilight Zone.
Yes.
Right.
But the light at the end of the tunnel was turned off.
They ran out of funding.
There was a bad light at the end of the tunnel for 13 eunuchs in India today.
Wow.
I don't know if you guys read the news, but this headline really caught my eye.
13 eunuchs killed in fire in India.
Think of it's a magic number, too.
Well, at first I thought, well, they must have been having a eunuch convention.
And they were.
Nobody had the power.
They were just throwing balls to put the fire out.
That was a left jab.
It was quite effective.
I just pushed the delay dump for the first time ever on this show.
Because you're making fun of me.
I know when people are making fun of me.
You know, I thought the eunuch story was.
I mean, I cried because I only had one.
And then I read about.
I read about the 13 eunuchs.
And they were at a convention of 5,000 eunuchs.
And the Yahoo commenters were shocked because they were going, well, how primitive can they be in India?
They have these.
And it turns out there are 700,000 eunuchs in India.
And they had to carry lanterns to the Ganga.
And they get put down.
And they're discriminated against and so forth.
And as I read.
More, I realized, oh, they're what's called transgendered people over here.
And although in a lot of cases, they weren't.
It's like their parents did it to them or like.
Well, not the Catholic Church used to do it to Europeans.
They need a certain number of little soprano boys.
Yeah, they'd shave everything off.
It might take.
You might have to do it to 50 of them to get one that survived.
But hey.
It was for Jesus, you know.
Actually, it was for a bunch of rich people and the Pope.
And if Jesus had heard anything about it, I'm sure he would have kicked their butts.
Probably.
Might have started a fire.
But, well, it's not funny that these poor eunuchs or whatever.
All of the ones that were interviewed were described as she.
And that was when I caught on.
Oh, that's it's people who can't afford a full tuck and roll.
Job.
They just get everything removed.
And that's how you are a transsexual.
If you're really, really, really poor.
So my fellow Americans who intend to become transsexuals, you better do it soon before the econo cataclysm renders you like those poor people in India.
She would have.
I'm still thinking about.
That brings me to mind that the Sultan's composition.
And Baron Munchausen.
The Terry Gilliam's The Adventures of Baron Munchausen.
The Sultan has a special organ that's plays by screams of tortured people.
And he had an opera called A Eunuch's Life is Hard.
And that is all.
Yeah.
Did you ever hear?
May I ask you this question?
Did you ever hear of the eunuch admirals of the Chinese Navy?
Just about the same time they discovered so-called discovered but charted the Americas in 1432, some 60 years before the Europeans claimed to have got there.
That's just because they didn't have windows yet.
Well, the Vikings had already.
They'd been hundreds of years before that.
I didn't know the Chinese kept.
Computer programming.
But they had they had thousands and thousands of these eunuch navigators and admirals.
And so forth.
The pilot of these ships, many of which went down.
That's right.
They call them Linux now, to be polite.
You know, we're going to get into an OS war here and we're going to have a discussion about, you know, that's an old joke, man.
The eunuchs joke.
That's really terrible.
What is it?
We you should be sent to Dr.
Dark's house for that.
It's what we can cringe.
Yes.
Cringing.
That's what.
That's what those puns are all about.
How cringe worthy can a pun be made upon my word?
I've never heard such a terrible pun.
He gave me one of the worst puns ever.
I have a sign that I found in a pet store that says, Beware of attack gerbil, which I thought was funny.
And I was telling her about it.
And she says, it says, well, I said, it says, Beware of attack gerbils.
And she said, you know, if they had only told the Nazis about that and that gerbil.
Fellow never would have caused any trouble.
Well, I'd say about half of our audience won't understand that reference at all.
You do not also make fun of the Fuhrer, so short of his birthday.
A friend of mine recently told me about a young woman he had had to explain World War
One and two to.
She's a good girl.
She had never heard of World War One or World War Two.
Had to use the old bathroom.
And when she saw one and number two, the the moon and the sky in the daytime, she thought it was a recurring round cloud.
This is the educational level we're facing in the United States today.
And we are you two are teachers.
We're setting the stage for the father.
Our school teachers in West Virginia, of all places.
So our kids think like that or four.
Right.
You've got it.
Yeah.
We've got hope.
At the time they're 40, they'll know that the moon is really a giant skull.
The moon is actually the skull of a huge monster that attacked the earth that the ancient yetis
beheaded it.
I'll go skeleton.
That makes more sense.
The moon is hollow.
Yeah, it's it's a head cheese.
Green cheese.
You definitely superstitious.
You have to be an idiot to think the moon was made of green cheese.
It's made of head cheese.
It's been in Revelation X and the new book made of south.
I didn't realize that, but it was mentioned in both books and I didn't.
It's the secret teachings.
It's repetitive.
And we didn't.
I didn't mean to do that, but I've been so long between books.
I forgot I'd used the same gag twice.
Well maybe it's been changed in the ebook version.
That's right.
Yeah.
Oh God.
Repetitive learning is the best way.
Especially if your neurons are misfiring real badly.
Learning is the best bet.
Best bet.
What does happen in the process of learning when your neurons are misfiring real, real
badly and you continue to try and learn or to read or to understand and nothing makes
any sense.
It's called Revelation.
Yeah.
It's called joining the church of the subgenus.
Okay.
Some people call that philosophy and that's probably the degree you should seek.
That's a good description.
I never have had any patience with philosophy.
I mean really.
It just seemed like math that didn't really apply to anything.
Yeah.
Formulas for human behavior.
There is no formula for humans.
I prefer quantum psychology.
Well there's plenty of formulas.
Quantum psychology.
There's as many formulas for slacks as there is ways to dress a hot dog.
Why would you want to dress up a frankfurter?
That's kind of silly.
I suppose you want to put it on YouTube or something and put some interesting dialogue
on it.
There'll be one on by tomorrow.
I'll bet you anything.
Like a Superman cape or maybe an AK-47.
You're giving somebody an idea for a YouTube video.
I'm giving you an idea for a YouTube extravaganza right this minute.
But if you cut carefully.
I don't think they have the mustard.
Open one up and you take all of the insides out of it, you end up with a Halloweener.
They're kind of like a meaty carnivorous jack-o'-lantern.
I don't like where this is going.
As someone born on Halloween, I'm a Halloweeney.
Ah.
Yeah.
What?
Not long ago, Princess, we was on the air at this station because we had an open house.
The station open house party was today.
By not long ago, he means hours.
Yeah.
Earlier today.
And swilling WCSB beer.
He still hasn't gotten over the beer.
I'm jealous.
I never got any.
Yeah, I want the beer.
I thought you were going to be searching the station for that.
All right.
See ya.
This is all in Stang's mind.
He's making all of this up except for the part.
I'm going to go.
Yeah.
For perfect sorority horror.
Oh, confused call father.
Sneaking? What?
Lizard?
That means like she's gone crazy, right, Lee?
Yes.
I have gone crazy.
Very far gone crazy.
Well, don't come back.
I wouldn't think of it.
Hey, Dave, recognize this music
in the background?
I just noticed it.
Dave did our background music.
It's like
detective. It's a good detective show
music.
Somebody on YouTube, make quick, make
a detective show about a hollow weenie.
It's suspenseful.
That's a good one.
I still don't think they'll be able to muster the ability
to do it.
It's a lot of catch-up work, you know?
Oh!
I can't believe this is the hour
of slack. It's become the hour
of snacks.
And you're laughing, and then they won't quit.
They keep tickling you.
Then you start crying, and once again, you lose your
confidence in your different
parts of your society,
I suppose, is what ends up lacking.
Your panjab falls right off.
I'm plumbed.
Aw.
Appalled.
And quite shiny.
You weren't applying your boots, were you,
when you said that, or were you just being nice?
No, I've had on sneakers.
I didn't wear my boots today.
I don't know if I'd want to be in the same room then.
Well, you know,
you were talking about the feet swelling, and with the sneakers
they have laces. You can loosen them up.
Yeah, and you have to keep applying
shav every 25 seconds.
A corset for your feet.
What runs
through what? Not this river,
buddy.
Is a corset for your foot?
Yeah, they have those.
Of course.
It is.
They have them for your beans.
They have them for every different device
you might wear on your body.
We're not cutting the slack.
I don't know if I can trust you guys.
Oh, God!
Man, I'm never going to do a show like this again.
This is the last time this happens.
It's a good thing we're going to split
for three months.
How come them women
are just doing all them little sideways
jabs and all that stuff?
That's what I'm saying.
That's what we're supposed to be doing all the time.
They run things, you know, as well as I do.
We're just their tools,
so to speak,
as it were.
But Pisces, they need you so much.
You must run things.
Someone needs to be told.
Someone needs to tell them to be told.
It's not so much
running things as providing
the appropriate suggestions
that's the key.
Well, now, that's a way of doing it.
In organizational communication,
they would say you are a yes-sayer
as a gatekeeper.
Shaping the environment.
Yes.
The problem with shaping the environment
is it's a lot of work.
Well, you could just go nuts a little bit.
You could kind of, like, design anything you want.
You know, just go crazy.
You could make people shave their nostril hairs
three times a day
and tell them things that are totally,
like, lies and make them inconvenience themselves,
you know.
They maybe even hurt themselves physically
without any liability to you.
That would be, think of it.
Potter Nostril is the expert
on that type of shaving.
His are braided right now.
I remember when he had
quite a jolly, like, Cossack mustache
when he was going through that period.
Do you remember those days?
The, uh, what, the Zappa?
No, it was on a big,
big fatty.
That wasn't a mustache.
That was nose hairs.
Oh.
I couldn't grow a mustache.
It saved my life.
Yeah, all the energy goes into the interior
of the nostril.
Ah.
So, yeah.
That's how I do it.
I sure wish I was on whatever you're on.
It's called the radio, you guys.
And we're supposed to be, you know,
making sense or getting something.
Some message across.
It's an important
responsibility, you know.
We have an hour.
We could talk about, you know,
something current, like
Occupy Wall...
What is it?
Shift?
Shiftless?
Our friend, Mr. Cissar,
the conservative, said,
that S in OWS stands for shiftless.
And somebody else said,
Occupy Wall shiftless?
Like, how?
Fine.
So, there's our political talk for the day.
What is this music in the background?
Somebody took Onan Canobites B.O.B.
and remixed it.
Is that a disco mix?
Now this person has more problems than anybody I've encountered in the church so far, it sounds like.
We've played this before, but I don't remember who did it.
Next week's show will be the safe-for-work version of the Ministry of Slack's live performance at 14X Day.
That's a lot of work to make that safe-for-work.
Well, Reverend Exister pre-censored it for me, forgetting that we also have an uncensored version of the show, but that's fine.
And it's insane. You think this one's insane?
I knew this one was going to be insane.
This is differently sane.
And earlier this week, I said,
This week's show will be even more insane than last week's show, although I'm just guessing because we haven't done last week's show yet.
See, I had to prepare shows ahead of time, pretending I was in the future, when I was really in our past.
Sleight of hand and very slight mind.
Yeah, very slight time control.
In fact, I have to whip out as many shows as I can before we leave.
I'll put it back in.
Yeah.
Just don't whip out the shows in public.
I mean, they'll arrest you for that.
Hopefully.
There's that whole legal issue.
I've got more shows than anybody.
I understand.
You don't have to be such a show-off about it.
Yeah, but you've only got...
And I have...
You whipped out the show.
I can't say I have more ball.
I can't say that on the radio.
You have more ball.
I can say I have more ball.
You have a ball on the air.
Yeah, I have a ball on the air.
And I have more shows to show than most people.
But the ones around the fringes are smaller.
It's the ones in the center that are more useful.
That ball's still in the air.
It's time to remember it.
Actually, believe it or not, as far as time goes, it's only five minutes until the end of the show.
Oh, dear.
Now, since Dr. Sinister knows we're here and he may come in late, which means we'll have extra time.
Oh, no, he's been here.
Oh, he's been here this...
Oh, I watched him come in on the security camera.
I've had an eye on it all this time.
I knew it right the moment he walked in I saw him.
You see, I'm monitoring the security cameras behind you, Evan Stang.
I'm glad somebody is.
She's not kidding, listeners.
What people don't realize is that with...
With the questions at different events about security, everyone's always just saying it was me or Lagoon.
It's actually we.
She's the one who runs security.
She's the queen of all the UFOs.
It is a dangerous business, too.
She runs security.
She runs her mouth.
She has the runs.
I do it all remotely.
It's all done with a bot.
She has her minions.
Petal is one of her minions.
She's like...
Sweet exteriors of fierce.
Oh, that's another thing.
Another thing we've never had before is two space princesses in the studio.
And neither one is watching in his or her underwear.
You're lousy with space princesses tonight.
No.
Yeah, we're going to have to spray for space princesses.
Yep.
Pepper spray.
That's it.
That's a new bumper sticker.
Pepper spray the space princesses.
No, don't do that.
No.
Don't do that.
No, don't do that.
Maybe cinnamon.
Well, some wouldn't...
Well, you know, like a little cinnamon with a little nut in it.
maybe a little vanilla.
Nah, the real stuff, baby.
Come on, you know there's some space princes
that'll go for it.
I'll pay you for the poppers
for the princesses.
Well, if you watch the UC Davis
events, like
no one ever did, where he
just calmly went over and sprayed everybody
and stuff, I don't know.
I think that would be kind of sexually exciting.
Well, you know,
I'm sure that there's a market.
Pepper spray in your face.
There's a market for that.
Obviously,
I'm not capitalizing on it.
You just gave me an idea.
I should be
making tons of money.
You know,
there's an obvious market for me in
sexualizing pepper
spray.
That's it?
And you could also become a mentor, too, for
other people who want to start franchises.
So you're saying that all these protesters
are really doing it for
the police?
The police brutality.
Yeah, the brutality.
I think it's more of a case that they all went up
to the event thinking, you know,
they got in the wrong line.
You know, and
he's there and he's doing that line.
And, you know,
it's like going to the...
You're saying the other line was getting
caught, right?
No, the other line was getting, like,
marshmallows.
Well, okay, I would have waited
for a chocolate line, but marshmallows would have been
a lot better.
Well, what you do is you go in the marshmallow line
and then walk over with your marshmallow to the
chocolate line, and then you have chocolate-covered marshmallows.
I miss the 70s.
The lines in the 70s were pretty good.
Yeah, lots better.
Are you guys talking about drugs?
We didn't even call them lines, we called them highways.
Yeah, interstates, baby.
Interstates.
Freeways.
On the road.
I could tell some stories, but I don't want
to embarrass myself.
Well, that's what this is all about.
Yeah, I've already done that for the last hour.
Right, for the last how many years
on this show? That's the content of this show.
It's embarrassing yourself.
Wait,
embarrassing him or embarrassing ourselves?
No, I was just saying that the dear
reverend is very fond
of telling the very most
horrifying and saddening events
in his life, in a very
ha-ha-ha-ha kind of way.
But that inspires the rest of us.
It does.
It is inspirational.
He is a mentor, just as many of you.
Well, yes, he is.
But by the same token, I forgot what I was
talking about.
I don't understand what you guys were talking
about from the beginning.
He's a mentor to his milliard
minions.
We don't allow minions in this particular...
This is the only religion that doesn't
allow minions.
We deprogram our own zombies
and I swear I spend
half my time debunking...
my own religion.
Well, you know it's true.
I do know that that's true.
Bob said he was a short-duration
personal savior.
Mm-hmm.
Bob's a short word, too.
He's not your crutch, you're his crutch.
You're his short-duration personal crutch.
That's all you are.
Don't get a big head out of it.
That explains the shoulder pain.
That really explains the shoulder pain.
You're Bob's ice pack.
You're Bob's aspirin pill.
You're Bob's little fanny throw mom.
Let's face it, you're Bob's...
You're Bob's diaper, basically,
when it comes right down to it.
That's what you are, friends.
You're Bob's diaper.
Yeah, you can depend on Bob.
Oh, man.
Bob depends on you.
No, you're Bob's depends
is what I'm trying to tell you.
You know, and...
You're always there in Connie's office.
On Judgment Day, somebody's gonna come along
and change his diapers.
And then where are you gonna end up?
Yeah, I'm gonna get...
Depends on whether they're recyclable
or the kind you just throw away.
I'd be in a bowl.
Then your afterlife will either be
in a washing machine or the city dump.
Are you wanting them to end up
in a spin cycle with the rest of them?
Depends on what kind of depends Bob's wearing.
Yeah.
And he's pretty old now.
I'm sorry.
Is this some bizarre version
that smells like teen spirit?
It most certainly is.
Oh, I'm reminded right now
of a very long time ago.
There's a Moog album of...
That's what it is.
Exactly 45 seconds in my reckoning.
Nailed it.
The Moog version of
Smells Like Teen Spirit.
Yep.
Ah.
I remember Boyd.
Bob Barbarigmy.
Bob Barbarigmy-isms.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Remember the spasmodic...
45 seconds ago what?
Wait, no.
I caught up.
Sorry.
Friends, you're listening to
Hour of Sight number 1335
from the Church of the Subgenius.
For more information about the church,
which you probably aren't interested in
at this point,
you can go to subgenius.com.
Actually, you can see pictures of Pisces
with her shirt off there.
That's quite impressive.
You can see Petal with her shirt on.
Cavorting with Bob himself.
Yeah, cavorting with Bob.
And Phaeton.
Bacon?
Phaeton.
Some people say Satan,
but he has kind of a lift in real life.
Yes, Phaeton was in X-Day and Starwood.
He kind of got assaulted by some kids, didn't he?
That was last year, apparently.
He increased his demon security this year
to protect himself.
Here on...
What now?
FM in Cleveland.
FM.
Because sometimes it's not in Cleveland.
Sometimes they hear it in...
Early 1934.
Atlanta.
They hear it in Pennsylvania.
In Pennsylvania?
In Pennsylvania, even?
Yeah.
Well, that's over the internet.
Through the interwebs.
Yeah.
They get on the thingamajob on the interwebs
in Pennsylvania.
And they hook up to the CompuLink net.
The AO...
The reticulum, we call it, actually.
The rep.
Right.
And they type in,
and then they listen to it on the interwebs
in Pennsylvania.
In Pennsylvania.
Now, we refer to Pittsburgh as Pennsylvania.
You're not allowed to go to Pennsylvania?
There's a lot of things I'm supposedly not allowed to do.
Actually, I'm...
Speaking of loud,
we've been loud for too long,
and it's time for Dr. Sinister's show.
So I'm going to turn on the...
Okay.
The Devo.
The new Devo album,
but without...
The voices.
That...
It's like the karaoke Devo that...
Devoid.
Well, that was...
Abnorm Nihil scored for us somehow.
Well, I'd like to...
This is not it.
What are you liking to do, Dave?
I was going to whisper a fond howdy doody
to Pudder Nostril and his lovely lady,
and also to Pisces,
who I haven't spoken to for the last 43,000 years.
It's good to hear your voices as well.
And also to anybody in the studio area,
and also those people,
on the street,
and just to dominate the conversation.
I'm sorry.
No, you're not.
You've said I'm sorry five times a show
for 20 years now,
and I don't think you were sorry
a single one of those times.
No, I couldn't.
I do think he's sorry.
I think it's like a hiccup.
He says that as a sort of a burp.
It is a form of a twitch,
but it's a psychological twitch,
as I have nothing to say further
beyond the I'm sorry.
But there is a humbleness in his sorry.
I always just say, uh...
Uh...
I'm sorry.
But it's so much more kind to be saying,
I'm sorry, you know?
I always have to...
When I imitate Dave saying,
I'm sorry, I have to punch my shoulders.
And turn my butt...
My rear up to the bull silver back.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize, Dave.
Don't apologize.
Don't let them make you feel like you need to apologize.
It's a sign of weakness.
A four-square clue or a hunch of a weakness.
I'm sorry.
I just...
See, there he goes again.
Don't apologize weakly
about any weakness
that you're apologizing for.
I apologize for...
And don't say you're sorry for saying you're sorry.
A real man doesn't apologize, mister.
Exactly.
We all wear the same boots around here, babe.
Okay, okay.
Here's the Devo.
Goodbye, everybody.
I'm going to hang up on everyone by now.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
Thank you.