The Stone Genius
Our
One
The Stone Genius
I'm dreaming of a white Christmas
Just like the ones I used to know
Where the treetops glisten
And kiddies
listen to you hear
sleigh bells in the snow
I'm dreaming
of a white
Christmas
With every Christmas
I pray
May your days
be merry
and
rosy
with me
I'm dreaming of a white Christmas
Just like the ones I used to know
May your days be merry
and rosy
with me
I'm dreaming of a white Christmas
Just like the ones I used to know
May your days be merry
and rosy
I'm dreaming of a white Christmas
Just like the ones I used to know
May your days be merry
I'm dreaming of a white Christmas
Just like the ones I used to know
May your days be merry
and rosy
With other humans
down attic
with others
May your days
be merry
and rosy
Oh, Christmas is just a day.
It's a frame of mind.
And that's what's been changing.
Yes, my friends.
An amazing collage there.
White Christmas by Corporal Blossom from the CD called A Mutated Christmas from the Illegal Art label.
And I'll be playing tons more sound being measured in tons, tons of that more.
And I will give their address.
But you can also check out www.tryagemusic.com.
Tryagemusic.com.
It says on their PR of this collection, a bad trip Christmas song collages.
And boy, that describes these next three hours of slack that we'll be enjoying over the coming weeks because we've got so much sick Christmas music.
But now it is time to go back and drink out of the Christmas trough.
Oh, look, Dave's dressed like Santa Claus.
Oh, he's like a cowboy Santa.
How jolly.
Oh, Jazz is giving, gives Dave the show pills.
Boy, I really need one of those.
What am I going to do about laundromat in this suit though?
I need the show bath.
The show de-lousing.
Oh, Dave doesn't even have headphones yet.
That's enough of that.
Oh, he's got headphones now.
I also have the part of my pancreas that I'd like to show you now.
It's been increased in size.
Oh, your pancreas looks lovely, Dave.
Look, it's swelling.
I actually have the capability of a man of 190 IQ's brain.
Come on.
I'll put more pills out for everybody.
Yeah.
Oh, those pills.
They make my mouth feel like it's on fire.
More pills.
And my brain feel like it's a puddle of liquefied crystals.
I'm shocked by the...
I'm sorry.
The red pills are really good.
I like to take the red pill.
The red one and the blue one.
Yes, the red one and the blue one.
At the same time.
That way you go in and out.
The warp mixes.
Up and down.
It's so high, you can't go over it.
You can't go over it.
Up and down.
You get to break up.
I didn't mean to only...
You can
Well, we're off to bed, daddy.
No fighting.
Nothing.
Which is wonderful.
Thank you, old man.
Ooooooooooooooooh!
Ooooooooooooh!
In excelsis Deo!
Here's Grubbot!
A robot you can program to perform eight different functions!
Upsy Baby.
The doll that stands up.
She's new.
From Kenner.
Where illusion is the ultimate weapon.
We must buy our toys.
We have devised a marketing scheme for children's toys.
It will empower us to resist us.
You will use your church as a vehicle to bring these toys before the power.
It will be a barber for kids.
Do you understand and accept?
For the usual plus expenses.
Good.
Okay, I think the girls will have the star.
A rainbow.
Rainbow pipes.
And for the boy.
A little tiny transformer.
Robots will change into dollar bills and back again.
Yes.
But how will the battle of good against evil be represented in your marketing schemes, human?
Good has lots of muscles.
Good.
The primitive earth societies should exist.
Except this value judgment.
Good will have pre-physical attributes according to human desires.
Sexual desires.
Latent in children.
Brought out.
Through the vehicle of this so-called.
So far we're told these boys have church batteries now included.
Uh, yes.
Uh, the old subgenius toy marketing scheme recorded there at Dockstock 1984.
And me and Palmer VDs.
Um, angels we have heard on high.
It was by the Philistines.
Uh, the collage called all the money you've got is from the great obtuse Christmas collage
album, which you can get for free.
Get this.
Um, check out this website.
Obtuse.com.
Obtuse.i-u-m-a.com.
That's ob- excuse me.
Some of these subgeniuses.
That's um, obtuse.i-u-m-a.com.
Free the obtuse thing.
And uh, before that, uh, jingle bells from the Mill Valley taters.
Uh, uh, oh, and this background music is a Christmas gas.
14 blasted holiday carols.
With Slim Spinkter.
Now his name is not spelled S-pink-tor.
But spinkter.
www.slimspinkter.com has, or you can write to slim at slim spinkter, but that's S-p-i-n-c-t-e-r.
Slim spinkter.com.
Ah, yes.
And next up, the real story of Christmas by Michael Shelley.
Oh, yes.
Old Solar and Time
Trousers
Santa's Little Helper
And that's the real story of Christmas.
Dave, Lonesome Cowboy Dave, a lot of people don't know this, but Lonesome Cowboy Dave was the original Mr. Jingling.
That was so long ago, Chaz. That was another life and that was another lifestyle.
I lived then with a very, very, very dear friend of mine still to this day.
Lovely Mr. Horace Joris Nobomont.
I was the inventor of the Betsy Wetsy doll.
Those were the days, weren't they?
I don't know. The sun never came up, but we still called them days.
That was a beautiful house.
We were feisty people then. The glass was always half full and we were always happy.
Wasn't that when you originally met Bob was when you were the original Mr. Jingling and you were hanging out down in the Greenwich Village?
Everything had tassels that year. I think it was 1953.
That's true. What bar did you run into him at? Was it Santa Claus?
You?
I think it was Bob.
We were looking for records at Bleaker Bob's one day and I was wearing the tutu.
And he recognized me as Swingin' Sam, also better known as Mr. Jingling here in Cleveland Town.
He could tell by my little elf tassels and the fact that I had the cute little arms.
How did that paternity suit ever turn out between Dobbs and Santa?
And who?
His dad.
Santa Dog.
I don't know.
I don't think it was Santa.
But St. Nicholas. This is fact.
St. Nicholas.
St. Nicholas punched another bishop in the nose and bloodied his nose.
And sucked him.
Really? The historical St. Nicholas?
Over the Trinity of God.
The original St. Nicholas in Turkey?
Who the hell is God?
Ask Dobbs one day.
That's the question we should be asking.
Suddenly, a lightning bolt struck from nowhere on that bright sunny day.
Bob did a backflip and from that day on, he too was a believer.
And from the snowdrift truck, a little child bearing flowers emerged.
And Chip, Chip, what else was on the TV bill with St. Nicholas?
Sip, sickened.
The historical Santa Claus is originally lived, as the caller knows,
as a bishop.
And the
fake beard and a CIA Wall Street credit card.
A saint he was, the girl said.
St. Nicholas.
Who invented the CIA.
That's good.
You got it, brother.
He snuck into people's houses through the chimney.
They knew when they were sleeping.
They knew when they were awake.
You got it, brother.
But like the CIA, he was protecting them.
That's Foucault, baby.
Foucault knew that St. Nick was a creeping, stinking spy.
What?
He knows when you've been sleeping.
He knows what you've been eating.
Hey, man, my kids still believe in St. Nicholas.
And who keeps that belief alive in their fevered, sick little brain?
Madison Avenue, of course.
No, the surveillance community.
And Disney.
Under your direction.
And the Reynolds Tobacco Company.
Miller Bear.
He's a very powerful being.
If you're bad, he punishes you.
If you're good, he rewards you.
He's probably the closest thing to Jesus walking the earth.
He's the closest thing to Big Brother there is.
He rewards those who knows when they are smiling when they're awake.
I think really if you want to make a deal, you have to do it with, you know...
Could Dr. Claus in fact be the wandering, quote, milkman?
Rumor has it that he's the one who's the most dangerous person in the world.
Rumor to have fathered our savior, J.R. Bob Dobbs?
Well, we find it a very likely possibility from the falsified documents we have here.
And also the fluffy beard that often grew on Bob's feet.
And the sperm count with the glowing red nose.
What could this mean?
Often, Bob's early girlfriends had to actually shave his feet, especially when he was...
Listen, if you're going to say Indians had to have flying saucers out in Minneapolis 15,000 years ago...
...and my dam got it...
It was for sure the beard, the fake beard.
And I want one of them new robots with the real intestinal bacteria.
Yeah, what about...
And one of those robots with a fish brain for a brain.
They're sold out.
And a new pony boy to scrub my sink.
Toys R Us has no more.
And whole peas.
Pat's got a pointer on the shelves.
Big player of the show.
Air teas.
Can't get them from Amazon.com.
Can't get them anywhere in time.
Hair rot's not boring.
I say.
Son of a...
Too late for Christmas.
Cause there's too many hair knots out there and...
Son of a...
Have yourself a merry little Christmas.
Have yourself a merry little sysmus.
Have yoursel-
Oh merry little hasmus.
Mmm-mm-mm-mm-mm-mm
Have yourself a merry little
Have yourself a merry little Christmas
Let your side be light
From the water triples with the outer sky
Have yourself a merry little Christmas
From the water miles away
Once a day as in olden
Happy golden day
Miles of earth
Let your heart
Be out of sight
Out of sight
The Jackson 5
One wish
And all the rest
Everybody
Merry Christmas
And a good new year
Miles away
Have yourself
A merry little Christmas
Now
.
Through the years
We all will be together
If the fates allow
Hang a shining star upon the highest bough
And have yourself a merry little Christmas
To me
From Mutated Christmas, friends.
Have yourself a merry little Christmas by No-L.
No-L.
Before that, some year-old ESO and Michael Shelley did that real story of Christmas
from the Tarkin Records All-Star Holiday Extravaganza.
I'm playing a lot from that.
So check out www.triage.com for that one also.
The Tarkin Records is also on www.triage.com.
And now, the Jethro's.
Here we go.
Go.
The Weirbobs and Ima,
those who have the psychosis that convinces them
that they are the Santa Bob.
Or that they're Santa Bob by night.
And they go shuffling through the snow
on their nameless, hideous errands,
the grin of Bob and the beard of Santa Claus
and the pipe of the Lord stuck on their face.
And they stop using the locks of their doors
and they just kind of float into the keyhole.
Oh, friends, it's tough.
And, you know, just going to church ain't enough.
You've got to send your money to the Santa Bob.
As a matter of fact, the people across the street from me
told their kids that Santa Claus bills them
for the toys he brings.
Can you believe that?
The kids were asking if their parents,
maybe Santa Claus will bring us two He-Man erector sets.
And the mom said, no, no, he won't because he bills us.
We can't afford that.
Santa Claus sends us a bill after Christmas.
Yeah, but at least he tells us.
He quotes the note.
Every Christmas Eve, children nestled in their beds
dream of Santa and the presents they hope he...
Hey, wait a second.
That's no kid.
All right, everyone, use your sign wings.
Sign.
All right, let's start Santa's workshop.
Don't worry, we're almost there.
See, that's where Santa lives.
Oh, wow.
Jinx, Jinx.
Is that Santa Claus?
What's going on?
Jinx is psychically projecting his story into our minds.
Holy Psalmate Jesus.
Is that Santa Claus?
Merry Christmas, Santa Claus.
A season for miracles.
Merry Christmas.
Oh, thanks, Wappers.
Don't forget Santa Claus.
And Jinx, too.
Is that Santa Claus?
It's doing.
Looks like we're gonna have a white Christmas.
We've got to.
Advanced dogmatic studies, dear.
Dear friends, also known as electricelfatloop.com.
How the Jinx Stole Christmas.
From their collection, have yourself an advanced dogmatic Christmas.
That's advanced dogmatic studies.
Did I say studios?
At, well, you can email information about that.
The whole album, which is available, the advanced dogmatic Christmas album,
from electricelfatloop.com.
Oh well.
Get him out, I-I don't have gifts to give you.
What's bothering you?
And they told me a rum pum pum pum
And you are going to see the rum pum pum pum
I'll find it if we make the rum pum pum pum
This is something for you to call rum pum pum rum pum rum pum rum pum
Rum pum pum pum
When we
Oh
That's fair to give our king a rock-a-bum-bum
Rock-a-bum-bum, rock-a-bum-bum, rock-a-bum-bum
Yeah, I'll play for you
Rock-a-bum-bum
For my drum
Baby, I'm a rock-a-bum-bum
I play my drum for you
Oh, rock a-bum-bum, rock a-bum-bum
Oh, rock a-bum-bum, rock a-bum-bum, rock a-bum-bum
...
Baby smile, me and my child
Me and my child
And, uh, amazing.
More from Corporal Blossom.
I am really impressed by their editing work.
And that's on...
Corporal Blossom and the Mutated Christmas
is on the Illegal Art label.
That's www.detritus.net
slash Illegal Art.
www.detritus.net slash Illegal Art.
And now, more Jethro!
Jethro!
And whose birth
do we celebrate with this new
century?
Who was nailed on that great
manger cradle?
But Satan Claus.
Oh my God.
Dang, come on.
Whose father, Paul Bunyan,
and whose mother, Big Sister,
Did they have Christmas
before there were malls?
created the conspiracy.
Before there were malls,
there was no such thing as Christmas?
Yes.
The Pilgrims for Babies?
There were, there was a
down-home Norman Rockwell-style
It's a Wonderful Life type of Christmas.
It was a, it was a, it was a
kite-flying Coca-Cola-drinking Christmas,
not a crack-smoking, rubber-snapping Christmas.
Rolling holy dough,
It was a,
when your little brother
broke through the hole,
it fell through a hole in the ice,
slid, and you went and saved him.
You didn't laugh at him
and huff some more glue.
It was a wonderful life back then.
Remember when Uncle Bud would come in
with the candles?
Like most people have
Christmas candles.
But today Christmas is lost its meaning.
He just beaten the crap out of us.
I mean, we're dancing.
Santa Claus could...
Strange lights appear in the skies
all over the world.
The wife of a carpenter
experiences virgin birth,
and a baby is born with a head
that glows like a fluorescent light.
Dare I ask it?
Yes.
Was the infant Jesus
neither man nor God,
but merely one of the countless aliens
that visit the earth each and every day?
The answer?
Yes, definitely.
Take that and shove it up the tube,
mark certainty,
in the fuzzy place
called the Twilight Zone.
Friends, try to imagine
that you're in the middle of the world.
Somewhere in the snowy north,
the Santaibob trudging mindlessly
through the Himalayan snows,
driven by strange forces
to complete his nameless errand.
And he may show up at your house, my friend,
if you've been a bad subgenius
or a halfway subgenius,
or if we keep getting tangled up
in these other shows
and having strange microphones.
Oh, shit, this is a situation.
Down in the workshop
All the elves were making toys
For the good Gentile girls
And the good Gentile boys
When the boss busted in
Nearly scared him half to death
Had a rifle in his hands
And cheap whiskey on his breath
From his beard to his boots
He was covered with ammo
Like a big fat drunk
Disgruntled Yuletide Rambo
And he smiled as he said
With a twinkle in his eye
Merry Christmas to all
Now you're all gonna die!
The night Santa went crazy
The night Saint Nick went insane
Realized he'd been getting the wrong deal
Something finally must have snapped in his brain
Well, the workshop is gone now
He decided to vomit
Everywhere you'll find pieces
Of Cupid and Comet
And he tied up his helpers
And he held the elves hostage
And he ground up poor Rudolph
Into reindeer sausage
He got Dancer and Prancer
With an old German Luger
And he slashed up Dasher
Just like Freddy Krueger
And he picked up a flamethrower
And he barbecued Blitzen
And he took a big bite
And said it tastes just like chicken
The night Santa went crazy
The night Kris Kringle went nuts
Now you can hardly walk around the North Pole
Without stepping in reindeer guts
There's a national crime
Guarded in the FBI
There's a van from the eye
Wind is loose
And helicopters circling round in the sky
And the bullets are flying
The body counts rising
And everyone's dying to know
Who's Santa why?
My, my, my, my, my, my
You used to be such a jolly guy
But now you're a little more funny
Yes, Virginia
Now Santa's doing time
In a federal prison
For his infamous crime
Hey little friend now
Don't you cry no more tears
He'll be out with good behavior
In seven hundred more years
But now Mason's in therapy
And Donna's still nervous
And the elves all got jobs
Working for the postal service
And they say Mrs. Clark
She's on the phone every night
With her lawyer negotiating
The movie rights they're talking about
The night Santa went crazy
The night Saint Nicholas slipped
Broke his back for some milk and cookies
Sounds to me like he was
Tired of getting chipped
The night Santa went crazy
The night Saint Nick went insane
Realize he's been getting the wrong deal
Some finally must have snapped in his brain
Whoa, oh
Tell ya
Some finally must have snapped
In his brain
You better watch out
You better not cry
You better not pout
I'm telling you why
Santa Claus is coming to town
He's making a list
He's checking it twice
He's going to find out
Whose body we're knighting
Santa Claus is coming to town
He knows when you're sleeping
He knows when you're awake
He knows when you've been found
For good
For the good
For goodness sake
You better watch out
You better not cry
You better not pout
I'm telling you why
Santa Claus is coming to town
and you better not wet your pants
Isn't Santa Claus a good name?
Santa Claus is coming to town
I say be a good boy
But no, you'd better be safe
Santa Claus is coming to town
You better not cry
Jingle, jangle, jingle, we're on a sleigh ride to heck
Santa and his reindeer are really wicked
Wrapped in wrapping paper, we're gonna break our necks
Got a rocket in my pocket on a sleigh ride to heck
Sleigh ride to heck
The elves are full of cheer, the kids are tucked in bed
What?
Santa!
Ain't coming, we're on a sleigh ride to heck
Their dreams are filled with toys, but they're out of luck
Cause Satan's taking Santa on a sleigh ride to fuck
Sleigh ride to heck
Sleigh ride to
Heck
Thank you.
Sleigh ride to heck.
Svenue ride to heck.
Almost time for the bank.
Sleigh ride to heck.
And we will all
And we will all go down together, and we will all go down together.
And we will all go down
town
Hey crime, they're trying to compromise humanity
Death crime
Maniacal fitness
Some genius not intent
Annihilistic fate
We're heading to hell, thank
Our holy sin, we're made
No time to repent
Sleep hate
We're heading to a salvation
We're creeping hell
Sleep hate
We're talking to damnation
We're walking to hell
Sex life is in the past
Our harlech heaven here at last
Immortal firms for us to bear
Stop genius and affair
Best of fighters lose
Work, tribulation and true sex hurts
You've all been taken through
Fallen hands on pleasure
No
Sleep hate
We're heading to a salvation
We're creeping hell
Sleep hate
We're talking to damnation
We're walking to hell
Transcend into next plane
Higher goals to attain
As God you've left we have
Behind super universe
Unwind!
Attempt the stations
Trail of earthly temptations
Over and over, there's a key
Assure, fire and guarantee
Once you've proven your worth
You'll begin the rebirth
To the super universe
In which you will immerse
Sleep hate
Now you're here to turn back
This is where your past is slack
Nothing left to hide
Now you're on the inside
Welcome to the fat head
And the curse that's straight ahead
All the things unsigned
Bring it to the punchline
Sleep hate
We're heading to a salvation
We're creeping hell
Sleep hate
We're talking to damnation
We're walking to hell
Sleep hate
We're heading to a salvation
We're creeping hell
Sleep hate
We're talking to damnation
We're walking to hell
We're going to heaven
We're talking to the inside
When the city is Superman
Sleep hate
utor
The mutants must appear The mutants must arrive
The saucers will fly And the darlings will die
The mutants will leave And fill our space
The doors will carry
The mutants will fly And the darlings will die
The mutants will leave And fill our space
The
Oh, scary man. Totally scary. Scary Broke Fran with his new nameless album and nameless song
about
the well I call it Gary's X Day song. Before that Saint Anne and Helena Handbasket with
Welcome to Hell from their CD by the same name which you can get from www.minitru.org.
Minitru has no E in it. It's M-I-N-I-T-R-U dot org. The Slay Ride to Heck of course was
the great James Kochalka from his new album and album. I'm going to have to say that it's
a great song. And that's also on www.tryedgemusic.com or Indie World with a Y. IndieWorld.com slash
Kochalka with a bunch of K's. Oh and the Jethro's friends here's their address 212 and a half
Miller Avenue. This is the Jethro's 212 and a half. This is a strange number 212 and a
half Miller Avenue. Who's that? I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know. I don't know who admittedly treated me like this I'm doing. This is weird.
Well you just flow the mind of a cow trying to do on it's own, son?
I'd be so Fallout under 13 years of marriage my set in a
liver And I just wanna have another of these
books. I just wanna have another one. Myani Boat Works and my dnces
such as all of them tellxy-Ouch. Just because R revealed that they think we were
part AA Myani did On and on. And R gave me the
really cool time in week and everybody made an ud chen keks pick up a $62 million
god is out right there. And then you think you are Cut Deck or something. And
the music brand Neel is in town with his Rarmed Threatt.lied Klu-n
And at the very bitter end, after the rants, shall be Reverend Mark Mothersbaugh, a silent knight.
Oh, thank you, Slim Spincter.
After all these friendly calls, I got one call from somebody who said,
what are y'all, the usual thing, the usual question, what are y'all trying to do?
And I go, we're trying to give you some slack, okay?
You know, they go, who's Bob?
I said, well, give me your address and I'll send you some information or whatever, you know.
I'll give the number at the end of the broadcast.
And this person, you know, I knew there was something that they weren't saying.
And finally, he goes, well, I just hope that, it was something like,
I just hope that, you know, you can get right with Jesus or something like that.
And just hung up. He hung up. That was the key point.
He said he didn't want to hear what I had to say back about that because,
you know, see, a subgenius has so much faith
that he not only can accept somebody making fun of Bob,
stomping on a picture of Bob, he'll do it himself.
He has so much trust and faith in Bob.
Bob is such a good friend that he can insult Bob.
Now, we subgeni, I hate to get on my soapbox in the middle of a bunch of entertaining tapes,
but we subgeni may be bad,
but our relationship,
our way of bad is holy, is holy compared to the evil of so,
not all, by any means, but so many American fundamentalists,
charismatics, evangelicals, et cetera, in general.
Of course, they and their corresponding types in Iran, Russia, Libya, South Africa, et cetera,
if you ask me, are actually the ace up the devil's sleeve.
Wolves in sheep's clothing, friends, just like Jesus warned about.
I, we're, Jesus and Bob.
Like we say, our old drinking buddies got nothing against Jesus.
It's just his fan club.
And now, we aren't saying that Bob is the ace up God's sleeve.
He's more like the smear on God's handkerchief, just like you or me.
But the uptight rival cults, they don't think God has a handkerchief.
Uh-uh, no, because God's perfect.
He doesn't even sneeze.
We're made in his image, except that we have all these nasty parts attached to us,
and we have to go in the secret room, the bathroom.
To do awful things.
But God, oh, he's clean and pure, according to them.
Oh, and he's male.
But he doesn't excrete juices and sweat and smelly stuff out of him like we do.
Because we sin.
Oh, yeah, we all sin.
We're bad.
We're worthless.
We're no good to God unless we sign a contract with his agent.
Well, friend, Jesus himself, he spouted just about as many great punchlines as Bob.
Probably more.
But, and this is true, this is historical fact.
The very early mainstream Christian church methodically censored about half of the existing gospels about Jesus.
And this, I'm not kidding, you can go to any real bookstore and pick up the censored gospels that they finally found years later.
They took out the parts where Jesus specifically said that every person had equal access to the Lord,
and that you didn't need no preacher between you and him.
That, in fact, was probably his main point, now lost in antiquity,
that you were the son or daughter of God just as much as Jesus was.
Or Bob, see?
But that's too humanistic for the conspiracy Christians,
so they wiped out the subgenius Gnostic Christians.
Anyway, I'm going to get off my soapbox.
We'll get into the hideous theological discussions coming up next week as we attack the Bobbies.
We interrupt this program for a special.
Promotional announcement.
Returns.
E-Bob and the bastards of the universe will be back after this message.
And you young people, listen to me today.
Quit playing games with Christmas trees.
Silent night
Holy night
All
is calm
is bright
Round
young virgins
Tender
and mild
Holy
night
Mother
and child
Sleep
in .
fare
in heavenly .
All again.
Tread on The .
is complete from ue the coming.
bo.
Christmas trees.