Friends, this is where we have to seize fire.
One God, one aim, one destiny, one race.
Especially in this political climate right now where it's getting pretty ugly.
I mean, I know the Democrats and the Republicans are just apple and oranges.
But I think the Republican bearer right now, torchbearer, he is toxic.
And that's where I'm going to stop talking right now.
I've never in all of my 30-something years that I've been in this nation.
It's horrible.
It's just horrible.
It's plain horrible.
So we have to remember that we're all brothers and sisters.
And that's it.
Somebody else is one of just, you know, we've gone that road before.
And we're trying to undo it.
And we're doing pretty good at trying to overcome it.
But for somebody to appeal to the lowest common denominator and it's not good,
that is where things are really bad.
And we, you know, I wish,
I wish Jill Stein or a third party can come in.
Nobody's really thrilled about both candidates.
At this point, it's just a lesser of two evils, you know.
What do you chime in here?
What do you think?
Well, Charleston, I've been around, I've been around this country since 1953.
And I can remember the late 50s.
Yes.
And it's about like it was in the late 50s.
Yeah.
We've gone back in time.
About 52 years, I'd say.
Yes.
You know, it's Georgia.
Who's running for president?
George Wallace.
Yeah.
Yes.
Who, by the way, eventually saw the light and changed, you know, before he, you know,
he left this earth.
But to see a millionaire who's somebody who's, by the way, he made his money ripping a whole
bunch of people off.
You're preaching to the saved, man.
You know, I've been following that guy's career since long before he got into politics,
long before he was on television.
Some of us actually knew who he was because we've been reading the papers that long.
Yes.
But other people have no memory or a short memory or a very, very selective memory.
Yeah.
But don't worry.
Putin will stay out of the Ukraine.
He won't go in there.
Not going to happen.
People won't go in there.
Let's hope not.
If he's right, if Trump is right about that, then he's just as right about every other
word that's coming out of his mouth.
Wow.
I guess so.
Yeah.
You know, yeah.
I just, I just hope this is not the time for, I really want to see you, I want to see the
political system reform.
I want to see a viable third option.
But at this point, it's going to throw it into the other.
And we remember what happened in 2000.
With W, you know.
Well, I, on the second time that Bush, W, George W. Bush ran, I thought, well, there's no way
that Americans are so dumb they'll make that mistake again.
So I voted a third party.
Yeah.
Bush won by one vote.
So I admit it.
It's my fault.
The second Bush administration was all on me because I was dumb enough to have faith
that Americans wouldn't be that dumb.
So I wasted my vote.
Yeah.
I think it was Ralph Nader or some other insane guy at the time.
But it was, I was, I just, I wanted to vote for another party.
Yeah.
It was a dumb idea.
You know.
Yeah.
I threw it away.
And people are making the same mistake again.
They're talking about, I mean, they're making the same mistake again.
And you know what?
Nobody's really crazy about Hillary.
But then again, I don't even know why they hate her so much.
I think it's just.
Because she's a woman, you know, that they're dumping this whole.
And that's.
Well, remember that she's been lied about since the 90s.
There really is a vast right wing conspiracy that routinely.
I don't know if exactly they're lying because they believe it within their enclosed bubble.
Yes.
They believe anything bad about her and anything bad about their guy somehow becomes, well,
he was just kidding or what?
He changed his mind.
Yes.
Well, he's not.
He's not going to tell you his secret plans because he's not stupid.
Yeah.
Yeah, he is.
Actually.
Yeah.
I'm afraid.
It's horrible to see.
Well, somebody has to represent the dumb asses, too.
I'm telling you.
I'm just surprised that there are so many illiterate dumb asses out there.
I'm really shocked.
Absolutely.
I just can't believe that they're doing this to a woman.
And it's all because of her really gender.
You know, all this nonsense.
Well, no.
A lot of it is because she's a liberal.
And liberal is one of the dirty words in the English language now.
Thanks to, oh, was that the liberal controlled media that made it into a dirty word?
Oh, how did that happen?
Yeah.
How contradictory.
How convoluted.
Yeah.
And that's, you know, yeah, that's sad.
But anyway, it's time to move on into our slack, I think, according to our time.
But WCSB Cleveland, we'll keep on fighting the good fight.
I don't really see any lesser evil and what I don't think Hillary's evil guy.
We know who is not Hillary.
Really?
You know, that's my opinion.
Then some people can disagree with it.
But no, you can't disagree anymore.
We changed the Constitution.
That man has no right to criticize me.
As Trump said.
Yeah.
He has no right to say I didn't read the Constitution.
Absolutely.
Well, actually, in the Constitution.
It says he does have a right.
So maybe you didn't read it, Mr. Trump.
He didn't read it.
And, you know, come on.
Come on.
Let's put this woman through.
It's about time.
Jeez.
It's about time we see a woman president in this country.
Why are they rising up against her?
Well, I'd rather see Melania Trump because she's a hooker.
She is.
And Hillary is just, she's the sea hag.
Yeah.
She's so ugly.
Her hair looks bad.
Yeah.
Where's my other beard?
They're coming out of the woodwork.
My pants don't fit no more.
Why did that button pop off my pants?
Gay-itude is a lifestyle choice.
But obesity, that's just genetics.
I can't help it.
Yeah.
I know those rednecks pretty well, man.
But let's leave things of this world behind
and walk now down the path of Bob for this brief minute of slack
from the church of the subgenius.
Release your hold on this tenuous practical joke they call reality.
Let your body be sucked out of your ears
for we're going to take you deep, deep inside yourself
to the place of silence in the noise.
We're going deep.
Deeper.
Deeper into your consciousness.
Down past the membranes of the fabric of your very mind.
We bore down into the cranium,
drilling through the irrelevant memories of job and normality,
piercing the squamous epizootis rolling around
in the hollowed-out inside of the skull,
scraping along the edges of the birth canal
and stretching the imagination gland until it pops.
Now, let all your thoughts drain out through the brain.
Tumble down through the sinuses, slide down the esophagus,
and finally, let them plunge to the base of the soul itself,
located in the lowest organ of your body, the foot gland.
And finally, an idea, a key, an ultimate plan
is born at the very bottom of your mind.
And it is Bob.
Let there be slack.
See www.subgenius.com
It sounds great.
What sounds great?
To bring all your drugs,
bring all your froth,
you know, go on the radio.
You think it's hot?
I think it's bitter cold.
What is the matter?
Hal feels the wind blowing between his shows.
That's right.
Show last night, show before night, show after night.
The shows, I'm being pelted.
The shows, man.
There he is.
Hal's coming out on stage now.
Hey, everybody.
Hi, it's me.
I've got shows.
Do I?
It's the real man.
Oh, my.
He looks younger than I thought.
What?
Have you been listening to music that has passed its expiration date?
You need new vibrations in your ears.
Yeah.
ears, foreheads, they don't wait!
The rhythm's human dancing,
got you feeling less than fresh.
It's a catchy little number,
we think that you should catch!
Don't let your soundtrack sound stale.
Here's a rhythm that'll make you wag your tail.
Please give your complete attention!
Vanity is a new submission!
Close the lid!
Open the door!
Give me a kiss!
Give me some more!
Tell me what to do!
I like it when you tell me what to do!
Put it in front!
Put it back!
Tell me what you need!
I like it like that!
Tell me what to do!
I like it when you tell me what to do!
Should I do it now?
Should I do it then?
Should I do it at all?
Should I do it again?
Tell me what to do!
I like it when you tell me what to do!
Tell me what to do
I like it when you tell me what to do
Should I move it here?
Should I bring it back?
Should I move it there?
Should I paint it black?
Tell me what to do
I like it when you tell me what to do
world
I like it when things go well
I like it when I
Like it when I
Thank you.
And I think it's going to be a long, long time.
The touchdown brings me around again to find I'm not the man they think I am.
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm Bob.
Starts with a B.
What is it, man?
I knew it when I came in here, man.
Ends with a B.
No, don't tell me.
Ten seconds, Bob.
Bob!
Well, it's really great to have you on the show tonight, Bob.
Well, it isn't that far out in Sullivan right on, Bob.
I am willing to admit that war has accomplished much in the projects of the world.
I'm willing to admit that there are certain crises in the forward march of history.
I'm willing to admit that perhaps it could not have been missed in any other way than by the force.
I'm willing to admit that war developed certain heroic traits in men
and furnishes a test for the evidence of the highest character.
I am willing to admit that during the Revolution of 1917,
the revolutionaries did not have a choice but to cause most of the economic crisis that plagued our flesh,
As such, I don't think statues belong to men,
but to fathers and children.
Those who sacred arelaughing are paying more than everything they deserve!
.
La la la la la
Truffle trail sandwich
Sandwich or champagne
I am in so good a shot
With the eddies and currents in that protoplasm, the probe could drift thousands of kilometers.
I am the jolly happy scrotum
I come from jolly scrotum land
He is the happy jolly scrotum
He thinks that genitals are grand
I found a very strange tie-in between Alistair Crowley and the Church of the Subgenius.
I mean, of course it has...
A lot of people do.
Yeah, but I mean, the whole thing with the kid.
I mean, there's something really big behind that.
Mm-hmm.
Um...
I just...
I just don't even know what to say about it.
The kid?
Yeah, at the end of that movie with the Manly P. Hall guy in the 50s,
where that Bob figure comes in.
They're in the court with Vincent Price.
Um...
What was the name of that movie?
It's about the history of mankind.
And the movie ends with...
It's called The History of Mankind.
The History of Mankind.
Yeah, and the movie ends with that kid.
And the kid...
The little baby.
Yeah.
And that's Bob.
Yeah, the Bob's in The Stranger, too.
Orson Welles played Bob in that one.
I think I have a...
You don't see any Eddie.
That's not a grand thing.
Somebody, I mean, I will.
I will put together some sort of new occult order.
Eddie Haskell?
Yeah.
Someone tried it with Beaver, right?
Someone tried the Church of Beaver Cleaver.
Yeah.
The Church of Jainer.
Doesn't work.
Yeah.
It only works...
Those are all the Church of the Earth.
The Church of the Subgenius is the only one that really actually works.
Oh, I see the computers flashing in the position.
Well, I've noticed some strange coincidences with Bob's kids.
Rod and...
Was it Rod and Todd?
Or Rod and...
Bib and Bob.
No, it's mentioned in one of the books.
I mean, I see this extension of it based on his kid.
And it ties into Rahur Kruit.
Right, right.
The crowned and conquering child.
Exactly.
And Tyche.
See, now that's...
You've picked those up.
You've picked that up.
And you're right.
There's a lot of, you know, stitching together of concepts maybe previously developed in other places.
I mean, I even signed up to the...
So thanks.
Yes, exactly.
Because he's listening to KPFA.
God, I love this show.
I love the books.
KPFA.org.
And I don't see Eddie Paye anywhere.
I don't see anybody else coming in.
Yeah, what's going on?
Should we change over to the other show format?
Okay, we just did.
Now it's totally different.
I've got...
Let people know.
Like those sad guys driving around with their RVs.
Sized off the hockey ring.
Of the hockey arena.
Capable of holding...
30,000 people inside of it.
Like those the NHL teams play.
You know.
In the middle of Colorado desert.
Max's mom capacity.
Uh, 30,000 people, yes?
Not all of them wearing skates, you know.
Some of them only have sticks.
Some of them even don't have sticks.
They just kick the puck around with their feet.
Looking toenails.
Infested with fungus.
And other smelly food disease.
Think about the odor on a hot summer day.
.
Now getting back to the business at hand.
Bob is here.
And I don't know Bob that well, but I do know him to be a guy that just never stops coming.
And that's certainly good, but...
And let's see if we can get somewhere else with Bob.
And see who he is.
I'm interested.
I know a lot of you people know him.
Because he's been around a long time.
And some of you may have grown up with him somehow.
I've always respected Bob.
He's a difficult man to talk to.
And uh...
So let's take a listen to Bob.
.
Basically, Bob.
Watch in front of...
It was a diplomat.
So the whole audience was blue haired.
Bob being you.
Bob being third person.
I'm like...
.
Bob wouldn't do that.
That's not right for Bob.
I'd like to talk to Bob about that.
Bob's not comfortable talking about this.
Because when Bob leaves here, he puts his...
What do you call it?
A glock in the car.
Yeah, the glock.
Yeah.
Or a nine.
Do they still use nines?
Bob's people do.
They do?
They use nines?
And glocks.
Nines and glocks and a blunt.
And a blunt.
For the other thing.
.
For that other thing.
Bob's doing...
You're opening Bob.
.
me
I wanna die for God
I wanna
die in a holy
hole and drown
the faint boys in the
normal state
if we have to
God can make them die
and we'll all
come back older
come back
older men
all over the
world
sing a gut to another kid
praise God
fill me Bob
I wanna die for
God
I wanna find us
the holy war
fulfill the faint boys
and the normal
state
if we have to
we can make them
die and we'll all
come back older
and we'll all
come out older
men if we don't
men there ain't no
reason why
all rob's
chisms they will
fall beneath our
feet
men we'll all
come back older
men in victory
the race
music
music music
music music music music music music music move music music music music music music music music
music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music music
music music music live music music music music music music music
I think it kind of scared him that we showed up this door.
But it's a complete mystery.
Yeah, Doug 3, we were numbering the Dugs then.
Before that song, there was a collage somewhere else with Bob,
with people talking.
That was cut up by Reverend Dr. Royal Decapitator.
We heard some puzzling evidence radio show,
and I think that was the large calling in to the puzzling evidence show
with Puzzling Evidence Dr. Howell and Dr. Philodrumon,
that we, of course, heard the Rudy Schwartz project
with a song called Surrey with the Durable Gelatin Sock.
The short piece called Bob Squad was by the Great Groovy Neptune.
There was a cut up, I don't know, Jethro Tull or something.
That was done by Lee Murr.
The 26th.
The 27-minute, or 27-second version of Oh Canada was the Psychoskeletons.
That was an old one, but it was preceded by a new instrumental
by the Psychoskeletons called New Shoes.
And the song and stuff at the very beginning, Tell Me What to Do,
was the band Exposed Four Heads,
who we'll be seeing at the Devotional soon,
August.
19th and 20th, I think.
And also the fantastic Plastics are going to be playing there.
I may have a bunch of bands, a bunch of real good bands.
The Spud Boys with Reverend Angry Larry standing in for Bob Mother's Ball.
What?
Although Bob Mother's Ball is also going to be there.
Well, you didn't know Reverend Angry Larry is in the Spud Boys now.
I did not know that.
Yeah.
He's going to be doing their guitar parts.
Oh, man, that's going to be the best Spud Boys ever.
Well, the Spud Boys are always the best Spud Boys ever.
They only get to play together once a year.
I know.
So this will be interesting.
Now, aha, this deck here was placed on single play mode.
We don't like single play.
So we'll go up to seven.
Bernard Herrmann music there in the background.
Yes, yes.
Bernard Herrmann.
I'm going to probably keep that beginning of the show there where African Abstract went kind of long.
Because I started ranting about Trump.
And don't get me started.
Oops.
Too late.
In fact, you know, I've decided that Big Sister isn't the lesser of two evils.
Actually, I love Big Sister.
And Big Sister loves me.
And I know that because I'm hot.
I mean, I really it's actually we're very sweaty here.
Wouldn't you agree, Princess?
It's a bit clammy here.
Yeah.
The air conditioning seems to be off and and it's hot in the station.
And Hillary got me hot.
I mean, Big Sister.
Big Sister got me so hot.
And it wasn't it wasn't a professionalism of her presentation or so much.
It was just she dared to say.
Four words.
The filthiest sentence I've heard anybody in the mainstream media say in a long time.
Well, it was four.
It was a sentence of four words, but it had the one dirtiest word in the media.
She said she was looking at me across the television ocean right right at my eyes.
And she goes, I believe in science.
I believe in science.
And I said, man, fluids just started coming out of my body right then and there.
You saw it.
I saw it.
He's not exaggerating.
Right in front of Princess Wee.
I was slobbering.
I was spewing.
I've scrum was all over everywhere.
He had scrum everywhere because he was in ecstasy after she said that.
She said that word that dirty, dirty word science.
Now, the next day I noticed that.
The conservatives were saying, I know what science means.
That's libtard for give make them give all their money to Al Gore.
Because he invented the Internet.
He invented the Internet.
Have you ever heard that?
He did.
He really did.
He invented the Internet.
And.
Listeners, if you could see Reverend Stang when he laughs like that, it's almost makes you wet your pants.
My teeth actually buck out and it hurts.
I actually physically transform into that redneck that they tried to raise me to be when I was growing up in Fort Worth, Texas.
It's pretty scary, folks.
Learning how to how to use gun safety and ride a horse and all that.
And I do know gun safety and I do know how to ride a horse and I have a gun and I'm not at all worried.
You know, Obama's had eight years to take our guns away.
And all it's resulted is is an eight year gun sale at gun shows.
Not a single gun got touched.
That just proves he's incompetent and arrogant.
Actually, arrogant was a new word they learned because they knew that it was not cool to say uppity.
They wanted to say uppity.
But it just, you know, well, I'm sure you can now.
The times have changed.
It's become much more.
Well, you just can't stop them from from talking nasty, saying words like science.
You know, science really means when a libtard says science.
So what that means is you give all your money to Al Gore again and again because it's like the summer.
I'm surprised when summer's hot.
I can't believe it.
Oh, because liberalism is a mental illness.
Let me spell that for you.
M.I.N.
T.L.E.
E.L.L.
N.I.S.S.
Mental illness because they're illiterates.
Ignorant.
It's so ignorant.
But so you can't talk to a libtard because they already made up their mind.
You show them the facts.
That's right.
Hillary killed those four people and cackled about it over drinks.
Yes, she did.
And you try to tell them that and they just they just look at you and they don't even continue the conversation.
They don't try to argue with you.
They just still go ahead and vote.
But they won't be allowed to do that for long because after we get Mr.
Trump in there, then we're going to be singing a different song.
Then when you go to vote, you only get to vote for the smart people like him.
And he's the only smart one.
I'd say that I was smart.
But when I say what he says, it just sounds stupid.
Putin won't go in there.
Putin won't go into Ukraine.
See, it sounds stupid when I say it.
Because two years ago, he already did invade the Ukraine.
But see, Trump was just leading them on.
He's trying to make them think he doesn't know what's going on.
But that's because he's outsmarting them, see.
And they can't tell sarcasm.
He says he wants Russia to destroy the Democrats.
That's not anti-American.
He's just being funny.
Right, of course.
Because I do too.
I want all of them to die.
I want her locked up.
Because I'm an alcoholic and I don't have a job.
And it's the fault of the media and the libtards and those Clintons that did this to me.
Because they invented ISIS.
Because they made it weak.
They made us weak.
They invented it to bring down America.
Because they're all muslims.
Don't you laugh at my bug-eyed face, woman.
You're not supposed to be uppity like that.
Y'all should be seeing this.
If you would see this, you would be wetting your pants.
Quit being so arrogant, woman.
Shut your mouth.
Oh, she's kidding.
She just about hit me.
I'm so whipped.
I love you, big sister.
But really, I mean, that one word.
Science.
That's what you call emergentile subgenius pornography.
A strong woman talking about science.
That's so nasty.
Uh-oh.
Now I'm turning into Philo, turning into the Joker.
But somebody has to balance Philo.
Somebody has to be the balance.
That's right.
That's me.
You put us on a teeter-totter, I don't know who'd win.
Because he'd probably cheat.
He would cheat.
He'd bounce and bounce until he cheated.
That's not cheating.
He'd think of some other way to cheat.
Before we even got to the playground, he would have put a lead weight on the bottom of my end of the teeter-totter.
And then he'd convince me to sit there.
Oh, this is a better end.
You know, I'm so generous.
That Philo drunk.
You can't trust a subgenius.
Except to lie or to disobey you.
And that's how you get him to do stuff.
You just tell him not to do something.
God, it worked like gangbusters at X-Day.
Only it backfired.
Only the problem was I was the one who cheated.
And he said not to do something.
And it backfired.
But we've already talked about that over and over again.
Or will.
And I've gotten so insecure about repeating myself.
I'm afraid to say much of anything.
Because how do I know I haven't already said it the last five shows in a row?
See, I did.
Didn't I just say, just what I'm saying now?
I know I said that.
Yeah, you probably did.
I should just quit.
I was going to ask Susie the floozy.
Should I quit?
Because I'm going deaf and I can't remember anything anymore.
I'm just an old man.
Maybe I should quit while I'm ahead.
Or before I get any much too much further behind.
You know, there's something missing from this picture.
I think I know.
I think I know the thing that's missing.
And it starts with a D.
No, it starts with an L.
Well, yeah, there's an L in there too.
And a C.
But.
L-C-D.
That's what I write down in my little notes.
Gaze.
But.
Oh, and yeah, I missed that on my notes on that puzzling evidence clip.
I think that was the large who's from Finland.
Yes.
And has an accent.
It did sound like the large.
And I think it was the large imitating Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
He said, even said something about eat our smelly feet or something.
That sounds just like something Dave would say.
He doesn't have to try.
He's kind of like the Finnish.
And the language.
Dave.
Naturally.
Without trying.
We decided that when we met him.
He achieved achieving this, but without trying.
Well actually as Bob can do that.
When we met him, thanks to Tanya and Bucky.
Yeah.
And we can't even tell if they're listening because we can no longer see the flags of
the listening countries or their 90s as they walk past the camera.
No, but praise Tanya and Bucky anyway.
Sounds good.
So, well, I think I'm going to cut back to music because that's what I would do normally.
Because we have this song by the Fantastic Plastics.
I can't understand the lyrics to anything anymore because of my deepness.
So I hope there's no cuss words in here.
But they're such a nice couple.
I think it was a couple when we saw them.
And she's so pretty.
She looks just like a stewardess from 1965.
I'm not kidding either.
And I remember stewardesses in 1965.
They were all females then.
Isn't that funny?
That's why they were called stewardesses.
But see, the men had to move in and wanted equal pay.
Not just those.
So I just want you all to be happy that you performed to this 1,000 bucks bill,
because we've received a recordnad new record.
it doesn't matter which number you got.
The more you rock it, the faster you get on.
You're welcome.
He's the best.
And remember,
you're not stupid.
I knew you so good
Mr. Computer
I work in a factory
Factory
And I build the machinery
Machinery
And I knew you so good
I knew you so good
Mr. Computer
Ditto, ditto
It's so simple, yeah, yeah
Ones and zeros in your head
Add them up, you'll soon be dead
It's so simple with a
Ditto, ditto
Yeah, yeah
My database
Told yours off
Then my computer
Shut right off
Oh no
My computer shut right off?
That was the Fantastic Plastics
And they will be performing
At the devotional
And Princess Wee
Made a little phone call
And reminded the Rewardian
That it is, in fact
Time to call the show
What an idiot I was
I thought it was
About ten after nine
He said was
This is our Dave
He's here with us now
I thought it was
About ten minutes after nine
I was like, well
I better start getting ready
Pretty soon
And then I get this call
From We Are Dose
Saying it's forty minutes
After the hour
Which, are you using
The sundial in your backyard
At nine-thirty at night
Or the sundial in your
Front yard at nine-thirty
Those things where the sand
Goes, you turn them
Upside down
The sand goes up backwards
An hourglass
An hourglass, yeah
I'm wearing one right now
It feels like a sausage
Or something
Stuck in the side of my head
I don't know
Maybe that was the reason
Why I dysfunculated
I didn't mean it
I really didn't
Was there something important
We were talking about
That I missed even that too?
Yeah, you missed
A Finnish subgenius
From Finland
Calling into the
Puzzling Evidence show
And imitating you
Oh, that's very good
Because I just
I just wrote me a story
About a Finnish monument
Which is listing to the left
That's not a political statement either
It's just the way it is
A Finnish historical monument
Of all the immigrants
In Fairport Harbor
Got eliminated by the wind
Goodness
Something
That doesn't sound good
I don't know
I just shaved my scrotum
What do I know about anything?
You know, I guess
We played a song about that too
There has been a song
About a scrotum this evening, Dave
There was a song about
See, I'm synchronistically lapsed out
And stuck right in
Even though I was
Where did I go for 25 minutes?
Then it makes no sense to me
I don't know
Well, that was the good part of the show
No, that was the empty part
With no Dave in
Actually, we had
Charleston Okafor on earlier
Because his show
Kind of lapsed over
Because he asked me what I thought
Right as his show was ending
And I started answering the question
And it turned into another
Five or ten minute discussion
Oh, wow
You have a lot of thoughts then, don't you?
Well, no
I was utilizing the thoughts of
The people I grew up with
In Fort Worth, Texas
I'm able to tap into that
And I can actually think
Like
A chimpanzee
I would say
It's a close call, yes
What are those?
Trimpanzees
What are they called?
That's a new simian genus
I get mixed up with the orangutans
Because they also have that orange tone to them
But really
They're not the same as the ones on Monkey's Retreat
Or whatever they called it in Spain
Or what's the name of a planet of the eight
I knew J. Fred Muggs
And you, Mr. Trump, are no J. Fred Muggs
Think like a trumpanzee
Trumpanzee
I knew Jojo the Monkey Boy
And you, Mr. Trump, are no Jojo the Monkey Boy
That might sound funny on paper
But you know it could be true
He could be Jojo the Monkey Boy's
Distant caller
There's possibility in this
You must rescind your operations
And refract on every
Single total possibility
Where would such an orangutan-like creature
Have actually come from?
Everybody knows
Oh, Dad gave a million bucks to start his own business
But where was he before that?
Was he in the Chicago Zoo?
Was he in the Bronx Zoo somewhere
Trying to hide now?
Or what was he doing?
Man
Eating bananas
That's all we know
Actually, there's a lot we know
And the funny thing is
My question has now been answered
I've been wondering
For months now
Okay, when is the real
Slapdown going to start?
Because they've been handling this guy with kid gloves
They've been just
Giving him a pass on everything
When do the gloves come off?
And when do they pull out the old footage?
When do they start pulling out the old lawsuits?
When do they pull out all the
And by golly
It has started
Yes
And it started with the
The King Ape himself
Insisting that
Even though he knows
Doesn't know Putin
Putin ain't gonna go in there
He ain't gonna go in
And if he does go in there
If he did go in
That was all
It was Obama was with him
When that happened
But it's okay
Everything's gonna be okay
Russia can be our friend
Well, yeah
What about all this Russia turmoil
Versus these people
The kind of people you grew up with
In Fort Worth
Who have hair on the back of their head
I knew Peter the Great
The Tsar of Russia
And you, Mr. Trump
Are no Peter the Great
Well
Ivan, a terrible possibly
There's a lot more in common there
With Ivan the Great
Ivan the Terrible
On the other hand
I'm probably talking over the heads
Of some people
Because not everybody has a degree
In Russian history
Like I do
Well, I have a degree in social sciences
And I studied Soviet politics
For three years
While I was, you know
Doddling around being an art major
Not knowing what I was doing
Except for playing in bands
And drawing goofy pictures
Oh, so that's what happened to you
And I would say that
On Facebook
They just recently
Had a cartoon
Not a cartoon
There was a picture of a monkey
And underneath it
There was these Russian ships
That they claimed were used as
An enneagram
A fosterator of our military prowess
Like at the Democratic National Convention
You know, has that ever proven
To be a real news story?
Oh, wait
Because somebody
Out the window of the convention
They could see some
Supposedly Russian ships
And they formed a code
Or something
What was that?
I didn't get that
Well, no
They showed ships
Our military
Might and action
Here on the Pacific
And then
They show a bunch of ships
And they're Russian ships
And the idea was
That some person
Working in PR
For the Democratic National Convention
Went looking for some pictures
Of American destroyers
And battleships
And put in
A bunch of Russian ones
Oh
It seems so hard to believe
That anybody could be so stupid
And be so high up on the
You know
It doesn't matter
He's not going to go into the Ukraine anyway
Yeah
Well, none of us are really hard
But speculatively
We're all kind of going to
Be thinking about it
Forever
I didn't hear the thing
About the Russian ships
And to tell the truth
If I'd seen them on television
I wouldn't have jumped up
And said
Well, that's a bunch of damn Russian ships
I just
It's like
If it's a long shot
Of a battleship
It's just going to look like
A damn battleship to me
They don't paint them
In red, white, and blue
Yeah, it's very suspect
I wanted to see
If it emerged
Into a true news story
It's just one of those
Facebook news stories
Oh, give me a break
I can write Facebook
In fact, I do it all the time
I know, yeah
You ever heard of Bob Dobbs?
He's this guru
From outer space
He can do anything
Give me money
Yeah, that's why I asked you
Because you're
You're great
You're great for
You're
And you're
You're great ability
To rescind
The following message
No, you're great ability
To follow through
On things like that
Okay
Director
Jesus is my rind
He protects me all the time
I'm soft on the inside
But he is my rind
Yeah, he is your rind
And I'm a grapefruit
And without him
Life's a grind
And Jesus is my rind
Yes
Because I'm just a grapefruit boy
See, we wrote a new Devo song
Right there
Yeah
I'm glad you did
We'll have to tell
We'll have to tell Jerry Casale
About that
Well, I'm glad you did
We owe it all to the sign
That had the F missing
From friends
Oh, yeah
That's right
We were in Texas
We drove by a church
That said
Jesus is your rind
Because the F fell off
And they never knew
About the E to begin with
It was pretty good
Jesus is my rind
Yeah
He's my grapefruit
Jesus and everything
I love that
He's my squeezer
Jesus is my squeezer
Now, this is
Friends, listeners
We don't have any problem
With
Jesus
Not at all
Or
The Buddha
Lucifer
For that matter
Or, well, no
Lucifer or Bob
It's just their fan club
Don't you know
How those Bobbies are?
They're just so obnoxious
They won't shut up about it
So, you know
Fanatics are the same
In every
In every culture
And if you're a subgenius minister
And you have followers
Do you know what your job
Is to do?
In the face of those followers?
To show them what subgeniuses do
To followers?
I think you know
That's why it's spelled
Job
It's spelled J-A-W-B
Because we want jobbers
We want people who can jabber
And who can just
Endlessly go on about the power
The mystique
The intellectual capacity
Of Bob
The earnest one
Always done for your earnest
I'm sorry
We're looking for people
Who like to draw
Flies
And I did do that
When it X'day
And I'm not going to do it again
See, again, Dave
We're having trouble
Remembering
What we said
On which show
On which rant
On which week
And if it has been played yet
We're looking for people
Who know how to draw
And then dot, dot, dot
Flies
That is so beautiful
It's ageless
And that's why
It will be repeated
Now and again
And you can't
You can't say
Oh, we said that
Last week
We can never say it again
It must be said
Every day
Every week
We're looking for people
Who like to draw
Customers
To our
Shopping cart page
Yeah, that's it
No
Remember those comic books
In the back of every comic book
The Ripoff Art Institute
Trump Art School
I joined them
Can you draw this pirate?
Can you draw this parrot?
And you draw this pirate
And you draw
Really, you know
Trace it
And send it to them
And they'd go
Wow, you're a really great artist
Send us 30 more dollars
Yeah
And we'll send you this book
About how to draw
You'll be in our art school
Yeah
I was dumb enough to do that
When I was little
I tried it
Like
I'm the world's greatest artist
Man
Here's a picture of
Lucifer Hitler
In a nazi suit
Because I was interested
In history at the time
And I drew a picture
Of Jesus Lucifer
In a nazi suit
No, I actually drew the lady
The one with the
Ski
Ski list nose
Right
Yeah, there were several
Different things you could draw
There was an Indian
A pirate
A lady
A bird
A cute
Like cartoon deer
Bambi
Actually, a couple of
I saw on Facebook
A couple of my
Professional artist friends
Did in fact draw that
And did learn
From that course
A little bit
They probably
Paid a little bit much
They could have gotten
A little bit more money
But they were
You know
How to draw two circles
And make them look like
A fat guy
And you know
At the art store
Those books were a dollar
Back then
I remember
I still have one of those books
I never did
Learn my lessons
Oh yeah, and how much
Were Mad Magazine's
Were only a quarter
Remember those days
When they were only a quarter
And they didn't have ads
No advertising in Mad Magazine
Up until about five years ago
And that was when
Our subscription lapsed
Yes
I think it was actually
Closer to ten years ago
Ten years ago
But I will take your word for it
Yeah
You know you may be right
You may be right
We originally got a subscription
To Mad for her nephew
Because Mad Magazine
Helps build young bodies
Twelve different wives
Well actually
He I think when he was seven
Requested it
He requested
But then we got one for us too
And I got him a subscription then
And I have maintained it since
Oh but you didn't maintain
Our Mad since
No
I was going to say
You haven't been maintaining
Very much
You know I mean
You're very well either
Because I heard some stories
About your screaming out the window
At all hours of the morning
So I don't think you've been
Really involved
Well now that was because
That was because
Back when I was about twelve
Mad doubled as like a playboy
The way the female figure
Was drawn by some artist
I'm thinking about you Dave Berg
Oh yeah
He was a jerk
Oh he was a jerk
But he could sure draw up dames
And quite a few
Oh and by the way
Jack Davis died
The great cartoonist Jack Davis
Died this week
He brought us many Mad Magazine covers
And whole features
And album covers
And he was just
He was everywhere
My favorite one was
The Norman Rockwell takeoff
Where the man shot off his thumb
At the Thanksgiving table
Do you remember that one
That was a Don Martin strip wasn't it
Or are you thinking
It was a cover
A cover oh okay
And it looked like
The Thanksgiving dinner
The Norman Rockwell
It was probably painted
By Kelly Freese
That's right
Yes
It was Kelly Freese
It's strange that we know these names
In some ways
But really you know
When we were twelve years old
We read every single word
On those magazines
Including the artists
And writers names
And we remembered stuff
From back then too
The funniest response
We could give to anybody
Was what me worry
And look at us now
We're still worried
And we're worried
No kidding
Actually I've seen
A couple of good Mad covers
Since the Trump Zoo
Was opened up
And the cages were unlocked
And they quit
You know they quit
You know the shovelers
Quit cleaning up
After the creatures in there
Now isn't there something
About the Trumpster
As some of the right wing
People like to call him
The Trumpster
Didn't he get into
A disvagary
With the family
Of the kid
Who was a Muslim soldier
Who saved the rest of the people
That's been the biggest headlines
For three days
Yeah
Well what's why
Except to the people
Who hear this show
Three weeks from now
There's a lot of people
Who are going to be going
Oh yeah I vaguely remember that
Is that the kid
That made the clock bomb
In Texas
Or is it
There was something
About a Muslim kid
Or a guy that died
Or some guy that
Said Trump was a jerk
That's right
I can't remember
Oh well that was
A long time ago
Three weeks ago
Yeah right
The cycles will have all
Run through by then
I'm sorry
We're on WCSB in Cleveland
Sometimes
But then the same thing
Ends up on WREK Atlanta
Or WORT
And then we're on
WPAI in Madison
Or friends I can't remember
The call signs of
In Knoxville
And Florida
You know the town Florida
Yeah Florida
I've got a list in my briefcase
Brrr
WFMU in New Jersey
Their ghost station
We were on WFMU
For years and years and years
But then like K&ON in Dallas
They changed leadership
They changed owners
Concern it
And since we weren't there
To do pledge drives
They cancelled the hour of
Slack on WFMU
That was their excuse
Now it could be that
The quality of the shows
That particular year
Were starting to get a bit
Raggedy around the edges
Not like now
But yeah you know what I mean?
It is
Speaking of which
My beloved Cleveland listeners
There's going to be a pledge drive
In October or November
And we're not going to be here to do it
And we're going to have to
I'll have to play the old
Pledge drive generic show
And hope that somebody
Probably Dr. Sinister can help
To get some money in
Because you know
Time things are tight
And what's also tight is time
Don't you think we can do a show
From far away?
Oh yeah I guess we could
We could call it. We could do a live show
And call it in
I keep forgetting about that
We can phone it in
They have phones in Texas
Yes they have phones
Yeah
I even have one strapped to my hip
Like a six gun now
Yes we should do a real live
Radiothon show
So we can appeal to our listeners
We still need a hostess twinkler
To expand on the product
Well we'll twinkle all we can
Over the phone
Friends you're listening to
The subgenius radio ministry
Hour of Slack
Number 1581
And we have to go now
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
So Dave I have to say
It's been a short one
But next time you need to wear
Your alarm watch
Strapped to your eyeball
Yes I definitely will
I certainly wanted to be on
For the entirety
Because I thought I could
And actually if I would have called
Right when I got off work
I would have made the entirety
But since it is a short one
And you know and I know
What we're talking about
We both know what that means
Shucks
I'll just go and vomit in the bag
Don't go and vomit in the bag
Oh god that's gross
I hate it when he does that
That's just horrible
Gross
So gross
Yeah
This is what we're talking about
We're talking about
And the next
To the world
We'll be right back.