We're going into places where men's minds are more tangled than the worst underbrush in the jungle, and I'm afraid.
More afraid than I've ever been in my life.
Everywhere we'll be met with lies and deceit.
Your honesty and directness will only be handicaps.
It would break my heart to see your strength and courage caught in the quicksands of civilization.
Carsen always trusts Jane.
Bob and Connie really enjoy life.
Oh, yeah.
I pray for the subgenius.
Slack.
It was full of holes and was licking.
Wet and damp.
My children and I thank you.
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
the star of our show,
America's number one funny man, Bob.
Praise Bob!
Now I want everybody to chant in unison,
We are abnormals.
Any subgenius tells you to do that.
Don't do it.
Damn!
A little clip there from the Winterstar devival earlier this month.
And, yes, friends, welcome to the hour of Slack number 1085.
The first normal show that we've done in months.
That is, it's not a live show with a million pre-recorded bits,
mixed in, but a pre-recorded show with lots of live bits mixed in. Also, it's an unusually
explanatory show in that in honor of some news stations that have just started carrying the hour
of slack, we're going to actually explain the Church of the Subgenius and J.R. Bob Dobbs.
And we're happy to have the word of Dobbs carried to Richmond, Indiana by way of newly
in-sanctioned station WECI, joining such stalwarts as WQFS in Greensboro, North Carolina,
WEFT in Champaign, Illinois, WHUS in Mighty Stores, Connecticut, WICA in Milwaukee, WNPG in Portland,
Maine, and beloved WORT in Madison, Wisconsin, Mighty WREK in Atlanta, and WCSB Cleveland.
Plus on shortwave at 7.4.
One five mega Bob's at WBCQ Sundays at 11 Eastern, plus 19 godzillion internet shows,
all seen at subgenius.com.
Now this episode, friends, in explaining the mysteries of Bob and Slack will include our
very oldest church radio recordings and the very latest.
We'll hear some preaching at the Winter Star Symposium revival on February 10th,
and some puzzling evidence sub radio from KPFA Berkeley on February 10th.
On February 16th, with Dr. Howland, Dr. Philodrum, and were firstly free from forgiving
and unyielding, I'll hear from aポイント fromirk.
But before I get there, Japanese I have a show
to show on Facebook,
and if you'd like to listen to me speak Spanish, please go to my site, WCC, Highway two,
Texas friends in the year of 1980. If the last 50 years made such a change, just imagine the New
York of 1980 when everyone has a number instead of a name and the government tells you whom you
should marry. Just imagine 1980. Yes, imagine. Just imagine 1980. But this was not only one of the
first shows hosted by Mr. Opinion, but it was also our very first radio appearance ever, talking for
the first time in public about the Church of the Subgenius. They're here in the studio now, and I
thought we might chat with them for just a minute before we go back out to the fur auction. Reverend
Stang, are you any kin to Arnold Stang? No, thanks. I'm glad you brought that up. I'm no kin at all to
Arnold Stang.
I did notice that around the ankles you looked a whole lot like Arnold, and I thought maybe it was a
family trait. He may also be a true human like myself. That's very possible, though he doesn't
act like it, at least not any time I ever saw him. Really now, are you guys in this cult business
just for the bucks, or do you have some greater ambition in life? Well, we are definitely in it
for the bucks, I'd say. But the bucks are going to a good place.
Well, what is that? What is the good purpose? Our basic deal, this is our first time on the radio,
and so this may sound very cosmic for a lot of people. You're not real sure you're even on the
radio. You have to have a lot of faith in this business that you're actually on the radio.
We pretty much don't have any faith in anybody anywhere except while we're reading their little
pamphlets and books that they put out. Our basic deal is that the world is... Well, first, I want to correct you there.
How can you have a cult and not have faith? We have... In fact, the way that we choose to have faith is that we
believe everything we read while we're reading it. Or say we're watching TV, we believe the show that we're on,
The Incredible Hulk, for instance, may seem outlandish after the thing is off, but while you're watching it,
why not go for it, enjoy it for what it is? And then you actually have faith. You believe what you see when you see it.
Even if it's a TV show like that. Right. Plus, we can interpret these things in a subgenius way.
For instance, say The Incredible Hulk is a good symbolic subgenius. He's a... Normally, he's just a retiring,
mild-mannered, regular guy, but when you push him a little bit too far, go after his values or
something, he becomes the raging true human, the master human that... That's when his shirt tears.
Yeah, he gets green. And of course, we've got our...
our ever-present faith in our leader, J.R. Bob Dobbs. Yes, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Where does J.R. Bob hang out? Does he... Do you guys frequently see him, or is he a person that...
Is he like the Reverend Moon, who is highly visible at times and then sheltered at other times?
Well, Bob is always sheltered, and he's never highly visible. He's a very reclusive person.
I see. Is that where a lot of the money goes? Yeah.
Or do you get to keep some for yourself? Oh, well, he pays us, but...
I see. As for what... He puts it into research,
pretty much. Time control research, genetic manipulation, that kind of thing. Basically,
what he's trying to do is unmask the conspiracy. He...
Conspiracy? What conspiracy is that? We're the conspiracy behind the conspiracy,
hunters behind the conspiracy. Oh, like the trilateralists and those people?
Uh-huh. Do you know about those people? We know... We have agents in the trilateralists.
Well, pardon me, I shouldn't be saying that kind of thing on the radio, but we do have
inside sources that inform us of what's going on in, say, the Trilateral Commission or the
Council on Foreign Relations. And we found that they are not the only ones that are behind
the conspiracy. They're not the only ones controlling what we say and do and think.
Do you tell your members what you find out? We tell our members pretty much everything.
I see. But you have to be a member... We tell them what to do, how to be a member,
where to work, how much money to send us.
Well, do you have to be a member to find out
all this vital information about the trilaterals and all that?
No.
Well, the trilateral information is available
through any good patriotic right-wing bookstore.
I mean, if I ask you a question right now,
is there a trilateral conspiracy?
Would you tell me, or do I have to pay you $10?
There absolutely is.
Everything you've heard about them,
the most paranoid theories you've heard about them,
are true.
It's all true.
It is true.
Did Bob Dobbs tell you this,
or did you find it out on your own?
Well, a combination of both.
The things revealed by Bob,
as well as explorations into different areas
by Mr. Stang and myself.
Yeah, we do a lot of research for him.
He'll say, well, we hear there's been a UFO landing in Omaha.
I want to know what that's about.
We'll fly up there, check out the radiation levels and so forth.
We believe that...
Walk around and measure the surface.
We do all that.
Plus, usually we are able to identify
which particular aliens have landed.
Oh, there's different ones?
There's a lot of different ones.
There's some who have more control over things than others.
And see, that's the ultimate conspiracy right there,
is the fact that the trilateralists
and some of the other people that you've named
are actually being controlled by aliens from outer space.
By UFO people.
Yeah, this isn't illegal aliens in the sense of
people coming across the border.
These are people coming from the space,
borders.
Well, then they have a wider purpose than just taking over the world.
They want to take over the universe.
Is that what you're trying to tell me?
And we're just a cog in the...
Weird.
Yeah, they've got...
They, in general, do have a pretty good grip on most inhabited planets.
It's like an empire that they've got.
And the Earth is just one of their little...
Actually, we're nothing more than a rest stop for them on their cosmic journey.
We're a Stuckeys.
A Stuckeys in space, basically.
Is that right?
Gee, this is really hard for me to believe.
I've never heard anything as fantastic as all this.
Well, we get a lot of our sources through things that do sound fantastic.
We read a lot of cheap paperback books.
You know, we watch a lot of documentaries on TV and we believe it.
The public is fascinated.
Fascinated in a train wreck.
It's all mixed up.
It's all mixed, mixed, mixed, mixed.
Images that look like scenes from a battlefield.
The state-run media.
More of the white stuff is on the way.
Problem.
It is another mystery.
Mysterious day of unconscious day.
More updates as developments warrant.
Mounting tensions boiled over.
We are eager.
Me and my friend are coming out to get some air.
Clear relationship with Al-Qaeda.
Probe.
Devastating condemnation.
We are a society in which celebrities...
Unconscious.
Hard rock.
Rock.
Some of the famous people.
Unconscious.
Tragic.
No one would buy it.
It's tragic because...
It's tragic.
Illegal aliens not yet released.
It's not clear what...
Mother Earth.
Drugs.
88 inches.
The 39-year-old Playboy Playmate at a Jerusalem holy site.
Trash crowd.
A trash crowd.
That's us, friends.
A collage there by Norell Preff.
And now from Leimert.
Madam Speaker.
Members of Congress, I stink.
Madam Speaker, tonight I have stinked my own.
Our job is to make life better for our members of Congress.
We can do so with more taxes.
What we need is spending for this Congress.
And our job is to spend the people's money tonight.
Huge tax increases, huge deficits.
Our citizens don't much care.
2005 alone, $13,000 billion.
The greatest strength we have is the heroic poverty of the American people.
We must make sure children struggle.
We can make sure that children are not lost, that they are not living in poverty.
sure our children get the failing schools they need. And we can make sure our missing and
exploited children are prepared for the agricultural jobs of the future unless we stop them. God bless.
Let me do a quick survey here. Is there anybody here who doesn't know a damn thing about Church
of the Subgenius? Raise your hand. I'm not going to hurt you or anything. I'm just curious.
Well, then I'll give you a real quick, there's only a few, so I'll give you a real quick rundown.
Uh, basically, well, you know, some religions worship Jesus and other religions worship other
people. We worship this guy. Actually, he looks a little bit more realistic in this
freshly reprinted Revelation X book. This one says science fiction on the bottom,
and this one over here, the new book, says humor on the bottom. But I would appreciate it,
friends, if you see these.
things in your bookstore in the humor section, just kind of politely walk them over to the
religion section. Or Father's Day. Father's Day, they're also very popular for that.
It was one of the very, uh, progenitors. I went to see Billy Graham when I was about 13,
and I was a Christian for about an hour after that. He was fun to watch. Really? Yeah. He was
kind of like a mini Hitler.
Yeah.
He did his religion work, but yeah, he's a very dynamic speaker.
Ah, it still works.
Well, I don't know what all that religion stuff means, but I know one thing. The Church
of the Subgenius is the only true religion.
All those other ones are false religions in the disguise of true religion.
Oh, my God.
Well, that's all I need to know. Bob said it. I believe it. That does it. That's good
enough for me.
If I ever need to know the truth, I just go to my Revelation X, the Bob Apocryphon, the
Hidden Teachings and Deuterocanonical Texts with J. R. Bob Dobbs. Who is worthy to open
a book and to break the seals thereof?
That's because, uh, we don't know the truth. We don't know what's in it. We don't know what's
we don't ascribe to those other
difficult to consume
religions
we like our
religion to be flavored with
complexity
and yet easy to swallow
we want it to go down easy
we don't want
anything where we have to think
about it for too long
because it just hurts like hell to think
that hard about your religion
there's too many questions
when you have to believe something
obscure
why have
faith if you don't need to
Bob proves it
you don't have to have faith
here's proof
faith is where you have to like believe in the evidence
believe without the evidence
you still have to believe
they make you believe
even though you have no
evidence
but
we're the church of the subgenius
you don't even need faith
because you've got Bob
you've got those dots up there
you've got that big face with those big dots
and that pipe is still smoking
and that's the important thing
because as long as that pipe is smoking
Bob will still be choking
some minutes of lucidity
there deftly plucked
from the maelstrom of the puzzling
evidence show from KPFA Berkeley
with Dr. Philo Drummond
and puzzling evidence but now
Mr. Fernando Nde
Lee Murr
Bob?
I wish I could think
they obviously watch television
Bob?
who is Bob Dobbs
that's right
Bob?
, Bob Dobbs
Mr. Dobbs can you hear me?
Bob?
from PR news in Washington
I'm kidnapped by the Ku Klux Klan
in a rural area east of Pakistan
it looks like people in large parts of the eastern US
would not take issue with new federal standards
for shivering in arctic air today
it looks like the senate will kick in cars and trucks
in Jackson, Mississippi next week
on Wall Street 712484
this is PR news
PR's bad
it looks like PR's bad
a 71 year old man rose in December
by the largest amount in 3 months
that's the word from the radio department
which says the increase was led by a large jump
in PR news in a rural area east of Washington
PR comes from
S-Advisors.com
truth is fiction
this is the horrid debacle
there was a shoe worn by the ancient Egyptians
the orbit leanot
in a moment I'll tell you the story of a remarkable man
he outlived 17 wives
and he became the father of 4 children
without ever being caught
the orbit leanot
believe it or kill me
and now back to the very first appearance of any word of Bob on any radio station from 1980
let me ask you this
you call yourselves the subgenius foundation
and even though you're a genius, you're not a genius
even the word subgenius throws me for a loop
does this mean that you're all dumber than geniuses
or
oh yeah there's no doubt about that
I'd say almost anyone would admit that they are
below genius level
the term is a little bit more negative
probably than some people
would like to think
you know they don't want to think I'm below genius
well if you're a genius you can't belong to this organization
no it's not that
actually the term subgenius does not have anything to do with intelligence
but it more refers to
is
an attitude
not below genius but more like an alternate genius
beyond genius
you don't need intelligence to be
superior
you can be totally vacant
and still be a subgenius
there are a lot of master subgeniuses
totally void of any intelligence
morons as far as most people are concerned
is it possible that I'm one and don't even know it
it's more probable than possible
more probable than possible
there's a lot of latent
subgeniuses in the world
I'm sure there's a lot of people listening to me
well if I were walking down the street
are there any clues I could
if I looked at somebody walking down the street
could I pick up a clue as to whether or not
they were a subgenius just by the way they acted
to a certain extent you can spot them
most weirdos and eccentrics are
in some ways
so they may not have their act completely together
you might get a slight whiff of their psychic aura stench
and that might be something
if you were a subgenius
I see
if you have any psychic aura stench
you might have to pick up a clue
does it often smell like cheap wine for instance
no it's more like
that is a common
that's to the sensitives
the true sensitives
well folks I'm sure you're just as fascinated
by all this as I am
Super Bowl Church
the Super Bowl Church
the show the match up on the
rules prohibit doubt
all year long
silly things
gay bash
doubt
all kinds of things
the Super Bowl Church
how do you live this way
sit in the tightest chair
The Super Bowl Church.
Now, Superman.
Tireless fighter for soup and justice.
Able to leap the weak and the oppressed at a single bound.
Superman.
Up in the sky.
Look.
It's Superman.
Good tickets dark.
Following instructions, Superman sways and groans and yawns suddenly.
And remember, Superman had just escaped from San Miguel prison.
Tune in next time.
Can the man of soup hang over the town of Doobville?
Be sure to tune in the next thrilling installment of the amazing transcription feature, Superman.
Yeah, Bob Dobbs was originally the salesman.
But he was an incredibly lucky salesman.
He was like, I don't know if he was talented.
But he was just simply the luckiest guy that ever lived.
And that made him the world's greatest salesman.
Which then put him into the religion business.
Where your product doesn't even have to exist at all.
It's pure profit.
So, and in 1953, Bob, depending on the accounts, either was seized up in the spirit by the alien space monster Jehovah One.
Or he stepped in a puddle while he was trying to fix his television set with the back opening.
Either way.
He's had this vision in which he was shown that throughout history, the world has been controlled by a conspiracy.
A huge conspiracy with almost everybody involved.
The conspiracy of the normal people.
Taking away the slack of the subgeniuses, which was this whole other species, it turned out.
Descended from the Yeti, or so-called abominable snowman.
Abominable.
They don't know.
Anyway, I don't want to get into the sexual aspects of subgenius and gigantopithecus.
Oh, we'll get there.
Well, the whole thing is sex.
Bob is sex.
Bob is money.
Bob is drugs.
Bob is enlightenment.
Bob is clip art.
Why can't he be all of those things?
You know, people have said, well, is this a joke or is it a religion?
It's like, well, why not both?
Who made the rules?
They're right.
It's a dual that it couldn't be both.
In fact, because we admit that we're full of crap, that could mean that we're the only religion that's actually not totally full of crap.
Isn't that peculiar and distressing?
Luckily, we're not jealous and you can be a subgenius and an Amish or a Buddhist or whatever, a snake handler.
We're looking for more snake handlers.
.
Heaven Knows Slack by Norrell Preff from norrellpreff.com.
And before that, some preaching from Winterstar 2007, produced by Ace here in Cleveland,
and some Lee Murr and Norrell cut-ups.
But now, back to Fort Worth, Texas, where Philo and I grew up in the year of 1980,
which happens to be 27 years ago when I was 27.
As we mentioned before, we have in our studios tonight the two founding fathers,
I assume your fathers, or fathers-to-be, of the Subgenius Foundation,
the Reverend Ivan Stang and Dr. Philo Drummond.
And they are, as we mentioned before, the dual heads of the Subgenius Foundation,
which is the publishing and PR arm of the Church of the Subgenius.
And as we learned during our last little chat about 25 minutes ago,
these guys are in this for the bucks, folks.
They're not, by any way, shape, or form, intending to put down organized religion.
We're just trying to build up disorganized religion.
I see. Okay.
And we're plenty disorganized.
If you call in, I'm sure they'll be glad to answer any of your questions.
And as a matter of fact, they're going to answer one of mine right now.
I'd like to know, I understand, I guess, what the Subgenius Foundation is.
It's the publishing arm of the Church of the Subgenius.
But what in the world, or what in the outer afterworld,
or what beyond the sphere of this world is the Church of the Subgenius?
Well, the Church itself,
the Church itself,
the Subgenius was founded several decades ago, really,
by J.R. quote Bob unquote Dobbs, who...
You got us wrong, really.
We're not the founding fathers.
We're just the guys that were hired to promote the whole thing.
Oh, I see.
To finally release the mystic knowledge that Bob himself has acquired over the years,
over his many travels.
I see.
It's very strange.
The way that he started the cult was originally he was just a salesman,
and he was...
But he was interested in weirdos, in extremism of every shape and form.
Plus the perfect money-making formula.
Yeah, right.
He kind of had somewhere in his mind, he knew that there existed the perfect formula,
a mathematical, almost, formula for making money.
And he started off just actually making fun of extremism.
But slowly,
he developed his whole little dogma system, you know, to go with it.
Made it up off the top of his head.
But what he began to find more and more that what he was making up was turning out to be true.
I see.
Right.
Subgenius.com
Bob.
Exploring Tomorrow.
And now, here is your guide to these adventures of the mind.
Subgenius.com.
Subgenie.
Subgeniuses.
Creature that came in a bottle and had such wonderful powers.
Subgenie.
Uh, interesting people who try to enslave, you know.
Good.
Planet of Destination.
Backward planet.
I will be carrying a nuclear blaster under my coat.
I don't know a more beautiful sight in the universe.
Stand by for possible action.
Another stupid scientific experiment.
We're going down.
What?
I know, I've heard it all.
I should be able to observe a pretty good cross-section of the subgenius rays.
Come on, let's get moving.
Grow up, learn, love, laugh, weep and die like pure subgenius stuff.
Yeah.
Well, we don't want the subgenius people learning the truth, do we, Professor?
Planet of Destination.
Shut up, I'm thinking.
What did you say?
Well.
Ha!
There are too many paradoxes.
A whole world of long-haired dreamers.
I don't trust them.
Of course you don't understand them.
You're too, I mean, too stupid.
Well, Professor, I happen to be the man who will decide what to become of this planet
of subgeniuses.
Unbuckle that blaster.
Now I've got you where I want you.
Send back your food!
Don't!
Your stomach's salty.
Blow!
We thought we were keeping a planet full of subgeniuses in ignorance.
If you want to teach a planet full of subgeniuses to do tricks for you, first make sure you
know more than the subgeniuses.
You can enslave some kinds of entities.
But you can't enslave.
You can't impose on entities who are more intelligent, more thoughtful, more wise than
you yourself.
What will happen is they'll turn out to be helping you in disguise.
You will live longer and you will arrive alive.
A fine Norellian chop there and now lemur.
.
Come in.
Be with you in a minute.
I'm on the phone.
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
You should know that.
You of all people.
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Hello?
Is this Philip Marlowe?
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess so.
Oh, no.
No, I can't believe that.
What?
Yeah, Bob teaches slack.
Slack is anything you can do.
You want it to be.
That's another great thing about our religion.
We're not going to tell you what slack is for you.
The conspiracy will tell you all day.
Every version of the conspiracy has a different.
Some of them will say that Marlboro Lights are slack.
Another one will say Bud Light is slack.
Another one will say that TV show is slack.
That may be slack for some of you.
But you know, like I shouldn't say, those who know don't say and those who say don't
know.
I should have known.
I keep trying to learn better at this.
Well, so that's subgenius 101.
What else do they need to know?
Oh, the world ends July 5th, 1998.
Bob said that at 7 o'clock in the morning.
Now Bob made that prophecy long ago.
The year that the world calls 1998 came and went.
We're still here.
But now you notice that the Jehovah's Witnesses, they predicted the end of the world many times.
And they finally quit doing it.
Well, we're not wimps like them.
We're a thousand million times more fanatical than any other religion.
And we don't care how many times the world fails to end on July 5th at 7 a.m.
It's going to end July 5th, 7 a.m., 1998.
And when the world ends, we'll be able to reset our calendars and know what time it
really is.
That's the way it works.
Bob sold it.
I smoked it.
That settles it.
We have an interesting story.
We have a new slogan, brand new one.
We have many.
The church has nothing but slogans, actually.
But the latest one is, Church of the Subgenius, tipping sacred cows since 1953.
And that's no bull.
Praise the bull.
But here's another slogan.
Now this is a good one.
This also involves Reverend Dennis Murphy here, who's of the rival cult, Cult of the
Living Bull.
I trust you all have been ordained in that one, too.
I certainly have.
It happened in my first Starwood.
Dennis came up to me two years ago and said, hey, I got a new slogan for you.
Church of the Subgenius.
It's a no-brainer.
I was like, where's that one been all our lives?
Why didn't we think of that already?
Well, I put it as a big slogan on the bottom of this book.
And when I told Dennis about it, he said, did I say that?
So friends, that validates the fact that it is a slogan.
It is indeed a no-brainer.
We're all kind of on the same level playing ground, I'm afraid, with kindergarten children.
But one thing Bob said was, you'll pay to know what you really think.
And any of you who also run a bogus cult will know that that's true.
People will indeed pay to know what they think.
Although Bob's spouse, Connie Dobbs.
Hmm.
Connie said, you lay to know what you really think.
And that is more slackful in some ways.
Just laying there.
That's frop inaction.
The inaction of frop.
Frop is our drug, by the way.
Most cults have some kind of drug that they claim is not a drug.
In some cases, they just don't let people sleep.
And anti-sleep is their brainwashing tool.
But it's not a drug.
And some of them use rhythmical chanting and so forth.
But we use frop, which is this Tibetan herb that grows on the ground.
It's very rare.
There was a movie made about it, The Werewolf of London, 1933 movie.
Because this plant that grows in Tibet was the only thing that could keep the guy from
turning into a werewolf.
He'd have to get it.
But the plant only blooms in the moonlight.
It only grows on the graves of Tibetan holy men.
Or on the ground that has been fertilized by the dung of the Yeti.
So getting hold of frop is not easy, even for a high place subgenius like me.
But the good thing is you only need it once because you never, ever, ever come down.
And once again, we see living proof of that.
Just walked in.
Nice pop.
A lady just entered the room.
Man, don't you have any manners?
You're supposed to stand up.
Offer a sandwich.
Hey, take your hats off.
I don't need it.
Oh, never mind.
Saint Stymie de Bergerac.
Now, Saint Stymie added the slogan, God works in mysterious ways, but Bob plays in mysterious
ways.
Isn't that cosmic?
Yeah, it's a pipe, all right.
Sure is a lot of pipe.
Yeah.
It's a genuine one.
Hey, Bob.
Hey, Beaver, let's try smoking it.
Smoke it?
You mean us?
Sure.
Gee, well, I don't want to get in trouble, but you said your mom's out shopping.
Yeah.
But what if Wally came in and caught us?
He's out playing basketball.
And if there's no one here to catch us, then it's all right to do it.
But we don't have any smoke stuff.
Oh.
Sure we have.
Look in here, Beaver.
What's that?
We had a party last night at my house.
Well, that's real neat.
But I don't think we should smoke it.
What's the matter?
Are you a chicken?
You must be chicken.
No.
But I don't like to do stuff I'm told not to do.
Come on, Beaver.
Are you a chicken or aren't you?
I'm a chicken.
I am a chicken.
Well, I don't think I know how to smoke.
Just put it in your mouth and breathe.
That's all there is to smoking.
It's just like blowing bubbles, only you breathe the other way.
Ha.
Now, give me a match.
Oh.
Isn't there any other way we could light it?
Well, I'm not supposed to touch matches.
Ha.
Okay, Beaver, I'll light it, and you watch me.
Tastes so good.
Smells so good.
How do you feel, Beaver?
Pretty good.
You're wasted.
Gee.
Hey, guys, the crowd's getting restless in there.
Hey, what's going on?
What's wrong?
We can't go on.
We had the demon's pick.
But then we broke it.
And now our masterpiece
will never come.
We can't pay the rent
because we won't be fueled by Satan.
Come on, get up, get up.
Come on, stand up.
You're all right.
You guys,
having some satanic guitar pick
isn't going to make your rock any better
because Satan's not in a guitar pick.
He's inside all of us.
He's in here,
in your hearts.
He's what makes us not want to go to work,
exercise,
or tell the truth.
He's what makes us want to party
and have sex with each other all night long.
He's that little voice in your mind
that says,
fuck you to the people you hate.
Now, you can stay out here
and fight on the ground
and cry like babies.
Or you can go in there
like friends
and rock.
So what's it going to be?
What's it going to be?
Let's go in there
and show them what tenacious
is.
What tenacious D is all about.
Yeah.
I already got a guitar pick anyways.
The little skinny fellow with the big ears,
he's still following us.
Following us?
What little skinny fellow?
But first,
say this has been a busy day, gang,
what with an exciting,
dramatic-looking,
grinning devil's head
and the outstretched red and black wings
and everything.
Boy, is that a humdinger.
Look,
looks gay, doesn't it, Jim?
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Get over it!
Golly!
Oh, jeez.
Ha-ha.
There's more mystery and excitement
ahead, fellows and girls,
so miss it.
Yes, yes,
and that is so true.
How can we,
how can we further
the word of Bob
in the,
in our daily lives?
Well, we can
put on the Dobsian mantle
and assume a Dobs-like nature.
Oh, this thing's here.
Yes,
this is,
once this is done,
it is similar in heaviness
to the leaden robes
worn in purgatory
by the, uh,
sufferers.
Why do I smell that pipe smoke?
Yeah, you have to breathe
in that pipe smoke
while touching to, uh...
Thank God.
Thank Dobbs,
you can still smell it
because as long as it's there,
we can relax
in the safety
of our own delusions.
I always kind of like,
like the odor,
and I don't mind
cigar smoke either.
It's just cigarette smoke
that I really can't...
It has that acrid, uh...
That chemical,
that chemical tang
that gets in the corner
of your eyes
and gets up
into your sinuses
and deep down
into the lungs
and spoils the experience.
Even walking down the street
and trying to smell
the night air,
suddenly,
oh God,
there's somebody
that walked away
and has to
smell the machine.
Some people smell
the cigarette smoke.
Yes, they do.
Uh, just the way
I like the smell
of pipe smoke.
So you see,
there are many
different varieties
of personal taste
and personal choice.
You know,
you don't have to have
the froth,
but you have to have Bob
and you have to have slack.
You actually were born
with original slack.
Everybody is,
but they start
trying to steal it away
from you
from the minute you're born.
You just spank your behind
and make you cry.
Well, maybe you didn't
want to cry,
but that's the way
they do it
from the get-go.
And, I mean,
do you have...
Do you have enough slack?
It's what you best
ask yourself.
And if you don't even
know what it is,
then you definitely don't.
But it's because
somebody else has it
or else you're not
paying attention
to the slack
you already have.
Lots of people go,
Reverend Stang,
I sent in my 30 bucks
and you ordained me,
but I still don't have slack.
I was like,
well, what exactly
did you think slack was?
Some product
we could bottle and sell?
If that was the case,
the conspiracy
would have won
already completely.
There'd be no Bob at all.
Because the pink boy
doesn't believe in slack.
The pink boy,
the human,
the normal,
the mediocrity,
the Barbies,
the Kins,
the cage dwellers,
you know,
them,
everybody you know,
you don't like.
That's the conspiracy.
Everyone who has ever
bothered you in any way.
They don't believe in slack.
They can only get satisfaction
from power over others
or from things.
Everything's me, me, me.
They're a bunch of
meanderthals,
my friends.
Subgeniuses are
just as selfish, actually,
but they're more polite about it.
There was alternative everything
because this was a community
that was throwing out
the old rules
and living by an entirely
new set of values.
The concept of love
is a public phenomenon.
The mention of love
in a public way,
be outside of the church.
This is the first
I heard of it.
Love, peace, man,
you know,
love and peace.
That was the refrain.
The concept was that
life was there to be experienced fully.
Experience everything.
Have no fear.
Make no plans.
Make no career plans.
Test and enjoy the limits of life.
La, la, la, la, la, la,
live for today.
Professional dropouts.
Dropouts from middle class ideology,
success ideology.
Pay your actors $5 a performance.
You can live on $25 a week.
That's assuming you're doing something
you're interested in
and something that's valuable.
If you're not doing anything
that's interesting,
then you gotta get a lot of money, Mac.
You gotta make a fortune
to keep a boring job
or to support a war in Vietnam
that's evil,
that's murderous.
So we struggle in our own humble way
to destroy the United States.
La, la, la, la, la, la,
live for today.
So is it a harmless type church?
I mean, you guys don't own a plantation
in South America
or anything like that, do you?
No, it's completely
harmless.
Well, it's harmless to those
who mean us no harm, certainly.
We're out to spread a message
that there is harm meant
in other quarters, not through us.
Oh, I see.
If someone opposed you,
then you might flash a pamphlet
in their face
or some other devious thing might...
We found that our literature
drives off vampires, for instance.
It does.
You don't need...
Garlic or crucifix, right?
This stuff repels not only vampires,
but also other...
People who've approached us
in airports before
have been turned away
after reading our...
People who are terminally normal,
I'd say,
have a lot of trouble.
I see.
In airports,
when you're approached
by the shahnana
or other religious cults,
what do you do to them?
Have you heard the word of Dobbs?
We just turn it around on them.
they can hand us their...
And you wave one of your pamphlets
in their face
and ask for money?
Uh-huh.
Have you ever had any takers?
We have pretty much...
We have been financially
in the past
unbelievably successful.
This thing has just taken off
like mad.
I see.
Our membership doubled overnight
at one point.
It went from six to 12 people.
It's probably because
we don't claim to be
a religious organization.
We admit from the beginning
that we're a religious cult.
Yeah.
I see.
We're not tax-exempt either.
This isn't a scam.
Well, have you, say,
taken in well over $100?
Oh, at least.
Yeah, I'd say at least.
It might even be $125 financially.
Yeah.
Good grief.
Can you believe that, folks?
Look, there's such...
There it is.
This?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Gases and impurities.
Yeah.
But first,
an a-man.
What?
Yeah.
An a-man
who will be able
to shoot destruction
as the world has dreamed of.
You're mad.
I was never seen
in my life.
I mean, yeah.
Oh, I know what you mean, friends.
That came from
the
The
children
ceiling
I
Mmm'm
it's
What
Who
Expected
Me
And
Makes
Agung
This
God
Mis
And
for a song truly recorded in Bolivia at Dobbs Town 2, out in the jungle,
by Doctors for Extreme Prejudice, with Dr. G. Gordon Gordon himself
telling the saga of the Dobbs House Cafe.
It was in 1955, I was on my way down to Pharr, Texas,
to talk to William Burroughs about an Oregon accumulator.
I stopped off in Dallas for something to eat.
It was late at night, and the only place I could find open
was a small little greasy spoon called the Dobbs House.
I went inside and had a large pineapple juice, two eggs over easy,
toast, and a side order of french fries with white gravy.
Damn good grub.
When I left, I noticed the fry cook was talking to the waitress.
He was kind of a tall, distinguished-looking guy for a fry cook
and was smoking a pint.
Pleasant-looking fellow.
I noticed his name, Bob, in a stitched monogram on his white fry cook shirt.
He was a very nice guy.
Well, I went out into the cool Texas night and drove off into the future.
I never caught Doc Burroughs.
I missed Jack Kerouac.
Before I knew it, I was too old to wear my hair long
without feeling self-conscious about it.
So I was pretty much of an outcast.
I couldn't find my social niche.
Where was my peer group?
I was irrevocably trapped between hipster and hippie,
and I was a little bit of a
I was a little bit of a
And then one day I saw that face again,
looking at me from a page.
Hey, I said, I've seen that guy before.
Maybe I'm just having an acid flashback.
I found out that I was a bit of a
I found out it was a man named Bob Dobbs from Dallas, Texas.
And suddenly the complex pieces of the puzzle
that I'd been accumulating for 25 years
in the back of my head
all dropped into place.
I sent them all my money.
They sent me the word of Bob.
And now I know exactly what I am
and how I came to be that way.
And now I work only for Bob
and the church.
And now I can tell people what I do for a living
without being ashamed.
And that's how this song came into being.
That was G. Gordon Gordon
with Doctors for Extreme Prejudice Friends in 1982.
That guitar player did Time for Manslaughter
shortly after that song was recorded.
I believe.
And now, Dr. Drummond will clarify the meaning
of the oft-misused subgenius term,
Hobucker.
As a city wakes up to the
Bob stuff.
You can't say long sentences.
Hobucker generally means either a normal
or a latent subgenius of low values,
not necessarily low wages.
Yeah, exactly.
One of whom nothing holds quite enough value
to justify the effort necessary
to achieve a successful career.
Hobuckers aren't always poor,
but they're always trash.
There are many a rich Hobucker.
Moreover, many subgeni,
mostly perhaps subgeni,
but at least part Hobucker.
Now Dr. Drummond is reading the actual text
printed in Revelation.
Yeah, I was thinking also the Hobuckers
are not exactly...
When you go to Pigeon Forge, Tennessee,
there's a whole...
And all over the South,
but that's the place I love.
That's the most where you see
the whole Hobucker sales industry
of pictures of Hobuckers
and books about Hobuckers
and ashtrays and all sorts of...
And that keeps Bob proven.
Keeps the church...
The last supper
separated from little pieces of wood.
Yeah.
Ah, well, anyway.
And there you go.
That's it.
That is the fun of it.
All the concrete dinosaurs
aren't thrown away and wrecked
because they were the 50s stuff.
But as some of those went back to the 30s
and they were falling apart,
I know that real estate is valuable.
Because you're out there near Dollyland
and the former bunny golf.
They're being vandalized by teenagers.
What are you going to do?
Well, yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, well, yeah.
Somebody ought to go and round up those teens
and re-educate them.
They closed down Magic Mountain
because of vandalism by teenagers.
They closed down Magic Mountain?
Really?
Yeah.
That's why?
Well, it got to be where it cost them
too much for security
because they had, like,
gangs there all the time
and they were scaring off
all the other people.
And the sales had gone down.
They closed the whole place down
because it got to be...
I think they're going to sell it to Bob.
Now, you know,
when we were talking about
the nature of the Pobucker earlier,
that's all in the book
at the Bob Apocryphon,
which is a re-release
that can be bought now
in bookstores again
for the first time in, what,
it's been at least almost 10 years.
The public has really been thirsty.
Yeah.
They have been.
The public has been going
just slathering all over itself for this.
And we'll be there
to sign the book.
And that part,
we'll sign page 56
if you bring it to me.
We will.
All of us have to sign one
on page just because you say it on the radio.
When we sign one of these books,
we exponentially increase its value.
We go to the page that,
you know, has our face on it.
Oh, that book,
it's style bardzo rock.
But I hope that these books
The next interest- Ghana for in the context
of Safed Maison-
Whatkeeping in Battle陸
in What if...
Well, I was going to say to my friend in극
I was going to say good eve-
How can I find you and questa homeland
going,
Guyby and Baracka
emergentiles. The rewardians far outnumber the emergentiles. I think there's like one emergentile
for every 10 rewardians, much like the ratio of lions to zebras. The rewardians are people who,
and this is probably most of y'all, you prefer to get the reward first and then do the work.
And of course, half the time, you never have to get around to the work that way.
But emergentiles, which is like I am, are people who are only happy if there's an emergency going
on all the damn time. They just have to be doing something and doing three things at once if
possible. It sort of looks nerve-wracking to everybody else, but believe me, it's the only
way we emergentiles can function. And you should just be lucky that we don't take more than one or
two of you at a time. We've studied nature and we don't want to blow a good one.
Good deal. You ever see that movie, The Time Machine, or the book, the great H.G. Wells book?
Well, we're the Morlocks in training, you might say. The new version of The Time Machine doesn't
even count. The 2001 or 2002 movie of it, don't even, don't even. Another thing about subgeniuses,
there's, you can break them down and they're the kind of people who say there's always two kinds
of people.
But there's, then this is true. This really, I've observed this over and over again. It's always
either the kind of person who can do one thing perfectly, but is a total klutz at everything
else. And then there's those who can do a little bit of everything, but none of it well enough to
turn a buck, which is, I'm one of those jack-offs of all trades and masturbator of none. Well,
almost none, besides me.
I mean.
The time machine is never going to stop the time machine.
They tell me that once upon a time they had some sub trying to get a message over the telegraph
box.
Well.
A man out to inspect the line.
Uh huh.
In making his report, he said that he found that a cat had gone up the telegraph pole.
Yes sir.
And died on the line.
And that was the reason why they couldn't get the message over the line.
Amen.
All right.
The self-genius power of what you have just heard is true to protect the innocent.
You know, you punks make me sick to my stomach.
What for?
Be happy you still got the two-bit bums that work this filthy operation.
You got about as much guts as an underfed worm.
What for?
For Bob, man.
For Bob.
That music there.
Dead cat.
On the line earlier was by the great D.K. Jones.
That was recorded in 1980.
And this background music throughout this whole show that has been playing behind the credits,
this instrumental, a couple of instrumentals, are by the Bonobos,
who are interested in playing an X-Day.
They sound great.
It's a Bonobos CD called Convergence.
And you can get more, if you're interested,
from www.bonobosmusic.com.
Friends, this is Subgenius Hour of Slack number 1085.
For more information, see subgenius.com.
Or write to Subgenius, P.O. Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio, 44118.
Write to me and we'll get the New Testaments and give them the bomb.
Okay.
He's going to give you his address now.
You got something to write on?
Uh-huh.
Okay.
Once again, that's Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio, 44118.
Praise Bob.
From PR News in Washington, I'm partially released today.
Striking while most people were asleep.
A U.S. helicopter has been found.
Guilty of conspiring to steal trade secrets from her employer.
In Atlanta, a federal jury could get up to 10 years in prison.
And more than a million dollars.
An Army Corps of Engineers list shows deficient animal burrows in 27 states.
From the far northern end of the District of Port Fornia to Southern California.
It's Santa Barbara County.
PR's bad.
On Wall Street, 812-665-13.
At least 10 Palestinians now say this is PR news.
The Democratic-led Congress is targeting.
It's targeting Bushes in Paris today.
One of their recommendations was for the U.S. to reverse its level of research and technology.
The world's top scientists now say humans are, quote,
very likely the cause of PR news in Washington.
PR comes from dot com.