Welcome to Difficult Listening Hour.
Shoo-bee-doo-bee-doo!
And now, the subgenius hour.
Oh, God, it reeks.
And it's so impulsive if...
Atomic batteries to power.
Turbines to speed.
You're ready to move us.
I hear people talking bad about the way
they're living.
They have to live here in this country.
Harping on the wars we fight.
Grappling about the way things ought to be.
I don't mind them switching sides
and standing up for things they believe in.
When they're running down a country man,
they're walking on the back side of me.
Hello.
Vinnie.
What?
I told you to quit bothering me.
Well, I won't ask you something.
What?
What's that big old green truck doing out there
in front of the showroom?
Well, that ain't none of your business.
He did it.
You don't supposed to be parking on the street like that.
That ain't none of your business.
Don't worry about it.
Goddamn it.
Now, I've noticed...
Vinnie, I'm gonna tell...
I'm gonna tell the police to have them move that old truck.
You tell them that, then please do, will you?
Well, Pete, don't...
Now, I've noticed...
You should come see my new house this weekend.
Ain't you got nothing else to do?
What'd you come see my new house this weekend?
Where's your new house at?
You lied to me the other day, too, about something.
What?
You said you had tomatoes out of your garden.
You ain't done it.
I have.
What'd you lie to me for?
This fruit stand's my garden.
Huh?
Fruit stand's my garden.
Well, you got one on me there.
Yeah.
Goodbye.
Vinnie.
Now, what motive?
Vinnie, we...
I asked you, God, not to bother me.
I won't ask you something.
That's what you say every time you call.
You said...
No.
It ain't none of your business.
It's my love.
Well, Barney wanted me to keep an eye out for you.
What?
Barney, well, now, kid...
Vinnie.
Now, what motive?
Barney wanted me to look out...
Look, quit bothering me.
Listen, why don't you quit bothering me?
Where are you going to eat today?
None of your business.
I saw you the other day out there across the hospital,
got the little cafe.
Yeah, well, why don't you...
Why don't you let me know who you are and so forth?
You eat out there a lot.
None of your business.
Well, I saw you eating out there a little day.
Yeah.
Listen, listen.
Now, why ain't the hell can't you leave me alone?
They got pretty good food in there.
I don't know.
Why don't you go try it?
Well, I've eaten in there a time or two,
but it's been a long time ago.
Well, listen, quit bothering me, will you?
I don't want to hear from you,
and I don't give a damn about you.
What?
I hope that I see you.
You shouldn't have been drinking a beer out there.
I hope I can see you.
I drink beer when I get ready or everything else.
You don't want to drink a beer?
I do whatever I damn please.
It's nobody's business of mine.
It's the boss' business.
Damn, the boss and you, too.
Well, I wouldn't want to see you get fired, man.
Tell them that I'm been fired.
I've already told you.
It ain't none of your business if I do.
I work when I please.
I don't have to work all the time.
Well, do you drink beer every day and then?
No, hell no.
Well, you don't need to be drinking beer at dinner now.
You're kidding me.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
Oh, I love to hear that.
We're going to be doing a recording of poor old Benny getting harassed by Arnie.
And we'll be hearing other excerpts from that famous tape.
Because tonight we're going to, on the hour of slack on this religious broadcast,
we'll be listening to some of the subgenius preaching from the Subgenius World Convention in Chicago.
Oh, about three weeks.
Two weeks ago.
But also tonight I thought we would indulge in a short study in poebuckers through song and prank call.
The word poebucker may need some explaining to some of you people new to our religion.
Poebucker generally means a person with very low values.
Usually an ignorant type of person.
The common.
Image is of a person in a pickup truck.
Or a person, the kind of person with a pickup truck up on blocks in their front yard for five years.
I mean, it doesn't always mean poor, but just means trash.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not saying anybody with a pickup truck.
You see, there's a lot of subgeniuses with pickup trucks.
There are many rich poebuckers for that matter.
A lot of subgeniuses.
Part poebucker.
I probably wouldn't talk the way I do if I wasn't that way somewhat myself, dear friends.
The term actually, many people figured what it meant.
Oh, that means a subgenius who's poor in bucks.
It's not.
It's a term that's a corruption of an African language word.
Booker or bookra.
Which meant boogeyman or demon.
And the African...
The African slaves brought to America, some of them called white people bookers or buckra.
And white trash, therefore, were called poor buckra or poebuckers.
Which is how my dad's family used to pronounce it.
And these famous telephone experiments would have to be a big part of any study of the rich texture of poebucker life.
The tapes of Arnie.
His many calls to Benny.
Benny Garrick.
At Al White Motors.
Now, and Al White Motors is in Tallahoma, Tennessee, I believe.
Near Nashville.
Benny was harassed by these calls for like three years.
And he recently died.
In fact, Benny died just in July.
We have a copy.
Of his obituary from the newspaper.
Now, why would we know so much about the people on this prank call tape?
Well, we were that curious.
And one who was even more curious was your fellow subgenius minister and scientist, Reverend Lou Minotti.
Who recently moved to Nashville and discovered a lot about these prank calls.
For one thing.
And another thing.
Arnie worked in the same building as Al White Motors.
In the Al White Motors building.
He worked in the parts room.
And Benny worked in the showroom.
When Arnie was making these calls to Benny.
He could see Benny.
And Benny knew the person who was playing Arnie.
Arnie was one of several aliases.
Another one was Roscoe.
And the.
Ah.
It's just inc.
Well, I think we should get back into these tapes.
And I'll tell you a little bit more that's even more frightening.
About the incredible Arnie and Barney and Benny.
Huh.
Tapes.
After this message.
Friends between us is not very far.
Oh Lord!
I'm giving my love to you.
Cause I only want.
To see you smile.
You got nothing to lose.
But a failure to choose.
And you're turning into somebody new.
Mean one.
Oh no.
Give a dog a bone.
Don't come thinking through the door.
You won't forget us.
Cause we were my legends.
We loved you.
Come on.
Get more.
More.
One more time.
TooEngine.
You had a pap Vou.
You may.
Play these.
unlimited.
Whether their medical.
やキャベ legen다 m Particularly.
Every degree.
Even all.
He stuck that gun into his ribs and said, here's looking at you, kid.
Ruby killed Lee Harvey.
TV proved he did.
And he thought he was a friend of mine.
A very good friend.
Leave me alone.
How about it?
Eddie?
Yeah?
Where's your car at?
None of your business.
You know it's raining this morning?
I know, is it?
Sure is.
Well, I'll be damned.
I can't see that.
You can't see.
You have to tell me that.
I didn't know.
You knew it was raining.
No, I didn't know it.
Well, guess what happened?
Well, I don't care what happened.
What?
Mondale picked a woman for his running mate.
Who?
Mondale.
That's good.
He picked a woman for his running mate.
Guess what else happened?
What?
The boss man went up on my house rent.
I'm going to have to move out.
Well, good.
I've been wondering.
Move out in the damn world.
I wondered if you could find me a place up there close to Fort Boyce, South Korea.
Get out of the state.
Excuse me.
Goodbye.
Eddie?
How are you, brother?
Why don't you leave me alone?
I'm busy.
Barney said you used to have some rent.
Leave me alone.
I'm busy.
Bye.
You got it.
And the beat goes on.
The beat goes on.
We became friends.
How about that?
Go ahead.
Bye bye.
Bye.
I say there's free instructions for everybody on karate,
sabotage, anarchism, everything there could be.
I say there's free lessons from the time of you two
on how to do everything there is potentially to kill another person.
There's no hope for humanity anyway.
I'm just going to watch the world end.
You're going to make a million dollars.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Praise Bob!
Somebody help!
Somebody help me!
Hey!
Now what, Moses?
Listen, buzzard breath, why don't you talk to me a minute?
Why don't you go to hell?
What's my brother been telling me? Is that true?
Well, listen, I don't even believe you got a brother.
Well, he said he used to be lovers over here.
Go ahead, go to hell.
Hello?
Benny, why don't you park up next to this car store?
What?
Why don't you park up next to the building for a while?
Why don't you tell me you're on business?
Hey, Benny.
What?
Benny, I'm on the phone, too. I'm Arnie.
Hey, Arnie.
I'm Barney.
I'm Arnie, too.
I'm Barney, Benny.
Yeah.
We're all together.
Good.
We're going to get together tonight, Benny.
I can't.
Why?
Because I said I can't.
We're going to have a good time.
Mm-hmm.
I'll do the cooking, Benny.
Yeah, you'll do the what?
I'll do the cooking.
I'm down for all of you in here.
Oh, Benny, you'd like it if you ever got it, Jim.
You will do it?
Yeah.
Hey, Benny.
Yeah?
I wish you would do something for me.
What's that?
I wish you wouldn't worry my brother about his boy
got killed over in Vietnam.
Well, I can't hear it, Benny.
But he told me you aggravated him.
I wish you'd quit worrying me.
We ain't trying to worry you.
Yes, you are, too.
I mean, we won't be your friends.
Well, come on up down and meet me
and let me see if I can be a friend to you.
Well, I don't care if I miss you,
but Barney says he don't want nothing to do with you.
Well, I don't care.
I don't want nothing to do with him, then.
Benny, you hit me in the head.
That's the way he feels about it.
You hit me in the head, Benny.
Well, you asked for it, didn't you?
No, Benny, I was mad at my own business.
You told me you asked for it.
You was after my woman.
Oh, boy.
Yeah, you was.
I know that's a lie.
But, Benny, it still hurts.
Well, I can't help it.
Benny was bad after women back in them days.
I know it.
Back during Count Forrest's ducky.
Now, who are you?
Benny, you was like a little old rooster.
I asked you, who are you?
I'm Arnie.
I'm Barney.
Yeah?
I'm Arnie, and he's Barney.
Well, both of you.
And you're Benny.
Now, isn't that funny?
Yeah.
Isn't that funny?
I'm glad you're getting a kick out of that.
Would you go to hell?
Oh, dear friends.
Just an amazing, unusually long segment there.
Although, after three years of calls like that,
Benny got to where he would get into long, sad discussions with Arnie.
Arnie would start claiming to be Benny.
Benny's son.
The bold surrealist, dear friends, Arnie Swenson.
Praise Arnie Swenson.
Now, what makes the whole thing even more surreal
is that everyone at Al White Motors knew who was pestering Benny.
Everyone in town knew.
The DA knew.
The sheriff knew.
Everybody but Benny.
They knew.
And people all over town served as Arnie's eyes.
Arnie could follow Benny around and know what he'd been doing at odd times of his life.
And just as Lois Lane never caught on about Clark Kent,
somehow Benny never made the connection.
Arnie did some spectacular things that aren't on tape.
At one point, he bought a broadcast microphone and set Benny's radio,
before he came into work, to the frequency that that little mic would broadcast on.
So when Benny sat down with his cup of coffee and his cigarette to start the day,
he turned on the radio and there was Arnie going,
Benny!
Benny, how come you parked your green truck over there by the fire hydrant?
And Benny, Arnie could, as I said, could see Benny when this was going on.
And Benny, when he did that, just reached over and turned it off.
That was all.
He didn't express any surprise that Arnie,
had even invaded the airwaves.
Because at that point, friends,
let's see, there was this network of spies, you see,
who, for instance, Arnie would keep tabs on Benny's movement, it says here,
and would call him at the barber shop and the liquor store, among other places.
Imagine, it would be as if,
well, as Lou explained to me, this is sort of like a crazed,
Andy of Mayberry scene.
It's like, what if Andy was secretly tormenting Barney Fife?
And everyone in town knew about it.
Floyd knew about it.
Goober knew.
Everybody knew.
And everyone except Barney.
It was like everyone had an evil side.
Anyway, I got a letter from Lou, who has some newly revealed background data pertinent to the Al White Motors saga.
And I know that many of my listeners wish they had this tape, but a lot of my listeners do have it.
It was a pledge giveaway in years past, and I know that we sent out dozens of them.
As Lou says here,
I have spoken to the individual at the firm who engaged in the protracted phone debate with Benny Garrick.
He actually spoke to Arnie.
I found him to be a warm-hearted, seemingly sincere soul,
who frankly spoke of his unique contribution to telephone research history.
Among the key findings,
Benny and Arnie were good friends before the calls commenced.
And even while the calls were going on, Arnie and Benny used to go fishing together.
Arnie speaks favorably of Benny today in the wake of his passing,
though he does admit that Benny had a stubborn streak and disliked anyone getting the best of it.
Arnie would make his calls early in the morning when both began work at Al White Motors.
Arnie would usually knock off by late morning,
then immediately walk away.
Benny would walk across the showroom and ask Benny who it was he'd been cussing out on the phone.
Can you imagine the gall to do that?
Approximately five hours of calls survive on tape.
We should be getting the complete series soon, but we won't play them all on the show.
Arnie reports that Garth Brooks, Clint Black, Chet Atkins, the governor of Tennessee, are among his fans.
Rumor has it that Senator Al Gore, the governor of Tennessee, is one of his fans.
Arnie also says that the governor of Tennessee is a big Arnie fan.
And Clint Black tried to give a copy to George Bush several years ago.
Now imagine how much better the country would be now if those bold Surrealists had indeed gotten through to them.
Dear friends.
A waitress asked me what we'd like to have.
And I said, I don't know where they are.
What would you suggest?
And she stood still.
She just kept staring at me.
And I started getting very nervous.
At the time, I had a beard and I lost a few pounds.
And I thought it would be very hard for anyone to recognize me.
This song is dedicated to Jesse Presley.
The aborted fetus twin brother of Elvis.
You can't arrest me, officer.
I'm not drunk.
I might be half-ass drunk though.
Whee!
Have a half-ass drunk.
Hell, you know who you are.
When you got a hangover and it's all hung over back.
Say to your girlfriend's car, have a half-ass drunk.
Just you and me.
Sergeant Carter haircut.
Gilmore Pyle hookup.
Living off of LSD.
Have a half-ass drunk.
This is a subject of the American Public.
And I'm feeling blue
Well a flood come in
And it washed away my den
And my water bill's still past due
Have a ass drunk
Called my boss
I ain't feeling quite right
Well it can't be Monday
Cause I don't remember Sunday
And my hands are sitting Saturday night
Sweet love song
Have a ass drunk
Hell I'm drunky
Well I used to have a job
But I'm sick of getting robbed
So I finally just up and quit
Mama had a fit
Have a ass drunk
Well my head feels odd
Well baby needs food
But his daddy needs a lude
Well the baby needs food
Baby better find himself a job
Have a ass drunk
And I'm having fun
Stopped on a hill
Cause I had to take a pill
But I couldn't quite find my tongue
Have a ass drunk
Hell I can see
Well they said the light was red
Now a couple of folks
Well there was 22 mangled
And there was one guy
That was gimped up pretty good
He had to sort of walk like this
For the rest of his life
Well there was one guy
Who was pretty neat
They had a huge bag of cigarettes
And it was hurt pretty good I guess
They had like this machine
That was like hooked up
Where he had this tube
Running up through his nose
You know
And that was the only way
He could breathe
And well there was this one dude
It was like a blade
He chopped straight down
On his toes
And last I heard
He still couldn't walk
There was one guy
Well this is what's weird
They found parts of him
On the front of the car
And other parts of him
On the back of the same car
I mean it sort of defies the mind
Doesn't it
How you could find
Pieces of the same car
The same person on the front and back
Of the same car
I mean it
I just don't understand
They ought to run
Some kind of scientific test
I don't even see
How that could even happen
And a couple folks dead
Well it
Well it sure looked green to me
Half-ass drunk
Hell I wish I was
Well I wish I was
Turned a brand new Trans Am
Into an old tin can
Trying to outrun the fuzz
Half-ass drunk
I'm a victim of lies
Well there's nothing wrong with me
Your honor I can see
Hell I got you damn
D-Dug your eyes
Half-ass drunk
Oh woe is me
Well I don't really pay
But it's steady every day
Breaking rocks
Till they're broke as me
Half-ass drunk
Hell I'm half-ass drunk
Lord I'm half-ass drunk
Just sorry I'm half-ass drunk
Oh man friends
That was Jainer Hypercleets
Doing half-ass drunk
As part of our study
Of the world of the Pobucker
Here on the
Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour
Of Slack
Hello
Sherry
Yeah
This is Tom
Listen I
Before it gets too late
I just thought I'd tell you to
You know not
Not with anybody knowing
You sneak out
Who is this
You sneak out your window tonight
When will you ever call 3 o'clock
Hello
Hi is that Maxon
Uh no he's in bed
Who is this
I'm not sure
This is Jerry Topher
I'd like to talk with him for a minute please
Okay just a minute
This is from another prank call tape
Called Calls to Okies
Yes this is Max
Oh huh
Okay Max this is Jerry Topher
HNA
You're living over there on Westbrook aren't you
You are
Okay yeah
HNA that's uh
I know it's late but I want to talk to you about your house a little bit
Yeah
So you're over there on Westbrook
And that
Well that HNA is the Home Owners
Neighborhood Association
Uh huh
And we'd like to talk to you a little bit about your house see
You know
Little things like uh
You know parking a car on the street
Uh huh
Long too long
Yeah
Trash cans sitting out there
And you're gonna have to start picking them up okay
Yeah
Well, I don't know. I picked my car scans up just when the drugs come along.
Well, it's none of that except that lawn, too.
Huh?
Your lawn needs serious mowing problems.
I think you're in the wrong place.
No, I just wanted to let you know that we want to have a nice atmosphere around here and you're going to have to take better care of it.
Well, I think you're in the wrong place because my lawn is not in bad shape.
Well, you know, you just need to mow it a little bit more.
You know, we're not too picky about it.
Well, I keep my lawn mowed.
Okay.
Are you sure you've got the right plan?
You're Maxwell Green, aren't you?
Right.
Okay. 1214 Westbrook.
Hey, what's up?
Well, you know, we don't want to, you know, you just...
Where do you live?
I'm right down here about four doors down.
They kind of elected me chairman of this here, so...
I thought I'd give you a call and be real.
You know, mainly about it.
Where's your book?
It's getting out of hand, Max.
Well, what's getting out of hand?
Well, you just need to take better care of your house and your things.
You know, we've got that...
Stings.
Huh?
It stings.
I didn't understand you.
What did you say?
I said you have to take better care of your possessions, you know, if you want to stay in this neighborhood.
Okay.
I'll blackball you.
You never...
You never get another house in this neighborhood again.
Well, I thought my house looked as good as anybody else's on here.
Well, you know, just consider this here a fair warning.
We'll just give you a couple chances, you know, and then things don't work out, we'll make an arrangement for you, Max.
Well, I don't know how you made me leave.
Yeah.
There ain't no small-time organization.
We take care of that one.
I don't want to get into that.
You know, that's...
We don't even want to talk about that.
Just take care of the lawn a little better.
We'll check back with you and take the progress on that.
What did you say your name was?
Jerry Topher.
Jerry?
H-N-A.
Chairman.
T-O...
How do you spell it last name?
T-O-L-F-E-R.
Now, we'll give you a call back here in about a month's time.
We'll talk to you later then.
See you later, Max.
Better beware, Max.
I want to tickle your love offerings.
Sir?
Hey, that's fantastic.
Is it?
I'm coming over, too.
Good.
I'm going to bathe your entire family tonight.
You're going to what?
How's that?
You know, in the tub with the sponges and the water.
Well, you sound like just the right kind of guy.
You betcha I'll do it, too.
You don't know us.
We get drunk.
We like to go canoeing and bathing.
Well, I'll tell you what.
I got a whole bunch of friends that sit exactly the same way.
Well, maybe we can get together.
Have one of them fleas yours or something.
What is he up to?
Says, how much money do you owe him?
Thumblite.
They like butt.
They feel like butt and a meditate on their necks too.
Go to tan.
I got to go to tic-tac-toe.
When I'm back, you got a costume for your daughter.
Oh, no!
No, not now.
No, you around me you ain't.
You mean it?
I love her, but I can't stand her
My girlfriend is a homeowner
I put the mirror on the radio on
Watch that driver dance around
Got a head start, beat the lock
This time it's a little bit like a dog
I love her, but I can't stand her
My girlfriend is a homeowner
Whoa, Swingin' Love Corpses.
They're live at the Chicago Subgenius Convention
with that lovely old hymn,
My Girlfriend is a Poe Bucker.
And, uh...
We'll be playing more material from the sub-con there.
You'll hear some Sister Mary Squared,
some Sister Velveteen Sly, actually.
I think we played most of Mary Squared's formal ranting.
But also some informal material
from the conspiracy panel discussion
with G. Gordon Gordon
and those aforementioned lady preachers
and dominatrixes.
And, uh...
Uh...
Yes.
Boy, we got a call.
We could tell a rumor on the air.
Ah, it would be so fun.
But I think we better be safe than sorry
because I would hate to have the Secret Service
call the station up and subpoena somebody,
make them go,
Where'd you hear this?
You know, where was the leak?
Uh...
Oh, well...
The eternal conundrum of Connie.
It's clean.
Connie knows that a cucumber isn't better than a man
because cucumbers can't cry for clemency.
Oh, unbelievers,
that Connie can castrate and cripple.
Connie comes and craters crash.
Comets careen from Connie's...
Connie's kiss cascades from her lips.
Lest it burn you.
Leave a tip.
Yeah, Connie.
Can you confront the candle of Connie?
Yes, no, I just...
Now, this chick...
I'm a chick with a Y.
Of course.
This chick has to cruise.
But the chronicles of Connie will continue
as I keep on co-opting conspiracy
and cracking clichés
for I am Connie,
the ultimate con.
Praise Connie!
Y'know, I love it!
I love all my Connie worshipers
me around here!
I don't know what Reverend St neol
has been doin' lately.
I remember he used to talk about
the makeup of the church
ISS!
Oh, I dunno,
a whole bunch of
computer nerd types,
People just
spend all their time
indoors, you know,
Never...
Never talkin' out
They just didn't know how to please a kind.
And I'm so glad to see this new young crap of a subgenius.
Yes!
Call MSG!
Whoever, one or more, are gathered together in the name of greed,
greed, confusion, control, and censorship, there is the conspiracy.
But I want to know, all you out there,
after hearing all this stuff that should have got you riled up tonight,
how big is your hand?
You know what's going to happen?
For 30 years, X day.
And our revenge will come on X day.
Our revenge will come because what's going to happen to those pinks and those normals?
They're going to go through the worst experience of their entire lives.
They are going to be forced off the stage.
They are going to be forced all of a sudden to be obsessed with sex.
And enjoy it.
And they are going to enjoy it.
But, you know what else they'll feel?
Because they're those pinks and those normals.
They will feel guilt.
They won't be able to help it.
You'll see those nice little ladies that you saw typing into Office.
They'll be like, ripping their clothes apart.
They can't help it.
They'll be like, oh my God!
I'm so horny.
But it's bad.
For weeks.
You'll see them for two weeks.
It's true.
And it'll seem like thousands of years.
That's what they will be doing on X-Day.
They'll be here, up.
Laughing.
Losing a squirty.
They are so uptight.
Oh, yes dear friends.
Some new prophecies about X-Day, the end of the world, as understood in our church.
The pinks will suddenly start having fun.
But they'll feel so guilty it'll be like hell.
They'll be ravishing each other in those offices.
But they'll hate it.
They won't be able to stop themselves.
Speaking of X-Day, Reverend Zaphod left a message on the church headquarters phone last night.
With the most outrageous request.
He said, can't you call Bob up and change the end of the world to, like, I mean, you've got it set up for 7 o'clock in the morning, July 5th, 1998.
And at 7 o'clock in the morning, everybody's going to be hungover.
It's going to be horrible.
They're not going to get up.
They'd rather burn with the pinks than get up.
They'd rather get up in the morning, get up that early in the morning.
So I'm sorry, Reverend Zaphod.
But even if I did call Bob up about that, somehow I don't think that the X-ists are going to change their schedule just because you don't want to.
But the idea is you don't fall asleep the night before, okay?
You just stay up.
That way you don't have the hangover.
It'll, of course, sooner or later it's going to catch up with you.
But, you know, I'm just sorry.
These godlike creatures from Planet X just are not going to set their alarm clock.
They're not going to be, I mean, you're just going to have to put up with their wake-up call, all right?
I mean, there's only so much that you can get for that 20 bucks.
I mean, eternal salvation is a lot to ask right there.
You ought to be satisfied with that.
The difference is when a pink, a human, sees something that shocks them, they run away.
Yeah.
They don't like it.
When a subgenius sees something that shocks them, that offends them, they go, what?
This is, I'm shocked, I'm offended.
I want to know more.
If they still don't like it, then they might lynch it.
But at least they're doing their job.
But that conspiracy, that confederacy of dunces, you know, the horrifying thing is it's not that they're stupid.
The individual pink may be much more intelligent than a given subgenius because look at the word subgenius.
It's not the intelligence that counts.
It's what you do with it.
It's common sense, sense of humor, and dollars and cents.
But yet these pinks, these mindless bovine stereotypes, and that's all they are.
They're walking stereotypes.
Come on.
Sometimes generic slurs do apply.
In the case of pinks.
This is Lee Edwards, commonly known as the Christian con man, because I have total confidence in the Lord Jesus Christ as my savior.
And now this being my first album in Hawaii, I want to dedicate this album new to you, my loving wife, for all the inspiration you have given me in life.
And their children are captains on the squad.
Oh, so happy with Stretch Lee.
Happy with Stretch Lee vibes.
Also happy with Stretch Lee vibes.
Et cetera.
I wonder, wonder, wonder, wonder, wonder, wonder, wonder, wonder, wonder, wonder, wonder, wonder who.
And all you have to do is squeeze your little finger, ease your little finger back.
You can change the world.
Whatever it is you want it to be.
Whatever else is true, you trust your little finger.
Just a single little finger can change the world.
Is that justice?
Is that proper?
I'm talking to you.
Life's so cruel.
Why not end it all?
Oh, man.
Happy birthday.
Hey, G, thanks, man.
I'm glad you went through all that trouble to write that for me.
Take a shot.
And if you can't whoop it, go down.
That's a lesser known slogan of Bob's.
No, go down is a slogan of kind.
I just want to tell you, don't pay no attention to my brother.
I ain't going to pay no attention to neither one of you.
He ain't got a good sense.
Yeah.
I just want to tell you, don't pay no attention to him.
I wish y'all wouldn't be worrying me.
You can't mention about driving me crazy.
Oh, no.
Yeah, and I've been trying to be nice to you.
You've been driving me crazy for the last week or two.
Well.
Don't call me no more.
No.
Don't get aggravated about it.
Don't pay no attention to my brother.
Here.
Don't call me up anymore either.
They haven't paid off about it.
Who is?
The company.
Oh, is that right?
Yeah.
Well, they don't know who we are.
No, and I don't either.
No.
Well, I wish you wouldn't bring it up to my brother about his boy.
He tears him all to pieces.
I ain't brought it up.
He starts crying.
I didn't bring it up.
He says you call him.
I ain't never brought it up to him.
You're the one who's calling me.
He says you call him about his brother.
Well, you know, Bob.
The hour of slack really is made for those who tuned in by accident.
That's right.
Those who scanned the dial.
That's what the show is for.
Leave me alone, will you?
Leave me alone.
You've got a house to rent.
No, I haven't.
Don't call this number no more.
What's wrong with your car?
Now, I've noticed.
The authority told me you've got some rental property.
What is it?
Have you got anything else to do?
As long as they can sit and visualize world peace.
Boy, that's better than folk.
You know what?
You think I'm a fool?
Boy, I've been good.
Because it's magic.
And think of the ant.
Oh, the ones you poison and step on.
They have rights, too.
Think of the lice that inhabit people.
What about the bees?
What about the ants?
That's right.
Nature is an open-ditch latrine in mid-summer.
Praise God.
Do not deny your evolutionary destiny.
Which involves lots more...
Sweating and being stinky and killing and stuff like that.
And frapping.
We try to keep the killing down and the frapping up.
That's right.
But realize if you can visualize the nuclear winter,
you can save in your air conditioning bills.
If you believe.
But only if you believe.
And nuclear winter sports.
The nuclear winter Olympics.
The nuclear winter is hot, but it's cool.
He's going down the slope now.
Look, his hair blowing off in little tufts in the breeze.
Chunks of radiated flesh flying out.
It's so poetic.
Dangerous sex on skis.
Bad words.
But you see, the things like abortion and pro-life and contra-life,
or whatever you want to put it,
those are all little issues that have been designed to keep you busy,
to keep you stirred up,
to keep you worrying about this and keep you worrying about that.
The war on drugs has eroded your civil liberties to the point
where they can kick your door in anytime they want.
All they got to do is say drugs and your wife is in jail,
you're in jail, your children are far now.
Your Cadillac's taken away.
They can walk up to you in any airport in the United States of America and say,
excuse me, did you pay for that ticket in cash?
Yes, I did.
Can we see your wallet please?
Here it is.
Sir, you have cash money on you.
We're going to have to confiscate it because you fit the profile of someone going somewhere,
probably to buy drugs.
This is not, this exists right now.
The war on drugs is probably the single most divisive and single-minded effort to erode,
erode every little bit of freedom that we've managed to wring out of these sons of bitches
in the last 200 years.
We've spent 200 years trying to spread that we the people to include someone else
besides land-owning aristocracy.
And now that we're finally beginning to do that,
we're going over to the other end of the Constitution and gradually saying,
you don't have the right to do this, you don't have the right to do that.
Everything that is not forbidden is prescribed.
And if you don't watch it, we're going to get you.
And that's what you've got to remember.
Nobody up there is a friend of yours.
Nobody up there wants to see you have what you would call freedom.
The whole purpose of this government in this country right now is to produce consumers
and workers who will keep the cost of the economy going.
The cost of labor down, the profits high for the earning people.
I'm not a communist or anything like that.
I'm just simply saying that if you believe that any of the people that are running for
office are going to do anything for you as a subgenius,
if you believe any of these people who proclaim to be on the side of liberty and freedom give
us what you want, then you have bought the conspiracy lie.
Fascism back for the people!
Fascism for the people!
People!
The subgenius church is behind people!
Fascism back for the people!
Fascism for the people!
The individual fascism!
Don't visualize world peace, visualize armed insurrection.
Every dad a Duce.
That's right.
Every mom an Ivetta.
So what are you guys going to do at this revival meeting?
You're going to make fun of religion stuff, right?
We never make fun of religion.
We're making money off religion but not fun of religion.
No!
No fun!
They can't have fun!
raise the slack area in this part of the country.
And hopefully...
These are called cribbage crotch figurines, and they're wanted
in every home across America. That's right, young man,
and you've won one. Well, as soon as you sign out the
jewel form for the Lettuce Leaf Kids...
At Jewel Co.
We have to put up with these guys because they know the right people.
But you can trust me, Ivan Stang.
Yes, you can trust me. I'm Dr. Ivan Stang.
And I'm prepared to take your money and give you back your slack.
And I'll be at the revival, the great subgenius revival on the 20th and the 21st
at the Victoria Theatre. So you can believe in me.
I'm Ivan Stang. I never lie, and I'm always right.
It extends throughout the rules and has to do with
the universe.
It has to do with...
It has to do with Gilligan's Island.
Actually, there is another big subgenius conclave coming up
in November. November 13th through 15th.
You might have a pencil ready because I'm going to give you their P.O. box
you can write to. Big subgenius convention.
Actually, it's part of a bigger event called Phenomicon
in Atlanta.
Atlanta, Georgia.
But the subgenius guests will include myself,
the Swingin' Love Corpses,
Janer Hypercletes,
and Father Joe Mama.
Plus, oh gosh, Reverend Susie the Floozy
and loads more of the very interesting Georgia subgeniuses.
As well as UFO abductees,
conspiracy researchers,
and just...
a bunch of cyber punks and so forth.
Who else?
Huh?
Um, and for information, you need to write to Phenomicon
at post office box 12141.
That's box 12141, Atlanta, GA 30355.
2141.
ZIP code 30355.
Yeah, big show.
You go to hell, you son of a bitch.
You're so, you're so sick minded.
Why don't you meet me?
I'm going to show you what sick human beings deserve in this world.
Yeah, what do we deserve, my friend?
We deserve your wife's swampy.
Yeah, how would you like to be mutilated?
I don't believe you, you sleazy, slimy, dripping.
Hold it down, I'm talking.
Okay, I'm going to get you out of here.
I'm going to get you out of here.
Hey, I'm going to get you out of here.
Oh, you're going to get me out of here?
That doesn't cut no ass with me, see?
My ass.
I'll tell you.
I'm going to get on some asses today.
Listen, I've been sitting here.
I'm putting it down in there.
I can't hear no air means but I ain't wanting any.
No?
Hell fire.
All right.
Okay.
There's something else, too.
Now, I noticed, I noticed that you were going to be a little bit more of a little
sketchy.
You know, I heard last Sunday that one of you put a quarter in the offering plate, see?
Yeah, Raymond Welsh.
You're the one.
You put a quarter in there.
You tight son of a — I'd see all that, see?
I'm up here where I can see it.
Y'all don't even look or nothing.
I can see it.
See?
Some of you are doing pretty good and others, you ain't doing
for nothing.
That's it.
All right.
I'm going to maybe go to another church.
I don't know.
I don't give a shit.
I've just about come to the end of the road.
Yeah, I've just about lost patience with you people.
You know we need a Sunday school space out there.
You say, oh, amen, praise the Lord and all that
when I'm saying something that you like.
But when I'm trying to get something done,
that's something else.
You get your ass out to the mountains or someplace
or hide in there and watch that damn tube.
That's what you do.
Listen, that ain't going to get it.
The horse and the horses, it ain't going to do it.
Uh-uh.
Listen, I tell you, this will determine the day.
I have no doubt whether I will be your pastor or not.
But I tell you, if so, fine.
That's what I want to do.
But if not, I'm done.
In fact, my sermon is done.
Don't give me no more.
Brother Woodrow, lead us in the closing prayer.
Whether you're going to do it or not,
I'm a stupid...
Dismissed.
How come you hit my brother so hard back here?
Just go with it, old man.
Well, I don't know.
I don't know.
I'm Arnie.
You hit my brother.
Oh, I did.
Well, he said it deserved it.
He said you knocked him loose with your shoestrings.
I did.
Well, that's good.
I'm going to hit him hard at night next time if I ever get a chance to.
This is potentially five and a half hours of calls.
This will test whether you're hardcore or not.
Yeah, yeah.
But I can truthfully say that these calls probably mean more to me
than any other calls I've ever heard,
including ones that I've been somewhat involved in.
These are, I think, the great...
In fact, speaking of folklore, he actually...
Somebody tried to contact Arnie from the University of Virginia
that was doing a folklore project.
They wanted to talk to him.
It's an example of southern folklore.
Wow.
Hey, so what is Arnie like?
Very interesting.
He's kind of like a Mayberry character.
He sounds like a likable guy.
In fact, the weekend that I called him,
he was parking cars in his lawn for the county fair.
Uh-huh.
He's just a working guy that works in the parts department.
He was friends with Benny for years.
He says that Benny was his friend.
He was a good guy.
Used to go fishing together.
He was just like what you would call a po-bucker,
a bored po-bucker,
who had been a prankster for years,
but this was the first telephone prank he had engaged in.
And he says he meant no malice from it.
He meant no harm.
But interestingly, he told me why the calls ended.
Benny got a brain aneurysm.
He's a good guy.
He gets his own church out.
Yeah, well, it's cold out here.
It's cold and lonely.
Nobody can understand what's going on
until the effects are turned down and your brain's turned up
because it's 435 in the morning and the president's inside your head.
I know.
But it's so quiet here in the station.
We're picking up dead bodies.
So the KPFA show fades off into their dawn there in Berkeley, California.
We don't have to worry about that dawn,
for it's the dawn of a new age here at the Dallas subgenius hour of Slack.
And dear friends, I feel that I should give you a chance to write
for free information.
I'm going to give you a chance to write for free information about the church of the subgenius.
If this is the first time you've ever tuned in and listened to this show,
well, there's a lot of other things involved in our faith here,
besides prank calls and seditious ranting about sexual freedom
and how bad the normal people are.
And you can get that free information by dropping us like a self-addressed stamped envelope.
It would be the best thing you could do.
You could just send us postcards.
You'll get a lot more with the self-addressed stamped envelope.
And the place to send that is, of course,
Bob at Post Office Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
You know, my Sunday night just doesn't seem complete unless I say that twice.
That's Bob at Post Office Box 140306.
Bob at Post Office Box 140306.
I am through.
In fact, my sermon is through.
Will, you want to lead us in the closing head launching?
Well, are you going to do it or what?
Oh, one last thing.
Boy, I've got some great videos.
I've got some great video tapes to edit from that subgenius convention.
Wonderful stuff, particularly with the swinging love corpses.
But I have to have a VHS editing system with controller.
You know, it needs to be a place where I could sit and cut that,
do some sync inserts, you might say, of my close-up footage with Toth's wide shot footage.
That's all technical church talk, you see,
for, well, stuff that we can't hardly pay for
because we've got to spend all the money on the food outreach, you know, and the slack.
...on free, kids, rolling right along with your own special brand of music.
And now...
Oh, yeah.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Hee, hee, hee, hee, hee.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Come on, baby, don't you be late.
I want your head, I want it tonight.
Cut your head off a hot pass, hey.
Now, have a look at my wall, got a hot pass pin, yeah.
Come on, baby, I want that head.
Come on, baby, want that head.
I want your head to hang on my wall tonight.
My sun, my sand, my surf.
Come on!
Place Mr. Bones, mighty fun board skipping stones.
You feel fresh as a lemonade setting in the shade.
Well, it's hot.
Well, it's cool.
Whoa.
Before I go too much further into this tape,
which ain't gonna be far,
cause we only got about one minute left,
I should mention that I don't know who sent us this tape.
Boy, people send us such wonderful tapes
and then they don't put their own name on it.
This says, look out Miami,
and lists the 10 zillion cuts of music and records
that were on it.
But I can't remember which envelope it came out of.
If anybody knows, tell us.
I don't know.
I'll have to look great.
I forgot the whole thing.
Oh, stop it, you're killing me.
See, it makes me feel much better just talking to you.
Anytime, baby, anytime.
Now I think that I know who sent me this tape.
Which you go to what's called La Plagna.
Make that Billy sweet William now
Married life done changed him somehow
He's the man the town used to fear
Now they all call him sweet Papa Willie dear
Stronger than Samson I declare
Till the brown-skinned woman's bobbed his hair
Excuse me
Good evening, you are listening to radio station KNON 89.3
Dallas-Fort Worth, the voice of the people.