Are you a voyeur? Do you like to watch?
Uh-huh.
What's your name?
Bob.
Hi, Bob.
Uh-huh.
What are you going to do with it, Bob?
Tell me. Tell me how you like it. If I came in your room right now, what would you do to me?
Baby, if you came in my room right now, I'd want you to put your feet...
Oh, boy.
Oh, yeah, Bob.
Oh, yeah?
Uh-huh. Do you think you can find...
Uh-huh. Do you think you can find my sub-G spot, Bob?
Uh-huh.
Come on, baby. Find it for me.
Yeah.
Oh, Bob. Oh, yeah.
Uh-huh.
Four, three, two, one, fire!
Welcome to the sub-genius radio ministry, Hour of Slang.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
Slang!
Now, you keep talking about this Bob, and I've seen pictures of him, certainly a lot of
drawings of him, and yet I've never heard... You sent me several of the books and the tapes
and stuff over the years. I've never actually heard Bob's voice. I've never seen a photograph
of him.
Well, you've seen plenty of photographs of him. You pick up any old Better Homes and
Gardens, Popular Science.
from the 50s and early 60s, Bob modeled for ads.
He's that guy with the pipe, the grinning, sort of a Ward Cleaver-ish,
Dick Van Dyke-looking fellow with this sort of slightly crazed grin,
and he's got a pipe.
You may have seen pictures of him spray-painted on bridge abutments
and dumpsters and so forth.
Let me quote it.
I created light and created darkness, created goodness and created evil.
Evil. I, the Lord God, do all these things.
God is the source of evil, and he admits it.
What's the burr under your saddle?
That's like if you hit your hand while you're nailing a hammer
and close your penis in the door of a car,
or like the channel changer maybe takes off and it's weird.
Weird crap, man.
That's what it is, Captain Whiz Boy.
Did I disconnect the wrong person?
I don't know if that was a person, was it?
No, it probably wasn't.
Another one of those discarnate voices from the...
The void.
I don't know what I'm doing.
Speaking of the void, how's your show?
I don't care.
He wants to go home.
He didn't want to come in.
I don't care.
What, are you all caught up with hours of slack?
You don't need anything?
I'm copying an old rerun of us being funny years and years ago,
back when we were funny.
Back when we were funny.
Yep.
Now we're just old and want sex.
Speak for yourself.
I don't even want that.
I just want to go to bed.
I was talking to you about...
My plan is to think of something absolutely new and revolutionary
which would change the whole face of the world.
The function of the order of Dionysus Abasios
is both the destruction of Christianity
based on the principles of the Satanic Bible
as written by Anton Zander-Levay.
Being of teenagers from authoritarian slavery.
Adolescence is only a social invention.
By nature, teenagers actually are adults.
Should be treated as such as puberty is nature's endowment of adulthood.
And so they should be...
Teenagers should be free to go out with older adults
regardless of how much older.
To become like a teenager.
To become one of them again.
Do you remember these?
Mother sits there and looks at the young child.
She says, my dear child, we're going out into the wide world
and you're going to meet an awful lot of strange people.
You must listen to your mother.
Don't contradict her and always remember these words.
Don't take gum. Don't take candy.
Don't get in strange cars. Don't talk to strange men.
Keep your legs crossed, your panties up
and come home from school in a group.
Your poor little girl gets in a modern car today.
Even a Nash, just for an instance.
Boy, the guy settles the car, pushes the button,
the bed comes down, you get your head caught in the drug.
You don't even know you had it.
Right, because trying to prove that there is,
you know, that there is or isn't a heaven or hell
is like trying to prove that there is or isn't a heaven or hell.
We can't prove that little pink elephants don't exist
in another galaxy somewhere.
We can't prove it, but personally,
Satanists do have principles,
whereas an anarchist will do just whatever he wants to do
with your life.
And being out of control is very unsatanic.
Do you like lying?
Because your name's not Eric
and you're the jerk of the day and goodbye.
And oh no, don't tell me they gave me Ron from Seattle.
Bobby, how's my lying, pandering,
carnival barker of hate
and misinformation today?
Excuse me, excuse me.
Bob, listen, please give me my time.
That's right, I'm Terry Carr
from the voice of the Midlands, Midlands Radio,
all the way from Leeds, Lancashire.
And tonight we're going to have a very interesting guest.
He says he's the man who is responsible for,
if you've heard of it, I'm sure some of you have,
the Church of the Subgenius.
I'm sure you've all heard of the name Bob
and seen some of the graffiti around town lately.
Is it a satanic cult
or is it just another little hyperbole?
We'll pick a group of crazies on the lam
looking for some fun.
We'll be back in five minutes after some words
and we'll be talking to Reverend Armit Say.
Praise Bob!
You've enjoyed Garrison Keillor's
homespun storytelling for decades.
Now delight as America's heartland humorist
brings to life the most memorable event of the decade.
Garrison Keillor's L.A. Riots.
Old Mrs. Laramie was surprised at the ease
with which she was able to waltz out of that electronic store
with the new staring boombox.
But then the store was owned by the man.
And of course she didn't know how to hook it up.
So she put a call out to the fix-it man, Otis Brown.
And he said to her, he said,
Mrs. Laramie, he said,
you've got blood all up on the side of this thing.
And then she remembered just how on her way home
she had used that boombox to clock a Korean grocer.
Yes, indeed.
Garrison Keillor's L.A. Riots.
Available on cassette from the Public Radio Catalog.
¶¶
With missionary zeal
You spit on the fur coat
Yet you wear the leather jacket
And you eat cheese from a goat
Lay your march and you write
And you vote and you scream
All you do, everybody, is scratch
In a big ugly machine
Oh, Mr. Correct
God, tell me what to do
No matter how many rules you got set
You still want to die
What a devil to have a guy
guitar solo
Let the
PC without seal
Cast the very first stone
But if you live in a glass house
You better lead me along
Unless you're a dirt-clad hermit
You're probably the problem to my friend
You've been sucked into the corporate death fence
Whoa, that Mercedes-Benz, Mr. Correct
God, tell me what to do
No matter how many rules you got set
You still want to die
Boo, boo, boo, boo, boo
You're a fool
You've been sucked into the corporate death fence
Nothing but a prude
You're afraid of sex and nudity
A vegetarian in Doc Martens
And the king of stupidity
Mr. Correct
God, tell me what to do
Do that part again
Oh, Mr. Correct
God, tell me what to do
No matter how many rules you got
You still want to die
Boo
winner South CHRISTIAN
border near
Am проис
Ray
Haha
Hey
Don't
We
Know
Those
Names
Hello friends and welcome.
The sermon tonight is entitled, What If?
It is called that for good reason.
Because you see, everywhere I go across this great nation,
everywhere I tour, every performance I give,
some sincere but misguided Christian accosts me in the parking lot
and barks a curse we've all heard a million times for the last 2,000 years.
Sinner!
They shriek, eyeballs bulging and bony finger pointing.
You may laugh now, but come judgment day,
what if you're wrong?
If I had but a dime for every time that thinly veiled threat was hurled towards a subgenius,
I'd have more money than all the trial lawyers in California and New York combined.
Yet, as mean-spirited as this rhetorical question sounds,
it is in fact a legitimate challenge.
What if, Bob forbid, we are wrong?
Such a premise.
It's difficult for subgenies to contemplate because one of the cornerstones of good salesmanship
is confidence in the product.
We will succeed because we know we will succeed.
It is a self-fulfilling prophecy.
To even question the outcome is not only defeatist and anti-Dobbsian,
it is the subgenius sacrilege.
And yet, in the interest of,
in a very open theological debate,
we will consider just this once the question of what if we're wrong.
Now theoretically speaking, not that it is statistically probable,
but hypothetically, imagine if you can,
a world come July 5th, 1998, where there is no excess invasion.
Oh it's painful, it's painful dear friends, I understand,
but remember, this is only theoretical.
A planet that is not surrounded by an angry,
alien spacecraft.
A globe not
littered. A globe not completely
polluted with the corpses
of conspiracy
dupes.
Oh, dear
friends, it would be a sick
society still dominated
by pinks and normals.
An earth where corporations,
governments, and well-equipped armies
still loyal to the system continue
to uphold the status quo.
They fight
to maintain their tight totalitarian
grasp on the very throat of freedom.
Oh, it's a nightmarish
vision indeed, one that makes my head
spin, but one we will contemplate nonetheless in the
interest of free and open debate.
Yes, dear friends,
this dark future of
Dobbsian defeat and conspiracy
conquest, this
desperate future where the last of
genius forces are holed up in the underground
bunkers awaiting the final
onslaught by conspiracy mercenaries
is a vision we do not
want to contemplate, but will this one last
time.
As the Kelvin bombs
explode far above on the planetary
surface, staying in his
subgenius generals huddled
beneath a flickering lightbulb, pouring
over maps of subgenius tunnels,
subway tunnels, and underground sewers,
examining any and all possible
attack routes, they will be
determined, determined
to fight to death and take the
maximum number of normals with them.
Woo!
Why?
Because we hate you!
Woo!
They will be dedicated to honoring Bob
through a dignified Dobbsian death.
It is even,
it is then that
some weak of heart heretic
will step forward, probably some Bobby
who always dreamed of being a real subgenius
warrior for a long time.
But when the chips are down for Dobbs wants to cash,
out.
This weak-willed wannabe Bobby will show his first real courage
when he steps forward and whines,
The Reverend Stang,
Bunker!
You promised we'd have something to show for our,
for our membership fee.
The bunker will fall silent like a tomb.
The collected gas will cause the barometric pressure to plummet.
The bobbing above will pause in divine reverence.
Stang will slowly turn to the trembling traitor,
glare into his frightened little face.
And with the thunder of Daniel Webster,
will proclaim the same answer I gave the Christian in the parking lot.
And that is this.
Even in hell,
we'll have the one thing the conspiracy tried to deny from us
all our living lives.
The one human life that we can't live without.
The one human right they'll never be able to take from us again,
no matter how much they lie about what we did or what they didn't do.
It's the one virtue Christians will never obtain,
no matter how much they beg, pray, or grovel to their God.
I'm talking about respect!
Self-respect!
The only commodity that can't be bought, traded, negotiated,
or stolen in any of the conspiracy marketplaces.
Appreciate it!
Hallelujah!
It's a concept foreign to all pinks and normals who serve the system.
They may have stolen our freedom, our slack, and even our lives,
but by virtue of our very defiance to them and their ways,
we've earned a self-respect they can't even pretend to want.
And you want to know why?
Why?
Because their religion is based on submission, while ours is based on self-respect.
Our religion is based on independence!
Praise God!
Give me a praise God!
So that, dear friends, is our answer.
That's what we get even if we're wrong, come Judgment Day.
The honor and dignity of self-respect earned through a lifelong fight for independence and freedom.
Only the devil could possibly win.
Only the devil could possibly resent a man for wanting to be free.
Any God that wouldn't want his followers to be free is no savior,
but a tyrant, an enslaver of souls, a devil in disguise.
And that leads me to my question to the Christian.
It's terribly original, so brace yourself for it.
What if, what if you're wrong, come Judgment Day?
Please think carefully before you answer, dear friend.
Because remember, your very soul dangles in the balance.
And that is the word of our praise God!
Amen!
Praise God!
Praise Father Joe Mama!
Oh yes, dear friends, praise Father Joe Mama.
A beautiful, beautiful sermon there from the Pittsburgh revival a couple of weeks ago.
Yes, and what else do we have there?
Oh, Mojo Nixon's song, Mr. Correct, from his new album Whereabouts Unknown.
We heard Garrison Keillor's L.A. Riots from the Not For Broadcast album by him.
And we heard a little bit of Bleepo Abernathy and Lonesome Cowboy Dave trying to introduce the church,
interspersed with distracting media barrage material from Reverend Nick Nolan and, of course, Bob Larson.
But you know what, friends, what Father Joe Mama was saying about that one side of the conspiracy?
It makes you wonder.
It makes you wonder which side of the conspiracy.
Which side of the conspiracy is running things?
I started getting paranoid about, well, the Masons, let's say.
Let's just say.
For all I know, I'm really worried about the Illuminati.
But, you know, it started with that America Online logo, which is a triangle with a circle in the middle of it.
It looks just like the old eye in the pyramid or the eye above the pyramid.
You know?
And I mentioned that to my friend Emot.
And Emot said, oh, that's just the beginning of it.
Haven't you noticed those triangles and the eyeball shapes are just everywhere?
And, in fact, they've even gotten quite obvious about the names of these businesses.
You guys ever notice the red arches that form a big M of the Sonic hamburgers?
Get it?
Sonic?
M-Sonic?
I think I'll have Masonic Burger now.
Or, he goes, did you know that Philip Morris cigarettes and General Foods were both owned by this gigantic conglomerate Kraft Foods?
Kraft?
The, as in, the Kraft?
Yes, friends.
And not to mention when they replaced that Popeyes place next door with Church's fried chicken.
Uh-huh.
Well, it doesn't stop there.
If you look around, next time you drive through town, friend, just keep your eyeballs open.
You may see things you didn't want to see.
Buildings one after another that look like, well, like the Temple of Solomon.
If it's not the arches, it's that Temple of Solomon shape that you see etched onto Masonic aprons and symbols.
Uh, my old supermarket nearby here, Menards, I believe he pointed out, looks just like that.
All of the Sam Walton stores.
Walmart, Sam's, Hypermart.
They're in the grand Masonic design, my friends.
Computer places.
Computer City, Discovery Zone.
The Best Buy stores.
All subtle Masonic symbols.
Then go buy your local water pumping station.
The Gas Company.
The Gas Company in most small towns is in the same building as a Masonic lodge, my friends.
The Electric Company.
They all, all of them, my friends, are part of one conspiracy or another, you know.
But what do they, you try to talk about things like this and they call you, well, the polite term, conspiracy researchers.
Or conspiracy buffs.
Or conspiracy nuts.
Or conspiracy kooks.
Or conspiracy crackpots, my friends.
Those are the real polite terms for the folks who attempt merely to lift the veils, peer under the rocks, and pry into the business of the authorities, so-called.
What I want to know is, friends, how come the conspiracy researchers get worse pressed than some of the conspiracy perpetrators?
It must be a conspiracy.
Uh, you know, I can tell you.
I don't wax as sarcastic as the next guy about some conspiracy theories.
I like to think I'm skeptical to the bone.
But I actually do believe a large percentage of those conspiracy theories.
Worse still, I believe in the conspiracy, yes, the plot, by ordinary, normal, everyday people to label conspiracy researchers as loonies.
Or as part of a conspiracy.
Now, contrary to unpopular opinion, friends, it's still possible to use mass media to expose mass media conspiracies.
But you have to couch your expose carefully.
You have to make it look like a satire.
Or a comic book.
Or a radio show.
Like this one, which is pieced together from the dead parts of history books.
And of course, some conspiracy theories are just that.
They're just theories.
Improbable.
Paranoid.
Predicated on few facts.
Like the one about the Masons creating the Greys.
They've obviously got it backwards.
Others are founded on pure coincidence.
And these, I would consider kooky, wouldn't you?
And, you know, one man's a paranoid lunatic is the next man's dedicated researcher.
And, you know, the problem is the domino effect, though.
There's those who see conspiracies everywhere.
Literally everywhere.
The crazy old bircher lady who fears commies under her bed isn't just a stereotype.
Nor is the religious nut who sees Satanists everywhere.
Nor the UFO cultist who mistakes something that could be cured with Prozac for messages from the Space Brothers.
But, you know, there might be something to some of it.
And once you're fairly sure of one conspiracy theory, it starts a tie into the other.
And you start to listen to neighboring conspiracy theories.
And pretty soon you believe in quite a few conspiracy theories.
And you start to sound like one of those nuts.
Unless you're selective about who you tell it to.
And that's one of the things that inclines you towards the conspiracy view of history.
It's the way the more trusting people around you respond to the very idea.
But, you know, try discussing the CIA's more heinous misdeeds.
In polite society, people edge away.
They just can't allow themselves to believe that men whose portraits still hang in city halls and corporate headquarters
were in fact amoral monsters and eager collaborators with Nazis.
Because that would imply that that smiling, rosy-cheeked, glad-handing politician they just voted for might be involved in something worse.
Paranoia has a bad rep these days.
But as the ancient saw goes, it's not paranoia if they really are out to get you.
And they are!
People should be a lot more paranoid.
And a lot of so-called normal people are.
Oh, they're in fact as paranoid as you can get.
They're just paranoid about the wrong things.
Since the FBI has no proof for organized satanic ritual murder cults,
the many little Christian fundamentalist conspiracies have invented them.
The same guy who can't believe the army could ever do anything evil and anti-American
may be convinced that the devil sends heavy metal bands out to corrupt our youth.
He's paranoid about marijuana fiends, but he drives drunk.
He's paranoid about sex and violence on TV, but thinks everybody should have their own automatic weapon.
He's learned that the media is controlled by liberals,
because he listens to right-wing blather all day long on the radio.
Shut up, little man!
Nobody asked you to say anything.
What's the burr under your saddle?
The burr under the saddle is you trying to shut us up and tell us where to hell...
Jesus says, believe in me or to hell with you, and I don't like that.
I'm getting tired of you guys trying to shut us up.
I'm not telling you where to go and what to do.
God's telling you what to do or where you're going to go if you don't do it.
But you know what?
What?
That's not a choice. That's coercion.
How do I know I'm not talking to a disembodied alien right now?
Well, if you don't have a clue that you're talking to a human being, then you're pretty stupid.
How do I know? Prove it to me. You can't prove it to me, can you, Bill?
See, ha, ha, ha. You can't prove it to me, Bill. You can't prove it to me.
Bill, Bill.
Empirically, you cannot prove it to me beyond any reason.
Any doubt.
Anybody that you've ever talked to, Bob, how do you know you've talked to anybody?
You're just living in a fantasy world behind a microphone.
Prove you've talked to anybody, including me, Bill.
Because there's repetition.
Because, because, my friend, I'm a human. I have a human voice.
That's how you know. Odds are you're talking to a Bill.
Get real.
Just because you have a voice doesn't mean you have a brain.
Correct.
I would be more of what I would call a, uh,
pubophilic Satan.
I would be more of a Satanist, um, as opposed to a pedophile,
because, because everything that he says makes 100% sense,
and there is, uh, little or nothing that he says that you can argue with.
I am a, I am a, I am a, I am proud to say I'm a jelly-bill do-do.
Yes, me, I'm Melina.
I am a jelly-bill do-do.
Hey, Bob!
I'm
Do
I must have a girl to call my own.
For I am Dobby, son of Goom.
You pitiful, dobbings-legged earth fools milling about in your cage of only three dimensions.
Dobby, go find me a nymph.
You don't know what we love.
Maynard, bring me a woman.
Bring me a bongo, bongo baby.
Give me a fury.
A hundred of little furies.
I want more.
Bring me harpies with chests of steel.
Bring me the furies themselves.
I want Medusa.
Yes, I will make love to Medusa.
Let her turn me to stone.
I could be no stonier of heart than I am already.
If only the fools would leave me.
And I'd be at peace to complete my experiments.
They want to know who I am and what I am.
Well, I'll show them all!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha.
It's here in this dark cave on the Aegean Sea, where lights have been seen for scores and scores of years.
Fishermen have noticed light in this cave for a period of five weeks at a time during the summer solstice season,
and after that, they do not know anything about it.
These crop circles, or frock circles as they're called,
originally appeared in wheat fields in England and Ireland, Scotland.
Lately, they've been appearing as concrete circles in the center of New York City in Chicago,
decorated with the bodies of mutilated cats, mysteriously mutilated cats.
What could this mean?
There are no secrets in the Church of the Subgenius,
and I will not be endangering myself or my family in any way,
despite rumors to the contrary,
because you, dear listener, will probably not believe a word of it.
It's all just more quaint fiction to you, just a lark, a joke.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Eh, well.
Well, if the frock circles and the smoke from Bob's pipe are just a joke,
then what is your life?
Your very life, my friend.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Where to begin? Where to begin?
There are so many impossible stories and bizarre events associated with the Church
that it is hard to choose where to start.
Oh, man, this is so like, dude, it's like the Lucians in the, like, Hollow Earth,
they sleep with the Nazis.
It's such a weird mess.
I mean, these people from the Nefertiti.
To set the tone, let me tell you what I've seen with my own eyes
while visiting Palmer Vredes,
actually the artist Hal Robbins,
a.k.a. Dr. Hal,
in his San Francisco apartment in 1993.
Hmm.
Well, I'm a good member.
Well, what the hell?
Oh, my gosh.
Lies and Vredes began an appearance,
a fairly innocent brag fight,
each proclaiming their abilities in the most outrageous terms.
But after a quarter hour without significant gain,
Vredes became agitated
and suddenly swept lamp and telephone from an end table.
He then seemingly lifted the table into the air without touching it.
It shot out the window and crashed onto the sidewalk two floors below
where it burst into flame.
Vredes changed the subject.
The subject immediately in the event was never spoken of again.
Having set the tone with that story,
I can pretty much say anything I want to
and be assured that no listener will believe a word of it.
On the same visit, I took a trip into the desert
with D. Woodman Atwell of puzzling evidence,
a harrowing experience all around,
for I saw him apparently drive his truck through a concrete...
...a concrete wall without damage of any kind to anything.
I was then shown a series of missile silos
from which shone beams of bluish green light
for a period of about two hours around midnight.
This is February of 1992.
There were a number of unusual gravitational and magnetic events
in the area around this time.
There were also a number of what I took to be very large sandstone rock formations,
which appeared to change...
...to change positions when I wasn't watching.
Think about it, though, friends.
I mean, really.
Reality, and even its distant relative history,
are actually a hell of a lot weirder than any science fiction.
It's something as far-fetched as Nazis getting paid by the CIA
to train Middle Eastern fanatics to fight the commies can be real.
And it is.
Then why not the CIA and aliens conspiracy, huh?
I mean, if the CIA conducted mass experiments on the citizenry with LSD,
and it did,
then why wouldn't it use some covered Christian organization
to turn earnest young weirdos into Manchurian candidates,
and make them kill anti-establishment rock stars, or even presidents,
just to make all earnest young weirdos look more insane than the CIA?
It's infuriating.
You know, you can't just uncover a conspiracy and leave it at that.
You always have to take into account the deliberate disinformation possibilities.
For instance, maybe the feds pay Bob Lazar
to talk about crashed saucers on air bases,
and soul-stealing gray aliens,
in order to distract researchers from something far worse!
The murkiness level can become literally maddening!
And that just might be the whole idea.
No doubt about it, you can go overboard, friends.
Way overboard.
There's those who believe the Holocaust was a hoax,
and all the rest of us are crackpots.
You know, heck, if you're gonna go that far,
you might as well believe that World War II didn't happen,
and the next logical step is to believe that nothing the press ever reported really happened.
And pretty soon, praise Bob,
you've got mountains of proof that you're always right,
and everybody else is always wrong!
And of course, naturally,
the conspiracies that people tend to believe in
are the ones that make them look good,
and, uh, absolve them of responsibility.
Over a hundred years ago,
some anonymous anti-Semitic Frenchman penned a hoax
called the Protocols of the Elders of Zion.
And to this day, thanks to that hoax,
thousands of frustrated, nasty old rednecks believe that the Jews control the world.
Now, believing that lets them off the hook.
The reason for their poverty and misery
isn't that they're a bunch of lazy, ignorant, alcoholic po-buckers.
It's the Jews' fault!
By the same token,
bitter black people who think that all white people must be out to get them
can find plenty of reinforcement in the nation of Islam, called.
Inevitably, friends,
those who are the most paranoid about a particular conspiracy
become a conspiracy.
They're a bunch of crazy, stupid, and stupid people.
So where is the balance?
Which conspiracy theories should you believe?
For that matter,
which conspiracy should you join?
Well, friends, we're here to tell you about the Church of the Subgenius.
You know, we started a lot of those conspiracies ourselves.
You can always come to Bob
to, uh, to, uh,
to find a conspiracy made just for you.
You can write to Bob.
I'm gonna give you that free information, uh, post office box.
Just say,
Bob, send me that free information.
And Bob is at post office box 140306.
That's box 140306, Dallas, Texas, 75214.
That's right, Dallas, Texas.
That's where we're at.
I remember a time when I thought all that babble
about multiple gun laws,
and the women in Dealey Plaza,
and the Oswald Doubles, and so forth,
was silly.
And it is getting awfully crowded up there on the grassy knoll.
But you know, as I got more educated about the JFK, uh, puzzle,
I learned a terrible truth.
If you investigate deeply enough,
sometimes you become part of the conspiracy.
I'm now a participant in the JFK cover-up.
I know why the Kennedy family had to go along with the Warren Commission.
But if I told, it would jeopardize lives.
Stop laughing.
I'll tell you, man, you start out paranoid about them,
and the next thing you know, you're one of them.
And maybe it's an infinite regression.
Maybe there's no escape.
Maybe, maybe there's no one single truth
that everybody should know.
And maybe there's no one single thing that everybody should believe in.
Not even Bob.
Maybe everything is a conspiracy.
You know, who knows, maybe one of these days we'll find out
even that's not so funny after all.
Good thing this is just a comedy show.
Heh heh heh heh heh.
This is nothing compared to the bizarre political and extra-legal connections
of the Church of the Subgenius.
Ivan Stang is known to have made trips to England and South America
in the past few years to meet with, among others,
high-ranking members of the P2 Masonic group
and an organization of which the Priory of Zion and Bilderberger Group
are sanitized fictionalizations.
Stang and Drummond are known to be 33rd-degree masons,
and Stang's position in a control group hinted at as a Texas mafia
is hereditary through his father, an ex-district attorney for Dallas.
Stang has employed a man named Stang, and he's been working for him for years.
He's been working for him since he was a child,
Stang, however, is his real name, although he now uses the Smith name
in his daily affairs.
I have met Smith and can assure you they are two very different people
of entirely different capabilities.
Smith seems to be a victim of arrested development,
and though he is the nicest guy you'd ever want to meet,
Stang is perfectly correct in calling him
dumb as Dave.
I have never met him.
I haven't met Drummond, but the stories I've heard,
uh,
are as strange as anything yet.
Relate.
Now, I've seen the real Doug.
I've seen the real Doug, and he is just as smooth as buttermilk pie.
He would never do a harmful thing to another human being.
This other man, now you can see there's a big difference.
Look at his chin right there.
There's a big scar on his chin,
and I don't see how they can get away with that.
I've told all my kids so far that this is it.
I'm just giving up on everything the government ever said ever again.
I just don't believe it.
Did you see what they had on the head the other night?
They had a man who could actually make a man,
make a man, make a man, make a man, make a man.
You know what I mean?
Oh,
you rag.
Let's say pour about eight identical glasses of tap water.
Send your loving energy selectively into one of the glasses,
and then you'll see that one of them basically blessed the water.
Leave the room.
They'll switch the glasses on you,
and then go up to the water's glasses with little dowsing rods,
and you'll find that the one that had been blessed
is the one with the largest energy field.
Not only that, but it's also the one that tastes the best.
It's the story of the lost jewelry of Atlantis.
Not that again.
Well, there it is in all its effulgent splendor.
Because we have with us Philo's brother.
Oh, yes, that's right.
His only nomenclature.
That's true.
But you know, I suppose there are areas,
there are places where Philo is his brother.
That's true, but it's never brought up quite that way.
So even on his business card, it says Philo's brother.
Yeah, well.
And he is known forever as...
I don't know what the future is in that.
My mom sometimes refers to Philo as my brother, though.
Your brother, I just can't believe what he did this time.
I just have to get to the bottom of it once and for all.
Whether a person is a brother,
a preference for poop dog hats runs in the family.
Actually, it's not.
She doesn't ever say Sphinx's brother, though.
It's your brother.
My brother?
Yeah, your brother.
See, that doesn't make any sense,
because she doesn't even know my brother.
My brother, the Sphinx?
Or doesn't know Hal's brother.
So if you know our brothers, you can call us.
And if you know we are brothers...
Brother, go find your brother.
And all out there, within the reach of my voice,
are truly my brothers.
Uh, uh...
4-4-12-5.
Related to me by...
intimate ties of...
Jerry Jeff Collins, join us.
Indeed.
My goodness, what a...
similar good memory you have.
Now let's go over that again.
You say you saw some sort of monster?
Mm, yeah.
It's my pet parakeet, Pete.
And what happened to him?
Oh, well, he's been, uh...
Whoa, there goes some...
Uh-oh.
That's what happened to pet parakeet Pete.
He was hurled out of a speeding taxi
in the middle of a busy downtown intersection.
Then dragged in a phone booth
while trying to make a phone call.
But you know, you know,
Philo's brother's here.
Been forced to...
Oh, yeah, that's right.
I said that. I said that.
This is not just a show.
I mean, Philo's brother's here, so...
If you have a question for Philo's brother,
that's what...
That's right now what you want to...
That's right.
The topic tonight is Philo's brother.
Philo's brother.
Do you have a question for...
Uh, journeys to Arizona...
Or, uh...
Who's this Philo guy?
...comment about Philo's brother?
Oh, my brother.
No, that's not your line.
That's the other guy's line.
We're talking about Philo's brother.
And then down here, the scratched out part,
it says, yeah, don't be scared.
I'm scared.
What's going on?
Your flesh will creep.
Your heart will bump, uh, et cetera, and so forth.
Uh-oh.
Punch the...
Punch the wrong brain.
Punch the magic dragon.
Okay, don't be scared and hang up.
Just speak now.
Don't walk.
Green light.
Speak.
Go through the door.
And speaking of dragons, I could tell you about...
Let me answer the phone.
...the very next, uh...
And if you're watching Channel 2,
you see that we've synced up
every single sound effect.
Caller...
Hello?
Hold in.
It's a slim lead, I know,
but it might get us some...
Hello?
Just one.
Just you.
Turn that caller to the cold and damp.
There he goes.
Oh, Hal just turned him around.
Now he's all cold and damp.
Well, it gets him evenly done on all sides.
So, uh, state short question, please.
The phone's busy, so...
Yeah.
So go ahead and call.
You see, there's so many different approaches
to this question of bind over matter
or transcendental reality,
is when I breathe in,
I visualize the energy of the universe
which is very abundant, by the way.
This is the same kind of energy, I think,
as the Tesla technology energy is.
It's similar to the energy of consciousness
or mind over matter.
It's a very powerful energy.
So you imagine this energy coming into your belly button
as you breathe in.
As you breathe out,
you breathe that energy through,
uh, in this case,
through the tips of my fingers,
laser-like into the spoon,
and I become at one with the spoon.
Oh, yes, friends.
You, too, can become at one with the spoon
if you're ready to give your all to Bob,
or at least a 32-cent stamp.
Come on, go for it, man.
Write for the free information.
Uh, here's that number again.
It's got, uh, music by Arnold Mathis
in the background.
Okay, here it comes.
Just write to Bob, my friends,
at Post Office Box...
181-825-7000.
1-417 Cleveland Heights,
Ohio 44118.
www.subgenius.com.
And, uh, as I said,
this is Arnold Mathis in the background.
Before that, uh, before this,
we heard a little bit of, uh,
puzzling evidence and Dr. Howell
on the KPFA Berkeley, uh, subgenius
or non-sub, anti-subgenius show,
whatever it is.
And, uh, coming up more,
and having been more of, uh,
Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
That's ESO Radio brought to us
from WCSB in Cleveland.
Praise WCSB.
And, uh, oh, and praise, uh,
Reverend Mike Cole
for, uh, interviewing that Satanist,
Joe Autrich, which we've heard
little bits of, uh, in between.
We're just, uh, scavenging WCSB
like crazy.
And, uh, thanks to Steve Bevilacqua,
who, uh, rescued that on tape
and put horrible music with it.
Oh, what's, uh,
uh, who else should I credit?
Oh, Nenslow.
Some of the, uh, uh, disinformation
about the Church of the Subgenius,
which I was reading there on,
uh, with Lonesome Cowboy Dave
and, uh, Chaz on that ESO show.
That was written by Nenslow.
I should definitely give Nenslow credit
for that, those particular lies
about the Church of the Subgenius.
I thought they were very effective lies,
myself, one way or another.
And, uh, so, we'll plunge back in.
Thank y'all.
Well, well, I just don't know.
I just don't know.
I wandered into this,
I wandered into this little,
uh, spook house, restaurant,
or whatever it was.
And they were, they were all
having some kind of a party.
And then they set fire to the walls
and just kept partying away
while the place burned down around them.
It was like a vision of hell itself.
I really, really, really, really,
really bad.
But people just kept paying money,
walking in,
swigging drinks at the bar,
their clothes on fire,
instead of just laughing it up
as if they didn't feel any of it.
It was kind of a,
a cult, like, and they,
and in the end,
they were all dead.
I stood outside,
watched the place burn to the ground.
It was like they,
you know, they, they all acted like
this was something they did every year.
Every night.
You got me.
Don't ask me.
I don't know nothing about it.
I'd just as soon stay here working at the,
at the quick shop
for a buck, two eighty an hour.
I ain't gonna send my money to that preacher.
That's just what he wants me to do.
I'm supposed to believe
in some kind of deliverance
by alien space fellers.
And if I believe on Bob,
then I'm gonna get to ride them escape flying saucers.
And I just, I don't buy into that.
Well, some of my friends,
now some of my friends are believers.
Some of my friends are believers.
I'm not trying to put them down.
But I ain't gonna give away all my worldly goods.
I've already been through.
I had religion once.
I was in the Jehovah's Witnesses.
Had me give my Cadillac away.
The world was supposed to end on April 23rd.
We all sat around the hilltop waiting for
the end of the world.
After a while, we got bored waiting,
wandered off.
So I ain't gonna fall for none of that stuff this,
this time.
But you know what I heard that was really sad?
I saw on this newspaper,
it said the Loch Ness Monster was dead.
I seen it right on the cover of that newspaper.
It was so sad.
It looked like a giant prairie squid
or a big oyster with flippers on it
and a cute little otter's head.
And she was,
did you know it said in there
she was over a thousand years old
and left a little tiny baby
Loch Ness Monster homeless.
Friends,
you don't want to let that little baby
Loch Ness Monster go hungry, do you?
No, for in her belly are thousands of spider eggs.
Well, here in the church of the subgenius,
we offer special food and toys
and modeling clay and clothing
to those slackless children.
You know,
Even cosmetics and toiletries.
Those kids that you see the pictures of
on milk cartons,
they're not lost, friends.
They've just found Bob.
They are frolicking with the baby Loch Ness Monster
now in a special swimming pool
at the home for slackless children in Malaysia.
Oh, there is no secret, Neptune Agenda.
Loch Ness is, Nessie's dead.
It was all a big hoax.
Well, we'd prefer not to go into too much detail
at this time about the origins,
since our own research is not quite clear.
But the church of the subgenius does seem
to have a direct connection with the program
known among conspiracy nuts as the Neptune Agenda.
And in fact,
The Neptune Agenda?
Yes, the Neptune Agenda,
which we can trace the beginnings
back to the discovery of sonar in 1915.
It's a watery, fishy theory of philosophy and conspiracy.
But it seems that after the first use of sonar
to create the universe,
to detect German U-boats in the North Atlantic,
unusual and cryptic Morse code messages
began to be received by listeners in many different areas.
A separate code of a logarithmic nature
was created to communicate with what turned out to be aquatic mammals.
I probably shouldn't elaborate further here
because some of the things I've picked up about this
seem very new-agey, stupid,
having to do with ley lines
and a global network of crystal skulls
used as mind control transmitters
to direct the actions of technologically advanced,
or left-brained, humans.
I can hear the teller currents.
This is the way I navigate.
I move my body close to the earth.
The teller currents,
it will tell the insides of my ears.
Sonar.
You can hear the whales.
The briny deep.
Moan out their love songs.
Lonesome cowboy Dave up there on the prairie
could hear them whales all the way out in the ocean.
And he knew he wasn't going to be lonesome for long.
He'd heard from old Bob
what fun a giant sea-cation, sea-going mammal could be.
Oh yeah.
They're not that different from human beings, really,
the way their bodies are set up.
They're warm-blooded.
Warm-blooded.
Mmm.
When you're in the freezing, frigid Atlantic Ocean,
and you got you a kind of
romantically inclined she-whale,
and you're a particular lonely cowboy preacher with a guitar,
you smell that ambergris floating on the ocean.
You smell that ambergris floating on the seashore, there.
Oh yeah.
Ooh!
You'll drop your sheep and your horses and just shuck your chaps and...
Liquid vinyl in lonesome.
Go swimming right out there.
Oh yeah.
Lonesome cowboy Dave riding them dolphins all the way out to meet his queen.
The great blue whale in the center of the North Atlantic.
Yes.
Yes, Dave Tristan, just as had his mentor, Bob.
But unfortunately, whereas Bob was man enough to handle a female blue whale,
Dave got tangled in the harpoon ropes and was last seen with his wooden leg a-flopping
as she sounded one last time.
I'm the Blue Devs with Davey Jones Logger.
We've got 1,000-10 stories of Neptune.
Yep, Dave's back down there underground, underwater, underneath the great web.
I can't breathe.
I feel like I'm suffocating.
This is not as fun as it was before.
I'm just going to relax this spandex.
Shh.
He was deep, deep inside the blowhole of the she-whale.
He thought he was going to be having some kind of a big, hot date that night,
and here he was, stuck halfway in the blowhole, halfway out.
She couldn't spout, and that's about all he could do.
Oh, baby, Leviathan be thy name.
I got a wooden leg.
He was, but they later got over there,
and they got their marital differences,
and they took up residence inside Mrs. Monstro.
I'll take it out of the garbage.
I will take it out of the garbage.
I'm going to take it out of the garbage.
All he had to do was occasionally empty the garbage out of Mrs. Monstro.
He'd scrape up the old license plates and tin cans,
and used syringes and so forth that washed into her stomach
that managed to get through the baleens.
He'd have to empty that stuff out now and then.
He was like a parasitic life form inhabiting the body of the she-whale.
Little maggots here, little maggots there,
little harpoon-looking here, little, oh, it's so shiny.
Their only natural enemy was Eskimos,
and Norwegians who had broken,
and Japanese whaling boats who had broken the international laws against such things.
Dave was Dave of the Whales.
I'll learn this baby's song, and then I'll record it and make a million dollars.
And Dave thought he was going to be a big rock and roll star
with the Cetacean Whale Song Rock.
See, now, these songs last about a year and a half,
and it takes about two years to compose them.
I figure if I just shrink it down in a databank,
and I'll take a whale all the way down to, like I say,
three vibrations for every 25 seconds or something,
I could have a perfect three-minute pop rock song.
A whale, a whale of a whale, a whale of a whale.
But unfortunately, the new age composer, Yanni, beat him to it
and made all the big money.
Dave and his wife, the female blue whale, Mrs. Monstro,
were left in the gutter.
They were singing bad country-western songs
hoping for spare change from the citizenry and tourists
who would walk down the boardwalk there.
Bleak ending for a man who never learned to live his life
and let it be that way.
Lost enough to wait like that.
A man like that has something wrong with him.
Well, no, actually, like I said,
the whale is not like it's a different order of animals.
They're mammals.
They're not that different from a person.
They have a vestigial sort of hind leg
and rather a longer tail than people do.
But, you know, they breathe air.
They cry tears.
They weep tears just like you or I.
Well, like you, anyway.
And they don't seem to be able to take very good care of their fingernails.
Why is that?
This fungal growth seems to have traveled all the way
to the base of the spine.
And this basal area here is completely covered with the fungus.
Lone cow, Dave, don't you know what they're doing to yourself?
Pills, pills, pills, bob, bob, feel me, bob, feel me, bob, those knuckles, bob.
I can't believe it.
Bop, bop, bop, bop.
Brop, brop, zippy, brop.