We're in a war zone, Dave.
Two motorcycle officers horribly wounded in a deadly crossfire.
The police seemingly unable to rescue them in spite of several desperate heroic attempts.
It's completely out of control now.
And meekness and righteousness.
And thy right hand shall teach thee terrible things.
Huh.
I guess with a sword in your right hand, you could probably learn a lot of terrible things.
Whoa, verse 5.
Thine arrows are sharp in the heart of the king's enemies, whereby the people fall under thee.
Huh.
Solomon doesn't seem really like too nice of a guy.
That is, if you're his enemy.
Steve, we can see the flag that was raised yesterday with the Star of David
and the Star of David.
The serpent on a blue field still waving in the background.
Has that been raised continuously?
That you, that you, that ye.
It's hard to separate everything.
Everything relates to each other.
For every action, there's a reaction.
We got to tell them that they got to come out of them dog tracks.
We got to preach, get that dog track.
A lot of people say nothing wrong with the dog track.
When you're in that dog track.
You are going to hear some orders over which you will have no control.
Bob?
The message is now part of and registered in your subconscious mind.
Every time you say, see, hear, or think.
Bob?
That's your key phrase.
It will trigger the entire message without your being aware of it.
And what exactly does this do for them?
Well, it causes them to forget everything they've learned and it prepares their mind
for the slate.
It's like impression, the imprinting of the true subgenius.
For the next hour, sit quietly and we will control all that you see and hear.
You are about to experience the awe and mystery which reaches from the inner mind to the subgenius.
Hour of sweat.
It's not a pleasant job, but someone's got to do it.
But anyway, thy throne, oh God, is for, huh?
Wait a minute.
Thy throne, oh God, is for ever and ever.
Now, wait a minute.
Is David saying that Solomon is God?
No, he's probably just saying that God is God.
Huh.
Well, why would a prophecy about Solomon have to do with God's throne?
Thy throne, oh God, is for ever and ever.
The scepter of thy kingdom is right scepter.
Thou lovest righteousness and hatest wickedness.
Therefore, God, thy...
Wait a minute.
Therefore, God, thy God?
What could this possibly mean?
Look, you can't figure out everything.
You can't put everything into a perfect box and be perfect and everything.
I took my clothes off and laid on the floor.
No, the coffee table.
Was that with sugar or with cream?
No.
I wish I could think up something very witty and funny that you would just have to listen to like ten times and just laugh.
But I can't think of anything, so.
I'm sorry.
Think of something on your own.
You do that.
You're funny.
I'm not.
Tell that prostitute that she don't quit turning tricks.
She only way to hell.
I expect the tape recorder to start laughing with that one.
Yeah.
Let me put it on pause here.
Every hell's ever heard of...
My hair caught on fire.
Our car caught on fire.
And my TV set caught on fire.
And our couch caught on fire.
An electric current.
This is very strange.
Or is it?
Well, let's look at it again a little closer.
At home.
Listen up, Reverend Isaac Stagg.
We have you surrounded.
Please release the children.
We're your friends.
If you come out, we promise not to prosecute.
Really.
We want to be your friends.
Dad, come on. Just let us get out of here.
This is boring. It's stupid.
We don't want to carry on like this.
Let's just go. Give it up.
Well, uh...
I, Reverend Ivan Stagg,
promise upon the broadcast of this 58 minutes of slack
that, uh, to, well,
release the hostages and the children,
uh, to come out peacefully with the people,
all the people, immediately.
We will, uh, give up all three of our nuclear weapons
and the canisters of BZ gas
and, uh, leave the radio station.
Uh, uh...
Once the people have heard my message
and heeded Bob's word,
I promise the preachers never miss.
Uh-huh.
Ahh.
Oh...
Mmm, mmm.
Uh-huh.
Mmm-hmmm.
Uh-huh, I would sang right now.
Uh-huh, so,änger over here.
This is in such a came-on place,
right now rather than be stuck here in this standoff clutching all these arterial wounds.
But that's okay. I'm only concerned about the lives of the branch Bob Dobzians here
and the lives of all subgeniuses in this world. This world without slack. If the Federal Bureau
of Demonology and Frappy and Cults would have just served as a warrant, I'm sure we could
have come along peacefully. All we were trying to do was summon the saucers and make a little
bit of money and some harmless target practice and ritual bloodletting here, but that's our
rights as religious Americans. Huh. But, you know, without Bob, without that mighty sales
guru, we have no slack. Why? Well, because. Just because. Bob sold it, we smoked it, and
that's it.
It's settled. Huh. The standard of Dob's righteousness is slack, and that's our divine
excuse. We don't need forgiveness. Just that excuse, which Wotan gave to Bob. This is his
sacred stupidity. And now we're waiting for God's video camera to get it set up before
we continue. So, for now, you're going to have to listen to this religious radio
parable by Brain Rot Theater. But we will come out with the children as soon as you
have heard all of these tapes.
And the dreams that you dare to dream really do come true. Someday I wish upon a star and wake up where the clouds are.
Tonight on Brain Rot Radio Theater, we're pleased to have a very special guest. A man who needs no introduction, so I won't tell you who he is.
You just have to guess. But here's a hint. Tonight's episode is called When Bobs Collide.
Two taut and twisted tales to tease and titillate concerning Bob Dobbs and the Church of the Subgenius.
Tonight's first offering is called The Wizard of Bobbs. It starts off in a raging storm of controversy.
Where are you going? I've been speeding. You know you shouldn't go out tonight. There's supposed to be super bad weather brewing.
Well, let it brew. Neither wind, nor sleet, nor rain, nor snow, nor face-riping bats.
I'm going to have to go to the radio station to do the hour of slack. I must continue to bring the messages of Bob Dobbs, no matter what the cost to my physical well-being.
Spoken like a true subgenius. Okay, lover, it's your funeral.
Oh, Bob.
Oh.
So brave, Ivan. Brave the old man.
He had the elements to deliver his message of slack and the cutting, though, to the eager populace's ears.
He was barely able to get to the studio through the gale force winds in his cheesy car, Cheval Vito.
But he did. While the winds worked themselves up to a fever pitch, Ivan began working himself up to a fevered pitch.
My fellow time travelers, thank you for tuning in to the hour of slack.
I'm Ivan Stang.
And so am I.
Tonight's message is one of hope and despair.
One of abstruseness and enlightenment.
For you see, there is an albatross looming large over the northern horizon.
Over Lake Irresponsible in the land of Canada.
Best spam I ever ate.
An albatross? No.
It's known as plagiarism.
Yes, it's rearing its ugly head job and setting its sights on the church of the subgenius.
Your church, my friends, our faithless, faithful legions.
Do not be misled or confused by claims or counterclaims by these false net prophets calling themselves the purveyor of Bob.
The Canucks are sneaky.
The Canucks are greedy.
The Canucks are rippling.
They're ripping us off.
The Canucks have high-powered lawyers.
And I don't.
Why would they bother to rip us off, you ask?
Because.
Because they see what the power of Bob can do.
What it has done and what it will do.
How it can transform mediocre existence into a metaphysical jitterbug.
They have seen the crippled begin to hear again.
They have seen the blind to walk and the deaf to throw away their canes.
And so they mock us by their plagiarism.
Do they say imitation is the best form of flattery?
Don't believe it, my friends.
Imitation is the best form of a lawsuit.
So what is this bastard aberration called, you ask?
He's called Bob Beans.
Not Bob Dobbs.
Do not get blown away by the rhetoric.
Do not get blown away by the fancy logo.
Do not get blown away.
What's going on?
Oh my God.
The hurricane is outside the window.
Oh my dog, it's uprooting the studio.
I'm airborne.
I'm getting blown away.
Oh.
At this.
Yes, the mighty tempest picked up that best little station in Texas
and hurled it skyward with its lone passenger inside.
For months it carried ...
No, no, mimic that, about an hour.
For about an hour it carried the station and passenger
until finally it came to land in a strange land.
One!
Two!
Oh, what the hell?
Oh, man, oh, man, a chevitz.
This don't look like Dallas anymore, in toto.
Jumping baby Jesus.
Look at that, will you?
My radio studio landed smack dab on somebody.
Just a head sticking out.
Wow, it looks like a deformed Bob Dobbs clone with a pipe in its mouth.
You can all come out now, lunchkins.
This nice man has just killed the wicked network executive of the South by placing KNON on him.
Who are you? Where am I?
I am Giselda, the good network executive of the West.
You and your radio station have somehow landed in the land of Bob's.
Bob's.
Right on top of the wicked network executive of the South.
All you lunchkins can come out now.
Wow.
We're rich kids, but it's just bad.
It's okay.
Bob's?
Look, this is a great premise, but I've got to get back to Dallas.
I've got lawsuits pending.
I cannot help you find this place you call Dallas, but I might know someone who maybe could get you some slack and help you.
Well, that's Grook and Fate.
Who is he and where can I find him?
The person.
Actually, he's not a person, but a...
surreal entity is the Wizard of Bob's.
And he's in the Animal World City.
Fair in the ruck as that.
How do I get there?
Tell him how to get there, lunchkins.
The yellow spit toad.
That's the best you guys could come up with?
Geez, that blows.
That blows.
Like the good character actor that he is, he followed the script and followed the yellow spit toad until he came upon a huge cornfield.
My, my, look at that big cornfield.
That must be where Brain Rot gets all their material.
Jumping mother of Pearl Bailey.
What an ugly looking black scarecrow.
I ain't no scarecrow.
It talks.
What are you?
Sure I talk.
I can sing and swallow and dance and all the things you humans do.
My name is Scabby Daze.
Could you help me get my brain back inside my head?
It oozed out again.
I had a frontal lobotomy.
It was in a bottle in front of me.
I got a spare brain on you.
I'm sorry.
I'm fresh out of brains.
An esophagus I could help you with.
I've got an extra set of several organs.
Say, why don't you come with me?
I'm off to see the Wizard of Bob's in Enema World City to cut me some slack.
I bet he could help you to get a brain.
Please take me with you.
Please, please, please.
Where are we going again? Italy?
Take me with you.
Sure, sure, sure.
No problem.
Something's got to move this plot along.
Come on with me and follow the yellow spit toad.
Ribbit.
I've to see the Wizard, the wonderful Wizard of Bob's.
Because, because, because, because, because, because of the surreal things he does.
And so Scabby Daze and Ivan Stang went along the road.
In their merry way.
Following the yellow spit toad wherever he jumped.
By chance, they happened upon another strange character in the Hollyweeds.
Say, look at that.
Look, it looks like an Indian.
And he feels frozen in some kind of yogi position.
Bob, Bob, you're right.
What's this?
A chanting book by his side.
The game of chants.
Let's take a chance and chant.
Let's do it.
And go, da, di, di, di, da, da, di, di, di, da, di, di, da, di, da, di, da, di, di, da, di, di, da, di, da, di, da, di, da, di, da, di, da.
Ugly.
Thanks, strangers.
Thanks for that game of chants.
Oh, my God.
It helps spirit get back in body.
Good thing, too.
That damn spirit was running my credit cards up again.
What's your name, oh faker?
And why were you frozen?
I've never seen him.
I'm a psychopath finder.
Indian medicine ball man of great stature.
Me searching for mantra with different yoga positions and chants.
One chant so bad, spirit leave body.
Take soul.
Now me have no soul.
Me like straight white man.
I wear wingtips.
I listen to Lawrence Wilk.
I can't jump.
I can't dance.
I lost my soul.
There, there, there.
So you lost your soul, huh?
Well, you know, this sounds like another job for the Wizard of Bob's.
Why don't you come with us to the Emerald World City?
I'm sure he'll cut you some slack.
Ugly?
Me come.
Wait.
Me better put ear to ground, listen for sign.
Uh-oh.
Buffalo come.
How can you tell?
Ear sticky.
Eww.
And so there were three off to seek the Wizard.
By now the yellow brick toad was getting a little tired and his hopping was erratic.
Our Zeros found themselves in a real crummy neighborhood.
Whoa.
Let's stick together, you guys.
This looks like a rough part of the forest.
I'll say.
I'll say it is.
Okay, hold on.
I'll do it right there.
Grab some sky, you guys.
This here's a stick up.
Look out, look out.
A dumb cracker has guitar pointed at us.
Better do as say guitar might be loaded.
That's right, he's loaded.
Like me.
I'll loan some cowboy days.
Give me all you valuables.
Else I'll fill you full of riffs.
I'll fill you full of riffs.
Yeah, like this.
That's pretty stupid.
Riffs can't hurt us.
That's absurd, you silly ass.
Call me names.
I mean it.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
I know I'm no good.
Don't look at me scornfully.
Quit gazing at me in amusement.
Stop it, stop it.
Don't hurt me.
I don't know flop.
I'm sorry.
What a wimp.
This fictional cowboy character has no balls on his feet whatsoever.
No balls.
You're right.
It's my problem.
All my life I've been scared to try anything.
Scared of failing.
That fear's kept me from trying anything.
I ain't got no balls in this business.
I need some balls.
I could be so very ready.
I could get a heady.
If I only had some balls.
Some balls on his feet.
I'd be bold.
I'd take chances.
I looked in my underpants and I found a pair of balls.
On his feet.
Oh, don't feel bad fictional radio character lonesome cowboy Dave.
You can come to Animal World City with us to see the Wizard of Bob's.
I'm sure he'd cut you some slack too.
And give you your feet some balls you need to get somewhere in your singing career.
You really think so?
Yeah, come with us.
Yeah, come on.
Okay.
I'm sure he'd cut you some slack too.
And so it came to pass that Ivan and his three neaters of things found the fabled Animal World City.
There they were taken before the great Wizard of Bob's.
In a giant production studio from behind a giant mirror they heard,
What is it you wish from the great Bob's?
Why are you before me?
I need some balls.
I need a good dependable mantra.
I need someone to take this ball peen hammer out of my cranium and give me a brain.
I gotta get back to Dallas.
See, I've got these lawsuits pending and it's just a terrible situation.
You've gotta help me.
Silence!
Enough of your banalities.
For me, you cut to some slack.
And give these things you seek to me.
You must, you seek, prove yourself worthy.
You must find the wicked program director of the North, Bob Bean, and bring back his pipe to me.
Bob Bean's here too? In Bob's?
Funny how art imitates reality.
And so our Zero's headed north.
Over the lake toward the tower of Bob Bean's.
But Bob Bean's was not one without tricks up his armless sleeve.
He'd seen them coming in a trailer and sent his army of flying junkies.
That's right, an army of flying junkies to kidnap Ivan and leave the others scrabbling for their livelihoods.
The flying junkies, with their hypodermics and cigarette papers, did just that.
They brought Ivan to Bob Bean's, the wicked program director.
The TV executive of the North and Psycho, Lonesome, and Scabby were forced to find the tower the hard way.
Probably by bus.
You! It's you!
You've even come to a strange land and ripped off the Church of the Subgenius here!
In a land called Bob's!
Is nothing sacred!
No, that's right.
It's working on Earth, it'll work here.
True, Bob Bean's here.
True, you were on the scene first by about eight years.
True, you built up the loyal army of subgeniuses one at a time.
True, I am a blatant attempt to cash in on your fame.
But, but in the land of Bob's, they haven't heard of you yet.
And they won't either.
Flying junkies, take him away!
Nothing can stop me, not even the Wizard of Bob's!
I'll get him too!
Well, it looks like the wicked programmer will have his way.
But wait, who is that lurking in the shadows watching these events?
Why, it's Lonesome, Scabby, and Psycho.
Busters must have been on time for a change.
Look at that! That evil programmer has Ivan over a barrel of junkies!
Hey, wait a minute!
This is the part of the story where we throw a bucket of water on it and dissolve it!
Wouldn't you know it? No way!
Scabby, put your drooling to good use!
Here, fill bucket with your drool!
And we'll throw that on evil programmer!
Keep going!
A little bit more!
Okay, great!
Hey, you Bob Beans, try a bucket of scabby drool on for size!
No!
What are you doing?
I'm moaning!
What a world order!
And so it came to pass, like a third in ten, that they brought the pipe back to the Wizard of Bobs and received their just rewards.
For you, Scabby, the one who wants brains!
Who needs brains?
Some of the smartest people in the world don't have brains.
No, but they all have this.
Loose change.
Because loose change is common sense, and common sense are better than brains.
And you, Injun, who is searching for soul,
Here's tickets for ten shows at the Apollo,
And ten meals at Little Sister's Savvy Soul Food Diner.
If you don't have your soul back,
You can't get your soul back.
After this, you're already dead.
And you, cowboy,
In search of balls,
You've already had them all along.
You see,
As a child, your parents let you take
Ancient oriental martial arts.
Part of the exercises
Was hiding the testicles
Inside your body.
Now, put your thumb in your mouth,
And blow real hard!
Wow! What a difference!
My voice is deeper!
I'm gonna be famous!
Gee, Ivan, everybody's got what they wanted!
Except you!
Yeah, what about Ivan, Wizard?
How can he get back to Dallas?
Very simply.
Just click your Air Jordans
Together three times
And say,
I wish I was in Dallas.
Oh, well, chumps,
This looks like
Where we part for good.
I'll miss every one of you
Very much.
Goodbye, scabby.
Goodbye, psycho.
Goodbye, lonesome.
And thanks.
We'll see you again, maybe.
I wish I was in Dallas.
I wish I was in Dallas!
Is he going to be alright, Doc?
Looks like he's coming out of it.
I'm back!
I'm back in Dallas!
Hooray!
Or did I never leave?
Oh, my head!
He suffered a little concussion,
But he'll be alright.
Boy, I had the strangest dream.
I dreamed I was in the land of Bob's
And I met these fictional radio characters
And you were all in it!
But it was a dream, huh?
Just a dream.
It was only a dream.
Ivan, there's these three people
From northeast Ohio
Who wish to speak to you.
Hey, you don't know me, but
You don't know me, but
My name's Lone Jim Cowboy Dave,
But you don't know me, but
Me, Psycho Pathfinder, pleased to meet you.
That's Scabby Days over there.
Listen, we do a thing called
Brain Rot Radio Theatre at WCSB.
That's WCSB in Cleveland, Ohio,
And we got a hip idea for you.
Boy, you boys look fairly familiar.
Maybe overly familiar.
You know, I can use you three
To help fight this cancer from Canada
That's causing me so much grief.
Yeah.
Yeah, I could use you three.
So, uh, now, what's your hip idea?
Well, we got this really cool idea
For a great radio show for you.
Yeah.
Listen, listen to this concept.
Big Wind takes you to the
Wizard of Bob's.
Get it? Wizard of Bob's? Get it?
Uh, well, sorry, boys.
It's already been done.
Boy, you three look familiar.
I never forget a face, but
In you three's case, I'll make an exception.
Well, this has been a fairy tale.
Kind of film noir, but
But in every fairy tale
Comes some truth, some moral.
And the truthful moral of this story
And the truthful moral of this story is this.
Do not accept substitutes.
Look for the subgenius trademark
Look for the subgenius trademark on the label.
And keep a wary and weathered eye
On the northern horizons
For a Canadian invasion.
If you see anyone resembling Canadian
Shoot first.
Ask questions later.
Sorry about that premature
Immaculate conception a minute ago.
We're broken people.
And they shall bleed
And travail
In their sorrow.
But unto them shall come
The voice of the ark of the heavens
And say, let there be
No wailing and
Remonstracing.
For ye all now walk in the house
Of Jehovah One. And if thou dost not
Walk, thou shalt crawl
On the stumps
Of what were legs.
For mine is the hand
That makes, and mine
Is the house of
Pain.
This is and is not, but lay ye
Down the tones and hooks of the brain
For these are evil
And they are
Unclean in the eyes
Of Jehovah.
For the brokers and the money-chains
Shall be snatched and
Rubbered, and from their faces
Shall be burnt their noses, and from their
Loins dried the fluids
The fluids, ah yes,
The fluids of the babe.
And it shall be gone
Into drainage.
Now that was pre-scripture 79 through 83.
And what do these things mean?
What are we really looking at?
The Revelation X is a pre-scripture of dogs
That Jehovah One gave to him.
That's him, quote him, unquote, end quotes.
And remember,
The most fearful warning ever given to subgeniuses
Is the warning found in
Batch 22, Neuronica 17,
Book of Moronix 73.
Which is the promise and warning,
The warning, yes, of X-Day.
When the men from Planet X
Will arise and descend
And rupture up,
Rupture up all the faithful
Twenty dollar dues paying subgenius
Ministers in a blaze of
Glory, not unlike the blaze
Of gunfire heard outside
Our little compound here. And why are
We so afraid?
Because the light of the great land
On that day will be speckled
With what looks like thousands
Of burning monks.
And these are the true believers
Being lifted up into the escape vessels
Of the sex goddesses.
Ah, yes.
And the other light on that dreadful morning,
The other light on the helmet
Of the queen of all the UFOs
Will resume blinking.
And on that day, you boys had better hope
You're on her good side,
Lest ye be fried
With those pinks
In thy own fat.
Huh. But we haven't seen your
Love offerings, so how's she gonna know you
From some federal agent?
And we want to save those federal agents, too.
All of them outside.
We want them, too, to have their own
Fortified compounds
And fifteen wives or husbands.
We don't want them, but Dobbs said
We had to have them. And we want
Those agents to be on our side
Before they come raiding us again.
That's all we're saying.
Bob's return
Will herald a millennium
Of rule under
The House of Dogs.
Huh. Well, what is this saying?
It's a rule of rule in slack.
Slack is the law. Slack over will.
Isn't that right, Will?
Old Faithful Will's here with me, friends.
He's trying to hold himself in one piece, too.
He's got a sort of
Unexpected vasectomy from a bullet.
But he's doing fine.
And Father Joe Mama's here, too,
With his video equipment,
Recording our last stand.
Whoa!
Excuse me.
Recording our last stand
For posterity.
Actually, you might call it the last brunch.
We've got a
Coke machine here
And a lot of quarters, so
Don't worry, we can hold out indefinitely.
But we promise
To come out when this tape
Has been played to all
The sentient beings on Earth Farm 1
Including dolphins, whales,
And those gorillas
Which have learned a sign language.
Oh, oh,
Excuse me, Will.
Yeah, I'll move out of the way here.
Friends, I have to move
So that Will can drag that old lady's
Corpse out of the studio.
But that old gal, she'll be sleeping
With Bob tonight.
She'll be in Bob's arms.
Maybe she's one of the lucky ones.
Now, uh,
I hope you can hear me okay
Over the bullet, uh,
Gun...
Uh,
Gunfire out there.
Many of you may mock us
And call us kooks and cultists
When we talk about the conspiracy
Of the normals that's always
Taken away our slack, and yours too.
Oh, and you say, oh, ho, ho,
Isn't that funny, those nuts
Think that there's a conspiracy.
Well, we happen to be looking down the barrel
Of about 10,000 assault weapons,
Uh, helicopter gun mounts
And grenade launchers, and even more
Than we've got, and I don't know about you,
Dear friend, but that sure looks
Like a conspiracy to me.
And what was our crime, I ask you that?
Uh, being weird,
That's about all. Uh, so,
Some of our so-called activities didn't
Strike you as being normal enough.
We didn't hurt anybody. Uh, those children
Volunteered to build that saucer landing pad.
That golfer's head
Was already decapitated before
We started launching it.
And what about the right to bear arms?
Well, we can only bear arms big enough to kill each other,
But not big enough to fight the conspiracy?
Huh. Well,
They deported Reverend Sun Yung Moon,
But you didn't complain, cause you weren't a Moonie.
Uh, they deported
Sri Bhagwan Rajneesh,
But you kept mum,
Cause you weren't a Rajneesh.
Well, they went and made Jim Jones
Part of a CIA mind control experiment,
But you didn't gripe,
Cause you weren't in the people's temple.
And they jailed Jim Baker,
And defrocked Jimmy Swaggart,
But you didn't care,
Cause you didn't steal money, or
Rape church secretaries, or frequent, uh,
Frequent po-bucker prostitutes,
Or at least you didn't get caught.
Now they're cheatin', the one true
Bob Dobbs, the one who isn't a
Gibbering Canadian, but you
Sit there on your duff, cause
You're not one of the 13 original
Apostles. Well, when they finally
Come for you, my friend,
There ain't gonna be nobody left to care about you.
And the sons of Israel
Shall be snatched up, per scriptures 107,
Uh, and behold,
My servant shall
Prosper, it says here, he shall be exalted,
Uh-huh, and lifted up,
Uh-huh, and shall be
Very high, very high, what is that?
Uh, he who knoweth the fools
Will prophesy for me,
Shall be made over
Men, over men, uh-huh,
Many will be astonished at him, for his
Appearance, his appearance, uh-huh,
Is so marred,
Well, beyond human semblance,
And his forms beyond
That of the sons of men. These
Who are over men, who have
Followed my almighty word,
Shall be the ministry of the
Angelic host, and they shall
Uh, speak for them. Now that's
Spiritual, that's spiritual, huh.
That shows that this
Show is not to be messed with,
Nor pranked with, by anybody
Who would dare think they
Can make, uh, speculations,
Or private opinions, or
Unlock the mystery of Bob's
Pipe, and the, the information
Therein, uh-huh.
Uh, now, pre-scripture says,
Uh, that a stang
Was made from the smithy,
Hmm, the two-edged
S-word,
S-word, s-word,
You might say, uh-huh, well,
And what does that mean? Which was made from
Dob's own pipe stem.
Uh, could it be that the stang
Was used by, buh-buh,
Bob, huh, to write down
Odin's message that would someday be
Revealed by Bob?
Well, I'm just gonna have to let you think about
That. We, we
Don't have to leave the compound here until this
Tape is all played out. And now,
Uh, we have some more holy tapes
Here that you're gonna have to listen to
If you want us to ever leave this radio station.
And then I believe that, uh,
Well, I believe that Father Joe Mama
Has a few words to say.
Welcome to Dallas, Father Joe Mama.
It is so good to see you here.
Uh, I'm gonna
Try to drown out this, uh, gun
Pop- wait, get down! Don't want you to get-
Stay away from the window! I'm trying to get in the back down there!
Okay. Keep it low! Keep it low!
Get down! Uh, can you
Hook your headphones in? Uh,
Try sticking them in there.
Does, does that mean anything to you?
Yes, Reverend Stang,
Uh, this is gonna be, uh, quite difficult, uh,
To proceed under these, uh,
Conditions. But we're
Not gonna give up until we've had a chance
To cleanse the minds of all
Our many listeners.
And with that, dear friends,
We're going to lead into our most
Pronounced of all wills
And testaments, the word
Of J.R. Bob Dockery.
You see, friends,
The sermon tonight is entitled,
The Last
Chance. Yes, friends,
1998 is fast approaching,
And a lot of people have come to expect the church
To start singing a different tune about
Judgment Day. They say, hey, did you
Hear the news? The Berlin Wall
Has fallen. Things are getting better. We say,
Is that so? They say, hey,
Did you read the papers? The Russians are
Now our friends. Things are getting better.
We say, is that so?
They say, hey, did you see
CNN? We won the war. Things are
Getting better. Is that so?
And now they come a-running and a-churring,
Roll out the barrel. We have
A new president. The Republicans are out.
The recession is over. It's the year of the
Woman. Everybody get naked. Wooo!
You poor
Pitiful little pigs!
Do you really think an eternity of
Sin can be erased so easily?
Are we now supposed to
Embrace the conspiracy?
And call off the excess invasion?
Do you actually believe
That you could defuse an entire
Revolution with a few
Scraps of conspiracy
Compromise?
Never!
These petty little sidelines
Of have a nice day news
Don't divert our attention from the
Real issues, not for a second.
They read, Dateline
Washington, new conspiracy president
Sworn into office, promises
New conspiracy healthcare plan to keep
Workah-drones healthy and more capable of
Serving state. More to follow.
Dateline New York, new inmeets
For conspiracy roll call vote of conspiracy
Agenda for conspiracy world
Domination. Renegade nations refusing
To conform to new world order
Will be penalized. More to follow.
Dateline planet earth,
Conspiracy in last ditch effort
To avert bloody overthrow.
Attempts to utilize all arms
Of conspiracy propaganda to convince
Subgenius rebel-rousers
That world is now A-OK.
Memo from
Memo from conspiracy high
Command states quote,
Conspiracy no longer hostile.
Conspiracy now friend
Of little guy. End quote.
Well, well, well.
The world is getting better now, isn't it?
We should just call off the invasion before
It's too late. Wrong!
You can fool some of the subgenies, some of the
Overmen, any of the time.
But you can't fool any of the overmen, any of the time.
They're much too attuned to the wily ways
Of the wicked ones.
I'm talking about you, Mr. Pico President.
Yes, you. The one with the firm handshake
And the easy smile.
You're not tricking anybody with your
Bold new vision or JFK idealism.
We in the church go by
One credo and one credo only.
Ask not what the conspiracy can do to you,
But what you can do to the conspiracy.
And come July 5th, 1990,
We're going to put the conspiracy
And we're going to
Line up against the wall,
Execute the ringleaders, and along with
Anyone else who tries to stop us.
Now to some, this may seem a little,
Well,
Extreme. That's perfectly normal.
To the average man in the street,
Witnessing a public execution of a criminal
May appear extreme.
After all, chances are that the street man
Is unfamiliar with the crimes of the criminal.
He was too busy making a living
To notice the misdeeds, the crimes,
The condemn perpetrated on society
Before being brought to justice.
Add to that, the criminal's emotional last words,
His pleas for mercy,
His insistence that everything he did
Was innocent, that he is not guilty.
And now imagine the prisoner's family
Stepping forth begging for his life,
And witnesses filing forward
To testify to the innocence
Of this great man so wrongly accused.
It should be no surprise
That even an intelligent but uninformed
Person would find themselves feeling
Sorry for the poor soul,
And wishing him a presidential pardon.
If respected newspapers were produced
And showed article after article
Supporting the accused, even the most skeptical
In the crowd would likely become sympathetic.
Why?
Because they would see in that individual
Before them not a criminal guilty
About the cruelest crimes
Of humanity against humanity,
But themselves,
Falsely accused and condemned to death
For crimes they never committed.
By now, the executioners
Should be more worried about their lives
Than the prisoner should his.
The crowd might well demand clemency,
And if refused, storm the guards
And free the prisoner by force.
If you were part of this intervention,
You would probably feel proud
For the good deed you performed
And the terrible injustice you averted.
But, if a few weeks later
You learned that the prisoner you saved
Was an insane serial killer,
That the witnesses that testified
Were all paid actors,
And the newspapers you believed
Were all frauds,
You might start to regret
Having been so compassionate.
Then, if by some quirk of fate
You stumbled into
Incontrovertible evidence
That you, the man that you freed,
Was now devoted
To his entire life,
To destroying yours,
That his new obsession
Was to capture you, torture you,
And sell your loved ones into slavery,
Well, you might start to feel
Anger.
Anger at yourself for being
A fool, anger at the actors
Who tricked you in the newspapers
That lied to you, and anger
At all the mental midgets still running
Around out there claiming the bastard
Was really reformed, only misunderstood.
This, dear friends,
Is how we at the church
Feel about the conspiracy.
Each and every one of us
At one time or another
Believed the conspiracy.
Each and every one of us
In one way or another
Served the conspiracy
And every single one of us
Knows in no uncertain terms
That the conspiracy is out
To get us.
Every day it tries to capture us,
Torture us, and enslave our kind,
And every single time
We get close to destroying the monster,
Some well-meaning,
But ignorant bystander starts whining
That we're being too
Extreme.
They say that the conspiracy is actually innocent
Because they read all about it in the
Conspiracy newspapers, or saw it all
Explained on conspiracy TV.
They insist that our allegations
Are exaggerated,
That the conspiracy is getting better,
And that we should just mellow out.
And then they try to
Tell us that we
Ought to give the conspiracy
SLACK!
Dear, dear friends,
These poor misguided morons
May be in the dark now just as we were before,
And we may have acted back then
Just as stupid as they're acting now.
But that doesn't mean
That we don't have the right,
Nay, the sacred duty,
To destroy the conspiracy
First chance we get!
Don't be taken in by any last-minute
Media blitz that tries to convince
You that the conspiracy has suddenly
Turned over a new leaf,
Because it hasn't, dear friends.
The noose is around its neck!
What do you expect the conspiracy to say?
We deserve to die?
Kill us, please? No!
The conspiracy will look and act
Nicer than it has ever looked
Or acted before!
Don't be fooled!
If you hesitate even for a second,
You give the conspiracy
A chance to win
The crowd over.
And if that happens, dear friends,
You may find yourself on trial
With no more X's around to pull your fat
From the firing squad!
There's only one X day.
Do not blow it.
Come July 5th, 1998,
You will kill the conspiracy!
Thou shalt cut off its head
And launch it through the bloody cosmos!
And it is the word of our
Praise Bob!
Praise Bob! Praise Bob!
Praise damn God Bobby!
Aye, aye, aye, aye!
Oh, my co- Jeez, why four
More people were killed right here
Inside this compound while Father Joe
Mama was ranting, and in fact I think
He took an arterial wound to the
Back of the knee. It's blood but it's
Just juice to kill for Bob.
Friends, oh,
Praise Father Joe, praise those
Who are fighting with us, who are,
And look at those Bobbies out there
Throwing themselves into the path of those
Conspiracy bullets to keep us
On the air. That's a lot better than I can
Say for some of you people that pledged
But never sent your money.
Oh, yeah, uh-huh.
Oh, there's that guy falling off the
It's the third time I've seen
That same agent fall off that same roof
Back there. Reinforcements, over to the left!
Watch that door.
Would somebody do something about that dead
Dog that's laying over there? That's making
Me sick. Chef!
Oh, friends, oh, well,
How much, how much time? Well, only about
Ten minutes before we finally,
Volunteerly, uh, leave the
Radio studio, uh,
Carting our, our
Canisters of souls and our
Tactical nuclear weapons
With us. Oh, but before
We go out to our almost certain
Death, uh, we'll, uh, give
Credit to, uh, Media Barrage editors
Who have worked on this show, inadvertently.
Um, uh,
Some of the, uh, barrages
You heard and will, uh, are about to
Hear were by Wes Jenkins
Of Radio Shorts,
The West Coast
Brain Rot Theater, yes, in San
Francisco, and also a cassette called
Audio Bull Dada by
Michael Taylor Duke of
Montgomery, Alabama.
And, uh,
Little, little bit of Reverend
Lucas there and so forth. Friends,
Okay, we're gonna be, uh,
We're gonna be communicating with Bob for the
Next few minutes, so I'm gonna sign off
Here and, uh, listen closely.
And statecraft,
Look at the pressed in kindness
We avoid thee
Upon these American circumstances
Who should fled to thee
From the staff of the tyrannized
And prostrate themselves
Upon thy cordial security
Yearned to signify
Henceforth tentative
Singular upon thee.
To thee
Organize they charisma
For the honorable of their justification.
To thee be adequate
They now consider up for that
Support and succor which
Thou alone canst furnish.
Grab them thus,
Nirvana dad,
Above thy cultivate mind.
Furnish them erudition
In Congress, and pluck in the grassland.
Overcome the
Vicious devise of our brutal
Colleague.
God in heaven looks to be a rock, doesn't he?
Oh, hard rock God, right?
God's long, God's hard.
But wait a minute.
Through Christ we can see that God is not
As hard as you think he is.
Look at God. Come up hither
In the light of the judgment,
And see the Father on the throne.
See the book in his right hand,
And watch him give it to Christ,
And watch him open the first seal,
And let's see about this man on the white horse
Who has a crown and a bow.
He once attracted more than
One hundred thousand to the city gate.
...
One of the few things they can do with their time
Is listen to radio or watch television.
He financed the communist revolution
In Russia with bank robberies.
...
forget everything?
All right.
I'll tell you what,
I'm going to bring
this tape recorder.
Science has freed us.
Chemistry has freed us.
Art has freed us.
Education has freed us.
Somehow we think
drugs are freeing us.
We supposedly have
broken a thousand
tyrannies,
and yet we may be
referred to as
restless men,
intoxicated with
a sense of freedom.
Now God is the one
who has written.
My heart isn't done
in a good manner.
I speak of the things
which I have made.
Is God a maker?
Is he a creator?
What does he want
to talk about?
He looks like the little
termite from the
Woody Woodpecker cartoons.
You know the one that
was always chewing
down the house?
Shut up,
and grow up.
That's right,
that's right.
Now we're tied up,
that's better.
Now, here's what happens.
We go into sudden death.
They are passed on.
I'm a mother,
I thoroughly age.
I examined her,
and she's not only
merely dead,
she's really
most sincerely dead.
That's it?
That's it.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
This just in?
This, uh, uh,
news release.
We will not welcome you
so much today.
Did they mention anything
about the claims
of child abuse?
Yeah, morning.
Yeah, that's what they
always try to get into.
OK, friends,
this may be our last chance
to give that subgenios
post office box number.
There will still be
a few free subgeniuses
left after tonight.
Uh, that you, that we'll
still be able to send you
that material,
that free information
about our church
And it's just a church,
it's just a religion.
Why do they have to call it a cult?
Why do they have to call anything a cult?
Get that pencil ready.
This is your last chance.
It's Post Office Box.
Now, you're writing to Bob now.
You don't have to spell out subgenius.
Just write Bob.
That's spelled B-O-B, by the way, for you sub-subgeniuses.
At Post Office Box 140306, Dallas, Texas, 75214.
That's right, Post Office Box 140306, Dallas, Texas, 75214.
And friends, I've been speaking with Bob just now while those tapes were playing.
I was speaking with Bob on the Aetheric Hotline.
And now...
I know that we said we were going to release the hostages and leave the station when the show was over.
But Bob just told me...
He said, now, Reverend Stagg, wait a minute.
You just wait a minute.
There goes that guy again.
He said he changed his mind.
And that we shouldn't be making it so easy on him.
And we aren't going to make it easy on him.
And Bob then, he said something had just come up and he had to hang up.
And he's going to be calling right back to tell us when to surrender.
So for now...
I think we're all just going to sit back and wait for Bob's call.
Will, would you go down there and get me another Coke out of that machine?
Oh, God!
Hey!
Tell that tear gas canister to get in here!
Tear gas!
Open the window!
My eyes!
Help!
Please open the window!
No!
Please open the door!
I'm listening!
I'm listening to everyone else!
Excuse me.
Um, how have you been listening in here!
Hey!
That is my kerana.
Thank you so much, Bob.
Thank you.
Honeycomb Drive
In Zone
Devil's Pen Creek
Honeycomb Drive
In Zone
Devil's Pen Creek
A woman's beating up a man
Beating up Peter Pan
She's got him
In a mortal headlock
A gog from the shop
Of the new bride
A woman's beating up a man
The man of her dreams
This is just shocking sometimes
When things aren't the way you thought they were
In Zone
Bellatize
Don't be weak
Inherit a mean streak
Don't even be so weak
Don't be pelletized
Bellatized
You can scream
You can cry
You can roll up your eyes
But don't come, don't come, don't come into your senses.
Don't be palletized.
Honeycomb Drive.
In zone.
Devil.
Spin.
Creep.
This piece of music is by Sister Slatshaw.
Which some
some subgeniuses, I guess,
sent us in the mail just the other day from Seattle.
Oh, Seattle Grunge Band.
Isn't that supposed to be cool or something?
And it looks like we got some extra time on show or something.
So I'm gonna run just a little bit here of our good friend, ah yes.
Where man among man, man among men.
Manly men, yes, manly men are we.
We're men among manly men, among manly manly men are we.
We'll sail up north and cross the ice and cross the bear and snow fields.
You gotta be tough and you gotta be a man to club the baby harp seal.
To club the baby harp seal.
We're men among men and manly men, yes, manly men are we.
We're men among manly men, among manly manly men are we.
We'll drive out west on a buffalo hunt in a Venture Bowl and daring.
We'll shoot one again and again and again while the others stand there staring.
While the others stand there.