I come from Thebes, and the women of Thebes are warm-blooded, passionate, and we know what we want.
What?
The self-genius, power of SWAT!
Bob!
The secret is obvious.
What you're about to see we call the Odyssey of Bob's 33 Cocks.
You're traveling through another dimension of dimension.
You're roughly 55 minutes from idle, Bob.
But what you've seen occur inside the cock of this Bob is no reflection on Bob.
It's a safe, well-engineered, perfectly designed Bob cock.
And the men you've just met are trained, cool, highly efficient cocksmen.
The problem is simply that Bob is going too fast.
Bob's 33 Cocks
And that sound cutting Fernanda Leamer is pretty swift, too.
This is an unusual hour of slack.
It's the kind we only release on the Internet, and it only gets played by the most daring or perhaps unsophisticated broadcast stations.
For some time, we've been collecting certain sermons and hymns,
and we've been trying to find out what they're all about.
And we've been trying to find out what they're all about.
The kind that are just too profane and obscene for regular religious broadcasts.
And the basket of tracks is now swollen to bursting,
so this material must be spewed no matter its possibly offensive nature to the sensibilities of some wussy listeners.
This approach is also, by chance, for me, your host and prayer partner, Reverend Ivan Stang,
a much easier shot.
I'm not going to go to produce, because there's too much cussin' for me to even think about bleeping and censoring,
activities which take up to an hour out of my precious week.
This is the subgenius doctrine that, with censoring, just wouldn't work at all,
would not be true to Bob,
wouldn't be prudent.
We start with a parable told by Dr. Le Guim, one which became legend in subgeniusdom,
oft quoted,
to the extent that it became a meme,
and that took over the recent New York City Go-Fuck-Yourself De-Vival,
which incidentally went great.
It was one of the best De-Vivals ever, as you'll hear on future shows.
Speaking of which, on November 13th, we have the Detroit De-Vival.
But now, from 13th X Day,
the great Dr. Katahdin Le Guim.
There was a time back in 1996,
it was the very first X Day drill,
and there was this young subgenius fella,
who had heard all the radio shows and read all the books,
and, you know, he was totally into Bob.
He said, well, I'm gonna go out and I'm gonna make that video,
and I'm gonna go to that pilgrimage at the Brushwood,
to hang out with my subgenius brethren.
And so he drove all day, and he drove all night,
and day after day he drove, until finally, in the middle of the night,
he pulled down that dark New York road to where his campsite was.
And he got out of his car,
and he walked off into the woods to look for a camping spot.
And while he was walking out in the woods,
he crossed paths with a bear.
The biggest, nastiest fucking bear you ever saw.
And that bear raped him, and raped him, and raped him.
It raped him, and raped him, over and over again,
in every orifice, in every position that the bear could get into,
for seven years.
After that seven years was over,
the bear became exhausted.
He rolled over and pulled his now drooping bear penis
out of the young subgenius' ass,
its tip still dripping with glee.
And that bear wandered away for a long hibernation.
And that young subgenius got up,
and he was up on his wobbly legs,
and he began to walk, and he was like,
thank you Bob for having this ordeal be over.
And suddenly, he found himself surrounded by wolves.
And the wolves raped him, and raped him,
and raped him, and raped him.
They raped him over and over again,
in all of his holes, in all of the positions that the wolves could get into,
for seven years.
.
Finally, being too worn out to be of any pleasure to the wolves anymore,
the wolves scattered and ran off into the forest.
And that young subgenius began to walk,
and he walked, and he walked,
and finally he heard the sounds of people,
and he came out of the woods,
and was greeted by a large man in a black hat,
and he said,
Priest Collar.
.
And that man in the priest collar looked at him and said,
Brother, it took you a long time to get here,
but you're welcome here among us now.
.
And they raped him, and raped him,
and raped him, and raped him.
There were so many of them, they made new holes,
and they raped, and raped, and raped, and raped,
and raped, and raped, and raped those holes.
.
For seven years,
in every position,
.
in every combination,
finally,
he escaped from those people,
.
and he made it out
to Bailey Hill Road,
and was hit by a truck.
.
His body was picked up by the local police.
They took him down to the local mortuary,
.
where the mortician raped him, and raped him,
and raped him, and raped him,
and raped him, and raped him, and raped him,
and raped him some more,
in every hole and in every position,
. and you can get into a lot of positions
when somebody's not complaining.
.
For seven years!
Finally, the mortician couldn't put the family off any longer,
and they put him out in a coffin.
.
And his family came to mourn,
. and they came through the chapel,
and they walked past his coffin,
. and they looked down at him, and they said,
. hmm.
. And they raped him, and raped him, and raped him, and raped him,
. they raped him, and raped him, and raped him some more,
. and spread out this immense chain of people,
. and this massive chain of rape,
. that spread across the land,
. and everyone died of dog and bear AIDS,
. the end.
.
. And when the bodies began to overflow the local morgue,
. they were spread out among the other morgues in the county,
. and they were spread out among the other morgues in the county,
. where they were raped and raped,
. and raped and raped,
. and raped some more.
.
. And the moral of the story is,
. is that when you're driving around New York at night,
. always read the street signs,
. because you might end up at Baptist camp like he did.
.
Die muthafucka die.
Won't you die muthafucka, die.
Every body sing.
Die muthafucka die.
Won't you die muthafucka, die.
Die, won't you die, motherfucker, die
Die, die, die, die, die, die, die
Die
Don't suck on the mic.
I've learned.
This vision of beauty on the stage,
this wonderful, wonderful, wonderful angel of slack.
Oh, jeez.
Don't lay it on too thick.
I'll deliver.
This is Suzy the floozy.
And she is to begin our ranchers for the evening.
So one more round of applause for Suzy the floozy.
Thank you.
Thank, thank, thank you so much.
You know, now there has been some criticism tossed my way
because, frankly, it's a little undeniable
that the floozy is starting to get old.
No!
Now, I noticed lately my lizard's been taking up
biting ass for shits and giggles.
He's kind of getting old, too.
And I've kind of noticed a sea change
in Dr. Lovett.
He seems to be, his love has ripened into vengeance.
And Stang, Stang's getting even more crotchety and ugly,
if you'll notice.
I mean, it's a natural progression
from compassion to compression.
Because when things get old, they get mean.
Yeah!
And I've been getting mean lately.
And I don't even have to channel even evil Suzy anymore
to get there, if you know what I mean.
Because I'm losing my looks, I'm losing my senses,
and lately I'm losing my mind.
But I plan on utterly embracing my hideosity.
Because I think there's room in the world
for another thing like I'm becoming,
because evil, after all, Edith Massey's dead,
so maybe there's room for something else.
Oh, there's room for me to totally let go,
because before I'm totally gone,
I'm here to seduce you.
I am here to stroke you.
Yes, I am here to exhort you to come over
and sit on the new face of the Church of the Subgenius.
Mine.
Because yes, it's true,
I stand before you with a mouthful of schism.
Look at it this way.
Staying here ain't done zilch point shit
in getting us off this planet, has he?
Look at him, look at him.
Well, why not just switch horrors in the middle of a stream?
Maybe that might help our luck some, I've been thinking.
I mean, in the middle of a steady piss stream,
try a new erection for a change.
Maybe that's what we need to finally get off.
Because I sure as Shynola can't be any more disaffected
than Commissar Stangevich's thousand-year plan here.
Because you know what I'm prepared to give you, seekers?
What's that?
Praise it!
Oh, dude!
I'm prepared to give you my heart.
Oh, man!
Whoa, field goal!
And if you give me your hearts,
if you give me your souls,
and let me hold your wallets for a little while.
For a processing, you understand.
Just don't think about that at all.
Think about this.
Yes, I'm laying it on the line, boys and girls.
You join my team, I'll give you a blow job.
After I carve a backwards S on your face,
so you don't think it's a five or something
when you look on the mirror, because I want to leave a trace.
So, hey, who's with me?
It's a chance to join my cult and get in on my ground floor.
So that's all I'm offering tonight, baby.
Who's going to follow me?
My tits are on fire.
Yeah!
Slack.
Anti-slack.
You know, there's been such good stuff on this stage.
Pardon me, you know.
There's been a lot of really good stuff on this stage.
I probably came three or four times in the past couple of days.
Easily just at the stage.
Not counting the shit in my tent, all right?
Because I've been...
You see, I am an uberfem.
I am an uberfem of the finest quality.
And I have been looking and looking and looking for that something special.
That certain something to finally get me off.
And you know what?
It's not what you're thinking or you're thinking or you're thinking.
Because I know what you're thinking.
You're thinking, she must be an insatiable fucking slut.
Well, this is true too.
But that's not what I'm looking for, brothers and sisters.
Because you can have a dick the size of the wall of fucking China.
And you can eat pussy like 13 motherfuckers.
But...
You really...
Really...
Really have to have a fucking hot brain.
You see, I don't necessarily want your cock.
No, no, no.
And you know, I like chicks too.
And I like pussy.
But that's not what I'm looking for.
What I want to do is crack that skull open.
And just grind on that fucking hot brain of yours.
I want to feel those synapses twitching in my synapses.
I want to feel your neurons in my naughty bits.
Now this is why I'm up here.
Because you know what I'm looking for?
Is someone to sort of encourage this.
You know, I see some brains out here.
And I tell you, well you see...
No, no, no. That one's worthless.
Let me scan.
Jesus, y'all drink a lot more than I have.
Somebody needs to show me...
What they've got in that brain.
Somebody needs to show me this.
I want to hear...
I want to hear your hate.
I want to hear your love.
I want to hear your slack.
I want to hear your...
And I've got to tell you, I don't know why you shouldn't...
Some of these guys have been okay.
This is open mic, you know.
I mean I don't expect fucking professional fucking ranters.
I don't expect you to blow my mind like Pope Black did.
I don't expect you to make me come in my undies like Susie the floozy did.
But for fuck's sake.
Let's really pull this off.
This is a challenger.
Thank you for watching.
I'll make the same mistake too.
It's all right.
But really, really, really, really, really, you have to understand.
Please, please, please, please stop fucking pinks.
Please.
It's nothing.
It won't work.
They're not ready for you.
Do not spread your legs unless they've paid their $30.
Please.
Oh, Bob, damn it.
You just don't understand.
Understand all the pink is going to do is just take your slack.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, it might be fun for a little while because you're all fucked up.
But you know, he's going to take your slack in the end.
Or she is.
She will.
Them pink girls.
But please, please, please, before I go on to the next answer, please promise me.
If you want to.
To get it on with that pink boy or girl.
If you really, for whatever reason, are absolutely getting the biggest dick or clit hard on for that pink boy or girl.
Just pay their damn membership.
Just pay the 30 bucks for them.
You know, don't fuck pinks.
Now, I want you to repeat this because I need you to understand this.
This needs to go in your head.
So here's what I want you to say.
I will not fuck a pink.
Let's try this one more time because I think it needs to get across.
This is a mantra that should be in your brain.
Die.
Motherfucker, die.
This is our beer.
But, you know, as an audience, you're pretty well lubricated now.
So this is going to be like throwing a hot dog down a hallway, you know?
Well, friends.
Hey, fuck you.
If you were to take a pair of what let's call it a chrono vision viewing goggles.
They look kind of like x-ray specs.
But, you know, kind of.
Clock kind of things.
If you're going to put those on and you look back through history, you would see a long cycle of pink civilization.
You know, creation and destruction.
They get to a point where they almost have something good.
And then some dumb ass decides, oh, I'm just going to pull the lever on the entire pink civilization toilet.
And then they're back to square one.
But like some kind of turd floater, the pinks seem to survive.
Now, if you try to try to picture one of those evolutionary posters you see in you would see in biology class showing the evolution of the pinks from pond scum to a monkey to whatever the fuck they are now.
Now, take that image.
And if you would just look to the side, you would see the entire evolutionary history of the subgenie all the way back to the Yetis sitting in lawn chairs, drinking beer.
And every once in a while going.
What the fuck just happened?
I didn't think they were going to do that again.
Hey, Astro Piscis, pass me another beer.
Oh, shit, that hurt.
Because, I mean, that's the situation, friends.
In this in this world, we are merely cosmic observers in the Jack Kirby sense.
You know, hecklers, galactic SOBs.
We're not here to do shit.
You know, the pinks might think they rock.
They might run everything.
They think they control the world.
They can try to give it a mediocrity shellacking.
But that doesn't get past the fact of the real the real strangeness, the weirdness of the world that's been seeping and boiling on this planet since, you know, since before, you know, they were even, you know, sentient life.
Back when they were pond scum, the Yetis in Atlantis were installing hyper dimensional Internet in Atlantis.
So, yeah.
So, you know, we may take that.
Fuck that.
Okay.
And, you know, some people have asked me, you know, in all this and all this.
Well, well, McGee.
Okay.
Well, we're in all this.
Well, what is the Church of the Subgenius?
The Church of the Subgenius, friends, is a big ol' face and we're all shitting on it.
We're all taking a big ol' shit.
But it's okay because that man, Bob, can take it.
He can take it because he's too stupid to know that he can't.
So you can, you know, take it.
Take the shit on Bob's face.
You can beat him up.
You can cut it.
You can get it all the way down to the bone, to the very gray matter.
And you'll, you know what you're gonna see?
Another Dobbs head.
It's gonna pop right back out.
Because like, like a lizard's tail, Bob just keeps coming back and coming back and coming
back.
He's too stupid to know that he can't do that.
And so, you know, as all the pink deities, you know, wither and die.
Or are knocked off the shelf.
Or are subjected to various factory recalls.
We here at the Church of the Subgenius can rest happily knowing that every microsecond,
there is a fresh Dobbs waiting for us to give us slack.
Praise Bob!
Praise that, praise fuckin' Bob!
Praise that face!
Praise it!
Praise Bob!
And so, for these last few hours, as we are awaiting the saucers.
We can just.
Just rest in peace knowing that as the world's burning and as all this is going on, we can
still laugh and enjoy this cosmic evolutionary just joke that's happening throughout the
rest of the world.
Praise Bob!
praise.
I ever joining Priestess Pisces in the vocalizing this time.
That band had Philo Drummond from the Swinging Love Corps,
Reverend Angry Larry from the Amino Acids,
Reverend Suds from Monkey Hive,
and a whole cast of characters, my friends.
Priestess Pisces also did the Don't Fuck Pinks and Fuck Your Brain rants.
Now we will go to Dr. Howell, Dr. Philo Drummond,
Pope Black and myself in an unseemly discussion
that had started out innocently enough
about the first subgenius feature film, Arise.
It was important to get this message out to the world's suffering millions.
Actually, Film Threat Magazine called Arise
one of the ten must-have underground videos.
Of course, they said that in the year of 1995,
so things may have changed.
Unless the Onion hasn't come to interview us,
yet.
I'm finding that really irksome.
They probably would consider anything they could get from us.
This week they interviewed Joan Rivers.
Now, what's with that?
Well, she's had a lot more Botox than you have.
Is that what it...
Have you seen her face lately?
I've tried to avoid it.
It's like a...
I'd do her.
Man, I'd jack off in her face in a second.
She is a tummler, as they say.
A fighter.
A striker.
I'd do it.
Just so I could say,
yeah, I'd jack off in Joan Rivers' face.
You can admire many obnoxious people
for their internal sense of strength and power.
Jackoff-ability.
Enables them to go on and on.
I was inspired by Pope David N. Meyer,
who bragged to me once
that he was going to date...
He was taking out a girl who was a Mormon.
And he actually said this to me on tape.
He goes,
This I vow to you, Reverend Stang.
I will spunk in the face of a Mormon.
That was what he was trying...
That was his motivation of dating a Mormon.
That guy, he has his priorities right.
And to this day,
I have never spunked in the face of a Mormon myself.
That I know of.
A moron.
Right, morons.
Well...
Look at this.
A brand new copy is worth 99 bucks.
Of what?
It's still in the shrink wrap.
Of the...
Arise video.
Boxed Arise video.
Brand new.
Still in the shrink wrap.
Same one that's in Swag Jack.
99 bucks.
Collector Shangri-La is selling it for $98.98
plus $2.98 shipping.
And the comments are,
Brand new in shrink wrap.
Rare and hard to find.
13 minutes remain to buy this item.
There's a topless young girl running around on the field out there.
Plus as an extra bonus,
you'll get a five minute video.
She doesn't get sunburned.
A five minute video.
What about the mana,
the magical effluvium,
which is manifest by this object,
the unseen,
palpable radiation of etheric forces,
which emanates from such an important
and keystone early souvenir of subgenius thought.
What about that, eh?
Can that be measured?
Is it not an intangible,
like the sunlight on a baby's behind?
What?
Are you playing that background music?
What is that weird noise?
It's gone now.
Don't worry.
Those were crickets.
Just, that was all, uh, nothing.
Nothing.
Yeah, don't ever give up.
I didn't hear anything.
I don't like to stress the
Don't ever give up your copy of Arise
dwindling time factor
because it looks like even the VHS
where the swag shack is concerned.
After all, time is a thing of dragonflies and angels.
The former live too little and the latter live too long.
But within a very short and easily achievable space of time,
you can transport yourself to the swag shack
and return laden like a fortune,
a fortunate trader,
triumphant with the spoils you have achieved.
We've talked about slack.
We've talked about anti-slack.
Yeah, because slack's whatever you make it.
Really.
You know, I mean, my slack might be watching gangbang porn.
That's all right.
Your slack might be watching furry porn.
That's all right too, though.
You know, that kind of creeps me out just a smooch.
But hey, it's your slack.
And you know what?
That's what that's about.
I ain't gonna fringe on your slack.
It's not my point.
Hell yeah.
You see, just because I've got tits in a cunt
doesn't mean I expect you to fucking worship me.
No.
Better not.
I don't.
But you know, I see a lot of that shit.
A lot of you boys falling for this game.
It's pinks. It's pinks.
You know, and they can say that they're subgenius,
but it's pinks. It's pinks.
Because you know what?
The great thing about subgeniuses is us uberfims are equal.
And you are equal.
You're equal to the uberfims, you boys.
It's the same.
You're blowing my mind.
We're all pinks.
No, I'm not blowing your mind, babe.
I'm not.
You know this.
And really what this is gonna come down to is a simple fact.
We all want slack.
We all want to get off.
And we all want to get off of this planet.
Can I get off?
Can I get a praise, Bob?
Praise Bob!
I can't hear you, motherfuckers.
Can I get a praise, Bob?
Praise Bob!
Hallelujah.
Hey.
Sometimes you feel the spirit just sort of moving you.
And then you realize, well, you know, maybe you just drank too much.
John.
Motherfucker John.
Look at the children dancing.
It's time.
Motherfucker, die.
Just stop breathing.
Close your eyes!
It's time.
Motherfucker, it's time.
Motherfucker, motherfucker, motherfucker, motherfucker, die.
Motherfucker, motherfucker, die.
It's time.
I love song for all the subgeniuses
With the eminence of the world
Die, die, die
Motherfucker die
Boys and girls, I know there's a couple other ones out there.
In fact, I see one right now.
And let me, you know, give you a proper introduction.
Yeah, I can't get mine out of this fucking corset, I'm sorry.
This is, you're fairly new.
This is a first sex date, first time up here.
This is Admiral Tit.
Admiral Tit.
And you have something you'd like to share.
Thank you.
I have a lot of things that I'd like to share.
Share your tits!
I'm shy of cameras, I'm sorry.
Catch me later.
I'll be here all week.
I've seen some of the most impressive drinking I have ever seen.
And my family is full of alcoholics.
So that's saying something.
Fuck yeah!
Yeah!
So I have a little song I'm going to teach you.
You are going to help me sing it.
And it doesn't matter how fucked up you are, because I'm pretty fucked up right now.
Yeah!
So if I can remember the words, you can learn them.
Now, who here remembers that glorious movie, The Sound of Music?
Yeah!
Yeah, Maria!
Who here knows their ABCs?
I do!
Okay.
So what we're going to do is we're going to practice a line, and then we're going to go into the real song, okay?
You'll know the first one.
Let's begin at the very beginning.
Come on, you drunk motherfuckers, you can do this.
It's a very good place to start.
When you read, you begin with A, B, C.
When you drink, you begin with beer, wine, mead.
Beer, wine, mead.
Scrunch, rum, gin, rye, beer.
You drunk motherfuckers, I love you.
Okay, here's how it's going to go.
I'm going to sing it, and then you guys are going to help me, and we're going to sing it a second time.
And then you're going to go home and offend friends with all kinds of wonderful stories from here.
Ready?
Let's begin at the very beginning.
It's a very good place to start.
When you read, you begin with A, B, C.
When you drink, you begin with beer, wine, mead.
Beer, wine, mead.
Scrunch, rum, gin, rye, beer.
Fucking cotton mouth.
Okay.
Thank you.
Crazy end of the month.
Praise Bob!
Beer is good and from a keg.
Wine is tasty from a box.
Meat is smooth and really sweet.
Scotch is best when on the rocks.
Gin, you mix it with some juice.
Rum, it fills you with good cheer.
Cheers!
Rye, it makes you very loose.
And that brings us back to beer, beer, beer.
Beer, beer, beer.
Beer is good and from a keg.
Wine is tasty from a box.
Meat is smooth and really sweet.
Scotch is best when on the rocks.
Gin, you mix it with some juice.
Rum, it fills you with good cheer.
Juice, rum, it fills you with good cheer.
Rye, it makes you very loose.
And that brings us back to beer, beer, beer.
Beer, beer, beer.
You guys rock!
Now we're getting the hang of it.
Hell yes!
Woo!
Starting to get a little mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm.
Hello my brothers and sisters in Slack.
Praise Bob!
I am the Reverend Dr. Priestess Princess Popus Pocket.
And I'm here to talk to you about a few things tonight.
There's one thing I really want to talk about.
And that is the end of the motherfucking world tomorrow!
Praise Bob!
Are you ready for the end of the motherfucking world tomorrow?
You paid your $30, and with that $30, you got two things.
You got the pleasure saucers.
And you got luck.
You got luck.
The luck plane.
I am not going to rant at you. I am going to preach at you tonight.
You people that are here tonight,
You are the luckiest
Yeti mutants on the face of the earth.
Praise Bob!
You know there's all this speculation
and bullshit. Oh, you pay your $30
and you're getting on that pleasure saucer.
I'm sorry.
Unless you are in a Dobbs approved location,
odds are, you're not getting on that saucer.
The X's, they ain't no bus stop.
They're not going to go house to house to come get you to go to space.
You lucky fuckers, you are here
and you're going on the saucers.
Praise Bob!
Can I get one more?
Tomorrow marks the end of all the bullshit.
We burn our hate.
It marks the end of all bad drivers.
The end of fucking Walmart.
The end of the fucking world.
Praise Bob!
And it all comes back to luck
in your $30.
And it's going to be a short rant tonight.
I do apologize.
But my luck has kind of turned and I think my throat
is going to fall out of my mouth.
So praise Bob!
Hail to luck plane!
And see you on the fucking pleasure ships!
Praise Bob!
Follow me on Twitter at
enquiries.
katarickme
Dagning
Way
Push your car
I ain't very happy I broke in the way that he broke
You're a stain on the carpet
Your mom, your dad
Your dad should have pulled out early
I'm talking with Bonanza
Eating a banana
Slip on a peel
Choking on a pit
Alright, I'm going to test you a little bit of a rate
I don't know if you'll be able to hear me or not
But I got this thing that's about bad drivers
And the fact that they don't know how to drive
And they don't use their fucking signals nearly enough
You know, you don't get taxed on that
You don't have to pay extra for your car
To use that little thing there on the side
That tells you which way
Tells me which way you're going to go back and forth
So use the fucking signal
We're not mind ringers
We like to drive
I told people that are driving
Don't have brains in their fucking heads anyway
Since I'm talking about brains and all the whole zombie thing
Zombies really don't want to eat your brains!
See, when you go to the supermarket
You don't just buy coconut
You buy coconut and it's already shredded up
Because it takes a lot of fucking work to get inside there
To get it out of life
Brain mass is on your melody
The zombie's going to eat you no matter what
It's not going to come from your brain
It's going to come from your arm or whatever
You dumb shit stick in their face
Oh, and all the guys from Rare
The big guys like
Like Jack O'Lantern
Like Kloss
They don't have to worry much
Because there's a lot of stuff to get through
To get to all the vital stuff underneath
So these fat guys are pretty much safe
They can walk through the zombie apocalypse unscathed
Unless of course they stick their hand where it shouldn't be
Don't try to be a hero
Just stay in your house and keep eating Oreos, you fuck
Oh yeah, and there's that Bob guy
Bob exists because he touches me in an inappropriate manner
Alright, not to sound all pussy and shit
But I love coming back to it every fucking year
Because you guys are family of mine
And I know that might sound gay or whatever
But fuck off
And this is the end of the show
And that's Dr. Music
And that's Philo Drummond
Look at those bands
Whistleys
Fuck yeah
We won't have bear or wolf age
We will be back
Look at Sudge go
Rip it up Sudge
I am Priestess Enshrina
Hello, hello
Alright
I came up here to tell you the good news
it's very good news
I think most of the
uberfems know but the
overmen
whatever they want to call themselves
don't know this because
they are not part
of Connie's cunt gang
I just want to let you know that
Bob is not dead
you know why Bob
isn't dead? He never
existed in the first place
no no
he was created
he was created by Connie
in order to succeed in this
fucking patriarchal bullshit
world
that's right
no
because as uberfems we're not a
fucking auxiliary
of subgenius okay
we're not a separate
sect we're not helpers
we are the church
we simply allow
the men to be here
because we understand without the men
we cannot succeed in the patriarchal
society in which we live
because of the fucking
peaks
so
this church
Bob is simply a
symbol for Connie's cunt
that's all
priestess and
Shrina from the ministry of
slack radio show
before that reverend angry Larry's
angry rant with many fisted tales
of Connie true old school
doctor music from Sunday
night at 13 next day
before that reverend pockets and
admiral tits
this is the hour of slack
internet-only triple xx day special
from the church of the subgenius
and anything you want to know about any
of this is only a few clicks into
subgenius.com coming up a subgenius
blues song by reverend panic but first
the climax of die motherfucker die that
lovely duet between priestess Pisces and
DJ Shaver
you're listening to the subgenius blues song by reverend panic but first the climax of die motherfucker die that lovely duet between priestess Pisces and DJ Shaver
die motherfucker die
die
why won't you die
we've tried everything
we want you to die
so fucking bad
listen motherfucker
why are you fucking my mother
what did she ever do
you must die
right fucking now
you must die right fucking now
there isn't a question about it ladies and gentlemen
die
it is time for you to die
we are going to
die
celebrate
perfect
dying
Die, you motherfuckin' die
Die, you meinem pumping die
DIE!
Motherfucker, die assistant
Die, you around here
I want to smell your flesh burning
from the laser beams of the X-Men saucers.
Oh, my goodness gracious, why don't you die?
Scream in the mind and pain as you are molecularly just a symbol.
You must die.
You must be extinguished.
We must snuff out your existence,
your pathetic, weak, wretched, disgusting, despicable, horrific, impinged,
sex-pathetic, horrific,
life must be extinguished.
The Pinks must die!
Die!
Die, die, die!
Die, die!
Die!
Hello.
I'm Reverend Panic, and I'm mostly up here to sing a song that I have,
and it's very important to me.
But the thing that made me right, it was there was a little thing in the back of my head
that was always telling me shit I didn't want to hear.
Always like, oh, why are you doing that, Joel?
Why are you fucking doing that?
No, I didn't want to fucking hear any of that anymore.
I didn't want to.
But you know what it was?
I realized what it was.
It was a part of me that was telling me what parts of me I should hate.
It's the parts that were pink.
It's the parts inside of me that were pink.
I hate the pink thing.
What pink thing?
I skinned that and made boots out of it.
That's what these are.
I wear it here on my finger.
That's the last little bit spit out right there.
I have it under my power now.
It's all because my guardian angel fueled by hate.
I need to act like a rock star for a second, even though I'm going to sing in a man's voice.
Okay.
Because I need to feel sexy.
Because my dream is to be a girl rock star, but, you know, that didn't quite work out.
I got balloons.
Don't let everybody see it.
My baby doesn't let me now feel with hate.
Poisoned by rage, I'm staying up real late.
But now I got a baby who changed my look.
I got a guardian angel.
Won't give a fuck.
My guardian angel's fueled by hate.
When I get low, she shows me the way.
Down that path of least resistance saves me from the starkest vision.
Oh, I'd rather be lucky than good any day.
So long as I hate those who get involved.
I'm on my way.
I have a winged chicken with drink in her hand.
Chain smoking, cutie withering, and one grand yell.
Bleeding that good, he'll have that.
So don't you worry about your net or life.
To worry about it will just bring strife.
You fight the kind, go on attack.
Oh, I got balloons.
I said praise Bob.
Find your slack.
Whoa.
My guardian angel fueled by hate.
Yeah.
My guardian angel, she fueled by hate.
You're a sweetheart.
Thank you.