Bob!
Dobbs!
Bob?
Oh, hello, Dobbs. What is it?
Well, it's probably not...
The subgenius power of Slack!
My God!
Okay, that was that hour.
Now we start...
No, no.
Well, soon. In a couple of...
25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30.
I have to do another minute of this when I'm done.
Radio or not, here I come!
Radio or not.
This is giving us fade-out time.
Oh, God.
I know the answer to that one.
Radio or not.
No soap.
We need to work on this radio you can smell.
Oh, no, no, no.
Have you heard radio recently?
Aside from WREK?
I can proudly say I haven't.
Oh, my good...
I haven't even heard WCSB outside of WREK.
I was quite tickled to find out that the second-string right-wing station in town has gone all Spanish-language.
Sports!
Oh, what juicy butthurt.
Oh, the shot in the right eye.
They're going to be Shelly Dankerting all over Atlanta.
Oh, they're a bunch of guys out looking for a job now.
I'm unemployed.
I can laugh at them.
Holding sides outside of the John Birch Society waiting for pickups to come by with microphones.
That was Alex Jones coming by with the microphone in the pickup.
That's how he started out.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, he'd drive around with a PA and yelling at us for pickup.
Oh, yeah, yeah, waking life.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
We are officially an hour or two, ladies and gentlemen.
Yes, now here we are.
The program you're about to hear, Bob's Slack Time Funhouse, is parody, satire, and comedy.
Any reference to Bob, the Church of the Subgenius, religion, politics, or any other touchy subject
is intended only as humor and should cast no reflection on the high standards of WREK Atlanta,
its staff, or that of Georgia Tech.
Wow, you've got another take of it now.
After all those years.
And you say it so much slower in person.
I've been tweaking it up higher and cram more content.
We're very content-heavy emphasis here.
Content is king.
Yeah.
Boy, the subgenius shows have been on a long time.
Puzzling evidence started in 1980 and two.
I was 12.
Wow.
I've been a subgenius for one year.
I was a father already.
Oh, wow.
You, wow, there is a resemblance.
Oh?
Papa?
Sean!
It's like Popeye finding his pappy, and he hates him.
Riverdiving trucks.
Oh.
It has a ring to it.
I van trucks.
It all fits.
Yeah.
Oh, no.
His middle name's Carr.
Yeah.
I van car and trucks.
That's terrible.
I'm sorry.
Oh, there's going to be another hour of that sort of material.
Oh, man.
It's comedy gold.
Well, in the previous hour.
Oh, that's just corn in it.
That was fool's gold.
Yes, it is.
Circling.
The previous hour of fool's gold, we managed to play two cuts by other people, but they
were really long and bad.
And I bet there's more long and bad things besides live radio that we can do.
I'll bet there are.
Oh, I brought long and bad with me tonight.
Hi.
How's it going?
You've got your
bad goes to the crazy.
Bad and long.
Bad.
Yeah.
That sounds like a drive time DJ team.
So come here often?
Your shirt says, kill legume.
Yeah.
That's a legume fan club shirt.
That's the way his fans feel about it.
Think how his enemies feel.
They're like, don't kill him yet
Don't kill him
Hold him down
Too easy
Don't kill him before we get to him
We've been going through the country
Stopping in unexpectedly on the homes of subgeniuses
And grading them
According to their level of weirdness versus pinkness
I was lucky, I had an hour's notice
Well, you've done pretty well so far
Hey Susie, we're here
Susie cleaned up the floozeum for us
Yeah, it's more than just paths
Actually, if you Google floozeum
And if you can guess how to spell it right
You'll be looking at pictures of
And it is a museum
Oh, thanks, absolutely
It's an incredible museum
Thanks for feeding my legion of stalkers
Well, you had those already
Yeah, true
And we're gonna, we'll make even
Wish they'd do me some good
Yeah
I know how you feel
Why can't we get the, you know, the productive stalkers
Yeah
At least get you in the newspaper
Get you some PR
What would I do with
No, I'm not going to go there
No, let's not
Whatever it was
I have no idea what it is
But let's not
Suddenly higher brain function and judgment kicked in
That's not a good sign
Here, drink this, it'll help
Oh, no
This old church
But yeah, Hour of Slack started in 1985
On Halloween, pretty much
And when did it, Bob's Slack Time Funhouse start?
January 1st, 1994
1994, well, that was just yesterday
So, yeah, yeah
Just 18 years, my damn show could vote
Oh, wow
It's all kind of relative
I was trying to talk my show into not, you know, being a fan of the show
I was not voting and I wasn't going to vote
No, actually, it's not relative
And it sneaked out and voted
They'll do that
Yeah, can't trust it, don't
No
Turn your back for one minute and the show's out the door
Yep
I wish
Man
Don't we have a pre-recorded show where we can just put it on and rock it
What do they do at KPFA, the Puzzling Evidence Show?
They really do
Just put on a tape of
Yeah
It's a years old show
And go out on the balcony and take a break for a while
People call in
Princess, we called in, in fact
And talked to a tape recording for about half an hour
Joined the conversation that had previously existed
And you couldn't really tell
You know, that's the funny thing
Well, it was that kind of recording
She knew that it was a recording
Recycled reality
She was playing along with it
Performing, sorry
Sure
Yeah
I mean, but I think
She
She called in
And Wellman picked up the phone and said hello
And put her on the air
But then he put on a tape
And went out
But the recording was full of people saying
Hello
So it was
Quite fun to play along with
It was your show at that point
Yes
Pretty much
I had the whole Puzzling Evidence Show
All to myself
While I shivered out in the car
Yeah
Yeah, she couldn't call from inside the house
Because it's like three in the morning
And all of her relatives
Were sleeping in there
So she had to go out to the car and call
But it was bitter cold
And yeah, she was
You were on all over Northern California
Talking to an old recorder
These things happen
Yes, they do
And friends, that's what's happening now
We're all just talking to old recordings of each other
Shivering outside in the car
Loops
And it's so random
That it appears to be
It could all be happening at once
But really, every sentence was recorded years apart
At least we aren't using
An all-computer generated show
Like Dr. Howell uses
Skillfully spliced together
Yes, you can hear the razor cuts
And the splices
If you listen very carefully
Like right there
Right
Very carefully
This show is printed on paper
I like it that way
When you hear the
The clumsy little edits
The hiss changes
The dub
The dub wing hat
Sewing machine
Where's the bobbing head
Talking old grain in a printed sack
I love you, Pappy
The dust blows forward
And the dust blows back
And the wind blows
Black through the sky
And the smokestack blows up
In the sun's eye
When am I gonna die
A white flake riverboat
Just flew by
Bubbles pop big
And the sun's eye
And a lipstick Kleenex hung on a pointed four-kid twig.
Reminds me of the Bobby Girls.
Never was my hobby girls.
Handful of worms and a pole fishing.
Cork bobbing like a hot red bulb.
And a blue jay squeaks.
His beak open an inch above the creek.
Gone fishing for a week.
Well, I put down my pole.
And I took off my pants and felt free.
The breeze blowing up me.
And up the canyon.
As far as I could see.
It's night now and the moon looks like a dandelion.
It's black now and the blackbird's sitting on rice.
And his red wings look like diamonds and lice.
I can hear the mice toes scampering.
Go for a walk.
Birds rumbling.
In pile crater rock holes.
One red bean stuck in the bottom of a tin bowl.
Hot coffee from a crimped up can.
Me and my girl named Bimbo.
Limbo.
Spam.
Thank you.
Captain Beefheart.
Yes.
A poem done completely from memory.
By two memories.
That's about all they came to.
Including the little skips in the record.
Yes.
That are mixed in.
Well, you know, the way that that song was recorded is that
that was the way during the recording of Trot Mask Replica
that all of the lyrics were done is he would walk around
with a little portable tape deck.
And he would sing the lyrics into it and get as far as he could
in one take and then pause it.
Oh, is that what it is?
And then he would unpause it and sing some more and pause it.
So it's a pause cut.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, OK.
So since we're on a new hour, I guess we should go down the line
and introduce ourselves.
Oh.
Are we the same people we were when we started?
I'm Uncle Onan Canabite.
Here's Reverend Velveteen Sly with me.
You can call me Velvet for short.
Yeah.
I'm Dr. Hell.
And I am Brother Xavier Onassis.
Xavier Onassis.
Well, that was all mixed.
I think we'll do that.
Oh, Xavier.
My charming wife, Mia Culpa, to my left.
Yeah, Uncle Onan Canabite can do that song,
that Captain Beefheart thing.
I can do that whole damn album.
Yeah, I probably could, too.
I do.
It was an influential thing.
It was a long time ago, kids.
Yes.
Trout Mask Replica by Captain Beefheart.
That was where many of us went, oh, my God, I'm not alone.
Well, I am alone, but there's something almost as weird as me
or weirder in that.
In the case of Captain Beefheart, he was a very, very weird man.
I didn't know much about his real life until after he died.
Then people started talking about what a jerk he was.
Yeah.
He was a very controlling, domineering band leader.
You would not want to have been in one of his bands.
He made some glorious music, but he was a very insecure human being.
Yeah, great albums.
But at what cost?
Yeah.
Which actually reminds me of my newest musical predilection.
I've recently been introduced to the music of the Shags.
They are pure.
Yes.
They are.
Very pure.
Their father is very much a Captain Beefheart figure.
Whatever happened to the Shags?
I mean, that was years and years ago that they had their brief moment in the spotlight.
They did.
And they reformed ever so briefly at the bequest of NRBQ singer.
No, it was the drummer, Tom Ardolino.
Ardolino.
Yeah.
He was on the song poem.
And yes, at the time,
the original drummer, Helen, Helen?
Helen.
Had passed away.
So Tom actually played with Dot and I can't remember the other girl's name.
So it was NRBQ's drummer with the two original Shags guitarists.
And they opened for NRBQ for an entire tour back in 93.
Wow.
Yeah.
I wish I could have heard of that.
But I only just now in the last month or so discovered their music.
Goodness.
Yes.
I remember one of those moments of, I love this and everyone hates it.
Well, it is terrible.
It is.
The Shags were.
It sounded as still.
It was a couple of, was it what?
Three sisters?
Three sisters.
Wigan family.
Yeah.
Their dad thought they were good and he paid to have a record made of them.
They were actually really, really terrible.
Yes.
But they were so terrible that they became the darlings of the snarky underground all
through the 80s.
The story goes that their father.
It's heartfelt.
Yeah.
Their father received a palm reading from his mother and was told that his daughters
would be the biggest girl group of all time.
So when they were still in school, like ages 11 through 14, he pulled them out of school.
And while he worked all day, their job was to rehearse and write songs.
And when he thought they were good enough, he brought them into your New York to record
an album.
Yeah.
He was like Murray Wilson.
Now, this father was also very strict.
He didn't let the daughters listen to any music or go to any dances.
So any influence that you hear in their music is purely coincidental.
They made all of it up.
They had no idea what music was, how it was formed.
They never had any lessons.
Their father just bought them instruments and said, go.
Their most famous song is about their dog, isn't it?
Foot Foot.
My pal Foot Foot.
Yes.
Wow.
Well, it's nice to see.
And the shags are still inspiring people to new depths.
Well, yeah, that's the roots of doctor music.
Yeah, they were a true doctor band.
It was like they didn't care about the audience.
They were doing it.
Well, actually, they had.
They were doing it for their dad.
That's that's new.
Most doctor bands aren't doing it for their dads or they're doing it.
They're doing them in spite of their dad.
Right.
In spite of their dad.
Yeah.
Yes.
On their up there in there.
Yeah.
Through their dad.
All the prepositions you can think of.
Actually, I never even bothered to tell Pappy about any of the bands that I was in.
But then I wouldn't want anyone to hear any of those anymore.
Oh, we used to sell tapes of Doctors for Wotan.
That was the band that Philo and I.
It was a copy band.
We were copying Doctors for Bob.
They were much more.
Doctors for Bob of Little Rock were much more conceptual.
You were like the Doctors for Bob tribute band.
Yeah.
They were.
They were way more pure.
I mean, our our band, we none of us knew how to play anything and we use children's instruments.
So that was that was that.
But Doctors for Bob, for instance, they did a song called Subgenius Alphabet.
And a I think was a drawer full of silverware being pulled out and crashing on the floor.
B was a pickup truck driving around town in circles.
Spike Jones.
Yeah.
Oh, they were way.
It was more like Christo or Andy Warhol.
You know, see, and this was these are this is a song that in fact,
Sternow put an ad in the Little Rock paper for a drummer and a guy showed up and said,
Oh, OK, what do you what do you guys play?
What do you want to hear?
And Sternow goes, OK, well, for for our first song, you're going to get a pickup and drive
over across town and and roll the pickup down into the river and then come back.
That's the first song.
Yeah.
I think the guy felt that he was being made fun of and went away.
And I'm not sure to this day if he was being made fun of or not.
They were headed.
They were so avant garde.
Doctors for Bob were that to this day, the world hasn't caught up to them and they still sound horrible.
No, actually, that's not true.
They they like so many doctor bands.
They eventually learned.
They learned how to play.
And in fact, Sternow is a killer bass player and he's learned.
He now plays sax and Doctors for Bob finally ended up doing a whole album of real songs.
But then Janer went Janer and we can't do anything with with.
There are none more Jane.
No, he was Janer than thou.
You might say, but he's he's Mr. TV now.
Mr. TV.
Wow.
Well, he.
He's a sidewalk busker.
The former subgenius superstar, Janer Hyperclete.
Well, the band broke up with him one by one and then reality broke up with him.
But the sidewalks embraced him.
And and he does.
He puts a TV, a hollow television on his head and does takeoffs on TV shows using like little.
If he's doing takeoff on a cop car.
He puts a little toy cop car up against the edge of the TV and moves it around and does sound effects and so forth.
It's a police squad.
The first time you see it, it's it's probably funny.
You can YouTube it.
YouTube Mr. TV and you'll be seeing the new Janer.
Boy, my ears.
Either my ears just popped or the volume increased or I touched the.
Your ears.
I mean, touch your.
No.
Hey, stop that.
Move.
Stop that.
Your knob like.
I'm going to touch it.
Have more.
How embarrassing.
That really is not on the Monster Hunter.
Have you no shame?
No.
There it goes.
Easy come, easy go.
I think having no taste pays off better than having no shame.
But if you can do that, both.
There was taste in my family, but it skipped a generation.
My son inexplicably has taste and I know he didn't get it from his mom.
What does it taste like?
Good.
What's this flavor?
It's a good taste.
This is starting to bother me.
I'm uncomfortable now.
Oh, velvet.
How could you?
Is that a Mad Magazine quote?
You know.
Anything with a word.
The word Melvin, the name Melvin in it, I instantly think of old Mad Magazine.
At this point, I think everything is an old Mad Magazine quote.
They've written enough that I think that any string of words can be found in Mad if you look hard enough.
Yeah.
Yeah, probably so.
And now they've all been scanned so you can do a search.
What? Me?
Google?
Maybe we should play something from that horrible.
Horrible album.
Which horrible album?
You brought buckets of horrible albums.
Yeah.
When Susie, Susie the floozy has.
I've got a few bad records.
She has entire rooms of horrible albums.
Yeah, basements full of horrible albums.
My bad record is going to follow me along.
Yeah, she has a bad record that follows her, she says.
She worked hard on that.
Which bad one is this?
Developing that bad record.
The one of the martyrs things.
Oh, are we back to the world?
World War II.
Worlds of youth.
Yeah.
More worlds of youth martyrdom?
Picture is the nasty picture.
The nasty picture.
That sounds pretty nice.
Ah.
This is two middle-aged fellows in the 50s communicating with today's youth.
Feels good.
Yeah, on the previous hour show, we had an ex, but the inter...
The entirety of cut four and side two, the martyr.
It was pompous and sophomoric and yet...
He said pompously.
Be pompous, obese and eat cactus.
Be dull and boring and omnipresent.
Criticize things you don't know about.
Be oblong and have your knees removed.
What is that from?
That is Steve Martin from Let's Get Small.
That's the grandmother song.
No wonder.
It seemed like something so buried so deep under so many layers and...
It's like the Grand Canyon of my mind.
Featuring Ted Nugent on guitar.
Yeah.
Man.
It's...
So we're about to hear the horror.
Yes.
Worlds of youth.
Pictures, the nasty pictures.
They smell so bad.
I see you're looking at that picture.
I'm cutting it out.
Do you know what you're doing?
Sure, I'm cutting it out.
I mean, what you're really doing.
What do the people think?
People like who?
People like anybody.
Well, let's start with you.
What do you think?
I think it's a controversial picture.
I think it's a dirty picture.
A real dirty picture.
It depends on how you look at it.
One of the dirtiest pictures I ever saw.
And you're saving it.
I'm displaying it.
I'm displaying it in front of my bed.
best friend this controversial, dirty, filthy picture.
Like how?
I'm mounting it and presenting it to the council.
The student council.
The church council.
That dirty picture?
That dirty picture to the men and women of this congregation.
And then to the whole congregation.
What for?
For Lent.
For the council for Lent.
You're kidding.
We won't take it down.
When they see it, no one will take it down.
No one.
That dirty picture will hang out there in front of the people.
The women and the children and the youth.
What's the matter with you?
Are you some kind of pervert?
Some kind of maniac?
No one will take it down.
They will look at it for weeks and weeks.
While they sit and sing and stand to pray.
They'll see it while he preaches.
You've got your nerve.
Everyone's got their nerve.
The man has to have his nerve.
This nerve.
To look at the two of them.
And him hanging there.
Naked between them.
It's a dirty shame.
A dirty, dirty, rotten picture.
Jesus did not escape sin.
He was no playboy, no superman.
No middle of the road politician.
Jesus lived and lives in the middle of everything.
He was born of a woman and came to pay all the consequences.
People lied about him.
Gave him false trials.
Hunted him like a criminal.
Tricked him.
And eventually they got him.
His life was under every strife.
Every segregation.
And he endured every form of sin in slow motion.
In Jesus we have the prediction of how it would all end.
How it would always be on the earth.
Like hell.
Hell on earth.
In Jesus we have the promise of what it could be among men.
Like heaven.
Heaven on earth.
The dirtiest and most disappointing picture in the world
is the picture of the son of man suffering and dying.
The picture is continually reprinted in all the black and white pictures of suffering and dying.
In the south.
And the north.
And anywhere.
There are many, many pictures.
Dirty and inhuman in every newspaper.
They need to be hung on the walls of the chancels.
So that all church councils can see them.
And so that congregations can do something about dirty pictures like that.
As vicious as pornography.
Oh, good heavens.
Someone get her some oxygen.
I always knew religion was pornographic.
But now you've got proof there.
Dirty.
Dirty pictures.
Sausage is not without sin.
No.
Yes, that was from an album called Worlds of Youth.
My goodness.
Jeez.
Sausage did not escape sin.
That is some of the most warped Christian themed stuff from the late 60s
when they were going for relevance.
The guy on the left here.
Herbert Brokering.
He looks a bit like Leo Laporte from the Twit Network.
If any of you know him.
The guy on the right here.
Man, he almost looks like Billy Graham.
Yeah.
This John Ridgegrain guy.
Yeah, he has sort of a bobbly.
The highlights on his hair though.
It's getting.
Yeah.
Very Grahamian.
Downright Dobbsian.
Dobbsian.
The Dobbs Graham bill.
I cannot figure out for the life of me what audience they were going for on this thing.
Just think at some point, sometime in history, those two were in a studio and it was the most important thing in that engineer's life to make these two gentlemen sound exactly the way they just sounded.
That was someone's job.
You started lilting.
Can we try it again in a monotone?
Their mission.
Their goal.
Exactly.
Mounting the dirty picture.
Their highest aspiration.
Get more Barry White on the show.
You could have made a lot of money right into that, could you?
Their highest aspiration.
Yes, yes.
Much better.
That studio must have been full of snakes.
There you go.
My voice doesn't Barry White very well.
No, it doesn't.
But that's okay.
The rest of you does just fine.
Oh no, he's letting Stang in.
Stang.
Oh no.
He's in the neighborhood.
It's a beautiful day in the neighborhood.
Here he's putting on his cardigan and his slippers.
Reverend Stang, exactly.
There's no need to change your shoes and put on a cardigan, man.
Just come on in and sit down.
Really?
No smoking jacket needed.
No, no smoking jacket needed.
Put the jacket out, man.
So?
What was that about?
Oh, you missed it.
You missed the filthy pictures.
Hey, no spoilers, man.
Oh, you missed it.
Oh, man.
You missed it.
It was smut.
Oh my God.
I'm still missing it.
The ghost of Luther King.
Luther Vandross inhabited the second speaker's body and all of a sudden-
The lower chakras were thrumming.
Exactly.
His voice was somewhere in the 32 hertz range.
It proved Christianity equals pornography.
Boy, I did miss it.
Yeah.
You'll never hear it again.
Damn.
You know, the subgenius A.I.
Zeppo, he occasionally utters these heavy statements.
And one of his best quotes is,
thought is pornography.
For most of us, that's true.
Yeah.
Out of the mouths of robots.
I thought he was real for so long.
Another thing, Zeppo.
Yeah.
You can have conversation.
I thought that's somebody I'd really get along with.
If you get on the, it's one of the more friendly people on the subgenius IRC chat network.
If you go to subgenius.com.
You can get into a pretty abusive little chat room.
Uh-huh.
And of, on which the most friendly person is Zeppo, who is in fact an A.I.
Robot.
But you wouldn't know it for a long time.
Slack will get you through times of no Slack.
Right.
That was Zeppo's great Bob.
He channeled Bob and said Slack will get you through times of no Slack.
Only a robot could come up with something or Bob himself would be capable of something
that was so inherently contradictory.
Is it possible that it is the actual Zeppo?
The Marx Brothers straight man?
The fourth Marx Brother?
Is it possible Bob is a robot?
I heard that.
That was a song.
Robob.
Bob is a robot.
There was a song by that name.
Oh.
By some band.
But I don't know.
I don't know about these bands.
I'm quite sure Voltron would have defeated him by now if that was the case.
More than meets the eye.
Autobots.
Decepticons.
I can't remember the...
You know, those Transformer movies were shamefully abusive of the original story, but I understand
that the Transformers video games are absolutely cleaved to the original Transformers TV show.
Well, good.
Given that that is the Bible, the true Bible of the Transformers was the cartoon.
How can you expect to improve on that?
Have you seen the most recent Transformers movie, Dark of the Moon?
Yeah, I did.
It made me angry beginning to end.
They had this Michael Bay character somehow arranged it so that on film they go to the
moon and they have this guy, Buzz Aldrin, to come on screen and talk about how the moon
landing was a government cover-up, number one.
Right.
Number two, they had a space shuttle explode in the course of the movie.
Too soon.
Number three, they got...
Those things do that.
They got Leonard Nimoy to say the goods of the many outweigh the goods of the one or
the few in the course of trying to blow up the Earth.
That was...
Yeah.
There's no Iron Sky.
That's for sure.
Oh.
Iron Sky.
Yeah.
Listener, if you're not familiar with the movie called Iron Sky...
You know I just have one.
You can certainly get offended by checking out the movie, Iron Sky.
Nazis on the Moon.
It's in a nutshell.
Oh, with President Sarah Palin.
Yes.
President Sarah Palin versus Nazis on the Moon.
The moon reef installed.
And it was produced and directed by people in Finland.
Mm-hmm.
And it was working with Australians and financed by the internet.
Yes.
Yeah.
It's an amazing movie with gorgeous, wonderful special effects.
Mm-hmm.
Slightly awkward racial...
Very awkward.
Yeah.
It's...
You can...
It's kind of...
It reminds me of 1970s race movies in the US.
It's a little bit...
The Nazis weren't PC?
The astronaut that gets...
The astronaut that gets stranded on the dark side of the moon and captured by the Nazis
happens to be black and they turn him white and send him back to Earth where he becomes
a hobo.
Yeah.
It's like water...
Great.
That's sometimes...
Of course.
And he said to the Nazis, like, okay, this ghost ship is ours.
This was old.
osa.
There's a HahYouN tweet.
Ooh.
There you go.
And he just says...
I don't know that he has a ho
in the future, hence the 25th Reich.
And in the future, they've put their minds
into giant robot spider Nazis.
And even the protagonist is a,
it's kind of subtly done actually,
but the protagonist is a gay dude.
A Reichsniess.
And although it has a happy ending,
just the arg moment, the big climactic arg moment,
he gets sodomized by the giant Nazi robot spider.
This is all on screen.
It's tastefully done, though.
I'd pay good money to see that.
That's the most bizarre thing,
is that what I just described
is actually almost sort of tastefully done.
The camera averts, you know,
the sensitive viewer is not...
I'm sorry, you have to see the sodomy.
Well, yeah, so that's the subgenius movie review, friends.
It's tasteful robot sodomy.
Iron Sky and the 25th Reich.
There's all sorts of...
Also, a Nazis at the Center of the Earth movie.
I can't remember the title of that one,
and it's not very good.
They're Nazis like the new zombies.
Oh, they're in Antarctica,
and it's all done on a white set.
It's just they got a white psych,
and that's Antarctica.
Everything's white.
Well, yeah.
And it has CGI that appears to have been done
on the old program Bryce.
It has that look to it.
It's about as good as I could do,
which is not very good of CGI on my old, old Mac.
Not as old as me.
I think probably, though,
the best bad film I've seen recently is Birdemic,
shock and horror.
Have you seen this?
Shock and terror.
Excuse me.
Birdemic?
Birdemic.
Yes.
It's almost kind of like a redo,
of Hitchcock's The Birds,
but with an ecological bent to it.
But the special effects are ridiculous.
You have, you know,
the way you know that the birds are attacking
is that in the extreme foreground,
there are three CGI birds hovering,
flapping their wings,
not moving at all,
while the actors swat their hands in front of their faces
and try and fend off these birds.
Yes.
I can just see the director,
we're going to add the birds with CGI.
Yeah.
And then at some point,
the CGI dude goes,
wait a minute,
we can't release this in a week.
I think it's going to take me five weeks
just to render one shot on this little computer of mine,
my home computer.
Well, we'll use it anyway.
My cousin just bought a copy of Raster Man.
He'll do it.
Yeah.
Let's use the test.
You know,
when War of the Worlds,
the Spielberg War of the Worlds,
came out,
there were two rip-off War of the Worlds
that managed to get released just before the Spielberg one,
so that Pobuckers entering Walmart would go,
whoa,
there's that War of the Worlds movie.
This doesn't have Tom Cruise in it.
One of them is,
word for word,
the entire H.G. Wells novel,
and it's four hours long.
Cool.
It's so low budget
that they didn't even have
real horses,
and they used horses from that program Poser.
The crowd scenes are done by the same ten actors
in the different costumes,
blue-screened over each other,
against a, like,
generic brick wall,
and that's London being attacked by the,
and yet,
the funny thing is,
it shows you what happens
if you try to literally make a novel into a movie.
You end up with a really boring four-hour movie
with a guy stumbling through the woods
for ten minutes at a stretch
while somebody reads H.G. Wells' prose.
Right.
I mean,
I read the War of the Worlds every two years
out of sort of a religious thing.
Sure.
They made you.
I understand.
Yeah, science, you know,
it was the first sci-fi book I ever read
because it's a time machine,
then War of the Worlds.
Right, and as soon as you memorize,
it's a time machine.
You have to burn it,
and then that will be,
you will be War of the Worlds
from that point forward.
Yes, I understand.
Actually, I'm probably more the time machine
and island of Dr. Moreau.
War of the Worlds is a little long
for me to remember.
Oh, well.
But, yeah,
there was yet another,
like a made-for-TV type of War of the Worlds
that they obviously rushed out
to get out before Spielberg
because the CGI is,
isn't even CGI.
It's more like production drawings
that they cut to.
And you only two or three of those.
So you hardly ever see
the Martian war machines that are,
and it's updated to modern times.
The four-hour version
was done as a period piece.
And with, you know,
like dinner theater,
Victorian or Edwardian British clothing,
all shot in,
they probably shot it in,
what's that?
Town in New Jersey
that HG Wells,
that Orson Welles used.
Ah, Grover's Mill.
Yeah, Grover's Mill.
Yeah.
That's probably where they really shot it.
So.
By accident.
Jersey dinner theater,
people trying to do British accents.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, it's,
it's unwatchable,
but you can't miss it.
The guy did come back
and re-release a shortened version of it,
which I,
I don't care about.
It's,
it's best to see the uncut,
horrible four-hour mess.
They managed to pack it all into one DVD.
If you're gonna,
if you're gonna commit to the Ring of the Nebulon,
you gotta stay for the whole 12 hours.
Yeah.
It's unbelievable.
You know,
was Eric von Strohan did Greed, right?
I don't know.
A silent movie
based on McTeague,
the novel.
And it was,
it was originally nine hours long.
That fabulous print is lost forever,
but they managed to reconstruct
a four and a half hour version of it.
Well,
you do know that before Dino De Laurentiis
got his fingers on,
on Dune,
the David Lynch version of Dune,
David Lynch wanted to make it about six hours long.
Right.
I understand the first cut was nine hours
and they managed to get,
well,
I,
right.
It's like Lord of the Rings.
You,
it would have been,
it would have been great as three movies.
I'm sure.
But the De Laurentiis is kind of what,
no,
six hours too long.
Cut it down to two hours.
Color.
And it's like a coloring book.
Yeah.
It doesn't make a lick of sense.
No,
no.
Here's something,
here's a great experiment to try
the next time you're wanting to
have an evening killed on Netflix.
Watch Flash Gordon,
the De Laurentiis Flash Gordon.
Yes.
Followed by the De Laurentiis Dune.
It's the same sets.
It's the same,
costumes.
They both use,
um,
uh,
Prague rock bands from the 80s.
Yes.
Toto on one and Queen on the other.
By Jove,
you're right.
It's,
it's the same movie.
Wow.
We had,
we had,
uh,
we were forced to watch the 80s Flash Gordon recently.
Very recently.
Yeah.
The,
the,
our station in Cleveland,
WCSB had a Halloween party with a Flash Gordon theme
and it was my job to project.
So I had to dig up,
I dug,
I dug up the original Flash Gordons,
the,
the TV show Flash Gordon,
which was really forgettable.
I didn't even project.
I was Flash Gordon,
which was much funnier than I remembered it.
And it's only like R rated.
It's not as nearly as nasty as people think it is.
Well,
actually there were two versions there.
I've seen the,
the hard X version.
What,
what we,
what I downloaded was the normal X version.
Semi soft.
Yeah.
Candy samples was in that,
uh,
but it has some great lines.
involving
take Gordon to the sex depletor.
No.
Yeah.
Emperor Wang.
That's an Emperor Wang.
Yeah.
It was,
and there's a penisaurus at the end.
He doesn't,
there's some Jim Danforth animation.
Yeah.
Right.
So all the,
all the,
uh,
sub Harryhausen guys got together,
you know,
you didn't get much work as a stop motion.
Harryhausen wannabe back then.
Uh,
but to,
yeah,
flesh Gordon,
it did have a penis source.
That was,
uh,
and a stop motion wiener with,
with,
uh,
teeth.
And then there was a real one.
Then there was like a dirty old monster at the end that carried a little Dale
Arden around.
And they did,
uh,
a lot of tip of the hat tips of the hat to,
the King Kong and seventh voyage of sin bed.
Oh,
there's a robot fight that is shot for shot.
Just like the skeleton fight in seventh voyage of sin.
Ah,
only it's a robot.
Yeah.
But it's a,
it goes up staircase,
little spiraling staircase.
And the music is even kind of a rip off for,
for us.
A stop motion nerds.
It was an orgy.
Well,
speaking of stop motion,
it was like Harry house.
Have you seen a para Norman yet?
No.
Okay.
There is,
there is a,
there is a tip of the hat.
To Harry housing in this,
but the one thing that they,
I'm surprised that they snuck it into a kid's film that it's set in this new
England town.
That's supposed to be cursed by a witch.
And they,
the town does what every town that has something supernatural about it does
all of the shops are witch related,
right?
So,
you know,
there's,
there's witches everywhere.
Well,
the end of the movie comes along and the town is in shambles.
And,
um,
the hot dog stand has been,
tipped over and the name of the hot dog stand is witchy wieners,
but it's,
but it's in neon and the w is blinking off.
The first w,
the first w,
not the second,
not the second one.
Witchy wieners.
Now,
what would make a hot dog stand?
You can put it in the hands of your attorney,
but it'll never stand up in court.
I think you're familiar with our state's penal code.
Yeah.
Yes.
Oh man.
When,
when I,
those jokes are all over my head.
I don't get any of that.
Three more hours of this thing.
Three.
Wow.
Oh yeah.
They didn't tell you.
Yeah.
And the doors don't open until,
until,
until four 30 in the morning.
It's a good thing.
I packed a brick.
Rick tease.
Oh my good heavens.
Well,
what other horrible parables of,
of morality do we have on,
on old LP records?
Oh,
we haven't,
we haven't.
I'm really sorry.
You didn't bring the Christmas amoeba.
Oh,
it really was a song called.
It was,
it was terrible.
Mitochondria.
You panned it.
Well,
it was awful,
but that doesn't,
that doesn't disqualify it for a subject.
Stang told me it was lame and awful,
and now it's awful.
Actually,
I left it at home and was castigated.
No,
you're so thin skinned,
Susie.
Only because he's beaten it to a thin sheet of meat.
Yeah.
I'm so,
I'm such a control freak.
Thin sheet of meat.
Lousy jerky.
Yes,
we're a princess.
We and I are traveling across the country in the I van,
checking on,
on subgenius shows and grading them.
We're,
this is our inspection tour.
Oh,
and we've also been inspecting the children of our,
of the subgeniuses.
This was the first place we stopped where there,
where there weren't kids or animals,
right?
Pop.
Now,
next we're going to lizards.
Next,
we're going to see Papa,
Papa Joe mama,
or otherwise known as father,
Joseph mother in Tallahassee.
And he's,
uh,
a dad.
All of a sudden he's got a five month old dad now,
but,
uh,
yeah,
we,
a real father,
a real Papa,
uh,
Pisces and suds Shaw.
We visited in,
in,
uh,
Virginia,
my mother's favorite subgenius.
That's some very promising up and coming subgenius youth.
Uh,
the,
the younger one.
I don't know.
I can't remember her subgenius.
I don't know her subgenius name.
Well,
you want me to go to the band and find out for you?
The older one is Reverend Echo Bad.
And I have a lot of hope for the youth of tomorrow.
I know,
I know many of my fellow ministers are not the,
don't have parenting instincts and think that children should be eaten and not seen or heard.
Oh,
but Echo Bad really refreshed our faith in youth.
Yeah.
She's twisted,
sick,
perverted,
full of hate and really talented graphic artist.
Really talented.
Takes after her pa.
Yeah.
Hardworking little artist there.
What shall it be,
Susie?
Oh,
I'm trying to decide.
What about forgiveness?
The boy looking natural.
You can enjoy a jelly roll.
Oh,
well,
there you go.
This is more worlds of youth.
Yeah.
Well,
see,
these will be good for these up and coming younger preteen subgeniuses.
Or there's computers.
Oh,
I wish I had a brain like that.
Teenagers.
Oh.
Have what?
Yeah.
Some computer thing or baptism.
Come to work,
girls too.
What a lovely war.
That sounds pretty cynical.
Want to try the war thing?
Yes.
Make it happen.
Make it so,
number one.
I wish I had a brain.
I just wish I had a brain to begin with.
I'll do a number two.
Not just a brain like that,
but I wish I had a brain.
Well,
you know,
Princess Wee,
where I come from,
we have the learned men.
They're known as professors.
And all they have that you don't have is a diploma.
Which costs them several dollars.
And you too can have a diploma.
They have no more brains than you do.
If I only had a diploma.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what came over me.
Don't give me lines like that.
Oh.
Ah.
They sighed in unison.
Oh,
I love when that happens.
Me three.
Suicide.
And then there's when you do Captain Beefheart routines in unison.
By reflex.
Yeah.
Much less sexy than two girls sighing in unison.
Much,
much.
110% lady proof,
that is.
Yeah.
It's kind of that acid reflex disease.
Because you sound like you was tripping.
On that beer fart thing.
Marijuana is the fuse.
But LSD is the Bob.
Yeah.
Okay.
Oh.
Now where's Worlds of Youth?
I don't know.
Do we have to shut up first?
No.
Well,
if.
It's not up to me.
Maybe it's 10 minutes long and we'll be able to leave.
No.
Those magic worlds.
And locking grooves.
You're stuck in this groove.
Round.
Oh yeah.
That's right.
This is a record with locked grooves.
Succulent.
Yeah.
That's very Christian.
Tightly packed worlds.
There's an amazing.
Worlds within worlds.
This sounds heavy handed.
Come to the war.
You mean I should volunteer?
You are drafted.
Now come.
You mean I don't even have a chance to volunteer?
You have a chance.
I dont.
to come as a draftee. Are you calling in everyone my age? Not everyone. Only the boys? Girls
too. Which ones? The ones drafted. Come. Where will we go? To war. But my father just finished
a war. This is another war. What's the name of this one? The war to end all wars. You mean we now use the secret weapon we almost used in the one just ended? Not really. This isn't that weapon. How do you describe this
war? It's war between wars. You mean a war getting ready for the next war? I mean getting rid of the last war and if possible the next one. You mean it's a war on war? Right. The war of peace. Who will train us? You are trained.
You have the armor. You know the strategy. Are you kidding? I don't even know the names of the battlefields of the last war and the ammunition factories have been converted. Come to the war. My folks may not let me go. At least let me say goodbye. They are also drafted. You are all in the troops of this war.
Okay.
Okay. Then I give in. You mean you give up? Give up? Yes. Give up war. Which ones? The last one of your father and the one of your grandfather and the one waiting for your children. What's the secret weapon? Forgive the enemy.
Which enemy? The ones already dead and the ones just being born. The enemies of your children in 20 years. Is that the battle line? That's two of them. The third is the big battle. Where's that one? Your enemies. How do I fight this war on wars?
Give your enemies. Must I? You are drafted. Who are the draftees? All the baptized. You are all called to war. To the war against wars. Come. The war of peace has begun.
Why didn't you tell me about this before?
How could I?
The Christian is never safe from the world. To be baptized into the body of Christ means to be baptized into the world of Christ.
The Christian is in the world. He is called.
Not to easy street, but to battle fronts. In baptism, he is named a member of a warring people. One understanding of man is that he is a soldier. Daily reminded and daily equipped to wage war defensively and offensively. Why fight in this world? Because it is the father's world.
Why?
With this kind of war comes peace. Daily peace. Eternal peace.
Wow. Man.
That was dark.
That green stuff isn't guacamole. It's world peas.
War is peace. War is peace.
I love Big Brother.
Eternal peace.
War is peace.
Oh, man.
My God.
Subgeniuses are called to eternal slack.
Sounds like a better deal to me.
Bob?
No kidding.
Bob.
The terrible, rotten smell of burning flesh.
Bob?
I'm hungry.
Bob.
I hear Ennio Morricone in the background.
Hmm.
The background music.
Yeah.
That's much better than anything we could say.
I love this music.
That's from For a Few Dollars More, isn't it?
Yes.
Yes, it is.
Does not lover come back?
I just love them rock huds and movies where it acts straight.
Yeah.
Marion.
Then Rocktree marries Doris Dogg and he piddles on her.
I'm doing it, friends.
I'm playing a video game while doing a subgenius radio show.
Congratulations.
You are now 16 years old.
Yeah.
That's right.
I finally caught up with the 16-year-olds of the world who can multitask.
This music really goes perfectly with the little thing on my screen.
Let's not talk about the things we see on our screens on the radio.
Well, one thing you see on the screen is subgenius.com.
That's right.
Don't call the number you see on your screen because you're hallucinating that number.
It's not really there and there's not a screen.
Bob?
But this show does have that effect on some people.
Bob.
Bub.
What's all the hubbub?
Bob.
Okay.
Mmm.
Bob.
Okay.
I owe Bob, but just this once.
Oh.
Well, friends, it's been lovely being here at the studios of WREK Atlanta, Georgia Tech.
The posh studios.
Yes.
Posh and polished.
We are honored to once again be, and it's a brand new, it's the newer studio.
It is fabulous.
I've been here when it was the olden days.
It's fabulous.
It's a groovy.
Oh, yeah.
As you said.
They burned that down in 2004.
I had nothing to do with that.
For Micah, as far as the eye can see.
Oh, it's for everybody.
You've been listening to the subgenius radio ministry hour of slack.
For free information, write to P.O.
Box 181417.
Cleveland.
Flint Heights, Ohio 44118.
Or see www.subgenius.com.
Praise Bob.
Thank you.
It's just this show, but subgenius.com and all the other archive sites.
But if you truly love Bob and want some of that slack back to rebound to you, you should
go to subgenius.com front page or especially the radio page or the catalog store pages
and help out financially as best you can.
Now we know what it's like to be on the brink of total poverty and we don't want any subgeniuses
to make their own situations worse.
But some of you still have jobs.
Even five bucks makes a big difference.
Even if it's only once a month from enough of you, 50 bucks makes an even bigger difference.
All we're saying is that blow jobs could go the way of Steve jobs if you don't pay
dogs.
We also take checks and money orders to subgenius foundation.
P.O.
Box 181417.
Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Thanks for anything you can do to help let there be slack.
We'll see you next time.