Thank you for listening and stay tuned for the Hour of Slack, dear friends.
Ah, yes.
Well, friends, I don't hear anything.
Do you?
Let's just see.
No? No?
But what about him?
The leader?
Perhaps he can help us.
For the first time in man's history, I'm president.
And I can do this with dash and daring do.
No.
You're too old. You're out of touch.
I don't think I'm out of touch.
Asked for too old?
Well, I have a very good memory about...
all the things back in my life.
For example, I can remember...
Senator Benjamin Hill in 1878.
When we were less than 70 years old.
Good times and bad.
Ronald Reagan.
You can see and understand the America of dirty streets and poor people.
The problem isn't being poor. The problem...
The problem is...
uh...
So, poverty isn't...
I'm supposed to be the big reactionary.
Okay.
All right.
What...
What people do you think you represented?
The John Birch Society was praising you.
Oh, yes.
All right.
The John Birch Society.
Sure.
Milton Friedman.
Certainly.
The far right.
All right.
The...
As a matter of fact, uh...
a few Republican panaceas, myself, and people like myself,
organized a task force of people outside government and inside.
Uh...
Well, this little group gathered, and we very carefully would open the car door with the window rolled down,
shove the man's arm across the window, and then break it.
The backbone of America, and then break it over the window.
Uh...
And then the pressure came on.
That hidden longing came out, and, uh...
Gunshot.
Gunshots, and so forth.
What about government's role in offsetting the negative consequences of the free enterprise business community you talked about?
Oh, now.
No, now you get back.
No, now you get back to what I said earlier.
What I'm talking about is the free marketplace, free enterprise.
The regulations that government exists to have, and are necessary,
is, yes, to ensure that someone can't sell us a can of poisoned meat.
I think, uh...
a can of poisoned meat had a problem that I think the people must recognize.
The problem is, uh, if you open a can of poisoned meat, hold it in your hand,
it gets warm very fast while you're drinking it.
We punch the holes in the top and drink it.
Well, this fella's made a very economic...
...stein handle.
You can buy a dozen of them and have them like you have your silverware.
You're serving people, uh...
poisoned food in the can.
You just clamp the stand.
Snap the stand.
You just clamp...
...clamp the stand.
Snap the handle onto it and people hold it, but the handle of the drink doesn't warm up.
And you're gonna make a million dollars.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
We're now deep inside the brain cavity of Doug Smith.
As you can see all around you there's sparking.
There was a short circuit.
All brain seems to have recovered.
Uh, there are sparking energy thoughts all around us.
Far more than the normal human brain.
but as we know, another misfire there, we know Doug Smith is not a normal human. No, and here inside the
brain of Doug Smith, we can observe some of the differences that make this man a unique leader among men.
Over here in this corner are the memory bags, and over here is the main printout area.
If you turn on the machine, this is Radio Yerevan. My name is Franz Ivanovich Hagen, and this is the news.
Wake up, puppet boy!
This is Doug Smith, radio operator.
I have a bucket!
No trouble.
Let's get...
Set, get going. Amen.
Recording.
Everything's going fine.
No trouble.
Welcome potential initiates, and remain with us for the next 30 minutes.
Bob?
The message is now part of and registered in your subconscious mind.
Every time you say, see,
hear,
or think.
What about Slack?
That's your key phrase.
It will trigger the entire message without your being aware of it.
And now, the subgenius hour of Slack.
Subgenius hour of Slack.
The subgenius hour of Slack that you are about to listen to is specially designed only to
be played on radio station KNON, and only in the city of Dallas, Texas.
Should any other shows be heard from or contacted in the course of this show, the listener is
advised to remain calm and only contact listed or unlisted officials in the event of any material
from this radio or other resource.
listening device being inhaled during broadcast.
Small animals or other children becoming exposed to the ultra-high or ultra-low shocks and
brain frequencies constantly scanned throughout our program should seek shelter in an approved
safety unit only.
This is Walter Teasdale reminding you that it's often a photon that light releases, but
truth is, not everyone gets the picture.
Hoping your time is all time, and all your unpermissible truths are happy truths.
Here is your host, Reverend Ivan Stang.
Oh, yes, dear friends, and Pastor Buck Naked is expected momentarily.
And plus, as guest hosts, we have here the TV crew from SMU.
They're here to try to get pictures of the poltergeist that's been harassing the show,
the airways of the show.
I don't know if a lot of you folks knew this, but there's a dead, old radio
radio station.
A radio preacher who used to inhabit this airwave belonged before KNO, and it was a
different station.
But he died while on the air, friends, on this very microphone.
And that's why we're plagued by certain technical difficulties that afflict this show only,
friends.
Yes, last week it was the needle gouging its way across records right after we put him
on the air.
So we're hoping to catch some of that paranormal manifestationary visitation.
Uh, here on this show tonight on videotape.
And, uh, yes, dear friends.
And meanwhile, Norm?
Nah, Norm right here.
Friends, you've heard about the KNON pledge drive coming up, and it starts officially
at midnight.
That just means that since this is the hour of slack, you don't get any slack unless you
pledge, friends.
That's right.
We want your blood.
We want, uh, well, we want everything.
Here's the thing, folks.
Uh, you literally have to pledge to KNON in order to keep us on the air.
I mean, look at it this way.
You're already paying the conspiracy, right?
All the time.
You're paying them to make you work, dear friend.
It's the truth.
So if you're gonna, you know, if you're gonna be getting screwed every day, why don't you
do it the way you choose?
Some ways are fun.
Pick, you know, I mean, if you're...
If you're listening to something else, you're paying for it with the commercials that are
in the silent radio signals that are broadcast into your mind.
Listen to those phones light up, friends.
Yes, some of them are saved out there.
And, uh, why, folks, I'm gonna be giving those phone numbers relentlessly to the, this tune
of, uh, of WKGB, our friends in Boston.
We got a lot, playing a lot of Boston tonight.
Uh, but those numbers to call, friends.
And you can, you can actually...
Talk to Phil and the Blanks in person.
If you call and pledge your $5, $20, $30, $40, or a million dollars to KNOM.
That's right.
You can praise Bob and praise Phil and the Blanks if you will call and get that pencil
ready, friends.
8-2-3-7-4-9-0.
That's one number.
Let's try that again.
8-2-3-7-4-9-0.
I'm not gonna quit saying that, friends, until we get some souls, uh, pledged to this station.
And, and, you know...
Souls aren't enough.
A lot of you have been pledging your ears for years and years now.
Pledging your ears and your prayers to KNOM.
You've already done that, but we want you to pledge.
I mean, you know, dig deep.
Pledge a million bucks.
Pledge whatever you've got.
I mean, there's little old ladies out there that are starving or barely got enough.
You know, for them, uh, $300, $400 a week to KNOM would be a lot.
You know, uh, so if they could just spare $100 a week, that'd be great.
Some of you, of course, can only spare $5.
And for that $5, you'll get a KNOM newsletter complete with abs for this show.
That's right.
And, ah, hear those phones screaming again.
Ah, yes.
Ah, ah, oh, the power.
It fills a DJ with lust, friends, to know that you're gonna, you're gonna call us and say that you'll give $40 to KNOM.
Because that way you'll get the KNOM t-shirt, the bumper stickers, the newsletter.
And if you, if you make sure and praise Bob, friends, if you make sure and praise Bob, you'll make your way into heaven.
So, uh, and we'll take Visa numbers, uh, Master Charge numbers.
And there's even a tricky bank draft thing, which you can talk to the, to fill in the blanks about.
But see, and I'm not gonna play anything else until we get some more calls, friends.
This is important.
Our status, the status of Bob.
Bob Dobbs and the Hour of Slack on KNOM depends on how many pledges we can get.
So get on them phones, boys, girls.
Prove that we have listeners.
I mean, we've been pretending we have listeners for a long time now.
We need to, we need to prove it.
Friends, your survival hinges on, on your pledge.
The very earth itself, even, even Bob Dobbs' survival on the, on the airwaves anywhere hinges on your pledge right now.
And I don't mean later.
I don't mean calling up.
Tomorrow morning when you get paid.
I mean, you know, you'll get paid later.
Pledge now.
Get on those phones or you're killing Bob, man.
You don't want to kill Bob.
Well, maybe you do want to kill Bob.
I mean, he, Bob's always telling you to kill him.
But, uh, friends, I just, I don't know.
I don't even know what to play next.
I think if this is one of these tank decks that's running, I'd stop.
Oh, nothing's enough.
God.
I don't know what to play next in here.
Well, that's, that's not true.
I mean, this isn't good.
No, we just got back to normal.
Would we trade something off to John Howard?
This guy really, really wants to live.
Tate Missoula remove.
Now you should do that.
Now you're aware of the war.
ain't no good. They won't double-cash it without that extra $500.
Oh, yes, dear friends. Well, has the station polder guy started up yet?
Video crew, say hello real loud.
Hi.
Yeah, that's the entire paranormal investigation team from SMU, friends.
What about the phone numbers?
Oh, the phone numbers. Yes, that's right. The phone numbers again, as we said before.
823-7490. These are more important than the sacred subgenius box number, friends.
823-8801. That's an easy one.
823-8801. 823-8801. And 823-8883.
That's going to be a strange year, friends. The year 8883.
The year when Atlantis will rise again from the ocean, and you'll have to...
Papa!
Master Naked just walked in.
Oh, yes, friends.
Hi, girls.
Tell them to use some of your special mojo sexuality charisma, you know, buck, to get them to send money.
That's all we care about tonight.
Are we on a pledge drive again?
What do you mean? This is the pledge drive, man.
It's wait until we actually start at midnight. You think this is bad.
All right, well, I've got my own little pledge drive thing I'm going to do.
But basically, here's my theme.
If you don't know if you want to pledge to the station or not, just turn the channels nice and easy right now.
Just try it.
I might be one of the first people who ever asked you just to turn around the other channels.
Go ahead and change the channel a little bit.
So call in.
That's right. Change channels. Listen to the trash for a minute that you heard before and then call back.
And listen to the trash that you've never heard.
And those numbers are the other the wimpy spirituals that that won't get you really massage gland on your foot.
Your massage.
Well, whatever.
Close enough.
We want you to massage that foot gland and then be in bed out there.
I want you to massage your sacred foot gland and ask it.
Should I pledge for Bob?
Reach deep, deep, deep into that most holy and sacred of receptacles on your whole body, friends.
Your back.
Your back pocket.
No.
Massage your foot first.
Well, yeah, but I don't care what they do to get the for the urge.
Foreplay.
That's right.
All right.
Anybody touching your feet yet?
I guess not.
823-7490.
Is there any up there?
That's 823-7490.
823-8801.
Well, I guess we're history.
We're out of here.
823.
Yeah.
Let's play in the other stations.
Can we do that?
Okay.
Yeah.
Well, like, for instance, this is what this is one of the other stations.
Listen.
Listen to this.
Welcome to the End Times, boys and girls.
We're going to shock shock the house with your brain and the world.
Bob is getting down with you here tonight.
Bob is getting down to help your plight.
Bob is coming here to ease your strife.
Karma suckers let Bob into your life.
Well, I'm MC Cleef.
I'm the master of rap.
I'm a dog like my mother's lips.
Gonna clap.
Y'all sitting out saying, oh, woe is me.
Well, I'm here to tell you it ain't worth peeing.
The End Times is here.
You're pretty mad now.
Time to make a pay for the past.
Who else is going to have to go through a real?
Rebirth.
And that means paying the spaceship Earth.
Exists will come from Planet X to remove from us the paintball sex.
In the meantime, we will have our say.
Get slack.
And fornicate every day.
Knock the conspiracy on its ass.
Make your life a ass.
Take your toes right to the hip.
Make the normal suckers fit.
Take the time to rape their minds.
Tell them to blow it out their behinds.
Take all their money.
Get what's your worth.
And continue to spurt to the rebirth.
Who's gone?
He gone.
Slack faster makes you damn faster than any other.
So to the bone.
He's the one.
How about he get out of your behind?
If you want to know the truth, then that's a fact.
Somebody scream.
Gimme more slack!
Do you like slack?
I like it.
I say, I love slack.
I love it.
Do you want slack?
I want it.
Do you need slack?
I need it.
Do you like niggi?
No.
How about nanini?
What about noo-noo?
No.
Look out for Shagadisma.
Get down from the roof.
Okay.
I'm Pastor Buck Naked, and I'm sitting right here now with Dr. Chaos,
Table Football League coach, head coach of the, what is it, Chaos City Crushers.
All right.
Well, the Crushers didn't get to play this time.
The DeSau Destroyers took their place.
And, Doc, I guess you got the standings, do you?
Let's hear it.
I got them.
Okay.
This is the Feebarch standings, February and March.
Number one, Dallas Assassins, 12th career gold, always deadly.
Number two, Downtown Underground.
Three, Wazonian Doctors.
Four, Uptown Peace.
Five, Dr. Rudy Ray Moore.
And one of the Steve Gold, Mike.
And the Mavs.
Five, Know What's What.
Six, Dallas Assassins.
So come on over here and give up the game.
Whip some scum on me, bitch.
Oh, give me all of your cash.
Return you wanted to whine about your soul.
Because when the exits come, you'll be right on my phone.
Dude, Doc's out in Malaysia.
We will go.
When you drink the cool, then I go home, home, home.
Yeah!
Now, I might be lying there with an ice pack on my nuts.
Or maybe I'll chase some other fine bucks.
But at least you won't have to wear machinery.
And you'll be free from the conspiracy.
Play begins 9.30 sharp, Saturday, March 22nd.
And while you're wishing upon a star,
you'll probably lose me and some interstellar bar.
Come on, Cleve, that's your 17th bottle of night chain tonight.
Let's go home now before you pass out right here on the street.
Woman, I can drink more wine and stay sober
than all the heathen Hindus in Asia.
Yeah, I heard that before.
Get your popsicle sticks and let's get your damn...
Oh, yes, dear friends.
Ooh.
Well, yeah, that's right.
And if you don't pledge that mighty pledge, friends,
to KNON, when you call 823-7490,
why, that guest host, Chaos,
will come and give you the very kiss of chaos
at your very personal home.
Ooh.
The ear-splitting, grinding, mighty caress of the...
God almighty.
Well, friends, that's 823-8883.
Uh, 8...
823-8801.
8801.
That's when...
That's when that time intersection starts to end, friends.
Oh.
Buck, I think you better read this newspaper article here while we...
I thought I was gonna talk about the Dick Army Corps.
Huh?
Oh, okay.
Hey.
Join the Dick Army Corps.
The Dick Army Corps wants you.
Extreme right-wing patri...
Patriot, psychotic...
Uh, political lifestyles...
Uh...
Not dead.
So...
Men, women, join the Dick Army Corps.
Dick!
Army!
Well, friends, that, uh, just before the, uh,
hilarious Dick Army Corps, we got the, uh...
That was, uh, Reverend Cleve Duncan doing Welcome to the End Times.
That's the first time we ever played that one on the air.
I had to specially censor that one.
Because, uh, Slackman...
Cleve was in town last...
This weekend.
And we were planning to have him on the show.
He's a great preacher.
And a lot of the...
The, uh...
Del Fuego's, uh...
Groupies out there were really hoping to hear Cleve preach.
Huh?
Nobody knows who they are.
Oh, you should have seen those normals, uh, in that great cattle pen at the Ritz Club.
Uh...
Wallowing in sameness, waiting to hear the Del Fuego's buck.
Reveling in their normalcy.
Huh?
You think any of them listen to KON?
They pro...
Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
I would hope so.
But they pro...
They're probably too normal to pledge.
You think they know who Dick Army is?
They're probably...
No.
That's North Dallas.
I don't think...
That's strictly the buck-naked section of town, I believe.
No, no.
No, the Dick Army Corps is up in Denton and Farmer's Branch.
If you live in Farmer's Branch, Dick Army is already your congressman.
And he may soon be your president.
Yeah.
Would you explain that?
Dick Army...
Dick Army is such a man that he lives in the gym.
He lives in the gym in the U.S. House of Representatives.
I'm not kidding.
They had to throw him out bodily out of the gym.
Because he doesn't want to sleep in an apartment.
He wants to sleep in the gym with the men.
Okay.
Oh, yes.
Well, friends, it's...
I'm not kidding.
These are X-rated church hymns.
We're spreading.
Yeah.
Let's see.
I remember when I was 16.
Sure, we'll never forget that.
It was a great TV movie.
The 60s were burned on our brain.
Those engrams were branded on those tiny, multiple-minded fissures and fractures in the old...
Why don't you ask about the 70s, Nebio?
We had some fun in the 70s.
Yeah, the 60s didn't really start happening until the 70s.
And then the 70s never happened.
And so then the 80s had to come along.
Yeah, but they just all repeated themselves and were the same thing.
Well, we often repeat ourselves.
It's that same old thing that makes a tomcat scream all night.
Just like Howard Hughes.
With all his billions.
And he still lies without one thin dime in his skeletonous hand.
Or Beau Pham Hughes, who spins every cent he gets.
How do you feel about that, caller?
In the midst of life, we are in jazz.
We're so laid back, we can't even see us.
Only front end.
This can be prevented by removing the heart, like so.
Ow!
I'm sorry, that's just not the way it is.
Yeah, you know what I'm talking about? You're on the air.
Okay, hello, you're on the air.
Thank you, guys.
This morning, you were...
You woke me from a terrible dream.
There are few areas, indeed, that are entirely free from the devious influence of our sworn enemies.
Case in point, this caller who just dialed in.
Dobbs has recently suggested to us that TVs emit non-detectable F-rays,
which mysteriously fuse brain cells into predetermined patterns that then control the individual's behavior.
It is yet to be ascertained whether these emissions are con or exist in origin.
Yes.
Exercise your corpus callosum, caller.
Hello, right side?
Hello, left side?
Well, now, if your right brain is all hooked up and your left brain hasn't been left, if you catch my meaning, you ought to be able to copy the letter M in a mirror.
Go ahead.
Okay.
Take this simple test.
Okay, well, I'll have to get all that white powder off the mirror in front of me so I can...
Please.
Isn't it true?
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, Guy, you're plugged directly into the show here.
And you can see the Hushpoo Wizard in the background.
Yeah, Guy.
The most important...
...inside joke is...
Fear not.
I do not accuse you of common...
We can't seem to get away from the strange creatures that invade our airways, friends.
It's the KPFHO from Berkeley, California.
The puzzling evidence, Hal Robinson...
And friends...
It's getting pretty violent around here, I'm afraid.
This is KNON 90.9 in Dallas, Texas.
But it won't be much longer.
It will be another insidious tool of the conspiracy, friends.
The conspiracy that controls your very mind, or what's left of it.
If you have ever had anything...
Well, you do, but you just gotta...
You gotta jump on it.
There's nobody by that name here.
Ivan?
Hm?
I think we got a call, Ivan.
I think that's just the...
Oh, really?
Do we have the...
The fated call from...
Let's see now.
I'll...
We're expecting a call from Little Rock, friends.
Alright.
And I...
His miscellaneous dial, don't I?
Hit on.
On?
Yup.
On.
Ah, yes.
And hit this.
And put your phone down.
Hello?
Put the phone down.
Ah, yes.
Hello.
Hello, can we hear you?
Hello?
I can hear you.
Try to talk to Doug Smith.
No, there's...
Who...
Who are you trying to talk to?
Do you want to talk to Ivan Stang?
I've never heard of that guy.
Oh, I guess you're right.
It is Ivan Stang.
Hey, look.
We're cutting you off unless you're ready to pledge a goodly amount to K-N-O-N, dear friend.
What does he say?
What's the decision?
You know, Doug, I was...
I mean, Ivan, I was just reading in the paper the other day how the Reverend Ike had 90 Cadillacs and Bob only had 89.
And I just thought that was the most insidious...
Yeah, but Bob just brought out those Rolls Royces from the commune in Oregon.
So even though Bob has less Cadillacs, he has more Rolls Royces than Reverend Ike.
Oh, wow.
Isn't it that way?
That...
That really makes me feel a lot better.
I was gonna pledge a million dollars.
I was so worried about it.
But since you told me that, I guess I'll just save my money.
Oh, no, no.
Go ahead, sir.
That million dollars would come in real handy here for the home for slackless children.
And also, K-N-O-N might get a new building, too.
Well, what about the research facilities in the commune?
We have the K-N-O-N tower here.
The research facilities in Dobstown, friend...
Now, you know, if we don't get a million...
It's not just a million dollars we need.
It's a million five hundred.
And if you're just pledging a million, I mean, I don't know what kind of an afterlife you're planning to get out of this whole thing.
I mean, are you trying to be a pretty boy or what?
Well, I could pledge a million four hundred and ninety-nine if you think that you're...
But he won't deliver.
I can whiff this guy.
He's a fake.
Hold on.
No...
Hello?
I just cut him off.
You did?
Yeah.
Well, thanks, Jayner.
I'm sorry, but, uh...
That was Jayner?
Yeah, that was Jayner, Buck.
Oh, hell no.
Thanks a lot.
Well, friends, we're gonna head on out into the, uh...
It was a fake, folks.
It was a fake.
You see your last flame, Saucer.
The last thing I seen was here Sunday week, is on the wheat field.
In the wheat field.
Isn't that a little unusual?
No, I think they must feed off wheat or something.
Well, the little green man's name was Real Head Cat.
Rockin' and a-rollin' through the crazy flats.
Brought out a sax and it started to flow.
Brought out the drums and it started to roll.
Blind Saucer, rock and roll.
I couldn't understand it.
A big head said it was a great deal.
The fans had beat it just to stop Mid-Dent Joe.
Thanks for waiting and go right ahead.
Yeah, I'm calling from Glenrose.
I talked to these two a couple of months ago about some cattle mutilation.
Yeah, you were the farmer, right?
Right.
I raise cattle and I told you all about the mutilation.
It's also a big, good idea if I sent some money in.
Might give me an edge.
Yeah, right.
Well, we've had another one down here.
Another?
Another cattle mutilation.
How much money did you send in?
Well, that's the problem.
I never got around to sending some money in.
Well, that's why, well, we can't, we don't have that much to do with cattle mutilation,
but we can help put you on the alert to who might be doing it.
And how to watch out for them.
Yeah, we, that whole situation with the cattle mutilations is pretty spooky.
Not very many people know about it.
Listen, you need to stop.
I mean, I've been to New York and they said, oh, two blacks had their heart, and I said,
I know some doctors and surgeons can't cut a heart out.
But, I mean, where, I mean, where were you just a few days ago when some horses came
up in Arizona and Wyoming with their hearts missing?
Six thousand sheep just fell dead out there in Utah, and this government made it look
like they didn't know what it was.
Well, it wasn't the visitors, they had to admit they ain't dead there.
That whole game.
Well, I still want me a Nobel Prize.
And the reason I want it, there's a lot of people in America that have Nobel Prizes,
but there's five white boys in particular that decided that their Nobel Prize had made
their sperms different.
So they decided to put their sperms in a sperm bank.
Well, that's why I wants me a Nobel Prize.
Let's go.
One, two, three, four.
.
don't make me say things
you don't want to be
they say
you can be anything
this time around
we had six million
and 432,000 incarnations as lower forms of life,
where you got to be a human being.
And then you got 200,000 incarnations as a human being,
where you grab that brass ring in the center
and can say, as I'm telling you right now,
I can be anything this time around.
You can goof with this time around.
You can get hung up on that power trip,
chase money, competition, success.
You've done that before.
You're not going to do that again this time around.
You can be anyone this time around.
You can be anyone.
You can do anything this time around.
You're God, baby, and it's your reality.
It all comes from you this time around.
Make it a good trip this time around.
Make it a love trip this time around.
I know you won't goof with this time around.
This is the moment.
We're on a date tonight.
We didn't, yeah, he was a patriot.
We didn't say, okay, hold on, hold on, hold on, we're on the air, we're on the air, we're on the air.
We're arguing about the Dick Army Corps, friends.
You know, Dick Army is your congressman if you live in Farmer's Branch, if you live in Denton and so on,
and hey, it's a free country.
I think everybody should vote for Dick Army.
So therefore, Dick Army's got my vote, and I'm the Dick Army Corps.
Well, friends, but what about you?
But what about you?
What about 823-7490 and that pledge, friends, for $20?
And I know that you have a...
This is not going to Dick Army Corps.
For $20, you can get that bumper sticker, friends.
All right, if somebody calls me right now, I'll stop talking about the Dick Army Corps.
How about that?
I'll stop talking about the Dick Army Corps before you light one up.
If you can kill Buck, friends, you can kill Buck by pledging $30.
That gets you a T-shirt, a bumper sticker, and an axe handle.
I'm leaving. I'm sleeping.
I'm kidding, Buck.
I'm mystery. I'm out of here.
Now, look.
Here we...
Whoops.
I like Dick Army.
I love the man.
I admire him more than President Reagan.
Before he came along, I didn't know what the true meaning of Dick Army was.
God bless the president.
Did you hear the president on earlier?
We had the president on the show.
The president, really?
Yeah.
How sexy.
He's sexy.
That man is a true star.
He's stud looking at him.
I mean, you ever see the pictures of him as a nude model, a semi-nude model when he was a young guy?
He was about 20.
Hey, are we still on the air?
Sexy.
I hope so.
Yeah.
See, the voice of me is moving.
Okay.
Somebody tune this radio.
Please tune that radio there.
And just leave it recording.
Call for Reverend Stang.
Call for Reverend Stang, please.
Let's get straight here.
We're talking about the unique section of Dallas Times Herald.
That's right.
Sexy.
And that's a funny, considering the subject matter of this particular, we're talking about the newspaper.
Let me see.
Hold on a second.
The 8237490 is open right now.
Pledge now.
Go ahead.
Okay.
And thank you for the pledges so far, friends.
You may be able to impress Kano and enough that we have a listenership that we stay on the air.
Now, as for this unique section, friends, this morning, if you open one of your newspapers,
you'll find this article about parents.
And punkers, which had some pretty incredible quotes in it.
To begin with it, they were talking about how the parents of punkers should realize their kids will outgrow the punk stage.
And that's the saddest thing about it, friends.
They will outgrow the punk stage.
They'll outgrow the politics of the punk stage, but maintain their fashions and hairstyles until they're 33 or 34.
But by then, they'll have to.
Or else they won't be able to get a job.
Yes.
But consider the fate of the burned-out freaks of the 60s.
Now, they still listen to their car radios all the time.
Well, that's not true at all.
I'm one of the burned-out freaks from the 60s.
And I don't look like a normal businessman.
No, you're an intellectual.
You were always an intellectual.
You were always a rebel, Stang.
I'm about the real burned-out freaks.
The guys that still have long hair and they still listen to the too loud stuff.
Okay, you're right.
Well, that's what I'm saying.
Is that there's...
Okay, there was those who became hippies or who now become punks because they were true weirdos.
But what about the Dick Army Corps?
It was their only hope for getting some.
Friends, Buck ain't gonna shut up about the Dick Army Corps unless you pledge.
That's 8237-490...
Oh, we got a pledge I'm gonna shut up now.
I've had it.
No more Dick Army all night.
Can I talk about it?
No.
No, no.
That's enough Dick Army, man.
That's enough.
If he starts talking about it, I'm gonna turn a tape on, okay?
This is my...
This is the King Stang Hour.
As long as I'm the only one who can...
Get him!
Oh, something, you guys.
Anyway, Janet says her punk clothes, and she wears only black, are a form of being her own person
and don't interfere with her interests at school.
The problem is, friends, now I know 375 people who look exactly like this punk girl pictured on the cover.
She says she's doing it to be different.
And yet her daddy, if you look further down the article, doesn't want her to be too weird.
And she agrees that she doesn't want to be too weird.
Are we getting...
She's getting weird.
Oh, okay.
Can I make a comment?
Yeah, go ahead.
I think her mom looks cooler than she does.
Hey, I was about to say the same thing.
Look at that, man.
I mean, that's my kind of woman.
No kidding.
Man, that is sexy.
She's a different...
She's a real sexy.
That's a real woman.
The more you look at it, the more you get it.
I say she's a desert cutie.
A desert cutie.
She does look like a cat.
Yeah, Santa Fe.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's more than my dreams.
Friends, if you don't send that money, we're going to give up.
Conspiracy style.
8-2-3-8-8-0-1.
Light that sucker up.
We want it on top.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you, Bob.
Oh, thank you.
They're lighting up good.
Oh, yes, friends.
Hold on.
Hold the line.
There is hope for this planet.
There seems to be some remnant of hope as long as these people can keep finally.
Please join our prayer family.
Yeah, you can hear them.
Please join our prayer family and send money to KNON.
Now, dear friends.
Let's give the address over the air just once, just for the heck of it.
Please do.
KNON Community Radio, Department 139, P.O. Box 141-199.
That's a pretty Bobby number.
Dallas, Texas 75214.
That's it, dear friends.
We don't need to ask for names.
All the lines are lit up.
This is the Swinging Love Corps is doing their beautiful rendition of Deadly Swill.
The
contemplative
It's back to the 60s with the Swimming Love Corpses, friends.
Yes, and Tim Leary.
And back to the punk.
You see, one of these days, folks.
Yeah, we've been in the punk.
One of these days, friends, what you punks have to realize is that the same thing is going to happen if your world-saving new order has happened to the hippie world order of my day,
which is that the conspiracy already owns it, friends.
But what about the beatniks of the 1950s?
They were the conforming nonconformists.
The beatniks?
They became the conforming nonconformists.
Then the freaks burned out.
And then the me generation became the us generation.
Everybody sold out, you know?
Everybody.
And then don't you realize that pretty soon everybody will be in the dick army course.
It won't matter anymore because we'll all be one people.
One America.
One movement.
One army to take over the world, to slay the dragons that threaten us, to finally stop the menace of creeping socialism and creeping individualism and creeping immorality.
Because immorality is subjective.
Remember that, friends.
Immorality belongs to you and all your friends.
And I want you to go out and tell the world that we're just going to live from now on.
Dick army.
You can tell the world by calling KNO and pledging your $20, $30, $40, or $1 million at 823-7490, 823-8801, or 823-8883.
Now, friends, and if you don't, you know what's going to happen?
Your music is going to become shopping center music.
That's right.
Your favorite punk hits are going to end up sounding like this.
Well, maybe not like that.
Maybe.
Maybe like, hey, what happened, man?
Huh.
Right now.
Ha, ha, ha.
I am an antichrist.
I am an anarchist.
Don't know what I want, but I know how to get it.
I want to destroy passes by, because I want to be anarchy.
No dogs, buddy.
Anarchy for the UK.
It's coming sometime, maybe.
Give the wrong time, stop a traffic light.
Your future dream is a shopping scheme, because I want to be anarchy.
Here's a break, boys.
Give me that oafish ho Nos symbols, girl.
I'll be there any minute
No, not that.
Oh yeah, I gotta think about those things.
You want me to help me?
I want to be anarchy.
Oh, yes, friends.
That's the swinging erudites doing Anarchy in the UK.
That's going to be, they'll play that in Skaggs in about the year 1998.
You know, if you don't be pledging that money, friends,
it's just 823-7490, KNOM, that's right.
And I'm serious.
It could be the end of free radio in Dallas.
Free Dallas, that's what I say.
But, friends, I'm talking about the fads that pass and go,
you know, that everybody thinks is going to save the world
and then they turn out to be idiocy.
They turn out to be.
A commodity, friends.
What will my kids have to do to freak me out?
One more time.
What will the, I've got a little boy
who's going to be in the graduating class of 1998.
I can't follow your sign language.
We have a caller.
Oh, okay.
That's a good idea.
Let's try a caller real quick.
Before I tell you what's going to happen.
This one on off, right?
Yep.
Hello, dear friend.
Reverend Stank.
Yes.
How's it going?
We're barely alive, but the slack will be forthcoming
as soon as I get off the air.
Great.
As soon as you send, have you sent your money?
Well, I was planning on pledging some money,
but I've got a stipulation here.
Uh-huh.
Okay.
Now, you know Reverend Buck, right?
Yes.
Okay.
I'm afraid so.
We're going to have to get Reverend Buck
to stop talking about his khaki shirts and the Dick Army Corps.
It's like, I have decided that I'm going to give $98.
Me and this friend of mine named Darryl DeBuzz, right?
Yeah.
We have decided that we will give $98 a week
for the rest of our lives in addition to our left gonad
if we can get Reverend Buck to shut up.
You guys, you said your left gonad
as if you both of you only had one between you.
That's right.
The one left one.
Oh, God, that's quite a sacrifice.
No wonder he said left gonad.
This man is a leftist.
I'll tell you what, guy.
When you send your check,
I'll stop talking about the Dick Army Corps.
But for now,
Dick Army!
I command this radio station.
I command you in the name of the power of Bob Dobbs,
be gone demon.
What?
I hate that old demon.
That demon got to my mistress,
left her in the car with the motor running
and ate sleeping pills in her.
No, no, no.
I hate that old demon.
That demon.
I brought to buy shoes for the children.
Go ahead and put another tape on.
I went to buy shoes for the children.
And the demon got to me
and he put me into a strain in his mind.
And I woke up and the shoes was gone
and there was three empty liquor bottles
in the backseat of the car
and the shoes was stolen.
And I hate that old demon.
Friends, it's bad.
It's mighty bad.
There's demons everywhere
and there's only one demon.
There's only one way to get that demon out
and that's to pay him to leave.
The number to call,
823-8801.
It's open now.
Please fill that sucker up.
Yeah, right now there's nobody
has called in to pledge
and these are serious.
This is quite serious, friend.
I ain't going to put any more colors on right now.
Friends, like I said,
I was worried about
what are kids in the future
going to try to do to freak us out?
You know, what are they going to do
to freak me out?
It's going to take a lot.
And if we, friends,
if you look to your concordance
of the Book of the Subgenius,
Dateline for Dominance,
check out these predictions of Dobbs.
We'll see what Dobbs has to say
about the coming end times.
Now, for the year 1995,
we find a reference to teenage,
it says marijuana still not legalized,
a teenage, it says,
extreme back-to-nature movement
among teenagers.
Friends, reversion to animal behavior,
urinating in public
to mark off territorial boundaries,
sniffing for identification like dogs,
mating rituals, and so forth,
as if we didn't already have mating rituals, right?
And the broomstick worn in the nether areas
becomes a major teen fashion craze.
Rich kids stick that broomstick
in, hang heavy jewelry from them.
Poor kids hang heavy things.
This is our future teenagers, friends.
And if we turn furthermore
to Prescriptures 41 and 42,
I believe it is,
and I assume you'll be reading along with me, friends.
He says,
There shall be in the end hours
wonders in the sky.
The living spirit of Negi
will be upon thy sons and daughters
who shall fall down,
your young men shall see visions,
and thine old men shall take drugs
and shall dump.
I will be upon thy women
which shall bear rotten fruit
of their wombs.
Men shall rave in the streets,
speaking in tongues and prophesying,
for thou hast besmeared
the name of my son,
and therefore ye shall not die
when most fervently thou desireth death.
Nyahaha!
I, Jehovah One, thy God,
shall laugh at thee.
Now, friends,
these are grim predictions for the future.
And another one here,
Though thy oils and petroleum fail thee,
these my children shall possess it
and keep it from thee,
but they shall spread their elixirs
and medicines of the secret
and shall sell them unto thee
and unto thy children
and thy children's children
and shall curse thee
through their drunkenness,
for they are drunk with the food of the gods
and none may raise them from their stupor.
Friends, and that beautiful lyrical poetry
of the prescription,
which I think is a great example
refers to your failure
to pledge at least a tenth part
of your savings of this week to K-N-O-N.
Because, I mean,
you know, the devil weighs your worth
in cash, money spent, friends.
And if you've been spending money
for heavenly things like K-N-O-N,
keeping freedom on the air, why,
you'll get to go to subgenius hell.
And that's so much better.
It's so much better than most of the other heavens, friends.
Big joke.
You think it's a big joke, don't you?
Well, we're coming up on,
God, look at this, the ghostly radio station.
I don't understand it.
This is the people's temple.
The Pope of Chicago, Michael Flores, did this song.
This is called Day of the Exist.
And I'm willing to do aba-ly-haded
Well, yeah.
Like I, like I'm 120 years old.
I know, and produto positive.
You know, somebody was talking
about Atlantis up a mountain in India l Peace.
I don't like people's
Can you tell me what that is up above?
Have the exes finally come?
I think it's the end, my friend.
Here's where the nightmare begins.
You have no right to take my life.
You have no right to change my life.
Come on down here and fight, space man.
Well, I wanted E.T. or the Space Brothers.
Tell me how to survive.
But the aliens have...
come from hell up above.
And the world is about to die.
I gotta drive.
I gotta make sure.
I gotta make sure somebody survives.
I gotta drive.
As the song was sung,
the movement of a curtain,
a pen drops to the floor,
a puff of smoke,
a bell chimed,
A thing just came through the door
You had no right spaceman
To fly by and scare me
On this dark and lonely night
Come on down here and talk
Or we'll knock your ship out of the sky
And we'll make you cry
Eric Hosek, yes
He made it, he broke his way into the station, friend, just to tell you that
And if you don't send that phone call to 823-8801-823-8883
Or 823-7490
Then we're gonna kill this young man
But we won't do it on the air
If you pay us enough money, we will sacrifice
A living sacrifice to Wotan, Odin, Ra, Jehovah One
Whatever you want to call it
Whatever it is that likes to watch humans suffer
Why, we're gonna offer up this young man
As a living sacrifice
And the next week after that, another one, so
I want everybody who knows the sound of my voice
To call this station and give them all the money you have
Yeah, why not?
And why stop at money, friends?
Why not send your furniture, your house
The deed to your, just not the whole house
I mean, that's absurd, that's ridiculous
What we mean is, you know, the deed to your house
Your voter's card, your registration card
Your library card, your credit cards
And if not, if nothing else
At least you can spare, you can spare 50 bucks
I mean, there's some affluent
I don't know what's out there
Probably some of them are true subgeniuses
But let's see if, it's that, we gotta do it, friends
We gotta do it
We're dead
Howdy, friends, I'm Lord Jim Cravington
From Medieval Motors, your friendly truck stop
Of transportation in the Diet of Words
Friends, whether you're in the body or at the lunch
We've got the Gryphon, the Minotaur
Or the sporty little Camel Leopard
To suit your imaginary travel needs
And gosh, what can I say about these little guys
Yes, it's your all-new cardboard Vampirettes
The economy transport that's got them all guessing
On the other side
Well, we've got continents and peninsulas
Of new and used transfigurations
And a secret rose garden of perfect color
And a great variety of unique values
So get your ass in gear and your oxen in here
So as we can trade indulgences and get you on your path
Now, we're just a painful mile off the freeway of lost hope
At the intersection of Down and Out Avenues
In the Citadel of the Angel
How you doing?
A lot of the good old boys are here tonight
We'd like to welcome you down to the television mission
Don't forget, if all you can do is sit at home
Then try to keep yourselves awake
And dial the phone
Call in for pledges
Call in for pledges, yes
We have a lot of our special beauties answering the phones this evening
And the best thing you can do is dial this number that you see on your screen
As quickly as you can
With a contribution to the television mission
Don't forget to call in a pledge
Talk about Jesus
Well, you never know who's gonna be here this evening
We're waiting for you
Yes, well, it's one
I know you are, son
I know it's one of the real positive qualities
Of the television mission
Is we just never know who's going to drop by
I mean, it's a lot of folks have been
The band is here
The band is getting set up
The band is ready
And I'm here to tell you that it's time, ladies and gentlemen
I want you to hold down your applause as long as you can
Because it's time you heard from Red, Greenback and the Blue Boys
Don't forget to call
The number's on your screen
Then you suspended head on
All of my day
Your my life
And RSVP
spicier
mean
As my fathers pick up jokes
And I went home and I pissed on the roof
Why must I be your teenager on the roof?
If I don't cut the shit, it's bright to see
I'm gonna spend my life doing PCP
Each night I hang around with a bunch of thugs
Why must I be your teenager on the roof?
My boss says next time I get thrown in jail
I love my daddy, gotta throw no pound
Each night I ask the stars up above
Why must I be your teenager on the roof?
I wanna get wasted, I wanna get laid
Eat up my gold, I'll drive to the Cape
Don't get no results, I'm gonna go away
I wanna get wasted, I wanna get laid
Eat up my gold, I'll drive to the Cape
Next time, baby, two bucks
And I might take the shit
Oh, yeah
Yes, dear friends, that was the Dogmatics
with that beautiful song, Teenagers on Drugs,
which ties up our, I guess that just sort of says it all.
That's a band from Boston, and that's a really obscure record
called Mr. Beautiful Presents All Hard.
Friends, and this is Kano and the subgenius radio ministry,
Hour of Slack, signing off.
And I want you to make that one last pledge call, 823-7490.
And even when you're listening to the Monday morning show coming up,
when you pledge, say praise Bob and tell him you're pledging for the Hour of Slack anyway.
Right, Norm?
Sure.
And then we'll just write it down and we'll make any difference anyway.
And friends, if you really want to get your soul saved,
just write for information from Bob at P.O. Box 140306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
Praise Bob.
Stand erect for your own abnormality.
Bob is a way of life to millions, yet half of them don't even know it.
He's the one true living Slack master with the spiritual know-how
to help you bash through the locked doorway to financial heaven.
He is the one real shortcut to Slack.
Now see another dimension on your TV.
Yes.
Fear the stark fist of removal no longer.
Become physically attractive overnight.
Attain status, luck, prosperity by blowing them off.
Bob's promise is to widen the scope and nature of abnormal behavior,
to explore new ways of going over the edge and coming right back.
Plus, people bring back toys you couldn't make it on your own.
You give them.
To help you create the highest possible earnings from the psychodynamics of abnormalities.
To turn conspiracy and blinded personality disorders around.
And channel them into an illusion of creativity that will fool normals and get you sex.
Bob.
Oh, my God.
Now you stay on the right side,
and I'll stay on the left side.
Now let's see this feeling.
Oh, good.
Now we're far enough away that hopefully you won't get whatever it is.
I've got massive vitamin C here.
This is silly.
I've got a lot of vitamin C.
I've got orange juice.
I've got a brand-new box of Kleenex.
I'm ready to stay here for as long as it takes.
All right, now, people, what makes...
Get on the phone.
Get on them phones.
What makes Kano work?
What makes Kano in work?
Obviously not the same thing that makes your mouth work.
Okay, but the reason Kano in is on the air is because people like you that are listening,
they care enough about Kano in, send us money, and make it possible for us to be on the air.
It is time to...
We only do this three times a year.
Has it been three?
Last time it was like this.
First time we're doing it in 86.
We had a goal of 60,000 last year.
We hit 75.
I mean, last pledge drive.
We can do that again.
We need to hit 2,000 during this show.
We need...
We need $40 and $50 pledges, okay?
That's what we need.
If all you can afford is $20, I understand.
We need $40 and $50 pledges.
If you can afford $10 a month, it's what I've been doing.
Last pledge drive, I pledged $10 a month.
I give them $10.
I've already given them my March check, right?
Yeah.
Okay, I send them...
You did that on the air as a matter of fact.
Always.
I do that every month on the air.
I have my million-dollar checks sitting right here.
Yeah, well, get out of here.
Okay, now.
Okay.
Now.
Now, I've pledged $10 a month.
I believe in KNON.
I don't get paid to do this.
It's caused me money to do this, people.
Okay?
Sure.
People that have sent money, we'll talk to them.
Yeah.
Okay.
We'll do it.
Yeah, send them in here.
Yeah, if you want to give us money, we'll talk to you.
Okay, that's how we're starting this out.
Line one, hit it.
Line one.
Money.
Go ahead.
Oh, boy.
Well, he was real serious about pledging, huh?
Did he drink the pledge?
He drank the pledge.
He made a pledge.
Well, call him back.
Call him back.
See how he is.
Take care of this.
I'm going to...
The reason I told you about...
I'm going to cough and sneeze and do nice things like blow my nose a lot.
So, John is probably going to be doing a lot of the talking.
I'm going to disappear every once in a while.
I'll just take care of these nice, trivial things.
But...
Yeah.
Anyway, if you were watching television this week...
That's what I was going to mention.
Thank you.
If you were watching television this week on Heritage Cablevision, channel...
Was it channel 9 or channel 25?
One of the two.
Wherever Dallas Music Videos was live on Tuesday night, you would have seen what we look like.
The gorgeous faces of Norm Ward and John Horton.
Not necessarily in that order.
Anyway, we were on with Kathy Blaylock and Lee Tranchen of Dallas Music.
Videos who will be our guests next week on Monday morning.
So, think up your local kind of music questions for Kathy and Lee.
And plus, they'll probably have some information on...
If you're in a local band on how to get your video on Dallas Music Videos.
Anyway, they will be with us next week.
And we had a blast.
We interrupted them.
We kidnapped their music news coordinator.
We have a tape.
Everything we ever wanted to do on television.
We did.
Anyway.
So, the phone numbers to call for the...
Thank you.
The phone numbers to call to put in your pledge for KON.
It's that time of the year again.
It's money time.
Tax time is until April 15th.
This is money time.
823-7490.
823-8801.
823-8883.
Get on the phones now.
Take a look at this one.
You know, we could have all sorts of money come in here.
And we wouldn't phone for a first year.
Or we sound a lot better.
As in Harvey Pollack of Dallas, Texas.
Who...
Spam.
Spam?
Spam is on this record.
Harvey, no relation to spam, has given us $40.
$40.
Rosenberg.
Ponzi.
being on the air here.
I pledge $10 a month.
Like I said, if we reach 2,000,
if we can get 49 more people at $40
or 39 more people at $50,
if we reach 2,000, I'll kick in another 100.
So come on.
We need you to help us.
If you don't help, we won't be on the air.
823-749-0823, 8801,
and 823-8883.
Your turn.
It's Norm's money.
Make him spend it, huh?
That's right.
Anyway.
Speaking of money,
where's our log?
The money program.
Our log is being burned.
Yes.
There is nothing on the log you shipped.
Pledge drive.
Here's the log.
Money, money, money.
Here you go.
Wrong log.
That's the PSA.
Wrong one.
Yeah, it says pledge drive, all right.
It says pledge those dollars.
Big bucks.
Moolah.
Cash.
Cents.
Pounds.
Sterling.
Gold.
Money.
Lots of it.
Here.
Hit turntable two.
Bring it up.
Welcome to the money program.
Tonight on the money program, we're going to look at money.
Lots of it on film and in the studio.
Some of it in nice piles, others in lovely clunky bits of loose change.
Some of it neatly counted into fat little hundreds.
Delicate fivers stuffed into bulging wallets.
Nice, crisp, clean checks.
Purch pieces of copper coinage thrust deep into trouser pockets.
Romantic.
Foreign money rolling against the thigh with rough familiarity.
Beautiful wayward curlicued banknotes.
Fiddly, copper plating cheek by gel with tumbling hexagonal milled edges.
Rubbing gently against the terse leather of beautifully balanced bank books.
Sorry.
But I love money.
All money.
I've always wanted money.
To handle, to touch.
The smell of the rain wash florin.
The lure of the lira.
The glitter and the glory of the guinea.
The romance of the ruble.
The feel of the franc.
The heel of the deutschmark.
The cold, antiseptic sting of the Swiss franc.
And the sunburnt splendor of the Australian dollar.
I've got ninety thousand pounds in my pyjamas.
I've got forty thousand French francs in my fridge.
I've got lots of lovely lira.
Now the deutschmark's getting dearer.
And my dollar bills would buy the Brooklyn Bridge.
There is nothing quite as wonderful as money.
There is nothing quite as beautiful as cash.
Some people say it's folly.
But I'd rather have the lolly.
With money you can make a splash.
There is nothing quite as wonderful as money.
There is nothing like a newly minted pound.
Everyone must anchor for the bulgeness of a banker.
It's accountancy that wakes the world around.
You can keep your Marxist ways.
But it's only just a phase.
For it's money, money, money makes the world go round.
Money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money, money.
That's the Money Program.
This is what you're listening to.
KNON 90.9 FM.
Dallas, Fort Worth.
The voice of your pledge drive.
Yes, your pledge drive.
These people.
I have, Bruce, I don't know if you're listening right now.
Bruce Anderson in Plano plays last time.
And I must apologize.
I have not made good on my offers I have for the t-shirt.
And the tapes from last week.
I have them.
They will be in the mail tomorrow.
My apologies and thanks to Bruce Anderson and Plano.
Also, Karen Haynes down in East Dallas.
All right, what do we got here?
We got from Denton, Texas.
You ready for this, Pat Fielder?
This is a student at North Texas, people.
A student.
A $50 pledge.
Okay, now.
From a student.
A student at North Texas.
No pizzas for two weeks.
No kidding.
Ooh.
Now, at SMU, there'd be no pizzas for one week.
But that's a different story.
Okay, now.
Where are the guys at the Sigma Chi House at SMU?
New, huh?
What do you say, guys?
I know you're listening.
You don't have to pay off the house anymore.
That's right.
Brand new house, you know.
I think, no, Sigma Chi, no.
I'm sorry.
I meant Chi.
Sigma Chi.
My mistake.
Sigma, what did you say?
I said Sigma Chi.
Yes.
I meant Kappa Sig.
Ooh.
The guys at Kappa Sig are listening.
Forget your pledges from Kappa Sig.
Forget the guys.
No, forget the guys at Sigma Chi.
The guys at Kappa Sig are the ones that are listening.
Okay?
They live next door.
To the KAs, and we all know what the A stands for, right?
And it ain't Alpha.
All right.
Never mind.
That's a different story.
Pat Fielder in Denton, Texas.
$50 pledge.
All right.
A Monday morning t-shirt also for a $50 pledge.
They're going for $50.
Guys, put this on here.
Put a Monday morning shirt on here.
I'm going to have to make some more, but I'll do it.
Okay, so we got $50 for Denton.
Explain to the people what the Monday morning t-shirt is for those of us.
The Monday morning t-shirt says,
I listen to Monday morning with Norm Ward on 90.9.
Or KNO and 90.9 FM.
All right.
Aaron Hurd in Arlington.
Head.
Thank you.
That looks like an R.
Yeah.
Sure.
Okay.
Anyway.
Aaron.
Let's change this typo.
Okay.
Anyway, Aaron.
We appreciate your...
Support.
$30.