The Subgenius Hour of Slack!
Ah, yes dear friends, welcome to Hour of Slack number 1030.
Again, brought to you this time entirely by Reverend Susie the Fousey
and to WREK, the greatest station of Atlanta, Georgia.
And now, some of you may still remember Hurricane Katrina and New Orleans
and the horror and stupidity that made it such an exciting TV show for people who weren't there.
Well, Reverend Susie the Fousey did four episodes of Bob's Slacktime Funhouse on Hurricane Katrina,
of which this is the second, Hell and High Water.
In which Susie actually does take us to Hell.
Louisiana's got fun and fun people, like in the mouth of the river.
We've got probably the most fun people of the state.
Before you go farther, be aware that now you are in this, the second ring.
Look well, for here one sees things which in words would be incredible.
No way. You were just kidding.
Right?
I am where all light is mute.
With a bellowing like the ocean, turbulent in a storm of warring winds,
the hurricane of Hell in perpetual motion torments them.
And now, I can hear the notes of agony in sad crescendo beginning to reach my ear.
Now, I am where the noise of lamentation comes at me in blasts of sorrow.
Long before the Superdome.
Where the saints of football play.
Lived a city that the damned call home.
Here their hellish Rondelet.
New Orleans.
Home of pirates, drunks, and whores.
Taki, overprice, souvenir stores.
If you want to go to Hell, you should take that trip to the Sodom and Gomorrah on the Mississippi.
New Orleans.
All right, I'll go to Hell!
For a starter, I'll steal Jim out of slavery again.
And if I can think of something worse, I'll do that too.
Because as long as I'm in, and in for good, I might as well go whole hog.
I think we're like big.
Oh, it's real.
It's real now.
It's real.
Yee!
I said hey, hey, hey, yeah.
Well, come on everybody, take a trip with me.
Hey!
All right!
Down to Mississippi, down to New Orleans.
Hey!
Hundreds of them growing on a hundred-cell plant.
Oh, yeah.
And I know it's growing there all the time.
All right, all right, all right, all right.
Every southern belle is a Mississippi queen.
Down to Mississippi, down to New Orleans.
Hey!
Yeah!
All right!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
Yeah, all right.
See you, Clark, burn down lots of entreprises.
Today will be an all-nighter for somezers, nighties, da Zhin.
We can't, exactly.
What kind of videography are we doing tonight?
I don't know.
I don't think it's going to be any better.
The very foundations of civilization are beginning to crumble under the dread assault of that horror long feared.
President Adolf Bush.
Eptom horrible bone-chilling news!
What is it?
Nothing.
New Orleans is a full-blown disaster.
Yes.
A terrible thing's happened.
Oh my God!
Call a brief!
There's no point in acting all surprised about it.
All the planning charts and demolition orders have been on display at your local planning department in Alpha Centauri for 50 of your Earth years.
So you've had plenty of time to lodge any formal complaints.
For the sake of mankind.
But it's part of the latest part making a fuss about it now.
I'm sorry, but if you can't be bothered to take an interest in local affairs, that's your own problem.
Well, this was a great stop to me.
Wednesday morning.
I'm sorry.
In the middle of the sea lies a wasteland.
A wasteland.
I wonder if it comforts him.
I appreciate that a lot.
But now must lie deserted like some worn thing by time decayed.
We have 22, 24, 26 feet of water in the metropolitan area.
Oh my God!
Ah, heck.
Where am I going to get a Danish?
Brandt!
No organ.
Come on, came to be heard?
Give me a hand.
Was there anything he might want to wonder about?
Yes, I know it is.
Additionally, you guys went on a vuelo on 01 August.
It seems there would be some kind of technology about that.
You fairy fucking martians game?
I'll call for martial law in the city of New Orleans.
This thing was going to blow wide open last night.
It's awful down here, man.
This is ridiculous.
I got a headlock, brother, and my life is a mess.
It feels like behind the door is poking through my chest.
Oh, baby!
And we don't have the manpower to adequately deal with.
We can only form a perimeter around them and hope to God that we're not overrun.
You know it looks like, tastes like, smells like, babies like hair tie.
So right now it's pretty much like New Orleans right now has just wiped off the face of the earth.
Therefore, I judge it best that you should choose to follow me, and I will be your guide away from here and through an eternal place to hear the cries of despair and to behold tormented spirits as they lament in chorus the second death they must abide.
Oh, baby!
But these were of a mode more bitter, for among the river were flames on every side bathing her borders.
Smoke them if you got them.
Oh, my.
You know, man, let me tell you something.
But it feels good, do it.
Burn the place to the ground.
Smoke on the water.
Fire in the sky.
Hit it.
They burned down the gambin' house.
It died with an awful sound.
A funky chicken was a-runnin' out.
Pullin' kids out the ground.
When it all was over, we had to find another place.
A Swiss town was runnin' out.
It seems that people lose the race.
Smoke on the water.
Fire in the sky.
The Warhead!
Help! Help us!
God dang old die man, this is old die!
Great!
Everything was going wrong.
So with slow steps we perverse that place of night.
Through rain and shades commingled once or twice beginning in the future life.
And so I said, Master these torments tell me will they increase after the judgment or lessen or nearly endure burning as much as now?
He said, I don't know.
Well I've been down to the pain and sorrow of good tomorrow's coming in.
But I put my pole to the river bottom.
And I've got to hide some place to find myself again.
So look out for me, oh muddy water.
You're Mr. Freeze, Parky Batwise.
And I've got a need for throwing some fish.
And I've got a need to climb upon your back and ride.
Meanwhile, far below the earth's surface,
422 are confirmed dead as federal hazmat teams force to clear the area.
While I was ruining myself, back down to the deep, someone appeared.
Okay, who's the head honcho here?
Huh? Who are you?
Me? Why I'm just a gun-toting weather girl.
What are you doing here? This is a climate control station.
What do you want from us?
I want you to make it rain.
Rain? But why?
Let's see.
You know, she became so hostile.
You couldn't depend on her just to pull off a job and then split.
You know, she'd always have to stick around and rough them up.
But she didn't used to be such a monster.
Lots of fun inside.
That's what she said! Woo!
Dark, accursed torrent eternally poured with changeless measure of nature.
Enormous hail and tainted water mixed with snow are showered steadily through the shadowy air of hell.
The soil they drench gives off a putrid odor.
You're not exactly smelling like roses either.
The water was purple black. We followed its current down a strange passage.
This dismal watercourse descends the grayish slopes until its torrent discharges into the marsh whose name is Styx.
Styx? I just heard them on the King Biscuit Flower Hour.
This club better be worth it.
Soon their course shifted and the merciless weather battered them towards us.
I called against the wind.
Oh, wearied souls, if another does not forbid, come speak with us.
Bob, I'm all turned around. Can you tell me how to get back to the road?
No way. It's fun because it's true.
Well, I'm so low, I want to fly the sea.
Crying for your kiss.
Oh, darling, must it end?
Like this, like this, like this, the lonesome waters.
Keeps reminding me that my arms are empty.
By the Lord.
You can stay here alone and watch what happens to this purgatory.
I'll be at the bridge that links earth to the heavens.
What did you mean by this?
I don't know.
Where is he taking me?
To his underwater palace. Just kidding, it's a lagoon full of bugs.
He's truly mad.
Where in the world did he come from?
Beast.
Beast?
These are the souls in anger over Canaan's son.
You know also that under the water are found others whose sighing makes these bubbles come
that pop the surface everywhere you look.
What we don't see is what's scary because of what's in the water, the metals, the poisons.
Under the water, you can't see it.
They have no idea where it's going, have no idea what's going on.
Any scientist will tell you he has no idea.
Lodged in the slime, they say,
Once we were grim and sullen in the sweet air above that took a further gladness from the play of sun.
Hey! Hey!
They can't see you. Conserve your energy.
I'm getting so tired. I'm just gonna close my eyes for a minute and stay awake.
Hey man, I did it, man. I broke off a dang old propeller, man.
Why'd you do that?
There's gasoline everywhere.
I don't know, man.
Well, smoke them if you got them.
Let's smoke on that water, man.
If anybody's gonna do it, Fernandez is gonna fight it.
Smoke!
Hey guys, there's an island!
Holy crap!
The island of the woods!
The island of the lands!
The island of the land!
Send me to the sun!
Send me to the land!
What the hell is this?
You've gotta be kidding me.
It's a bad joke.
I'm out on the interstate
No! No! No!
Out in the dusty desert winds
I'm out on the interstate
She goes looking for a friend
She sees the light around the bend
I'm out on the inner state
I can hear a soft voice calling
Calling to bring my good times
I understand how the anxiety people can grab
So there is frustration
But I want people to know there's a lot of help coming
This is a public service message from people
Well, that's life in the 21st century for you
You just have to learn to accept it
Damn you!
Where I come from we don't hold traditional woman
You're looking to get a nice big cross turned on your lawn
Excuse me
But emotionally disturbed
She's from Alabama
You won't forget
How could I?
I look for the first lawn with a burning cross
Reflect and try and come up with better strategies
My biggest flaw in my opinion was to basically assume that
If I got everyone up to a high place and safe and out of the water
Then the cavalry would come in two to three days and they didn't come
And reminding him
You know that a strategy has been the murder of US citizens
How do you know?
Well, he's a f***er, that's how I know
Nobody's coming to get us
Try to be patient
Federal and state help is on the way
We'll be ready for you when you're ready
This is the FEMA radio news service
Try to be patient
Federal and state help is on the way
Dead bulls*** man
Whatever
Ding
Today was out of sight, out of sight
Temperatures today range from about 56 where you are to 450
Wooo!
That's where I am
Throughout the day we had this green, purplish, diagonal thunder
That was shooting all around here
Well, y'all should have dug it
We're going away this weekend, you know, have a good trip
Wooo!
That's green!
But while we're killing time we might as well soak up some rays and catch some fish
Oh, well alright
Now we must fake the Hulk, see if they bite
Pull them in
Woke up this morning
I wanted to cry
Then I remember
Yes, I knew why
She a real good one for having the cake
I'm gonna go fishing or jump in the lake
Yes, I'm gonna go fishing
Mmm, that's what I'll do
I'll think about nothing
Not even you
Catch a real big one, a big speckled trout
Snappin' in the water, I'll pull him on out
I wonder if I'll ever see a stream full of fish again
Where'd you ever see a stream full of fish in Ireland?
At the movies
Oh, here in the water
Ooh, look at him shine
There goes a big one
Okay, fish
Mmm, that one is mine
Whoa! Holy mackerel!
Cast out the reel now, I got the feel now
Snapper goes my fly rod, I'll catch me a trout
Ah, what a fish!
The dead channel one rose a beam coated with mud and addressed me
You!
Are you deaf or what?
His eyes found a man
Who had given himself to the river
Who let the flow of the river carry him away
Hey, what gives?
The general flow pattern is for things that are in the landfill
To become liquefied by rain
And to leave the landfill and go into the nearby water that we all care about
That is true
Woohoo!
Oh my god!
Oh!
We're doomed
Then I could feel the terror begin to ease
That churned in my heart's lake all through the night
Ah, good times
As one still panting ashore from dangerous seas looks back at the deep he has escaped
Lake George
My thought returns still fleeing
To regard that grim defile that never left any alive who stayed in it
Don't worry, Mr. Ulrich, we'll get you to the hospital
Right?
Oh!
He!
Oh, gee!
Oh, yeah, right
So at once I understood beyond all doubt that this was the dreary guild
Of repellent both to God and his enemies
Hopeless ones, never alive
Their bare skin galled by wasps and flies
Blood trickling down the face
Mingling with tears for harvest underfoot by writhing maggots
I am not especially anxious to mingle
We've been out here for days
So help me, I'm gonna slug you
I'm starving
Dick, y'all gonna have a gassy day tomorrow
It's gonna be sunny
It's gonna be blind
It's gonna start with the sun coming up in the east like a big yellow ball
Then it's gonna get bigger and bigger
And then it's gonna envelop the whole universe with love
Love, y'all, love!
No problem
Oh, my youth!
So while we're killing time we might as well soak up some rays
What a...
That was my very favorite song
So monstrously huge
The sun comes out
Twice a day
I cannot move
I can't get away
Him with his pants on fire
So long ago
When my life was young
I did not know
The dangers of the sun
And I'm steering
Steering
At the sun
I couldn't breathe
Still today
I can't see
For everyone
I cross all the miles
Facing black and green
The horizon is so bright
icide
A child's call
For his mother
What upsets
And shouts
Tens of
Cont案
A À
Aah
Argh
something so beautiful and now uh having a veritable sewer you know what i think i think
this place is jinxed let's get out of here get out of here what's the best way out of here
master i said it seems by this dim light that all of these are eager to cross over
can you tell me by what law and who they are do you know
well it might be a lady or a girl with a baby a man on a bike a boy with a kite a kid with a puppy
a girl with a bunny a guy with a smile someone running a mile a stranger is anyone whoever you
are i have always depended on the kindness of strangers
i won't look at everything
you
nobody's coming together everybody's probably
i can hear yourself
nobody's coming everybody's probably for god's sake shut up and send me somebody
children are laughing
in the city
i count their voices one by one
the bridge that links earth to heaven that's great i need to get out of here
well there's my ride then came skimming across the water
skiff guided by a single boatman of the house
welcome aboard the ship of lost souls
the name in the bag is honey bunch yeah i've been meaning to paint over that
take me in the lifeboat take me in the lifeboat it will stand raging storm
take me in the lifeboat
it won't fire my spirit home
you'll have us in your boat only as long as it takes to cross the bend
oh whatever
she boarded the boat it bobbed without a sign of being laden until it carried my weight
as soon as we embarked the ancient crowd turned swiftly from shore
made a deeper cut into the water than it was worth to do with others
then when i turn my eyes farther along our course i could make
making out people upon the shore of some great river.
We are hard beset by the enemy whose power grows ever mightier.
Only the river now lies between us and the dark powers of Mordor.
Now come and meet the rest of the dam.
Did I mention their lost souls?
Well, actually you did.
Truly, I should like to see that spirit pickled in this swill
before we've made our way across the lake.
Hear, hear!
Before we see the shore, you will be satisfied.
For what you seek is pity.
Come, stranger. Join our circle of infamy.
Tell us your story of ennui.
Water, water everywhere.
Another drop to drink.
What's that?
It's a poem.
The first poem you learn in high school.
What's high school?
It's where you should be.
It's where you learn things.
Say what?
How bogus.
You're disgust even me.
Well, yeah, I know.
The last time I trust the strangest people on earth.
He sobbed and he sighed
And a gurgle he gave
Then he plunged himself into the billowy wave
And an egg he ate
And an echo arose
From the suicide's grave
Oh, willow, tit willow, tit willow
Swept to the bottom of the briny deep
Swallowed whole by the treacherous, unforgiving sea
Sank, I guess, would be the one thing to take away from this part of the seminar.
It's much too early to determine...
What happened out on that lake.
Just the people that were out on the boat were taking as many people they could out of the water.
And they were even some of the people who were rescuing the people out on the lake were very shaken and crying and stuff because of what they had seen out there.
What's going on?
My old man always used to say,
When a ship goes out to sea, either it keeps sailing or it sinks.
There's nothing else.
Ain't that ironic?
Uh-huh.
Well then, laugh.
Laugh a little more.
It's nothing to laugh about!
It progressed into the deep, dug moats that circled near the walls of that bleak city which seemed cast of solid iron.
Lead, mercury, arsenic, cadmium, a whole array of toxic chemicals.
Chemical plant across the street
Leaves of steam that colors our white sheets
It's been happening for years
Now I'm crying rainbow tears
One day my dog went out to play
He said, I was gray
He came back colored yellow
The chemical man said, stay mellow
It happens all the time
Now Scotty's skin is slime
We focused in our report, at least on kind of the southern Louisiana coast,
the Mississippi Sound, dredge material, and sewage sludge.
We looked at a lot of sewage sludge, farm runoff, something else.
Oh, that is funny.
Let's wampum!
Attention jet skiers, I have a court order here requiring you to vacate these waters.
No court order is gonna tell me what to do.
Oh, man, it's notarized.
Let's boogie!
Okay.
We journeyed on to complete an immense circuit before we reached at last a place where the boatman shouted...
And if you look off the left side of the ship, you'll see a bunch of homosexuals.
How awful.
Not at all amusing.
I'll have to leave if this package raid continues.
Fanny bandits.
In such poor taste.
Now get out, here is the entrance.
Come on, get out of here.
Graham, on your way.
We came to a tower's base.
Now the fun begins.
Through me you enter into the city of worlds.
Through me you enter into eternal pain.
Through me you enter the population of loss.
Abandon all hope, you who enter here.
Okay.
Well, that was worth the eight year boat ride.
Probably should ignore that.
It's in Revelations, people!
Sounds like a wager to me.
I'll take a piece of that.
Look!
Watch a broken and living,
Obey, obey,
Who was there to save you?
Come on in!
Well, I guess this story has a happy ending after all.
Just like that last one, son.
Ha ha ha, ho ho ho, and a couple of tra-la-la.
And through the gate entering without delay,
there was a great dispute.
Uh, see, uh, reverend,
are we gonna get a chance to do any fishing?
Oh, I'm afraid not.
Yeah, I'm leaving.
Me too.
Come on!
Hey!
Where do you think you're going?
To Baton Rouge.
Gracious!
I should bust a cap in your ass.
Sometimes you made me enter within this dome,
which is the lowest and darkest place ever.
Do you know where it is?
No idea.
Excellent.
It's all going to place.
you'll backpedal to the lower depths of the travesty
getting the hard-won treatment and my own orders i command you to see for yourself
a seething string of torment and revulsion hangs over you an orgy overweight with immorality
will scandalize you yeah what's the matter with that by giving this country over to them
what's had no hand in the fighting for it why because they come off a boat crawling
with lice and begging you for soup oh my anyway
and then i heard them nailing shut the door into that fearful tower a pounding came from the
barber hearing that noise i stared into my
children's faces not speaking to them beside me i was turned to stone so hard i could not weep
the children wept
and my little anselma peering at me inquired father what ails you
and still i did not cry nor did i answer all that day and night
until the next sun dawned stay tuned for an urgent public safety message from fema
pets are not allowed into emergency shelters this has been a public service message from fema
oh
unbelievable he answered you read the deadly inscription that he
bought what are you talking about man oh i don't know man hey wait a minute oh yeah
the super dome that's the damn call home farthest from the heaven whose dome encloses
everything in creation oh that
oh
wow
,
wow,
awesome !
wow symphony
?
what
wow
down
in
Brotherhood from sea to shining sea
Hi kids, this is Fishbone Fred.
We live in America, the land of the free,
but that doesn't mean that we're free to do anything we want.
We all have rules to live by.
Listen closely to these safety rules I'm going to sing about
so you can live safely in our land of the free.
The songs you're about to hear will help keep you safe
by giving you knowledge to spot dangerous situations
and teach you where to turn for help.
America, America
From sea to shining sea
This is a public service message from FEMA.
I'd be a doggo.
Yeah, that's what you'd think.
Wednesday was
Thursday
is also safe
Remember that stuff we used to eat a long time ago?
Oh, I don't know, man.
What'd they used to call it?
What did they call it?
I don't know.
Oh, yes, I know.
Food.
Do you like oysters?
What the hell are you talking about?
No, that's food for four.
This must be Thursday.
I never could get the hang of Thursdays.
On this particular Thursday,
things were moving quietly through the ionosphere
many miles above the surface of the planet.
That, uh, anybody who...
Great one.
Who lies disdainful?
And scowling.
Seeming to pay no heed.
President of an Eastern land syndicate.
It's great.
Just great.
A couple of million dollars in oil under that lake
and you stand by and let your stupid brother raise fish in it.
We all know this is an agonizing time for the people of the Gulf Coast.
Yeah.
Boy, I think they really miscalculated.
So word for word my master spoke.
And I asked him for the food to fill the appetite with these words in his spine.
And of course, it answered,
God the Creator has by his mercy made me such that I cannot make you suffer.
that I cannot feel what you suffer.
None of this fire assails me.
Probably not much of it.
Why can't you be a little more supportive?
Because I don't care, okay?
I can't make an interest in this,
and I'm an expert at making an interest in your kooky project.
What kooky project?
You know, the first date thing.
Oh, this is an outrage!
Truly cruel you are.
Uh, that's reality.
George sneered and attempted bravery.
And if not now, then when do you shed a tear?
The children wept.
I would have done everything in my power to kill the American people.
I thought he was going to die laughing.
And you heard what we have been hearing for 15 months.
Now you know what we're up against.
But you tell me over and over and over again,
my friend,
how you do.
I don't believe we're on the eve of destruction.
Don't you understand what I'm trying to say?
Can't you feel the fears I'm feeling today?
If the button is pushed, there's no running away.
There'll be no one to save with the world in a grave.
Take a look around you, boys.
It's bound to scare you, boy.
And you tell me over and over and over again,
my friend,
how you don't believe we're on the eve of destruction.
The issue isn't whether you're paranoid, Lenny.
The issue is whether you're paranoid enough.
Huh?
Hey, nothing means nothing, man.
You know that.
Look around.
The whole planet's in total chaos.
The day of reckoning is upon us.
You gotta get what you can, while you can,
because some few curtain come put a 22
in the back of your head any second.
Meanwhile...
Take your glasses off.
Oh, no, you haven't.
How do you like that quick thing?
You're on her side now for all I've done for you.
Who the hell's one of you done for me?
I warned you.
I didn't vote for Bush.
Well, I'm not...
I'd be grateful for that.
Oh, I'm true.
We are getting nothing back here what you deserve.
And one of the girls a dick goes to death.
I hate you.
I hate everybody.
And I can't emphasize it enough, man.
This is crazy.
I've got 15 to 20,000 people over at the convention center.
It's bursting at the seams.
We...
It's...
It's awful down here, man.
Anxious to learn what their condition was,
we populate a fortress so guarded.
I cast my eye around as soon as I was there.
And saw a great plain filled with woe and torment.
Sounds of woe so great,
those within surely suffered horrible pain.
Master, I said,
who are these people that are shut and separated
within these coffins of stone,
making their sounds anguished from inside?
He answered,
know much about purgatory.
What?
It's a place between heaven and hell
where those who are not purgatory are.
Where those who are left behind,
unable to get into heaven,
continue to suffer.
A place of struggle and pain.
In other words,
the world that we're in now.
Wow.
That's it?
There are 30,000 inside this sphere alone.
Open it up and they start to replicate.
I was raised in a very similar establishment myself.
Now everything you see belongs to me,
for one degree or another.
The beggars and newsboys and quick thieves here in paradise,
the sailor dives and gym mills and blind tigers on the waterfront,
the anglers and amusers,
the sheehees and the chinks.
Everybody owes, everybody pays, because...
What?
That's how you stand up against the rising of the tide.
That right boy is a pair of the thread.
That's bulls**t, man.
You can't scare colored peoples no more.
Yeah!
Times changing.
Colored peoples took enough horse s**t already.
You ain't pounding no more on.
These people, you know, who have been called refugees,
on TV are not refugees.
They're Louisianians, they're Americans of cities.
They're American citizens.
And it's gonna require American response.
It's gonna require the federal government and the American people
to step up to the plate and allocate resources to do this.
Louisiana isn't a state in isolation.
The last time I checked, we were partied.
It's all undertaken from you.
Get back here, you jackals!
It smells awful.
My stomach is beginning to churn.
You wanna go back on the street?
Thank God my mustache filters out some of the stench.
My olfactory is all over the place.
It's already beginning to send out stress signals.
This was not supposed to be a shelter.
This was the last thing we had.
We don't have anybody but the red front.
This is police.
We're running this whole operation.
What we got in here, they started treating us like we was inmates.
You know what I'm saying?
We got rifle guns, passing out food with guns on the side of them.
They had...
We trying to go through the pay phone.
They're telling us we can't use the pay phone.
We can go one by one.
You got about 50 million people in here and you're telling us one by one we gotta go to the pay phone.
It's kind of difficult with people who don't understand that there is no place to go.
They wanna go home, but there is no home for some of these people.
This is stagnation of the masses.
We got revenge no questions asked.
To pay out.
All these questions and aspirations.
God's increasing desperation.
In a breathing stigma of rock and roll.
Bramble of dead and faces of living souls.
Oh vengeance of God, how much should you be feared by all of those who read what my eyes saw.
It was a great assemblage of naked souls in herds.
All of whom mourned most miserably.
No!
The old man and people living on your ceiling, and the people living underneath your feet.
People living to the left and to the right, they're all watching different television channels at the same time.
This tribune is breathing back.
Master, what people are these whose pain has overcome?
I will make brief answers.
They have no hope of death
For the blind life so abject
They envy any other fact
To all memory of them
The world is death
Mercy and justice disdain
Let us not speak of them
Look and pass on
It looks like
Tastes like
Smells like
Weathers like
It's my
It looks like
Tastes like
Smells like
Weathers like
Hell time
You know it
Look and like
Tastes like
Smells like
Weathers like
Hell
Some lay upon the ground
Super
Some sat hunched up
While others walked restlessly about
But it was they
Who breathed
With joy
In the tunnels most loosened by pain
What do you mean you lost him?
Oh my god, that's his lucky red hat!
He's a bug!
My boy's a bug!
Damn you!
A bug!
If you need any help with the coffin, call me
FEMA will be ready for you when you're ready
I'm a knuckle, what a lie!
What do you really mean by that?
I don't know!
I don't know, I'm just a little confused!
Hey, is that your sister?
Ahhhh!
Wow!
Hey, you want to keep her in the league, man?
She's crazy!
It's like a M of pain
But with more dirt and rain
Check out the tombstone bullet to the young blood stain
It's a shame but nobody ever loved me
Nobody ever cared for me
I said it looks like, tastes like, smells like, it feels like hell
What's happening?
The country stands with you.
What a bad joke.
George Bush doesn't care about black people.
You're wrong on that.
He was almost totally unaware of their presence.
Are black people invisible to you, you racist bastard?
Yes.
He looked straight through them.
They went unnoticed for all these years.
Gracious.
Hey, now you get me.
Whoa.
I see that you've wisely decided to hire a particularly terrifying negro
to protect you against your enraged and cheated customers.
What's this?
I see a mouthful and I can't hear a word you say.
Look at those dark glasses.
All his system is swimming in dope.
I wasn't swimming yesterday.
Diving from my gun.
I got a little water in my ear.
You, uh, you guys know I have no problem with black people, right?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, I don't know.
You did say you hated Crookland.
Hey, you.
Get me out of here.
Get me the hell out of here.
Get the hell back in there.
Ah!
So well and good for sheep, but what are we to do?
What am I going to do about it?
Laments at first were so loud, resounding through starless air, I began to weep.
Strange language, horrible screams, words imbued with rage or despair.
Cries as of troubled sleep or of a tortured shrillness.
They rose in a coil of tumult.
Along with noises like the slap of beating hands, all fused in a ceaseless flail that
frenzies that dark and timeless air like sand in a world.
Trap!
I'm trapped!
What did I do to deserve this?
Painted myself into a corner.
No windows, doors or a ladder.
Trap!
I'm trapped!
Trap like mice or rats.
Ah!
This is a public service message from FEMA.
I hope the media isn't making it a bigger thing than perhaps it is.
Every time they see something and they go out and say,
I'm glad they started filming it and that's what we get to see.
I hope this isn't being created beyond what it really is.
This is the FEMA Radio News Service.
That's right. Don't hurt them right away.
We'll let them think about it a little first.
Trap!
I'm leaving.
Your henchman has terrified me completely.
I shall never make the mistake of even passing by this vile pigsty.
Oh no you won't!
You're gonna stay here!
I have no idea what they're doing, but I will tell you this.
You know, God is looking down on all this.
Ah, this sure ain't no good.
And if they are not doing everything in their power to save people,
they are gonna pay the price.
Whatever it costs, we will pay.
No, for that heavy period between the lines.
We will die in the time it's found out.
Because every day that we delay, people are dying.
See, I believe out of this terrible evil can come some great good.
And they're dying by the hundreds, I'm willing to bet you.
Mourn for the dead, and forget when they hung up.
It was the voice of a man to whom history will give enormous credit.
That's good satire.
God, we're lucky in this country.
We've had so many blessings.
President Nod.
Away from me, loser.
Meanwhile, far below the Superdoll,
called hunger's tower after me, where yet others will be closed up.
It smells terrible in here.
Well, what do you expect?
The human body, when confined, produces certain odors which we tend to forget in this age of deodorants and other perversions.
I woke up before dawn, hearing the complaint of my own children,
who were with me there.
Funny, funny smell.
Whimpering in their sleep, and asking for bread.
That's what she said!
You grieve already,
for truly cruel you are.
As you think of what my heart began to dread.
The children,
they were awake now.
The hour when food was usually brought us drawing near.
When one speaks,
a small ray found its way into our prison,
and I made out in their four faces the image of my own.
I bit my hands for grief.
When they saw that,
they thought I did it for my hunger's pain,
and suddenly rose,
Father, our pain,
they said, will lessen if you eat us.
You are the one who clothes us in this wretched place.
We plead for you to be the one
who strips it away.
I calmed myself to grieve them less.
We stayed silent through that,
and then the following day.
Leave on Friday.
I get down on my knees.
And I pray,
and I pray,
showing up.
Lord, I pray.
I pray,
Lord!
You've been eating my legs!
Yes, see, now this is why I didn't say anything.
I knew you were going to get like this.
What the hell is wrong with you?
You've been eating me!
Okay, you know what, let's just agree to disagree.
degree. When we had reached the fourth day, Gado lay stretched at my feet where he had fallen down.
Dying tickles.
It is a field where Spidey used to play until on the warden number 42 was dumped in it one day.
I think it's so funny. I laugh until I cry. Just me and I.
But we'll need some liquid persuasion.
Do a puppy cook. I never. I never eat canned food. Canned food is a perversion.
I suspect that it is ultimately very damaging to the soul. Where'd you get it? Well, I acquired
it legally. You can be sure of that. Oh, yeah, right. Come on. Who's this?
I'm glad you get it. Don't make me come over there. This wretched bush.
Snacks. Hey, is it just me or am I picking up some negative vibes out there?
He didn't touch it, did he? No. Great. I did once and I could feel my intestine starting to atrophy.
God's sake, you can pull the lid off your own can of pudding. Fine, I will.
Father.
Why don't you help me, said Luke, and died.
We have a place for babies like you. The box.
One by one I watched the others fall till all were dead. And I, already going blind,
groped over my brood, calling to them, though I had watched them die. And then the hunger
had more power.
Ah, and even sorrow had to over me.
Ow!
Die!
It's too doggone late.
Yeah, my butt's so mad, it feels like coagulating. I'm sitting here just contemplating. I can't
twist the truth. It knows no regulation when human respect is disintegrating. And you tell me,
that you're in pain.
I bleep.
I Yep, now you feel the pain when you think,
Where we at?
We on the prairie.
That ain't our county.
What's your Аnes, man?
I've been looking for you you eitherлен air of business or schools.
We're not talking about anything.
All the mysenizers' business.
I'm afraid I'm there.
We're quick to say the least. All this truth period. We won't give you drama. We're running. I was in the PH from cow. A lot of cotton flies into my sewage간.
Sounds like a...
So do it.
Either f*** or get off the pond.
And f*** he did.
Sitting in the morning sun.
Where is the beast?
I'll be sitting when the evening comes.
There is nothing happening.
Watching the ships rolling in.
And these goddamn ships that are coming.
Then I'll watch them roll away again.
I don't see them.
They're not here.
Sitting on the dock of the bay.
There is BS.
Come on, man.
Watching the tide roll away.
And they're feeding the public a line of bull.
Sitting on the dock of the bay.
And it's spinning.
Wasting time.
And people are dying down here.
I left my home in Georgia.
I am just...
I'm at the point now where it don't matter.
Nothing to feel for.
People are dying.
Look like nothing's gonna come my way.
They don't have homes.
They don't have jobs.
Sitting on the dock of the bay.
The governor's problem?
I don't know whether it's the president's problem.
Watching the tide roll away.
But somebody needs to get their ass on a plane.
Sitting on the dock of the bay.
And figure this out.
Wasting time.
Right now.
Lickety's Quick.
You have been listening to Hour of Slack number 1030.
Which this particular time was really a two-month-old Bob's Slack Time Funhouse.
By Reverend Susie the Flusy on Atlanta's WREK.
Which is always on and streaming from WREK.org.
For morons of the Church of the Subgenius.
See www.subgenius.com