Hey
Who's that?
Bob?
Totally lacking in sympathy or imagination
the modern racketeer
Psychologists say that such character can frequently be traced back to
The Self-Genius
Power of
SWAT
CREED
Hey
Weee
We bought him away
In the White House, the mighty White House
The liar tweets tonight
In the West Wing, the self-obsessed wing
Ah, ah
Hush you doctors, hush reporters
Hush you science nerds
Look my ratings are through the roof!
Hush you science nerds!
When I just say happy words
Ah, ah
John A. Sondheim
The Night King
Everyone can get a test
It's just the flu
It's a hoax like all the rest
A left-wing coup
We've got lots of pee pee
The cupboards bare
It's Obama's fault you see
The buck stops there
In the country, the quiet country
No nurses sleep tonight
But in the White House
The of shite house
The liar tweets tonight
Ah, ah
We are in the way
We, he, our
We are in, the way
We're in, the way
We're in the way
We, we, the way
We,we, the way
Stay to including
We, we, the way
This is the darkness.
These are the days
when the shadows
hid in human hearts
step out of the haze
and stand like blots of ink
in the bright of the day.
And the light can't chase them away.
This is the darkness.
Where is the sun?
You've traded your god of light
for one with a gun.
Empathy, justice, and mercy
only for once.
He deems to be the chosen.
This is the darkness.
This is the plague.
This is the embodiment
of all we have made.
Greed, personification,
heat in a suit and a tie.
A corpse searching for his bride.
This is the darkness.
These are the times
when you must decide
where you stand,
which side of the line.
Who you're gonna believe,
what you're gonna define.
For he will bend the truth
to fit your fears and absolutes
and it will leech into your soul,
pollute your mind.
This is the darkness
Where is the light?
It must still be up there somewhere
But you might be right
It might be days, weeks, and months
Of this long polar night
But I believe there's more of us
Than them
And prodigals return again
And scales can fall from clouded eyes
And moons can set
And suns can rise
And swords be hammered into plows
And all that crap
But this is now
This is now
And this is the darkness
This is the darkness
And Alec Baldwin
And here's the thing
Alec Baldwin
And the thing
Come back on mic anytime, Mouse Gang
Oh, thanks, Dr. Falk
I almost forgot
That last song was
Bob Walkenholz
This is the darkness
Brand new
From his Patreon page
Although he said
This hit was for free
So I can play it on the radio
Pretty damn somber
And old Bob is starting to sound
Even more scratchier voiced than I am
Although I like to think
He's just taking advantage
Of the high pollen count
Which is also affecting my voice
We're only about a month apart in age
But the cheery song
Before that
The Liar Tweets Tonight
Was by Roy Zimmerman
And on the same basic subject
Uh, yeah
Some of us miss our country
Okay, so I'm gonna do
Something different this episode
Actually, I probably did it before
But in 1984
What happened is
I pulled out my CD
Of the first two Oingo Boingo albums
Which were among my absolute faves
In the 1980s
For reasons that'll soon be obvious
If you're unfamiliar with this band
Oingo Boingo
Which later turned into
The movie composer
Known as Danny Elfman
Anyway, I hadn't listened to
Oingo Boingo in years
And I was surprised to discover
That I still remembered
Every single lyric
And I was not surprised
When all those songs were
Suddenly turned into
An immense brain worm
That's been tormenting me
And Princess We as well
For days
And of course
Like Cove Theft 19
The only way to cure myself
Of this brain worm
Is to give it to you
Dear listener
Oh, sorry
I should have covered my mouth
Or worn my new shirt
Or my Dobshead face mask
Which we have now
So anyway
I wanted to do this
Mostly Oingo Boingo show
But the big decision was
Do I arrange it
So it starts with the light
And hopeful stuff
And ends with the scary
And dark stuff
Or the other way around
And I decided on the other way around
And on a positive note
Let's not increase
The suicide statistics
Among subgeniuses
Which is the most common
This song
Perfect System
Is about where we were heading
Before all the crap
Hit the fan
And society may well
Head that way
Even faster
Once the virus
Kills off one type
Of dumbass
But leaves the other
Type of dumbass alive
The kind of dumbass
That's fine
With perpetual mask wearing
Complicated rules
Enforced manners
And isolation
From the others
Except by Facebook
Forever
I'm in love with you
I know
And I know that you love me too
I'm in love with you
I know
I'm in love with everyone too
Everyone too
When all comrades now you know
We're all brothers under the skin
We're all living in adjustments now
Living in a perfect system
The adjustments simple
There's really no pain
You hardly notice anything has changed
Living in a programmed life
Nothing really helps
Up and down
There's no need for fighting now
There's no reason to worry
Around one another
No, no, no
The perfect system
There's no confrontation
Unnecessary friction
To repeat our concentration
We've simply done away with
Unnecessary friction
I live in a system
I get enough occupation
I get enough nutrition
By eating protein
Biscuits
Recommended by the system
It's routine regulation
I've handed an operation
To all the reasons
The definition of Www...
This isptions
Unquestioneable
Publicity
Reason
Mind
Unity
Health
I'm in love with you, I know
And I know that you love me too
I'm in love with everyone too
I can tell by the look in your blank little eyes
That you agree, but you're not a bit surprised
Living in a programmed life
All the really hells of send-off
Don't need my fighting now
There's a tour of realm
I had an operation
With a reckless reaction
They tapped it with my brain some
It helped me see the reason
For living in the system
We're all brothers in a perfect world
In a perfect world there is uniformity
In a perfect world there is continuity
We're all brothers in a perfect world
There's no need for spontaneity
Perfect system
We're all brothers to the end
Brothers to the end
I know
And I know that you love me too
Promise to the end
I know
I'm in love with everyone too
Promise to the end
I know
We're all comrades under the skin
Promise to the end
I know
Living in a perfect system
Promise to the end
To the end
To the bitter end
I kind of want that operation he's talking about
Do you suppose some of these songs might be meant in
I don't know, in an ironic way?
Boy, just thinking about that makes my head hurt
I'm going to go to Trump's stop
And have one of those doctor prisoners
Give me that operation that makes me as intelligent as the president
I bet I'd probably sleep better
And I hear they have snacks
I'm sure they wouldn't lie about that
I'm pretty sure that everything the government promised us is coming
And it'll be just like they said it'll be
the end of this day
What you see
What you see is what you get
Don't relax, you're not home yet
Put your life in my hands
Look around, you'll understand
Put your life into my hands
It's the 80s, idiots
What you see is what you get
It's the 80s, little fools
Don't forget the golden rule
What you see is what you get
What the hell do you expect?
Ritchie Red Rose
White puppy noses
Men with rubber hoses
It's more like it
What you see is not always what you get
A lesson we must not forget
One never knows what to expect
So close your eyes
And you'll get
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Here's what you see
And what you get
Open up your eyes
And look around you
Wow, wow
And who's the giant Mr. Growl?
You've got to be thankful you're alive
And how much longer can you survive?
Underneath the mask there's something brewing
Underneath the ground there's something we will find
And it's the golden rule
Put your life into my hands
Look around you and understand
It's the 80s, idiot
Idiot, idiot
What you see is what you get
What you get, what you get
It's the 80s, idiot, fool
Don't forget the golden rule
What you see is what you get
What you get, what you get
What the hell did you expect?
Pretty red roses
White puppy noses
Men in thwopper hoses
It's what I like it
But you're not the sweetest one for all of their friends
Bask you around and you'll make it like them
What you see is what you get
What a comforting song, don't you agree?
Yeah, eh, Oingo Boingo specialized in that
It's funny, it was announced that among the many musical combos
Danny Elfman was scheduled to perform at the now canceled
Bonnaroo or Hullabaloo or Woodstock or Coachella
One of those things
And all these kids were going, what's he gonna do?
Play the score of Batman
As if Oingo Boingo had never existed
Well, there you go
I'm old
And tonight I'm playing oldies
That might have well have been recorded tomorrow
This upcoming song addresses the paranoia that so many of us feel
Especially those who are cooped up and surveilled
And feel like they're being watched all the time
I don't have to worry about that
Because for the last five years
I've been hacking and digging out escape routes
Through the deep woods surrounding our compound here
So when the black helicopters come for me
They'll never catch me
Until I get to the highway
Or unless they have dogs or infrared or armed sniffing drones
So yeah, I have nothing to worry about
Doing this anti-establishment show from a cult compound in Texas
Kind of near Waco
What, me worry?
I'll make a sound or even move
Don't give another doozy
I think they're looking for me
I get to run
There's someone calling in my yard
There's someone creeping on my roof
There's someone tapping my ears
There's someone creeping around
I feel it deep in my bones
They want to throw my intuition
They want to find out what I know
Why don't they leave me all around?
I get to run
Might need a catcher
Or a night controller
Can't be too careful
I take precautions
They're very clever
I get to run
Faceless surgeons
I'm with razors
Cut out our imagination
There's someone knocking on my door
I think they're looking for me
But then there ain't nobody home
That makes a sound of even no boom
No giving nothing to see
I think they're looking for me
I get to run
Might need a catcher
Or a night controller
Can't be too careful
I take precautions
They're very clever
I get to run
But then there ain't nobody home
Might need a catcher
Or a night controller
Soon I'll be my own
If I run
I go have to get glasses
There's those lobotomy surgeons again mentioned in that song.
Back in the days of Oingo Boingo, the 80s, we were worried about chemical and surgical lobotomies.
In the end, the invention of social media took care of all of that.
The prisoners are happiest when they build their own cages.
And seriously, do you think they're looking for you?
You wish. They don't consider you important.
And besides, you're throwing yourself at them every hour that you work at your 24-7 non-paying database entry job for Facebook.
Thank you, Oman.
Late at night, my wife and I have been dancing frenetically to these old songs.
It's good exercise and it baffles the dogs.
But I wish y'all could see my air vocals.
I also do air guitar.
I play guitar, drums, and keyboard when appropriate.
But I'm most proud of my air facial expressions and air vocals with Danny Elfman's remarkably theatrical and melodramatic singing style.
It's great rubber face exercise.
I'm proud of my own clownishly overdramatic facial and bodily poses.
I studied under Jimi Hendrix and other masters, so I realize I can't sing.
Now, that's for who we, but I look great faking it.
At least in my own mind and according to New Agers, that's all that counts.
Now, during this strange year of the new abnormal, a lot of my friends, the older ones and the ones who can still work at home,
which is a privileged bunch these days, are finally starting to go nuts with this sheltering in thing.
On the other hand, some are weird.
all like, hey, I could get used to this. I hate people anyway and feel horribly awkward in any
social situation. Me, I'm an old hand at being a hermit except when I have to pretend to be a
normal person in order to get things done and, you know, make a living.
This is my private life. I've got no friends to fear. I've got no problems, no cross to bear.
If you can find me, come and get me out of here.
This is my private place.
Everything is neat and clean.
The skeletons are hidden in the closet.
This is my private place. Can we get me out of here?
This is my private life.
Can we get me out of here?
These are my private things.
They're there against the wall.
The dirty pictures, religious objects.
These are my private things.
Can we get them out of here?
This is my private bed.
This is where I lie at night.
Staring at a light bulb hanging out the ceiling.
Waiting for dreams to come and get me out of here.
In my humble room at night,
I often wander what preserved are not there.
What made kuroocs to look so wallet.
I stare at the people passing by.
They could not see me through my windows –
No shades, looks like I'm not even there
This is my private life
There's something dangerous I like
And all my problems are in trouble
What I really want to know
Has it always been this way?
This is my private life
Islands in the sea
Are so much like me
They don't help that change
No emotion, no emotion
Islands on the land
Fly like feathered sand
Islands in the city
All alone in such a city
It's about to rain
Just face to face
When will it change?
Islands in the sea
What's come over me?
We are both surrounded by the water
Empty waters
Keep living sorry
And the fear it brings
Anything at all to break the love of life to me
It's about to rain
Just face to face
Anything at all to break the love of life to me
It's about to rain
Nothing to lose
Aw, so much like me
They don't ever change
No emotions, no emotions
Island farmland
Dry like desert sand
Island to the city
All alone in such a city
Island to the sea
Oh, oh, oh
Pretty grim, huh?
I'm personally not all that isolated.
So I have a solid and nearby family and a large network of friends that I actually know well and like very much.
So, see, I have a safety net.
Heck, I've got nothing to fear.
Nothing at all.
Hey, neighbor, let me give you some advice.
The Russians are about to pulverize us in our sleep tonight.
That is, if the crazy Arabs or the right don't get us first and the fire will rain down from the sky.
The fire will rain down.
Now, drop your chest and drop your drop.
Hey, little girl, won't you come this way?
If I give candy or perhaps a chocolate shake or perhaps a nice cocaine.
Or perhaps a little kiss.
Or perhaps a ride in my big car.
Perhaps a ride in my big car.
Don't be afraid.
Won't you make an old man happy?
Won't you let me show you paradise?
Don't ask your mother for advice.
Listen if you know the
music
There's nothing to fear
Temperature's taking a drop now
Everyone says
We've come such a long, long way.
We're civilized.
Isn't that nice?
We've gotten so smart.
We know how to build a whole world of fun.
When it comes to the simple things.
Like living together.
Ha!
Why'd we have to come all this way?
Is anything easier to understand?
Our life is better than written in man.
We've been born in love, but we know better.
We've got to get it all just right together.
Stop wasting all my time.
Why'd we come all this way?
Why'd we have to come all this way?
We couldn't quit while we were ahead.
We can't stop right now.
Why'd we come all this way?
Why'd we have to come all this way?
Why'd we have to end up like this?
We should've just stayed and understood.
Why'd we come all this way?
The road was long and the journey was hard.
That we're even dreaming that we've come so far.
Oh, ha!
We've been born all this way.
Why'd we come all this way?
Why did we come all this way?
Does it look like this?
Doesn't it look enough like this?
Why did we come all this way?
And did it have to end up like this?
Why didn't we come all this way?
I've been doing that lately.
I do really good air vocals and expressions to this one.
Have you seen my girlfriend?
She lives in a pig pen.
I can't seem to find her.
Perhaps she is hiding underneath a plate of scraps.
Let's take the holy off.
Have you seen my new house?
Looks just like a dog house.
Someone saw it walking straight into the ocean.
Thought it was an ivory boat.
Let's take the holy off.
Maybe.
It's just a bad dream and a wake up soon.
But I don't think I'll be so lucky.
Maybe.
It's the first one of those strange days when nothing's right.
No, nothing seems right at all.
When I threw a paper on a bathroom wall.
But I can't remember who I wanted to call.
Operator, can you help me?
We just dragged her to the bathroom.
I will find a bet.
You think you could lend me one?
I am going to have a go at you.
I am not gaming to win.
The only bad thing about cybersecurity is if the game makes you bendin' a finger forever.
What?
Anyway, think about going to school.
Is there nothing helping us to live when we're getting that routine?
Let's go home.
I ain't ain't.
Go away.
Have you seen my girlfriend?
Okay, you think that one was a good rewardian subgenius theme song?
Listen to this.
It's a true all-purpose subgenius anthem from Oingo Boingo's second album,
the opening song, Grey Matter.
They say you're stupid that you're too young to fall
They say you swallow anything that they show down your throat
They say that you can't think that you haven't got a brain
That you're just there to listen, that you're just being trained
There's something inside your head
They say you lost the ability to even think
That your tiny little brain moves down the kitchen sink
They say that you'll buy anything that they turn away
That you're listening to everything that they decide to play
There's something inside your head
Grey Matter, Grey Matter
её
They matter, they matter
cess
Their music
I think you like it
Like it
To be told
What to do
Ain't that true
I
Think you're better
Better
On
Storm come dead
Without your head
They say you're stupid
That you're too young to know
They say you'll swallow
Anything that they
Choke down and throw
If they say
You're doing it
They say
Right now
You're doing it
They say
Turn around
You're doing it
They say
Hit the ground
You're doing it
They say
Fight the big weenie
You're doing it
If they say
What is that good
You're doing it
If they say
Dead and over baby
You're doing it
If they say
Take it out
Now
You're doing it
There's Leading Inside Your Head
There's Dreaming Inside Your Head
There's Something Inside Your Head
Great Matter Great Matter
Hall
All
Great Matter Great Matter
They matter, they matter
Oh yes, dear friends.
Before I end the show,
with the ultimate Oingo Boingo subgenius anthem,
let me first explain I'm not personal friends
with Danny Elfman of Oingo Boingo.
We've never met, although we have friends in common,
and I have a picture of him as the devil in Forbidden Zone,
personally autographed to me personally.
He was given a copy of Book of the Subgenius
by Dr. G. Gordon Gordon under pleasurable circumstances,
a lot of pleasure.
He was a long time ago,
so he apparently remembers us well.
So it's mutual.
Anyway, this is Hour of Slack,
number one thousand seven hundred and seventy-six.
Seventeen seventy-six, huh?
You'd think I'd have some kind of
pertinent numerology quip about that.
But what's way more important is subgenius.com,
where you can learn about everything,
everything old, but also available.
It offers pathways to the newer subgenius things, too.
For instance, check out freethinkradio.com,
which carries all of the other subgenius shows and this one,
and triologiesoaps.com,
which can get you clean with Dobbs Head Soap,
and some of the ten million authorized and unauthorized
subgenius Facebook pages and whatnot, and so on.
But now, friends, a real anthem,
a feel-good anthem for subgenii from, like, 1980.
Boing-a-boing-a.
I'm just a clown, but I ain't got no pride.
I'm on the outside.
The girls look really cute, they really make it work.
They think I'm just a jerk.
I'm on the outside.
I never cooked and still, I never was too hip.
I never caught the ride.
I'm on the outside.
I'm on the outside now.
This is where it all begins.
Right here.
On the outside looking in.
I'm on the outside.
I never was a punk.
I never shot junk.
I never even tried.
Counterculture passed me right by.
Don't talk to debutantes.
Don't eat in restaurants.
The patrons sit and stare.
The winners make wisecracks behind my back.
The teachers there in school, they front me by the rule.
They said I have no motivation.
These are all delicious brains of dedication.
Honestly, am I so sure right?
I'm on the outside.
I'm on the outside now.
This is where it all begins.
On the outside looking in.
Looking in.
I am you.
I'm just a alien through and through, trying to make believe I'm you.
Trying to fit.
Just a stranger on the outside looking in.
The pistol makes me sick
I wear the wrong clothes, I see the wrong things
You know I can't dance, my feet are much too wide
Who thinks you set the trends?
You wear your head as right, your clothes are out of sight
Your house is modern, really kitsch
You get so macho when you're with your bitch
I see them go to work, I see them go to sleep
I see them on TV, I see them laugh and cry
I'm on the outside, I'm on the outside
I'm on the outside
On, on the outside
I'm on the outside now
This is where it all begins
I'm on the outside looking in
Looking in at you
I'm just an alien through and through
Let's cut back on the talk
Trying to make believe I'm you, trying to fix
Just a stranger on the outside looking here
I'm on the outside, I'm on the outside now
I mean, some of us have work-at-home jobs and pensions and whatnot,
and Dave is worse off than most of our other old friends.
He's unemployed.
He was a newspaper reporter, but they don't do that anymore.
And he just had a car wreck, not his fault, other guy's fault.
But the lawyer wants money, and he doesn't have a car.
He's desperate to get a hold of a car because he can't walk to the stores anymore.
It's over a mile, and he's having problems with his legs.
Yeah, Dave's not in real great health.
He's actually, I think, about 70 years old.
Yes.
And has had heart conditions.
Probably coming back.
And he's a charity case, man.
And there is a GoFundMe on the subgenius.com radio page.
You should just look at subgenius.com, look across the top.
There's a bunch of little indexes.
One is radio, HOS for hour of slack, or hose.
But it's, you go there, and there's a link to the GoFundMe.
It's too complicated for me to read like this.
And you wouldn't want to have to write it down on the slide.
The other simple thing to do is there's a little donation button on the beginningofsubgenius.com homepage
and in the hour of slack page.
And if you want to just throw some, you know, 10 bucks of PayPal money at Dave, send it to me.
Just say what it's for, and I'll send it on.
I'll send it to him.
I send him a check every week for his phone bill and then some for the show
and advance royalties on his book Neighbor World, which is also still available.
And if you haven't read it, it's great.
It's really amazing.
It's not like anything else except Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
It is like Lonesome Cowboy Dave, but not in the way you expect.
It's another.
It's a novel, a science fiction novel with characters.
Well, you can draw comparisons between that and Stand on Zanzibar, I think,
and the one in your little bit on the back cover that you wrote.
Oh, well, we compare it to the Firesign Theater, Federico Fellini's surreal movies,
Kurt Vonnegut, and, oh, of course, William Gibson.
And Clockwork Orange, because it's written in future slang to some extent.
Anyway, Neighbor World, it's only $14 for the print version.
I think the Amazon Kindle version is only $7.
Dave gets more if you buy the print version from subgenius.com.
But really, if you've got anything to spare, you know, I don't do begging very often.
Not nearly as much as some preachers do.
And this one is for a very, very specific and spectacularly needy case.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
Dave DeLuca.
Look at the subgenius.com radio page or the donations button.
And send me a little note.
Stang at subgenius.com.
It's not like we're overworked and flooded with contributions.
So go ahead and feel free to help out in any small way you can.
Any way you can.
It'll help the morale of the old cowboy.
Yes.
He is pretty lonesome.
He's got a sister, and he has a grown son and grandkids.
They're in Ashtabula.
But friends, Ashtabula, Ohio is kind of like Appalachia, West Virginia.
It's one of the most depressed areas in the country.
It really is.
You can find heavenly spots there, but Dave's house is not one of them.
No.
He just needs to get a $300 car to get him here and there.
Just.
We can just get back to some vestige of a human life.
And we owe Dave, friends.
And yes, I'm helping Dave as much as I possibly can.
So you can too.
Praise Bob.
Praise Dave.
Hate to get serious on you like this.
But hey, you know, Church of the Subgenius can get kind of real.
In fact, to tell the truth, friends,
and I say this as Reverend Ivan Stang, Sacred Squad Number 273,
what surprised Philo and me the most was how useful it would be socially.
We honestly didn't expect that.
But people keep telling us they meet their very best friends.
And I know that's certainly true of me and you, Princess Wee.
It seems to be the hallmark of the religion to me.
It's the.
Alliances made within it.
People's friendships.
Like marriages.
And marriages.
Yes.
Mwah, mwah, mwah, mwah.
Anyway, okay.
Thank you for listening.
And we totally appreciate.
If you're too broke, we understand.
We sure understand.
We understand.
Do not consider.
I mean, I'm only saying if you are one of the lucky ones.
This might be a good time to help.
Praise that old Bob.
He.
He wasn't as bad as everybody says.
No, he wasn't as bad as everyone says.
Praise Bob.
Yadda, yadda, yadda, yadda, yadda.
Yadda, yadda.