E.B. Slash
Worshombie
Bart, give me my hand
No
Thank you, Bart
Oh, I'm so late
I'm so very, very late
Well, no wonder you're late
Why, this park is exactly two days full
Nine
Eight
Seven
Six
Five
Four
And six
Five
Four
Three
Two
One
Bob?
See you, Bob
13 reporting
Everyone, please, this is the end of the partner
뿌
Because of fact that the對啊
You returns
you
Some scientists were experimenting with Bob.
That was by Fernanda Nandeli-Murrer.
Before that, a piece by Artemia Salina.
Authorization denied.
I am the guardian of the river.
I am the bursar of Dumpstown.
Mr. Sheehy.
There will be no subcutaneous violence here tonight in the halls of separation
where all of the among us have met.
There are so many here.
I can't believe it.
I can see their faces gleaming in the dark as if they were wearing their own hats.
And I can just see my fingers passing very, very lightly over these pages.
And I don't look good.
This show is in Braille tonight.
So we went up the hill to the church that the old man had built.
Yes, it was an exquisite little building on the side of the cliff overlooking the ocean.
Only to be shot down by the song.
And it's deadly, the cynical.
Raising up of the eggheads.
Directing your dreams.
Arranging your dream world.
Now, please have your dream world arranged as you enter the show.
Look, there's monks on TV that are setting themselves on fire trying to stop the show.
Human sacrifices won't stop them, folks.
That's what the Aztecs were doing.
They were trying to stop it for real on the show.
Oh, now.
Okay, maybe the song has died now.
I don't know.
Can you hear the song behind?
A pop song?
I can hear the song.
A polished AM style talk show theme.
Can you still hear the song right there?
Or has the song died?
Was the song carried out of the bomb shelter looking blue with an oxygen mask over its face?
And maybe one of its sons is dead.
Yes, this could be you shuffling from universe to universe
with a big, happy, sleepy, goofy-looking grin on your face.
Transcending the limits of the astral plane.
And now we have a special announcement.
Drugs!
What did they give you?
Thorazine?
Haldol?
How much?
Learn your drugs.
Know your doses.
Elementary.
We're talking about the secret amendments to your constitution.
Make sure it don't stop.
The amendments made while you were sleeping somewhere.
Off slack lustered in your bed.
Look at your insignificant little...
...rebellion Skywalker.
What happened to our insignificant little rebellion?
For crying out loud.
Geez, they just swept that under the media rugs.
All your friends would soon be dead.
Or sleeping soundly.
Looking comatose with their feet up in the air.
La la da da.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
La da da da.
When I walked you home the other night.
I wanted so much to hold you tight.
But I was relax-ful.
Relax-ful Bob.
They call me.
I saw the love light.
She yawning in your eye.
I wanted so much to be your guy.
But I was relax-ful.
Relax-ful Bob.
They call me.
Will you ever change?
Will you ever grow up and lose your relax-ful name?
You're missing lots of love and lots of kissing too.
From Judy, Joyce and Mary.
From Peggy Sue.
From Mary and Peggy Sue.
I was going with the girl's head on a plate.
He's trying to get a body for the head of his fiancee.
So he has to freak with these sleazy strip keys clubs.
And he brings these bimbos home.
We'll may distract the audience into believing that the song has stopped.
But it isn't.
In reality it keeps on going.
You know we tried to cripple it.
Nobody knows the words to it.
My grandfather knew the words.
But he's dead now.
They say aliens dropped the song here trying to get rid of it.
They damaged the song.
But it just hid in a hole until it healed.
Then it came back louder than ever and hurt everybody's ears again.
When they pulled the plug on it it just thundered along but never quite got down.
It just turned into sort of an acoustic song.
So they gave up on that.
But it still walks the earth.
Roaming the countryside.
Shambling about like a swan.
Like some hideous zombie.
Never knowing where it'll go next.
And there it goes.
The show.
Shambling down Main Street.
Your town.
That's a bully shoot at it with a knife.
Because it refuses to die.
Maybe that's the show's.
That might be the show's theme song.
That refuses to die.
Maybe how when the show moves the wind blows.
Like the show the song is an ancient animal.
It extends back to the time of Pangea.
When all of the planets and all of the earth's continents were one giant single continent.
A place of paradise and harmony where all creatures lived together.
Worshipping the song because it still extended back that far.
Into the one world land.
The dreamy paradise.
True greatness of the continent of Pangea.
Which was the prototype of it.
Mew.
Hey what's that knocking at the door?
Oh my god don't let it in.
Don't don't don't let it in.
It's the song.
Oh my god it's Roam the Countryside.
It's back now.
Tell your kids to stay away from it.
Don't worry about your neighborhood.
Property values go back up after the song leaves.
Yeah you hope.
You wish.
But the song it just never stops.
It just keeps going.
Sometimes the only lyrics to the song are the lyrics to the song.
Where thousands of people in torment scream.
Do they still have the Kennedy car?
I didn't see the Kennedy car the last four times I've seen it.
It never stops.
Where's the Kennedy car?
They've got the hip hop and the hot rod.
The Kennedy car.
But they don't have the Kennedy car.
Even when the DJ tries to pull it out of the mix the song just keeps on going.
It just keeps dropping.
They got their motion activated marking guards though.
Hey Overman this guy misplaced the caller.
Uh oh.
They have the horizontal.
I would speculate that the song kidnapped him.
Many a chance.
I took it to another channel on your mixer there.
Try another channel.
Try the A channel.
Which generates up to 50,000 volts.
Is the song.
Is the caller there?
Caller are you there?
Is the song with you?
The legendary rock hard abs.
In six minutes.
Maybe if you don't move the song will be at least a little bit merciful on you.
Yes with the ultimate nutrition pack you rub the oil of origin into your ears.
Don't move.
You'll be just an empty husk when the song sucks the life out of you.
I'm sorry.
The results will delight and depress you.
How can you kill a song that's already dead that's the real question.
It shambles on with an unholy life of its own.
It's lived for centuries and it can't stop killing.
Strap yourselves in folks and take a journey into the unknown.
Now, friends, what's coming up.
You may have seen ads for send in your song and we'll turn it into a record.
Our friend John Truby saw that ad, and he wrote this song and sent it in there, and they turned it into this record.
I got high last night on LSD
My mind was beautiful and I was free
Warts love my nipples because they are pink
Vomit on me, baby, yeah, yeah, yeah
A blind man's penis is a wreck because he is blind
It's a wreck because he is blind
A blind man's penis is a wreck because he's blind
It's a wreck because he's blind
Let's make love under the stars
And watch for UFOs
If little baby Martians come out of the UFOs
And fuck them, yeah, yeah, yeah
The zebra spilled his plastina on Venus
And the gelatin fingers oozed electric marbles
Ramona's titties died in hell
And the Nazis want to kill
To kill everyone
A blind man's penis is a wreck because he's blind
It's a wreck because he's blind
I'm celebrating May Day now. This is the International Workers' Day.
And you guys are just too freaking bourgeois for me.
I'm a wobbly stank.
I know, I know you are.
I respect that.
I remember old Joe Hill and everything.
I know, I know. I respect that.
Yeah, you guys died for our sins.
And then they took six guys out.
Go to the basement.
Us 70s drug brothers are really into what you wobblies did for us, man.
I told them.
Those guys died or something for something, man.
These arse-fits-boozies are like, screwed, man.
Go to the basement level and let them in.
We're the man's little bitch, dude.
Go to the basement.
We're all the man's little bitch.
Get down in there, boss.
He's got his keys and his signs, man.
His stop signs.
Come on, stank.
He's got a control thing, man.
And they've got this machine where they can tell if you're thinking or not.
They've got a TV.
And if it's off, you're guilty, man.
Mom?
Dad?
Kids with drugs.
Every day.
So ask them.
What?
Where?
When?
It's pestering.
Sponsored by the Office of Drug-Free America.
Now, a ranch has got 800 head of cattle.
Half the herd weighs 50 pounds.
The other half loses 20 pounds.
On the way to market, each one loses 50 pounds.
The other half loses 700 pounds.
All right, son.
How much does a herd weigh?
Paul, I'm glad those two robbers hit my head on that road.
Each one weighs 20 pounds.
Paul?
Hmm?
I don't think too bad.
I came to help.
Half the herd weighs 50 pounds.
The herd weighs 700 pounds.
I don't know.
For it never sleeps or lies idle.
Every filament of it always working.
It's never at conflict with itself over such human considerations as honor or love or pity.
From now on,
you will answer the question.
From now on, you are...
But the Krells forgot one thing.
...to work in the uranium mines.
Monsters taught.
Monsters from the Id.
Making reduced plutonium.
Monsters from the Id?
Oh, I can't wait for X-Day when the monsters from the Id come to raging life
and your hormonal unconscious comes belching and erupting up with living beings.
Your very fantasies of beautiful women, men, monstrous aliens,
and...
All will become real.
Real to the pink next door.
Who will flee in terror but he can never escape.
Because he's in your nightmare now.
He's in your nightmare.
Because it's X-Day.
X-Day.
And you paid your dues.
And Bob will save...
Now that's a name I've not heard in a long time.
...the mechanics to save any man.
Yet to save his own precious bodily juices as they flow freely from his neck and his thigh muscles.
He is a man on a mission and I dare not say what kind of recalcified mission that might be.
He's an emissionary.
He is the emissionary.
Don't be proud of his technological terror you can stop now.
He is the spermatic royal.
He is the king of squids.
You and your aliens can never defeat us, Bob.
You and your squids, your gigantic prairie squid army, can never live forever.
I trust you know how to cure the subcutaneous impurities.
Your mind is going to be going soon.
I hope you know at least where you are now, Dr. Stang.
Don't be too proud of this technological terror you've constructed.
Take the red, white, and blue pill.
Earthman.
Wonder if there are any other words that rhyme with pill.
Pew.
Pew pew pew pew.
Pew pew pew.
Pew.
Pew...
I don nonsense.
My name's John, and I'm writing this mandarin out to make my blood boil fast and
Here are a few limericks that I wrote.
There once was a girl named Donna who liked to smoke that guano.
And now she's scooping marijuana.
There once was a guy named Dent.
Let me tell you a story about Bill.
There once was a guy named Blue.
Sponsored by the Partnership for a Free America.
At 17, I knew too much to listen to the wise.
The world of hippies beckoned and I joined the rebels' cries that said,
Tune in, turn on, drop out, see how free you'll be.
Now I'm an abject slave to what they said would set me free.
My God, my eager hopes and dreams have wound up unharmed.
They're all on the shelf.
And I'm no good to anyone, least of all myself.
In this mad dream to find myself in pot and LSD,
I'm shackled beyond hope to what they said would set me free.
My life's become a living hell.
I beg and rob and steal.
Somehow, I can no longer tell the fancy
from the real.
I may have killed.
I just don't know.
A soul gone blind can't see.
A heartless, mindless slave
to what will never set me free.
I sometimes think I feel my mother's warm and loving hand
come through a psychedelic fog,
but like the rest,
it's just a dream.
I'm in a world of mescaline and pot and LSD.
And link by link, it's forged a chain
that's made a slave of me.
The devil's strumming on my nerves
and fires within me rage.
My tortured mind so gone,
I can't recall for sure my age.
I think I'm 22.
I know I won't reach 23.
But hell can be no worse than what is made a slave of me.
Fear.
al des grbec.
The fear attracts the fearful.
The strong.
The weak.
The innocent.
Slack is the mind killer of the mind.
I must not slack.
Slack is the killer of the mind.
I must not mind.
I don't mind.
I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not.
Wake up, wake up,
Welcome to another world.
You ass-nater!
I shouldn't have taken that other half!
Don't worry, my friend, you didn't take the other half.
The other half is waiting for you here.
It took me!
In the bottom of the mind.
Look, look, look!
It's a shadow of your own face.
It's a reflection of your own mind.
Look, friend, it's you!
You're staring blankly, mutely into the...
dark horizon and see nothing but that...
slap-shot, slap-shot face.
You must!
That face!
I've seen it before.
I think I...
I find your lack of faith disturbing.
Never mind.
My mind is not my mind!
I'm aboard, kiddo!
Like slack, popper, booper, popper,
eeper, eeper, bleeper,
rattle on its way,
convo, bound, points unknown!
Out aboard!
Never mind!
My mind is no longer my friend!
I'm repeating, we're not in Kansas anymore.
Do you mind having things taken
and placed where you can't find them?
I'm repeating, we're not in Kansas ever!
Hey man, hey man, do you think people are gonna think,
do you think people are gonna think,
do you think people are gonna think I'm, I'm, I'm...
I'm repeating, we're not in Kansas anymore.
Are you on one, dear?
You feel persecuted, left alone.
I'm repeating, we're not in Kansas anymore.
I'm being locked there!
Are you on one?
Yes you are, a fabulous eight-hour day,
chained to this machine!
You will see the way, as void.
This is not the true void.
You can know that which does not exist.
That is the void.
It is not included in man's knowledge.
The inscription on the wooden post reads,
In the void, sharp and sharp,
and strong, it can be used to cut, sack, and stick priests. This is not the true void. Of course,
the void is nothingness. A long-armed monkey holding a rope in his left hand to bind evil
and a sword in his right hand. He sits in flames, reaching out for a reflection of the moon on
water. There is the true void. In this, dreaming in heaven is where there is nothing. That is the
void. Must be the void. The Void by Reverend Cobblestone. And before that, Buck Ritchie did
The Slave. There is a place that I often find myself at and uh... Oh yeah? In your dreams? Yes.
No, I am a floating spirit without entrails, without a need for
anything. I am a floating spirit without entrails, without a need for anything.
Ingestion or digestion? It depends. You go to bed looking at a book with pictures of
insects and you can have insects in your dream. You can direct what you do by...
That is true. Just before you go to bed. That is true. That's probably why I always dream about,
have dreams about women. Yes, if you go to sleep looking at voluptuous imagery,
then that will percolate through your dream. That makes a lot of sense now.
Cause and effect, so to speak.
Could be. Could be. Could be. Yep. Uh, well, of course...
Do you believe that you can change your dream by your diet?
Much to regret in our pasts unless we are condemned to relive certain incidents over and over.
But... That's what we have F.R.O.P. for.
Yo-Yo... Yes. Well, that's another superstition.
Some people believe that F.R.O.P. suppresses dreams, but it does not. It simply makes you sleep more soundly so you don't tend to wake up.
And remember your dreams. But you have them all the same.
If you don't have them, you start losing your mental health very quickly.
Yeah, you still get your REMs, is what you mean, right?
You still get the byproduct which the brain wants, and that's the rapid eye movements.
You get the flushing out of the repressed psychic substratum.
Sort of like... The flushing of the mental O.G.M.
It's sort of like driving your mom's Dodge Dart 63 Dodge Dart backwards around in a circle in the park.
You have to wind the miles off of it.
But your brain has to do that every night.
It does that when your eyeballs are blinking.
Rapidly blinking.
They sound like this.
You don't know they sound like that because you can't see them.
Because you're asleep. You're sleeping.
So you don't know you're actually doing that.
People are watching you do it. They're sitting there laughing. They're holding their guns and they're laughing. They're going, ha ha ha.
You are such an idiot. Look at that idiot.
They're looking at you and they're taunting you. They're making fun of you.
And they know that you're laying there. You can't hear them because you're sleeping.
You should ask the protection of Saint Pedro of Penelope.
Then before you wake up, they leave.
Really? And then Saint Pedro would just do a mechano.
He might just do that.
So that later on they can show you those pictures and play you those tapes.
And you can then feel stupid.
So stupid.
Listen to what the...
The price is yours.
Obey me and live or disobey and die.
I'm... I don't want to wake up. I don't want to wake up.
I don't want to wake up.
I'm trying to...
Get those shoulders up in the air. Look directly at the face of his beatitude.
I can't.
Look at him.
I can't bear to look at him.
Obey. Obey.
I cannot gaze upon him.
Obey.
I'll be blind.
He is too beautiful to gaze upon.
Never mind the brilliance.
For in the light is where the signals and signs come into the inner ear of your vapid brain.
I feel shame before him.
Yes, you do.
You've been a bad man, haven't you?
I was afraid of him.
You were afraid.
I saw him.
You detested him.
The man with the pipe.
Yes.
Surely you can't be serious.
I am serious.
True.
And don't call me Shirley.
It happened though.
Yes.
But it is true.
Yes, you were envious of him.
You must believe me.
You looked at his nozzle.
You said if only the Lord had provided me with a Winchester like this, I could fly with the duck vehicles.
I could live.
I was.
Escape.
No escape for you, my friend.
You're stuck here.
I'm staying.
Unplug me then.
Unplug me.
Quiet, man.
I'm trying to get the plugs out.
Take drugs, Danny.
Why are you doing this to me?
Bring around the fizz water.
Come on.
We got to get him out of here.
Look at that stuff coming out of his ears.
Oh, my God.
I think they really got him this time.
Oh, man.
They put Stonky and George in Daniel Bush's prison camp and licking him now.
Authorization denied.
My God.
Why hast thou forsaken me?
They turned a political and religious priest into an American in 2005.
Oh, man.
This is sick.
Look at all the welts on his neck.
Somebody's been sucking his ear.
I think.
Authorization denied.
I know.
The mask is a thing.
Authorization denied.
I'm going to go to jail.
Everyone has different dreams.
Authorization denied.
The past does not hope.
Change in the air.
Authorization denied.
Demons.
Man, I just can't get it up.
This just ain't doing it for me.
I am the king of the world forever.
You need one of these.
I mean, it hurts, but not enough to come.
You know what I mean?
Well, try one of these.
Check it out.
Oh.
Look at the little spindle here.
Directly.
Red, white, and blue pills?
Well, these are more than red, white, and blue pills.
These actually make the whole thing go.
You know what I'm saying?
Oh, it's like a little tiny world inside that pill.
Yeah.
Don't stare too hard.
You might get sucked right in there.
Just rub it very gently on your lower parts.
Oh, yeah.
Not those parts.
Hey, more of them kind pills, Dave?
Yeah.
I've got a whole bag here.
Oh, man.
Those pills feel good all over my body.
I've never had one of these.
These are the only red pills you could wear.
Are you who?
Can I try one?
The pills that worked on the outside instead of the inside.
Remember that old weird Coddy song?
Whoa.
Yeah.
Hey, your molecules are starting to evaporate.
The inside is bigger than the outside.
It's expanding.
It's out of focus.
It's rising up.
I know.
It's inflating.
Can you adjust the horizontal or something?
Here, let me try this little knob over here.
Sure, sure.
One soul per breath.
It seems to be, I don't know.
I don't know.
Grab the knob down there.
You want a fabulous eight hour day.
Give it a good old tweak.
Hey, try it.
How many still?
Thanks for the iron lung, Bob.
Totally destroyed.
Oh, man.
Now he's growing an iron lung out of the side of his neck.
Huh?
Don't pass out on me yet.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
not yet.
Not yet.
Don't pass out on me yet, you rock noinker.
You rock noinker.
You have a frag-
There is infinite power in the red, white, and blue pill.
You rock noinker.
You are invincible once you take the red, white, and blue pill.
You can only see fields of green and the waves.
The balloon has gone up.
Hit the playground.
You can only see F6 and 14.
You are clear to hit the playground.
You can only see an M14 or 16.
After the playground.
You know the numbers.
Move on towards Disneyland.
It is time to provide drugs for the citizens.
Drugs for citizens are more important than community responsibility.
Citizens need drugs, not just a profit.
It is time to stand up on the table and most of all stand on the disabled low-income children
for the proposition.
The basic right to disrupt unacceptable reality is essential for all of our citizens.
Thank you all.
Keep up the good drugs.
EBSL.com.
Really?
Or zombie?
Bob give me my hand.
No.
Thank you Bob.
Expensive secret.
Come on.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Dangerous.
Ridiculous.
More and more goodness.
Brain.
Heart.
Liver.
They're in your sink.
Kids sniff.
Research shows that one in six 8th graders has sniffs.
Protect your sniffs.
Thanks.
Sponsored by the Partnership for a Free America.
Chris.
Chris, it sounds very different from, uh...
Well,
Christmas
has other meanings, hasn't it, Bob?
Bob.
Don't do that!
I'm not resisting arrest, sir.
But you are resisting your bowels,
aren't you?
You argue with your body, don't you, Stan?
And you continue to believe
that you do a radio show
rather than a radio show does you.
It won't let go.
It's hard.
It pulls.
And then it tightens it up.
And then it...
And then I think it's gonna let go
right when I can't...
Just right in front of everybody.
You never know when it's just gonna go.
Yeah, that's right. You never know.
Because there's nothing you know.
Freaking out, man.
I shouldn't have took that other half.
Crime doesn't pay.
Okay.
Mom was right.
I thought I was gonna be cool.
Stop cutting back, sir.
Will you have your miracle this year, children?
Will this be the year
you have your miracle?
Stan, Chaz,
don't you guys think sometimes
that X Day's redundant?
I'm talking about X Day.
Well, even if the thing
is the 4th of July redundant...
I'm talking about the party
at Tranquility Base, goddammit.
But I mean, you know,
just all this waiting
and never happening.
I mean, why...
Maybe they'll come to our houses.
Oh, maybe this, maybe that.
Dave, maybe they'll be here tomorrow.
Maybe you don't know what time it is.
Maybe you don't know what day it is.
Maybe you don't know what year,
what century it is.
I have no argument with that.
I don't know any of those times.
But are you ready?
That's the question.
Have you drilled?
Have you prepared?
Are you ready for the end times?
Are you ready to be ruptured?
Are you ready to meet Bob?
Are you ready to be meted by Connie?
I've already met Bob,
and I did not,
not like the experience one bit.
He was drunk.
He was loud.
He tried to tickle me
in front of a huge number of people.
He vomited on his shoes,
and he had to be escorted
by two large bald guys,
balder and larger than me,
out of the area.
He never stopped smiling
for a second, though.
Yeah, you call that a smile?
With all that torn flesh hanging?
Happiness.
He looked ecstatic the whole time.
Satori, indeed.
Slack.
The nth slack.
The extreme slack.
Slack.
Square.
Sure.
It's not just the smile,
it's the placidness in that face.
The expression in his eyes.
Just the cool, calm.
He is definitely in moon pants
every hour of the day.
I know he's under 24 hours.
It's sighted lust.
It's the grin of
infinitely sighted,
infinite lust.
The first thing I...
Infinitely being sighted.
Before his desire has had a chance
to barely form.
It is instantly sighted.
By fate.
The subgenius performs memory editing.
He buries his arm deep in the archives of the score,
gropes for the proper file and its specific remembrances,
and retrieves it to stand at leisure.
And he knows that this file,
and his archive,
are but one drawer in the greater archive of all creation.
For everything is but a pattern,
an intersection in the code.
Everything exists at once,
it just shifts position continuously.
Every distinct object we see around us is but an opening into the files.
Don't worry, if you missed something,
it's all in the can.
It will all be aired again,
in some better world.
And the angelic host which must soon descend
will bring an index to all the shifting patterns of the code,
providing us with a guide to the anti-laws.
But we have been warned of the tampering.
Once one has gone swimming in the fourth dimension,
this dry land bound pace seems excruciatingly ordered.
It's a shame that we have to go back to the past.
It's a shame that life on this plane is so chronological.
Many are the subgenii who have gone waiting in the turbulent surf of time,
never to return.
It's hard to get back in step once you've changed the setting on your astral wristwatch.
Nyaa-oy-nay-bob-ay!
Open your eyes wide in the continuously ride
Just a military persona knows without knowledge
That this town has S Acts
A restaurant in the motives was cold
We still dream
A paradise with that minimize
A sweet-time in mind
Nyaa-oy-nay-bob-ay!
I'm a woman, I'm a woman, I'm a woman, I'm a woman.
I'm a woman, I'm a woman, a woman, I'm a woman.
I'm a woman, I'm a woman, I'm a woman.
I'm a woman...
Legitimate!
Click here to join the promotion and phishing tour!
LOVEicles.net
Loveicles.net
resemble, maybe it was just an action
center. Didn't have to have
any higher thinking.
See what I mean?
And once they catch you that way,
they can bleed you and
suckle from your teeth
like vampires.
Your blood is no longer
your own. No, it's going to be someone else's blood
very, very soon.
See, um, my colon
is not my colon, but it's actually
parallel with the needle.
So,
share shit with Gilligan.
Gilligans.
Thousands of Gilligans
in your closet
and shower.
Millions of Gilligans
everywhere.
Gilligans under the bed.
Millions of Gilligans marching across
the desert.
Millions of
Gallions of
Gallions of Jones.
Millions of deserted
and beaten,
What did I—
Millions
and
considerations
fill
around
you.
Daniel
of
The
留言
Although the church of the subgenius, well, let me put it this way.
If the church goes down, well, civilization goes up.
In flames! In flames, my friend!
And when the world goes up in flames, the subgenies have the weenies!
We will be the ones barbecuing!
Ah, yes!
Friends, you know, the news, you turn on the news today and it's pure surrealism.
Did I really see jiggly pixel vision of Geraldo Rivera in the desert
with these 1,000 troopers pointing guns at 20 skinny little Afghani guys
who were all, one of whom is standing there going,
when the Taliban finds out about this, they're going to kick your ass!
It's all relative, friends.
You know, those guys weren't getting CNN, but maybe they know more because of that.
We have to get used to the idea that at any moment, anything can happen.
Both the imaginable and the unimaginable.
Sometimes the impossible, but more often, the unlikely.
I wish Rod Serling was here to say that instead of Mr. Sister who wrote it.
Sometimes you're the screwy and sometimes you're the screwer.
More often we're the screwy.
And the way I read it, we're one screw short.
Of World War III!
Which I grew up looking forward to because I like atomic monsters.
Oh, once again, the worst it could be was Planet of the Apes.
That was pretty cool.
And the best, Road Warrior.
Whoa!
Blood for oil there.
Ooh la la.
But friends, you know, it's scary because the craziest train engineer in the world is at the helm.
Not Dennis Murphy.
No.
But Casey Jones, the craziest train engineer in the world, is at the helm of Spaceship America
as it careens out of control with that drunken, coked-up madman at the wheel.
And what is America's final destination, friends?
The moon, the future, and Hooterville.
Especially Hooterville.
Oh, man.
It's so depressing sometimes.
And I mean, I get...
I get depressed at watching the normal folks go through their routines.
But you know, the do-gooders can be just as bad as the evil-doers at times.
And they mean well.
But if you happen to be evil and you're a do-gooder, think about it.
You don't even know you're evil.
For instance, anti-smoking.
Anti-smoking bullshit eats up a lot more slack than secondhand smoke.
I have no doubt about that.
And I swear, the smug do-gooder...
will be the death of us all!
For our own goods, of course.
You know, they're fairly easy to spot, the smug do-gooder,
because they oftentimes practice what we would call flamboyant humility.
Or conspicuous humbleness.
You know, a sort of grandiose self-effacement.
Like Buddhists who never cease to remind you of how egoless they are.
You know who I'm talking about.
They just...
They just want you to notice how egoless they are.
That's all.
You know, listen to me when I tell you, go beyond ego.
You don't know who you're dealing with, man.
Listen to me.
Go beyond ego.
Because I know.
It's easy to be a social Darwinist.
Survival of the richest.
If you're that kind that puts the evil in evolution.
And I like to think...
You know, somebody said, you sub-geniuses are just a bunch of elitists.
Well, yeah.
Duh.
For one thing, we won't let any geniuses in.
But it's...
Like, you know, it's not that we look down on the cow manures.
We just don't believe in their shit!
Bob noticed how some people believe this and some people believe that.
You know, oh, I believe the world was created yesterday.
No, no, no.
I believe the world...
The world crew happened by accident seven billion years ago.
Well, Bob said, believe me out of it!
You believe what?
Just relax in the safety of your own delusions, friends.
Just keep them out of my delusions.
We'll stick with the contradictions that make good sense.
Thank you very much.
You know, I think you mistook me for Mr. Give-A-Shit.
When I don't have my head stuck in a black hole,
I always listen to the hour of slack because it makes me laugh and I like to laugh.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Oh, you mustn't forget the nice letter.
Oh, my...
Uh-oh.
That's right, laddie.
It's an important physical document which you must keep with you at all times.
Especially now that the...
Dear Paul and Gary, you stink.
The show was a fake.
How can you guys laugh at my show behind your backs and still get away with it?
What was the show to you?
Some sort of sub-clown parade to impress your sick, groupie, fringe friends?
Like Nina Hogan and Mark Motherbrow?
I put my artistic life on the line.
And I get the subgenius Ed Sullivan show.
I work like a little devil trying to balance the forces of good and evil in three cities
and get the drum set set up and tuned each time,
the foam head adjusted, the radios and explosives in place,
the zombies checked out and nuked, the stage managers go get them speeches written,
and the line to tie Cleve in through the board done.
You guys just sit on your smiles waiting for someone to help you tear the veins off the sound man's amps.
Between Gary's asking where the food is and Paul,
your bitching about not wanting to clean where the banners are,
I was just about up to my sub-gland and too much is always butter for not enough.
Gary, you sad mop of a man.
Where do you get off thinking a child's towel is the way to go on stage?
With a band that now sounds like bus brakes,
you want me to play drums to what?
Hurting dolphins may be funny to you,
but it simply gives little Jerry Jeff callers everywhere the wrong and the long idea.
If you'd taken your mom up on that hair deal,
we could have had a decent light, man,
and some better church air, but no,
you said it's Bob's will,
and walked away.
Nice lights, Gabo fam.
Paul, you sniveling art snot.
To make it all your show,
you've moved the damn thing to LA,
and I had to blow it up on the freeway before we could go on.
You probably think putting the sponge head in the middle instead of me on the drums was pretty funny.
Intent as you were in wrecking my show,
I tell you, everyone,
with oral contract,
that I will wear my space suit,
and you scamper out to your friend to borrow his gorilla suit and space helmet.
If this is the new church,
the new take what you want from whoever you want,
well, you lowerites can sit on it and extrameditate.
I'm gonna go back to the legitimate religion where the sneakers become suckers the old-fashioned way.
We burn them, not each other.
Smith, that lost little fool.
He couldn't find Philo's shirt.
He's a show-hole with both pipes.
And he expects everyone to be excited about his limp dishrag of an act.
My buddy, D. Meyer, poop of all, etc.,
worked up some of the best lines and runs in the mouth history of the church.
And you steal them all the time, all of you, every line.
Then put him on last so you may deliver his best lines first, badly,
driving away all the people who know what we mean and leaving precious little for the audience.
For him to swing and swig and swoon to.
And for me, when I shot Bob, there were 200 tops left.
I could have shot all the audience, too.
There were so few left, I had enough bullets left in my gun.
I may have, I was so mad.
Why save the best for last?
Those people want to see Bob shot.
And you, school marmalade of a man, Smith, act for two years like it was you I shot.
I hand you the biggest publicity ploy since Jane and I.
And you complain the curse and cry to Paul, your sleep genius S.F. lackey,
about how it's just a blank.
And oh, he just does the best.
Really, well, you just coming up if you think you have been.
Uh, uh.
Where did you dig up those Arkansaniacs?
Funnier than a gravel mixer, yes, and noise that matches one.
But next time, get someone who knows how to dress
and won't sit in the middle of Broadway to eat his dinner.
Sticks, rocks, and knives.
Feuding.
Cemetery.
Graves.
No trespassing.
Stolen pig.
Escalated.
People died.
Killed and hurt.
Fight argument.
Hilliard Hall.
Fight rumble.
Gang fight.
Tattoos.
Fraternity.
Feud.
Uh, feud.
Don't forget, folks, the song that wouldn't die.
It's still in your brains.
You may not be able to hear it.
But it'll be with you always.
Following you through life.
In cover versions by Liberace and Herb Alpert and Gioanna Bratt.
Together.
The most horrible thing you can ever imagine.
With Tina Turner singing background vocals.
And Nancy Sinatra and Lee Haverwood.
And Yoko Ono.
And a cameo appearance by Mel Gibson as the World War II soldier returning to his daughter.
Melanie and Claudine Rosés.
With Bob sharpening knives.
And the Ghetto Boys.
The letter was written by Puzzling Evidence in copying David Rudepra, the amazing pope
of New York's first letter critiquing the first show of the first century, of the first
millennia, of the first group of subgeniuses that ever were.
That is the show's way.
Okay, we're just moving the body of the show out of the way here because in two minutes
I've got to hide this thing under the set.
Yeah, we've got to get it under the board.
Roll it in there.
I'll let them show it the other way.
I know what you mean.
I know exactly what you mean.
An elite padre, a random rogue group of renegade subgeniuses are responsible for this outrage
that we of the church utterly deny and show.
Can't figure out.
Can't think clearly.
And separate ourselves.
Friends, a little bit of KPFA in Berkeley.
Puzzling Evidence, Dr. Howell.
And, uh, Dr. Philodrum and other.
Well, we're about ready to wash down the worm, as they like to say in Cozumel, where
I like to hang my britches every Tuesday and some of the kids like to hang out with me
too.
I've got a good joke for you.
One of my friends, one of my little friends told me, he said there was this little boy
and kind of like a 40 year old man.
They didn't really know each other.
They were walking off towards the woods hand in hand.
And the little boy squeezed the older man's hand and said, I'm afraid, I'm afraid to go
in the woods.
And the man said, you're afraid.
Think of how I'm going to feel coming out alone.
And you know, that's what I think is wrong with today's people.
So true.
They just, they don't understand that when their time is nigh, they might as well plop
one in the eye.
They might as well forget the whole thing.
They might as well forget the whole routine.
Give up.
Give it up.
And buy one of these beautiful, beautiful synchronized goat shirts, ghost shirts from
the ghost dancers out there in the Lakota lands where the wind blows free and the bison
Now that's the name I've wanted in a long time.
J.R.
Bob Dobbs.
Oh, you didn't even know J.R.
in the mains?
I ain't give anything for another bowl of J.R.
Bob Dobbs maple syrup.
Oh, I remember him.
The only maple syrup drained straight from the cow's throat.
His fingers are like a knife.
His fingers were as black as the coal from all the coal he dug.
He'd circumcise the rectums of those when he would mutilate a cow to get the syrup all
down.
I remember.
He'd be put by any other name would smell his feet.
Dismembering a cow with Bob, now that was a fine Sunday.
Better than singing and going to the mines.
The old fashioned way.
Old fashioned.
That's the way to do it.
And yet there's no other way than the way that happened yesterday.
Day, day, day, day, day, day, day, day, day.
Oh, yesterday.
It's no time for an old man no more.
When I was a young baggie, we used to take three and five year olds.
We'd pull their hair out as long as it would go.
Really?
And drop them down into the shaft to see if they'd make a splattering sound.
Those were the days.
Before the damn English owner came here.
Absolutely disgusting.
Wouldn't let us start a union.
Those were the days when I was a young baggie.
Oh, you had a little bit of hair.
A little one-eyed fella.
Always standing up for his own rights and lefts.
Always eager to please the height.
Oh, he was.
I liked Jonah and the whale.
Until next week.
Keep your hat on tight.
You're back to the winter.
The sack and the saddle.
Keep your hat on tight.
That's after Princess May.
No, that's where it belongs.
She's a mysterious girl.
Order!
Who is it?
This is my rifle!
There are many licenses, but this one is mine!
This is the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
And you can get more information about the Church of the Subgenius from www.subgenius.com.
And friends, if you've got some kind of tapes or CDs you want to play on that you think is suitable,
is suitably bobbed and slacked up and conspiracy bashing and ear bone ripping to play on this Auguste Radio Show,
then you can send that to me, Reverend Ivan Stang at this address.
Stang at Postal.
Post Office Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
44118.
That's Box 181-417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
Praise Bob. Praise Bob. Praise help him.
You eat it back.
By the way, friends.
That song.
Earlier days and confused or believe that was my bomb water.
He be slacked or zombie.
Bob, give me my hand.
No.
Thank you, Bob.