Hmm. Hmm. Hmm. Hmm.
Hello?
In just a moment, enjoy feverish activity.
Oh!
But first...
The Self-Genius Power of Swag!
Oh, boy!
But, gee whiz, I don't want them!
I'm sorry.
Oh, gee whiz!
I see. Well, I'll tell...
Who?
Oh, boy.
Yes, the electronic brain will analyze the results.
Goodbye.
What?
I'm Reverend Ivan Stang from the Church of the Subgenius.
We worship this man, J.R. Bob Dobbs, who we've never met, which makes him that much more impressive.
The reason we're here at the Cannabis Cup is because, for some reason,
something about the nature of our religion, our videotapes and so forth,
seems to have...
appealed to these potheads and cannabis smokers.
I just don't understand that, except for the fact that what the religion that Bob preaches
is a religion devoted to slack.
Slack is the quality that we all want, but it's different for everybody.
The conspiracy of the normal people will try to make you swallow their form of slack,
and we, the subgeniuses, are what you might call the weirdos,
the disbelievers,
or people who believe anything,
who are fighting the conspiracy of the normal people,
in the name of this man, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
Praise Bob.
I, I, I, I, I...
I...
The subgenius.
Power of...
I'm a dirty dog, I'm a thief, I'm a fraud, I'm a flake, I'm Bob.
Thank you, Bob. I'm glad to be here.
Now, just in case the boys and girls have never seen you, would you mind telling them what a Bob looks like?
I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm big, big, about a foot. Yes, yes, I'm a very stiff one.
Tell the boys and girls why you're called Bob.
Bob, Bob, he really respects me because I destroy lots of horrors.
Are you nocturnal?
Yes, I love the night, Bob.
Oh, you must have.
Bob, yes. No way. Picked one off at a time. Bob, I had no failure.
I'll bet that was hard for you.
You've got it. Totally dark.
Okay, I've got you.
Okay, Bob, Bob.
A totally dark night. It's heart-shaped.
Okay, Bob.
You're kidding.
Bob.
Bob, and they're deadly.
Any sound that comes from the left, Bob, you've got it.
These sounds go to my brain, Bob, and a little hor-hor-hor is drawn in my brain.
Vertical or up and down directions?
Yes, up and down.
How does that work?
Higher. How high?
Okay, I see now.
Down on the floor, come together.
Incredible.
Less than a half a second.
And instantly, even though it's totally black, Bob.
Bob.
That Bob.
That part in my brain.
Bob.
That part in my brain now coming into my ears.
And you know what to do next.
To open up, and I'm on my way.
Fantastic.
laff
double stomp
club
off
close
place
log
off
I'm like a big summer gun, see how it flies.
I'm a liar.
Sitting on a cornflake.
Waiting for the fact to come.
Corporation t-shirts, stupid floaty Tuesday men.
You've been a naughty boy, you'll let your face grow long.
I am the end man.
They are the end men.
I am the worst.
Mr. City Policeman sitting in a pretty little policeman in a row.
See how they fly like Lucy in the sky, see how they run.
I'm crying, I'm crying, I'm crying.
I'm crying.
He's all the best, sir.
Drinking all the dead dogs I've found.
Covered like a fish, wife, pornographic beast.
They're spoiled men and naughty girls, you'll let your pictures down.
I am the end man.
Now wake up little Susie.
They are the end man.
I am the worst.
Goo goo goo goo.
I am the end man.
Now shed his Brock Coleman and see that no deutlich queulated anger and durosoleness lot of white men.
Hey you just義ó buena chica bilha de VE
I'm theB ettman, whoo.
UUU toot toot, woo.
I am the end man.
Wayyyyyyyy.
I am the worrestch uuuu momentosh woos y
Good, good, good, yeah!
Expat, expat, joking smokers
Don't you think the joke could upset you?
See how they smile like pigs in a stye
See how they snide
I'm crying
Semi-interfiltrate
Loaming up the iPhone tower
Get down from the high
Love the mickleーン
See how I miss the man
You should've seen him kick the nigga out of the door
I am the Eggman
We are the Eggman
I am the Morris
Hibiki-chou...
Hoy Snapchat
Hoy...
Aujourd...
We'll be right back.
Yay!
We're here to change the brain cells inside your head.
Bob can help you get rid of the brain cells you don't need, my friend.
With overwork and television,
the conspiracy has added more brain cells than you need.
We're here tonight to kill some of those brain cells.
Your brain cells can't be afraid to say,
kill me, Bob, if you want to know slack.
You have to be ready to be killed by Bob.
Most of you don't even know what slack is.
You think you have slack.
I can afford to go out and party at the disco, etc., etc.
Now I can afford to go out and get some slack.
That's the biggest lie in the world.
And the church is full of lies.
But that's one lie we won't join in on.
As long as you believe you have to afford slack,
then you have to pay for slack.
Your soul belongs to them.
But as long as you don't need money for slack, my friend,
the conspiracy cannot win.
So I have spoken from my script.
What?
So he has spoken?
We only have a limited time to kill those brain cells.
And so we have spoken.
So we have spoken.
A few short moments.
Fifty minutes, in fact, to kill every brain in your cells.
Friends, the world is ending.
You can see it in the website signsofwitness.com.
The birds are vanishing.
The polar bears are melting.
The tigers have all been eaten.
Genetically engineered chemtrails fall from the sky,
and all of us are dead.
All of our food is made of antibiotics.
People still name their teddy bears Muhammad, and that's bad.
But raping and killing civilians in Darfur, that's okay.
And China has declared cyber war on us all.
And American brain viruses are in every airport in Africa.
American brain viruses?
Yes.
What makes them so much different, Shorty?
What makes an American brain virus a little bit more stylish?
A little more crinkly on the edges, corners, and pigment.
They make the Africans sicker, and the African viruses make the Americans sicker.
It makes the Africans more aggressive.
And vice versa, same with China, and you could name, slip, slide any country into that slot.
It makes them want to build skyscrapers, and tanks, and bullets, and guns, and cheese.
It makes them want to stomp in big, huge boots all over your family.
More skyscrapers!
More.
We need more.
We need to reach the skies.
Say, I should give, speaking of reaching for the skies, how about that cover of I Am the Walrus medley?
I'm scrying.
That was, I believe, Phineas Narco.
Reverend Phineas Narco put that together.
That was our Phineas, yes.
He's really good at that.
He's too bluster.
He's from National.
National Cynical Radio dot com.
National Cynical dot com.
One of those two.
I can't remember.
National Cynical Network?
Something's not right.
You're killing your own brain cells, Stang.
Tonight, we kill the brain cells of the public.
No.
Well, yes.
If the public has some brain cells left, then we can kill them, because there are none left for us to kill.
In our own brains.
No.
Our brains have been homogenized into one uber cell.
Yes.
Well, Princess, we and I, we're glad that you have your brain cell, your one huge cell.
The monocelic surround it.
Because our...
It's like a sun.
It's like a planet.
Our two half-brain cells have been depleted completely.
Flattened.
Our brain cells are gone because we were at the Amsterdam Frop Cup devival.
And field trip.
In fact, actually, there's been two big devivals since I've last been on the radio live here.
And this...
Because we did...
There was the Baltimore devival.
You're in the town of Lord Baltimore, and then you're in...
No, the town of Tim Orr.
Timor?
Yeah.
Tim Orr is what that town is named after.
East Timor?
Baltimore.
Oh.
Reverend Tim Orr.
Oh, I thought it was named after Lord Baltimore.
And his white wig and his funny socks.
Tim didn't show up.
But everybody else...
Baltimore...
Baltimore devival was wonderful, and we'll play tapes from that when we can edit the curse words out.
Same with the Amsterdam devival, when we can edit the brain cells back in.
Re-suture, re-snip, a little link here, a little snap there, a little whoosh, whoosh, whoosh, whoosh, whoosh, whoosh.
And they're all re-hexed.
Just like the Babalox.
Remember, the Babalox will keep up with you as long as you can keep up with it.
And if you don't want, then you don't have to.
Ah, shuffling through papers.
I see something.
It's...
Oh, my God.
It's a message from J.R. Bob Doobes.
Who the hell is Doobes?
Bob's cousin.
Bob Doobes?
The infamous Doobes family.
Doobes.
Yes, they were drug smugglers.
That explains why it's...
The Doobes brothers.
It's not a pipe.
They were also rock stars.
Yes, they were kind of third-level rock stars.
Many hits, but very few twits.
And look.
Oh, my God.
It says Doobes was married three times to an angular woman from Apachinata, a place in Spain, I guess.
What a lovely life.
A long and happy and healthy life, unlike the life of J.R.
J.R. Bob Doobes.
Who?
Insert name here.
If only I could wedge my name in that little spot.
But there's no room above the title for me yet.
Well, there's ESQ, after all.
One of these days, though.
I've got a lot of other directors I have to kill.
Actually, I've got to start with Matt Grenning of Futurama.
You want to hurt him?
Oh, yeah.
I saw the new Futurama movie, which is a straight-to-DVB movie, last night.
And I cried because he had beat me.
Not only had he beat me to several good ideas I was going to use in that subgenius movie script,
but he pulled them off better than I was going to.
Damn him!
Don't worry about that.
Oh, well.
But I don't care, because my brain has been cleansed and flensed and resurrected
after our brainwashings there in Holland Headland, Holland.
So did you have to wear the little metal helmets with the cybles?
No, that's for the people in the cannabis cup, which was going on simultaneously.
Oh.
We, however, were with the FROP Cup.
Now, Governor Rotnar and Dr. Howell were with us, and they were judges in the cannabis cup.
And Reverend Daddy Joseph of Jesus was there, and Claudia, his true yeti mate.
And they were vendors at the cannabis cup.
And we helped them.
We were willing, with some arm-bending, to go from coffee shop to coffee shop and advise them,
help them judge.
But we had our own business to do there.
We had devivals and radio shows, and we had the FROP Cup judging, which was different.
You know, FROP is not a drug.
FROP is an herb.
Well, first, you should probably describe the actual cannabis cup, and then describe the FROP Cup so we can make a comparative judgment.
Well, the cannabis cup is kind of a rip-off for dumb college kids, essentially.
They pay $175 to go and get a little program book at this big convention hall,
where they can also wander around.
Smoke cigarettes and buy overpriced Thai junk food.
And look at the latest in pot smoking technology, such as clear rolling papers.
Yes, transparent rolling papers.
Someone we know tried them.
And it's like the visible joint.
But they actually do work.
They're not very healthy, are they?
I'm told.
And...
Well, they make...
Well, I heard this year at the cup, the Copa de Oro,
that there was a randomness vector that interrupted both the FROP escapade and also the cannabis.
And not to mention the D-cup.
It spilled over into the D-cup as well, and the ex-porn star party.
Well, that happens a lot.
Which was last night.
On the shores of the good old Zyder Sea, there's a lot of flopping going on regularly.
As a matter of fact, we knew it was going to be a good trip when we walked into the apartment we were allowed to stay at,
except...
We couldn't walk in.
The door...
We couldn't open the door all the way because there were two subgeniuses making love sweet love
right in the middle of the living room floor of the apartment we thought we had all to ourselves.
But nay, a British subgeniusman...
Spreading orgasmatic rays everywhere.
An American subconnyite had met and fallen in instant lust.
Shoredurper lust, you might say.
Shoredurper lust?
Now, if it was...
He's a subgenius sort of affair.
We waited until they were through before we moved our suitcases in.
Wouldn't they naturally or subnaturally be making hate instead of making war?
I mean...
No, instead of making love?
Well, you know, you said it was two subgenii copula...
Yes, they were doing sex hurt.
It's the divine battle between man and woman.
And so each one hurts in turn, or each one...
First he thrusts, and then she thrusts, and then he thrusts, and then she thrusts...
Ouch!
And then she lays her eggs, and he fertilizes the eggs.
And then he does a rhythmic dance, waving his waver over her waver.
Right.
Spelled W-A-I-A-I.
And then if he's the suicide show at the subgenius revival, such as our new friend Crazy White Sean,
after fertilizing the eggs, he hammers his member to a board and puts hooks in it and swings bowling balls from it.
Schwarzkogler, baby.
You know, we worked with...
We worked with sideshow marvels before at subgenius devivals, like the Great Circus Apocalypse and Andrew the Impaled.
But the aptly named Crazy White Sean was even harder working than the subgenius sideshow freaks that I've seen.
By a quantum leap.
Yeah, Princess, we couldn't look at it at all.
Also, I've got a list.
Actually, I have a nice list of what happened at the subgenius devival when...
I mean, it was a normal devival up to a point.
I preached.
Dr. Hal preached to Pope Black and so forth.
Reverend Lucky Bastard.
But then Crazy White Sean, his performance involved in part, not necessarily in this order, and this is all true, friends,
drinking his urine, which was demonstrably his, eating worms and cockroaches, lining his penile and lips with mousetraps,
making a pincushion of his face and then blowing wine out the holes in his cheeks.
Stapling his...
His...
Sack to his belly.
And stapling notes to his forehead.
Well, my grandfather used to staple his sack to his belly on the way home so he would not, you know, lose the procedure and have to go through configuration again.
Well, I just have never seen anybody do this before in, you know, modern times.
This guy, Crazy White Sean...
I mean...
Of crazywhiteshawn.com, if you don't believe me,
would suck live worms into his nose and then let them kind of...
Crawl live, still alive, out of his mouth.
He could work them in and out of his sinuses like that.
Well, that guy's old.
They do intestinal gags now.
Swinging billiard balls on chains.
You're right.
Actually, the real...
At the big devivals, we do the...
They open their guts up and let people play with their bowels and stuff, like you're saying, and palpate the liver.
Yeah, well, they say...
They're still beating hard in the audience's hand.
They say that a lot of those people are plants.
Anyway, I'm sorry.
The ones that, you know, come up and fondle the organs.
That's so to speak, yeah.
Speaking of plants...
Like vegetables, right?
The, um...
Some people don't understand what the cannabis cup is.
And, uh...
What a segue.
When you spend your $175 or whatever for a ticket,
they don't...
You don't sit at a big table with other judges and have silver goblets of bud brought to you.
No.
You have to...
You have to walk from coffee shop to coffee shop,
buy the contestant samples by the gram,
and judge smoke them,
and then pretend that you're turning in some kind of a ballot,
but in fact, all the winners are already picked.
It was G13 Hayes from Barney's this year, I think, was the top prize for those guys.
That's a true name now?
This is not a...
That's a Barney's Hayes-y thing?
Barney's G13 Hayes was the top winner, I think,
uh, what?
Princess Wee, I can't remember the...
Some of the other...
There's Blue Cheese was a good one this year.
These are real pot labels, by the way.
These are things that they call marijuana these days.
Amnesia Hayes.
The aptly named, uh, Amnesia Hayes.
But why a...
Isolator, because it's made with ice.
Well, I would think you would be very paranoid and sit in a corner while everyone else was also sitting in a different corner.
Now, where did the name Blue Cheese come from?
Is it like Blue Cheer being funny?
Or do you actually start smelling it?
Because it smells sort of like smegma.
Smegma.
The, um...
Now, this is all kid's stuff, though.
Princess Wee and I didn't...
We watched...
It was fun, actually, to go through the Canem's Cup and watch all this stuff.
But we didn't mess with that kid's stuff because we had to save our blood cells and brain cells for the Frop Cup.
And, uh...
Which was just amazing.
And I have a list of winners here of the Subgenius Frop Cup in Amsterdam.
Can I just say that I heard, as a rumor, before you read the names of the beauteous ones, that the Prime Minister of France, Sarkozylgian...
Yeah.
Put on a funny...
Sarcophagus.
Put on a funny mustache and a wig so that he could attend the Frop judging.
All those Bilderberger guys were there.
In fact, we were at the Suzanne Bilderberger Gallery.
Had a big party for all the Bilderbergers and Burger Beisters.
Where CFR says...
I'm not kidding.
Country fried...
You think I'm kidding?
I'm actually not kidding.
And those things did happen.
But, uh...
Yes, we...
Let me list some of the winners here from the Frop Cup.
And these were all judged by subgeniuses.
Humans can't even handle this stuff.
The number one top winner was Super Jenkum Hayes.
Super Jenkum Hayes.
I don't know that brand.
From Zandy Smith's Laboratories.
Limburger Skunk.
Was second place.
And Bloody Cough Mist...
Ha.
Was, I think, third place.
There was a special prize given to a strain called Former Genius Afghani.
And I think Bleepo Abernathy won with Candy Frappy Skunk Stool.
Now, was that a windowsill variety of the stool?
Was the stool a windowsill variety of stool?
No, it's outdoor.
Oh, okay.
I think it was outdoor.
Those are hard to keep track of, usually.
There was a Dutch one that was really good called Niederlobotomy, or Nederlobotomy.
I never was sure how to pronounce that.
I think, yeah.
See, Screaming Skull, Mind Crash, Hash, Brain Poo, Haze.
You're forgetting the Silver Schizo.
Yeah, Silver Schizo, Screaming Skull.
Mr. Nothinghead was...
That was a name.
Actually, I can't remember.
Mr. Nothinghead just zoned me.
Bionic Manson was popular, I think, just because of the name.
Probably, yeah.
You know, character recognition and reference thing.
And Black Trainwreck.
I forget who grew that.
Or I should say, I forget which Yeti dropped the fertilizer it was grown on,
or which Dead Tibetan Holy Man's grave it was grown on.
Yeah, you did say...
Because these are all grown on certain...
Like, there's a Tibetan guy named Krunt.
Certain deaths, actually.
Certain dead guys, actually, you know.
Kimo Krunt Flash is grown on that Krunt's, Llama Krunt's grave.
Now, what was that necrohighlight?
I don't remember.
I mean, by definition.
That is a problem with...
Yeah, that's why you can't...
It's the one you least remember is the winner.
How was the Bloody Mist?
Well, you know, it was...
Mint Mist.
But there's no recollection.
There's nothing left to hang on to recollection.
It's all dripping out of your ears now.
Oh, goo-goo on the head, spinning around.
That was the Bloody Lung Mist, or Bloody Cough Mist.
Now, speaking of bloody lungs,
Lunk, you know, is another category that got prizes.
There was Ice Lunk, which is...
Do you know what Lunk is?
Oh, it's the...
It's the...
It's the silly person who won't do his job.
Okay, say somebody's a heavy fropper.
Oh, he's a Lunk.
When they die...
You big Lunk.
When they die, the other people who are in the Lunk Club
get to smoke the scrapings from the lungs of a heavy smoker who has died.
It's lung junk.
It's like squeezing a frog's butt.
Right, but it's...
It used to be that you just, you know...
Like I'm in the club.
When I die, she'll...
Whichever one of us dies first...
Yeah.
...we get a scrap.
Yeah, I've seen your tag.
But we got...
They've made this Ice Lunk,
where they can make a Lunk more powerful
and get ten times as much, you know, whatever off of it.
Do they freeze dry at first,
or is it the Lunk is just from the usage?
I don't know, but I met the old lady who invented the process.
Wow.
Mila Bella or something like that,
and she was...
Doc Frop is a big fan of hers.
Is she also a Dutch sword?
Oh, they have Lunk oil,
which smells awful, but is...
You know, you put a little bit of it on a...
Dead person, and it will raise the dead.
And then sniff it, and it's better than Jenkum.
Death Lunk Hash,
which is...
I guess what that is, is like they...
They find people who've only smoked...
fresh,
and then scrape that from their lungs.
But it's not...
They can't use anybody who's been mixing it,
you know, with like tobacco or pot or anything.
It has to be pure.
Yeah, I thought, you know,
frash is real delicate.
Anyway.
So, I think that's...
Oh, blue brain damage was one of them.
Oh, I found...
Oh, Time Warp Mania dub.
Funny names.
So, does that one actually work?
Hey, speaking of funny names,
at the Cannabis Cup, there was one...
This is honestly true.
There was one called Princess Bob.
Indica.
Princess Bob Indica.
Well, what you're saying is that they changed genders
during the hydroponic procedure.
And that's the same thing they do with some of the frop
and some of the llama's graves.
They just change the light to like an organ blue light,
and it makes it more...
It'll change it from...
...digestible.
And I'm sorry, what?
Well, I think...
And they cross them, too.
They'll like crossbreed and make these hybrids,
where something is part pineapple death star
and part of its sonic death star.
And then they'll just boom sativa.
Man, if we could just remember what they felt like.
I know.
Well, but if you could,
you know you got ripped off.
If you could remember it,
you'd know it wasn't any good.
But if there was some way we could like,
you know, put some sort of memory device
or something in our brain that would record it
so we could view it afterwards, you know, after the...
I'm sure that the RIAA will figure out a way to do that.
The record...
American Record Industry of America?
Right.
Oh, okay.
They're ahead on spy techniques.
They're ahead of almost everybody, except the Chinese.
Well, that's because the Chinese are married into the British family now.
Well, and they're Chinese.
Well, no, they're part bird, too,
if you want to really, you know, get way, way, way back
about nine million years ago.
Or no, it was nine billion...
Nine was in there somewhere.
Well, we all were part bird back in the...
Oh, yeah.
Only a little part, though.
Well, you don't want to be the littlest part
of the little part of the bird.
What's the word?
The bird is the word?
The bird.
Speaking of...
You know, you can talk about all your blueberry haze
and your super bubblegum stuff,
but there ain't nothing like a big old bottle
of Thunderbird wine from Modesto, California.
Yeah.
America's fine.
Aperitif wine.
Yeah, it's fine.
You can get it in the 12%...
You can get it in the 12% blue bottle
or your 19% red bottle.
Yeah, the red's always the one I win for.
No kidding, buddy.
Beat the damn bejesus out of white port and lemon juice.
That's the silliest damn drink any girl ever drank.
You need a red tea bird.
That's what you need, you know,
and then you wink three times and your eye falls out.
Thunderbird.
Serve very cold.
I actually just recited, I think,
all of the words on the label of the Thunderbird bottle.
I used to do that back when I was a kid.
You needed to...
I drank a lot of bottles of Thunderbird,
and that's why I'm the way you see me now.
I'm 25 years old, and look at me.
It looks more like 52, if you know what I mean.
Backwards.
25 is backwards, man.
And on those tea bird bottles,
do they also have the substantial alien gum?
Or any of the other, you know,
you may lose your body dust,
discorporated at any time?
I don't know.
Those used to come with a great comic book
on the inside label.
You know, once you drank the bottle,
you could read it through the bottle.
And there was some lantern jarred guy.
It was Hand Grenade Joe or something.
Hand Grenade Joe.
Yeah, Hand Grenade Joe and his little sidekick.
And Popeye Fishman.
Yeah, that's his name.
He was a short guy, kind of funny, you know.
Funny looking, I can't remember.
They never made any sense,
but that was the charm of it.
Yeah, especially when you can't get it out.
You got to that last drop.
You know, you kind of could make,
just come up with the lyrics as you wanted,
you know, as you pleased.
There was a rumor that Ernie Bushmiller
did the Hand Grenade Joe comics
on the inside label of the Thunderbird bottles.
You know, the guy did Nancy comics.
Remember Nancy?
It was pre-Zippy surrealism.
Yeah.
See, that's how I could get confused.
I thought you were going to say Anheuser-Busch
or George Bush or something,
but I see there was no Bush in there.
Man, you know, George Bush is so awful
that I actually miss his grandfather,
Emperor Anheuser-Busch.
I mean, I never thought the day would come
when it was like, man,
George W. is so bad.
George Bush would be,
George Bush the first would be better.
Anheuser-Busch would be better.
Anheuser-Busch would be best for all of us,
or could be,
but this is not a commercial station,
but that's a real man,
well, if you want to call him a man,
that's a real corporate being,
or corporal.
Did I say that?
Corporal, real being's name.
I miss Nixon's head.
I miss the smell of his feet.
I'd save his brain if I could.
I'd save Nixon's brain if I could
if I thought that would replace George Bush's.
You're not the only one, lad.
There's a lot of people in the basement here
who would like a good whiff of Nixon's brain.
Tasty.
It's like that Orson's ads are brought.
I know.
Have you ever huffed the Fuhrer's brain?
Have you ever taken the extra time
to sniff a good Fuhrer?
No.
Sit on your knees in a casual pose.
Now appear very formal.
Remember, you're wearing a suit for a Fuhrer.
I'm all formal now.
A suit of cards.
You're the ace of ducks.
Now bend over and smell the Fuhrer's brain.
Ah!
Ha ha!
Uber stench!
Let me smell.
Smell.
Smell the Fuhrer's brain.
Max smell!
Max, please sit down.
It's only a demonstration.
And this is only a puff of what?
And only a gun in my hand.
It's not a real gun.
It's a...
beat handgun.
But it will still shoot you and kill you.
It's a gun from Dobbs!
Oh, I don't think it's a real gun from Dobbs.
They'll kill you if you have a toy gun.
They'll give you a medal if it's a real gun.
Princess Wee, do you remember having the rice table meal like Dave suggested?
Remember?
You're not allowed to use that word with me.
You know, remember?
Remember?
No, we went to the rice table restaurant, but we didn't get the rice table.
Lonesome Princess Dave.
It's true though, Lonesome Princess Dave.
You had suggested that...
You said, go to the Malaysian restaurant and have the rice table.
Well, that's what I heard was really, really swinging and Amsterdam-er.
Well, we saw...
We went by a place called Indonesian Restaurant.
I think that was the name of it.
How creative.
And they had a poster outside for the rice table.
And we ran in and then did not order the rice table.
But we saw the pictures of the rice table, just so you know.
It's exorbitantly large, right?
It was a bunch of bowls. It was a bunch of stuff.
But we had a bunch of other stuff.
Of equal quantity?
I think we had grüntesupp.
Grüntersupp?
Grüntersupp.
Was ist Grüntersupp?
Das Grüntersupp is like the drugs.
In the Badkammer.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I remember everything from every meal from every restaurant.
I can tell you what everybody ate.
Every single one.
Governor Ragnar had duck.
That's right. He always had duck.
He had duck. That's easy to remember.
Ragnar wouldn't eat anything but duck.
Mmm.
But duck is very tender.
But duck was at the Indonesian place?
No, but duck was some stuff we smoked.
Oh.
Mixed with the Jack Harer.
We met Jack Harer, who for you non-pot smokers out there like ourselves.
Such a real name.
Pot connoisseurs would go,
Oh my God, you met Jack Harer?
Here's the interesting thing.
I didn't know what Jack Harer looked like or sounded like.
He's a guy that invented some real powerful drugs.
And he wrote a book.
He wrote a book called The Emperor Wears No Clothes,
which is a good history of the illegalization of hemp, etc.
Anyway, this is a guy that really smokes a lot of pot.
And he talks like this.
His voice is like this.
So I thought that figures.
If you were going to be a serious professional pot smoker,
that your voice would turn into a gravel pit.
He earned that voice.
Which mine seems to be doing right now.
Does he have indeed sarcophagi in his throat then?
Has he pushed this healthy drug into a non-healthy thing?
Or is he just has a, you know, a wispy voice?
He probably smokes cigarettes too.
I don't know.
I don't know nothing about it.
For a long, long, long time.
I do know that Christmas is coming.
And in Netherland, Neanderthal lands,
they have a different tradition than Santa Claus here.
They call it, actually our Santa Claus is based on.
Sinterklaas.
And instead of a bunch of little elves,
he has a bunch of little Moors or Ethiopians,
depending on how you look at it.
But they're very, his main one is called Black Peter.
Well, that's a, that's a disturbance.
Have you ever heard of Black Peter?
That is a disease.
I've heard, I've heard a lot about Black Peter myself,
but this is somebody's name.
Although I thought it was by the necroprosis of the peanuts.
P-I-T-E-R.
Peter.
Black Peter.
Or Schwarzpeter.
Schwarzpeter.
Is I think his name there.
And the funny thing is though that he's,
they have these graphic illustrations of him.
There's all these Santa, Sinterklaas,
who looks pretty much like Santa Claus.
But Black Peter is depicted in a way that is not offensive,
apparently in Europe,
but in the United States where we have this past unpleasant history.
He's wearing lipstick, right?
He's, yeah.
He's like something out of an old R. Crumb comic
that nobody got and got very angry about.
He's like something out of an old Max Fleischer cartoon
that they don't show anymore because you know.
He's like something out of a Tarzan movie that makes you go,
oh, no wonder they don't show those Tarzan movies anymore.
Yes, they don't show his fine garb.
They just show a lot of lipstick and rouge and mascara.
But in the context of the Netherlandish history,
there's apparently nobody gets terribly upset about Black Peter.
But he's about as PC as our Clevelandian brave smiling head,
Chief Wahoo or.
You know, that's an interesting thing that you brought up,
Chief Wahoo, because I just heard recently on the Racial Epithet Network.
Yeah.
It was a right wing talk show guy.
He said Indians love me and I love Indians.
And then he went on to explain why it was so good that we won.
Meaning, I guess his uncle, Jerry.
I don't know the actual guy, you know,
like if he was related to custard or any of those famous snakes in the garments.
He was saying that it was icons, you know, back in the day.
Anyway, well, you know, I suppose the Native Americans probably could have kept the invaders out.
Had they quit fighting amongst themselves?
Or if they had automatic weapons, it would have been better.
And that is the lesson for all people who are being invaded.
Quit fighting with your neighbor and fight the big enemy.
Subgeniuses, quit fighting each other and fight against poverty.
Yeah, that's it.
Fight against poverty so that you can get rich and have lots of money and buy donations to this station.
That's it.
Yes, but subgeniuses.
I almost said the wrong thing.
But subgeniuses cannot enjoy poverty.
Because their lifestyle requires a high configuration when you go through a relapse or something.
Or if you keep having different parts removed.
Right.
What if you have like the whole bottom part of your torso is like exchanged, as we like to say,
you know, with some sort of celestial being.
What do you mean, what if?
Well, I mean, you know, once it's done.
Last time, you mean.
And then you're like, you know, a T-bird drinking bum, you know, looking around in dumpsters for something.
Right, right.
And so what does it all avail you?
I mean, what does avail mean?
Oh, what is it?
Okay.
But that's just, that's the way I saw it.
I was cross-eyed at the time and I was also pinching different nerves.
The karma, the Burma and the Dharma nerve, which makes things go backwards too.
But not like Dobbs does it.
Nah, he's.
I don't know.
He fat, spelled P-H-A-T.
That's old school, but it still stands true.
Uh huh.
Ah ha!
Yeah!
You know what?
Uh, Reverend Joseph Daddy of Jesus went to Fez, Morocco and bought Fez's.
Oh, I thought you.
And gave us, gave, gave, and gave me, brought back a Fez and gave me a Fez and he gave Dr.
Howell a Fez.
Oh, Howell has a fine collection of Fez's.
Right.
I actually had a Schreiner Fez myself, but a Fez, a Moroccan Fez is not quite the same as a Schreiner Fez.
They're cooler, aren't they?
They're shorter.
They're squatter.
Yeah, they're more squat and they don't usually have eyeballs.
balls
emblemized on them.
Or naked women or anything else.
Like mine do.
You have an eyeball on yours?
Hal has an eyeball on his and mine has
naked women on it.
Oh, you got a naked lady on your dress?
Well, it was Dallas Shriner group I got from.
I thought yours said hell.
No, the Masons.
They're into group sex, orgies and all that.
Baby sacrifice.
Haven't you been reading the internet?
I didn't know you actually had to read the internet.
I thought you just sat there.
You don't anymore.
As of this week, everything on the internet is now a movie.
It's all YouTube and it's TV.
That would take care of a lot of problems.
You can't upload.
It's back to TV.
Birds, sycophants, non-readers,
excremeditators.
You know, all these different people who have no real
reason to sit down
and study an object.
They can just clarify it in their own mind and say
this is it or it isn't. It doesn't exist.
Mm-hmm.
Princess Wee, do you remember your favorite shop
on Calverstrat?
Wee.
She does remember it.
It was a shop called Wee.
W-E.
They forgot the I.
We met a French lady named Marie.
And when Princess Wee told her her name,
she went, oh, so you're the opposite
of Princess No.
Oh, Princess Wee-Wee?
She said that?
She said, oh, no, no, no, Wee, Wee, Wee.
Well,
that Marie, what a punner.
Actually, that woman would have been good on this show.
Yes, she was.
English was not her first language,
but she was an unrepentant
punster, or punstress,
as I suppose you might say.
A punita, sometimes they say when they tie you up
and smack you.
Is that the Spanish, the punita?
No, that's more like when they put you in a dark room
and they have to wear, like, big, long hats,
red hats and feathers and stuff,
and then they squeeze and twist.
That's, you know, the punishment idea.
I am a punero.
A puniero?
No, not puniero.
That's come together.
I'll kill you for saying that.
A punero.
A punero does it with...
A punero is like a caballero,
like a horseman, only it's a punman.
Oh, it rides a pun.
You know what a pun is, or a pun.
It's a play on words.
Right.
Like Joe Smell.
I pun.
You know, like you download from I pun,
you get these word plays.
Well, most of them are dirty also.
I mean, not physically dirty,
but they're salacious in nature.
Most puns are.
I mean, just think of Fonda,
you know, when you were in school.
That's...
We shouldn't go there.
No.
No, no, no.
We should go instead to the Vondelpark.
Not the Fondal room.
Yes, let's go to the Vondelpark.
Is it a real or virtual...
We'll go wandering in the wonderful Vondelpark.
Is it a virtual...
Was it a virtual park?
And we have some of the worst waffles there.
Oh, bad waffles?
Waffles.
No, no, worse.
Not bad.
They're very good.
Sausage waffles?
The worst waffles are very good.
Yes, that's the brand name, Dave, is worse.
It's V-E-R-S-E.
Worse.
So it's worse waffles.
Yeah, waffles.
W-A-F-E-L-S.
Death to the Dutch for confusing their W's and V's like that.
Princess, we and I have the most fun reading Dutch labels
because the words are funny.
They all sound funny.
They all sound like American curse words.
You know, we got...
You pinterkass, you.
Pindekass.
Yeah, that's a pindekass.
You pindekass, you.
What's a pindekass?
Peanut butter.
Oh, you peanut butter.
You pindekass.
Actually, it's the cheese of the peanut because kass is cheese.
So it's like peanut cheese, yes.
Oh, my God.
Pindekass.
You're our pindekass.
Well, not always.
Sometimes it's simple.
What a bizarre group of little Hitlers.
They should smack them right in the desire to see.
They killed Frank and they were proud.
They were proud of it.
Each and every one of them.
Their ice skates and their foreheads and...
I remember I came up with an idea for a movie last night.
After Matt Greinig stole all my ideas, I came up with a new idea.
Greinig is a Dutch name, Stan.
Greinig is a Dutch name.
Greinigsip.
Yeah.
Oh, and oh, speaking of Dutch names, our friend Orton Nenslow, the subgenius,
his real name is Ken DeVries.
Okay, I know that's Dutch.
Okay, well, he's therefore related.
He's related.
He's related to a woman named Vera DeVries, whose house we had a big dinner at.
In fact, Rocknar and Dr. Howell stayed there.
But you know her as Xaviera Hollander.
Oh.
Xaviera Hollander is a subgenius.
So it would be like if you decided to become a prostitute, you would call yourself Reverend
Ivan American.
The happy...
Schnooker.
Leg Humper.
The happy Schnooker.
Yeah, Xaviera Hollander, for those of you who don't know her, she's a woman who's been
doing a lot of work in the United States, but she's also a woman who's been doing a lot of
She's a woman who, who are ignorant, wrote a book.
She was actually the most successful madam in New York City in the late 60s and early
70s.
She wrote a book about her experiences servicing and providing for rich and powerful figures
in world history.
It's called The Happy Hooker and several sequels.
It was such a big deal.
Did you ever read The Happy Hooker?
Stang.
You should have.
I would bring up the fact that you know that back in those days I was a very wealthy young
man and I traveled in those circles.
Oh, so you already knew Vera.
And the nose piercing and also the bladder enslavement and the...
You know that a lot of the quotes in that book...
You probably helped Xaviera write her book.
I was the research dodo.
I was the dummy box.
That explains a lot.
I was the surface area of a cube.
That explains everything.
Yep.
Lonesome Cowboy.
Dave and Xavier Hollander together again.
Well, I wasn't there.
Mysteries unfurled before us.
Starring...
Let's see who...
Now, who played...
Xavier was played in three different movies.
She was played by Joey Heatherton, Lynn Redgrave, and Martine Beswick.
I don't remember the Martine Beswick one.
I think that was after the short-sighted.
But who played you?
What was that guy who played you in those movies?
It was that bald-headed guy that's in those Die Hard...
What's his name?
Dr. Phil.
No, no, no, no.
The Die Hard movie guy.
What's his name?
That bald-headed guy?
Oh, Die Hard.
Die Hard Smith or something.
Yeah, Mr. Knuckles.
Clint Eastwood?
No, no.
You know, Mr. Knuckles.
He's like a real right-wing type of guy.
Actually, Clint Eastwood could play Dave now.
Clint looks...
Clint and Dave look...
Clint's about 70 years older than Dave, but they look about the same.
Clint Eastwood?
It's not tall enough to play Dave.
He's an Easterner, too, by the way, Sting.
I'd like to...
Clint Eastwood is?
Yeah.
Oh, no wonder he's got that name.
Ivy League.
Cornwell.
Prince of Poopo.
Really?
Yeah.
Is that so?
I don't think it's so, but that's true.
It's true.
Okay.
Prince of Poopo?
We were talking about bees before.
Who wouldn't play Dave in a movie?
Oh, man, I keep on forgetting that bald-headed guy's face again.
Every time I hear his name in my mind...
Bruce Willis.
That's right.
That's the guy, Bruce Willis.
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
I won.
But he was funny in the one where Alexander Graham Bell came back to life.
Now, Mel Gibson did a pretty good job of playing you in Conspiracy Theory.
He did a better job in Apocalyptic.
Apocalyptic.
He didn't act in that.
He directed that.
He was the invisible...
Oh, I gotcha.
No, seriously.
Did you ever see Conspiracy Theory?
I saw it.
Didn't you, like, want to sue Mel Gibson for playing you?
Well, he wasn't bald.
He just had the same manners.
He had the same hat.
And he had this sort of way of talking in this excited way that was hard for his people to, you know, his fares to understand.
And then he would say...
I'm sorry.
Oh, yeah.
I remember he was feral.
He was wild.
Yeah.
Yeah, he had to actually smell different.
It was as if he'd been listening.
He'd been doing research.
He'd been doing research for the part by listening to Brain Rot Radio Theater.
This was in the 90s.
Well, don't...
Didn't you just get done saying that the Radio Industry Association of America has a lot more power than you think it does?
Well, yeah.
And, you know, there's a CD of the surveillance that's on the web now.
You can...
They owe explanations to so many, but you'll never, ever, ever get them.
They owe explanations to the many.
And gravy to the few.
The kind that you cook and liver and enjoy with a hot snack.
Like that light going off in your head.
That little light just went off in my head.
That's a caramel-flavored light in your head.
That means something sinister is coming.
A lime light and a strawberry light.
I'm sorry.
Something sinister is coming?
Yes, something sinister is coming.
Soon.
I thought that was the smell of new shoes.
Do you remember the new shoe smell?
I remember the new shoe smell.
You know, when we were little girls.
We'd go out with Mom and Dad and Uncle Fritz.
He was really mean.
But we'd go to the lounge afterwards and we'd just drink water or like Tinky Punch, they called it.
And there'd be like a little Tinky bottle or glass.
The smell of new shoes always reminds me of those punches.
I know.
Every time I...
And my dad beating me.
Punching and hitting me.
He wasn't really beating you.
He was just trying to execute you.
He didn't know how to do it right, so he had to, you know, use his fists.
If he had any brain, he would have just shot you, but...
A little bit at a time, you know.
Now, there's something like seven minutes to show end.
Is there anything important we needed to remember or do?
We owe thanks to the listeners that paid their pledges and death to the ones who pledged but didn't ever pay.
Unless they're planning to pay.
Yeah, they're in the future.
In which case, they can't die.
And let's see.
I'm going to...
Oh, I'm going to be in San Francisco next week on Castro Street.
Wearing a wig.
I will be sleeping on Castro Street, but in Martinez, not in San Francisco, which is different.
And, you know, because there's some sort of a devotional thing about Devo, but yet they're doing subgeniously things, too.
And I...
Does it have a name that you can't mention?
It's on December 8th on subgenius.com, if you really wanted to know, at the 12 Galaxies Club, I think.
But like I say, that's an African brain virus, and we've got to be careful about the airport when that happens.
Because it's over $1,000.
Remember saying that's not the right...
Which we got compensated because they overbooked the lobotomy lab.
And we had to wait an hour and a half to get our lobotomies, and they paid us...
Uh...
$300.
$300 each.
For each...
To compensate us for having to wait an hour and a half for our lobotomy.
Can you believe it?
This is a pretty good deal.
$300 is like $500.
Well, that's all...
Well, by now, it's probably like about...
Each suture costs...
Or $700.
There's another $700.
That's how they do it, by the suture.
Yeah, it goes...
That's more bucks per euro per minute.
That's the way it's working now.
A homo sapien insecurity is what I call it.
But then that's when they keep you at the airport so long that your body starts to decompose.
And before they find out if you have any contraband...
Are you kidding anywhere?
It just pops out naturally with its own free will.
You know what?
I accidentally smuggled...
Once again, I accidentally smuggled contraband into the United States without knowing I was doing it.
Completely accidentally.
I've done it going both ways.
I've smuggled contraband into Holland and then discovered it.
An orange.
And I've smuggled contraband into the Americas without knowing it until I got home and unpacked and went,
Good Lord!
If I'd known this, I could have carried 5,000 pounds of hashback and made a million bucks selling it to school kids.
See, it just shows how much more laid back they are than the Californians.
But I wouldn't do that.
You know why?
Because it would be wrong.
Ah.
When you go to California, they ask you if you have any fruits or vegetables and they mean,
Are there any little children in your back seat?
Right.
Or under the back seat is what I meant to say.
So why...
What is the point of smuggling vegetables in California?
It's not as if they have the lock on the deal.
We all make our own vegetables.
Yeah, but an orange in California costs like $7.50 now.
For a single orange.
For one orange, yeah.
Well, you know...
Well, here they're only like five bucks.
Yeah.
Well, I think once we get parity, economic parity with the Californians,
then that will mean that somehow we're happier.
And I think Dobbs couldn't have put it better.
As long as you have economic parity with a parrot,
adultery with an adult tree,
you know, you can perform all kinds of functions in the new world.
That's coming soon, I hope.
Yes.
Well said, Dave.
I didn't think so.
Or pedophilia with a foot.
Well, there you go.
I mean, why would you want to have pedophilia with anything?
Oh, pedophilia.
Yeah, pedophilia.
With anything but a ped.
Is that like a foot fetish?
A fetish.
Spelled F-O-E-T.
No, foot fetish was...
Footish.
I think the greenhouse was selling that.
Oh, okay.
Or was it the grasshopper?
I can't remember.
Yeah, they were selling foot fetish hash.
In Amsterdam.
Which smelled just like old socks.
So you knew it was going to be really good.
Well, it was called skunk sock or something was where it was derived from.
Well, I think that...
Gym sock skunk hybrid, where they mix skunks.
They managed to genetically engineer skunks that are crossed with gym socks.
Yeah.
And you smoke their jenkum.
Yeah, after you don't...
Do you know what jenkum is?
It's the straining of the underwear of certain...
You make it like a tea, right?
Yeah, and you leave it in a jar for a long, long time, and then you whiff it.
Oh, I thought you made it into a tea.
And you see your ancestors.
Oh, jeez, man.
I didn't know that.
See, I never...
You have to...
On the way home, we'll have to explain to Dave what jenkum is.
And friends...
I'm going to have my fingers in my ears and be going la, la, la the whole time.
Friends, you're listening...
But the frog makes you forget, so I could never...
Maybe I did know what jenkum is.
You're right.
Maybe I'm wrong.
Jenkums...
Ladies and jenkums, we're listening to Hour of Slack number 1,128.
And if you would like to know more information about the Church of the Subgenius and the
Frop Cup Devivals, you can go to subgenius.com.
Or you can write for free information about the Church of the Subgenius from Bob, or our
Slack, or Reverend Stang, or anything, at P.O. Box.
1-814-17 Cleveland Heights, Ohio.
That's Ohio.
44118.
And, oh, the collages we played at the beginning of the show were by Fernanda Nandy-Lemur, and
the Bob on a Totally Dark Night was by Nora Elpreff, as is this one that I should be playing
right now.
Oh.
Jane, look.
Radiation.
Oh.
I don't know.
It's...
Secondary domain, or pneumonia.
And we decay with every minute.
Fleshless things glide around here, and with your efficient ministrations, turn my father
and my mother into jelly!
But these people had no life.
You're a genius.
Oh my God.
What?
Fuck.
It all happened so fast.
Free.
Help.
No matter.
Call now.
Nine.
I don't know.
You've turned me into a freak.
Survival as a vegetable survives.
A vegetable!
Oh.
Now, madam.
Will that be all, ma'am?
Life.
Life!
Normal.
And then die.
I want my freedom!
You're geniuses.
Every.
Every day.
Hi.
Brainwash.
We're going to live like normal people, do you understand?
Normal people.
We'll take trips and parties and...
Something's not right.
What is it?
Robots.
Why?
Oh.
I'm a thing.
I'm a machine.
A machine.
Noises and neuroses.
What is your power?
I just sort of shake my butt.
Get those ass waves kicking.
Madness.
You can say that again.
Thank you.
Madness.
Madly, passionately, illogically, miserably, all-consuming.
Furiously, fiercely.
I love you.
Thank you.
Toxins.
Antitoxins.
Oh.
Nothing.
You disappoint me.
The eradicate.
I don't think you're making any sense at all.
It won't hurt her.
Well, let's get this over with.
Oh.
Come here, baby.