Test, test, bleep, test, test, test, test.
Ah, yes.
Your friend.
We're back.
I thought we were.
Are you too stupid to see what's going to happen?
Yes.
I know what's coming.
Have I got to beat you to make you understand?
No.
What?
Our slash.
It's going to end more horribly than anything in all history.
That much I know.
And at the very door of the day of the wrath of God is at hand.
And that if you plan to get saved, you'd better do it now.
In this temple lodge of the church of the subgenius of Little Rock,
and before we begin this sacred spouting,
I think that we should all bow our heads.
And let's all have a minute of noise.
Ah!
Have we started yet?
Oh.
Well, that officially happens at 7 a.m.
Test, test, test, test.
So that would have put it at 6 a.m.
That's one.
Is that right?
Let me tell you, we'll be on our way.
5 a.m.
We'll be counting down.
5 a.m. is the time.
Of course, that's the time this show is normally drawing to a conclusion.
And you hopefully will be able to work the end of the world in just before the show ends.
Time marches on.
Just because the world is ending doesn't mean we shouldn't.
Right.
Just because the world is ending doesn't necessarily mean that the show doesn't have obligations,
as does the show that comes on after this,
because it's only the world as we know it that's ending.
The world as we don't know it will continue on.
We're...
Eons, centuries, decades even.
Gee, thanks for letting us know that, Phyla.
Mightily zooming along in a way that we never thought possible.
And bouncing energy off of this space.
Because it will be the future.
And we'll enter the thousand-year millennium
into the weakness of the eternal void.
So often spoken of by those people who come to my front door when I don't want them to.
July 5th, next day.
Pleasure ships are on their way.
Quit your job.
Keep your slack.
Chair dust.
Got your back.
Hail Connie.
Hail Bob.
On your knees.
Self-righteous love.
Give it up.
Give it in.
Find yourself.
You get it, kid.
New religion radio.
Hell Pope gonna blow.
Pay to find out what you know.
Pass the pipe.
Take a trick.
I'm telling you, this is my joke.
Spirits see, steer clear.
A tournament.
A tournament of lies.
Offer me solutions and you offer me alternatives.
And I decline.
It's the end of the world as we know it.
Bob feels fine.
Are we going to start the hour of slack somehow?
At sunset?
Oh, uh...
This is your mic.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's past time to start the so-called hour of slack.
That's not plugged in.
Although I could plug it in.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Here, look.
I can do this.
All this talk about plugs is just subterfuge, ladies and gentlemen.
That one cuts in and out.
We don't want to.
I just use that to establish authenticity here.
Actually, it's completely automated.
The problem is every time you add another headphone, they all get quieter.
Quieter?
Quieter.
I can hear quite a lot, including a background rumble, unless that's just me.
That's the oncoming train of slack.
Train of thought.
Oh, no.
Horrible, scary train of thought.
Yeah, most of my train of thoughts are pretty scary.
Here, let's start things off.
It's 2 o'clock.
Yes, it's beyond 2 o'clock.
Really?
You're just now saying it's 2 o'clock?
No, it is exactly 2 o'clock.
All right, I'm off.
I'm quite off.
It's okay.
No one's ever mentioned that to you before?
And now, oh, no, wait a minute.
Yes, it's the hour of slack from Caffeena's here in the middle of Wisteria
at X.
Day 18.
Yes, dear friends, I and Reverend Ivan Stang are here with Priestess Pisces
to inaugurate a series of mind-ripping bobcasts done from this historic site
in situ at Caffeena's, where the elite meet and greet and eat,
except that they...
The food stops the moment our show starts.
That's neat.
No, no.
It's all wheat.
As the week goes on, there will be more food.
And again, I think I said it earlier,
if you buy one of those beautiful purple and silver mugs,
you can get free refilts.
I saw that.
That was offered to me.
Your free Caffeena's mug.
The only problem is that when one takes off into space,
one needs to keep the load.
And so I can't burden myself with it.
I understand that.
But remember, most of the hour of slack listeners,
which includes most of the subgeniuses here at Wisteria,
who don't ever watch us,
they can't grab that mug.
And those listening by internet can't grab that mug
because they didn't come.
Perhaps they can't come.
Perhaps that's why they're...
Or what?
Maybe they're...
Maybe we're the ones who can't.
Well, now, let's...
They're all having fun.
I can do just fine.
Thank you very much.
And we're sitting at this picnic table
at Tarzan's radio station
doing a show again.
Yes, in one sinuous movement,
Lord Greystoke arose from the branch
on which he had spent the night in easy slumber.
I hate having to say doing a show again,
but even worse is the phrase,
here we are at X-Day again.
Again.
Did I say that?
You have to say that.
I didn't say again.
I've said again.
I didn't use again.
I did.
I've been saying it's X-Day again
18 years in a row.
I'm tired of saying it's X-Day again.
Yes, dear friends.
I'd like to someday on some sunny July 5th
simply say it was X-Day after all.
It was X-Day again.
Come and gone.
And woe to the naysayers.
Woe to the naysayers.
Of course, you know,
those naysayers,
you know what's going to happen.
The world will be destroyed
like one of those,
it'll look like Neo-Tokyo
at the end of Akira.
But there will still be one pink guy
standing on his soapbox
screaming about how some guy,
whether it's Obama or somebody else,
that's the reason there are no more rats
for us to eat.
It'll be Obama's fault.
They're just trying to find the goat.
When in reality,
the reason those guys
will have no more rats to eat,
is Bob.
Bob is the one.
Bob is the one who did not give them,
who didn't leave them enough rats to eat,
and they're forced then to eat themselves.
Those rats aren't half bad, actually.
Bob ate all the rats.
Bob probably did eat all the rats.
You know, I mean, it's possible.
They're not bad, honestly.
Try it.
At the end times,
there won't be ketchup, though.
That's the thing.
Okay.
Ketchup doesn't survive the end times.
Now, on the other hand,
on the other hand,
Manx Darkpaw's saucer
actually has a ketchup factory in it.
So when you guys leave the planet
and you want ketchup,
seek out Manx Darkpaw's saucer.
But if you wanted ketchup on your French fries,
I don't know whose saucer has the French fries.
That's the problem.
Possees, you might want to cause some sound effects
by slipping that condom over the end times.
The mic is also called a wind stream.
All the subs at Wisteria liked X-Day a lot,
but the pinks who lived just north of Wisteria did not.
So we were driving up here and I saw this truck
and it had pink camo.
And I'm really confused why pink camo exists.
Like, are they trying to raid Barbie's dream house
or is Lisa Frank under attack by the blue meanies?
And you need the pink camo
and a green camo.
And a yellow camo.
To save the rainbow pooping unicorns.
Slow down, I'm taking notes here.
Are the misfits launching a co-op offensive
against Jim and the holograms?
Because you know that would be truly outrageous.
Well, let's keep up with current events.
You know, I subscribe to several news feeds,
but I really can't say I'm up
on every little change in the Neosphere.
But all that's going to be smoothed over
and a blank slate
when X-Day comes down.
day rolls over the quaking
citadels of man.
But how? Pink camo.
Pink.
I can't think of anything
more. It's
pink camo.
On the way up here I saw, and probably you saw,
a pink church.
It was a church and it was pink.
What more
needs to be said than that? Did you see it?
It looked like an angel food cake
in color. I wanted to go in there
and worship. It looked so appetizing.
There wasn't enough time.
I wanted to go in there and worship by
devouring the inhabitants.
You know when you say pink church, I'm imagining this giant
I want to be a cannibal redneck when I grow up.
It's a traditional church. It looks
as if it's a Plasticville
model from a train set.
And it's pink. I bet every
Saturday they give out
pink salad. Do you remember that
from your childhood? Or is that a southern thing?
Pink salad. They served
that crap at my elementary
school. What's in there? I didn't like it
even.
Even then. It's like cool whip
and jello and fruit.
Like I said, I don't know if that's a southern thing or what.
It's a Pobucker thing.
It's like, what do we have left
in the refrigerator? We've got
jello and cool whip.
Well, these benighted souls
don't know that they're supposed to make pudding
and put fruit in that,
which far exceeds any
Pobucker
cool whip. But then you need a trifle.
You need the trifle.
Exactly. Alcohol.
And that's really trifling. All the way down.
Lovely decoction of
alcohol, pudding,
fruit. You never get to the
bottom of that.
A little bit of cake. But it's not pink.
And it's not pink salad.
Angel food cake. You don't see
that much anymore. You know, when Bob called upon
us to destroy the world of
the pinks, he didn't mean the color
pink.
You know, it's more, it was
an attitude or something.
I believe.
I'm worried about, you know,
the sort of racist
possibilities of killing only
pinks. I'm one of,
you know, if you're talking about colors,
I'm one of those.
I'd hardly say that your color was
pink, Stang. I just want
to drown a pink in pink salad. Is my countenance
crimson? It might be
from telling these outrageous
slanders and prevarications, but
our coloration is
more beige.
At the best of times. Unless you have
sunburned, and then, yeah.
I like to be the devil's advocate.
And Bob is the devil's
devil's advocate. You know, the devil,
we were talking about this the other night,
has pulled me out of jams before,
just as you were saying
how he'd pulled you out of jams.
So, I'm not
going to slander him too much. But how did you get that much jam to get stuck in?
It was actually
honey and feathers, weren't you saying?
Yeah, yeah. The first
X-Day drill.
Well, what turned out to be the third
X-Day drill, and what the pinks
called 1998, I was,
for some reason, people,
well, we didn't have the bob dummy
then. They had to take
their anger out on somebody when the saucers
came, so I got dunked
in honey. I got strip-naked,
honey poured all over me, and then a bunch of
pink feathers.
And then thrown into the rancid
scummy pond.
Yes.
And it was a guy
dressed as the devil.
And maybe it was the devil himself
wearing a devil mask.
He came and rescued me
from those redheads
and the crowd of 300
jeering mockers.
Yeah, you've got to watch out for those redheads with the freckles.
But what about your friend Thayton,
Prince of Darkness?
Oh, you're thinking Reverend
Mickey Mephistopheles.
Yeah, he's another one of your
demonic pals.
I'm sure he'll be here for Starwood.
He goes,
he got scared at X-Day.
Oh, Mephistopheles.
X-Day scared Thayton
that one year.
I was greatly helped in the desert
by Mephistopheles once.
Really?
Really.
Helped me a great deal.
Normally it's Jesus that helps people in the desert.
Is it? Does Jesus help people
or does Jesus simply set them
on the proper path?
I've read it.
Jesus sets you straight, but you still have to find your way
down from the church spire or out through the desert.
But there's something none of these holier-than-thou
Joes never figure on.
Well, I want to hear about the devil saving you
in the desert.
Well, it was when
I was in a
a show.
It was that thing,
The Secrets of Uranus.
I may have told you about it.
Was this at Burning Man?
It was at Burning Man.
Oh, well, of course the devil's at Burning Man.
Well, he was part of it.
It was all about
how God was constipated
and couldn't release his load.
And Sigmund Freud and the devil
were there, but
I had to say the crucial lines
that ended the whole show.
And I was down in this little wooden shack
with an actual
hunchback guy pulling levers
and glowering at me.
There's a lot to this story.
Too long.
But at the appropriate time,
I said, well, I'm ready to say my lines.
Nobody told me about it.
There isn't any microphone in here.
And I thought I'd had such a great time
up to then that now it was all going to be ruined
and it was all going to be my fault.
And there wasn't anything I could do about it.
So I ran out of the structure
and I ran around it just looking for a loose microphone.
And Mephistopheles said,
Here, here, Dr. Hal, up here.
Here's my mic.
And so I did.
I did.
Say the last lines
and everything went off to perfection.
Did Jesus hand you a microphone, son?
No.
Jesus wasn't in that.
Who handed you a microphone?
It was all split foot.
They had Jehovah in this show,
but not Jesus.
Although once when he threw a red robe over his shoulder,
the father resembled the son a little bit
to my mushroom resonating brain.
I thought that was...
I do remember you telling me about that
because I remember the moment...
It was...
It was incredible.
I was hoping that you'd been rescued
literally by a fork-tailed devil
out in the desert in Tucson.
That time you went looking for the mating
Sonoran Desert toads to lick.
That was a different occasion.
And I did come to the mating ground of those toads,
but there was no devil involved.
But...
It's true.
Dr. Hal has actually found his way
to the mating ground of Sonoran Desert toads.
It's an incredible place.
And those are the kind that you can lick.
No, you can't.
Well, you can lick all of them.
You can't and you should never lick a toad.
If you tell people they should lick a toad and they die,
it's your fault for spreading misinformation.
But they're probably going to die on next day anyway.
Toad lickers.
Well, maybe so.
But on the other hand, it's irresponsible to tell people...
You rub the sweat off and dry it and smoke it, right?
It's not sweat.
You have to squeeze the venom glands
until they spurt out the liquid inside.
Oh.
It hurts the toad.
Yeah, it does.
Yeah, that's what they say.
In fact, the toad is...
They like it.
Ooh, ah, oh, Lord.
Yeah, exactly.
Squeeze me some more, Dr. Hal.
You squeeze the bubo on the toad.
Squeeze my bubo.
Oh, oh, oh, squeeze it again.
I favor squeezing it onto a clean sheet of glass.
How many times have they asked me to do that?
You have such huge bubos.
A clean, sterile sheet of glass.
The spurt goes there and let it dry.
Then you scrape it with...
May I palpate your bubo, little toad?
Then you take this scraped off stuff,
which has the consistency of rubber cement,
and you rub it on the toad.
And it's quite smokable.
And you put it in a pipe in which you have never smoked anything else.
The pipe must also be sterile and clean.
And then you light it.
But first you have to make sure that your body will be in a place
where nobody will do anything with it for half an hour or so.
And off you go.
Yeah, just lean back and talk to Bob for half an hour.
With...
It's the most intense thing, but it's over in half an hour,
unlike...
Like other trips that go on and on for days.
Well, it's DMT type of chemical.
It's the only one secreted by a vertebrate animal.
And that animal is Bufo alvarez,
the Colorado river toad of northern Mexico,
southern Arizona, New Mexico, and California.
Daddy, look, she has big bubos.
And you know what...
Daddy, why are you squeezing that little Mrs. Toad's bubo?
There were some educators, some nature educators,
who were arrested in California
because they were...
Because they illegally possessed these illegal toads.
And their names...
How do you make nature illegal?
They freely confessed that they smoked the venom of Bufo alvarez.
And their names, you should be interested in knowing,
were Bob and Connie.
I saved the newspaper article.
Yes, they were martyrs for toad venom combustion.
Hmm.
Friend, don't be a martyr for toad venom.
Just do it.
As Stang just toad you.
Toad away, toad away.
Where do you go when you're toad away?
And now a moment of silence.
For Peter Bergman and Phil Austin of the Firesign Theatre.
Now only half of Firesign Theatre is left in these straightened times.
These terrible end times that came according to the prediction.
We are deprived of them and all sorts of others
who were help in less pressing times.
Ah, yes, the tribulation times.
Actually, I keep reading on the internet that America has been destroyed.
And usually one guy did it.
Obama.
I think they're giving him a little too much credit.
And it worries me sometimes.
It's like, am I hallucinating?
I went down to the supermarket.
I want my country back again.
And everything looked normal.
I mean, the supermarket was still there.
People were shopping.
People of all ages and races.
And sizes were shopping.
All phantoms.
Most of them in little carts since they're determined to become obese.
They're too large to move under their own power.
Just like in Wall-E.
The Walmartosaurus was so huge and heavy that if it were to leave its shopping cart,
its bones would be crushed under its own weight.
And would soon die from asphyxiation.
On the floor of Kroger's or wherever.
No, Walmart.
Walmart, okay.
I am offended by those Walmart shopper mocking photo collections where they show all these
horrible wretched po-buckers at Walmart because I'm a Walmart shopper.
I'm sorry to say, but by golly, a stack of 100 blank CDs is 10 bucks cheaper there than
it is at Mom and Pop's.
Little hideaway shop.
Well, is this a wall of shame?
And Mom and Pop's is 40 miles away.
Walmart's just around the corner.
What's a feller supposed to do?
These are like pictures in some Italian restaurant of the beloved customers, only it's the Walmart
customers.
No, there's websites that...
Oh, websites.
Elites post pictures of poor people who are badly dressed.
Now I know what you're talking about.
They're trying...
You see, the internet is all about shaming.
Yeah.
They're either trying to build you up or shame you.
And they're trying to make you look like a poor, poor, poor, poor, poor, poor, poor, poor,
poor.
A lot of people are about how terrible these po'buckers in Walmart are and how badly they
dress.
Well, I mean...
Well, they were never thinking that they would be on some sneering joker's website.
And that guy is probably the stereotype at home in his tighty-whities eating potato chips,
you know.
If anyone saw him, he would be far more horrendous than some poor Walmart shopper.
But just remember, the greatest thing about the internet is everything is on the internet,
and the worst thing about the internet is everything is on the internet.
And it all has equal weight.
Falseness and fury, hatred, deformity, all get...
A deadly internet.
Yes.
I think that if America is destroyed, it will be because of the internet.
I think the internet is making everybody stupider,
because anything you want to believe,
you can find a hundred thousand other people who believe the same idiotic crap.
It's definitely...
And the next thing you know, it's household knowledge.
It's definitely making everybody stupider,
because that's what people use everything for, to become stupider.
But the danger is...
But everybody knows that that Amtrak station is a secret camp
for the government to round up all of the good American citizens
so that they can brainwash them and make them make goods for the Chinese and the Russians
when the world takes over the Americans.
And then, you know, you have to worry about the lizard people.
You don't understand.
It's the lizard people.
The lizard people are coming forward.
And they're going to round us up in camps.
Actually, as usual, the lizard people are the good guys.
Right.
Yeah.
They always get that kind of crap.
And that's what they learn from the internet.
Oh, I want to believe that vaccines caused autism of my child
rather than all my drinking while he was in the womb.
And they can find out, wouldn't we all know, obviously,
astrology causes autism.
Well, the problem with the internet is it's hackable
and it's also vulnerable.
Everyone thinks the power will never go off.
But if the power goes off, you're screwed.
You said astrology causes autism?
And finally, it's the imposition of a monoculture,
which is dangerous in any case.
Palmistry must cause chronic masturbation.
Well, I'm sure you can find several articles
that will say that very thing on the internet,
so it must be true.
Well, I've said it, so it must be true.
Well, it...
Well, it's true.
And we've recorded it.
And we're on the internet.
Yeah, it's done.
There you go.
So there you go, folks.
Palmistry causes chronic masturbation.
And palmers for to saken,
sundry stranders,
inferny hoes,
booth and sundry launders.
Where can I find somebody who can help me with my palmistry?
On the internet.
It has to do with...
You see here?
Well, okay, it depends on...
Not the map of Michigan,
but this right here and then that.
Those lines on your hand?
This bump represents your spleen.
And this one represents your nephritic ducts.
We're not talking about the map of Michigan.
No.
Your feet are down here by your laugh lines.
Right, right, right.
Oh, because your hand forms a map of Michigan.
Yes, yes.
Michigan is the one state that is lucky enough
that they can show you where they live.
Here's a map of Texas.
Looks like shooting a fangirl.
Yes.
All them Yankees.
Right, right.
But no, no, no.
You see this line here?
That's the one about...
That's the one about your sexual taste.
And then this one here is the one about
what kind of lube you should use when you're masturbating.
Michigan for champions.
I can't see the lines of my palms through this hair.
Does anybody have a comb or a razor?
Then I can get my palm done.
Oh, we can cut for Sooners and for suckers.
And actually, actually for the females,
you'll see there's a little pattern right here.
And on females, that pattern tells us things.
And that's how we...
That's the connection, you know.
There's little swirls there,
they're a match up to, you know,
the pattern that you're doing as a female.
Oh.
Like a jigsaw?
Right.
Every woman's pattern is...
And just like every male's hair...
Did you learn that on the internet,
on that all women's Facebook page?
No, no, no.
Secret women's Facebook page
that I'm not supposed to know about,
but I've seen it.
I've seen it.
And all they do is just talk about their husbands snoring.
No, we talk about more than that.
They just sit there and sip about their husbands snoring.
And we all snore.
No, no, no.
We talk about more than that.
Snoring is a serious problem.
We all talk about our lady parts.
Nobody told me about the all men's internet page
or Facebook page until you did.
Yeah, well, actually,
you accidentally told me about it,
and then Hal mentioned it,
and I realized,
oh, I wasn't invited onto this men-only
such genius Facebook page.
No, they don't, you know,
it's, it's, it's,
the thing is,
is that they're jealous of your,
your, your gift.
It's actually about athletes...
It's a, it's a bunch of,
what did you say?
It's a bunch of pink softcore porn, actually.
Yeah, that's what...
I mean...
It's the same old tired tropes of misogyny and...
Yeah, you know, I mean,
it's, it's, it's, it's, you know...
Not the good porn.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's, it's, it's basically
a lot of, of, of silicone sports illustrated.
Plastic.
It's too plastic, man.
Then there was the subgenius
post pictures of your own.
Dick page.
Yes, and many have done that.
That made me so insecure,
just looking at it.
Many have done it.
That I was against it.
You know, you don't have to feel bad
that they have more peni than you.
I mean, it's okay.
No, I, well, that's...
They're spoiling their political careers
and their chances of becoming
a Supreme Court judge.
Well, I mean...
Right.
I don't, yeah...
That's not the gavel there.
Well, it could be.
No, truly, there was a...
They sure didn't bang on things like that.
A secret Facebook page where
exhibitionist subgeniuses were...
I guess they're still doing it.
No, no, no, it's gone.
They get up in the morning with the...
The same one is still doing it.
A tentpole and go,
oh, I better take this picture right now.
And they're all so proud of their
one gigantic, huge dick.
One!
Well, they might enjoy it while they have it.
You know, that might have been, you know,
an issue, too.
I mean, they may have been, you know...
They didn't want me on there
because then they'd feel outnumbered.
But I have to ask this, you know,
as a female subgenius,
I have a really important question
about this multi-peni question,
which is how many boxes of condoms
do you have to buy for one sex act?
Well, I got a vasectomy a long time ago.
Oh, okay.
That's actually why I only have one nut.
Well, no, I'm just curious
because for the other subgeni with multiple...
I mean, do you get the 36-pack?
I mean, and how many...
I mean, it seems like a lot of work.
I just retract most of them.
Oh.
Most of them are so tiny,
they're hardly...
Hitler has only got one ball.
I didn't realize that they were retractable.
Himmler has two, but very small.
Or rather, Goebbels has two, but very small.
Himmler is somewhat similar.
And Dr. Goebbels has no balls at all.
You know, there's a second...
There's a second stanza of that.
Yes, I didn't do that right either.
How does that go?
The secret beefcase.
Gehring has two, but very small.
Himmler...
Himmler is somewhat similar.
And Dr. Goebbels has no balls at all.
I refuse to go all the way to Berlin
so that a one-testicle madman can pin a...
Oh, I'm not wearing my decoration.
You have decor?
Yes, I won the Fleur de Lis award at Burning Man,
and I really worked to win this thing.
A Fleur de Lis?
Yes, the horror film.
The Fleur de Lis.
The Fleur of France.
In the French Quarter at Burning Man.
They tried to throw us out of there.
They didn't know I had special connections.
Horror.
Horror flower?
The French Quarter where they build their...
The fake New Orleans and balconies and...
Oh, okay.
I thought you said something else.
I thought you said horror flower.
I say the French...
The horror flower of France.
The Fleur de Lis.
It was branded on My Lady de Winter by Louis XIV.
I was going to say the horror flower of France
had a different name.
And that name is?
I don't remember her name.
But, yeah, she...
You know, I didn't really...
You know, that's not my thing, man.
Well, I...
The thing is, it's not like there's an office with a time...
Yeah, you know, I mean, it's...
The business cards are, you know, a little different.
And, you know, there's not a...
It's not really in the phone book.
I mean...
You have seen the Fleur de Lis before?
Oh, yeah.
It's a cocktail to the acanthus leaves
on the top of...
The Corinthian columns?
Yes.
And the closest thing to the venerated lotus
that we have in Western art.
Yes, Fleur de Lis are all over
classic architecture on the East Coast.
Oh, I'm all over Fleur de Lis.
I'm...
I'm just over it, man.
I'm over that.
Well, now you seem to have a book here,
The Sexual Relations of Mankind.
Yes.
By Professor Mantegazatz.
Oh, cool.
I have a pretty good section marked here.
Oh, well, perhaps you'd better share it
with our listeners.
Oh, wow.
I happen to know that there has been introduced
into Europe and is in use there today
an ampelang
that is not so cruel in character
as that of the dyax,
but which is equally well adapted
to purposes of debauchery.
It is said that already at Paris
they are binding the member
with a...
with downy strips
from the feather of a goose
and that rings and India rubber stars
are for sale
for equipping the masculine lance
and rendering it more pleasing
to the daughters of Eve.
In addition to the desire
for increasing voluptuous pleasure,
not the least of the motives
behind such diabolic inventions
is, we are inclined to believe,
the whimsical temptation
to try out new things.
And to play with organs
which during life's fertile period
are the object of so much curiosity
to both sexes.
And then there's an article here
about the world's first cock ring.
What year was this?
This is a pretty old book.
Let's see.
I think it was published...
Yeah, 1935.
1935.
Okay, this quote is from
18...
71.
Alrighty.
They blank out this guy's name,
but it's the number two
and a letter B.
Mr. Blank.
2B.
A married man of 59 years,
September 1871.
A week ago, for the purpose
by no means original,
he inserted the penis
into a nuptial ring.
Upon his visit,
he was found with the ring
fastened below the glands
of the prepuce.
A considerable tumescence
was perceptible.
The prepuce was in a state
of paraphimosis,
and the strangulation
exerted by the ring
had produced an uneven ulcer
quite deep on the upper side
of the penis,
superficial in the lower portion.
Urination difficult,
but still possible.
Had no ability to put it
on the internet, too.
The ring was sawed in two,
after which cicatrization
was rapid.
They call it scarring.
And two days later,
the patient left cured.
Yes, I'll bet.
The gangrene of the penis
from mechanical causes is rare.
Oh.
Let's be thankful for that, at least.
Of course, from non-mechanical causes,
it's not rare.
That's a good question.
We've got to watch out.
I was in the pond,
and I felt some little thing
attach itself to my thigh,
which I had to dislodge.
That was a candiru toad.
Something like that.
It wanted to get,
more friendly.
I had to knock him off.
Suds had made friends
with the woodland creatures
when we first arrived.
It was the strangest thing ever.
They were all hopping around
like in a Walt Disney.
Little furry, adorable creatures
would come up to him
and try to nestle in his pants leg.
Yeah.
You know, and just,
it was really cute.
Give him some popcorn.
Well, we gave him a cashew,
and then we just said,
you, you,
adorable woodland creature,
your new name is Cashew.
Cashew on demand.
Absolutely.
Well, you see,
all one needs to do
is show a might of civility
and friendliness
here in nature's wonderland,
and all these stories
about evil creatures
simply melt away.
They aren't rape bears.
They're affection bears.
They're love teddies.
Here's a good one.
In 1868,
M. Guilbeau communicated
to the Society of Hospitals
the cases of a man
of 50 who had inserted his penis
all the way to the base
into a series of seven
very strong and tight brass rings
for the purpose, so he said,
of procuring for himself
moments of pleasure.
These rings remained in place
for 11 hours.
Yo.
The penis was already
indurated, cyanotic,
extremely swollen,
and of a gangrenous hue.
After any number of attempts
to get them off,
the rings were finally,
finally sawed in two,
one after another.
Within a week,
all local traces had disappeared.
So all that stuff
about grabbing the brass ring
is only so much...
In conclusion, I may...
This is the conclusion of the chapter.
In conclusion, I may mention
two well-known cases.
First, that of the soldier
whom Larry found with his penis
snared in the tube of his bayonet.
What about Moe and Curly?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
That of the man
in the back of his bayonet.
The man in the bathtub
who was found with his penis
up the faucet.
Wait, wait, wait.
He put his...
He put in the...
In his...
Wait, wait.
In a bayonet?
A bayonet tube.
You've heard...
They say fix bayonets
in the military.
I...
Oh, he was fixing his bayonet.
Is that what they call it now?
Yes.
Is that what the kids
are calling that now?
There's a reason he put it
in the bayonet, which...
Well, you know,
I don't want to shame him.
Well, this is on the internet,
so go ahead.
And shame him.
But I would imagine
that the tube of a bayonet
really isn't that large
of an orifice.
So, I mean,
I suppose he was
a fairly lonely fellow.
Lonely Corporal Hitler?
Think how many bayonet tubes
I would need.
Well, you could get
some custom manufacture.
You could use
one of those pan flutes.
They're all, you know,
it's all there for you.
Um, uh, this is, of course,
entirely speculative and...
No, no, no, no.
Not that I'm suggesting
that you put anything
in the orifice
of any musical instrument.
I'm not suggesting that at all.
I don't...
Please, you know,
don't put your parts
in a flute
or a tuba
or a trombone.
It would be really unacceptable
to somehow
put something, you know,
inside your sousaphone
or your French horn.
I never do.
You know,
that's not appropriate behavior
at all.
I mean, that would not
be acceptable and...
It's sometimes necessary.
And, uh...
I know there was
the one time at band camp
and that's okay,
but no, no,
please do not put
body parts,
especially not in
brass instruments.
Speaking of band camp...
Oh, yeah,
speaking of band camp,
that's a good point.
Those of...
If you don't know already,
the Church of the Subgenius
is now releasing
in digital format
amazing material
at subgeniusfoundation.bandcamp.
If you're interested,
you can check it out.
We can't give prices
on this community,
supported radio station,
however.
However, you'll find it there.
Actually,
it's a buck a song,
ten bucks an album,
and I'll have to cut that part out
for the broadcast version,
that's all.
As you can see,
it's reasonably priced.
These aren't millionaire prices.
They're even within the reach
of Joe Subgenius.
Absolutely reasonable
and acceptable.
Yes,
he's no normal dude.
Dude.
And his cousin,
Joe Lunchpail.
Yes,
they're not batshit crazy
like subgeniuses are.
Then there was Joe Bob Lunchpail Genius.
Oh.
He was a confusing fad.
Well, it's hard to keep the many progeny
of Typhon
separated.
Look at that.
She's over there shooting the moon.
What?
She was over there shooting the moon.
What gun can send a bullet that far?
No, no, no, no, no.
It was an amazing...
That's all right.
...amazing moonshot.
That's okay, Pisces.
Don't worry about it.
Well, the moon's pretty tough, really.
I mean,
and that's okay.
I wouldn't feel too bad for the moon.
After all,
we did stab it with a flag and...
And left bottles of astronaut pee up there.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean,
that's like the worst kind of trucker bomb ever
when you really think about it.
I mean,
but at least nobody has to mow the moon,
you know?
Not yet.
Well, soon.
Soon.
I mean,
they might have to on the other side of the moon
we can't see.
Oh, no.
There aren't any gardens there anymore,
but we can set some growing.
Not anymore.
Well, yeah, I guess.
I'm trying to remember what the...
Who...
What style were the gardens on the dark side of the moon?
Well, they were like hothouses
in elegant, now ruined cities.
The uses of sulfur.
But,
lunar soil is great for growing anything.
It has been proved with the soil
that was taken back from Apollo expeditions.
It made plants grow practically instantly
and grow huge.
And now that we know there's water up there,
not only within the lunar regolith,
but as freestanding water in deep craters,
which the sun has not touched,
why,
we can have our farms of kale and alfalfa up there.
Or frop.
Or frop, exactly.
You take a good,
good-sized crater and you roof it over
and pump some air in there
and you've got plenty of solar energy.
You're all ready to go.
Moon frop.
Yes.
I don't know about moon frop.
Stang would have to explain to me a little more about...
Well, when you smoke it,
it would draw you in a tidal fashion toward the moon.
Ah, moon frop.
Well, we're done.
We're done.
Oh, you have more of the book?
Yeah, I was distracted.
I didn't hear anything you guys said
because I was reading that love's most shameful phase,
shameful above all,
is sodomy,
which a man may practice either upon a woman
or upon a person of his own sex.
Here we go again.
Sodomy with a woman is sufficiently common
and is born of a curious desire for new experiences
or is resorted to with a Malthusian objective in mind,
that of...
limiting the progeny.
It is impossible to draw up even approximate statistics
as to this vice
for the reason that it remains hidden
among the mysteries of the marriage bed
and where it is indulged with with the consent of both parties
never comes before a court of justice,
which would be highly embarrassed
at having to deal with such a case.
This guy's a real drag.
And we seem to have driven most of the audience...
away with these scientific musings and revelations.
The woman in this variety of sodomy is passive.
The act is a painful one to her
and she yields to the shameful proceeding
only out of weakness or a passion for sacrifice.
No.
I don't think we chased them off as much as I think they may have had to, you know...
They got hot and had to run off and try that sodomy stuff.
Yeah, yeah, you know, I mean, you know, sodomy...
Well, I'm all...
I want to try some of this tribidism they was talking about
and this sodomy and...
Tribidism, huh?
What was that about amperangs and sticking goose quills up your wee-wee hole?
Well, aren't you...
I'm not fine.
Aren't you due for such a procedure?
I love it tonight.
The medical profession has its plans for you, Stang.
They plan to introduce something, I understand.
You know, in the old days...
They have been sticking things up my wee-wee.
They stuck the camera up there.
And a clapper...
A bloater boy.
You could stand there with a little clapper going,
take two, prostate inspection, bap, like that.
It's amazing what they can do these days.
Jesus Christ, that guy hurt like hell.
It made you feel like you had to pee all the time.
In the old days, they could break up the stones in the bladder
by a procedure known as sounding a calculus by percussion.
In this case, a steel rod is inserted through the urethra
and then when it finally reaches the stones in the bladder,
they strike the other end.
They strike the other end with a hammer.
And in the steel engravings depicting this procedure,
the patient always has a contorted expression on his face.
A cow.
I had a contorted expression on my face in calculus class too, so it's alright.
Oh, there you go.
It's called sounding a calculus by percussion.
But today, in our modern age of moon rockets and microchips,
we have completely different ways of going about this,
as Stang is to find out shortly.
Oh.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
So much for Ars Medica.
Bob has, I have an appointment to meet Bob.
Yes.
After X Day.
After all, we located the human soul in the, uh,
Unfortunately, it's located in the bladder and it has to be removed.
Uh huh.
The gigantic soul.
There's a picture of it.
Benign aphasia of the soul, they call it.
In the Revelation X, there's a photo.
But why are they doing, they never took the Dobbs hat out of my retina.
That's to keep you from having hot sweat.
They're gonna spot and fall off.
I mean, why are they taking the Dobbs hat out of your, you know, your innards?
They didn't take it out of my retina.
We must all be cleansed and prepared.
Is it a really big Dobbs hat down there?
Cleanliness is next to godliness.
I was born with a really large Dobbs hat.
Oh, yeah, my, the one on my retina is pretty small.
In the wrong place.
I mean, it's not.
No, you don't even, no, girls don't have Dobbs hats.
No, I have a Dobbs hat in my retina.
Well, yeah, but that's an eye Dobbs hat.
That, that, uh, that's different.
That's not, it's flat.
It's a two-dimensional Dobbs hat, right?
These are theological critiques.
I'm talking about a big Dobbs hat with a large pipe.
And it's blocking things.
Oh, that kind of Dobbs hat.
Yeah, yeah, the, the, the Dobbs hat that grows in your, near your bladder.
Oh, oh, we just have saucers.
Not Dobbs hats.
You don't have Adam's apple, neither.
No, no, no.
We have little,
That makes it hard to go.
Yeah, we have these spaceships with these really cool entry doors.
Oh, right.
Right, I've seen pictures of those colorways.
And, yeah, yeah, yeah, you know, the, the, it's a, it's a really, we don't have Dobbs hats, though.
Seems like that would hurt.
We have, we have really cool spaceships and, and, um, they're, they're really safe and warm and comfortable spaceships.
And I hear that many,
And everybody wants to get on board, don't they?
Yep, everybody wants to get on board that spaceship.
Get in that spaceship.
But it is, it's, it's a one-seater, though.
You know, you can't fit more than one.
I don't know, man, I've seen some weird pictures on the internet.
No, no, no, when you're putting more than, there is no true two-seater.
If you try to make the spaceship that we, that we have a two-seater, it's really cramped.
I don't know.
I'd be willing to try Pisces.
Ha, ha, ha.
Yeah.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Boy, this is a great show so far.
Yeah, it certainly had its brush with low comedy.
Um, but,
No, we were doing educational stuff until everybody ran off to try the things we were explaining to them.
And, and they're totally missing, we could be giving really good lessons here and, and, and teaching them important information, but they couldn't wait till the end of the class.
You know, we taught them, you know, they learned about the basics and they have to try it.
You know, some people just have to try it instead of listening to the full instructions.
It's like the guy who puts together the furniture and refuses to read the instructions.
We're here trying to give them the instructions, save them a little time, you know, so they don't stub in the body parts.
Right, they hear about the prairie squid and they run off into the woods to find one, but they missed the part about the de-beaking.
And there's nothing you can do about that.
And they come back singing in a high voice.
And they're all angry because,
Dang it, Stang, you didn't tell me that I was going to have to do this extra step.
You know, as well as I do, that no, that people don't read instructions.
But do...
People, yeah, people, sure. I actually do read the instructions.
But do they read the schedule?
That's why I'm the one pushing the buttons here.
Right.
Let me see.
It takes time.
I'm not really good at button pushing.
Well, I am, but not that kind of button.
Yeah, I know a couple of people whose buttons you've managed to push.
I don't need to.
Me too.
I don't even know how.
I know, I know.
Oh, man.
That's what X-Day's all about.
Getting really, really bent out of shape.
Everybody hates it.
By the end of it.
It's all my fault, again.
Hey, it could be Burning Man.
Well, that's not totally my fault.
That's not my fault.
It gets even worse.
That is totally not my fault.
You get even more bent out of shape because of the sand in the crevice.
I, I...
That was a great band.
Yes, you'll never go hungry there because of the sand-witches there.
Oh, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
I've never heard that.
I think we're going to do a quick swap out and...
Swap out?
Yep, we're going to swap out here.
We are?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're going to put a different beautiful...
We're going to put another voice on here.
Very good.
You were about to say a different beautiful uber-femme, weren't you?
I was going to say...
But you didn't want to sound vain.
No, no, I was going to say boobs, but that's...
Balloons, balloons, and not a gray one to be seen.
Boo-boos!
Audience, more boo-boos to squeeze the poison out of.
Have you ever seen a gray balloon?
Of course not.
There is no such thing.
So welcome to our next contestant, which is, of course, Reverend Baby Bear here.
And she's bought a beautiful green balloon.
No, this is actually for sound effects.
I'm making my own sound effects for the radio.
Very good.
Wow, Philo would love that.
That would make Philo so happy.
That's not even the most annoying one.
That one was pretty good.
Don't let all the air out of it yet.
This is the sound of creatures metamorphosing, werewolves changing.
The squeaky sound of a balloon.
You'll hear, if you listen for it in cartoons, you'll hear the balloon squeak sound effect.
And you'll realize, I've been hearing that my whole life.
For Are We Not All balloons, Mir Bek.
There are two bags of unfulfilled appetites.
Humans, they are ugly bags of water held up by sticks.
Yes.
Do you have a bunch of Monster High stickers all over your console?
He do, and look at this.
I've just handed Baby Bear the official Monster High sticker book, which I've been using
to identify all of my equipment.
Boy, you can stick those stickers everywhere.
Other people put their initials on there.
But when you find camera...
I've got cameras and recorders laying around that have Monster High toy franchise characters
on them.
Those belong to me.
I like how they add slightly different angles to their face and cheekbones to try to pretend
like they don't look all exactly alike.
Right.
Well...
Well, some of them have little fangs and...
The dolls are very slightly different from one to another.
You know, the weird thing about the Monster High franchise is it...
Well...
Well, the weird thing about the Monster High franchise is it teaches mostly young girls,
but sometimes old perverts, that it's good to be different.
You should celebrate your freaky flaws, or as we say in the church, exploit your abnormality.
That's a really big thing in the Monster High plots.
They're cartoons and so forth.
Yes, secret propaganda.
And bullying is bad and so forth, and it's cool to be a weirdo and cool to be a monster,
but there's one thing that rings just a little odd.
Uh-oh.
I'm a little hollow about that.
And that is that every single one of those girls, although they are monsters technically,
are hot.
They're all skinny.
None of them are overweight.
So, in that...
There is a special one.
Ghoulia.
Is she overweight?
She's the special student who happens...
She doesn't...
But she's also the smartest girl in school.
She's a zombie, so she's kind of slow in some ways, but she happens to be the best
hacker.
I'm way behind you in following these episodes.
I haven't seen these recent ones that you speak of.
They just had a bunch of old Bratz dolls, and they just didn't know what to do with
them.
They monstered them up.
Yeah.
But it's a big improvement over Bratz, because it's monsters.
Yes, it is.
Absolutely.
Wait, is that one...
Is that Draculaura?
Yeah.
Is that one me?
That's you.
Yes.
Draculaura.
Yes, we think that one resembles you.
I had them all...
I actually read the names of all the subgenius correspondences.
All right.
You might as well tell the names, since you're looking at their pictures.
Yeah.
Maybe there was Draculaura because of physical resemblances.
She's small and kind of squeaky.
Okay.
I'll take that.
And 16,000 years old.
Yeah.
We don't need to talk about that in public.
Or 100 years old.
I'm sorry.
16,000 years old.
I think it was just we who corresponded to Laguna Blue because they look alike.
Pantiera also looks sort of like Ghoulia.
Because of the glasses.
And I've changed my mind.
I've decided that Pisces is Abbe Abominable, the daughter of the Yeti.
Who is...
Because she's tall.
Who is Robecca?
Popes Lilith.
Oh, okay.
Susie the Flusie corresponds to Operetta.
Oh, that makes sense.
So she does.
Well, she has red hair.
Well, I'll be.
And is hideously scarred underneath this mask.
And theatrical.
Right.
So...
Oh, Fat Man D was the sassy urban werewolf girl, Claudine Wolfe, just because she's
sassy and urban.
And a werewolf.
Yes.
Well, you didn't want to...
She can't be here this time because it's a full moon.
That's right.
July 1st is the full moon, everyone.
You can go out and cavort under the lunar beam.
It's good for you.
The full moon.
Even a man who is pure at heart and says his prayers by night may become a wolf when the
wolfbane blooms and the autumn moon is bright.
Yeah, there's two different versions.
How old is she?
Um...
There's only one version written by Claudine.
Oh, Curt Seodmack.
Can I have stickers?
Yeah, I want stickers.
Who also wrote...
Go ahead, Draculaura.
I want a Draculaura one.
Daughter of the vampire.
Yes.
Curt Seodmack also wrote, when the house is filled with dread, turn the bedsteads head
to head.
Oh, I ruined it.
How could I fail at getting a sticker off of a sheet?
I've had that problem myself.
It's...
Poor shoddy workmanship.
Yeah, it's like the backing comes with the sticker.
Peel off another one.
Where was this made in?
In Dobstown?
In Taiwanaland or something.
Just tear off another one.
Glandlandistan.
I got it.
I figured it out.
It's in Sadd-Sakistan, over the border.
Glandlandia?
No, Slaklandia.
Glandlandistan is...
Is that your Minecraft?
We can have a little play.
We can cut out the figures of these monster girls and you can put them on these little
cute sets.
If you have...
To save this background.
If you're sent to state prison and have enough time...
Not state prison.
Too scary.
All right.
But I mean, who has time to cut out a million little statues of monster teenagers?
They're pretty cut.
Oh.
No child, no modern child has that kind of skill.
They don't teach them scissors and coloring.
They're not allowed to use scissors anymore.
They don't even know what the word stay in the lines means.
Their scissors are plastic.
There's no blades.
As you're pointing out, kids these days can't sign their names.
Not kids, adults.
Because they can't...
Yeah, they can't sign their names.
Adults that come out of school can't sign their names because they don't...
They don't use writing instruments.
Yeah, they...
Oh, but come on.
Nobody signs their names.
They make a loop and then squiggles.
Right.
They make a pharmacist's squiggle these days.
But the point is they can't.
The techies do.
I have a friend who makes a little Pac-Man eating marbles for his signature.
That's how he signs forms.
Now, which?
What?
He makes a little Pac-Man eating, going down the line of dots.
Eating marbles.
That's how he signs forms.
He makes a signature.
Well, I heard this poor old patriot telling me about...
He used to try to sell replicas of the Declaration of Independence at gun shows.
And he said these kids were just staring at his Declaration of Independence things and
they asked him, what is this?
What's a Declaration of Independence?
Can't you read it?
A wasp again?
What?
A wasp.
It might sting Baby Bear over her heart.
Dr. Howell, you're not doing your job.
I still actually have a scar on my tattoo from where I got stung by a wasp last year.
Yes.
That was a terrible thing.
We don't want that to repeat.
A scar on your tattoo?
Yeah.
Well, it's more polite than saying on my boob.
It's right there.
Look.
See?
It's all bubbled up.
It's a weird scar.
It won't go away.
It's become part of the thing.
That happened last year.
You have to add another one down at the bottom to make it balance, make the design balance.
No.
Don't let another wasp anywhere near there.
I got stung last year because I was in charge of putting the tarp up or back down over the
speakers at the main stage.
Weren't you tracking on this thing?
As I was climbing up the scaffolding when they were showing me, yeah, you just go up
there and do this.
It's easy.
Yeah.
Just go on up.
Oh, but you do need to watch out for wasps.
You do need to watch out for wasps.
As they said that, it flew directly into my chest, stung my boob, went down my shirt,
but then managed to fly out without stinging me again, which was lucky.
That bastard.
Yeah.
Well, I think he ended up in my room later that night.
It was painful.
Dr. Howard, you're not doing your job.
Remember I told you the reason we fly you in is because mosquitoes love you so much.
They do.
That causes them to leave me alone.
That's because I'm so all-fired delicious.
I can't help it.
Mosquito magnet.
Yeah.
And I lost that insect pen that I had.
I must have left it somewhere, maybe down at the pond or on the grass or something.
Now, I have no protection against the swarms of buzzing night flies that disturb me.
It's over.
Yeah.
Well, we'll see.
Anyway, my point was modern-day wasps can't read the Declaration of Independence because
they don't read cursive.
Yes.
They're not taught cursive.
They can't write it, and they can't read it.
White Anglo-Saxon Protestants?
Wasps?
No, just the insects.
Oh, okay.
No, just people who work in the high-technology industry in California.
They all tend to be about seven feet tall because they're all grain-fed, super slender,
long-headed.
They never have round heads, always long, doliose or something.
encephalic heads but this increased height is certainly noticeable especially when they come
in and sit down right in front of me at a concert at the very last minute no matter where i sit even
if i'm standing on an apple box then some eight foot guy comes and stands are we are we stereotyping
tech nerds into a new race i believe they are i i observe them all the time you know they that is
one thing we started talking about how they can't sign their name but uh what else do they do they
eat cereal standing up that is one of their uh horrid yeah and abhorrent yeah um and of course
they uh never look where they're going but that's the old old stereotype they're trying to read
their google glass here's something that happened look where this really happened in san francisco
a maniac had a gun and he got on a bus wanting to kill somebody his plan was to just get on the bus
and kill somebody with the gun so he got on the bus
and he brandished his weapon and uh nobody saw because they were all looking at their screens
so uh eventually he got behind somebody who was getting off the bus and uh shot the guy in the
back of the head and everybody looked up but then there was nothing to see so they looked back down
there was no witness uh you know the the bus camera has a grainy video of this but uh everybody's
bent over
looking at the small portable electronic device
and with the end of that motor the hour of slack must come to an end start me up again sting start me up again
because we've recorded about an hour's worth all right an hour's worth of babble it was all awful
you've been listening to our slack number one thousand five hundred and uh yes about penises and uh
genius.com and uh
so let's now um move to uh um something more elevating and talk about 100 year old monster
movies or something 100 years old every time the second that i sit down second that i sit down you
guys just want to talk about 100 year old monster movies well uh you could of course lead us out of
discriminatory you could ages show us i'm gonna i'm just gonna fade this out and push stop okay
i'm fading out i'm fading out we're fading out now i'm pushing stop there i pushed stop