Something familiar, something peculiar, something for everyone, a comedy tonight.
Something appealing, something appalling, something for everyone, a comedy tonight.
Nothing with kings, nothing with crowns, bring down the lovers, liars and clowns.
Old situations, new complications, nothing portentous or polite.
Tragedy tomorrow, comedy tonight.
Something convulsive, something repulsive, something for everyone, a comedy tonight.
Something aesthetic, something frenetic.
Something for everyone, a comedy tonight.
Nothing with gods, nothing with fate.
Weighty affairs will just have to wait.
Nothing that's formal, nothing that's normal.
No recitations to recite.
Open up the curtains!
Comedy tonight.
The Power of Slack.
Put your hands up!
Curious.
Cupidity.
Timidity.
Mistakes.
Fraud.
Lies.
Tumblers.
Grumblers.
Bumblers.
Fumblers.
Did you do service this morning?
And you obeyed.
Yes, I did.
So the pastor just prayed for me.
And I came this morning.
And I feel in my body that God has delivered me.
And he does.
God, please.
I'm going to show you how to pray.
Somebody pray to the Lord.
What did the Lord do for you today, honey?
The package is bent and dark yet.
I'm going to go back to the house of the Lord once again with me and my son.
My mother's home is here.
And I feel that God has touched me.
Do you believe God has touched you?
He has touched me.
Somebody give the Lord a hand clap.
Someone give the Lord the clap.
And we'll all sing this happy song.
You ask me why I sing all day long.
I'm oozing.
I'm singing for my Jesus.
I'm free from sin.
I'm singing.
Yes, our Lord and Master Blaster Jesus H. Christ was not only a man of the cloth.
He was a man of the silk panties.
He used to walk this way and that.
Up and down the Palestinian riverbed looking for beautiful young women.
What did he find among the rocks there?
He found nothing but desolation and estrogen.
He found rivers of estrogen and piles of pus.
But let's leave things of this world behind.
And walk now down the path of Bob for this brief minute of slack from the church of the subgenius.
It's a squirting universe.
If you enjoy this verse of verses, we'll be open-ended for a Celestial
Then tasty area, very tasty area for the zoom and know that we're for you cheerful
arrogance minute if you close your eyes and then listen to me engage in him
because what's written on it on that sign is that he will sing stirring with strength
but get free from anything and out of room come undignified men in the house I'M the
Zer's
He got nothing but the libido.
S Geb mutation been lifted.
We're running in a whole 360 degree complex system, and it's gonna get rid ofוכ Garland
and it gets meGEU
just because all of you would want me to come clean.
We're gonna sing and we're all gonna love better.
friend, I've heard people call the church of the subgenius a joke, but I have to wonder,
is the subgenius church a joke, or is this world a joke? Bob Dobbs owns deed and title to the church,
but who owns deed and title to the world? Not Bob yet. I'm afraid not. The conspiracy
owns this world. Let there be slack, my friend.
I'm afraid not.
I've got an apartment complex, here at the apartment complex. I've got an apartment complex,
here at the apartment complex now.
Pre-set, competent, level, or lighting apartment life.
Couldn't be more exciting. Laundry room and clubhouse too.
I don't have a worry till my break comes through. Watching Sun and Beta max night after night
is a tidal wave of suburban delights. Hey, hey.
I've got an apartment complex, here at the apartment complex.
I've got an apartment complex, here at the apartment complex now.
Oh, I know you like to live in the complex, a middle-aged.
Tell you about it, it's so easy to see. Apartment life is such a current rage.
Well, you can make it here on the middle of the wage.
Ooh.
My friends come over and they think you're so fine.
Well, they don't know none of it is mine.
Rental furniture and color TV.
None of my belongings belong to me.
For if life looks real critical, I'll play.
Cuz I always On a sim that I make to the bank.
Hey, hey, I've got an apartment complex here at the apartment complex.
I've got an apartment complex here at the apartment complex.
Cleveland State University with Chaz Smith and Lonesome Cowboy Day.
Special guest, guestess, princess, we are the dome.
And yours truly, Reverend Ivan Stang.
Coming up, friends, we've got a sing-along with Onan Canobite.
Plus, many collages by Fernanda and Endely Murr.
In fact, all of the cut-ups.
From tonight's hour of Slack number 858 are by Lee Murr.
Except for one great big one near the end.
It's about alien invaders.
And speaking of alien invaders, check out this news item that was not covered very much on the mainstream media.
A federal rectal exam list intended to keep terrorists from smuggling drugs and explosives
aboard planes is snaring innocent people at most U.S. airports,
triggering complaints that civil liberties are being trampled and innocent assholes are being repeatedly violated.
And while several federal agencies acknowledge that they contribute names to the congressionally mandated list,
none of them could or would say which agency is responsible for managing the list,
except that they are known for, quote,
having a thing for that sort.
A representative thing, unquote.
Equally troubling is that to avoid accusations of racial profiling,
a blonde white woman is routinely selected for the intrusive and thorough anal exams from each flight,
often several times at the same airport while waiting for her flight.
In the instance where such a woman has several connecting flights,
she could be anally violated dozens of times in a single day,
said one attractive woman.
What's scariest to me is that there could be this gross interruption of civil rights
and nobody is really in charge,
but everybody wants to shove their fingers up your butt.
Nobody thought that 1984-ish America would be like an anal intruder's porn movie.
Well, friends, as New Monet said about that news report,
we have seen the future and it is...
UGH!
Ehh.
And the future continues.
Here in Cleveland, where we make this...
where we finally assemble this show,
we lost a newspaper.
The alternative weekly called the Free Times
was absorbed by the other weekly, leaving now
only one city in the United States that has two alternative weeklies.
I think that's Los Angeles.
Newspaper.
So all them people be going down the...
Communism!
Communism.
In communist countries, they only have one newspaper.
Communism is good.
Christianity is stupid.
In communist countries...
Communism is good.
People can't decide what the government's gonna do in the war zones.
And that's why I say this Bush man is a communist.
I'm amazed hearing that coming from a Texan.
The devil pretends to be good.
And communism...
And you know the damn meaning of the word,
Politarianism.
God dam...
Pretends to be a capitalist.
But it's communism...
Communism?
That is creeping into America.
I have felt the...
Yes, communism.
In the form...
Of...
Of capitalist capitalism.
I think it's also called couch potato-ism.
And the other muted hues...
Commons are coming!
And I feel that we are slipping slowly down the backslide...
Of a...
Of becoming more common.
Of the nations that have gone before...
It's common.
It is creeping, communism.
Common men are everywhere and communists...
It is a form of Marxism, socialism, and all those other nasty, nasty words.
Common, come over here.
Common?
Please.
Communists and Nazis!
They're under my bed...
I like them there.
They're under every one of my beds.
Both of them.
Commies and Nazis.
And pinks.
And I don't mean pinkos.
And the Genghis Khan hoops.
Hordes, I like those uniforms too.
Humans!
Another low flyby.
We're still the next to go.
Stay sure once you can.
Another number came up.
I think it was 45.
We will bring them down.
Someday, their kind will fall,
and our kind shall rise up
out of the ditches and the holes.
Like a phoenix from the ashes,
we shall swarm skyward
and spute our maelstrom upon.
You're listening to WCSB Cleveland.
Let the humans laugh at us now.
Our time is coming.
Why, they still have teeth and jaws
and those tendons that go behind your chin
and nostrils.
There are no more teeth.
Radiation is our friend.
We eat uranium and old, rotten wires.
And we shall dispute them
at the nuclear plants.
We shall displace the humans.
We will...
We will be the new conspiracy.
There's a worm.
You can evacuate so easily
with just one thought.
It's like Gidget already went to...
The roaches shall be the new exterminators.
The new exterminators.
And the humans will be the bugs.
The shrimp.
The barbies.
The kinmen.
The soundboys.
We'll get and get them.
They must...
And all their friends.
Is your nightmare ending yet, man?
We should fame.
You've been tossing and turning for a long time.
We thought you were gonna break your collarbone arm.
But he comes by me hating fair and square.
Look, this one's got six toes.
We ain't named as long as you have.
Look at this one's eyes are sewn shut.
And no problems with him keeping dreaming.
No problem at all.
Stay asleep.
Don't...
Don't wake.
That...
That's the opposite message of...
This is about corporate accountability.
In this week, you'll find information about attacking President Bush's policies toward Iraq.
Just click for a leading clip.
Congressional Democrats stand in the corner.
Now a look at a Treasury Secretary Paul O'Neill on the proposals to create kidnap children.
And later.
Officials from three consumer groups and their abductors, also known as spam.
And csss at noon.
Only on Book Ban 2.
Treasury Secretary Paul O'Neill talked about corporate accountability.
Joining us now at the table is Treasury Secretary Paul O'Neill.
O'Neil. I go to a place where there's rampant corruption and see $100. Did you...
Tomorrow, the House Resources Committee will look at Gail Norton.
Did the...
I said it, Enron.
Did you see the picture in the paper? That guy's in his best suit.
Man, that's got to be a $2,000 suit he's wearing going to prison.
Did you see the stain on the back of that suit as he did that so-called perp walk?
That's a Bill Clinton stain if I ever saw one.
He was trying...
I know.
He was trying to...
He was trying to do a lepetomane as if that was going to get him off.
You know, some people think...
It kind of backfired.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
As it were.
Or bear backfired.
Fred's out.
Who's mounted the little Lucifer puppy?
Bob's out.
Why is that a Bob, man?
I'm sorry, I just cut a Bob.
Bob's your uncle.
I'm afraid you're going to have to step back to Lucifer.
It's like Bob is like this concept that's burned in...
to everything like, you know, a screen that has like, you know,
a little logo burned into it or something because it was on there too long, you know?
Those old computer screens.
Yeah.
It's like even when there's another pattern, Bob is underneath the pattern.
It's part of the wallpaper so you don't even see it.
Oh, that Bob weave, man.
That's a part of reality is the weave of...
The lattice of coincidence of Bob.
You know, that's...
It's like the woof and the warp of the...
The rockabilly wolf.
Fabric.
Man, that's Bob smiling, drooling.
You forget he's there until you start smelling the smoke from that pipe.
And this jet fuel.
I'll just hear, like, sometimes now I'll just hear a certain, like...
Spinal threads.
One guitar note, one just little...
On a guitar, you know?
Yeah.
I'll hear that and I'll just know where...
There they go.
You know, the connection is.
The rainbow connection.
It's the rainbow connection.
With your spine.
They're taking off left and right.
It's the new age, man.
The new Aeon.
Yeah.
Just smile and wave as they go past.
I heard that they will be drinking Shaddam Hussein's spinal fluids at the Bohemian Grove.
Oh, and by the way, go down to that local...
As a special sacrifice.
That little deli on the corner that's owned by, you know...
Aries.
Which deli?
Wait, which deli is that?
And go buy your American flag to put on your car.
Because that's important.
One or two could be sufficient.
But if the climate changes...
You may need five or six flags.
Now, Princess, we and I have noticed...
Six flags over Oklahoma.
Yee-haw.
I've been there.
One year on...
I mean, exactly speaking.
...flags on people's cars that they bought exactly one year ago and that have now been
worn by the wind down to just nubbins of about an inch or two of flag.
I mean, really.
I am so flagged.
I do pledge my allegiance to that flag.
For which I stand in here, one nationalistic res pubic, with freedom and justice for the
upper 10%.
You guys sound like a bunch of flaggy boys.
That's pretty flaggy.
A bunch of flaggots.
I hate flaggots.
I burn the flag.
My life is my art.
Bush burned the Constitution.
Stop flagginating yourself.
I'm flaggots.
Well, we've had our way with the flag, haven't we?
A symbol.
A symbol of freedom.
But in these days and times, a symbol of what?
Of oppression.
Of oppression of the entire world.
I'm reading off the wrong page.
I'm supposed to be reading off the page that says,
We must install democracies wherever they is.
And wherever they...
I'm sorry.
We'll force them.
We shall.
They'll vote or we'll kill them.
And if they don't place their ballots in the box, we'll place them there for them.
We will install democracy wherever it can be.
We will make them free if it kills them.
It's not happening.
Oh, there goes another one.
Bye-bye.
That was another flyby, man.
I think we're going to be the next to go in a few seconds.
Got your helmet, Dave?
Yeah, I'm wearing it on my backside.
We'll free those people if we have to go into slavery to do it.
And my fellow Americans,
I hope you're prepared to do just that.
That's the cost of freedom.
Your freedom.
Fork it over.
Oil.
To build freedom.
Boy, oh boy.
Boy.
It's kind of disgusting.
I know how you feel.
The show sucks.
Boy, it's even worse with all this oil all over me.
And dust.
I...
You know, you're going to...
You're going to wear your helmet on your backside or else...
The show is hell.
Shut the...
Hello?
They ought to hang me.
The Lord has given me these songs.
I'm giving them right back.
A newly discovered...
Listen.
...see what you can do if you're just listening to yourself?
Invest in youranswers 괸el
Starville Sa tenho vida en Abism,
Me ekak пр tunedallu
I just want moj.
The Los Angeles White House is now backing suspected hijacker Mohammed Atta in Prague.
CBN congressional correspondent Paul Sorrell was involved in the terrorist attacks.
The Senate wound up in prison for bribery and tax evasion.
Republican obesity in the U.S., Texas trouble.
The new bill would authorize more than 150 million children to help the two fat congressmen for tax evasion.
And with both the House and Senate in prison, all the races are overweight.
Paul Sorrell in prison for bribery and tax evasion.
Capitol Hill.
And for more information on what's happening in Washington, then ask Mike Reed, Capitol Hill Prayer, every Friday at CBN.com.
The contemporary Christian can describe this, asking itself questions like, just how Christian does Christian have to be?
CBN News reporter Sarah Pollack has about a 1 in 250,000 chance.
Ever since he grew up.
From the time they started getting the wee little man.
From that time, really, I was hooked.
Paul came shortly after he wrote a song.
His sprinkle blood.
Oh.
I want smell-o-vision.
I want all the others.
Now Paul's officially better known as God or Jesus.
I wonder one day who.
Oh, I wonder who.
No.
I don't think any of that even came up.
No dogma?
Well, I guess we're just all burned out.
I was driving to the station and I was thinking, shouldn't we draw upon our energy reserves and do some protest places?
thing about some, you know,
pertinent, cultural,
socially relevant,
you know, some
giant argument that the humans
and everybody else is all
upset about. Well, the giant humans
are always arguing because they take up
so much space. But everybody just took their
clothes off and now they're dancing.
Is that positive or negative?
Yeah, Byron's going on and on
about this, too.
Byron wants everyone to be weird,
and he's offended that I'm having parties
where girls are dancing naked and getting
all painted up with liquid latex.
Actually, he just says that's old hat
and that's not weird enough. That's so pink.
Now, of course, he has no suggestion as to
what would be weird. Yeah, absolutely.
Nothing at all. All he knows is that
he's going to attack my pleasure
vessel. We may not be all that
weird, but we know our slack.
That's right.
At least we know our slack, damn it.
You do. You are quite aware
of in each inch, each
centimeter of slack that escapes from your
vowels.
When I had no slack, then I felt
like, oh, everything has to be weird
and then I'll have slack.
You have learned
the secret of life, or at least deodorant
like from a distance. No, actually,
I didn't learn. All I know is
I got some slack, and
I don't care whether it's weird
or not weird.
Weird is what the other guy
thinks. I don't care
what the other guy thinks.
I don't care what you think.
I don't care what Bob thinks.
There you go. It was worth it.
I paid to know what I really think,
and I don't care what you think.
I don't even care what I think at this point.
What a beautiful, pathetic thought
for such a scrambled up gentleman.
For 30 bucks, it's worth it.
Look at his mind now, like laying there
on a piece of paper in front of him.
I saved my world.
Listen to the drums. They're calling.
Those are the calling drums.
They're calling you to whoop your ass.
Your pants down.
I would like to be Kaisa Girl.
Just forget toilet paper. Who cares?
Just live natural.
Forget toilet paper, I think, should be the name
of our new political movement.
That was a great movement. A great band.
The toilet... Wait a minute.
Forget toilet paper.
That's the name of the band.
It might even really be
the band that's playing right now over the airwaves
that you're listening to.
But it's spelled with a number, right?
Four.
Get toilet paper.
So all the rest do not get toilet paper,
but four get toilet paper.
Four?
Are they the four smelliest?
They're the four horsemen.
The four most worthy.
The four horsemen of the port-a-san.
The four strongest or the four strongest smell?
The four get toilet paper.
Indian times,
before things became
very, very small,
they were the four horsemen
of the port-a-potty.
Why are you hooked on your toilet paper
and your chem cans?
Why can't you just live
like in the past, in the good old days?
What's the difference
in a port-a-potty?
Live life without any focus
on excremeditation.
Screw that excremeditation stuff.
All you need is a hole in the ground
and a cactus and some sand.
You don't even need that.
Just grab a branch
to hang on to and
let go.
There you go, baby.
Just let go.
What's wrong with a good old
is to go
lean back and let go.
Right.
Woo-ha!
You know what I'm saying?
It's so bristly and tough.
Don't you want to take
a big piece of life like that?
Just walk up to that
old saguaro cactus
and put your arm around it
and give it a big old fat kiss
and say,
Dobbs, I quit.
You know, you don't.
That guy's nuts, really,
when you think about it.
I mean, he don't make
any sense at all, right?
Do you think so?
I don't think.
That's right.
That's the problem, sir.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
I've been bothered
by the soldiers
killing innocent civilians.
Let, let, let, let, let,
that, that, that,
uh, uh, the, the,
the, uh,
Musica, Musica.
Get this.
48% of 63%
of 3%
of 43%
of ethnic white Latinos,
55% of 25%
of frickin' ethnic Jewish voters
who are beginning to scratch their...
Thank you, doctor.
Looks like I might have a happy ending.
The snake condo.
The, uh, uh, universities.
The multi-call science.
Uh, our universities.
Uh, uh, Josh.
Yes.
Mystical scientists.
Go, go, go!
Hey!
Yeah!
A science party!
In the laboratory!
Late night at the lab!
Everybody's there!
Doctors, professors, PhDs!
Scientists with yellow hair!
Someone's pulling off
a anatomic-powered Cadillac!
Geniuses with matching lab coats
carrying a portable telescope!
To the science!
Science party!
Science!
In the laboratory of love!
Hey!
Someone's spiked the test tubes!
Laboratory's out of control!
Hands off that ad!
Equipment boy!
The Sonic Mind Probe is not a toy!
Take it!
Hey!
Oh, alright!
Yeah!
Well, bakers!
Wires!
Test tubes!
Electrodes!
Microscopes!
Terrascopes!
Electros!
Spectral!
Isotopes!
Chemicals!
All over the floor!
The pool and the kitchen sink!
Someone get the sonic broom!
When Cog invades your pony room!
Science!
Science party!
In the laboratory!
You want more science? We'll give you lots more!
You need a diploma just to get on the dance floor!
Wake up the lab rats, turn on the party droid!
Stay away from the nuclear waste-oid!
Science!
A science party tonight!
Science party tonight!
Science!
Uh, let's see what's going on at, uh...
Let's see what's up in the news here at NASA.
Yeah, check some science news. I haven't been... I've only been looking at the bad news.
The science news is so good! It makes you feel like everything's gonna be fine!
We'll have robots, uh, building robots that make better robots, and soon the robots will just take care of us all the time.
That's what we've got now, damn you!
And we won't even know they're doing it! We'll think that they've left the planet, been outlawed, but they'll be taking care of us.
It all makes sense. I was reading that Isaac Asimov robot series, and, you know, those were written in the 50s, but...
Was it iRobot?
You could see more... yes, that's the very first of the series, and then...
Actually, I kind of read the very end, and then I read the beginning, and I'm working my way towards the middle.
Well, NASA is apparently having a rocket...
Thousands of books.
A rocket contest.
A rocket contest?
Yeah.
That is disgusting.
Look, there's a big red rocket right on the screen there.
It's apparently a red rocket contest. Do you know anything about that, Dave?
Well, I know they glare. I know they, uh, glare, and also there's a...
Oh yeah, you've got a big dog. You probably know about that red rocket.
I thought you were talking about the rocket's red glare.
No, look at that big red rocket right there.
Not the sunshine left over from your effluvia after you gazed into the nostril, the third nostril of the solar disk, for so long, you were...
Your, your sinuses fry.
Do you think, uh, NASA is hoping that some super genius will stupidly reveal the, uh, perpetual motion, uh, faster than light engine...
So they can suppress it, yeah.
...that runs on no fuel, just breath?
So they can have a spokesman come out and say,
Yeah, you know, there never will or ever has been a machine that would focus your breath in a way that would make you move faster than a speed of light.
Safely. Uh, well, not really travel faster than light, but...
...a, a part through wormholes, using the power of your mind and your breath, and garlic.
Oh, that's, well, that's a yogic thing. You can get those at Safeway now.
Wow.
Travel without moving.
Look at here. Yeah, here.
Sex, IQ, and ET.
And now your icons are in your brain.
How we got big brains.
The same way we got it in the 80s.
Apparently, space.com is apparently running a story. Yeah, they have a picture of an Oberman there.
A job, big head man.
Waterhead.
An Obermansioner.
Brain head man.
He's a high macrocephalic.
A hot woman who doesn't have a big head.
She's a macrocephalic.
No, but she's looking very pensive and has a wonderful smile on her face.
Do you prefer macrocephalic or macro booty?
She's like hot for the brainiac.
You know what a big head means.
Yeah.
What goes with a big head?
So this is what space.com has degenerated to.
Big hat.
Look at, they're floating around the Amazon River looking...
Searching in boats.
What?
For a missing meteor.
Oh, yeah, sure.
That apparently was used by this guy to come to Earth.
Big headed thing rides...
We gotta describe this big headed guy.
Suddenly appears in the Amazon.
He has small jowls.
With women falling over in his feet.
He's got kind of a flabby foreskin around his neck.
His jaw protrudes a little bit, but not enough to show him as an Obermansion.
He looks more like an Untermansion with a macrocephalic problem.
Perhaps maybe hydrocephalic.
As if somebody poured the whole gallon there.
And the CIA is desperately trying to find his spaceship.
His spaceship, which has crashed in the Amazon.
They're telling everybody that it's a meteor.
Yeah.
Every time you hear about a search for a missing meteor...
I just thought we were somewhere in the West.
Anyway.
Looking for a meteor.
I'm sorry.
I just, I don't know what the good and the bad and the ugly came out of that meteor.
And out of that macrocephalic.
It was the Amazon, dude.
But that's where they also look, quote unquote, look for missing meteors.
And quote unquote dinosaur bones.
And whatever it is that they cordon off a huge area.
And white Indians.
That are so important to the United States government so they don't have to pay up.
We've got to stop them.
They're gonna kill us all.
When they took you up in their spaceship, did they do any sexual things to you?
That's what I call a closed encounter.
Its structure is just solidified on the surface.
I think it's anticipating the attack.
Anticipation denotes intelligence.
What was that?
Uh, it's a...
A what?
Space herpy.
That's disgusting!
Alien approaching.
Don't run.
We are your friends.
Oh my god.
Oh my god, coming.
Another one coming.
Imagine for a moment that this thing is not anything that can be identified because it prefers not to be.
Wherever there is life, it brings death.
Because it is evil.
Absolute evil.
One more reason to shoot first.
What if it goes out and melts down a busload of nuns?
How would you like to write the headline on that one?
Nun soup?
Behind me are the raging flames of where the Dome of the Rock, one of Islam's most sacred
sites, once stood.
Just moments ago, the ancient shrine was rocked by a devastating explosion that...
You lost the feed!
How do I know what happened?
Over three million are dead and thousands are seeking refuge after the free fall of
the Greek meteor shower hit Eastern Europe.
It is written in the last days, a world leader will rise up.
When possessed by Satan, he will declare himself God and embark on a reign of terror until
the Lord comes and destroys him.
The final battle between heaven and hell approaches.
I have a really bad feeling about this.
What doesn't kill you makes you stronger.
Look, I really don't think they flew 90 billion light years to come down here and start a
fight and get all rowdy.
If you calculate the time it takes to destroy a city and move on, we're looking at the worldwide
destruction of every major city in the next 36 hours.
We're being exterminated.
Flush the bombers, get the subs in launch mode.
We are at DEFCON 1.
The city is headed for a disaster of biblical terror.
What do you mean, biblical?
What do you mean, this Old Testament, Mr. Mayor?
The city is headed for a disaster of biblical terror?
Real wrath of God-type stuff.
Exactly.
Fire and brimstone coming down from the sky.
Rivers and seas boiling.
40 years of darkness, earthquakes, volcanoes.
The dead rising from the grave.
Human sacrifice, dogs and cats living together, mass hysteria.
I don't think I can cope with any more of this.
I think I'll just go and have a little lie down.
Jell-a-boom.
Boom, yeah.
I understand boom.
Baa-da-boom.
Big bada boom.
Big bada big boom.
Big boom.
Yeah, big bada boom.
Bada boom.
Big boom.
Big bada boom.
Man is an endangered species.
We'll stop any attack that they could begin.
Provided the attack is lame and poorly thought out and it's our grandma's.
Save your energy.
Save yourselves.
Avoid the planet Earth at all costs.
Farewell.
DJ Epoch did that collage, I think.
And before that, ESO Swamp Radio.
Lots of ESO Swamp Radio from WCSB.
Which is actually the Einstein Secret Outlaws band
with a mystery...
Every guest guitarist is heard in the background
jamming at Tranquility Base at Brushwood.
Before ESO Radio, we heard that song Science Party
is by Consortium of Genius,
a funny band that you can check out at their website,
www.consortiumofgenius.com
That's all one big word.
Consortium of Genius.
And now, friends, a live recording from the Akron Revival.
This year, sponsored by Reverend Toth Wilder, in which Reverend Dr. Uncle Haj Onan Kanobite
leads us in a sing-a-long.
I know a man, whose name was Bob, and selling things.
And I know a man, whose name was Bob, and selling things.
That was his job.
I knew a man, his name was Bob, and selling things.
He sold his things.
From door to door.
If you had some.
You'd buy some more.
I know he sold from door to door.
And he had some.
He'd buy some more.
He drove his car.
From town to town.
And believe me.
He got around.
He drove his car from town to town.
And believe me, he got around.
Jehovah One.
He think that one gave him a plan.
Soon some genius,
Soon some genius.
He'll rule the land,
He thinks that one gave him a plan.
Soon some genius,
He'll rule the land.
He thinks that one gave him a plan.
Well X day came
Well X day came.
And X day went.
Was all that cash
Truly well spent
It's true the cash
We won't give back
But we don't care
Cause we have slack
It's true the cash
We won't give back
But we don't care
Cause we have slack
Will this song end
Or go some more
Funny at first
Now it's a bore
Will this song end
Or go some more
Funny at first
Now it's a bore
And so I'll end
This endless tale
Returning to
The saint of sales
And so I'll end
This endless tale
Returning to the saint of sales
I knew a man
His name was Bob
I'm telling things
That was his job
Yeah!
That's kind of corny!
Thank you.
Yeah!
We are here tonight
As representatives of the church of the subgenius
We've covered the subgenius part
And I think you know the of-the part
But I would like to remind you
that this is not the hermitage of the subgenius.
This is not the monastery of the subgenius,
nor the nunnery of the subgenius.
This isn't the sit-at-home-alone of the subgenius,
or the play-on-your-computer-all-day of the subgenius.
And it's definitely not the come-to-the-limespider-and-don't-talk-to-other-people of the subgenius.
If each and every one of you don't meet someone tonight,
you have cheated yourself.
Perhaps it's a little intimidating to meet somebody tonight,
and so we're going to organize something else.
And by meeting somebody, I don't mean you should go up and talk to the sexiest person in the room,
because there's only one Chaz Smith here,
and if you're not going to meet him,
you don't have to go around.
But some of you should believe me.
That's what I heard.
You tried your best.
But as long as we fall back,
your future is over.
Because Chaz Smith is a dead man who decided to kill his stupid half-اب
and make it so little more obvious.
That's an adjustable percentage.
You, well,
that shouldj' y.
That shouldj' y.
It was Radi Pizza.
And your affection.
Oh B-Fan, Big-Fan, Big-Fan
Assassin's Creed
B-B-B-B-B-B-B by Doctor Onan's Wotan Band
Part 2 of remix number 2
Yes, and now a live instance of the Swingin' Love Corpses, the greatest of the old school
subgenius bands led by Dr. Philo and Sphinx Drummond and Ray Hay and Leif Cowabunga and
Mojo Skippy Butcher.
This is the way they would open their concerts, and this is actually their best song.
Gentlemen, here come the Swingin' Love Corpses.
Swingin' Love Corpses
as an apology to all of you beautiful fans who came out here tonight, we're going to
start with our best.
The Church of the Subgenius online pamphlet Shut Up or Gun Stand Up.
The brag of the subgenius.
A fragment.
Transcribed from a cassette tape recording made at a seance in 1973.
I picked the goddarned terror of the frigging gods out of my nose.
Pardon my language.
But yee-haw, let the sons of God and man bear witness.
Even in the belly of the thunderbird I've been casting out the false prophets,
I'm busting a nut and blowing my o-ring, and ripe to throw a loaf.
For I speak only the frigging truth, and never in my days have I spoken other than.
For my every utterance is a lie, including this very one you hear.
I say, have sex with, em, if they can't take a joke.
By God, anything for a laugh, I say.
I am the last remaining.
Homo correctus.
I am the goddarned man of the future.
I'll drive a mile so, as not to walk a foot.
I am a human being of the first goddarned water.
I'm insured for X, O God and Satan.
I was shanghaied by bodiless fiends and alien zoos from a corporate galaxy, and got away with their hubcaps.
I cannot be tracked on radar.
I wear nothing uniform.
I wear no goddarned uniform.
Yes baby, I'm 23 feet tall and have 13 rows of breasts.
I was settled.
My triceratops.
I gave the anti-verge in a high protein toxo-wash.
I'm a bacteriological weapon.
I'm armed and loaded.
I'm a fission reactor.
I fart plutonium.
Power plants are fueled by the sweat from my brow.
When they plug me in, the lights go out in Hong Kong.
I sired retarded space bastards across the cosmos.
I cook and eat my dead.
Yahoo.
I'm the unshaven thorn tree of the Atlantis Zoo.
I pay no taxes.
The devil's hands are my ideal player.
I hold the ground.
I hold the seven-bladed windbreaker.
The wheels that turn are behind me.
I think backwards.
I do it for fun.
My imagination is a frigging cancer and I'll pork it before it porks me.
The say a gonzillion is the highest number there is.
Well my god.
I count to a gonzillion and one.
Yes, I'm the purple flower of Hell County.
Give me wide berth when I drop my drawers, mother nature swoons.
I use a python for a prophylactic.
I'm thicker.
Harder and meaner than the Alaskan pipeline.
And carry more spew.
I'll freeze your seed before it gets the bathroom tile.
Yee.
Let's go.
All I can say is the basic problem is that the whole phlegmatic system has to be blown
out.
But what are you going to blow it out with?
Have you got the blow outage power that you need or g-
No, you have to blow out the phlegmatic buildup.
Well, you know, we have a saying around here what comes around goes around and our heads
are all stuck up our own asses.
No.
Oh.
You know.
Which is why we have the squeeze bulb syringes.
Oh, I can feel it right now.
It's kind of like...
You insert it into each nostril, and you squeeze it out first,
and then you insert it in the nostril, and you release the bulb, and it expels the fluid.
Now, where I'm coming from, I feel like there's a pair of buttocks wrapped on my head like a hat,
and somehow it makes me psychic.
Am I getting the right thing, or have I gotten something I shouldn't have?
I knew you were going to say that.
I knew you were going to bring up the whole psychic thing.
You are psychic.
Yes, he is.
It's your buttocks wrapped on my head, aren't it?
Isn't it?
It is.
I often think that there's somebody out there who's recording every word that happens in the show,
and then eventually they'll all be played back again.
And those are random, recurrent moments beloved by all.
Yes.
Order now, while surprises are limitless.
You may be asked to call upon for a certain favor.
Uh, maybe someone want...
Francis, this is the year 1962.
Imagine somebody listening to us at the same time in the year, oh, say 2002.
Boy, that's 40 years past. Can you imagine such a thing?
Ask not what your forehead can do in this small space.
Ask what my forehead is doing in your house.
But it's amazing the way you've got these records from the future.
I like that.
It's very...
It's very small and unique, like a snowflake.
It's emboldening.
It's emboldening and embossing as well.
Absolutely.
And I have heard you been called Snowflake so many times.
Yes, because she melts whenever you touch her.
Oh, yes.
She's a frosty little thing, huh?
Well, no, she's not frosty.
Something's lost and something's gained.
If you could see her now...
I mean, I never thought of it that way.
You would want to carve your own...
What does that mean there?
Something's lost and something's gained.
For every yin, there's a yang.
And living every day.
Yes, it's the yin and the yang.
It's a psycho-scrotal squander.
One step forward, two steps back.
It's a cosmic unbounded fugue.
Yeah, isn't it?
Isn't it?
So let us all remember the retching motion that Sri Hajambo has taught us.
Begin with a very, very deep breath and then start...
.
...
Till next week.
You must remember this...
A kiss is just a kiss.
But a nuclear explosive device...
Information is not knowledge.
Keep your head on tight.
You're back to the wind and you're sacking the saddle.
Well, he's got a point.
Keep that sack in this home.
I like that.
Phew.
But knowledge is not wisdom, and wisdom is not necessarily truth.
And truth is not necessarily...
Oh, thank you, ESO, Swamp Radio, WCSB, and special guest caller, Reverend Gilippo Abernathy.
Friends, you're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
And you can send me Stang tapes at...
Oh, got that pencil ready. P.O. Box 807 Glen Rose, Texas 76043.
You can also get that same information from www.subgenius.com.
Or you can write for free information on the Church of the Subgenius.
From Subgenius at P.O. Box 807 Glen Rose, Texas 76043.
I am Stang at subgenius.com.
And here is Heart Ignition.
وأ clinician
ِтак Zombie
وأ layers
WOW
vy
a И
ver
Thanks for watching!