From PR News in Washington, I'm being punished for speaking out against authorities.
Barack Obama and John McCain are false.
John McCain at a rally in Columbus, Ohio.
Obama in Hawaii.
Hillary Clinton on March 4th.
President Bush in Africa.
Mr. Bush in Africa is not the same as a military base.
We contemplate adding new bases.
In other words, this is baloney.
Or as we say in Texas, that's a big military base.
Mr. Bush visits Liberia with the exception of Liberia.
The opposition in Kenya was up a bigger than expected four-tenths of one percent last month,
reflecting increases in the cost of food, health care, and PR news.
In Iraq, a powerful Shiite cleric says he may expire as soon as this weekend.
Vasily Alexanyan, tax fraud, AIDS, and cancer, blind and needs life.
His lawyers chained to a toilet.
Lawyers being treated like dismantled animals and denied proper PR news.
Moscow.
The Labor Department says this is PR news.
From Washington.
PR Today.
It is the subgeneration of slack.
Order!
Now!
I will not accept aהоль,심 Mot'rára'rán that has nothing to offer to toughen up the
We respect it.
Hence we have ghosted a woman with eye drops.
We hated her for receiving refused grants until today, on November 3rd.
And we couldn't gather the original本 under the personellense mandate.
Ms.
veya η twiceâte班 yay'h.
and, oh no, one religious fanatic. Constable Visit saluted.
Permission to speak, sir? Go ahead, mumbled Vimes. I'm pleased to tell you, sir, that our mission is
clearly divinely approved of, sir. I refer to the rain of sardines which sustained us in our
extremity, sir. We were a little hungry. I wouldn't say we were in extremity.
With respect, sir, said Constable Visit firmly, the pattern is firmly established, sir.
Yes, indeed. The psychulites, when being pursued in the wilderness by the forces of
Oflarian mytholites, sir, were sustained by a rain of celestial biscuits, sir. Chocolate ones, sir.
Perfectly normal phenomenon, muttered Constable Shue, probably swept up by the wind,
passing a baker's shop. Visit glared at him and went on, and the Murmurians,
when driven into the mountains by the tribes of Mishmik,
would not have survived.
But for a magical rain of elephants, sir.
Elephants? Well, one elephant, sir, Visit conceded, but it splashed.
Perfectly normal phenomenon, said Constable Shue. Probably an elephant was picked up by a freak.
And when they were thirsty in the desert, sir, the four tribes of Canli were suckered
by a sudden and supernatural rain of rain, sir.
A rain of rain, said Vimes, almost mesmerized by,
That was from the audiobook of Terry Pratchett's wonderful novel, Jenga. This Hour of Slack has a general theme of religion, my friends.
And so we'll hear the appropriate clips from recent shows, such as the Winter Star Symposium preaching,
Season in Hell from San Francisco,
superb Limeur cut-ups, as heard at the start,
and Aurelian collages to follow,
and the puzzling evidence show from KPFA Berkeley,
where at first, even Dr. Howell was at a loss.
Oh my, well, I really don't know what to do now.
I'm, uh, I'm probably, uh...
That music's too loud, puzzling evidence.
It is?
I can't hear Dr. Howell properly over that sappy music.
That's...
Think of the deaf.
Doesn't anyone ever think of the deaf?
We do, on this show.
We have a certain portion of our show content is directed at deaf people.
Can you guys imagine how hard it is for me to do a radio show
when we're having total deafness now?
We can imagine how hard it is for me to do a radio show.
Is that increasing, like Beethoven's, uh...
Getting more and more hard-o'-hearing?
Luckily, on this show, it doesn't make...
It don't make... No, never mind.
It would be a show idea.
Don't make one damn bit of difference.
...they're all crazy.
It's there for me.
Face me.
You can be me.
Make the world we never know.
Don't move it up.
Stand on the internet.
WTF?
What the fuck?
You can't imagine how many times I've had to remove or reverse you guys saying that.
And you're listening to Puzzling Evidence.
Really?
We don't say it very often.
And you will be listening to the hour of slack.
Yes, you will.
If you'd like to be a part of us, of our broadcast right now,
give us a call at...
Unless you're driving.
If you're driving, just crawl in the backseat and relax.
That's...
For sure.
We'll take care of itself, much like you're driving.
First dial a one and a five and a one and a oh and then eight and then four and then eight
and then four and then four and then...
Where's this going?
Yeah, what is that theme?
We were going to do a theme, right?
There was going to be a theme or a skit or a sketch or a plan or a script or a note.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, here's your script, baby.
Here we are driving in a car.
Driving into each other.
That's what we caused here on...
94.3.
Into a big hole.
If you're in one of those cars, we're sorry.
Simple 19th century...
Hey, man, we've got listeners in Algeria tonight.
Wow.
What?
The Moroccan...
Moroccan roll, man.
I'm going to go over to the highway.
Oh, I know who that is.
I know who that is.
That would be the worst day ever guy.
Stop ex-torturing me.
Oh.
I used to call him...
Akbar because I didn't want to give away his real name.
Yeah.
Yeah, we get interesting e-mails at the Subgenius Foundation Incorporated headquarters.
However, you know, I did bring a script.
What I have here is the program book for last Sunday's Mission Peak Unitarian Universalist Congregation.
Well, I'm drilling down onto this site right now.
I made notes.
Whatever.
Drill down.
I made notes.
They did an inspirational show without mentioning Jesus or Jehovah.
Well, that in itself is inspiration.
And here was my comment on the Unitarian Congregation.
Did they wear unitards?
Yeah, whatever.
Here's my review.
The word nice.
Nice.
That's nice.
Like Captain Nice.
See this gorgeous cover?
Actually, this listener...
Shot in the dark.
Track 14 is...
Brewer, Cleve, and his lush orchestra.
Really?
We have a lot of interesting people in here.
There's somebody else in there.
Oh, Mr. Lucky.
No, that's the same.
This is right outside of...
It's in Morocco, outside of Dar el-Baeda.
It's a neighborhood called Setat, it looks like.
And we have a listener in Setat tonight.
In Selak?
Hello.
My goodness, a caller.
The right place to be in today's world.
Hello, you're on the air.
I zoomed in on you from a satellite view.
It was great.
It really felt good.
And if we push this one button, we can wipe you out like George Clooney, man.
George Clooney, man.
Let's not make any threats.
After all, we're all...
Actually, it's a download going on in Setat.
You know, some...
Some...
Ten and eight.
Trouble.
It reached a point.
It had reached a point.
Problems.
Ten and eight.
Didn't know what to do.
They went in to see the minister, and the minister said he wanted to talk to the boys by themselves.
The minister said that he wanted the eight-year-old into his office first.
He called the eight-year-old into his office, and he sat him down in a chair, and he looked at him, and he said to this eight-year-old little boy, he said,
Where is...
And he goes into the restroom, he goes...
Now, we're, you know, if you think about it, we're in a cult...
A cult...
Where is...
Dumber...
Drive-by...
Stalking...
There...
Is...
Stink...
Um, watch this.
Here at the top...
What...
Mental...
Go...
Check out...
Nah...
Big deal.
How can we really know?
Think about it.
Come together.
Stink...
Who did this?
Drive-by...
Word...
You're gonna be...
Coming...
Nah...
Dumb...
Pretty outrageous...
Absurd...
Live...
After...
I wanna...
Be...
Really...
Really high...
Check this out...
Two plus two...
Equals...
Two...
Three...
Jump off...
I'll go down...
Yep...
I went down...
Um...
When I went down, it didn't surprise any of you...
I went down...
I'll go down...
Every time...
Touch him...
Check that out...
I want to have a relationship...
I want...
You...
Me...
So, um...
Another thing that the Church of the Subgenius functions as...
And this is purely out of our own cruelty...
Is...
As a sort of...
Kook...
Flypaper...
Not so much the church itself...
But, um...
The internet part of the church...
If you ever look at our...
News group...
It's called...
Alt.
Slack...
It's one of the oldest news groups on the internet...
Because...
It's a church for geeks...
And...
Among other things...
But it was...
Really...
You know...
The spaz church of macho irony...
That appealed to the people who invented the computers...
And invent...
Were inventing the internet...
About the same time that Bob was inventing his church...
And, um...
There's this forum...
You can...
Get to using Google...
On your browser...
Just type in...
Alt.
Slack...
You'd never know that it's been there for...
30 years...
And...
Man...
It is like...
This...
You know...
You know how unpleasant flame wars are...
This is...
The flame war that never ends...
Because we attract...
The...
As you might...
Guess...
We attract...
All kinds...
In...
Uh...
The differently...
Sane...
We like to call it...
You know...
I wouldn't want to be...
Rude...
Or...
Uh...
And, you know...
Why do you think they call it...
Sub...
Genius...
Uh...
So...
So there's a lot of...
What you might call...
Tom...
Cookery...
Going on...
But...
Uh...
And it's fun...
It's really fun...
To...
Get...
To attract...
They...
My favorite...
Ones...
Are the ones that call us...
Satanic...
Masonic...
Jewish...
Conspiracy...
And, you know...
Those...
The...
Satan...
Jewish...
And Masonic...
Don't usually...
Just automatically...
Fall into place...
Except for a certain type of person...
And to them...
It's all the same...
And...
You know...
It's still just terribly obvious...
So...
The church is...
Helping to...
Helping crazy people...
Make asses of themselves...
No...
Let me...
Let me do this right...
The church is...
To...
Crazy people...
Making asses of themselves...
What bug zappers are to bugs...
What matadors are to bulls...
And what...
Lucy Van Pelt...
With her football...
Was to Charlie Brown...
That's...
What we're...
Here for...
That's a nice description...
Don't you think...
Of the church...
Not original to me...
I got that from our...
Cook fly paper...
And...
Another important point about...
This particular religion...
Is unlike most of them...
And unlike...
Most of our fellow...
Cooks and crackpots...
We admit...
That we don't know everything...
Can you imagine that?
I mean that's really...
That's not much of a religion...
Because part of a real religion is...
You get to feel like you know everything...
Like you are so special...
That you deserve to know...
Why the universe is here...
You deserve to know what...
God meant for you personally...
Because you're so special...
And to God you probably are...
I can't...
I'm not gonna pretend to speak...
For God...
Because lots of people are already doing that...
I've noticed...
People feel like...
Poor old God can't handle his own problems...
They gotta take care of it themselves...
You know...
So oh my gosh...
Look at that...
Those people...
They're in the wrong religion...
And they're raising a child...
We better take that child away from them...
Because God isn't powerful enough to do it...
You know...
Just me...
The great New York family judge...
However...
Can help God out...
And we've seen...
By the way...
Speaking of the infamous...
Subgenius child custody case...
They lost...
And then...
The biological dad...
Screwed up so much...
That they won the kid back...
So the Bevilacqua family...
Of Jesus, Magdalene, Conbo...
And their new child...
Reverend Bonecracker...
They are all together...
Magdalene had a new child...
With Jesus...
Who was such a powerful little subgenius...
That on his exit...
Into the world...
He broke her coccyx...
And thus...
Although we won't reveal his real name...
His subgenius...
Or his slave name rather...
His subgenius true name is...
Reverend Bonecracker...
Tough little devil...
So yeah...
You know...
What rule book is it...
That says we have to know...
Why the universe exists...
Or even if it exists...
That's the real...
Mystical stuff...
You know...
Personally I feel...
Like I am the poor blinded...
Cyclops...
Stumbling ever towards...
What I think might be light...
And it always turns out to be...
One of those damn Dobbs heads...
But it still looks friendly to me...
After all these years...
Some religions may...
Represent themselves with a cosmic diagram...
And those are good...
We have plenty of those...
Some religions represent themselves with...
Pornography of a naked guy being tortured...
That's fine...
We've got lots of that in our videos...
Over there...
Boys and girls...
But we are religion...
Is represented by a smiling guy...
He does have a pipe...
And some people think that...
Is unhealthy...
And then they're always going...
Bob's smoking in his pipe now...
He's smoking...
Actually...
If you study this illustration...
On my chest...
Which I'll show off to the video cameras...
As best I can...
Bob is...
There's a brain here...
And there's fire up here...
That brain is you...
You're smoking...
Bob's brain...
Using Bob as a pipe...
And the bowl of his pipe as the stem...
In other words...
Look...
This isn't the crime...
This is the crutch of the subgenius...
Bob...
We don't want you using Bob as a crutch...
It would look like a dog pile...
But you let Bob use you as a crutch...
You don't ask Bob what he's smoking...
You jump in his pipe and let him smoke you, baby!
That's what this is about...
Let Bob smoke you!
And I...
You know...
To tell the truth...
I have no idea...
What happens after that...
But...
That's the thing about religion...
You don't question that kind of stuff...
You don't...
As Bob said...
You don't use your mind...
To think about your religion...
Because that just wrecks everything...
It's pointless...
It's based on faith...
Or a face in this case...
This is a face-based religion...
That's all we need...
Is that face...
And I'll tell you...
I'll tell you...
Something that's not even a very big secret...
We stole that particular picture of Bob...
From an old Yellow Pages clip art catalog...
That wasn't copyrighted...
We used it across state lines in commerce...
For two years...
And it became our trademark...
Then Jesus screwed up...
And we lost the trademark...
But before anybody noticed...
We got it back...
Don't you wish you'd known...
That brief period of time...
You could have taken over the church...
By asking your parents...
...you're escaped away from church...
From...
...faith...
You're still...
Toique!
Who's Nice...
I'm Isabelle Lemut!
Aaaand...
heps bam...
Siggle!!!
Nope.
Silenced.
Christ and the Bible, or ludicrous
matter, free speech
should take preeminence in today's world.
Deny the existence of
God, me, me, me, me, me, me, me,
what you say, what you say, God,
Jesus Christ and the Bible,
depraving public morality, holding us
as, as, as, shake it, shake it, as, attack
or insult religious beliefs.
Shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it,
shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it,
shake it, shake it, shake it, shake it.
Little callers, I should point out that
on tonight's show,
we've got, uh, Hal.
Hal. Philo.
Philo. Ivan.
Ivan. Cardhouse robot.
Nope, that's Cardboard Bob. Nope, that's
Cardhouse. I thought you said Cardboard Bob.
Robot Cardhouse. So we should go on, uh,
on his, on his
show, don't you think? Who, Cowboy Bob?
Or, or who?
Copy Bob. Copy Bob.
Oh, yes. Yeah, we're, what happened to Copy Bob
the other night? He left and we never got a
chance to really get anything arranged.
He actually went down the entire line of subways.
Subgub DBs.
And got to me. Subgum Chowdini.
And was, you know, as his usual polite self,
but then he wandered off saying, I'm drunk, I'm drunk.
But I felt so sorry for him because I thought, yeah.
Drunk is a stupid thing.
But we believed that every one of those guys was really us.
Wine is a mother.
I was, it was so funny to stand on top of the building
watching our doubles talk to that guy.
Now, tomorrow or later,
I hope Copy Bob calls tonight.
Did I go to the same concert you did?
I saw, like, UFOs
that made this guy black.
There were so many of them.
Wow.
That's where I was? At the roundhouse?
I thought it was at Calumet.
Yeah, that's where they
turn locomotives around
so they can actually
go back the other way
on the same piece of track.
X-Day is just around the world from us now.
It always is, and that's why we can escape
its wrath as the heat ray
moves towards us each year.
Okay, so let's do the little,
I'm doing a little Flash movie here of what the end of the world
looks like. Flash!
It's kind of hard to make out.
Okay, vary your delivery style, alright?
Would you please provide variation
in your delivery style?
I'm sorry.
Surely you got the software upgrade.
This is in excess of the...
Reintroduce the show after each
show break.
Uh-oh. Show break.
I'll tell you when Peter and John
come down there and begin to
preach about the Holy Ghost talking in tongues,
he come...
Yes, I'm dying.
These wicked Israelites shall
slide in...
That's just dumb.
That's about the dumbest thing I've ever heard.
What you just said is stupid.
It's just stupid.
That's just dumb.
And God says,
stand in shock
to have your hair stand on its ends.
And maybe you drunk.
God says,
shock him.
That makes his hair stand on end.
So, nothing.
Nothing.
Well, I was praying last night
when an angel broke the lines.
He said, I'm gonna have to put you on hold
for a time.
I said, hold like hell.
Let me talk to the boss.
He said, I'm sorry.
Sinner is the boss's day off.
And I realized
that the wages are same.
Plus two bucks an hour
and work a weekend.
And I wish,
I wish I could have a good day.
back to the closet.
God,
did, did, did
this son of a bitch
all I said I would
if I could?
I can't, so I won't.
Well, I wouldn't want you
dancing your hair with some gold.
And I realized
then that the way is the same.
Cause all the lumber
you can carry,
all the nails you can get,
and the wages are seen.
Though he wore a clear
moody and fretless
second to me.
Damn him and his feelings.
No sexy, no show.
And I'm not sure
that I really want to go.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Yeah, you been
missing him and saying
the price that you'd pay
is now obligating
but I'm never saying
think.
To the church, to the stage
you gotta cut your cap,
atus, and the Bronx,
Thank you.
Must be great drumming.
You and Norm have a good time
in Chicago.
It'll be warmer
in here.
I'll stay here. I'll stay here
when the wind blows.
Oh yeah, we're waiting to see
Yeah, we're waiting to see
That's it
I feel like I'm running
I don't know
How do we be supposed to know about these nut religions
and occult kooks out there?
You've never heard of Alistair Crowbar?
That charlatan, that poser, that charlatan
why he went on a mountain climbing expedition
and caused his good friends
to fall off a rocky rock
and get morass
and impasse
You can tell what kind of a magician
somebody is from the way he behaves out in the bush
Hey look man
I
I'm not responsible for that
I am a consecrated magician
of O.T.O.
and I will not
brook to hearing
point one
Well what are you going to do about it buddy?
This is a subgenius hour
Hey listen
Hey listen pink boy
These
These may be subgenies
but they're
they're sanctioned by yours truly
Mobius Rex
I'm Priest King of Pacifica
and I'm initiated to
higher mysteries
than anyone in the O.T.O.
can possibly claim
so
watch your car
and let's go
Be careful
I'm not here to
We're scared
and we got this transmitter
and we don't know what to do with it
Please
That's right
Don't subliminate me
Subgenius Revival
We regret the interruption of our service
and promise
to be able to continue
to support
People if you hear about on the radio
every week
Stationers who attend our writing workshops
know that 20 kilofiles
and 90 ounces of air
are broadcast every night
You're an addict to pornographic movies
and vice versa
File
Passions
of sexual perversion
Be
not
unseemly
It's happening here
You say well how?
MTV
VHA
US1
F Time
H Max
Show X
VHVO
Need I go on?
No
Why?
It'll shock you
It's happening here
It's happening everywhere
And the problem is this
We have not said
That Kinky Friedman
Was the only way to heaven
You never did
Need I go on?
No
Why?
There's gonna come a day
If it hadn't already happened
Where Kinky Friedman
Reveals the root
Need I go on?
No
Why?
The fruit reveals the root
But yet we've become a society
Where we're not
The only way
That just embraces
Kinky Friedman
There is
No
Other
Way
Need I go on?
No
Why?
Honey buns
Sauerkraut
And donuts
Horseradish
And cakes
You say well I know that
They taught me that in school
Yeah I know they taught you that in school
What they didn't teach you
Was don't forget relish
Need I go on?
No
Why?
One Bob buried his wife
in Canada
One Bob alive in Canada
Don't even mention that pink Canuck
That's an evil counterfeit Bob
As we all know
Who espouses the political philosophy
Of Lyndon LaRouche
And commits idolatry
At the altar of all people
Marshall McLuhan
Oh lord
And with his rich friend
Give him helicopter rides
He seems to have some ability
To convince the unwary
That he is
He himself is Bob Dobbs though
Politely asked to cease and desist
His messianic zeal
Has not permitted this to take place
What happens when somebody
Says they're Bob
It's obvious they're not
And they post themselves on places like
You know MySpace
Does Bob ever say
I'm Bob
No one makes that claim except
The one who has to commit
The crime of falsehood
What do they put quotes around it?
Just as no one who says
I'm just as good as you
Is ever as good as the person
That he's saying it to
Because otherwise why say it?
Maybe they are
Well but then
You know maybe really
Maybe they really are
But have an inferiority complex
However in that
So therefore they're not
Right there
They are defective
Just for that alone
Remember we must be as harsh as truth
And as uncompromising as justice
Praise Bob
Oh I thought of the phrase
I was trying to explain to somebody earlier today
That our church is a self validating philosophy
And all the really great like Scientology
The Mormons and so forth
They're self validating
Because they have worked into their philosophy
Something that discounts anything against the philosophy
In other words it's like
A perfect recipe for eternal stupidity
But who cares if you get slack?
When was the last time being smart got you a date?
Actually in the case of a lot of us
That's probably about the only way we ever got dates
But you know what I'm saying
In the normal world it's
As Bob said act like a dumb shit
And they'll treat you like an equal
Sad but true
And we learn that on the job almost every day don't we?
I had to because of one of the many I'm a Bobs
That we have to deal with
People get as crazy as all this sounds
We actually have people that get so into it
That we have to deprogram them
We have to deprogram our own zombies
And some of them you can't deprogram them
You can extremely
You can cross your fingers and tell them all kinds of stuff
Oh it's just a piece of clip art
We're just making fun of religion
You can go away now
No no I'm not going to pass miracles
Please please
And we had to explain to someone
The term solipsism
Solipsism
Noun
Number one
Philosophy
The theory that only the self exists
Or can be proved to exist
Two
Extreme preoccupation with and indulgence of one's feelings
Desires
Etc
Egoistic self-absorption
Wait a minute
That's the new age
And the church of the subgenius
Forget what I just said friends
Is there really a place called hell?
No
Yes
There is subgenius heaven
Or wait no subgenius
Is hell better than Christian heaven?
There is a place called hell
You didn't ask Dr. Hell
At Revelation X
But don't confuse that with ask brother Hal
Which is on pirate cat radio
I just don't believe there is such a place as hell
But there is
No how
It's a character in a movie
If you believe the Bible
See that's what's happened
Movies have influenced so strongly
That everybody thinks they're real
Hell is speaking into the microphone
Oh hell exists friends
There is a place of eternal darkness
Where in leaping flames
Leering demons
Plunge sizzling pitchforks
Into the quivering buttocks
Of uh
Sordid sinners
I'm telling you
I've seen the imps of Satan
Leaping in the flames
Yes yes I have
Dr. Hal
And uh the monsters too of hell
Gorgons
Hydras
And Chimeras
But aren't there a lot of naked chicks in hell?
All the pictures I ever saw
Yes there are
Uh didn't I show you that 15 minutes of footage I got from hell?
You really should see that
Maybe I could bring it over the files
Oh the 1930s movie?
Uh or Dante's Inferno?
Yeah
I would love to have
Yeah I have seen that uh that footage
And it is some hot stuff
In more ways than one
And what are you talking about?
There's a Hollywood movie about hell that involved
I would have loved to have been on that set
Yes
It would have been like being on the set of Prospero's books
Shows all these nude babes being tortured in hell
You know that's a
Um
They could get away with it because it was religious
What was the name of the movie?
Dante's Inferno
Yeah it was based on an old children's book
You've probably heard of it
It was
I want you to catch that for a moment
God has never intended for one person to go to hell
With Spencer Tracy
Hell was created not for man
It's Jimmy Swagger
God has done everything he can to keep man from going there
Despite the fact that almost all
I don't hear any fart sounds
Have I got the right channel?
Has gone
Well you know I thought that was Michael Pepe
But I guess it's
If you go to hell it's kind of like being in Beetlejuice
But hell is
Well everyone knows
Everywhere you look are
Sites of
Horror
Um
If you listen closely to the Beetlejuice soundtrack
Danny Elfman threw in a little tip of the hat
To the Godzilla theme
Do you remember which uh
Any track specifically?
No
But somewhere in there there's that little
Tiny tanks tiny tanks lots of little tiny tanks
Oh right right
I don't remember what that is either
I just
I just kind of scratched the part that's got
Dan dan dan dan dan dan dan dan dan dan dan dan dan dan dan dan dan dan dan
They had a picture of you in this thing
It gets ya it really gets to ya after a while
It got to me Philo and
Look what happened
There's some puzzling evidence show there
And now two musical interludes
The first by the classical composer Fernande Nande-Limure
And the next by the jazz master Norell Preff
And now the finale
No
Yeah
I
Thank you.
Hopefully the first of many.
Can you see the future ones also being a subgenius-themed night?
Yes, yes.
We'll try to get all the subgeniuses on board and take them up north.
And when's the last time that there was a gathering of such subgeniuses in the San Francisco area coming together for one event, one night?
Last January.
And then next February again.
Oh, wait.
February, oh, wait.
February, yeah.
What's the event?
Mongo is putting out another one of these things.
And that's the name of it, right?
Yeah.
He doesn't even know about it.
Yeah, we'll come up with it.
We didn't tell you yet, sorry.
We'll make it up next time.
But I was saying, Stan will be back here in February, so that's when you have to do that.
Yeah, but that's for my nephew's Bob Mitzvah.
The Bob Mitzvah.
Yes, we'll have to work this through.
And I understand puzzling evidence will be circumcising.
Yeah, yeah.
Is it a Bob-er-is?
A Bob-er-is, a Bob-er-is.
Squaring the circle.
A Bob-er-is.
Are there any...
December holidays in the subgenius calendar?
Yes, Existlessnessmas.
And what's the date?
Which corresponds with the pagan Christmas and the Christian Christmas.
So right the same day.
It occurs on the 25th of December.
Susie the Flusie calls it Slaternalia.
Oh, very good.
The holiday of Slaternalia or Existlessnessmas.
And what kind of symbols are popular with this holiday?
What kind of?
It's like with every culture.
Well, winged eyeballs.
Yeah, you spend a lot of money and get real drunk.
So no tree, no candelabra of a special resort.
Instead of giving gifts to your loved ones, you're supposed to steal something from all your loved ones.
Very nice.
Well, then there are the angels here.
What didn't they get for their holiday?
Well, there are many things.
Definitely Bob.
Very good.
Are there any other holidays within the calendar that correspond with the pagan Christian calendar?
Actually, the other name for the Christmas holiday was Turnover.
You know, it's sad.
That's all in Book of the Subgenius, but I haven't been reading my prescriptions all that well lately.
I need to go through that section.
That's chapter 11, I believe.
Or is it chapter 9?
Thank you.
to subdivisions. Butters, Butters, there you are.
Uh, uh, uh, I'd like to go ahead. Uh, I, uh, feces. Uh, so what?
Butters, Butters, I have a lot of special feelings.
Mantle, Mantle.
Butters, Butters, Butters, Butters.
Child pornography.
Senator Butters.
Knowingly views child pornography. And I would move.
Butters, Butters.
Butters.
Uh, sexual.
Hi, hi.
Butter, Butter.
Penis, Penis.
Butter.
Butter, Butter.
I have passed out.
The homo, they came together in a compromise.
Butter.
Yeah, isn't it great?
That was me at DocStock2.
Get a little shot.
This show really is hurting.
My back.
It hurts my head.
Normally it hurts my ears and my, and it is true that there is a pain between my ears.
A dungeon.
But my back hurts this time.
That pain between your ears is called your brain.
As one great furnace flames.
Well, thanks for informing me.
Yet from those flames, no light.
Okay, get on the elevator now.
Go ahead.
Darkness visible.
I hate following you guys around the studio.
Served only to discover sites of woe, regions of sorrow.
You're all just stepping on somebody's heels.
Doleful shades wet my face.
You're stepping on my face.
My heels, I'm stepping on your heels.
Rest can never dwell.
Hope never comes.
We gotta make some copies.
Don't forget we gotta make some copies.
But torch without end still urges, and a fiery deluge fed with ever burning sulfur, unconsumed.
What happened to Copy Bob?
Oh, he went off to get some coffee, and then he fell into the coffee machine and was consumed.
And it could happen to you.
Subgenius listeners.
Are you the next Copy Bob?
Are you Copy Copy Bob?
Or are you an original, ready for others to copy you in the endless matrix?
The evolution of subgeniuses happens like this.
If you copy the same thing over and over again on a Xerox machine, each copy will be only
slightly different, but the one at the end will be quite different from the one you started.
It is a perfect example of evolution, a window into God's methods.
And then it hit me.
For God, there is no zero.
Even though I was a tiny, runt-like midget, all God's creation was still large and glorious,
which was a great soothing comfort considering I was about to be sucked into the abyss.
I was sucked up by a bacterium twice my size.
I still exist for the time being, which gets increasingly smaller, because as I get smaller,
time goes super fast.
Oh, is this the director's cut of Incredible Shrinking Man?
Yes.
You know, they should redo that one since they're redoing I Am Legend and all these
other things.
I've actually been surprised that that one hasn't been redone.
What, Galaxy Quest?
No, the Incredible Shrinking Man.
It's the coolest, man.
It's got little buttons.
It's got little monsters and they go to Utah to film in Little Pumpkin State Park or wherever
it is.
What are you talking about?
The little evil baby planet.
Of course, the second Omega Man, you know, the second one did have Charlton Heston.
It also had Woodstock.
It had Whitey Gravy in it.
Yes, Charlton Heston would go to a movie theater.
He's the last man on Earth, so he'd go to a movie theater and he'd cue up Woodstock
and watch it and go, you beautiful, crazy kids.
He's sitting in the audience watching Woodstock.
Damn it, they blew it all to hell.
Go, go, you wonderful, crazy, beautiful monsters.
Just some old guy watching movies.
That's it, kids.
Make love, not war.
We frequently went to church together on Sunday evenings at St. Stephen's.
And one Sunday evening after service, I asked him up to my apartment.
And as we walked along, we talked.
Dr. Branson, it's midnight.
I wonder why.
Now I shall look up and say...
Money.
Exactly.
Five thousand dollars.
That's the same thing they told me.
So if you will take these rubber gloves, put them on, please.
All right.
But what about next time?
And the next?
I don't know.
Well, time is moving on.
No one would've believed that humans were intelligences greater than man's...
Looked across space searching for Uranus...
Surrounded by an unbreathable atmosphere of methane gas.
If they start anything, we can blast them right off the Earth.
Better than a lion farm or a snake pit.
Thank you, sir.
From P.R. News in Washington, I'm plunged into chaos because of alleged corruption.
Atlantis has undocked from the International Slaughterhouse. The crew has been trying to
determine if any beef they served in their cafeteria could pose a danger on reentry.
The shuttle has completed a nine-day mission in which astronauts made a public call for
the beef grains on Wednesday. Former First Lady Nancy Reagan is likely to be going into
the food supply. PR News is bad. PR is bad. More than 50 top former Philippine government
officials recognized today that this is PR News in Washington.
Thanks to Lemur, this is the Hour of Slack from the Church of the Subgenius. For more
information on the Church of the Subgenius, please go check out subgenius.com or write
us at P.O. Box 181417 Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118. The music in the background is by Stephen
Kent from his CD.
Oil and water. And now, an important message.
We live in a country in which a person cannot get elected president if he openly doubts
the existence of heaven and hell. This is truly remarkable. Given that there is no other
body of knowledge that we require our political leaders to master.
Even a hair stylist must pass a licensing exam before applying his trade in the United
States. And yet, those given the power to make war and national policy, those whose
decisions will inevitably affect human life for generations are not expected to know anything
in particular before starting to work. They do not have to be political scientists, economists,
or even lawyers. They need not have studied information and know that they are not the
relations, military history, resource management, civil engineering, or any other field of knowledge
that might be brought to bear in the governance of a modern superpower.
They need only be expert fundraisers, comport themselves well on television, and be indulgent
of certain myths.
Our president regularly speaks in phrases appropriate to the 14th century, and no one
seems inclined to find out what words like God and crusade and wonder-working power mean
to him.
Not only do we still eat the awful of the ancient world, we are positively smug about
it.
Gary Wills has noted that the Bush White House is currently honeycombed.
It does not seem out of place to wonder whether the myths that now saturate our discourse
will wind up killing many of us, as the myths of others already have.
It seems extraordinarily likely that our descendants will look upon many of our beliefs as both
impossibly quaint and suicidally stupid.
It is time we admitted, from kings and presidents on down, that we are not just a bunch of fools
who make headlines for291.
Chapter II
ES англий이
tech平
megafon
r
uy
lly
x
varios
galю
of civilizing insights that the human mind has only just begun to inscribe upon itself
through secular politics and scientific culture.
We will see that the greatest problem confronting civilization is not merely religious extremism.
Rather, it is the larger set of cultural and intellectual accommodations we have made to
faith itself.
Self-religious moderates are in large part responsible for the religious conflict in
our world, because their beliefs provide the context in which scriptural literalism and
religious violence can never be adequately opposed.
Every sphere of genuine discourse must, at a minimum, admit of discourse, and hence the
possibility that those standing on its fringe can come to understand the truth of the world.
Understand the truths that it strives to articulate.
This is why any sustained exercise of reason must necessarily transcend national, religious,
and ethnic boundaries.
There is, after all, no such thing as an inherently American, or Christian, or Caucasian, physics.
Twenty minutes of show.
An hour of midnight here on the West Coast.
Your list.
Listening to the slack-stuffed final moments of A Season in Hell.
This time, the show was infested with subgeniuses.
You are lucky enough to be tuning in right now, even if it is later.
You have the opportunity still to call us.
Where is the...
Reverend Ivan Stang is in the studio this evening.
Dr. Hal Lloyd-Mongoloid puzzling evidence.
K-Rob.
And myself, John.
Yes, we are all here hashing out some of the finer points of subgenius doctrine and history.
The latter being the reminiscence of old cronies, old coots and doddering gray-bearded moons,
trying to recall in their shattered minds.
What is, uh...
From the dust heap of history.
What is Bob's stance on cronyism?
Well.
We're all the cronies of Bob.
We're a lodge.
A friendly, back-slapping, towel-snapping lodge of like-minded individuals.
Well, that makes me feel better already.
Because you're included.
Oh, thank you.
But, uh...
Bob also said...
That music in the background is by Mark Mothersbaugh.
Believe me out of it.
Next, friends.
We shall die.
At first, with a clip from Anthony Hopkins' great movie, Slipstream.
You may have noticed I really like that movie, Slipstream.
And finally, with the late Professor Chaz Smith, covering a Bob Dylan song.
One of the very last recordings Chaz made.
You know, he was falling all over the place.
He was perspiring.
And I don't know.
His gun fell from his hand.
And then the next thing he saw, he was like, oh, my God.
He collapsed.
And so that was, you know, I don't know.
That was it.
You know, the actor died.
And we were left high and dry.
Literally.
Wow.
Yeah, wow.
But the spooky thing was...
What?
Oh, I don't know how to describe it.
It's like...
It's like we're...
We have no control over anything.
Like we're being pushed about by something.
Everybody on the set felt it.
It was like a big joke.
A joke?
Yeah.
I mean, it was like a big joke.
It was really strange.
How?
Well, the guy who wrote it, he did it for a laugh.
That's what we heard anyway.
Who wrote it, Kevin?
I don't know.
Nobody knows, really.
Nobody knows who he is or where he came from.
It's kind of scary.
How do you mean scary?
Like when you're a little kid and it's dark.
Keep thinking that you see somebody you don't know looking at you through a window.
It's kind of like a dream.
Yeah.
Alex is a good DJ.
Yes, he's a good DJ.
Oh, yeah?
I see it too.
And he really likes music.
He's right.
He's very rich.
Stay with me over Christmas.
Yeah.
I've got to go.
And, thank you.
Isn't that a KC thing?
Yeah.
Knock, knock, knockin' on heaven's door
Mama put my guns in the ground
I can't shoot them anymore
The cold black cloud is comin' down
Feels like I'm knockin' on heaven's door
Knock, knock, knockin' on heaven's door
I'm knock, knock, knocking on heaven's door
Oh yeah, I'm knock, knock, knocking on heaven's door