Somewhere in the forbidding tundra mountains of Lapland, high above the Arctic Circle,
a group of mining engineers were prospecting for copper.
But what they unearthed was a story.
A story that was to terrorize the whole world.
I'm in there and have to dig life with father, and I mean Father Slack.
The Soft Genius Power of Slack
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry
Let me get you radio boneheads going.
Watch out. No, no, no, no.
Okay, okay, watch out.
Okay, all right, get us going.
We're waiting.
Lay before me, Earthman.
Hey, he said he's going to get us going.
Ivan, come on, let the guy talk.
Emperor of planet Earth.
Okay, shut up, Ivan.
And I have...
I have come to destroy your beauty.
The cause is going to get us going.
Lamo, both of you are Lamos.
I know, I think he's in for the world.
The first group are right over there behind Reverend Patterson.
How do you know there's both of us?
How do you know there's not three of us being Lamos?
Each time he says it, he has to pay that.
Obviously, there's four of us being lame here, not two.
Both would imply a couplet.
Yeah, it's easy to say lame.
It's easy to say lame.
I can say lame.
Lame, lame, lame, lame, lame, lame.
The lamest show with the lamest callers.
So if you get really close to the mouthpiece, does that mean you can talk a lot more loudly?
I don't know.
But you can say lame.
Come on, say lame.
One more time.
Lame, lame, lame.
Oh, my God, there'll be a molestation.
You're an adolescent and you overcompensate.
Oh, no.
How many cans of Red Bull have you had?
Adolescent.
Adolescent?
Yeah.
Adolescent.
No, I just reached puberty.
Hey, I have four hairs on my nuts.
Are you sure?
That just stopped the show.
Hey, we're cruising now.
That's not what your mom said.
I should make jokes about flame over there.
Because we are cruising now.
Now we're cruising.
Thanks to that caller, we're kicked off.
We are cruising down the road.
I feel the wheels turning.
Yeah, and I have to.
I feel the gears meshing.
I feel the wheels meshing.
Michael Poopy.
Because this is the last show of the millennium, folks.
Michael Poopy on the last show of the millennium?
Yep.
It is the last show.
The show is cooking now.
Have you noticed that?
There's a little smoke coming out of that box over there.
Oh, yeah.
Nice.
Eggs Benedict.
Smells kind of like Eggs Benedict.
Or you could think, some could say it smells like burning rubber.
Yeah.
to it in a state of hyperthermal activity.
But you know, friends, the real subgeniuses are the ones who literally, totally gave their
brains over to Bob.
Now, that turns some people off.
That's why we're not, maybe, we're a little faster growing than, say, the Scientologists
or the Mormons.
But we're not there yet.
And I think it's a lot of times because people, they see these subgeniuses who are really
into it, and they're acting just wrong.
You know, there's just something.
But friends, you can't imagine how much those are the ones who truly, truly believe in Bob.
They have given their brains to Bob for good, forever.
Forever.
They're never going to get those brain cells back, and they don't want them.
Those weren't the brain cells they needed in the first place.
But friends, you, too, can give your brain to Bob just temporarily.
You don't have to do it for all time.
Just say, for tonight, you know.
Once you've been slack, you'll never go back, my friends.
If you could be slack for one Saturday night, you'd never want to be pink again.
And, you know, as, now, some people also question the church.
And, you know, I'm not going to give you a track record of our track record regarding
ends of the world happening every July 5th or not.
And, as I've said before, are we going to let the Jehovah's Witnesses out-cook us?
Hell no.
But, you know, Bob has held these, they're drills.
They're sort of culling drills that we hold every year to weed out the faithless from
those who have faith.
And, friends, here in the Church of the Subgenius, we have no faith!
We don't use faith instead.
We use magic.
But it's a special kind of magic.
The Bob's keys to magic begin, his first key to magic is, get off your ass.
And his final key of magic is wash your ass.
And I think I'll let you worry about the in-between stuff.
We can't, you know, give away all our secrets for free.
But, you know, depending on magic is kind of tricky.
Because, you know, we're not going to be able to do it.
But, you know, in a way, what you're saying is you're feeling lucky.
You know?
So I'm going to go ahead and invest that money that I borrowed from my friend, because I'm
feeling lucky.
Friends, when you feel lucky, you taunt the subgenius demon, which is called Nihigi.
You taunt him.
It's as if you're saying, oh, Nihigi, you are ineffective.
You can't hurt me.
I feel lucky.
No, no, no.
You have to get off your ass every now and then, friends.
I've been constantly and I hope dispassionately considering this very problem.
I have come to the unalterable conclusion that man is unfit as yet to receive such knowledge,
such almost limitless power.
An invisible being that cannot be disintegrated by atomic fission.
That is our God.
That is a scientific impossibility.
There's your answer.
Only for you small minded monkey man.
It must have been renewing its molecular structure from one microsecond to the next.
Trapped in the middle of the universe.
Trapped in your cage of only three dimensions.
Take it down now.
Take it down.
We're scoping this entire life for you.
Now listen to him.
Maybe if we reasoned with him.
A meddling idiot.
As always, Abe's brain could contain the secrets of the Krell.
Reason.
As if reason would be the key.
They could hardly have understood what power was destroying them.
Reason could turn as quickly as a watch into the hand of death.
You have got to reason.
I've got to reason.
You could hardly have understood what power destroyed them.
You know, I just don't think that's the right word.
You're just a fool.
You think I've ever given me a chance to be me.
Nothing but smoke and ashes man.
From miles and miles we found a stream and well like it was all pink.
Yeah and it was slimy but we drank and where it moved we cupped our hands and we took as
much water as we could in because our gills were already expanding and the mutations were
starting to happen.
We knew it wasn't going to be easy but we tried to have fun along the way.
Any way we could.
Our sensations were expanded.
Not much more.
The pain was more and so was the joy and the pleasure so we advanced ourselves along those
lines.
He who thought unpleasurable thought was unfit.
He who thought painful thought was unfit.
He who was painful was unfit and was excluded from us or else we would perish from our own
suffering.
Sure ma.
Sure pa.
So man, what are you people talking about?
What.
Are.
You.
Somebody restrain on you.
What.
Are.
You.
Eat one quart of milk in a heavy utensil.
What are you, dude?
Now we're on the show in milk for fewer calories.
Yeah, man.
Is the beat doing something for you?
I'm swinging.
Hanging mighty low.
Hanging low.
Did you never think.
So, get out of the devil's seat.
There are insecurities.
How you doing there boy?
I think you're a killer.
I'm a killer.
Sure, yeah, yeah. Okay.
Well, things have taken a much worse turn.
Look at them all.
Get up all of you.
Spin their heads around like that, they'll pop out.
We use a big old wad right on top there.
More recently, what if you had a shot at killing Hitler?
You see, it's kind of a slippery slope.
Justifying premeditated murder.
Oh, yeah, sure.
That's easy for you to say.
You keep saying that.
Saying you can justify murder.
I don't believe so.
I don't believe you can...
Well, okay, I take that back.
I do believe you can justify murder.
So now you have to kill me.
Under certain conditions, yes.
You have to kill me.
It's part of Cult Stock, 2001.
Eli, Eli.
Eli, like a dog, like a scurvy dog you are.
I want you to let me kill someone that's...
Kill her.
Sure, yeah.
Kill them.
Kill them all.
That's what they say.
You killed my baby!
Dear Barbara.
It's a hard, hard work to blend so many different spices in your head.
Y'all, come back down on the flip side.
Because it's gonna be a groovy time here.
And...
Oh!
You know I can't refuse.
Build it.
And you.
I believe as I did before.
In theory, it should work.
Always theories.
Jigsaw puzzles on paper.
Aren't you fellows ever positive?
I am golden slippers.
Only about doomsday.
Touch me, levitate now.
Yes.
I have the power in my feet.
Look at my carpical toenails.
Look at the fungus, it shines.
I...
Now I look down at you.
See?
And I can move around the room with it.
You think being an insect is not...
Of doomsday, we are all too sure.
Damn that man.
Spend too much time with the stars.
You don't know anything about living.
The law of the jungle.
The human jungle.
I do.
I've spent my life at it.
It's coming.
You don't know what your civilized people will do...
to cling to life.
I do because I know I'd cling if I had to kill to do it.
And so will you.
We're the lucky ones.
The handful with the chance to reach another world.
And we'll use those guns.
You'll use them, Doctor.
Yes.
To keep your only chance to stay alive.
Yes, I'll use them.
I...
There it is.
If I can figure out how to make this thing work.
My friends...
It's backwards, sir.
It is imperative that you listen closely.
I was in the cave painting these pictures the way we saw them on the viewer screen.
Why were you doing that, Doctor?
Well, I was trying to get my hands on the picture.
So in case you did wipe out the human race, there'd be some record of how it happened.
Go on, go on.
I need guidance, great one.
For the first time in my life, I am not sure.
You sound like a human, not a Roman.
Can you not verify a fact?
I'm bossy.
You're so bossy, you ought to be milked before you come home at night.
Calculate your chances.
Negative.
Is there a chance that you'll be a human?
I never had a choice between a painless surrender death and the horror of resistance death.
Show yourselves.
I think you're just a big bully picking on people smaller than you are.
Now, I will kill you.
Raise, raise, raise.
Because I love you.
And you've got to let me eat your brain.
Frankie, have you ever, uh, had unnatural urges?
Alright, I'm not gonna say that.
I just wanna say that I've had a couple.
Do you know the way to the Hershey Highway? Do you know the way?
Oh, you make me sick!
So how'd it feel, girl?
Felt good. Felt real good. Yeah.
Had this big particle on my toe and I couldn't get it off, so I had to take a pair of pliers and I grabbed that sucker and I wrenched him over.
What?
Yeah, I grabbed them pliers and took them pliers and...
Hello, Ivan. How you doing?
Oh, it's you guys!
Yeah, it's the show, man.
Do you have any pliers?
Yeah, I got some pliers for you, son. Right here.
I got your pliers swinging.
Must be 5 a.m. there or something.
And we're on the last show. This is the last, last show.
What'd you do? Did you get up early?
Oh, you wish it was the last show.
It's the last show.
We don't have any more to do.
It's the last show of the millennia.
This is the last show.
It's the last show of the old age.
But now the new old age begins.
The new age.
Ever more infirm.
And Alzheimer's ridden.
We hobble on into the future.
Yeah, you hob. Hobnob.
For this time, young baby 2001 is actually still just old man 2000.
What's that dripping sound I hear?
Is that you dripping?
The morphine drip.
Are you dripping wet?
No, I think that's just the morphine drip.
What time is it there in the middle, mid-America?
Oh, here in the great salt mines underneath Lake Erie, 6.57 a.m.
Wow.
So you don't actually feel the cold and horrible temperatures that other people are stuck with there?
No, no, not, not.
Well, I would if I let down my concentration.
I would let down my concentration for a little while.
Yeah, I know.
Like the Yeti, I may wander naked through the snow.
Yeah, I saw those pictures on the website.
Melting the snow before it hits you because of the radiant heat you generate with your mighty brain.
Well, it's not my brain, actually.
It's the mighty bowl of chili that I eat every hour to fuel them.
The huge cans.
The one-ton cans being emptied at one end and the thoughts coming out the other.
Yeah.
I was one of the benefactors of the leftover chili.
I actually, well, Dr. Drummond, please, you are my mentor in this arena of pyroflatulation.
Yes, it's an art form that some of us claim mastery of.
Some of us are still learning to be ascended masters and some are just...
I have often been burnt by the heat of your passing.
You quit your sassum.
Boy, I've pulled you out of your mother and I'll shove you right back in.
Now, you get in that truck and you skedaddle.
Ha, ha, I like knockers.
Do you ever fantasize about being killed?
One question, Frank.
This guy's screaming in here.
You sure he's a dead cadaver?
Why don't you open the door and find out?
No, it's all right, Frank.
I'll take your word for that.
They report they can't use the flamethrowers.
Can't get close because of the acid slime.
All right.
We'll take other measures.
You're going to love this place.
It's a dynamite camping spot and it's got a pond to piss in.
Sniffing butts is probably more the articulate science.
Not just X-Day, but the combination of X-Day, all of them subgeniuses, and Brushwood itself.
The weird energies of that strange campground in Sherman, New York.
That sounds like an immune system deficiency.
It changes people.
Yeah.
It does change people.
It's an immune system thing.
I've witnessed that firsthand.
Well, there's also transitional drifting.
People do things out there that they would never imagine doing.
Have you noticed trans-dimensional drift?
Back in the world.
Have you noticed a trans-dimensional drift in some of the subjects or unsubjected ones who are out there?
Perhaps floundering in the field, kissing a rocket butt or something.
The next thing you know, they've disappeared off the face of the groin.
I believe that there is a reason for that.
An explainable reason for that transference.
Explain it if you can, but I dare you not.
I believe that you will not.
Well, what I have to say would sound so ridiculous and so ludicrous to your ears.
Well, as if what we've been saying so far was so erudite and clear.
It would almost guarantee disbelief, so I might as well go ahead and say it.
Oh, so I believe everything you guys have been saying about Mojo's huge testicles and the rockets coming out of his head and everything so far like that.
Well, many of us feel like we're on the wrong planet, sort of.
Ha, ha, ha.
You know, right.
Susie the Flusie said right hemisphere, wrong planet.
Ha, ha, ha.
I see.
It's like a trans-dimensional gate or like a Zardo's plate.
Maybe we really are on the wrong planet.
Now, you know that it is possible to move planets out of there.
Or to orbit to, in fact, even switch planets.
And many of us have suspected, of course, that the planet we now call Mars, the dead, empty, poison-atmosphered planet,
is actually what was once Earth, the native planet of some of us in our yeti days.
But it was polluted by the humans.
It was made red with the blood of many, many creatures.
And what we used to call Mars had brought it to this part of the solar system.
Earth.
One second.
And we now live on what was Mars, only it is now called Earth by the conspiracy.
And in fact, to make it, they are trying to make it more like Mars.
Covered with concrete or rock, whatever, concrete for now.
Painting the buildings red.
Poisoning the atmosphere.
Painting people's eyelids red as if they hadn't slept for days.
Exposing them to radiation.
Making them take nitrogen and subcutaneously anally.
Recreating Mars here on Earth.
And yet Mars.
They're secretly planning to turn it back into the...
Into their special conspiracy hideout.
But it is our planet.
Earth.
Back to Mars.
So few astronaut Americans have been willing to come out and admit that, yes, Fred, sure,
many of you at this point are going, yeah, maybe Sang's right.
This all makes sense.
It's no wonder I felt so weird in high school.
No matter I'm such a mutant.
But what if, friends, of course you're thinking, but I'm sure they did this switch thousands of years ago.
No!
It happened in 1953!
In 1953, Earth and Mars changed places by the strange forces wielded by the conspiracy and their alien allies.
And to this day, the mystery of it is, how did they do it without anyone noticing?
It is very hard.
But if you look at the...
If you look at the comic books, if you look in the bottom of the wine bottle after it's been finished off,
you will see that what I say is true.
It did happen in 1953.
Earth was switched with Mars.
Okay, now let's elaborate on the substance of it, you MSNBC-ish guy.
You've made the point that Clinton was a dirty liar or something, whatever point you wanted to make.
I'm going to miss Bill.
Now let's have the proof.
I don't care what you guys say.
It's hard to change planets midstream.
Imagine Chaz over there trying to catch an RTA.
That is why it's...
I don't expect you to believe me.
And yet what I said was the one serious thing I've ever said on this show.
It doesn't matter.
You can burn it all down.
Burn the whole planet down because we're going to get off soon.
Let them burn it down.
See, Chaz, that's where we differ.
But see, they don't want to let us off.
They're trying to keep us here.
They're going to get off soon.
Chaz is like an Earth let's get off guy.
And I'm like one of those Earth first guys.
I think we should turn this into a terrestrial paradise.
Yeah, I believe in that.
Earth first.
Then we can...
Then, you know, torch the other planets later.
But see, they've already done that.
Attila the Chaz.
We're just now getting the idea.
The conspiracy's been doing this for billions of years.
This is the last planet of the solar system.
They've already done it to all the other planets.
Well, I can't wait to turn it to cinders either then.
Man, Neptune was great before the conspiracy started building walls on it.
We swam on Neptune.
We were like...
It was the air and it was the water.
It was like this nitrogenous stuff.
And it was like a jelly.
And Saturn didn't used to have any atmosphere at all hardly.
Until we blew that up too.
That's really a small planet actually.
Those rings were originally a beautiful moon sculpted in the shape of Bob's head.
It was our home.
The conspiracy destroyed it.
We lived in that pipe and we blew it up.
We're killing everyone.
We lived in the pipe.
We are the children of the pipe of the ring of the pipe of the ring of Saturn.
No, that was pretty good.
We are the children of the pipe of the ring of the pipe of the ring.
Of the children of Saturn.
Ring.
Saturn.
Whatever you guys are on.
I don't want any of it.
Talk about B-Wolf and all them guys.
Jeez, man.
Yes, this is the last show, folks.
The last show.
Oh, thank God.
The very last show.
It's about damn time.
Can you believe it's lasted this long and they hadn't killed us yet?
Really?
That's the thing that amazes me.
I can't believe it.
So now that...
Uh...
Staying in...
The final line of call to Burning Man is...
Is Doug going to go to...
Well, I'm going to go to...
Yeah, to...
To Jane-er stock in New York.
Hey, get out of the way, man!
Hey, shut the door.
I think we just...
There was a terrible controversy over whether the giant subgenius party of 4X Day should
be held after the world ends or before.
Yeah, I like those questions.
Well, what do you think?
What's the vote count?
I vote yes.
Well, there was a vote and the principal...
...chose to party aboard the escape vessels.
After July...
In other words, the celebration of X Day will begin at 7 a.m. July 5th, which is Thursday
this year.
Sure.
And we'll...
I vote maybe.
And it will never end.
This will be the X Day that never ends.
Bring your moon pants.
Breach them not.
Bring your...
And you enter the vacuum.
Ah, yes.
Wow, free watermelon.
Bring your moon pants.
And your, um...
Your moon rocks.
Bring your moon rocks, too.
...mellor...
Mellor...
Bring your moon rocks, too.
...mitten devices.
Bring your...
Bring...
Yeah, your...
Your gland shoes.
Bring your mattress.
Prairie squid.
Bring your mattress back with you.
Go to camp, man.
I'm bringing mine, hm?
Bring your old mattress back there.
Take her on down.
Back in that back room, you know, where all that stuff is.
Back where we made the real plan.
Hehehe.
I'm going to go.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Are you talking about the place where Tendively convenience waxed Sterno in the head?
That back room?
Yeah.
That was the corner room of the...
That was in Chicago.
...back of the head.
That was a long time ago, folks.
Well, you'd have hit him in the head, too.
Yeah.
You could have.
You're just jealous because Tendively got there first.
Here's Tendively dancing around naked in a tunnel, whipping a dead cow.
Everybody wanted some Sterno in the head back in those days.
I really wanted some Tendively head.
Now these people are old, crotchety men.
Sad, old bags of pissed off-ness.
Sad, old bags of...
Hey, I remember when...
...self genius owned the world.
I remember when they was the preeminent cult in America and now the Mormons have completely
taken over.
I've got everything in sync, and I don't mean in synchronization.
I take a load now and then
Some people flush it down the toilet
I depend on the sink
The sink
And then the plumber happened to arrive
And they took that little electrical snake
And they plunged it down the sink
And you wouldn't believe what they came up with
In the sink
So anymore I don't do that procedure
Cause it stopped up the drain
It stopped up the sink
So if you've got a master bed
Don't use the sink
In the sink
Cause you're just giving a dog
To a plumber
Don't top up the sink with cum
Don't shoot your wand
Down the sink
It's not the kind of thing
That works against the sink
Don't sink your wand
Down the sink
In the day it does
When heaven and earth
Belong to one
You can look back in the sink
I hate these memories
I hate the sink
Everything goes back to the sink
How do you make babies
How do you stop births
Short of abortion
How do you do it with a sink
How do you stop babies
Without abortion
How do you do it
Well I say you do it with a sink
You push them little spermies
Down the sink
Oh yeah darlin'
Ooh, I've got this
That's done
Down, the sink
Down the sink
Like
Ale
Hay
to the Alt Binaries Slack News Group.
And friends, we've also been listening
to the last show of the millennium
on KPFA in Berkeley.
The subgenius, non-subgenius,
more than an hour, less than a show, show
with puzzling evidence.
And normally has Dr. Howell,
but in this case, Dr. Philodrummon,
the overman, the true, one true,
the only overman yet so far
that we have in the church.
The only proof we have that Bob is even true.
Oh, no.
Oh, man, no wonder.
Well, anyway, that show was all mottered up
with the ESO Swamp Radio show
at WCSB Cleveland
with Professor Chaz Smith
and lonesome cowboy,
Dave, and yours truly,
and maybe Princess We Are Doe
got in there somewhere.
And there's some media barrage clips,
monster movie stuff
by our friend New Monet,
the mysterious New Monet.
The music in the background
is Einstein's Secret Orchestra
with Ron Slade
recorded just a couple of weeks ago
at Winterstar Symposium
sponsored by Ace.
This show is a great way to get to know us.
We're going to be back next week
with a song called
Trippy Beard P-Boy Muff.
Oh, speaking of hippie weird stuff,
I've got the schedule for Winterstar
where we have to work, boys.
What do we, do we have to slosh the kitchen
or do we have to remove the urinals and stuff?
You have to do a consciousness expanding jam
at the end of the evening.
I thought I was the P-Boy.
Get this, man.
Halim El-Dab.
Halim El-Dab?
Notice that name, Halim El-Dab,
who is a pharaoh,
an actual pharaoh?
I am proud to call an acquaintance,
perhaps even a friend.
Certainly, I admire his great drumming
I know you used to hang with Ramsey's
and Tootin' Common
and all the rest of the guys
that are seriously mortified.
He will be drumming across the great rivers
while you can stretch yourself out of pain
Oh, string theory again.
with Anomi, that abnormal girl.
You can turn yourself into a G-flat
or an A-shark.
And Halim El-Dab,
will guide you in slack.
And at 3 o'clock, actually at 3.30,
then I give a scientific talk
about the scientific basis of slack.
Okay, now who's the guy?
My new neighbor, Nathar,
will be doing the electronic meditation devices.
Do you have a new home or domicile?
Something is happening.
You don't have to say where it is.
I'm just saying.
We're tunneling.
Let me put it that way.
The tunnel is progressing.
You're taking the bags of dirt out
and you're making sure that nobody knows where you're going?
Yes.
We have to hide the bags of dirt.
Imagine.
That ain't easy.
Oh, and then Pope Bob Wilson
I noticed your toenails were filled.
after it doesn't,
will tell it,
give everyone a new map of their consciousness.
Pope Dozier?
Pope Bob,
Robert Anton Wilson
is his fancy author name.
We'll connect our consciousness
in the key of a flat tire.
But we subgeniuses know him
as just a regular feller pope.
Who appears and disappears
magnanimously without any reason.
Sometimes in a bar or a kitchen,
escutcheoning it with his...
It's the way.
It's the way?
It's the way it's been done for billions of years.
So what was life like to an early dungeon of the pipe of the ring of the pipe of the ring of the moon of the Saturn?
It was like working at Playboy.
It was like as if you worked at Playboy.
I was gonna say it's like working at Kmart.
The endless droning.
No, it's like working.
The blue shirts.
The red shirts.
It's as if you were the photographer's assistant at Playboy.
We are happy to help you.
No, the makeup.
The makeup person's assistant.
Can I help you?
At Playboy.
And what else is happening then?
The spritzerer.
I'm the spritzerer.
The one who comes and spritzes the babe.
What else is happening then?
You're supposed to look sweaty.
Um, oh and then, uh, I, that's when my page ran out.
But what they didn't dare print on,
my printer refused to print was something about a space jam
in the middle of the frozen night in those cabins.
Covered with icicles.
Did it say anything about Space Trance 1 Workshop Meditation Trance Drone?
It may have.
I think I'm on five.
I'm on right across from.
Look at www.rosencomet.com.
Yeah.
.
. . .
. . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . . .
I
Give up your civil rights from 9 to 5 every day.
You know, and don't even think anything about that.
You clock out from what freedom you pretended to have,
and then you go home and watch TV and go to sleep.
So what is left, friends, except to use every spare second,
every spare stolen minute, working like a crazed lab rat
with a wire up our asses on anything that will give ourselves slack.
Even if that means laying in bed watching TV for hours.
Praise Bob.
But it could also mean energetic monkey wrenching.
And I don't mean monkey wrenching of machines.
The machines are our friends.
You know, the robots, let them serve us.
But the monkey wrenching of men's minds, friends.
Yes, you know, a strong pink back is a terrible thing to waste.
And some of my fellow subgeniuses feel that on July 5th, 19, well, 2001, whatever,
when the aliens finally arrive and the dues-paying subgeniuses
are ruptured up into the escape vessels of the sex goddesses,
on that day, some subgeniuses, the holocaustal group,
feel that we should just simply wipe out every normal human being
who didn't send Bob 30 bucks.
Now others, like such as the evangelicals,
the schism that I got stuck with,
we believe that, you know, why waste them if you can put them to work, you know?
If we can control their drone-like behavior, like is already being done,
like the toy robot stick men they already are,
why don't we do it, you know?
Now, how each individual does this,
that's between you and Bob.
Unlike every other conspiracy and religion,
we're not going to tell you what to do or what to think.
We'll just tell you how to think.
That's the, really, that's the great thing about this church, friends,
because only you pay Bob to tell you what you really think slack is.
No other subgenius will even try to tell you what your slack is.
And the real subgeniuses, they know that,
that if they could telepathically gaze deep into the soul of another subgenius,
all of the other ones would seem utterly incomprehensible and completely insane
at the basis of their very soul.
And they are!
But we know that, and that is the difference.
Praise Bob and hail Connie.
Whoo!
Ugh!
Soon a Star Wars battle will be fought among the planets,
and the headquarters of these spirits will be transferred to the Earth.
Who are these ETs?
Lucifer and his fallen angels,
the devil and his demons.
Who's behind it all?
What this mysterious ET called Satan.
We must have all good, young blood for this kite war.
The evil is free.
May God have mercy on us.
Select a card to order this startling new video for a gift of just $24.95,
plus three dollars shipping in handling and here you have our to the manager of the
cut
this
devils
small
of a
slow
ocean
Download.
Transporter.
Thank you.
Dive into the plasma pool, aren't you?
You're afraid to be destroyed, recreated, aren't you?
You're afraid to dive into the plasma pool, aren't you?
I seem to be stricken by a disease with a purpose, wouldn't you say?
Praise Bob.
Good luck.
The Dobsian gene pool has expanded.
Incrementally.
Have you ever heard of insect politics?
Those are the best.
Insects.
We don't have politics.
No, not bad.
But insects are sex.
They're very brutal.
Yeah.
No compassion.
No compromise.
No feeling.
We can't trust the insect.
I'd like to become
the first insect
politician
you see, I'd like to.
And don't we have one?
Isn't George W.
I'm afraid, John.
W.
I don't know what you're trying to say.
I like what you're saying.
I'm saying, I'm an insect.
Yes.
I'm saying I'm an insect.
Who dreamt he was a man.
Yes.
And loved it.
Loved it.
But now the dream is over.
Now the dream is over.
I know now.
The insect is awake.
We're all insects who dreamt we were men.
But now the dream is over.
They're saying I'm an insect.
At the board of unemployment, they're saying I'm an insect.
At the job I'd like to get, they're saying I'm an insect.
My church and in my home, they're calling me an insect.
And your insect has arrived.
You can just step right on it here.
As you're off, you'll fly again.
I think I...
Uh-oh.
Call me an insect, man. I'm sick.
Death of a fly.
By the way, Ivan, have you ever listened to this show on KPFA.org?
I just did.
I listened to the whole first half of it just this morning, but...
It was your show.
It was the same damn show.
CD that I just sent to you
only if it sounded all watery.
That's right, because we were upstairs conferring.
Yeah, we had to be upstairs conferring
to get my drift.
If you catch my
mean in there.
Let me do some more show here.
We had this Norton show.
Oh, man, this is a great show.
All right.
I think this show's been stepped on.
See, that's our version of Popus Lilith
doing her, you know,
hey, is that a frop?
I thought that was
hilarious, actually.
And you know what's funny?
I recognize it right away as Popus Lilith.
It was Popus Lilith pretending to be a guy.
Did you know that in his lifetime,
I'm going to give you a little fact
here, Reverend Stans,
that in his lifetime, the average person
will have eaten, I know this assumes
that they're not a vegan
or a vegetarian,
but they will have eaten 14 cattle,
12 sheep,
2 calves, 23 hogs,
35 turkeys,
770 pounds of fish,
and 880 chickens.
I heard it was thousands of chickens.
Well, yeah, it could be thousands by now.
I mean, how does that help us with our last short of the lalunium?
Less calves and more chickens by now.
I don't eat as much veal as I used to.
Only 14 cattle, but they're big cattle.
They're like ox.
I don't even want to think about what they do to calves.
Calves.
Oh, they torture them mercilessly
before they eat.
Before they kill them and feed them to us.
They make us eat them.
But that's okay because it's people doing it.
It's not other calves.
Yeah, it's okay.
It would be brutality if it was another cow doing it.
My God, that would be unthinkable.
That would be.
I couldn't think about that.
As long as I know that's not happening.
By the way, folks, if you're watching on Channel X,
you can see Ivan saying eating psychopops.
I've heard that do that.
They forced the animal's parents
to do it in other foreign countries.
Boy, it's going to be an exciting,
subgenius show.
The one and two's gone.
In some foreign countries,
they force tigers to eat antelopes.
They force lions to eat zebras.
Did you know that...
That's how cruel people are to animals.
In this country,
they force cats to eat songbirds.
We raise house cats
so that they can go out and kill the songbirds.
And that's why we have so many bugs.
Good night, Ford.
Four hundred million girls
were interviewed
after why they had
their gentleman, Beebees.
They said,
not just the words,
but Beebees.
I don't believe I'm crying, Steven.
No.
I will when they make me
feel conscious, though,
won't they?
You figure that out if you want to.
They instigate wars,
terrorism,
assassinations,
murders,
rapes,
and every other evil act
committed globally.
The Soviets,
You don't know what Jim Jones is all about. You can't even follow him.
These are not just the words, the beats.
The fertility rights of the jungles are the same beats
incorporated in this modern rock.
We haven't gotten next to him, but I've got all kinds of things in store.
Who and what are these ETs?
Who created them and why?
Can their existence be proven?
Sex on the street.
You who are stupid piss ants and reptiles and lower than the primates,
you can make a hoopy if you want.
Sex on the street.
So you can make your hoopy while I do.
Do you feel blind? Are you mad?
Do you feel like moose about to run planet?
That's where the music comes up and everybody gets really, really, really scared.
What's the matter? Haven't you ever seen this?
Man, this has been a lot of fun.
It's been a lot of fun because we've had the...
We've had everybody here tonight.
We've had the only three important people in the Church of the Subgenius.
Yeah, that's true.
Phineas, me, and Wellman.
Wait, let me look at my card here.
Hey, what? What?
Yes, you've been listening to the last show of the Millennium.
Only the three most important, but not the greatest of all subgenii.
Where was Bob in all this time?
Well, Bob's just a made-up...
Bob's a made-up guy. Don't worry about that.
And where then was Bob in this time, son?
I'll tell you about him.
Bob's in your mother.
Where are you thinking of Bob?
If I were one of the subgeniuses, I'd claim that I made up Bob, right?
About now.
Did you even have the common decency to pull your knife out of Bob's belly that day, eh?
I'll tell you where he is, Stans. He's at your mama's house.
Eating the black stuff inside your skeleton.
I was going to ask, sir, what about the black stuff?
Hey, cut your belly open and I'll show you the black stuff.
I'm going to show you the black stuff.
I'd like to rub your little round belly with the black stuff inside your mother's skeleton.
Is Sal there?
The rabbit suffer.
Sal?
I'm going to go to the rabbit stew.
Sal who?
Sal Army?
That's funny.
Sal Army!
It's just Sal Ro-
This show has been very good.
Thank you, thank you.
This show has been good for me, too.
This show has brought me to a new level.
delivered me it's brought me forward this show has been arthritic for me too it's been it's been
a frightening experience it's been a carbuncle on the butthole of society but other than that it's
it's been great yeah that and this you know last five minutes of the last show the last five
minutes theoretically second of life last five minutes of the last show this plane the forces
of good are a sworn enemy and i repeat they must be exterminated and i mean lethally little man has
done it to us again he's made a monkey out of the forces of evil is he dead yeah he's messed up as
bad as those two back there suppose that saucer or whatever it was had something to do with this
your guess is good as mine larry one thing sure
specter clay's dead murdered and somebody's responsible
what's the matter
friends if you're in any state of confusion at all now
urine remember you're in state of confusion free information
did you know you're in the state of that sacred p.o box which still exists
in mysterious dallas texas even though there's nobody left there there's just a p.o box
just a town that used to be there but now it's just only a stick in the middle of town with a
box on it and it's the po sacred p.o box because the rest of the city is going mtv tape folks that
you saw on mtv so many years ago there's a picture of the guy that answers that box with his family
one thing that you can see in the foreground a little box a little mailbox the sacred golden box
it's made out of solid gold now it glistens in the distance as people draw closer to dallas
yeah it's got a little puppy on it it's a shimmering yes gilded sky as they approach the
golden p.o box next day's coming that's bob p.o box one eight one four one seven cleveland high
Lights, Ohio 44118.
And also see subgenius.com.
Order now.
Shine the light of whatever.
Not available in any store.
Shine the light.
Sold separately.
Batteries not included.
Some assembly required.
Not stored in souls.
I'd almost forgotten that old saw.
Saw, that clever play on words.
Not stowed in sores either.
So sad not to have it anymore.
But you can get it back.
You can get it back.
With only a self-addressed stamped envelope.
From just what they said.
Post office box 181417.
Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118.
www.subgenius.com
Hey friends.
And amazing.
It's the puzzling evidence.
Einstein Secret Orchestra.
Radio Swamp.
Philo Spew.
And Dave Brain.
We also heard some.
The satanic jamboree clips.
By Jupiter Research.
And the song Wilderness of Bob.
By Chaz Smith.
We heard they're recorded at Winterstar.
And also my rant from Winterstar.
There friends.
Congratulations by the way.
To Einstein Secret Orchestra.
For winning the Free Times Music Award.
Here in Cleveland.
For best instrumental electronic music.
Of course.
And oh and while you're at it friends.
Check out on the web.
www.subgenius.com
And then go to www.pandromeda.com
I did that finally.
And for the promise.
The promise of Mojo World is so great.
It is.
So great.
Grandiose.
So truly grand is the promise.
Yes.
Ah.
It is a.
I will.
And I did.
It pulls and tugs at me.
Like a Pied Piper.
I'm like a rat of Hamlin wanting to follow the promise of Mojo World.
That's www.pandromeda.com.
The Pied Pooper.
Where the.
The Pink Bob rules.
And the Mojo.
The Bizarro Bob.
Me no like slack.
Ugh.
Me Bizarro Bob.
Me hate slack.
Get to work.
This man.
Legume has slack.
If you call him a man.
Take it away.
Has designs on your consciousness.
That was an actual quote wasn't it?
Look into your computer screen.
Don't you see what's happening?
Your mind is being Mojo-ized and you don't even know it.
Stand back Dr. Grineker.
I have to disconnect the wires.
It's okay Dave.
It's a problem.
I've seen Dave.
Don't freak out on it.
Just accept it.
It's the new paradigm.
I have seen Dave get freaked out just looking at an ordinary videotape of computer animation.
Just some real trippy computer animation.
And Dave late at night we exposed him to this stuff and he was going it's getting too.
This is too intense.
They're going to watch us back.
He watched it.
It's all virtual.
Nobody has a real life anymore.
He pulled his head right up to the screen and he said.
I need blue light baby.
I need blue light.
I see you a
Th Dios.
I will follow your steps
I will stay on the way
I will go through the night
And save the night
I will stay on the way
I will go through the night
And save the night