Hello, boys! I'm back!
Knock, knock.
Say hello to my little friend!
I have come here to chew bubblegum and kick ass.
And I'm all out of bubblegum.
Oh, shit.
Ah!
We had a conversation about our teenage daughters earlier.
What kind of creativity will they have?
Kind of being shaped in this biased experience in their formative years.
And so, mentally, in what ways?
This time period, or because we're all kind of, you know, the creativity is pent up a little bit.
Guided by the belief that the arts of humanity is essential to the well-being of diverse,
and democratic society.
Ah-ha-ha-ha!
Ah-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
The subgenius of...
...Slack.
Ah, yes, that's better, huh?
Welcome to...
...the Elko Coffee.
Is this your family?
Ah, I like to go to the lake, and...
...and the north and the east will be introduced.
And people will have a number in their hands, in their forehead.
Someone with a lot of energy.
Okay, your code number once more?
237.
237, and you're calling from Dallas.
Sorry.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
Now you're online.
And without it, you can starve.
Yes, my code number is 237.
This is not a rerun.
It's a...
...something a bit different.
The very careful speaking entity in Cleveland calling itself Sheridan sent 50 minutes of great collage and bulldada,
some of it from our oldest Media Barrage albums,
with some kind of happiness theme.
But some of it hurt my ear bones,
which, like my lumbar vertebrae, are already beat up enough.
And I don't want what happened to me, dear listener, to happen to you,
because then your listening powers might be as terribly weakened as mine.
So, into the holes from which I surgically amputated the dangerous parts of Sheridan's corpus,
I injected foreign matter also from Cleveland, but from long ago,
such as excerpts of Chaz Smith's ESO Swamp Radio show on WCSB Cleveland,
on which lonesome cowboy Dave and I had blabber rights.
But now this.
From Reverend Bleepo Abernethy, great radio producer,
and now a moving picture of the world,
and now the world's greatest actor in Hollywood,
known as Bill Cates.
This is one he did a long time ago in the future.
Has this ever happened to you?
Why, I should have been there, Ted. It was great.
There was free booze, great music, one of the best parties I ever went to.
Where were you that night?
Oh, I just kind of stayed home and watched TV.
I guess I should have gone, huh?
Didn't you feel stupid?
Didn't you wish you could go back to that night, that party?
Well, maybe now there's a way to learn how to do that.
Well, I'm going to do the very thing, introducing Bob's School of Time Control.
At Bob's, you'll learn how to speed time,
slow time,
and make time run backwards.
But most importantly, you'll be learning how to make time work for you.
How, you may ask?
Well, just ask this man here, an actual graduate of Bob's School of Time Control.
One day, my dog ran out in front of a truck. Blango.
My dog was dead. Was I sad till I met Bob.
Bob showed me how I could go back, get the registration number for the car,
do a slip job on the brakes,
and wouldn't you know it, that truck went off into a ditch and burst into flames
just exactly a block before he could hit old Booger.
Ain't that right, fella?
Yes, just imagine the horrible things that could be undone tomorrow
if you had only gone to Bob's School of Time Control today.
Courses start yesterday, but you can catch up.
Just right, Bob's School of Time Control, the universe.
Bob's School of Time Control, Division of Subgenius Industries Unlimited.
What bothers me is that they're marketing a video game now called Prince of Persia,
The Sands of Time, where one of the features they're advertising is time control.
Really?
Wow. That sounds like a libel story.
Well, it took a conspiracy long enough to rip it off, didn't it?
Yeah, well, if your character dies, you can wind time back and...
Cool. And you are the character, of course.
So we're learning how to control time in our own existence just by focusing on a video game.
In the old days, it was very realistic.
It is.
They're giving away our real time control, and they're selling us fake time control in a damn video game.
Wait a minute. Okay, so you can somehow wind time back by doing things or something like that? Is that it?
I think there's like a, you know, some button or control key.
Yeah, gotta find a secret room or something like that.
It's a control key, and then you go, you know, and you're back where you started.
You know, in the old days, that used to be called...
Einstein lied.
He lied.
Start over.
Yeah, well, I mean...
Play again.
I think he can...
It was called play again in the old days.
Well, that's what it's going to be now in the new world.
That's what it's going to be.
People are going to be asking to replay their lives and so forth, and they'll be able to do it because of the implants.
Yeah.
When you get to the end, is there a play again button?
Well, you gotta make sure you have a record apparatus implanted in the back of your skull.
And once you do, at the moment of your leaving of this body, you get a number of previews.
And also, when you get previews from the next things coming up and trailers from what you already did called This Life...
Unfortunately, many people...
Many people forget to punch the erase tab.
Well, some of them are...
They have an erase tab on their brain and they go ahead and blank it all out.
And then overdub it.
There's the next life.
Right.
And then it comatose...
It overdubs right over it.
Yeah.
You've got two lives going on at the same time.
Well, that's...
That's why institutions are filled up with these people in chairs, you know, wrapped to the chair and duct tape.
Well, I think that's what I want to do as far as being a criminal is concerned, is I want to overdub my past existence.
And I would like the police state to come in and overdub me and for my crimes.
That makes sense, doesn't it?
I just want better background.
That's so whimsical.
According to Bob, the problem with time control is that to travel, like, for instance, into the past, you have to...
It's like a slingshot.
You have to go way into the future, stretch it real hard until you're way out in the future, then let go and it'll shoot you.
It'll slingshot you.
Well, see, way, way, you got it.
There's not a quantity that we can quantify.
There's another way to do that.
Way, way.
What's way, way?
Wait, there's another way to do that.
The Silver Surfer proved that.
To go so fast and far forward that you break through the wall of inertia.
Yeah.
And then pop back to the beginning of time or wherever you want to dump off.
Well, after you break through the wall of inertia, you're just in the wall of momentum yourself.
I mean, I hate to sound so realistic, but...
I don't know.
Once inertia flops by...
I'm not a scientist.
...you become part of Mr. Momentum, who's a much harder guy to stop.
He's like one of those weasels.
You can't get a grip on it.
You can't wrap your teeth around it.
You can't smoke it.
You can't wear it to bed.
What do I know?
You can't buy it a little glass of wine or give it a little sleeping pill.
But it'll sure knock you upside the head.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
You know, it's...
Knock your head.
...more than smoking banana.
One cannot see or touch the wind, and yet the wind has great power.
The wind may caress you while you know it not exists.
I mean, you know what I'm saying.
I think I should just drop my drawers and let it run right up me right now.
We're not interfacing with the elements.
That's another illusion.
The Zervins ain't got nothing to do with it.
As long as it's in color, that's all I ask.
Well, it's colored.
It has many different colors, but it's not in color.
We didn't even see in 3D when I was a kid.
It was all flat.
Everything was flat?
Yeah, but as long as it's in color, man, that's virtual enough for me.
Did you ever turn the paper on its side?
Kids don't know that.
They don't remember that.
They think...
Right.
Well, you know, before color TV...
They don't know about the old age.
...there was black and white TV, but before black and white TV, there was only a two-dimensional
world, a flatland world.
Right.
All your grandparents grew up in flatland world.
And to get from point A, you had to get a three-dimensional being to write A on a piece
of paper...
It was only since color TV was invented that the world...
...and put a point there and write B and draw a line.
Yeah, it was only since color TV was invented that the world became three-dimensional.
In fact...
Well, only when we started breeding the people with the two eyes that you could even tell
the difference.
That was a good idea, two instead of one.
And you know, like, just think of like Goliath and some of these guys that had the one poked
out.
Just think if you're in a battle, you could have...
You can't take that crap for granted.
They think it's always been, oh yeah, we've always had two eyes.
Oh, we've been gifted with two eyes.
It's always been stereo.
That Bob or some other character didn't bestow them on us.
Of course he did.
Or else how would they have come into existence, you know?
I remember when you were billed for color.
I remember when you were billed for having an extra eyeball.
Remember that?
What happened to the Cyclopses?
The Cyclopses went the way of Mother West when they just passed into the flying, into
the air and never returned.
People think that's like a myth.
There really was Cyclopses.
The Betamax, the Macintosh.
Yep.
The American Empire.
Yes, the revolution.
Uncle Sam, all those other extinct creatures.
The flat Cyclops revolution.
Freedom.
Happiness.
3D freedom.
Other dying things.
Liberty in 4D.
So to speak.
Oh, screw that.
Let's just come up with some formulaic pop idols and sell them as rebellion.
Why don't we come up with...
I tried, man.
What, the little bobble hedge?
I'm lucky if I can get, you know, five or ten CDs sold at a D-Bible.
I tried, man.
I like the Jesus Christ bobble hedge, the Reverend Ivan Stang bobble hedge.
These are...
Well, then obviously you don't have the right pop icon.
Idol.
Well, no, I guess we should use the pink bob that Dr. Legume designed for Mojo.
Then it would be as rich as Mojo.
No, you still...
You gotta like, waitly that way.
I think Jackson should be martyred and sanctified and consecrated in the blood of the Lamb.
Look what works.
Britney and Christina.
That's what sells.
If we could just find the perfect teat.
The perfect one tit and nipple.
It lasts a week, though.
The perfect tit flavor only lasts one week and then it begins to sag and then there's
a new tit flavor.
Well, but then you got your money and you can...
What you are laundering is the munchkin or the little people flavor of the entire universe.
You're not really copulating with what's great, with what's superb and what's essential and
quintessential.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, you're putting down bubble gum bands, man.
You gotta get sexy in your gorilla...
No, I'm not.
You're a snob.
Are you putting down stupid dribble pop...
No, I'm not.
I'm not snotting.
There's no mucus in my thought.
This is what I am saying is that they should take at least one tithing's worth and give
not only to Bob, but to Bob's birthday.
And to his minions and his denizens as well.
Why give it to a fat or skinny like Michael Jackson?
That waif, that strange waif.
Look at all the money he's accumulated so he could engage in perversions.
We engage in simple perversions.
We don't need that much money, but we need some.
Dave.
His skin doesn't have any color either.
I know, man.
That's some sick-ass shit right there.
His songs are just a little more hummable than yours.
I don't know about that.
Look at how he hums with that weird triangle and all that.
That's a nostril area.
Except for beat me to a pulpit.
That's very...
I wake up with that going on in my head sometimes.
Yeah, that's a happy little ditty, but...
We got decent recordings of the band the other night, by the way.
That's incredible.
Even your band.
How strange.
Yeah, it was weird.
On the c Bravo.
Uh––.
So-
N'y-y電 A-or-b For-a Bit-a-Db
N'yという
eth
hanes
Well, I keep on thinking about you
Sister golden hair, she flies
I feel people together
Don't you listen to what the man says
One of these nights
I'm telling the night
Baby, baby, falling in love
With that light
Like a rhinestone cowboy
Take things over
Sorry things ain't what they used to be
I like love
What you want, you make me want
I like it
Let's do it again
Hello, and we're back
And you're listening to
WWYN
And what's with you now
PM Radio
Brought to you this week
from Mama Slithroat's dungeon, conveniently located below the outhouse in back of Uncle Warthog's farm.
Come on, come all, you'll be flush with joy.
We've just heard Upchuck and the Swallow Charlies with Pancake Vomit from their new album, Told Ya So.
Before that, we had Big Wheel and the Hubcats with Don't Tread on Me.
We started out that set with a record that skipped, so I don't give up.
Oh, it was.
Now this business news from Shauna Zurbuck, filling in for Grinnell the Pumper, who is currently folding chairs in a church basement.
The report from Wall Street is people are doing stuff.
However, Wall Street is closed this morning,
as they didn't feel like doing anything.
They're going to make Yellum today.
An investigation into the business practices of funeral parlors was dropped today,
as Slabum Inc. presented their latest irrefutably true ad slogan.
It's why we go to funerals, to make sure they're dead.
Back to you, Bunny.
That's Raphael.
And that's Shauna.
One Easter Egg Party.
Haunt.
And you'll never live it down, folks.
Support for this Hour of WWYN is brought to you by Yoder Table Legs Cow Powdered Amish Neon Conglomerates.
It's utterly ridiculous.
And be sure to tune in tonight for another episode of the Yoder Table Legs Cow Powdered Amish Neon Conglomerates.
We're going to have a new interview and live performance with hairy skin in the shavers.
Lead singer Cleaver Hornschnitz is back on the bottle, folks.
So we should expect better than that God-fearing crap that tanked them in the charts.
Sobriety sucks, people.
So don't try it if you're not prepared for failure.
And abject poverty.
Well, that's it for now, folks.
I'm Raphael Schlickerhutz, waiting for the checks to bounce and checks to bounce and checks to bounce and checks to bounce and this last weather forecast from that crazy manicure lady at the tattoo shop.
Stay inside, people.
Just stay inside.
Friends, get your ears vaccinated every week that you listen in because otherwise, well, there ain't no telling what happens.
Well, the lines are lighting up.
All we have to do is accuse you of not understanding a damn thing.
And then they call it, you know.
I get it.
This is some sort of a joke.
This is some sort of takeoff on religion, isn't it?
Oh, you go ahead and believe that.
As you go down, deeper and deeper into your mire of ignorance, ignorance and foolishness.
I call the plane got off in Spain, pulled it out and did the same damn thing.
I claim all these garbage dumps.
And that moment.
That's.
I'm going to be slowing down of time.
That is what savoring is all about.
And that is sort of the antithesis of habituation.
Hey, how you do your work is up to you.
What we give you is clear objectives.
And then you figure out how to get your work done.
If you want to be more productive, you know, go buy a Cal Newport book or something like that.
But it's better to die on your feet than to live on your knees.
You have it backwards.
It's better to live on your feet than to die on your knees.
Enjoy life like Bob.
Just enough faith for you to believe on your own what is real and what isn't.
It feels like playing a game.
Where somebody cheated, but there's nobody else there.
And you're not even playing.
I came to the realization that I had every symptom of burnout.
Every single one.
And I assure you that's not a good place to be.
There is a massive industry of happiness studies, self-help manuals, helping people to overcome all sorts of unhappinesses.
Trying to help people find meaning in their lives.
Trying to help people make better decisions about their lives.
You know, I feel like there's always people who feel like no people have to be punished.
Because they've messed up.
Right?
This is the rule.
If you can't follow the rule, you have to be punished.
And money is the way we punish people.
So, in this kind of world, I think that we have to be more productive.
In this kind of world, a good life is a balanced and a virtuous life.
Not a single-minded pursuit of income.
This is a joke, but it is a very serious joke.
We are the first non-tax exempt church around.
We're the first industrial church.
We want to be proud to pay our taxes and let people know we're not doing a skate-buy on the cops thing.
We don't want to fool anybody.
Isn't it a fact, really, that you've invented this whole thing?
That you've thought up all these little gimmicks.
And you're taking advantage of a lot of ignorant people by getting money out of them.
People who believe in you and your silly preaching.
See, we're not saying anything that none of these other modern-day, new-age religious cults aren't saying.
The only thing is, we're not denying it that we're in it for the money.
And we're not disputing any of your belief systems, because we believe in just about every one of them anyway.
Sir, we absolutely believe in everything.
We believe in it wholeheartedly.
Hey, how you do your work is up to you.
What we give you is up to you.
We give you as clear objectives.
It was by far the biggest private employer in the region.
And many would say, the best employer, too.
We're going to see a moment of punctuated equilibrium.
Where one day we're all doing email and Slack all day.
Four years later, that's going to be considered incredibly old-fashioned.
Boy, right on the head!
No! No!
That's not the whole story.
And making it all about suffering and oppression, also not the whole story.
Everything is complicated.
Everything has nuances.
So, we should advocate for changes when we can.
But we shouldn't assume we know what those changes should be without listening to people's stories.
When I pulled that bubble wrap out, her eyes opened wide.
A bubble-popping junkie.
She reached out.
And popped one.
And stopped.
Knowing I needed it for packing material.
A week later, I shipped her a box of bubble wrap.
With a note.
Enclosed, you will find two sizes of bubble wrap.
One size is for your hands.
While the other is better suited for your feet.
Choose wisely.
As you must top them all.
The next day, she had to travel out of state for a business trip.
Two days later, while she was gone, burglars broke into her house.
Upon entering the front door, they were immediately startled.
She had laid the thin bubble wrap underneath the welcome mat.
Hearing pops.
They froze in their tracks.
They thought they were being shot at.
It was quiet.
There was no alarm sounding.
No people rushed to confront them.
It could be a home alone movie moment.
They smiled.
Shrugged.
And continued stomping on the welcome mat.
Gotta pop them all.
By the time the police arrived.
Due to the silent alarm.
The cops thought they were being shot at.
They riddled the place with bullets.
Kicked in the door.
Walked on it as they entered.
Popping even more bubbles.
And began firing into the house.
Anything that wobbles after a bullet grazes it is a target.
All personal collections, photos, letters, bills, and entire worth of the house are dispatched with deadly force.
After demolition and rebuilding of a new house.
Including a room special for the police.
The house was naturally designated to be filled with assorted types of bubble wrap.
She was heard to say.
You just don't know your limitations.
You just had to pop them all.
Didn't you?
And then.
The poorly built roof caved in on her.
și
Și
ì
Gratitude, the dark side of gratitude is that it could lead to complacency, to be like,
oh, everything's wonderful.
And they are deeply happy.
They radiate happiness.
They're surprised.
Why?
Because they're grateful.
So it is not happiness that makes us grateful.
It's gratefulness that makes us happy.
If you think it's happiness that makes you grateful, think again.
It's gratefulness that makes you happy.
And let's think about each and say, how do we actually want to execute this process in
a way that doesn't require us to keep chucking channels?
That is not really what's going on inside, but I love that there is the radiating.
Okay.
And I said, this is, I knew it was going to work to my competitors.
Still didn't think it was going to work.
They thought, but I could feel, I was close to it.
I could feel the walls were shaking and they were going to fall down.
I can build up enough pressure on it.
Like an earthquake.
It was gonna, it was gonna, it was gonna work.
And we're not disputing any of your belief systems or cause we believe in just about
every one of them anyway, sir.
I can't believe the weird thing.
That people get in.
And there he adds and start teaching.
J R Bob Dobbs.
He says, I don't want everyone to be able to reach me directly.
This is crazy.
The way this is set up, we have to change who can report to who I need to drastically
cut down the number of people who have direct access to me.
And, uh, yeah, it was when you.
Nonprofit freedom from religion foundation works to educate the public on matters
relating to non-theism and to promote the.
Constitutional principle of separation between church and state.
The foundation is the nation's largest association of free thinkers, atheists,
agnostics, and skeptics with over 16,230 members since 1978, the foundation has acted
on countless violations of the separation of state and church and has taken in one many
complaints and lawsuits to state church.
Entanglements.
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh.
Hey, babe.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Shut the fuck up.
Set processes for how decisions are made.
You would come in, you had to prepare a document in advance.
You'd present your case.
You'd present your answer.
He'd give you the feedback.
You'd move out.
He streamlined all of this so that he could focus on one thing at a time, make the best
possible decision or be as useful as possible and then move on to the next.
Hi, boss.
I was just starting to put.
I know.
Uh, is this the right room for an argument?
Is this the right room for an argument?
That's where you see it really add up and really impact people's lives.
And especially the people we want to serve most.
Don't just want your credit cards.
We want your library cards, your voter registration.
Give it all up now.
They don't realize that you have just integrated them in a process that just got rid of seven or eight back and forth email messages.
Repeat process after process after process.
How can I, given what I can control, reduce the amount of back and forth messaging required to get this process done?
And just by pushing a button, I can have a hundred things going at once.
It's just amazing.
And we get all these people calling in going, this is the first time I ever listened to this show.
Oh, what are you guys doing?
What kind of a show is this?
Well, dear friends, this is the show about Bob.
Yes, the first mate of our great ship.
And you know what they mean by first mate.
First mate Bob and the crew of the good ship Grace.
The voices from the harbor called Haven of Rest.
I'm told that everybody likes it.
The story.
They like the story of Bob.
And life is a story.
Because Bob, Bob was a story, you know, but at the same time, he was a reality more hideous than anything you could imagine in your wildest dreams.
Those two wild and crazy guys.
Tonight's the night I should be talking about a flu.
The subject of word assertion.
Association football.
This is a technique out of living, much used in the practice makes perfect off psychoanalysis.
Dr and brother and one that has occupied piper.
The majority rule of my attention squad by the right number 123 for the last five years.
To the memory.
It is quite remarkable way for Charlie how much the Miller Sun is so called while you're out word Association immigrants.
Problems influences the manner from heaven in which we sleep it.
Karen Timorous Beasties.
All Americans speak the famous Explorer and the really well that is surprising partner in.
Crime.
Is that a lot in his wife, the last feeding time.
We may be CD effectively quite unaware of the fact or fiction section of the Watford Public Library that we are even doing.
It is a far, far better thing that I do now.
Then now, then what's going on with Christine Barra, the famous hearty part of the lettuce now praise famous mental homes for loonies like me.
So on the button, my contention causing all my headaches is that unless we take into account of Monte Cristo in our thinking George the fifth, this phenomenon, the other hand, we shall not be able to.
Satisfactor fiction.
Section of the Watford Public Library again early to understand retention when I'm talking to you and stop laughing about human nature.
Man's psychological makeup some story the wife will believe and hence the very meaning of life itself is passed to kick him in the balls on road.
And I saw this in the gratitude project.
I would wake up in a very my default mode of grumpiness and and I would force myself to call people and thank them and it was often very awkward.
How happy are you right now?
How happy were you yesterday?
And there we can see that whether what day of the week it is impacts our happiness levels and people are happier.
No big surprise on the weekend that they are on Monday mornings ready for a religion that considers you equal, not in your soul or in heaven, but in that most sacred of all parts of your body, your wallet.
Us too.
Now, just a minute, lady.
I won't haggle.
I'll double the amount of money.
Well, I don't know what money.
Did you say money?
I remember this stuff.
What do we do?
What do we sign?
Give me those contracts.
Grateful living, that is the thing.
And how can we live gratefully?
By experiencing, by becoming aware that every moment is a given moment, as we say.
It's a gift.
You haven't earned it.
You haven't brought it about in any way.
You have no way of assuring that there will be another moment given to you.
And yet that's the moment.
That's the most valuable thing that can ever be given to us.
This moment with all the opportunity that it contains.
If we didn't have this present moment, we wouldn't have any opportunity to do anything
or experience anything.
And this moment is a gift.
It's a given moment, as we say.
Close your eyes and pretend with me for a few seconds.
Because I am whatever you say.
Oh, God.
That's it.
This is not a rerun.
I eventually convinced her to sit down with producer Latif Nasser and sort of just walk
us through the tape.
Go for it.
You're in control there with the space bar.
All right.
Yeah, I'm on.
God, I hope they don't play this for a long, long time.
He's saying this guy's an outbred.
He was...
J.R. Bob Dobbs.
J.R. Bob Dobbs was on the number one list of frauds and phonies for Time Magazine.
And I didn't know who he was.
Exactly.
And J.R. Bob Dobbs is the creator of the Church of the Subgenius.
This guy, the Reverend Ivan Stang, is one of their...
Disciples.
Yeah.
All right.
You know, it's funny.
I don't think Jesus had a disciple named Dopey.
Oh, but you are so wrong, pink boy.
Jesus did in fact have three disciples named Dopey.
And one named Grumpy.
And one named Sneezy.
Yes, and here comes Grumpy.
And he's well-named, too.
You'd better watch out for Sneezy or everything you know will be blown away.
Sharla, pink boy.
The most frozen and fearful of all the little dwarves, Sharla.
Sharla can hardly keep it together to do his whatever it is he or she is doing.
What is it doing?
It's making a chain of flowers.
No, it's meditating.
Look, it's...
It's not making...
It's making the flowers, but it's meditating on higher purple.
The burning elastic thing.
What is that?
It's thinking of new ways to kill.
Ah, it's one of the spandex used to kill its victims.
Slack takes many forms, my friend.
Killing is one.
Dying is yet another for some who pray to die.
Others pray to kill.
Which are you, my friend?
I'm a ghost.
Why don't you come into the bosom of Bap and of mortality who is actually a better bosom.
Yes, the EEE bosom.
And learn all that you can know about the forbidden sciences and about occult incantations
that can lead you to mastery and power over your own wallet and your own personal guardian
demon.
Hey, I am the One, or the Signet.
Three times.
Take the Alabasta pepperoni and put it nearless.
your nostrils. The third
nostril will expand and the magic
door is not so
magic anymore.
Power and slack, I tell you.
Beyond your wildest imaginings.
Slug, it is called by my
people. We have yearned
for slack for so many years.
The name we use is
slug. It sounds
crude and simple to your people, I am
sure, but one of these
days we will master slug
and climb from the slimy pits
near the river where we have been
banged.
And we shall...
What are we going to do? Look, there is the slack.
Now, climbing up the banks
of the slimy river.
Yes, it's...
Hulking and looming.
Why?
Look at that slack.
Hulking.
It's majestically
looming.
It's the grandest and greatest...
No, no, no, no, stay back!
No, no!
Ah!
I didn't want to know
an evil book.
I don't know after all.
Even a man who is pure at heart
and
thinks he has his slack.
Yet if he eats
those pickles too soon,
we'll have pimples on his back.
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
I think that was on their brains, don't they?
Pimples and milk.
Oh, good old pimples and milk.
And pimples.
Mmm.
Ho, ho, ho!
Hmm!
Quiet, numbskulls!
I'm broadcasting!
Ah!
Do you know?
Oh, where you going to?
I'm going to sell
the X11.
Say what?
Fifty ways to leave your lover.
Oh, yeah!
I'm just a little machine.
And I won't work for nobody but you.
Oh, what a night!
Late December, back in 63.
Shake it up, shake it down.
Who are you?
Me?
You?
I'm a disco major.
Just let your love go home.
Like a mountain stream.
Welcome back to that same old place that you laugh about.
Forget these bars.
Now just put it down.
You'd think that people wouldn't have had enough of silly love songs.
And I want to get over.
Sweetest hangover.
Skyrocketing.
Fly!
And dream delight.
Let's just kiss and say goodbye.
You're the brain in my heart.
I want to be in your heart.
Say it again.
Shake your booty.
Play that fucking music, white boy.
I'm a disco major.
Baby, I'm a disco major.
And you love me hard.
I like salsa.
Can we have a few more shots?
A unbelievable manager of sorts.
And a раст Democrat.
The good awakening of a newτοq rati!
Well, I wonder how .
We're ready...
In Bible's truth основe, damn girl needjミ subscribing been.
Love that Batman's doing good!
A nochar rather than your Duke's stupid.
I watched her.
Born between July.
I'm led by the light.
A new kid in town.
You're soft as an easy chair.
You're a rich girl.
And you're going too far.
But you know it don't matter anyway.
Watch that scene.
It's so easy.
Don't give up on us, baby.
Don't leave me to stay.
We're back.
And it's just too early.
And you've already missed all the good stuff.
You're listening to WWYN.
What's with you now, PM Radio?
We've just heard rat semen in the toilet, dwellers.
With courtesy flush.
Before that, we had Sheeta Gray.
And the forecast 500.
With puddles for poodles.
Ahead of that, we had Cavity Search.
With their sugar sweet.
We started out that last set with Last Box.
Doing their hit Quit Looking from the LP.
Lost and found.
Now this news from Grinelda Pumper.
The president continues to angrily send relief to grief-stricken victims
in between sips of mocha-frosted, halo-infused Kino horse
through a crazy straw.
Visits to the devastated area.
Are scheduled by people that don't wear earbuds walking through the flooded town square.
This is the news from WWYN.
Simple, contagious, and deliberately true.
I'm Grinelda Pumper.
Back to you, Bunny.
That's Raphael to you.
You.
I swear.
One cross-dressing parade in your branded folks.
And now, this message from our sponsors.
Life doesn't let you slow down.
That's why you drink.
Often and earlier.
It's 8 AM.
You'll get up at least a half hour.
Here.
Have one now.
And now, here's an excerpt from tonight's exclusive interview with a well-renowned scientist
that quit.
If you are the leading expert on that particular disease, why?
Is it still a disease?
Yes.
Well, we are currently awaiting funding to research just that aspect of our...
Uh...
What was the question again?
Now, here's Horace Lake with a look at the business news.
With the sex-hemp.
Well, Horace.
Nice big unexpected twist there today.
Is again, five pic anh thui e.
Uh, Planetárias might be wrong, but is today, congratulations,
Con'y rr bueno y Qu Merry Christmas a toda a que?
Thanks, Chester.
this last weather forecast
from that crazy manicure lady
at the tattoo shop.
Stay inside, people.
Just stay inside.
They need to be pushed into shape.
They need to be molded.
These children need to be molded
like Jesus' head.
Remember how they molded
to Jesus' head?
And how they took each little frond
of hair and put it on
and then they had a chin curl.
So when they did the final...
Speaking of Jesus' head,
has anybody seen that porno movie
about Jesus that's going around?
I mean, not to be disrespectful
or anything, but...
Where they're slapping the Lord?
You know, there are some people
who would want to go see a movie
where they beat up Jesus
for different reasons
than others might.
Some might want to identify
with their Lord,
but they're not going to.
I just want to hear him go,
ouch, ouch, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow,
and stuff like that.
Yeah, some people just want to see him
get beat up.
It's the sound.
It's kind of like an audio thing for me.
I want to hear him go,
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
I'm sorry.
I'm not into that.
What?
Hearing him being put up.
I'm not into anybody
getting beaten up, okay?
I'm not into anything.
I mean...
I'm not into anything either.
Well, you look like you're trying.
I'm like out of it, totally.
You are.
Okay?
But you look like you're trying
extremely hard.
That is so nihilistic, man.
Well, nihilism,
this is where we're at now.
This is the lowering of the table
and the connecting of the floor.
We're in the same place.
Everybody...
Nihilism is...
rules the land now.
Well...
You're not going to find
a lot of optimism.
a lot of creative exuberance
going on.
No, man.
Nihilism rules.
No, nihilism rules.
I don't know.
I mean, within the nihilism part,
there's a lot of sick,
sick, sick depraved enthusiasm.
Well, it is a form of enthusiasm.
Enthusiasm for people
for torture.
The elongation of the tongue,
disconnection of the maxillary glands,
mispronunciation in vowels.
Making fun of Jesus,
such as these...
Of course, the subgeniuses,
when that movie came out,
had to come up with
their best one-line review
of Mel Gibson's Passion.
And among the wonderful
one-line reviews we got
was Jesus Christ Reanimator.
I spit on your mouth.
I spit on your empty grave.
Who's afraid of Judas Iscariot?
The Longest Day.
The Great Escape.
Merry Christmas, Mr. Christ.
Rosemary's Messiah.
Last Tango in Bethlehem.
Well, this is one of my favorites.
The Fool on the Hill.
Apocalypse Later.
And what else?
Oh, Mr. Sister had the best ones.
No Weddings and a Funeral.
This is, of course,
Mel Gibson's The Passion.
One-line reviews.
The Unforgiven.
Mr. Iscariot's Holiday.
It's a Bad, Bad, Bad, Bad World.
One of my favorites here.
Lost in Translation.
And The Ghost.
I like The Fool on the Hill
because it reminds me
of the old school joke where...
Oh, My Big Fat Roman Crucifixion.
Lord of the...
The Nails.
The Silencing of the Lamb.
And The Ghost.
And Mrs. Magdalene.
Oh, those don't sound like they required an awful lot of thought, dang.
They absolutely do.
Someone is contemplating...
Stop!
Enough is too much!
Go on and sing her!
About your moon and your June about a swinger!
About a sky of blue or a T for two.
Anything with a swing or two.
And I love you, I love her too.
I love her too.
Sing!
If you don't want to boil your brains in the zombie business corridors of empty pinkness
or grinding poverty.
If you don't want to feel the meat cook off your bones in a nuclear oven that was once
your hometown.
You'd better drop your mental candy bars and step out under the blinding light of the sun
and make witness to what you really are.
So I'm on the fence nervously watching what's going to happen here.
What happens if I push that button?
In fact, we don't really know the secret of fire.
We are relying on the pagans to start those.
Oh!
I'll make powder on them.
Now leave it alone let's come out there.
Lately what's going on here?
Pick up that stuff and get to work.
So help me, this child ass.
Stop!
Come back here you stupid little...
You.
I pay you.
Do not do it.
I won't.
Come on.
Perhaps the impact of the zombie in me.
This man will smooth out the swamp through out the mountain of misery.
I will assist.
I got a lot of dog food!
Ah!
Whoa!
No!
Ah!
Ow!
Woo hoo hoo hoo!
Ha ha ha ha!
Hey la, hey la, come on for a big bag!
She is coming, better cut out on the double!
She wore blue velvet, and everybody calls it the sugar shack!
Woo hoo hoo hoo hoo!
Oh, the city gone wild!
I'm leaving now!
I'll be you!
Let me niggity-gitty-gitty-gutter my way,
Just like that, oh dear, poor little dog!
And there I've said,
I'm leaving!
Not this record!
I'll see that Mrs. Bixby hears this record,
and I hope she'll hire you for her program.
All we gotta do is knock them dead with your song, and we're in.
Just be careful of that record!
Nothing's gonna happen to it!
Well, it might get broke!
Not with me handling it!
Just be careful!
Shut up!
With me handling a record, nothing...
Look what you did, now we're cooked!
No we ain't, look!
Here's a lot of records!
You're getting a half a brain in your skull now, huh?
Now all together!
You know, I may not always be happy,
but I'm sometimes trying to trick my mind
and say, acting as if,
what would a good person do?
What would a compassionate person do?
What would a happy person do?
And trying to do those actions.
Wow!
World Capt час
World!
Ha-ah!
Nae-ce!
Na-eh!
Hu-hin!
U-kun!
If the sole function of language was to communicate,
we'd have one language.
We have more than one language,
therefore we have more than a sole function.
We are...
Why must we always wait for future events?
What would it mean to you
to wait for now
or wait for the
past?
Can you translate
what those whales are saying?
How much tax
do I have to pay for this oil
on my
baleen,
sir?
Can I get
a dentist to clean my
baleens?
Doctor?
But I'll tell you what, friends.
I believe in America.
I believe America could be the greatest
nation that has ever walked this earth.
Yes, America,
or, in scientific terms,
Brontotherium Amerigo,
was the largest land
mammal known in the
anals of history.
Although technically not
a carnivore,
the great America was able to
use its thermonucleotops,
or magic
horns, to rend and
tear the flesh of both its vicious
foes and, during mating
season, members of its own
species. This
rough beast slouching its
way towards Bethlehem,
this Beelzebush,
consumed over
87 times its own
weight daily, and excreted
107 times
that into
its own environment.
Experts theorized that it
had to spend most of its time
afloat in its own
fecal sea in
order to prevent its bones
being pulverized by
its own enormous bulk.
Thus, it
wallowed complacently
in the primeval seas,
never guessing that it soon
faced extinction at the
hands of parasites,
tiny bacteria
bred from the endless
smoldering heaps of its own
refuse.
It is said that nuclear
fusion could occur at
room temperature within
the vast gullet of
this behemoth.
They lived
in small parts of their
balance parts of the
spermeltic cell of
the human sperm.
This is the
of the
carcass animals
at the
in the
vast
Aurium
and prejudice.
Depending upon
the
that the terrorists are bringing into our country.
Yeah, you're going to feel real groovy.
Yeah, man, the terrorists brought some smack into my veins.
They'll do that every time.
It's not my fault the terrorists shot that dope into my needle using my hand.
Those terrorists mind-controlled me into driving drunk.
Those terrorists mind-controlled me into destroying the Freedom of Information Act.
Those terrorists forced me to declare war, terror, and freedom both at the same time.
I'm not responsible.
Freedom for Johnny Appleseed and the boys under the hills.
It's a world of death.
It loves it.
It's death.
They worship death.
Not at strip joints, they have.
No.
You ain't been going out enough, man.
Dollars.
Oh, yeah, man.
I've been going out plenty.
Out of my mind.
Don't you see what they're doing in the strip joints even, man?
It's everywhere.
That girl takes off this, she takes off that.
She's putting something back on in your mind.
Until next week.
Keep your head on tight.
Back to the wind.
And you're sacking the saddle.
Get that tag to Princess Pearl.
Beneath the stains of time.
The feelings.
Disappear.
You are someone else.
I am still right here.