So, you will be greedy.
Now I'll tell you a story about a mouse who was greedy and came to a bad end.
The Strange Doctor Weird
The
Self-Genius Power of Swag
Joe Doakes was just a guy who liked to tinker around his barn.
Some people thought Joe was lazy.
Some even thought he was nuts.
But one day, he had an idea.
Bob?
Exclusive, exclusive, easy, full, comfortable, custom, perfect, new.
Real hair.
I'll just step up.
I thought I was good.
I was mental.
Bro-bo-bo-bo.
Very mental.
A couple of ladies.
Guys.
Very mental.
Mental.
You just get mostly left to you.
You get a phone call and it sounds great.
You're mental.
Forget about that phone call, whether it happens or it doesn't happen.
You better be mental.
Hello.
I'm blessed to be mental all the time.
I'm blessed being mental.
That's the way I see it.
No matter what you say about me, I think I'm mental.
That's what you gotta be, mental.
And if it ain't good enough for the person next to you, that's just unmental.
Very unmental.
Another word for unmental is unmental.
Well, in fair space, we're trying to locate you.
You might dare be drop-ass.
You know?
Mental.
Very mental.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Maybe that's all Bob is.
I'll say hello later.
What?
God!
Okay, so here it is.
Now, this is what happens.
Again and again and again.
And when it does, when they probably don't.
So there you are.
Now, here's the problem.
But hey, sponsored by the Partnership for a Free America.
I'm on my way to heaven.
To heaven.
Yodel my way to heaven, to the Father, Jesus Christ.
You know, I ain't a church-going person, but I swear that's going to be a thing of the past.
Um, let him be all right. I didn't hit him hard.
He should still have one good one left in him.
5, 2, 5, 2, 6, 6, 2, 8, 6, 9, 10.
Oh, may he be loved.
Love?
Beloved, I wish above all things that it's mine.
Flush it down the toilet, because it's mine.
How long will you sit? But it's mine.
Sin, sin, it's mine.
Hatred, hatred.
Mine.
Bitterness, it's mine.
Covetousness, it's mine.
Bible says that it's mine.
This little heart pounding excitedly.
Let's begin.
According to the nursery rhyme, what term refers to a Roman Catholic?
Uh, uh.
Yes, what letter found in 1937?
Uh, Old Golda Meir.
That's right.
Yes.
Ooh, uh.
No.
Ooh, a cat.
Yes.
B-b-b-b-b-b-bob filed for bankruptcy in October 2001.
Ooh, uh, uh, ooh, uh, uh, uh, no.
Yes, uh, you got a bunch wrong.
Ah, I f***ing bought.
Now let's see what you got around here we can tax.
Mmm, let's see.
Hmm.
Oh.
1-11-7-9-3-5-13
My name is Coco, and the reason I do drugs is because I have Down syndrome.
Because having Down syndrome, I can't really tell what's right or wrong.
So I do drugs because I have Down syndrome, and I feel that I need to do drugs.
Spotted by PCP for Free America.
A nice lucky number.
Well, you better hope I don't.
You can't.
Oh, you can.
Right.
This man's drugs.
I know.
Yeah, well, watch it.
Whatever.
So he's trying drugs.
All right.
He's spending more time with his drugs.
Ah, yeah, don't mess with me.
And it works.
Parents give their kids drugs at www.freedrug.org.
Sponsored by a partnership for Free America.
Nub.
This is my last committee hearing as chairman.
And I hate education.
And I hate New York.
I hate Salad.
I hate Southeast Asia and Southwest Asia and Colombia and every place else.
I hate younger and younger people.
And I hate families.
I hate kids in grade schools.
When you kill one, there's 10 or 20 or 50 waiting to take his place.
I hate society.
And I hate people like you.
But I have one question that nobody ever asks.
And that's this question.
What would happen?
I'd like for any of you to answer that.
I'd like to know what your goal is.
There are some things you just do.
Like smoking marijuana.
Because when you get high, it's your mind you're messing with.
So what?
My brother Jeff's gonna drop at the mall tonight.
The good stuff.
Sponsored by the Office of Drug America.
How's it going, dude?
Listen to the wind.
For Aika.
You'll be in the sky.
I'm a machine.
God knows what the machine is supposed to do.
Coming in on a wing and a prayer.
Step on into the chapel.
You're marrying men and women of character and touch.
Flowers and vegetables.
Each and every thing unto its own self.
A gift of love.
I implore you.
Hey, Houston, look up.
Out.
I think we got this.
Hub, hub, hub, hub, hub, hub, hub, hub, hub, hub, hub.
You have no alternative.
You know it.
Everything will be all right.
You are in my hands.
I am here to protect you.
You have nowhere to go.
ou met me at the end of this shit they say.
Don't I know anything from my life about you.
O mE taK.
You were miles away from me from rock cardio.
A qui revolverführίο?
Sorry.
Getting so ahora seguido.
Please come back.
You have nothing to be afraid of.
We are going back.
This is your last chance to return.
You have no where to go.
You cannot survive.
We only want to help you.
This is your last chance.
There can be other creatures in this alien environment.
Hunters.
Hunters are fast and maneuverable.
They eat the floaters.
Both for their organic molecules and for their store of pure hydrogen.
But there can't be many hunters.
Because if they destroy all the floaters, they themselves will perish.
But have we neglected one of the most important items necessary for being effective for the kingdom?
I have come to an amazing and startling conclusion that this here great mass that we stand upon,
heaving and throttling below us like a mighty, mighty poultry,
is the only thing we can do to save the world.
This thing we call America, this great continental division between us,
cannot and must not be ripped further asunder.
I say to us,
Tramp, it is our manifested destiny to touch the stars and have our damned hands burned.
Ha, ha, ha.
What do you think, boys?
Let's do it.
What do we do?
You ask that question now?
The Major no longer asks it.
You know the answer, Major.
Sure.
We'll circle around.
Then we'll crash.
No, no, no, no.
No, it'll be all right, my boy.
My words again.
Have peace.
Peace forever.
Prophecy is an easy thing.
For rarely is the prophet brought to judgment.
Tonight I bring you a false prophecy.
The place of our story is a great rocket speeding away from the moon.
Now, as you notice, some of these ships are made of cardboard.
If you've got the will, if you've got what made America great,
if you've got a heart as big as the sun and an ass as big as the moon,
you make it.
You'll storm on.
You'll go on through those stars like a laser through butter.
Yeah, man.
Yeah.
Come on.
Don't worry about that plastic wraparound.
It's not real plastic.
No, that's a solar shield, man.
That'll protect you.
It's not plastic and those cigarette wrappers on the floor.
That's insulation device for when you're in deep space.
But you've got to believe.
You've got to believe.
You've got to believe, Earthman.
Deep space.
In the slash, slash, slash.
Yes, yes, yes.
I've always known.
Yes, I agree, man.
It really makes sense.
Yeah.
That's how we are, man.
It really makes sense.
Yeah.
Susie?
Forget it.
You better run along out if you want to have your invasion before dark.
It is later that you think.
Think.
I'm sorry I couldn't ask you that.
What?
Wouldn't I?
Could you have 기 cirке.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
My DTFA go DNA.
My powers come on a certain depth, someone may save yourank out.
Been a little
topsy tulsy.
I don't need it, I don't have time to worry.
I don't care who asked that question.
The things that's important to control her mind.
What was the issue?
Invasion?
Drill?
Zero hour?
There are a lot of kooks out there.
There are a lot of people that will use, you know, what the scripture says wrong.
They will interpret it in a way to benefit themselves.
And then I go and I pick the potato.
And then I cut the potato.
And I eat the potato.
And then I make another potato into a potato flute.
And I go up the mountain and I yell to greet the new day.
And then I yell to greet the end of the day.
That is my potato life.
I'm so full of happiness.
Hooked on something new.
Life is such a tricky thing.
Doesn't anybody believe me?
Sometimes I feel like I do that every morning.
Push the wrong button.
Hit the wrong button and disconnect the command module from the lander.
That's a long time.
Right.
And your two buddies were in the lander.
Yeah.
Of course you are.
And I end up having to hose out the mess that used to be my buddies' space.
The only thing to be really good at the most part about going to the moon is that you didn't get a chance to spend as much time around the earth.
I was going to show you.
To me.
To talk.
And your son gets dead.
There's something wrong.
I wanna go home.
That's what they were saying.
They came down that last 15 minutes of flight.
I wanna go home.
Fifteen minutes from landing.
We set sail on this new sea.
Because there is new knowledge to be gained.
And this is my room.
And you're all here.
And I'm not going to leave here ever, ever, ever again.
So what's your theory about the...
I think they slapped the taste right out of Chaz's mouth.
Don't you think it's highly distasteful to talk about that jam?
What got the shuttle?
I think it was Zeus with his mighty blue thunderbolt.
He's got some great thunderbolts this year.
Who's got blue thunderbolts besides Zeus?
I mean, it might be the Zeus Liberation Army,
which I guess is very fundamentalist in their beliefs.
They go back to Deer Zip.
I don't know. I've heard that Ra has green thunderbolts.
No, but you notice the thunderbolts that rolled off good old...
And Bob has great big red straps.
Great big bungee sticks for using on Chinese...
So I heard that NASA knew from the beginning of the flight
that that was going to happen, but didn't tell the astronauts
because they couldn't do anything about it.
Oh, man. What a grim thought.
You know, I had...
And then they made up this whole thing that they're going to do this big,
you know, inquiry and all that to cover that all up.
Oh, actually, I had an even more...
More paranoid whole scenario unfold in my imagination.
In your underwear?
Shortly after I heard the thing.
It was like a movie.
It was just like an action movie.
Well, imagine if those guys were up there,
and they're, of course, they're always having to...
Just having a smoke after some copulonquoitus interruptus.
Just check it out.
I'm listening. I'm listening.
All right.
And...
Okay, the astronauts have been instructed to dump this mysterious cargo into orbit.
One of them does some homework and discovers that it's a doomsday privacy-erasing device
to be put into orbit that could easily be used by the wrong hands
to enslave all humanity under fill-in-the-blank.
The astronauts confer and decide not to activate the evil device.
But one of the astronauts is, of course, secretly with them, the big them,
and he pulls out a death ray or something on the other astronauts
and makes a standoff.
Ah, stand back!
I'm going to bring this baby down!
This one woman astronaut who he had knocked out earlier,
she comes to behind him.
I am waking up now.
And she's just in time to clobber him from behind.
And there's this dramatic fight aboard the shuttle
as it's coming in for a landing.
Wow.
Okay, now the good guys, the good astronauts,
defeat the bad agent astronaut
and have informed mission control,
we're coming in for a landing with big news
that will shake the world and shock everyone.
And that is when they, in Washington,
or Langley, or wherever,
ordered the secret button push
that makes the shuttle explode upon reentry
just as if a heat panel or something
had been damaged during takeoff.
And they even had fake footage of that standing by
just in case of that kind of emergency
and sudden cover-up.
And that makes me a real conspiracy theorist
and made-for-TV movie director.
You think as a movie director
they could come up with better prosthetics than fake feet?
Hey, who's on the line?
You know?
You man, Stank,
you've been working in the meth and phoenix.
I've been working in the amphetamine mines
way too long.
Look at his fingernails.
They're all, like,
Fu-manchu-ed and long
and have weird veins.
I knew how dangerous it was
when I went up there.
We all wanted to get off
and those American,
those brave Americans
got off Earth.
Frozen as frost.
Just a bunch of flaming monkeys
falling from the sky.
I can't see out the window.
They're all glazed open.
Matt, have you ever saw
flaming monkeys falling from the sky before?
Well, of course we've seen it numerous.
We saw it, like, 17 years ago.
Well, sure, back when the amphetamines
were good.
Reverend Strickland.
Strange.
He knows about flaming monkeys
and amphetamines.
This whole thing gives me
a great new idea
to start up a whole new cottage industry.
A new burial technique
for people with way too much money.
Cottage cheese.
Shoot their corpses up into orbit.
Cremation by re-entry.
Oh, I thought you were going to
turn them into a cheese.
If you can't afford it,
a hundred grand will descend
your head up and re-enter your head.
No, you don't even have to.
You just have to pump them up
a little bit.
You know, you don't even have
to get them that high.
And those could just come back down.
You could probably do it
with a military device.
Why not leave them
in the methamphetamine labs?
You just take their monkeys
and you throw their corpses
on the heap
with the rest of the rotting monkeys.
Why not re-amphetimate them?
You know what I mean?
Bring them back to life
with the amphetamines
we've created in our lab.
Admiral Timothy Leary, yeah.
Right.
Admiral Leary was honored
by that type of cremation.
But he couldn't ejaculate
at the wrong moment
and so he was incinerated
just the same.
Of course we believe in it.
You really believe we okay?
We've actually been in space.
It's dog.
We've never been in space.
Hey, really, I don't believe
we walked.
I don't believe we walked
on the moon.
I don't.
Nobody's ever really made it
past those warehouse walls
with Shell Beach painted on them.
We're going to go
back home now.
Bye.
Thank you.
camera five you want to take down the shorts on the uh numerator over there looks like we've
only got a high profile until a midway shot looks like we need to go for a full shot of the
i don't believe me how do you fix this robot man
i don't believe it i never could the robot's head exploded dude
you know phil specter actually grazed the shot you know columbia as it was coming into our air
space as he was aiming at xena's double he was already confused by thinking he was shooting at
xena he shot her double but actually he fired five shots one went off the rim of the old canister
there next to the neck you know next so it was one of phil specter's philiac pool and ricocheting
bullets it might have been phil specter's ricocheting brought down the
think
think of it numerologically speaking phil specter has 11 as the numerological bedroom which comes
out to two okay let's just say all right that two is an interface between the yin and the yang as
we both know it's just circulating and everything okay so you've got the yin and yang you've got a
perfect balance and then he throws it out of balance and what have we got going on in space
we've got a curry party we've got people talking about golf and next time michael jackson admitting
to sleeping when the boys have to play it's a hit these are all hits but the space shuttle
was a hit michael jackson is having hits all over again his crappy albums are selling better than
ever okay here's a conspiracy theater did you hear that michael jackson and the reason for his weird
intolerance to sunlight and his facial diseases is that he was a former shuttle casualty so i've
heard that i thought he was just an evil that's from a canadian is an invitation michael jackson
an alien or just a severely damaged astronaut
somewhere up there in the land of pan never never land you know like waiting for captain hook i guess
to come out of the sky you know i'm i'm captain hook you're captain hook well i'm peter pan
come to me tinkerbell i am captain hook i am your father peter come to me come and sit upon my pegged
lap i will tell you the stories of seven leagues deep
that's right a modern pirate on a modern ship capable of taking down air force and army weapons
was that was that virtual too i mean was that so-called nano virtual or was that just like a
i don't know what you're talking about i'm not in here i'm talking about old blue eyes
you know talking about the lounge mood
you're proud of me i'm proud of you
i'm proud to be a ding-a-ling
i am i'm past that cigar and give me a martini
i'm proud to swing my ding-a-ling against your empty brain pad
such a big thing
hi i'm not a baby dangler
i'm not i'm not a baby dangler
you're not a baby dangler
i was just hanging out with my kids
he's not a baby dangling so you can take that two ways
you know that's very logical because he's known to expose himself to the elephant or whatever the name
if there is a god in the sky
he made everything beautiful how'd you guys get here
we came on the plane
we do not need people that are hung up this way
that is the exact same grammatical form obviously just reversed
but i have a real problem if it means one and only one obviously under 60. a person who is sober-minded
and if you can't handle that we do not need people that are hung up this way
you would get people more in tune with what may lie ahead
i couldn't tell you what city it was or what where everything started being somewhat civil
and pockets that are missing underneath civilization the upper floors of the high rises were just desolate
luster jumped bail two weeks ago halfway through his date rape
uh obviously he has friends all over the place
i think i think people everywhere are concerned
and determine that yet.
Here we go!
Look out!
The Grand Galope by Leonard Solomon,
also from that Orbitones Experimental Musical Instrument album.
Before that, a collage by Reverend Cobblestone,
who has been sending us stuff lately,
also under the name Solar Wimp.
And now, from Heart Ignition,
the very voice of the alien space god,
Jehovah Wimp!
I want to tell you about a super new form of death and destruction.
It is called good kid and bad genitals,
based on the focus of youthful retardation
in atomic structured forms of hell and a kind of melting heaven
that only I, J.H.V.H.1, can allow.
It all started when I shot, with my own two fingers,
a kind of magnetic ray, belching, if you will, into smoke,
covered clouds and metallic shavings
that send songs about diseases brought over the insignificant planet
known as Monkey Culture 90.
I was a child of the
Earth by the Elder Gods,
but Earth by the things that dwell there.
Oh, how I love the monkey wine,
a kind of char,
the native sorrow,
a merlot of Archer,
that I feed on.
It brings me such nourishment to know that they,
the lower moldy monkey funk,
that blankets the planet,
are suffering like the fatal yupp-yupp-iomastic stories of Poompit
and their neuter friends' tails.
Deal with it, you snoozing bastards,
you elder turkeys,
chungis,
that sleep like the little boom babies you are.
I am the Supreme God,
the Supreme King,
sign the land of El-Wichi's pie.
Idiots.
Now there is a guy on the West Coast named Philo...
Philo?
I never heard of him.
Some folks in Dallas think a lot of him.
Yeah?
Which folks?
The folks to bet.
And he's well known in California.
I think we could get a good piece of action on this one, Jim.
Hmm.
All right.
You set it up.
But what of Wolwo?
We forgot Wolwo.
In the great rush of progress of the 20th century,
all of the deities left by the roadside
have forgotten the Hells Asia all the way.
He had a Swedish affirmation, it's not to say.
The miracles of the Purim that had begun in thee
have been done by Sodom and Gomorrah.
They would have repented long ago in Cyclothane.
Epluap.
And the other stupidly named deities of the forgotten pantheon.
What is he talking about?
Oh, Saint Stupid.
He's talking about Saint Stupid.
Might as well be.
He's got to be talking about Saint Stupid.
Same difference.
He won pretty true saint.
That's right.
Four for two, four for three.
Six and a half dozen of the other.
Patron saint of civilizations and...
parking meters.
But you don't know that.
You're not Catholic, are you?
So it's all like church stuff?
It's all church stuff all night long.
That's right.
Another hour and a half.
Another hour and a half in your ear.
Church on one channel.
Pornography.
Hardcore porno on the other.
Or you could call in now and stop the show.
You could call in at the 1-0-VAL-4-8-4-4-2-5
and stop the show now.
That's literally true, isn't that?
That's the way he would have wanted it
if someone would have given him a chance.
Absolutely.
That's the choice.
Yes.
Had they really thought about it and dialed.
The 1-0-VAL-4-8-4-4-2-5.
As many men...
Could call in now and stop this madness now.
That's right.
That's the way he would have wanted it
if he wouldn't have wanted it that other way.
Ladies can call free.
Tell us there was not in this horrible heat...
Wait, that's you.
What the heck is going on?
No, that was my mentor, Jimmy Swaggart.
I studied him.
Oh, they were animals and not human beings and...
He's talking about last week's...
Let's go eat some vegans for breakfast after this show.
I give you my word, I will smite this cancer.
Smite, smite, smite.
Smiting, some more smiting.
Must be a band thing.
Smite you.
No, Smite was the guitarist.
He's the lead guitar guy.
The United States Supreme Court...
Oh, I used to listen to the Smites.
He may be a human life, but...
Come up now.
Although he may have a heart and a brain...
What's his name?
He lacks courage.
Hicks.
But all he...
What do they have that he doesn't have?
They have medals of honor and valor.
We should not concern ourselves about him because he has no legal right.
Bob had no legal right.
Bob was not a man as we call men.
But let's leave things of this world behind.
We'll walk down the primrose path of Bob's gauntlet of torture.
What?
Gabrofine...
I can't say gabrofine.
The Supreme Court said it better.
The Supreme Court said it...
Don't call me a gabrofine.
Ah, yes, dear friends, this is Reverend Ivan Stank.
Yes, these wonderful moments of the past can be yours today.
If you call in now.
If you call in now on the miracle of MP3.
Over 700.000.
No, 200.000 hours of subgenius broadcast.
On one cv.
More than you can listen to in an entire lifetime, and you'll be forced to.
Don't screw me.
Incredible.
7.5.
You'll be influenced by Donstown.
Dolly .
Donstown.
Where am I going?
Help me.
Why am I going to...
Did I win that cd?
Yeah.
Now listen to this song.
And it's hypno-theory.
Ironically enough, the Dobstown song is from Lee Murray.
That's right.
I thought it was Wilbur Harrison.
He knows that.
I mean, we must brainwash our children.
What are you guys on when you're doing that show, man?
Oh, yeah.
Come on, you can tell me.
I see you've done a toilet on your floor.
Hey, Song.
Song.
Caller.
My little son, Caller.
This song is dedicated to you and your trippy amp today.
Can you just fast forward the whole show?
I don't want to get out of here.
I went to downtown already.
No, down.
Just, you know, go down.
Down.
Just go down.
That's not a show.
Oh.
But I did.
I did.
No, come on.
Just down.
Hey, how's it going?
Just go down.
And then say stereo.
I am a tape.
Fernando Mandela.
All those cutouts.
Reverend Isaac's dying in the studio.
You know, Slack mixes by you.
I've heard you in the forums.
And all else that has that power.
I know.
Which one? Oh, tiene menina!
You seem a little nervous, my friend
You are the strength of my soul!
You're selling me from beyond!
You'd better be ready
To speak your piece
You call me from beyond!
You disturb my rest of sleep
With your childish games
You don't know what you're playing with
Listen!
Listen, I give a little voice in your soul
This is your life
Look, we're not just another stupid army of elephants!
Listen to your music backwards in reverse
It's the joke they were putting on the show!
You're in the...
Heavy metal! Heavy metal! Heavy metal!
I'm on stage right now!
We're only in the hollow, cut!
The bottom is dry and loose!
Heavy, get it?
Cool!
You ran for me!
I used to be a nice guy just like you
And then I found
The truth is in the deep
You know I'm a soul which I will eat alive
I'll mix you up and spit in your face
But you're not my enemy!
You're not my enemy!
You ran for me!
You couldn't be ready to face the consequences
It's never too late to redeem yourself
One last chance
That's all you have
It's up to you
You ran for me!
You rang from Reverend Bill T. Miller.
And you can get a lot of free Reverend Bill T. Miller music from www.billtmiller.com.
Bill T. Miller dot com.
When girls go by, then I play high.
I thrill them with each note.
Ha!
Oh, how I get their goat.
I'm the fellow with the fiddle.
Oh, boy, I can play the best in town.
I make a smile from every round.
And every time I start to play, I say the whole of Dorna Town begins to sway.
A votey, votey, votey, and a frat's hat's hair.
A rooty, tooty, tooty, and a razzmatazz.
When I play, though, the girls say, oh, and tremble like they're freezing.
I know that I'm the reason, for I'm the fellow with the fiddle.
When I play, they look at me like I'm the boy.
Just a little girl, she'd come in, and she'd see, she'd know it.
She said she can run all around.
And she'd want to ask her mother for a fiddle.
And she learned to sing for it.
She'd tell her mother, say, sing for your fiddle, and you can get it.
And she'd jump out in front of him and sing.
Give me a little fiddle.
No, Titty Mama Titty.
Titty Mama Titty.
Just gimme a little titty, please ma'am Just gimme a little titty, please ma'am
You're a
Titty on the hill, mama Just gimme a little titty, please ma'am
Thank you.
Like the smartest amoeba that ever existed and the most mindless man.
He was like big brother and little daddy at the same time.
You felt like love, hate, and one emotion at the same consternation.
Right, like the tallest midget and the shortest giant.
You knew both concepts at one time.
You'd see him, you'd know height and small at the same time.
You could feel it, you could smell it.
He was like the essence of everything.
Like the cleanest dirt.
Oh, they used to use that clean dirt?
Bob used to give off clean dirt that sprang flowers and little vegetables out.
He was like the driest water.
He was like Santa Ana winds blowing a big old polar bear.
Or trying not to.
He was like burning hot ice.
He was like that polar bear in a bad dance club.
He was like the furniture you can't believe in and yet you try.
He was the source.
He was the...
He was...
Bob!
He's gonna be back.
I know he's gonna be back.
J.R. Bob Dobbs, if you're listening to me now.
I have faith!
He's gonna be back.
Faith in you, Bob!
He made the salmon sweat.
He made the eye cheese come out where it's not supposed to grow.
He made the Eskimo buy ice.
He made the ice for the sorcerer.
And he kissed each and every one of them with an Eskimo.
He sold hate to the Nazis.
He gave love.
He gave love wherever he could find a place to sit down.
He sold hypocrisy to the Baptists.
He sold retardation to the subgenius.
He sold water.
He sold...
He sold water to old Saint Nick.
He sold a fluoroscope to his uncle.
And then he sold himself out of business.
But he still kept on being and seeing and being the source.
He had insurance, my friend.
Bob had insurance.
Did you?
Do you have Bob's insurance policy?
Bob, if your insurance policy, my friends,
and it's just one payment you make,
the premium lasts forever and ever and ever and ever and ever.
It never comes back.
And if you, for any reason,
you should chance to die or drive into a car
or perhaps just fall asleep and not wake up sometimes,
that's your problem.
That's Bob's?
He's your insurance policy?
And he's what kills you both at the same time?
Bob resold your insurance policy
to a crooked bunch of weird scam artists at the Pentagon.
Because he loved you.
He had so much love for you.
Look, look, look at his leg.
He's loved.
He can't.
Bob loves you more than you love anything.
Oh, those chromosomes are so bleak.
But at the same time,
if you could just pack one little bit of that essence.
They're rock hard, the chromosomes are.
You'd be rock hard like those chromosomes.
Oh, yeah.
I'm not a baby dangler.
Bob's a baby dangler.
He dangled you at the moment of your birth.
And it's taken all this time.
Are you going to wake up?
Is he going to smack you?
Are you going to wake up and start breathing and being alive?
I'm a baby boom, boom, bang.
Are you going to just be a reprobate?
It should be on your DTO screen now.
Reprobate.
Pay close attention to the following transmission.
Your eyes may become unfocused.
You may feel heat around the back of your neck and shoulders.
The forehead may become indented.
Ooh, that feels good, Bob.
Further down.
A little further down.
I'm phasing.
I'm phasing now.
I got a squishy.
Wait a minute.
Pipe down.
Pipe down in there.
Bob's trying to sleep.
Hey, pipe down.
Relax.
Let go.
Oh, it's very, very easy.
Here you go.
Yeah.
You talk to the leper first.
You don't encourage the leper.
You talk to the leper.
It's hard for a leper to change its patches.
You're in there.
Bob's got some special glutes.
Hey.
A little throttle today.
APPLAUSE
Looks scary enough.
A good song is the same.
Tell me a story.
Tax assessor?
A little music there from Fellow with a Fiddle,
and now more from Reverend Cobblestone's collage.
The global war of, I think it's the one world order, the new world order, whatever you want to call it.
The culture of death.
You know, I guess I was vaguely weak, but until you said it flat out, it hasn't been in my consciousness.
Isn't that special?
Well, I think you learned here that there was a sense among all charities that the American values had some value.
I'm not going to take that right.
No, I'm not going to.
Let's have a moment.
A moment of silence for the little twinkle, twinkle little stars that burned up in the atmosphere.
Yeah, that is kind of, you know.
They got off.
You know, I'm always so radical in my stances.
I get all sheepy when I think of, what's your name, the Indian girl.
Dave's got the hot, he's looking at the pictures.
Well, I have, I have no necronomicon or whatever you call them.
You know, I'm not a necrophiliac.
Or affiliated with any of those.
You're an asher.
An asher.
And I can try.
I, eh, I like a try, don't I?
Eh?
Just add water and you're back to, all the basic ingredients, just make them up in your own mind the way you want them.
A moment of silence is a kind of a heart.
A little crack.
When you have a day.
Did you hear?
A day.
It's a moment of silence.
God bless America.
God bless the space program.
And may we continue to shoot monkeys into space.
In the name of science.
Yes.
It's the best way, it's a better reason for killing people than some you can come up with.
Yeah.
May we continue to hook small animals up to car batteries to see what happens.
Plastics are the building blocks.
That's a taxpayers expense.
And also about the things.
Work for me.
After all, the shuttle program was funded by CIA drug money.
I thought you were going to say CIA druggies, you know how good they are at fooling things.
No, it's all funded by the CIA drug money.
And labored smuggling.
Why do you think they called the first shuttle Columbia?
Can I ask you a secret question?
Are you a bonesman?
They don't want you touching the wreckage.
They're afraid you'll find the CIA stash that was hidden in the cargo bag.
Bales of cocaine falling all over Midwest.
The aliens.
Well, I think Chaz had it right on the nostril.
No, it was actually Stang who had the wrong nostril, right?
You claim.
They discovered the dangerous satellite they were putting out in the nick of time.
And we're about to land and explain what had happened.
And they were silenced by them.
Good night.
That's right.
Till next week, keep your hat on tight, you're back to the wind, you're sacking the saddle.
See y'all.
Give your sack to Princess Wayne.
Become an astronaut.
Achieve your dreams in the sky.
Look to the blue as your nostrils inflame, you will realize...
Now the party's over.
You're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
Sponsored by the Church of the Subgenius.
For more information about the Church of the Subgenius, write to Bob at the O-Box 204-206,
Austin, Texas 7872.
We'll see you next week.
Oh, or visit the Subgenius website at subgenius.com.
Thank you for listening.
And praise Bob.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
No, no, no.
Good night.
Come in.
Oh.
Good night.
Goodbye, dear Pietro.
.
Praise Bob.
Whoa, whoa.
No way.