Usually radio announcements merely recommend a product, but this station provides its clients with a special service.
The Subgenius Hour of Swag.
In the radio studios of Bob, the technicians, the entertainers, the commentators, the administrative personnel,
daily unite their efforts in the creation of programs to please and entertain a vast radio public.
Ah!
The wide variety of broadcasts include group discussions, political speeches, and comedy.
On this program, frank opinions are expressed in response to their leaders' questioning.
Questions of the day are discussed and opinions and attitudes freely expressed on issues of the moment.
For there is keen interest in a radio program that invites personal participation by the public.
This is...
This is Independent Radio in a Democracy.
Music
då
The
fan
You can't stop it
It's in question
You gotta pop it
Do you wanna light it up?
Light it up
We all know
There's still time
Now we're gonna
Fire up your minds
Do you wanna light it up?
Light it up
Fire, fire
Knock, knock, no one's home
We don't wanna dance alone
No, no, can't behave
We'll get tortured
We'll get in the cage
Uh-oh, there's no time
We don't wanna lose our minds
Oh yeah, time to change
Wanna see you use your brain
We don't wanna lose our minds
Get tired
We don't wanna be so
In this secure
Just forbidden
In a
Amphitheatre
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, we're gonna
Light our minds
Fire up your minds
Set your minds on fire
Time has come
For us to use it
Fire it up
No time to lose it
Do you wanna light it up?
Come on everyone, join the fun
We've got thinking on the run
The Earth is circled by the sun
Creation Science Polka
Science classes in our schools
Taught by superstitious fools
Jerry Falwell sets the rules
Creation Science Polka
The universe was fabricated
In six literal days
The humans and the dinosaurs
Shared a condo in L.A.
Carbon dating makes us cringe
We're the right wing lunatic fringe
Jesus died for our sins
Creation Science Polka
TH cinq
The Bible says the earth is only 6,000 years old
Deny and Jesus Christ will roast your balls on burning coals
Come on everyone, join the fun Ignorance has almost won
Get geology from a nun Creation Science Polka
Take your children out of school Homespun dogma is so cruel
Prop them up, watch them drool Creation Science Polka
The Rudy Schwartz Project, dear friends
Of course, their Creation Science Polka
Played that for a special friend
And there'll be another one at the very end for the same friend
Which we'll be talking about
Pretty soon
However, after Dave calls in
In the meantime, I'm going to read a quick rant
That I got off of the Scrub Genius Forum
A rant by the good Reverend Roger
Whose stuff I read a lot these days
This rant is called Why You're Screwed
He actually uses stronger language
Than I'm going to use
On the public airwaves
Weirdness is in the human being
Almost like a muscle
The more you use it, the stronger it gets
But the flip side of that
Is that when you stop using it, it atrophies
It shrivels up until one day
You're wearing dockers and khakis
And working on the TPS report
And looking forward to the Knicks
At the sports bar after work
Horrible, eh?
But that's how it goes
One day you're up to your butt
In freaks at the gay bar
And the next you're eyeing that Lexus commercial
With silent contemplation
You aren't going to buy one, of course not
But you're just curious as to
Whether you can make the payments
I mean, it's not like you'd be one of them
Even if you did
Because it isn't the car that makes you weird
It's you, right?
Right, right, right?
Oh, you're screwed
This is how the machine
Trademark
Gets its hooks into you
Baby steps
After all, it's had 8,000 years
To feed you
And figure out how to get the square pegs
Into the round holes, hasn't it?
I'll be weird tomorrow
You say you're tired
Burned out
The coming weird times are here
And now you're exhausted
But are you?
What have you done to get so tired?
You sure it isn't lethargy?
Some of you do have a lot on the ball
Granted, but shouldn't all these activities
Give you more of an excuse to be you?
As if you ever needed one?
The machine
Trademark
Has many ways of neutralizing freaks
If your last name is Snowden
There are active ways of getting you to shut up
If not, though, it has more passive methods
One of which is to make sure you understand about
Tomorrow
Trademark
Is the product that lets you stay weird today
Without actually doing anything
Because you'll do it
Tomorrow
Trademark
Then one day you run out of tomorrow
And you're out of your mind
Your headstone reads
Good citizen
Well done, that man
Shut up, you can't tell me what to do
No, and I wouldn't if I could
The people I'm talking to already know what they're supposed to do
They're just too busy to do it
Busy, busy, busy
Too busy for public, uh, ad improvement
Too busy for making everyone move to the other side of the room
Too busy for Bob
And doesn't that sound like the sort of persuasion
The machine Trademark would use?
Go ahead and rattle those prison bars to see which ones are loose
Tomorrow
Today you need to apply yourself to your monkey training tools
Like Farmville or whatever time-sensitive game is hot right now
Remember Tamagotchi, the virtual pets?
Neither do I
But I'm not sure I'm going to be able to do that today, but I'm going to try and get a little bit of a break from the game today
But I don't feel like Saturday night
That's okay, Saturday night doesn't feel like you
It is still out there, just, you know, without you
The fun never stopped, you did
The party still goes on
It's been going on since Babylon
And it'll be going on long after your dust
Because, like the machine, Trademark
Saturday night has had 8,000 years how to figure out how to deal with Wallflower
And it does so by grinding over their bodies
With horrible squelchy crushy noises
And rumbling off into the sunset
So you can take your lurking and your TV and your crappy beer
And your wasted days and wasted nights
And your lethargy and your cause
And your whatever else the hell you've traded for your very life
And you can jam them up your arses for all I care
Me?
I'm off to pee on the power lines
Because Bob made me that way
Or kill me
Well, yep, there's another subgenius rant that ends with the phrase
I actually was planning to play a canned show of my Starwood rant
Just an hour of me talking
And I read a couple of rants by other subgenius
And they both ended
They all ended up with Or kill me
And, you know, we advise people not to commit suicide generally
Well, subgeniuses, anyway
We tell subgeniuses not to commit suicide because
You're gonna die anyway
We all end up on our heads, every single one of us
And, uh, um...
So you gotta make the most while you can
And, um...
We have a friend who did
We're gonna be talking about that
Oh, I should mention, um, the music that I was playing at the beginning of that rant
Was the Rudy Schwartz project from his new album
His latest CD
Uh, an instrumental called Fortnight of Glistening Stumps
Lovely
A lovely little fortnight there
And, uh, I've gotta prepare that last Rudy Schwartz project song for later
The music in the background is from classic Universal Monster movies, friends
And, uh...
Yes, yes, yes
It's...
It's been a long week for a lot of, uh, subgeniuses
And, uh...
I can't complain myself
We got our driveway covered
Oh, oh, I'm sorry, Princess We is here also
I didn't even have you turned on
Well, now I'm turned on
Mm-hmm, now everybody's turned on
When Princess We gets on
Come on, Dave, come on, Dave
Oh, I shouldn't say that
Um...
Well, I'll go ahead and tell you what's going on, friends
Uh, it's about our beloved subgenius
That, uh, a lot of you know in person
If you've been to any X Day Drill
Except this very last one
The one this last July
Because our friend was too sick for the first time
Ever
He has been at every single X Day Drill from 1990 to 2020
1996 to 2016
And there at 7 in the morning
Well, that's, yeah, that's the other thing
He was the only other person besides me
Who was not only at every X Day Drill
He was at every single 7 a.m. on July 5th
The hardest part of my year in some ways
And he, and he alone was always there to help
Always
He also brought a drive-in movie every single time
And, um, the person we're talking about is Dr. Dark, of course
Dave
Who's not a flash of a person to begin with
No, I just now, um, explained who we're talking about
I didn't know until this afternoon I got a call, I thought, from him
I was thrilled because we knew he was really sick
And fighting cancer and kind of almost in hospice
And kicking ourselves for not going to see him every day
Well, but no, he didn't want people to come see him
I know
But we got, uh, I, I, I thought I was getting a call from him
But it was actually his sister-in-law, Candy, using his phone and calling his, his old friends
Yes, Dr. Dark boarded the saucers last Friday
Um, evidently at the time and in the way of his choosing
Given the fact that he'd been fighting all kinds of cancers for many years
And he beat them too
Until now
And, uh, I was told that it went quite fast at the end there
The cancer was spreading fast
And last Friday he decided he was ready to shoot through, as my late dad put it
And, uh, if I understand correctly, he went into hospice
And spent the day with his close friends
And his closest family members
Um, that mainly being the family of his wife, Her Highness Hell-No
I'm told he watched, uh, his fa- I guess one of his favorite shows
Rachel Maddow all the way through
And then, uh, spent his last moments alone with his wife
I was told there was, uh, no pain
And he felt surrounded by love
And, uh, and he did
He did get the big, uh, get well card that everyone at the X-Day party in July signed for him
And apparently that really meant quite a lot to him too
Um
Yeah, if you get a special envelope that's got the little furry critter inside and stuff like me over here
Thank you, thank you, thank you
And you close it up and you start crying and stuff like that
I don't know if it was the kind that talks
I'm not sure if it had a furry animal but there were lots of furry, lovey expressions expressed
Well, there was some great artwork on that card
There was
Well, there was some really good art, there were always really good artists at X-Day
Mm-hmm
Well, mainly because they were lunch, they were, uh, officially manicured lunch windows
Or, uh, what do they call those things you wear on your chest when you, that has the daily specials on them?
Lunch cards, no?
I know nothing of this
Have you seen like in pictures of the 1930s and 40s there's like a person that has like a billboard on his side of the clock
Sandwich board, it's a sandwich board
Right
That's what you're looking for
Sandwich board
Yes, a sandwich board
And it says hot dog or whatever flavor wiener or something like that, $2.95
And then there's a person, you know, there's like a little cacophonous sound that accompanies each one of the arguments
You know, it's like, like it's
They're gonna bite you somehow, you know, you get scared but you still continue to, you know
Well, another thing that sandwich boards are famous for is end of the world predictions
Mm-hmm
The world is ending is often on sandwich boards in cartoon world
Jays
Um, anyway, uh, obviously it's, uh, Dr. Dark's, uh, boarding the escape van
And, uh, the one of the two vessels was not unexpected
But, of course, it's not fair either
Uh, he's just maybe a little bit older than me
And, um
Maybe a year, I mean, not much
But he, he and her highness, hell no, did get to spend the last couple of years traveling and visiting all the places they wanted to see
In a big minivan
I know they've been to Easter Island at least twice
Yes
Apuaku
Yeah, we got to see a great, uh, slideshow of that once
And they brought us back gifts from there
Friends, uh, for those of you who didn't know Dr. Dark, you've actually heard him on this show in the background for decades
Because he was the greatest of all subgenius hecklers
The Clipster
He got the Bobby Award for best heckling of subgenius preachers
Every year for 22 years
Even the year that he and his friends made the Bobby Awards
He couldn't help it, he was quick
He was just born quick
He could spew out like 25 jokes within 25 seconds
It was just like
Or some other number like that
And there would just be this whole expository sandwich right out for you to wear on the sandwich board
Well, I mean, uh, you, uh
You hear him in the older DeVyv 4 years
And he's got a lot of wonderful recordings
Clearly, I was not, I didn't have time to find any examples of that
Apparently he narrated one of the, uh, the wrestling
The naked blood wrestling that we used to do at X-Days
Uh, I found a note saying that he did a great running commentary of that in 99 and I need to find that
I did find a couple, a cassette where he called, uh, Chaz's show
And I'll play that in a little while
But yeah, friends, um, he was, uh
His heckling was funnier than my preaching
And sometimes it was like he made the show
Absolutely
Yeah
He had this bizarre talent for punning
His fevered brain just
Spontaneously, spontaneously too, yes
Fiendishly churned out puns
Like nobody we've ever known
And we've known some really serious punners
Yes, it endeared him to puns
And he was mad at me very, very strongly because that made, reminded me of my father
And these, these weren't just regular bad puns, friends
These were god-beswogglingly painful puns
They were all original and all soaringly, inspiringly terrible
You know, I mean, that's what makes puns great
And he was the greatest
Yeah, in fact he's not
In fact, here's a, well this isn't exactly a pun, I guess
I found this line at one point
Somewhere on old subgenius forum
Do not go genital into that good night
He said
How apropos
Yeah
He was, he was a master quickenheimer
He was like one of those people who just like
Would fire off this barrage of puns and other humor, humor devices
The most unusual I thought was his ability to actually
Quip style deliver the
These jokes
Guy walks into a bar and it's like over in like less than two seconds
But it still was wonderful
Well, and he would coin words too
Here's an example
That's why I feared him a lot of times
Did you ever fear him?
No, not in the slightest
I did, like well I hope Dr. Dark is not gonna start a night late call because
Stuff like that, you know
No, I did not fear him
I depended on him
Well, I'm not, is that to say I'm stupid or something or
No, no, I mean I, I, we were, we were good friends
Um, but uh
Oh here's, here's one
He posted a word of the day back in 2004
On alt.slack
Word of the day
Gaia Rhea
Proper noun
New age blather
Ex, uh
Example of use in a sentence
There was a lot of Gaia Rhea going around at Starwood last year
Uh, here's another one
Oh this is just a little, a very
He didn't post a whole lot
He, uh
Cause if he had I would have found it
I s-
He wasn't anti-postal
He just didn't find it
The way he does
At one point he, um, he announced that uh
He and her
Her Highness Helena were going to go on a trip to Paris
This was in 2003 I sugge- I, I think
And one subgenius suggested uh
The Pavillons de Bercy or something and
Uh, he said
He looked at the link and he said
Looks swell, too bad I can't read French
Now I know what an illiterate feels like
Not ever having been there before
I like to imagine Paris as being like the city
Depicted in the movie City of Lost Children
Ever see it? Very atmospheric
As a subgenius tourist
I'll eschew the Eiffel Tower
For the sewer tour
The Louvre for appreciating the art
In piles of dead people's bones in the catacombs
Uh, plus the two great places I've been tipped off to now
Thanks y'all
You know what, I did that
I went, I saw the, the piles of dead people bones in the catacombs
Instead of the Louvre
The one or two days that I was in Paris
Of course we couldn't get into the Louvre
There's not a long line for the catacombs
But uh, yep
I really don't know where to begin with that
I know that uh, Louis Quatorze was quite a
Was a vicious old swine
Louis Quatorze
But he wasn't as bad as history reported him
But he did, he did turn out to be a traitor
I'm not saying I think Dr. Dark was a traitor
In fact I think he's befuddled in the chemist at the same time
Or you know, like any combination of the three
Well he was a trader
He would trade
Right
Copies of rare obscure movies for copies of other rare obscure movies
And he could, he could whistle and or hum
Each and every one of the theme songs from any of those B-movies
Or any of the ambient music as well
Yep, they're playing in the background right now
Well that's very, he didn't do that on purpose
Mostly he was just like
Heckle people who were trained to perform
Well you know Dave, um
Unlike many subgeniuses
Dr. Dark believed in an afterlife
And therefore he still does
Um, and evidently he mentioned lots of plans I was told
Plans to contact us from the other side
So I'm expecting to get some faint but very distinctive heckling in my head
In the wee hours of the night sometime
And I am too
I expect tricks
The old Italian ladies used to say you can't wish to communicate too hard
Or the spirits don't come
Well didn't you
You have to relax and let your mind be open
I don't know if that requires like taking a butter knife or a surgical instrument to your forehead, you know
It would with me
It would, he's gonna have to heckle pretty hard to contact me
I'm pretty thick headed to
Right
Now didn't you get
Didn't you feel a tremor in the force?
Well I often do, I often before a friend of mine just
Who also had the big G
Um, just departed and he made through our
What did you say his veins collapsed around his forehead again?
No that's me, that's what happens with me
That's what I had, yeah
Well that's what it usually means anyway
And I didn't say I thought of him that way
I just, I forgot of him in that way if you know what I mean
Like quote unquote
Huh, huh, huh, huh, huh
Well apparently he already had, he already started playing tricks
The second he shot through
Cause his sister-in-law told me that
Um, when she came into the room where he was laying after, I mean, well his body was laying
He had departed
And she put her hand on his neck
And she put her hand on his head and leaned over and kissed his head
And the nurse ran in the room and said
Hey what are you doing? His heart just restarted for a second
So she took that as a kind of a last little um, you know
Ha ha, you think I'm, you think I'm, he ain't gone yet
Wow
I have uh
Well I know, I believe in such things are not, you know humorous subjects to be discussed on the Hour of Slack
I'm sure, or I don't
But I, I, I share it a lot in common as far as the view of the afterlife which is like um
Um, Hindu or something almost
Or Patagonian, I think it maybe describes the shrimp people cause they're so small
The, the briny little shrimp people
The actual briny shrimp
No, we have to, we have to
Like the kind near Las Vegas
We have to talk about uh things
Like the big C and death on the Hour of Slack
Because people still need slack
No matter what
And yet the, I mean obviously you, you, you can't laugh at it
But you can
You have to
You can't but you have to
Yeah I was gonna add to that earlier
But whatever service he's going to have
Is going to be a joke fest
Excuse my language
But whoever gets up and starts talking about it
Stands up for him and says I remember Dr. Dark
Or I forgot his real name right now
I wasn't gonna, actually
You're not supposed to
We probably shouldn't say that
Because there's a couple of people uh who
They're unlikely to find out on this show
But they might on Facebook
And that wouldn't be cool
Uh I was given permission
By, in fact I was encouraged by, by him
By his uh survivors
They said oh yeah he'll be listening
So hey Dr. Dark
We really miss you already
Now that I think about it
But I'm here to be a laugh riot
Because speaking of things that you were just talking about
A friend of mine who recently died
Everybody seemed to laugh
When people would go and stand up and be
Tell something that was only moderately humorous
And people would be slapping their
Thighs and crawling around the aisles
And barking like animals and so forth
Well laughter and tears are very close
They are
And then a picture
A picture that was in the memorabilia items area
Flew at somebody and everybody went
Whoa
And looked at each other
Well yes
Well of course things become more meaningful at times like that
Oh god I remember Chaz's service
It was a
It wasn't exactly funny
And uh
They played his last song
As they were carrying him out to plant him in the ground
And I lost it
I had not cried up until then
But I completely broke down
And it takes a lot
It takes a train to laugh or something like that
Or a train to cry
Well that's an air conditioning system
I ended up uh
Um
It's like when I finally bust loose
I
You know I'm crying for everybody
I know
I remember you were leaving road apples all over the floor too
Before we
Set our bon voyages
Dr. Dark was also sick
And I mean he was sick in the Lenny Bruce kind of way
Yep
Sick, sick humor
Um
He probably would not have lasted long
On a radio show like this because
Talk about not being politically correct
Now this guy was the biggest libtard
Uh in the world
I mean uh
Well I shouldn't say that
But I know that he was a dedicated
At least in this dimension we're in right now
Yeah uh
Uh
I'm sure he'll be watching the continuing train wreck from
You know his HDTV set
The Akashic
Uh
Viewing room but uh
Here's an example
This is from actually from years ago
Uh
This was he was filling us in on some news about Bill Cosby
This is before
The word really was out about Bill Cosby
He said um
Uh
To quote Dr. Dark
He won't face criminal charges but comedian Bill Cosby may face a lawsuit over allegations that he fondled a Canadian woman
Pennsylvania authorities could not find enough credible and admissible evidence since it melted
Against Cosby that would lead to a criminal conviction but
A former Temple University student says
Cosby drugged her with a date rape drug riddled
Jello pudding pop
And then fondled her with a strap on jello pudding pop
At his Philadelphia home
Cosby
Wiping his fingers on a trademark Huxtable sweater
Denies the allegations
The woman's lawyer says she will probably file a lawsuit
Since there isn't always room for jello
See what I mean
Yeah
It's uh
That's not the kind of thing I would say on the
College radio
I
Oh wait
I noticed
Yeah she was capable of hitting the mark depending on the time
Depending on what kind of shoe size she was talking about you know
It'd be like if one moment you would be marvel
If not marvel at the um
The um adaptability
Of the species especially with a long nose named John
Or some kind of Arabic title
Suleiman
Nahoo
Not only was Dr. Dark unbelievably sick and twisted
But another thing that made him a true subgenius
Top to bottom through and through
Was his terrible taste in motion pictures
B
Or rather his superb taste in what we might call great bad film
Yes
And I don't mean just mediocre movies we're talking about
Oh no not just mediocre
The movies that are so good that
So bad
That they reveal more about the human condition than they ever intended to
The Plan 9's that we dream of when we're having our munchkin feisty parties
Or we're lying asleep trying to consume a brownie with our rectum
It's just those strange nights that we call out to Bob or anybody else who will listen
And we just and these films were that's the reason
Um
I found one of his playlists from a uh
A Dr. Dark's drive-in
This was uh the
These were the movies that said
And it really was a drive-in
Yes
Uh you could in fact in the early days he even had like a radio broadcasting the soundtrack
That's right
So that you could listen to the movie in your car
On your car's radio
And watch um
Which they still have it didn't go away Stan
No um
Well uh
It it uh
He had he didn't usually use it
He used a 16 millimeter projector that was usually a video projector
But it would
He'd put it put it on the great big screen at Brushwood
And then later on the big screen at Wisteria
Here's here's a list of the movies that we got treated to
One X Day
Okay
Attack of the Crab Monsters 1957
Attack of the Robots 1966
Bride of the Monster 1955
That's from uh Ed Wood
A Bucket of Blood 1959
Which has beatniks
Can't Stop the Music 1980
Creature from the Haunted Sea 1961
Flash Gordon 1974
Frankenstein Meets the Space Monster 1965
Freaks 1932
Glenn or Glenda 1953
That's another Ed Wood
Hercules in the Haunted World
Invaders from Space 1959
Iron Man but not the one you're thinking of
No
Jan Joe the Beast from the East
Oh Joe Riley's Japanese Monster Mash
And there's another
Late subgenius
Saint Joe Riley
He was a collector of bad films
And he made uh cut cut-ups of them and media broadcasts
And stuff
What a brilliant set of
He was one of those uh
One of those fellows who was
Everyone and himself thought was in
Perfectly normal health and just
One Wednesday night
He fell over dead in his kitchen
From an undiagnosed heart condition that he'd always had
But no one knew
What would you prefer staying if you were to expire tomorrow?
What kind of certificate would you want on your luminary tablet there?
Oh I've given that some
I can't make up my mind between
I'll get him for this
On my tombstone
Which is a pretty vain
Forlorn hope
Or
And this one came from our friend
Tonya
Uh
Keep off my grass
Get off of my lawn
Get off my lawn sorry
I blew that one
Typical
If there's two ways to say something I'll say it the wrong way
Keep off my gra-
Yeah get off my lawn
Keep off my grass
Right
I personally don't want my
Uh body laying in a box in the ground
I'd rather have uh
Mortuary students play with it
Yeah especially if they're gonna plant you like a tree
Or a piece of statuary
Somethin' I guess they're doin' that lately
They're having these little like statue parks
Where it's the actual person entombed in a cellophane glass of
Of cement and obscure items
Uh
Somethin'
And they all have to drink it at the same time or something
I don't know
Well I'm not sure I mean
To you it's all division and extraction
To me it's multiplication man
You lost me on that one Dave
Sorry
Well where the
Where the hell were you expecting me to go?
I got lost at the pass
Okay I'm gonna-
Well the pass had three corners and like Stang said
We are only here for 45 minutes
And then we have to go and argue with the
The agent and make sure we can get another gig
You know what I'm sayin'
I know I know
Well here I'm gonna try and experiment
I- this is something I haven't done in a radio station for about
20 years
I'm gonna play a cassette
I found this uh
In my searchings online
I found that there was a recording from a
An ESO radio show
One of the Chazz's shows
And you and me were here Dave
Or in the old studio
This is from hour of slap number 724
This is from 2000
The year 2000
And it's Dr. Dark calling in
Although here's the thing
He wasn't Dr. Dark then
When we first knew him he was Dr. Gorgonzola
Like the keys
Yeah he was Gorgonzola for a long time
And uh I believe this is him calling in
It doesn't sound like him
They also made a fine uh salad dressing too
But it doesn't sound like us either
Cause we're-
Well it's got that kind of munchkin quality
Once you- you're over like over 25 years old
You hear everything like that you-
When you were 15 you sound like a- a hoss
Okay, okay let's- let's see how this sounds
Okay he doesn't- as you might expect
He hardly got a word in edgewise
Cause of you and me
So I'll fade it out after- after
He- his last words I think
On this tape
Let's see if this works
Yeah
Our merchant credit card company
Quit doing business with us
Wow
Having looked at the website and discovered that there was
Quote questionable material unquote
So Jesus- Jesus
Fat- fat naked people in a swimming pool at Brushwood
Yeah Jesus had to call up
That is always questionable
A new bank
And who-
We had to find a- a- a pornographer's bank
That would do anything for a buck
Praise Bob and God bless America
Where there's still people who do anything for a buck
And understand the values
You're on the air with Lonesome Cowboy Dave
You know you were complaining about the one world advertiser
I- I think it's a fine little giveaway paper
I find on my doorstep
Every day
The one world paper boy throws it in here
Look over here
One- one church of the subgenius for sale
What?
Yeah
It's on page three of the one world advertiser
Underneath the garage sale listings and the lost kitties
Well
The church of the subgenius has been willing to sell out for a long time
It's in the shopper
They haven't had any buyers yet
Oh man if you get it in the shopper that means it's definitely going down
Those guys see they're- they're very anxious to jump the stories they say in those local news gardens
Market analysis summary
The subgenius market is not restricted by age, gender, belief system or even international boundaries
Anybody might be interested
The majority of our members fall in ridden males 18 to 25
Above average intelligence
Computer literate and somewhat rebellious
That's not what this says
It says almost free to good home
And then tape jacks
Sounds like a good profile of hackers who may have attacked the sites over the last few days
I don't know if they got the profile
They got you know John Douglas
They might all be in this together
The same people that knocked down those sites
Can you imagine the FBI profile
I think someone called up Talk of the Nation today and claimed the church of the subgenius had something to do with that
Figures
Wouldn't that be a funny joke
As long as they spell the name right in the newspaper
You're an RBI
I'm referring to Papa Joe's stunt
Yes
The world's first Macintosh virus was blamed on the church of the subgenius
It was a lie
A lie
Because it was a peace message
Well that is the reason why the genetic spawn that you have for fornicating apples have ruined mankind
And have ruined our business structure
That's why we have to leave
Have ruined the social infrastructure and our cultural beliefs
Look at what it's become
It's you know it destroyed everything with that
It's like the story of Para Ubu
Like the absurdity of mankind
Yeah
Well I'm gonna fight that out
That's I think that was the last that we heard from Dr. Dark on that recording
Goodness
That's unbelievable the voices
I thought yeah
I thought it was quite well done
It sounded like him
It was a little more tenorous
Stan was slightly very slightly more tenorous
I was a bit bit more tenorous
Oh yes
But I think that's a quality recording
As far as like going bowling with it and trying to pick up some prostitute or something
I don't know if it's gonna make any sense
Well you should try that
Go ahead and try it Dave
Oh so you're urging me you're spawning me to take my spawn the spawn of my loins
Which is hard and fast and heavy for many thousands of years right now
Especially when my genetic coding
Which is about
Looks like a regular standard draft paper
And that's why I had to leave the Air Force
It's
You know the abuse you take every few moments
Now here's a recording of from another ESO show an even older one
I would list this from hour of slack number 664
Which would make it about a year before this
The one we just heard so this would be about 1999
Oh that makes sense because
We had just done the
Subgenius new
In woe
New world order game with Steve Jackson games
It was a role playing game
Card set
And we were talking you and me
Were talking about
What the
Something about how aliens
Sex with God
Then aliens hiding in plain sight
And then it says quote Medusa versus Gorgonzola
And we were talking about like if when you play the subgenius card game
If you draw a Medusa one player draws Medusa card
The next one draws say the doctor Gorgonzola card
And they hit they pit it against each other here I'll just play this type
Those are the aliens that are hiding in plain view
I mean they're right out in front of us
You never actually saw one of them though they had a real face right
I mean
Well if I how would I know
I mean we all might have they might be around us all the time we wouldn't know
Yeah but you made it sound as if you had heard or had some taste of
Clonians going on where people were saying that they knew what they described their face to
And you said it was horrific like was Gorgonzola and Hegesys them guys
Yeah exactly they were hideous like Gorgonzola like that thing that drips off on you
And you can see the blood on his face
Yeah
When he gets all worked up
And that's why Medusa had to hang a shield up there so he could look at it and say check this out man you need a shield you know
Right and yeah it was stupid it was like Medusa had the super power of turning people to stone
But Gorgonzola had that smell that could even kill Medusa
Well that's what you were saying if the guys wanted to be actually decomposed in space
They would have to transfer them smells into their chambers where they make them into the blood
And they would have to go into different homes where they are
Like if you're playing Illuminati New World Order on some secret orchestra
And you use the plug in the Gorgonzola plug in
You can like if you get that when it's infected that will take your opponents
Chainer device or Legume or Lonesome Cowboy Dave or whatever
And you know then you can convert you could you get their powers
Yeah but if you start double clicking on them things come up I heard that whole civilization's disappeared
This is Dr. Q Ellis here coming to you live from Friendly
Well so there was a little bit of that in there
I think I accidentally cut off my cordon
Quite an adaptive an adventurous soundtrack which I think is equals parallels none
I could tell by the sound
If you divide something by zero
That was when I was calling WCSB from Texas
And recording the shows off the internet
That's why it had that unique horrible quality to it
Hollywood is what you meant right that unique Hollywood quality
No I wouldn't say that exactly
Well would you say Meekie or would you say devout or impersonal
Or any of those other four letter words
I would say praise Bob
And I would say hail Connie
I would say
Hail yeah
I would say apparel
But
If that's your name
Yeah well this was a show that we didn't expect to do
But I'm glad we did it
I hope that Dr. Dark approves and I'm sure he'll find out a way to let us know if he doesn't
Yes and we will be highlighting those as you encounter them in the future weeks I'm sure
Well you know I don't believe in ghosts
Because I'm scared of them
Me too
They're the worst in the haze
Yeah that just freaks me out
And so we'll see
Well we'll see
President we'll see the third year
That's the guy who started all this with all these random things
And strange thoughts and strange recollections
Who?
That's why Randolph Scott or Wilma Jane Turker or something
I forget
The heck is he talking about H.P. Lovecraft
H.P. Lovecraft that's right he was lurking here someplace
And he said that if Dr. Dark was going to come back he would come back as a French werewolf
A dark haired lovemeister French werewolf
With paws and teeth
Let's see
I didn't make it up I just related the information
That's all I ever do anyway
To convey any idea of these monstrosities is impossible
They were of the reptile kind with body lines suggesting sometimes the crocodile sometimes the seal
But more often nothing of which either the naturalist or the paleontologist ever heard
This is H.P. Lovecraft
These are from Papa Joe Mama's H.P. Lovecraft trading cards
Papa Joe makes trading cards on the side
He just gave me his 100 card set of dinosaurs
Yes quite impressive
I'd never heard of 99% of those 100 dinosaurs
Well what happens if you lose your Cthulhu card
Can you send back for another one?
No you can use the Gorgonzola card
And use the stinky cheese power
Right
To beat Cthulhu
Absolutely
You know if you use a subgenius's abnormality power
Is its greatest power
And each of us has different abnormality powers
Our subject for tonight
The late but early to the saucers Dr. Dark
Was had many many great abnormality powers
Unfortunately he had some that weren't
He told me at one point he was really a genetic mutant
And that was the reason that he had to deal with all those cancers
And he did beat a whole bunch of cancers
Oh he sure did
But you know and I'll say this every day
I'm not going to lie to you
It's tough being a large mammal
There's just no way around that
It's even very difficult to be a small mammal
I don't know how the side figures into it
Although I certainly agree with the sentiment
Especially where the wisecracker army is like really
Is facing certain doom you know
And they're all lined up on the sides of the hills
And they're ready to set their underpants on fire
In front of a thousand people just to fight them
And watch the spectacle
Well most small animals don't know
That they're going to die
Right large mammals have these big brains
They can think all about it
Yeah they can fret
Fret
Or plan as the case may be
Or why not both
Tread to access
When they offered
When they offer me the red pill or the blue pill
Why not both
That's what I'm going to say
Friends you're listening to the hour of slack
This is episode number 1635
That's how many we've done
Although we sometimes run reruns
But mostly they're fresh
And it'll be canned
A new canned show that no one's heard next week
Actually people on the internet have heard it
We're doing everything out of order
And that's another thing
That endears us all to
B-b-b-bad
I like to think
Yes that's why
That's why TSLA was a
A hack and a heistermeister
And like if they were
Dr. Dark were still
In the reptile room
Without you know not being able to
Have to cause me trouble
Cause remember he used to wear
A sweat mask something
Or not a sweat mask but a
He had a Mexican wrestler mask
Yes
Oh I was talking about the surgical mask
Oh yeah remember his penis nose mask
God he would show up with the most outrageous costumes
He had a penis nose face thing
And who wouldn't want one
Well it fit him perfectly I must say
It was you know quite a
Handsome penis nose
Gross
That's why they call them titanium microns
But if you're into that sort of thing yeah
You're afraid of business
Because that's what my grandfather used to
That's what he tried to teach me
He said you know
The wisdom of the little people
Or the starlings
Or the hectorades of confusion
It's one of those groups
In Washington D.C. near the beltway
Where they have like secret temples underneath them
And they're like the earth
Because I guess Washington D.C. is on a
33rd
33rd degree parallel
Of longitude
Well you're listening to
Subgenius Hour of Slack
And if you need to know more about
Any of this
There is a subgenius.com
Which is like a bottomless pit
But the simplest thing
What a lot of people do is they skip all the instructions
And just go straight to some free Facebook page
And there's lots of those
There's even one called
There's too damn many subgenius Facebook pages
Yes
So Dave I'm going to play this last song
By the Rudy Schwartz Project
I think that Dr. Dark would have approved of it
And I hope he enjoys it
Although I think I had to cut one of the cuss words
Three or four times
Rudy Schwartz
Thanks for calling Dave
It is difficult work
And we'll do it again
And meanwhile here is the Rudy Schwartz Project song called
Kill for God
See you Dave
Bryan
I want to join Islamic Jihad
I just want to kill for God
Praising Allah is the life for me
I'll use pipe bombs, what the fuck
Killing Hebrews brings good luck
Gotta make Khomeini proud of me
Load a car with dynamite
And drive into a synagogue without any brakes
Nothing could be better than
Impaling your intestines on a big rusty stick
Hand grenades and cattle prods
Let's go out and kill for God
I can hear Mohammed calling me
Yowza, yowza, yowza
I'll have пот on myavantela
And I'll be
Intended 0-0 to be
Uptown madman of myantela
Winning And've got to end them then
Though the Koran seems quite odd, I still want to kill for God.
Praising Jesus is the life for me.
Fuck those pagans, they're such cynics.
Let's bomb the abortion clinic.
Jerry Falwell is my cup of tea.
Never thought I'd make it big by selling God to idiots on cable TV.
What the fuck, it's not GE, but still a better way to use my business degree.
Use a rifle, spare the rod.
Let's go out and kill for God.
Praise the Lord and hand that gun to me.