oh yer yer yey Oh Oh oh yer O praticamente
vowel
music
You ask me why I love her?
Give me time.
I'll explain.
Have you drifted on a cold fog drifting over Kansas, sir?
Bayoued over San Francisco Bay?
Have you heard the bellow of a Bob White calling in the diesel in the Appalachian Mines?
You look with awe and wonder drifting way up high where men who braved a hard new world first stepped on the diesel in the city dock?
Do you think of them when you stroll along a rock way high?
Have you seen the mighty Peet?
Have you seen an eagle roll along Missouri's shore?
Have you felt it rage along the shore?
Is the word why a mayor read?
From a...
Alaska's Everglades.
The mayor.
My heart runs out.
My pulse rises fast.
The might of her domain.
You ask me why I love her?
I have a million Appalachian Mines.
My beautiful Appalachian Mines.
Beneath God's wide old fog sky.
And found my hood from shining...
Sea to Sea.
Ah!
Like this movie is for kids!
John Wayne and Lemur.
Oh my gosh I kind of love vendo i can afford 50 kids
MEMPLE SA Сейчас настроğu
Things However mismos
What is this here...
HUH?
It's his mind!
I'LL STAY AC不錯
STILL
Hour of Slack number 929.
The Yeti of El Queso.
Hour of Slack.
Uh, yes.
It is 5000 BC.
Look around.
See how there is nothing here to listen to.
No radio.
No television.
No phonograph.
Nothing but the wind and the rain.
The rhythm of the wind.
The beat of the raindrops.
See how man listens to that.
And now see how he starts to create strange rhythmic sounds of his own.
Sounds that excite his emotions.
Is that not some cowboy dance over there?
Goomagawoom.
The storm has driven the Yeti out of the high mountains into the old palace.
That is not good.
If the Yeti cut our contact with the outside world,
it could mean a slow death to the village and to us.
What were you saying about the high mountains?
I gotta get a new memory.
I gotta get a new memory system.
Oh, yes, friends, and I got one.
And now I can quit doing reruns
because this is a special show
about our cousins
in the primate world.
The apes.
The big feet.
The yeti.
What?
So far, no complaints.
Well, this is about our ancestors,
the yeti from outer space.
And, friends, it's an educational show.
I'm trying to tell you.
I'll be your monkey's uncle.
Get your sticking paws off me,
you damn dirty ape.
Do you want to touch my monkey?
I don't make monkeys.
I just train them.
No more monkey business.
No!
The Monkey Babies
Birds and the bees and the monkey babies.
I thought Sir Edmund Hillary proved that yeti
or the abominable snowmen don't exist.
That's true, but sometimes native superstitions are just as powerful as the ones that are in the wild.
There's also a scientific proof.
Thank God we can enjoy this pain.
Speaking of bears, now, recently,
two weeks ago, this bear photographer naturalist and his wife were eaten by bears.
And this week, squirrels invaded our house.
Our house has been...
I came downstairs this morning and found a large ratty squirrel.
Now, wait a minute.
With a Swiss Army knife.
I opened the door.
And he waddled slowly out.
Cleveland-aged squirrels.
Okay, man, I'm leaving.
A very well-fed squirrel waddled out.
Get that broom away from me. I'm leaving.
Actually, he was.
We later discovered that he had taken a bag of candy out of a purse or something.
And we still don't know where the rest of the bag is.
Dark chocolate and crystallized ginger.
You have to make sure you don't...
We found little black objects here and there around the house.
That's called squirrel poo-poo.
Is that what you call it?
Oh.
And if you infuse enough of that into your herbal teas, you will get the...
I thought those were smart pills.
Yeah, I thought those were smart pills.
You will get the well-flavored Navajo Plague Whey.
You know, a couple months back, I was on the air and I even said that the wild kingdom is in rebellion.
Yes.
Well, this has been said by...
The animals are smart and smarting up.
The animals are telling...
Hey, this is what they're going to say one day.
They're going to walk up to us and say,
You know how to build rockets?
Get the fuck out of here.
The squirrels are going to say that to us?
All of them.
Squirrels don't need rockets.
Look at how they propel themselves from branch to branch.
Humans, go back to Yeti laboratory.
Yeah, you humans, back out to the space.
Go back to the alien lab.
Back to the silver mines of ancient Atlantis where you belong.
Earth, back to Mars!
It must be true because, you know, there's no monkeys that can kind of talk.
Yes, there are.
There are baboons have a vocabulary of about 250 words and they sound weird as hell.
Their word for lion, for instance, is java and it sounds like...
But you can't teach a monkey to speak a language.
Well, now, that's arguable.
Coco the gorilla is a famous example.
That's all sign language.
Yeah, but that's still language.
But they are reflective of our human verbal language.
Understand my point.
There's no link between a human who can just blabber on and on forever and ever, take Dave,
and a monkey who can sort of blabber a little bit.
Well, monkeys can hand sign.
There's no links between the two.
We have to be implanted from outer space.
Well, we've all been implanted, but it has nothing to do with monkeys.
It has to do with superior sexual experience.
Or, no, it's not sexual experience.
It's kind of like the hell world, actually.
You'd think there'd be a few monkeys that could pick up a few English words and go,
Hey, man, throw me that fucking banana.
Oh, I think they would probably use that word, too.
You're thinking of apes and they can.
They'd probably say...
Throw me a fuck, you bananas.
They saw that movie Planet of the Apes, and they know what awaits them if we know that they can be trained to do it.
Yeah.
Let's take out the garbage of white tables.
...watching their TV screens.
The maintenance men thought it would be amusing to let them watch hours and hours of Planet of the Apes on DVD.
But something went wrong in that laboratory, didn't it, on the...
Well, the thing that disturbed me is that...
...Sar Cornelius...
...is Saturday afternoon.
Yes, my leader, Cornelius.
Great Caesar.
King of the apes.
Chaz.
Huh?
Chaz, you better watch you don't talk like Cornelius.
If you know what I'm saying.
Hey, man.
Ten minutes, you'll be smoking in hell.
Well, I mean, you know...
Hey, amigo.
It's bad enough what happened to the indigent peoples of this continent and so many others, actually.
We should make fun of short people.
And other planets.
But think what we do to the apes, dude.
What?
Well, that's what you do to the apes, Steve.
I mean, they still serve chimpanzee meat in Belgium and they're cutting their brains open and hooking their little rhesus monkey robot arms up to robot arms.
Ape...
Macaque brains operating robot arms.
Yes, they do.
They pluck them from the wilds.
I want one on my living room table.
Eating their jaundiced dingleberries and their happy fruits and their strange philosophies and put them in a science laboratory where they are cold-cutted and masturbated to oblivion.
I want my monkey brains well done.
And they'll be done for you.
To quote J.R. Bob Dobbs, actually he was ordering monkey brains in a Malaysian restaurant, but I want a monkey brain on my living room table that operates...
You didn't have monkey brains for Thanksgiving?
...a robot arm.
You didn't get the monkey brain dish at the Thanksgiving dinner?
No.
Oh.
Those are illegal now, man.
But that's still a delicious snack.
If I did have it, I sure wouldn't say it on the radio.
Your cat ought to do that point.
Looks like a Yeti convention.
You lie with the Yeti.
Seeing as how you know everything, what's the scoop on this Yeti stuff?
They're also called abominable snowmen.
They have feet that point backward, scream like a banshee, and are invisible.
Well, if they're invisible, how can anybody see a Yeti?
No one has Yeti.
Oh, come on.
Good evening.
Oh, look, Maggie.
What is that?
Do-de-ki-tron.
Do-de-ka-hee-tron.
He does.
I don't know what you're doing, but it's very strange and your father's trying to worry.
Ahhhhh!
Ahhhhhhhhhhh!
Ohhhhhh!
Aaaaah!
I work hard at my job, and I hope that by my efforts rendered faithfully over a period
of years, I'll move up through the corporate hierarchy to a position of security, power,
and prestige.
In order to improve my chances for advancement, I dress conservatively, keep myself well informed
in the arts and current events, hold popular opinions, and socialize in the best circles
with those who have influence.
But these efforts have been so far in vain.
I remain the Night Watchman.
The Grey Plannel 8.
What is death?
If I put the barrel of a gun against my forehead and pull the trigger,
what will happen?
Where will I go?
I wonder if expressions we have come casually to use when referring to death
actually reflect reality.
For example, the term,
bought the farm.
Could it be that when I die,
I will actually come into possession of a farm I've purchased with my own money?
Is it possible?
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Raise the...
And Norelpref.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Who did this mix in the background?
We don't know what Mitchie says.
Even the strongest have their moments of...
Lie with the Yeti.
I'm just... I'm fucking fatigued.
Yes, we lie with the Yeti, friends.
You've been hearing clips from all manner of places.
From ESO radio on WCSB Cleveland, of course,
with Lonesome Cowboy Dave, Professor Chaz,
the new Monet,
a mix called Monkey Man preceded that,
and lots of Norelpref mixes,
which will be throughout the show.
We had a little Evolution Control Committee clip
that's rather in keeping.
Yeah, baby, because we lie with the Yeti.
The titles of this show were by the El Queso All-Stars.
And, friends, this is going to be an El Queso All-Star and Yeti show,
number 929.
Yes, the Yeti.
Because, friends, we were brought, we, the so-called humans,
were brought from space by the Yeti.
Actually, the humans were invented as lab rats by the Yeti.
But 80 million years ago, they got out,
there was interbreeding, and the result was we, the subgenius.
And, yes, we lie with the Yeti.
So there will be tons of El Queso All-Stars.
In fact, they are working on a Yeti,
a Yeti opera about a Yeti named Rufus
and his journey to a final triumph over the conspiracy.
Friends, you are not going to believe the tales of Rufus the Yeti,
which follow.
Ah, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
I see it, but I hardly dare believe it.
You can believe it.
The Yeti have taken vengeance into their own hands.
We, the subjects, will take our revenge.
Good night, dear and interdependent friends.
I long not to see you again, sisters of El Queso All-Stars,
for you am a bread to my magic.
Under all circumstances,
theFreeCast has been temporarily stopped
To disappear in a flash of light
You can't imagine that it happened
But it happened to a yeti one night
Abducted, transported
But unanticipated
His vibration calculated a break
In the beam that held him against his will
But he remained still
We've read the situation
Then he showed his agitation
By jumping to his feet
And confronting his abductors
You guys aren't the exes
You bug-eyed motherfuckers
It was the greys
The alien slaves
The ones working for the pentagon
For six decades
This must have been a mothership
As he was hip deep in the creaks
He knew a little slip
Would cause him to sleep a long sleep
So he fixed his gaze
On the horde that confronted him
He cleared his throat
And then he spoke in their native tongue
I slayed greys for days
And ways to pay
When I played the game
That you didn't know I came here to play
You'll regret the delays
That you caused me
Cause greys are way too weak
To fight a yeti
Rufus took a stance
And began to breathe
His eyes turned red
And he began to weave
He made a noise
And sounded like a tiger's sneeze
And then the lights blew out
And the aliens screamed
Crimson eyes flashed in the dark
As he ripped apart his first victim
It didn't matter
If the splatter from the alien
Did ever whittle up into his presence
Cause he ripped them all to tatters
In a heartbeat
It was all over with
Rufus on the bridge
And turned to Troy
On the ship
Black space above
Green earth below
Which way should he go?
He didn't know about the aliens' control
So he put on his magic blindfold
His magic blindfold
Put it on and started spinning
Faster and faster
Reverting disaster
With a casual press
Against a panel or a button
He was just touching
What he needed to on accident
He didn't understand
The symbols or the consequences
The earth grew larger
As the ship came down
Rufus crashed land
And at the outskirts of town
Hey, any lender
You can walk away from
Rufus stepped out of the bushes
And he got out of sight
His cruelty grew
He knew the plan
He had well known
That inside wsbridge
It was true
That Kelly
This was Rufus
At my very best
In this world
Which he said
He was not
By equipment
Rufus
ológica
Who he was
R америку
Come on
AAAAAAAH! AAAAAAAH!
It is the cry of the Yeti! The Yeti!
Knob? Knob? Knob?
It's the dance of the Sacred Pumpkin, calling the demise due to all things pink.
It's the dance of the Sacred Pumpkin, Rufus doubled over and released his stink.
It's the dance of the sacred pumpkin
Rufus doubled over and released his sting
On the side of sand
Lost in a bad world
Like the fart of a time man
Rufus got the shovel and she dug the grave
He didn't give a crap for the shit that he gave to the people
The slave or the dwarf or the creep or the dumb on the street
They're all slackless and weak
But the dance in his feet and the beat from the pulsing pumpkin
Caught something alive from the pumpkins that died
In a circular trap until Rufus arrived
With his wits and his slack and the will and the balls
Nailing every last beat to the walls of the stall
In the shithouse they built that was fashioned of lies
And they couldn't wipe their asses, Rufus cut them down to size
No, no, they couldn't wipe their asses, Rufus cut them down to size
The wall is tidy, let's fight
And they were swirly, orly, thick and not just any trick
With a pork so Rufus had to exercise, he had to dance
And dance
It's the dance of a sacred pumpkin
Calling the demise just to all things good
Only a yeti could bring on such terror
When Rufus arrived at the tit of all trees
He was very alive
He was crawling with fleas
He was swarming with flies
There were scabs on his knees
But the look in his eyes said his life would not soon cease
He kept a bucket of disease that he would use to mark his trail
He walked it slower than a snail to buy his time half up on sand
And so when finally he reached that ancient tavernry of green
He held his sacred pumpkin high
And the Rufus screamed
And then a disco ball
Descended from the sky
His lapels grew long
And the fleas burst into song
Peach decked in glitter
And feathers the senders
That snooped and swirled
That rendered their ane to blenders
That rendered their rectums
And reduced the slack
That this brave yeti Rufus
Will fight to get back
And with the introduction of the fleas
The tit of all trees granted Rufus a nipple
And with a near instinctive ease
Rufus dropped to his knees and proceeded to suckle
And a vision then appeared in his mind
Of a world unconfined
Of the con and decline
Of the pink left behind
Of the slack that's combined
In a plan that's designed to make the gods knees buckle
There's a question that's taken
To make this vision come true
Twenty morning trials
My eyes have seen
Can't defeat
The choice to slow your hand
But for now
Take the last train out of town
Ple colleague help the prowler
Rufus took the last train out of town
He moved the Потом out of town
Let's get the last train out of town
Step forward on the right, step forward on the left
Step out on the right, lifting the bent left knee
By the right foot
Step back on the right, step forward on the left
Step back on the right
Rufus took the last train out of town
Yee-haw!
This song is magical
As magic as Doug Heating's act was gay
Rufus had watered for
He waded through a field of fresh toupees
He kept his mini nostrils closed
He would not smell the mayonnaise
He would not eat a single piece of cheese
Though he was hunted by his foes
He ordered pizza every day
His magic unicycle helped recombine his DNA
But Coldwood gave him chicken skin
So he would rarely bite that way
Rufus was a good boy, he was a good boy
He was a good boy, he was a good boy
And when he woke up in the morning
He was usually still high
And with his pumpkin brained and polished
Kissed the chicken's lips goodbye
To pay an AIDS
And artificial covering disgusting glaze
That's hiding us and smothering all the ways
That we could be discovering a way out of the maze
And end to all the buggery
The con's driving its pink caddy up your dirt road
You'll just watch TV and do what you're told
You don't even care that your soul's been sold
You're just not aware of the blue space mold
Or the powers that it has on the rulers of your land
And how they have both your balls in the palm of their hand
Way too...
Too to pay an AIDS
The whole damn world was too to pay an AIDS
So Rufus spent his idle days concocting all the many ways
That he would make the pink boys pay out
Come the day he got his way out
Of the senseless mental trap
That feeds its mindless zombies
And someday Rufus will come back
And give to pay an AIDS
A slap
And a kiss
And a bust
In the face
With a bridge
Ooh...
Way too...
To pay an AIDS
With a...
Too to pay an AIDS
Way too to pay an AIDS
Wow!
Too to pay an AIDS
Ooh...
Ruff
Ooh
to Chris
I love you so much.
The El Queso All-Stars,
dear friends of preview of Rufus the Yeti.
And you can learn more about the El Queso All-Stars
and download material from this website.
You lie with the Yeti, don't you?
Okay, here it is.
www.soundclick.com
slash bands
slash two, the numeral two,
slash
crotchlessleatherwheelchair.htm
crotchlessleatherwheelchair is the name that El Queso All-Stars also goes by.
So you can go to soundclick.com
and look for crotchlessleatherwheelchair.
I love you so much.
There must be something we can do about those monsters.
You know, I'm for going on a Yeti hunt.
No, it would only further arouse the Yeti.
Every.
Human.
Culture.
Has its creation myth,
its Garden of Eden,
Fall from Grace,
and Great Deluge.
All are tissues of lies,
but all are based on real events,
of which only Dob's revealed word
and scrupulous research in the forbidden sciences
can give an accurate picture.
Around 65 million years ago,
near the close of the Cretaceous era,
the Exist came from space
and planted on Earth
those mighty men of the Biotic,
the true covenant men of antiquity
who lived 999 years,
the Yeti.
Yeti, of course, is only a convenient term.
The proper scientific nomenclature
is Gigantopithecus correctus.
Yeti is what the Nepalese of the Himalayas call them,
and we find it more dignified
than the epithet Abominable Snowman
or the Native American Sasquatch,
which literally means raping demon.
We especially resent
the popular racist term Bigfoot,
which is not even particularly accurate
if a minority must be characterized
by the size of a physical feature.
Most people who have actually seen a Yeti
probably remember it less for its feet
than for other organs.
The scientific community,
in its infinite wisdom,
upon encountering ancient Yeti bone fragments,
announced the discovery,
quote-unquote,
of a giant prehistoric ape
called...
Gigantopithecus.
My friends, the Yeti,
were the Nephilim of the Old Testament,
the patriarchs and matriarchs of yore,
the giants of great stature
encountered by Cain east of Eden.
Those who came from on high,
who found the daughters of men
to be comely and mated with them,
bringing forth the Sarim,
the hairy ones,
or...
early...
the sons of Esau.
The biblical Nimrod and Goliath
were among these.
Giborim, the half-breed,
divine people.
But long before they invented man,
the Yeti were breeding dinosaurs
the way we breed dogs and turkeys.
Oh, our public schools still teach
evolution or creationism.
What we aren't told in conspiracy school
is that...
some of those so-called
Neanderthal skeletons are recent.
They date from last year,
and that Piltdown Man was no hoax,
but a recent genetic failure
that had to be hidden from the press
and mainstream scientists.
These facts, were the truth known,
would be sure proof
not only of ongoing interbreeding
between humans and Yeti,
but also of the existence
of an entire race
of Yeti.
Yetinsin half-breeds.
Us!
The subgenius race!
As well as the institutionalized genocide
of our kind
by the conspiracy.
Friends, the Yeti are all around you.
If you know what to look for,
you should be able to spot your fellow Yetinsini
among the purebred pink humans.
Whereas the pinks display bland,
barely mobile, smooth-veneered,
difficult-to-read features,
our mugs are overstatements,
with every emotion vividly portrayed as we talk.
We're self-parodies, granted,
but at least there's a self there to parody.
Compared to pinks,
who are all average,
many subgeniuses are brutish Neanderthals,
geeky goons, etc.
But better that than these emotionless,
contented, pampered, bovine, zombie,
pod people.
Yet they think we're funny.
Oh, they humor us.
Their smugness denies us
even the pleasure of seeing them jealous.
Only subconsciously do the pinks
bitterly envy our vitality.
Some of us buckle under from this iniquity
and turn hate-negative.
The heartier of us tend to be more magnanimous.
We can afford to be patient,
charitable, and generous
in our bestowals of condescension.
Why try to insult them?
They wouldn't get it anyway.
It is in the very bowels of the brain,
where an altogether different alchemical mix occurs,
that the yeti's descendant,
the subgenius,
still differs most from the human.
The humans would begrudge us this,
were they capable of knowing it.
But since most of us grow adept at mimicking them,
we have thus far been able to slip between the cracks of their knowledge.
Those humans who happen to stumble upon subgenius materials like this show
think it's all a joke.
Were they aware of us,
truly aware of what we represent,
they would hunt us down one and all and slay us,
and bury us in pits of quicklime.
That future generations might never again be tainted
by the subgenius gene.
The music in the background was by
Reverend Angry Larry,
automatic robot fish.
Praise Bob.
The readings from Revelation X,
the Bobapakraphon.
Thank you.
There are enough yeti outfits and supplies here to equip a small army.
We're all monkeys.
Think of us as brains with massive brains.
You're talking about unscanning subgenius.
Astronauts say it was,
the first unbaked unoctured гigos
created a cy chama
called the
Spencer Gary.
Hey look, Merry.
Oh, we'll never get a better deal, Harry.
He says, all we have to do is smoke this thing called prop, and Bob will justify our sins.
But what about forgiveness, Harry? Aren't we supposed to be forgiven for our sins?
I cannot do that. This island is not for me anymore.
Mary, he says, probably not. Where we'll be going? What do you think he means?
Probably to do the groceries, Harry. That's what they all mean.
Mary, he says we need to take action before the pleasure vessels come with the sex goddesses and destroy the universe.
Action? What action, Harry?
Oh, I can't talk anymore. I can't speak. I don't know.
Mary, got your pencil ready? We just have to write to...
Bob.
Bob?
Yeah, yeah, I know. P.O. Box 204206, Austin, Texas 78720.
Oh.
Mary, you speak Yeti, too?
Well, ha ha ha ha! But of course, dear. I've been sleeping with them.
Bob, my hero.
Like a monkey ready to be shot into space. Space monkey.
Oh, yes, friends. Mary the Hairy Yeti.
An edit by Self-Subs.
Players.
Get on it. What?
Oh, look, Maggie. What is that?
Dodecahedron. Dodecahedron.
Jesus. I don't know what you're doing, but it's very strange and your father's trying to worry.
The terrible snow creatures have come out of the high snows.
It's like, look, a picture of, um, J.R. Bob Dobbs.
He's like one of those weird Hindu saints.
It's live.
And he's got Monopoly money coming out of his nose. Just like we do.
I'm a general. You have to come back today.
Ay, campesinos, no puede ni español.
Um, um, um, um, um, um.
Que suele ser un bien.
Why is that vibrate? Are they ready to take everybody back now or just refund them or what?
I wish they would. That's what we've been waiting for, for them to take us back.
Sour sweat. You know what I mean? The sour smell of sweat. The urgent smell of too much to go. And, uh, being left behind.
Well, the smell of humans in general, I understand.
It's unpleasant to most non-human animals and creatures.
Well, I heard that Julia Robertson taught a orangutan how to wash her clothes or something.
I don't know if I got the right thing.
That's how it started in the Planet of the Apes series.
That was, that was how we got started.
They taught us how to wash clothes.
What if Jane Goodall went back in time and had, she would find out how she was taught how to wash clothes.
She would find out how she was taught how to wash clothes.
Like an orangutan.
The orangutan would teach her how to have secuval sex, too.
Giant, intelligent, super intelligent orangutan taught the early anthropologists and humans how to wash fruit.
And when they taught the first one, hundreds of monkeys on the other side of the island instantly learned at the same time.
Yeah, they, you know, any time you imitate washing your fruit, everybody will imitate you washing fruit.
What would you do with a brain if you had one?
That's what the new age is all about.
You know, I might have been, if I could conceive myself in time, I might be one of the first people who ever washed a meatball in a river.
And was, you know, watched and instantly eulogized by thousands of other parasites.
Well, thousands of years down the line, you'd be, yeah, the parasites in the publishing and music world, the scientific world, you'd be eulogized.
But at the time, you'd be just another monkey.
But like with most people, they way out of a book-
Fisherman, yeah.
There was no shitin'.
Trying to get out of this world.
Yeah.
Think about time…
For a while, I thought.
I have confidence.
Confidence by Norrell Preff.
Friends, and you can download lots of Norrell Preff from heavyconfetti.com.
Coming up, Dr. Mr. Sister and Le Mer.
Here's Bob One for A1 Slacks.
Double your trousers, double your legs with A1 Racers, tapers, and...
Hi, kids.
And remember, you can take A1 Slacks out of the country, but you can never wear them out.
Thank you, Bob.
What?
And now, back to our movie.
A1 Slacks.
I had to admit it.
Uh-huh.
And I live near San Francisco.
That's not true.
Well, I guess that about does it.
Goodbye.
Good evening.
I'm Adele Arakawa.
I'm Jim bitumen.
Nine News reporter Ginger Delgado has meth labs like that fellow.
Yes, Jim.
It's a job that is so dangerous, it could eventually explode, cause fires, or worse, cause life.
And because of that, he has decided to share his cancer.
He will not reveal Bob since he was 12, since 17.
I don't think there's any person who's interested in me.
Not really, but...
Why?
Because I'm brown no more.
Today, Bob is dying of his teeth.
In short, an explosion has ruined his life.
He now says the quick high he got was worth it.
You know, it's fun for a minute.
No one should see.
He wants to keep making the same fatal mistake.
And his meth lab's growing at an alarming rate.
Authorities in 31 drug labs.
The next year, this year.
Authorities say this year.
Then last year, here in Colorado.
The indiscipline .
All the doctors go the bomb.
Plan as little as possible.
Know youradenamnetie. huhuhuhuh huhuhuh
Finally, radiation percent.
It's gonna Сhsey lan-
C-shsey lan-
From the favorite movie Baldi hacer.
Slack, and now, a final El Queso All-Stars closer.
I'm gonna do it right.
He's suspended at a birthday party.
He's a flesh piñata.
Give me a mirror and a line of Lucille Ball's ashes.
The fashes have dashed my hopes of necrophilia.
By burning the butt, I've been yearning to fuck.
I've been down on my luck, jerking off to Buck Rogers.
And woman-fearing spandex camel toe.
The dirty hoe on that show turned little Gillard to a homo.
If my mustache could throw a sausage,
I would name it Jim J. Cole.
And I would name it Jim J. Cole.
It would be a movie star.
So far beyond the gayest me.
Far, far, and all, but no perversions.
But it takes its acting back to six.
The person you could meet
at a mighty admosy.
If my mustache could throw a mustache,
a kiddie who is watching match.
I'd name it Jim J. Cole at two.
It'd offer you and the stars
and make a god of Jamie Farr.
Oh my god. I'm gonna die.
Poor damn music.
True me.
It's a book.
Blackout, mindshot, looking at your face, pal.
Pass mile, park on, watch without a doubt.
Excess bleed, off course, adapter.
Over chest, roll the lock, bus transfer.
Roll it down the door, cause you can't find the answer.
Vigency beyond the limits of the frequency.
Living for the quest to contribute to delinquency.
Suck grinds, good times.
Dodging middle landmines.
Black eyes, moonshine.
Actresses, nature's lies.
We're to cross the ties of automation.
Lost creation, repressed apathy, total manipulation.
Tend of forger, disco, discord, poly, yester, clad.
Of rising, sat, leap, propaganda, Danny.
Break two into anti-glyphed and shifting into obsolete.
The sheezy now's their blood and species.
The sheezy's torn and reborn above the scorn of sin.
We're pandimensional, invisible.
We're psychic pimps.
Pushers of buttons that open and shut open.
Slap of a lion, my third, in his crimes of the night.
For solutions polluting the visions of minions of purvey and kings that would nay say the truth.
Blast my Several as you are.
The sweetest I will say that a task to this better king can be acquired only by 옮 and Drac4l3rf7n F personality more than his other conta Filter.
You fizmond baby很多事 ausgexploited Normalcemoscómo использовать Normalensescomo para purificar Normalcesconformatasvoke.
All of slept right now, grinding a landing function.
What varesexito
novel
With a drunken husband, she's a flesh piñata.
Like Alan Alda, if we ever hurt him, he's a flesh piñata.
Flesh piñata.
Like a cripple at recess, when he eats the meat, he's a flesh piñata.
Like a mouthy woman with a drunken husband, she's a flesh piñata.
Like Alan Alda, if we ever hurt him, he's a flesh piñata.
Flesh piñata.
You can beat off. You don't need to have another woman.
I don't want to be vulgar, but...
I don't want to be vulgar.
Take it easy, sister. One peep out of you and I'll drill you.
Please.
Get down on the floor behind that counter.
And don't move if you want to live.
Yes, sir.
I don't want to be vulgar.
The hairless monkey thing?
The hairless monkey?
Yes.
Hairless monkeys who came here from a distant land,
a distant world far beyond the fringes of the cosmos.
To an alien from outer space.
Looking for sharp items with long-sleeved logos.
Which titty ain't no different from anybody else's.
And big hooded sweaters.
No, no, no.
They're not looking for that.
They're looking for the gold of the alchemists.
What's the name of that thing again?
Gold? What do you say?
The alchemy.
The stone?
The philosopher.
They're looking for the philosopher's stone.
I want the gold, Ben, and the diamonds, and the map, and the girl.
The philosopher's stone.
And the treasure.
The holy grail, along with the blood of Christ.
Would you like to take a look?
Verified by the Institute of Irrational Science.
Oh, it's the creed.
I want the creed.
I want all of the creed.
Every bit of it.
No, it's all yours, my son.
Sit at my feet.
Ten minutes, you'll be smoking in hell.
Kiss my goatee foot.
Yes, boy.
Yes.
Kiss it.
Now raise your head up.
In ten minutes, you'll be fropping in hell.
We'll all be fropping in hell in ten minutes.
In Cleveland, Ohio, DNA level C.
I have pretty good fropping hell, Bob.
Hell, yeah.
Lower levels.
Hey, look, there's Bob Dylan.
He's not even dead yet.
Bye, Bob.
Nope.
But he's still walking around Cleveland begging for spare changes.
Spare, like, werewolf changes or blank-eyed stare changes.
All those philosophical insights.
Psychological changes you can go through when you've fallen to Earth from such a lofty place.
Get real, man.
Yeah.
Come on.
Listen to the music, man.
Get grounded, dude.
Let flow down the river, man.
Get on the stream, baby.
Get your head in the clouds and your feet on the pavement.
Flow down the stream.
Turn off your mind.
Relax.
None is the color and none is the number, dude.
Flow downstream.
The light builds on within you and, like, without you.
It is not dying.
Place the bowling ball on your lap.
Who are the brain police?
Cross it gently.
Yes, you shall make some yamma on this bowling game with you.
Some yamma?
Yes.
What will you do if the people you know...
A sacred and holy meditation on this bowling ball.
Inscribe with the words Brunswick and Cleveland's.
And the plastic that melted and the chromium, too.
Your tiny little finger shall fit in this bowling ball.
And you shall run down criminals, evildoers, falsifiers, and all of those.
Blasphemous!
With this bowling ball, you shall become a superhero.
The pins are your mind.
The bowling ball is Bob.
You are the pin, man.
Become one with the pins.
Now, roll.
Bob into your mind.
And knock down all the pins.
Strike!
Praise Bob.
Friends, you're listening to the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack.
You can get more information from www.subgenius.com.
You can email me, stang, at subgenius.com.
And if you need a physical...
You can email me at subgenius.com.
We've got plenty of those, too.
See the website.
Praise Bob.
Hail Connie.
This background music is automatic robot fish.
Reverend Angry Larry.
Worried about covering the lower half of your body?
Here's Bob One for A1 Slack.
Things go better with slacks and trousers.
Things go better with slacks.
Hi!
This is Bob One for A1 Slack.
This is Bob One.
And I wonder how many of our go-go-now-generation-action-man-on-compass realizes
how important it is to keep the lower half of your body covered
without disguising the fact that it is indeed the lower half of your body.
Well, there's nothing like a pair of trim-fitting A1 slacks.
They're better than skirts and a lot warmer, too.
Thank you, Bob.
You're welcome.
And now, back to our movie.
Looks like we're going to find more than we expected.
And, friends, yes.
That was the fire.
Fire sign theater.
Ancient fire sign theater recordings.
Some of you may be too young and little to know of the fire sign theater.
But it is they to whom we owe so very much in our blabbermouthitude.
And, in fact, when I say,
dear,
dear friends,
that's a little tip of the hat to our dear,
dear friends at the fire sign theater.
And I think I disagree with Chairman Bob.
I do agree with Chairman Bob.
That Chairman Bob can't be working.
I don't know.
I recall that Chairman Bob went that route.
Right?
Right.
I think the thing,
things,
the thing,
and I think some,
and I think, in essence,
that Chairman Bob can't be working while they're type alive to investors.
We've viewed and so forth.
But how to,
uh,
close,
down the law.
But now,
uh,
one final question,
if I could.
Uh,
anybody on the panel who'd want to address Chairman Bob?
no,
no.
Okay.
Attention.
All biotech personnel.
This is a biohazard alert.
Until further notice,
containment protocols are in effect.
Bob!
Bobby!
Dana, what's going on?
Sheriff Morse, they locked the doors.
Bob's inside.
Why lock the doors?
I don't know.
Who else is in there?
Just about everybody, I guess.
I'm sorry.
Bob! Bob!
I found the problem and there is no biohazard.
It was a false alarm.
You can unlock the doors and let everyone go home.
This is a non-event event.
The moron.
Back to the end.
Motherfuck you, Big and Flynn.
We are the university majors in Los Angeles, California,
who had our Harvard University deans come to teach us.
We'll not have you goddamn bitch kidnapping us, sticking us with needles.
The reason I did not, none of your goddamn business.
None of your goddamn business.
You didn't even hear a thing.
You have no sense using your goddamn needles.
And those goddamn old men who used to suck.
You baboon ass pussy motherfucker.
Had no business giving you nothing.
There's been no people or no buzz knowing that you are an animal.
None of your goddamn business.
And they've been listening for a long time.
You motherfucking baboon.
And here's the line, goddammit.
Licking on Doc's wick and we know he is a baboon.
We have studied him for years.
But listen bitch.
Stand your goddamn face.
The deal is hard goddamn.
Have me higher over you motherfucker.
Shut up.
I don't want you goddamn bastards to get rid of this whore.
She licked me between my sacred legs and I am Mrs.
The only reason I demand her death.
I need her death goddamn.
And they have her here at the crazy house.
Now you goddamn bitch.
I don't care who you think you know.
Just go along.
Just go along bitch.
Sit your ass down bitch.
Sit your ass down.
And you do not call people.
You said people.
You are an animal.
It is wrong for you goddamn bastards to have missed a goddamn bullet when you cut their tails off.
Because you and me.
And because you and me.
And left on these goddamn bastards of asses like you and me.
When they were born with monkey asses.
And when they take an x-ray of this bitch ass they'll know that it's a animal.
Now that's nothing to tell you bitch.
You didn't even understand.
You did not represent yourself with names.
That is how ignorant you are.
If you don't.
I am not a spy.
I have nothing to tell you bitch.
You went to the crazy house.
Said you were going as a student to the crazy house.
You went to the school.
You are abnormal because we have schools here.
In all the cities.
In all the suburban areas.
And other suburban areas.
But usually the same children are sent.
To a boarding care home.
To get away from you abnormal motherfuckers.
And you shouldn't have been in these suburban places.
Can you start talking about going to Harvard.
No I'm telling you.
No it's nothing.
We are graduates.
We have our choice.
And you should have had some goddamn Salvation Army things on.
You know your goddamn doctors.
Who are supposed to buy you motherfuckers things.
And send your goddamn life's ass clothes to the laundry.
You are not good on stable people who live at home.
Grabbing the clothes.
With a small ball of fluid and everything.
Did you hear what I said?
And this stands for all of these black people.
My name is on the social media.
I'm a social medicine.
I said our name.
You.
You slut.
What's up.
You haven't even been back yet.
You went to the crazy hospital.
Plunged there.
They sent you to the administration building.
With your baby animals.
To take a test.
You were plunged there.
No I'm talking about you.
You're not psychoanalyzed.
And nobody ever baptized you.
You are a kid younger.
A child molester.
You're so young.
And I saw you on the street.
I hate the black-headed bastards.
And to put my name up there.
You don't gotta look at me like that.
Cause you bastards are gonna die.
You motherfuckers are all right.
But the chin of this man is on the go.
And for the life of you kids of mine.
Getting in the poison.
You gonna do like a bitch.
And motherfuckers guys.
Is it here.
It's up back there.
Did you hear what I said?
You.
Goddamn false teeth ass motherfucker.
With your real ass.
You got a wig wearing.
You got a wig on your goddamn head.
You are a ugly motherfucker without somebody making a wig for your fucking head.
They calling you beautiful.
Shit.
Look at your god damn crooked teeth.
Tell me about something that you.
It's nothing to tell.
You mother fucker.
If you could.
If you think sucking dick and being fucked in your baboon pussy ass was making you graduate.
You are goddamn lying.
No, motherfucker, that's how I'm expected, you goddamn cocksucker.
And I'm asking God to damn you and any motherfucker like you
licking between women's legs and their blessed wounds, motherfucker.
Not an animal's cock.
Well, the goddamn doctors made an oath
not to take no motherfuckers in those hospitals
and fuck no goddamn baboons and things
and sit around in no goddamn circle
like you motherfuckers was in the jungle.
You weren't to have been brought here to a civilized nation.
And them motherfuckers who fucked your ass
and them motherfuckers looking like them were cursed.
That's why God let them look like them
when they come out of the goddamn fur.
Because baboons have their own female species.
By MC 900-foot Jesus.
Praise Bob.