There is nothing wrong with the subgenius hour of slack.
Stupid, stupid is there. Large, polluting, the time-space continuum with J.R. Bob Dobson!
You send a dollar to the church, and the subgenius, the old boss, one, four, oh, oh, oh.
And every of my days have I spoken of it then, for my every utterance is a lie, including this very one you hear.
I am the last remaining homo correctus. I am a goddamn man of the future.
I'm 23 feet tall and I have 13 rows of teeth.
My physical type cannot be classified by science.
I communicate without wires or strength.
I am a fishbowl.
I am a bird.
I am a trilateralist.
I am a gold rush.
You will get annoyed.
Sex, money, Bob.
You will get sex.
A subliminal message brought to you by the UK Subliminal Message Corporation.
Sex, money, Bob.
These three concepts will always be in your mind.
Yes, this is a continuation of it.
Close.
The doctor says,
God, press this.
Money, Bob.
These three concepts will always be in your mind.
Sex, money, Bob.
Yes, this is a continuation of it.
Now if we do an Ask Dr. Howell session later on today,
people will need to write their questions down on little sheets of paper.
That's the way it's normally done, but if in the absence of little sheets of paper
we could have the direct question and answer.
I prefer the little sheets of paper because that provides a necessary remove,
allows the shy to express themselves more vigorously.
Anyway, it's on the docket.
It is scheduled for today.
And also scheduled for today, the gland escaping and acubiting,
the other important subgenius acts which are to be performed here on July 3rd.
And don't forget the Quijibo snooty beer and wife swapping party
at 5 o'clock at Hydra Station.
That's right.
Oddly enough, I believe...
I believe that we'll see a lot more subgeniuses up there at the Hydra Station
or Quijibo Station than we see here now.
Because we're not giving away free beer or snooty wives.
No, they're not free.
They're with snooty wives.
It's that boy, Papa.
That one that keeps following me.
What do you want?
I live here now.
I thought if your girl gave me so much eye back there,
I might return some of it.
What I gave you the other day was a looker indignation for what I've seen you do.
It was you give me the eye.
You should have seen him, Papi.
Look me up and down.
I started my own church.
I'm gonna be preaching it on the streets.
You can't leave me alone, can you, boy?
I didn't ask you to come here.
I ain't asking you to hang around.
What the hell kind of a preacher are you?
I'm asking you not to see if you can save my soul.
Goddamn Jesus hog.
I'm going to come around with pieces of paper if you have questions for Dr. Howe.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Yes, Ask Dr. Howe Show is done that way.
You write down pieces of questions and then usually if we are going to have any pretense of authenticity,
someone else reads them to me.
That would be you.
Reverend Stang or perhaps even Princess Wee Ardo would care to be the one who attempts to decipher the snaky labyrinth of subgenius orthography.
Not everyone writes clearly, but we will attempt to give a clear answer however tangled the query which is submitted.
Mr. Dot.
Nom Nom.
The
Adler
Adler.
large asset. The large who made that little cut. And now, friends, Ask Dr. Howell is coming up,
but first we have some sexy stuff. I hope you don't mind. It starts with Or Kill Me Radio.
Almost every X-Day, the great entertainer DJ Shaver sets up his mix boards and a transmitter
at the Brushwood Campground, and long into the night, broadcasts within the legal five-mile or
so radius anything he wants. And much of it is from his huge collection of Bulldottom music,
but he also loves to grab random subgenii and put them in front of a microphone,
and that's all great, but one thing always befuddled me until now. Let us return to 12X
D-Day.
12X D-Day, live in the past.
What's another thing I don't understand about Or Kill Me Radio?
Why would somebody go to a campground to listen to the radio? Why would somebody go to a campground
to watch a drive-in movie, for that matter? Well, because it's raining, that's one reason.
When you're driving to the store, when you leave the campground or return to it,
you go to the store, you're listening to the radio, see?
Well, all we're supposed to do is freaking camp.
No, you're supposed to run around half-naked and do crazy stunts for Bob and, you know,
do homemade weapons and funny costumes and get real drunk and hurt yourself and get a Bobby Award
and tell all your friends about it and your friends all go, I'm going to check out subgenius.com
right now. I did, and look what happened to me. Princess Wee and I were driving around
Brushwood one night at X-Day in the pouring rain and tuned into Or Kill Me Radio.
We heard people, young ladies, saying such salacious things and making such sexy promises
that I could scarcely believe my ears, and so I struggled to turn on my portable recorder,
but was a hair late. This is going out across Amish land.
I was like, damn it, I missed the hot part. There was just a girl on X-Day or Kill Me Radio
talking about, come on over here and I'll suck your penis.
She actually did. I just heard that. Those very words came out of that girl.
Was that Reverend Gilda Valerie?
She wanted to do something funner.
Yeah.
Damn, we missed it.
Yeah, we did.
So there is a reason to listen to X-Day Radio.
I know.
I mean, it was just like one second ago.
I've just been thinking, why would anybody listen to X-Day Radio when they're at the
camp out?
And I turned it on and there was this amazing pornographic, well, I wouldn't be able to
play it on an hour of slack anyway. Not even a smidgen of it. It was so steamy.
Oh, you could have played it on one of your online X-rated shows.
Yeah, I know, but you have to. Right. That's true. I wish I'd recorded it.
I wish I was fast.
I wish I was faster than draw. I wish I hadn't failed.
It's a Maryland number. No, how can they rate me by knowing my phone number? Anyway, no,
my phone number is 379-4532. If you have heard me tonight, please text me. You can't
call me because I don't respond to calls.
I don't recognize the number, but you can text me.
It's the radio station.
It is?
Yeah.
You can't hear me.
Hi, I'm talking.
Sit in my face, Stevie Nicks by The Rotters.
90.3 FM.
How very strange.
Oh, by the way, last night, folks, you may not have tried this yet, but there's a,
there's a, there's a, there's a, there's a, there's a, there's a, there's a, there's a,
there's a subgenius radio station that only happens during Brushwood or Kill Me Radio,
90.3 FM.
If you drive into town, you probably won't be able to hear it, but here on the campground,
it's quite clear.
Now, yesterday, I asked, I posed this question.
Why the hell would anybody go to a campground to listen to the radio?
Although I'm sitting here saying this at the campground for the radio, but last night,
we turned it on.
As we were driving around to inform people that the drive-in had been moved, we turned
on the radio, and I heard one of the new reverends who's come here for the first time, Reverend
Dildo Valerie, who had earlier been claiming that things should be funner.
I had to explain to her that this was an impromptu party of old friends, and she just didn't
know anybody, but I heard her on the radio say, if you come up to the radio station,
we'll suck your penis.
And man, you should have seen old Ivan Stango hand over feet, gosh, guttling down to that
radio station.
She gave her phone number.
Well, Princess, we and I were both listening to this.
I immediately grabbed my little recorder, you know, and said, God, why do these things
take so long to start up?
And by then, DJ Shaver had cut some funny musical thing, but every time a song would
end, he'd put these two new subgenius girls on who really wanted some business.
They didn't bring their own libations, and they were willing to promise anything, which
that's a subgeniously thing to do.
If a subgenius girl says, I'll blow you if you'll bring me beer, that don't expect necessarily
the blowjob.
By the way, on page two of your brochure, you'll find directions to the nearest liquor
store in glorious black and white.
Okay.
So do tune in, especially if you're horny kids or alone, tune in or kill me radio, and
you might hear an offer like that.
They were giving out their phone numbers and email addresses, Facebook, and these were
cute ladies, too.
We did, in fact, drive by the radio station immediately after hearing that and peeked
in and saw them.
Were you one of the promisers?
Right.
Okay.
How long was your broadcast?
Does the offer still hold?
That's...
Did they go on for hours doing that?
I don't know, because we stopped at Doc Frop's camp to let people know that the drive-in
had been moved to the studio, and then we never left.
That's like an elf's or a gnome's secret area.
Where you're...
If you pass through the stones into that camp, you'll come out, but it may be 20 years later
and all your friends are dead.
So just be careful.
Be aware of that.
Yes.
Anyway, friends, the long and short of it is that the questionable ladies, mainly Dildo
Valerie and Reverend Bunny Day, since X-Day, have decided to start their own radio show.
Radio in Tarot Bang.
And they did.
And you can hear the podcasts at...
Get that pencil.
RevBunnyDay.com slash blog.
Bunny Day sounds like French for good idea, but it's spelled B-U-N-N-Y-D-A-Y.
What follows is an excerpt from their first episode.
All right.
Here's the question that somebody wanted to ask me.
I'll listen to the question.
And Dildo Valerie, they said,
Dear Bunny Day and Dildo Valerie,
Will I be able to avoid having sex my whole life?
I am 17, I am straight, and many girls think I'm attractive.
One of my female friends gave me a list of reasons why I'm attractive.
I know that I'm good looking, but I don't want to have sex.
I think it is just weird getting naked with a girl, and I view the whole act of sex as
weird and primitive.
Plus, she would probably laugh at me when she sees me naked.
Because I have a penis, and it is large.
I hate how penises look.
The problem is that while I want to avoid sex, I can't stand the thought of being alone my
whole life.
I want to have someone to be there with me, laying next to me in bed with me, keeping
me warm on cold nights.
No matter how stupid that may sound, that is what I think.
Obviously, if I'm sleeping with a girl like that, I would be having sex with her.
You just don't sleep with someone like that and not have sex with them.
Okay, the answer to your question is that yes, you can go.
You can go your whole life without having sex.
And you probably should, because you're, you have...
Asexual.
It's called asexual.
You have asexual.
But you can't go your whole life without having sex with me, because I will get to everyone
eventually.
Leigh-Anne, next question.
And also, a lot of girls do not like sex.
Like, maybe.
So, you can just lay next to them.
Lay next to them all night and think about how cuddly you are.
Cuddly.
You should get some stuffed animals, because stuffed animals are really soft and fluffy.
And you're wrong, because penises are really beautiful.
Don't you want to put it in your mouth?
He doesn't want to put his own penis in his mouth.
He wants to put other people's penises in his mouth.
He should date a tranny.
Yeah, he should date a tranny.
Me and K*** were talking about dating trannies just a couple hours ago.
We both want to date trannies.
Opposite trannies.
I...
Well, I have the hots for, like, everybody.
Let's put pictures of your boobs on the podcast.
Boobs.
On the ink computer.
Hey.
Come here, come here, come here.
He just said...
Shut the f*** up.
You're being an asshole.
I don't know the answer.
I don't know the answer to the login questions of y'all.
That one's fun.
We should smoke more in our lives.
Oh, you can put it in all my...
All of them.
Oh, yeah.
Put it in every one.
Bunny Day and Dildo Valerie.
Radio Interrobang.
Revbunnyday.com
Incidentally, I should mention that the costumes these gals wore to the 12X Day X Costume Ball...
They were both delightfully stark naked, but for a string.
A piece of twine.
That was attached by duct tape to the belly button of one and then to the cooter of the other.
An umbilical cord.
They came as a young mother and newborn fully grown up daughter.
It was actually pretty hot.
And death shall have no dominion.
No more shall gulls cry in their ears or waves break loud on the seashore.
Where blue a flower may flower no more.
Lift its head to the blows of the rain.
Though they go mad and dead as nails.
Heads of the characters hammer through daisies.
Break in the sun till the sun breaks down.
And death shall have no dominion.
And here is Priestess Pisces.
I was just looking and we have lots of questions.
Lots of questions.
And more.
Which will be answered.
Job lots of questions.
Now, so you know how fortunate you all are.
And can appreciate the fact that you are all here.
And can appreciate the singular mark of fortunes favor upon you.
I just like to say that usually in my act people give me money with these questions.
In fact that's how I put three squares on the table.
And pay the landlord.
And keep from staring old man Stoavation in the face.
Yes sir.
But in this instance the questions are freely asked.
And no emolument or premium is required.
And no reward is awarded to me.
No pourboire will I accept.
Well that's not necessarily true.
If you choose to pay I will certainly accept.
But for the most part consider the ask Dr. Hal fee to be prepaid with your registration fee.
And your other tithes and mathems unto Bob.
So we're still awaiting the magical hour of four o'clock.
And coming up heavily on the clock.
And when we do we're going to lead with the old haymaker.
And throw the first punch in the free for all battle for existence.
Otherwise known as the ask Dr. Hal show.
Thank you.
Have you anything to say in your defense?
I mean your conduct in relation to your cloth.
In relation to your church.
Your licentious behavior.
Your drinking.
Your going with women.
During the time that I've been here you've tried to teach me the confession of my sins.
And your lies.
That is good for the soul.
Well.
You also removed all temptation from among us so that there's no chance of any sin here.
I've merely tried to put that right.
When I go to confession I don't offer God small sins.
Petties, squabbles, jealousies.
I offer him sins worth forgiving.
How dare you blaspheme.
God would never bless someone so steeped in sin with such a gift.
It must come from the devil.
The devil.
Who knows.
I only know I have this power.
I have always had it.
I can feel it burning within me.
Driving me on.
It is here inside me.
It is in my hands.
And I warn you.
I warn you all.
That I Grigory Efimovich Rasputin intend to use it.
The power is mine.
And I shall use it as I please.
Sin is a trick on Bobs.
Sin ain't on my books.
Why don't you and I switch places Stang?
We'll accept them.
Are you taking these?
Do they go in a pitcher?
They're in my boots.
They're going in my breast.
They usually go in a special pitcher but they're going between Priestess Pisces breasts this time.
Yes we're piping it in.
We're uh, we're going in a special pitcher.
Making it up as we go along.
But it is a version of that well known trope.
The Ask Dr. Hal show.
We'll get to that in a moment.
For now let's hope that you're all enjoying this special historical moment at 12 X Day.
And have made adequate preparation for the end of the old and the beginning of the new.
Are there any more questions?
Only one hour for the beer tasting eh?
Yes.
I don't know.
Should we move Ask Dr. Hal forward 10 minutes?
Because that will make more room for the bull dada auction.
And more room in my bra.
I say why not.
Questions are still being selected and collected.
They will go between Pisces breasts.
But now who's going to ask the questions?
It can't be me.
I have to give the answers.
Um, I could if you want.
Very well.
Let us begin.
But shall we change places here to do it?
This works just fine because I have trouble sitting on that in this skirt.
Alright then.
Let's begin the Ask Dr. Hal.
Because as I said,
sooner begun, sooner ended.
So the first one I pulled...
Oh.
Goodness.
The first question was memorable already?
Why, there was an emolument.
You know, in the show,
if I get an exceptionally generous one,
I do what we call a bardic recitation.
I erupt in some kind of poem.
The bigger the bill, the longer the poem.
I just got 10 bucks.
So I'll do a poem sometime.
Not immediately because I have a question to answer.
The question is,
Dr. Hal,
how would you punctuate the following sentence?
Alright.
Buffalo, buffalo, buffalo, buffalo, buffalo, buffalo, buffalo.
That is, first of all, a sentence.
Let me point out that it is a sentence.
I'm sure many of you have heard it.
Many of you are familiar with the works of Dr. Steven Pinker.
His works on the development of human language.
The Language Instinct is one of his most famous books.
In it, he shows,
and I would say proves,
that such things as grammar and syntax
are not the arbitrary constructions
of grammarians
or people with too little time on their hands,
but the way language naturally occurs
and naturally falls
into the hard wiring
of the human mind.
And that is,
sentence structure is a given.
And even in weird languages
like Japanese,
they still do it, they just do it backwards.
But they do it in the same way.
And Professor Pinker has proved this
with the sentence just quoted by
Priestess Pisces.
That sentence I will now repeat again.
Buffalo, buffalo, buffalo, buffalo, buffalo, buffalo, buffalo.
Sentence structure automatically
imposes itself
on this sentence
and to punctuate it
maybe brings the
meaning out.
We don't have forever.
And I will now explain the meaning of the sentence.
Everyone knows what a buffalo is.
It's a large
graminivorous ruminant
with two horns and a big
frizzy head.
The meat animal of the
extinct Sioux and Cheyenne
Indians and so forth and so on.
This large animal
of buffalo exists
in the endless plains
or did at one time of our
country, the United States.
But for purposes of supposition
we're going to say some of these buffalo
live in Buffalo, New York.
Therefore they are
Buffalo, Buffalo.
And the first two words of our sentence.
They are the subject of the sentence.
Now we have to go a little bit
farther and ideally a little bit faster
since I see some of you nodding off.
We come to the active part
of the sentence. The verb.
The verb to buffalo.
Which we in the subgenius know well.
Yes we do. It means to swindle, to con,
to put something over.
If you are buffaloed, you've been swindled.
Therefore buffalo from Buffalo, New York
buffalo somebody.
Who do they buffalo?
Well the sad fact is just as in
most ghettos the crime
is committed by the people in the
ghettos against each other.
These buffalo, buffalo from
Buffalo, New York who buffalo others
actually buffalo other buffaloes.
This is the victim and the
direct object of the sentence.
Buffalo, buffalo.
Buffalo.
What do they, who do they buffalo?
They buffalo other buffaloes from
Buffalo, New York. Yes.
Buffalo is a plural as well as a singular.
Buffalo, buffalo. Buffalo.
Buffalo, buffalo.
But what
kind of other buffalo
from Buffalo, New York do they
buffalo? Well the kind
that they can buffalo.
The kind that buffalo,
buffalo, buffalo.
You see? You get it? You see?
So it's like buffalo,
buffalo, buffalo,
buffalo.
Right? Right? I dig it.
Now curiously enough
now that I've explained it,
this sentence requires
no punctuation whatsoever
as it is neat, concise,
to the point, and without
clauses or any
other additions. Let's go on quickly
to our next question. Dr. Howell, that was so
impressive that I'm presenting you
with the
wasp attractant.
Oh yes. This was sent to us by
some crazy person.
To those who weren't here yesterday,
the amusing thing about
it, it won't be so amusing
if a cloud of yellow jackets appears,
but the same person sent us a little
package of clear yellow
jacket attractant that
came in the envelope.
Obviously someone had a little bit of mischief
in mind, but Reverend Stang
determined that no one would
bring that plastic packet of
yellow jacket attractant to
Ex Day. However, no one can tell for
sure whether someone didn't
pick it up and bring it, I would say
in passing. Anyway,
let's hurry up and answer another
question. Dr.
Howell, how can I defend myself
from the idiocracy?
Well, how can you defend yourself?
They come at you from all sides. They come at
you with knives. They come at you with guns.
They come at you with disrespectful
comments and
things which damage your
dignity and your sense of self,
your amour-propre.
Can you deflect
these slings and arrows
by wearing thicker and thicker armor?
Well, if you were, you might end
up as an immobile statue
encased in glittering
steel and safe, but
unable to move. The fact is,
for maneuverability,
for movement, which is more
valuable than protection, you need
to give up a little bit of protection.
Movement is in itself protection,
and if you can bob and
weave, if you can dodge
and duck, then you
have something better than armor.
You have the potential, the
kinetic possibility of being elsewhere
than the place
the bullet, the arrow,
the catapult, bolt,
the crossbow bolt, or the, um,
oh no, oh my,
well, we're going to introduce another
Dr. Hal tradition here.
Anyway,
the best way to protect yourself is to keep
on your feet, to be nimble.
Don't hunker down in your
fortress, because as
General George Patton said,
fixed fortifications
are a monument to the stupidity
of man. If you can overcome
mountain ranges and continents,
you can overcome forts,
fortresses and redouts, and you can
overcome the individual who
thinks he's going to be a
survivalist and do it all on his own.
That guy is the first guy
to fall when things
change. Folks, every now and then,
in the Ask Dr. Hal show,
we have a little ritual
which we perform, and that is
if you ask a question which we consider
an exceptionally good one,
we pour you a free shot
of Fernet Branca,
the miracle liquid. Oh,
it's a miracle. Why anyone would drink it?
But it's the subject of its own
cult, and I think whoever
asked the buffalo question already
deserves a shot and should come up
and drink the shot.
So please do,
and while you do, we'll answer another
question, just to keep this thing
rolling further on.
This one also comes with a little bit
of cash. Oh, how that is
elevated, progressive, and correct.
And the question is,
Dr. Hal. Yes?
What?
Yes, that's what it says.
Well, what is
that which
exists but is not
known? And what,
written with a question
mark, is interrogative
and is a question?
The question is, what
is that which exists and
is not known?
The sensory apparatus
of humanity is
only capable of bringing in
a certain amount of information, and
then we also rely on the
neosphere, the
extrasomatic
load
that we have
laboriously constructed, like
an anthill or
a termite mound. Around
this are human
civilization. Or as
the Roman writer
Terence wrote,
exige monumentum requere
circumspeci. If you want to see
a monument, just look around.
Because it's rather
hard not to
find the what.
And if you can avoid it,
then maybe you can find
something even better. Which,
as you focus on it, is
clearly the which and not
the what.
One more, Pisces, please.
Okay, one more. Let's see.
More
trying to read. It's really long, I'm sorry.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
If, as Pisces mentioned yesterday on the
Live Hour of Slack, that the auditory emanations
of a female in pain are similar to the
female in orgasm, what does that
tell us about the sacred subgenius sacrament
of sex hurt?
Well, it says that
this female, whether
in orgasm or in
pain, needs the assistance
of a subgenius.
And therefore,
subgeniuses should always be
ready when these telltale
sounds are heard to
come rushing to the
assistance of the afflicted
or orgasmic individual.
I know none of you
will falter or fail
in this sacred trust.
There are lots, we have lots
of more questions, but this one... Well, keep shoveling
at them because... This one is pretty blatant,
which is... Blatant? Nothing's
too blatant. Dr. Howe! Yes?
What the fuck are we doing here in this cold
weather?
They've
said...
Somebody said that...
What happened to that bottle of Fernet?
We're looking
for suitable drinking cups.
Ah, yes, that's good. You sure can't
swill it out of the bottle. You might want to drink it out of the cap
because some people think the
fewer drops of that you drink,
the better. I'm sorry, please remind
me of the question very quickly one more time.
What the fuck are we doing here in this cold
weather? Yes. It has been
said that the person who
repeats the same thing over and over again and
gets the same result, which is not the
desired...
result, is a broken person
or a crazy person.
But I say unto you
that this is potentially
a wise person.
Because sometimes you need to hammer, hammer,
hammer on that hard
road of discovery to
receive what reward one
can get from intellection.
Or to put it a different way,
if the fool will persist in
his folly, he will become
wise. Therefore,
it is my ruling here that you are
all here because you are on
route to becoming wise
guys and gals.
Well, there's also the
fact that we... I mean,
we could have these in a hotel
like a sci-fi
convention or a comic book
convention. Hey, that would be fun.
The showers run forever.
That's all it is.
You know, the fact that we have to
survive this brutal
weather, it bonds us, it brings
us together. Better to go off into
a remote wilderness
to do what we do.
Alright.
How about that Fernet Branca, huh?
Not for nothing is it called the
miracle liquid. Let's put the bottle right up
on the table as a reminder
of the reward for asking a good question.
Yes.
Let's answer another one quickly.
I cannot even hardly read this, so I'm going to read
what I think it says, and if I'm wrong, then that's their fault.
You can also hand it to me. What are your
favorite topless celebrity and why?
I'm not sure that's... Favorite
topless celebrities.
That's an interesting one. Let me see if that
is what it says. My favorite...
Tipples. Tipples?
Tipples.
Tipples? T-I-P-P-L-E-S
Tipples, which according to the
drink are... according to the
dictionary are drinks, the forms of drinks.
But then what does it say?
Tipples...
And what are these next
three lines?
And what?
Tipples... This is a bracket,
a parenthesis, and an end parenthesis.
Oh, alcohol. Alcohol.
What are your favorite tipples and why?
Well, my favorite ones are
all the ones that the doctors
won't allow me to have. Yeah, the doctors.
Those medicos, they've really got
it against me. The ones that I
long for
are the ones that I'm just
not well suited in my
dotage to drink. Rum,
for example. Delicious
rum. Rum, rum, rum. It's mostly
sugar. Can't drink it. But I
sure like it. Yep.
My favorite ones may be the ones
I can't drink. The ones heavily
freighted and weighted
with nature's perfect food,
sugar. But
that's... You know, I used to like to drink
white Russians because
of that movie, because I had a
girlfriend who liked that movie where
everybody drank white Russians. And sure, why not?
I drank those. But
now I have to
drink the more purely
alcoholic concoctions.
Vodka and whiskey neat.
Of course, it does say in the old
book, take a little wine for thy
stomach's sake. And since I would
hardly want to slight
my abdomen, I do that
too. Okay.
The next question is, how is
babby formed?
How is babby? How is babby
formed?
Babby. Yes, babby.
Babby in his mama's
womb. Well, you know,
a long time ago,
not so long as we measure
time, they used to think that
ontogeny recapitulated phylogeny.
And that
was a very satisfying
explanation. And like most satisfying
explanations, completely erroneous
as to
whether the
scientific
documents in question were
deliberately falsified.
I think the jury may be out on that
because once you stare through
a microscope for so long,
your waters start
to eye, you know.
And then
you realize you might be drawing
structures which you really think
are there, and by gosh, ought to be there,
but what do you know, other more
keen-eyed, eager beaver
scientists can't see them, and they
will rake you over the
coracal coals.
So this is indeed
what happened
in the case of the great creator
of art forms in nature,
and his
ontogeny recapitulates phylogeny
theory. It was thought that
in the womb, Babby went
through early evolutionary stages.
At one time having the gills
of a fish and the tail of a reptile.
And it's true, but that's not
because it's going through evolutionary stages
ontogenetically.
But because,
folks, we are
that reptile. We are
that fish. Those are just parts of
us that are developing in
the brew, in the stew
that you get when you make
a humi like me and you.
And
Babby is formed
very elegantly in most cases,
except some of those
who come out not
losing and still able to be
using their reptilian
or fishy adornments.
And I've known some of those folks
out there. The nicest
folks you'll ever meet.
Priestess fishy there.
And speaking of
origins of things,
the next question is, Dr. Howell,
what are the origins of Dada?
Dada.
Well, Dada occurred
when a bunch of people
got together and decided society
was too stodgy and needed
to be lit up and stood up
on its end and hollered at
and slapped several times and hit
in the kisser with a wet fish.
And at that time when everybody
had to wear collar buttons,
stays, silk hats,
and waxed mustaches,
things certainly were uptight and
they did need that
pisces wallop. But
ever since, everything's become
Dada. And so now
people try vainly
for a refuge
from the avalanche of
meaningless surrealism
which falls upon us from
every direction, largely because
of poor planning and
that old bugaboo
human pig ignorance.
And yet, if we can
locate and center upon
the stodginess, then
we can still produce
meaningful Dada.
Rather to say, meaningfully
meaningless Dada
which would delight the
heart of Alfred Jari,
himself.
Reverend New Monet coined a word
for the crappy
fake surrealism
that's used in TV commercials
and things now.
Surreanality.
Mmm, sounds painful.
I don't know if I'm pronouncing it right, but I think
it's Surreanality.
That is loosely connected to the next question.
Well that's good, and I see
Princess Wee is coming up with a
vessel from which the
postulants can drink their
coffee.
I think that's a good question.
Since the idiocracy
and the singularity are perpetually
canceling each other out,
will computers eventually become stupid enough
to compete with human or yeti foolishness?
Those computers will fall by
the wayside and be
judged to be a human
artifact by the remaining
purified level of computers
who will be on their own.
Just because the singularity
has occurred doesn't mean they will
take all computer garbage
in unto themselves
as anything more than a
small and rarely consulted
file of historical memory.
Okay.
Let me double check, but I think
we only have one more. Hold on.
Very good. Then I'll do the poem.
And then we can start getting ready for the
fabulous slack auction
which is going to occur right here
on the stage. The Bulldada auction.
You don't want to miss this, folks.
But we still have one question left in the air.
Ask Dr. Halstow.
And the querent inquires,
who put the queer in query?
Who put the queer in query?
That's a very good one.
You see, most people
say query, but
you can say query. That is one of the
pronunciations that the dictionary
offers. Now,
on the other hand, the word
queer
has always meant
non-standard or
non-usual. It is seized
and run as
a guide on by the
militant queers
and transgendered
pansexuals,
transsexuals, and so forth.
But they are
taking on themselves
the glory of
anomalousness.
To others, anything
which is out of order
is suspect.
Like the famous story
of the Greek tyrant
gave the answer for
control of the populace.
When you see stocks that are higher than the other stocks,
you chop them off.
And then you have even
stocks. Now, who put the queer
in query?
More of those folks I was talking about
early. We call them jailers
because they want to jail
you, to confine you in categories
and make you ashamed
for transcending your
categories or even
reaching out of
autism far enough to reach
the medicine cabinet or the
light switch. Well, thank you ladies and
gentlemen. This seems to wrap up our...
Oh, you have one more? One more. It was a
last-minute entry by
a beautiful woman. I couldn't really
say anything else about it.
We say we're going to show the last
question, but then there's another one.
This is truly the last question. It was a last-minute
entry by a beautiful woman.
And the question is,
Dr. Howell, what is hip?
What is hip?
Yeah. Oh, what is
hip?
Didn't we have that one before?
I think we've had it before. I've certainly had it before.
And I've had it with that question. But
you'll never get
hip if you want Dr. Howell
or somebody else to define it for
you. You've got to be out there making
that large, embarrassing,
flagrant example on your own.
You won't necessarily
be hip, but you certainly won't be
if you don't try it. But
hip, which originally
derived from the 1940s,
HEP, or
being a HEP cat, a cat
who was HEP or
in line, or in a line of
understanding to something that was going on,
was ripped off
by the intellectual community
from where they get all their ideas, the black
community, the community of
black musicians.
And then, since white people are
thin-blooded, they wouldn't even
continue to pronounce the word
HEP with its
soft E, but had to make it HIP
just the way a lot of people
want to borrow a pencil
or that sort of thing.
You know, a very irritating way of talking.
But it does affect the evolution of language.
So, one
is HIP if one is
in line with
that type of thought,
which it is good
to be HIP too. But you have to
try all kinds to
triangulate
yourself. Unless
the benevolent
Bob-tism of Dobbs
shineth upon you. And then without even
trying, but effortlessly,
the ripe fruit will fall
into your palm. And you will find
that you possess the uncanny
and previously unsuspected ability
to surf the luck
plane as Dobbs,
our E-popped and ascended
master, has done
and continues to do.
I will close
with a poem. And then when that's over,
we will begin the thrilling
Bull Dada
auction.
Or will we, Reverend Tsang? Is that what we're going to do?
We're going to do the auction?
That's down there on the plan.
On the plan sheet. Now what poem
should I do?
The Skeleton
in Armor. How about that one?
Do you want that one? Or what about
Leviathan by
W.S. Merwin. Which should
it be? How many
want The Skeleton in Armor?
I see some hands for The Skeleton.
How many want Leviathan?
I see about the same number of hands
for Leviathan. Well, it's a
toss-up.
Well,
well,
alright. I'll do Leviathan.
I'll save The Skeleton for
another occasion. We'll have another occasion
for The Skeleton. But now,
Leviathan.
This is the
Black Sea Brute, bullying
through Wave Rack. Ancient as
the ocean's shifting hills,
who in sea toils traveling,
who furrowing the salt
acres heavily, his wake
hoary behind him,
shoulders spouting, the fist
of his forehead over wastes
gray-green crashing among horses
unbroken from bellowing fields,
past bone
wreck of vessels,
tide ruin, wash of
lost bodies bobbing,
no longer sought for,
and islands of ice
gleaming. Who ravening
the rank sea flood,
overmastering the dark sea
marches, wave marshalling,
finds home
and harvest.
Frightening to fool-hardiest
mariners, his
sighs were difficult
to describe. The hulk
of him is like hills heaving,
dark yet as crags
of drift ice, crowns
cracking in thunder.
Like land's self by night
black looming,
surf churning and trailing
along his shores rushing,
shoal water boding about
the dark of his jaws.
And who would moor at his side
and fare on a foot
should find gates of
no gardens, but the hill
of dark underfoot diving,
closing overhead
the cold deep
and drowning. He is
called Leviathan, and
named for rolling.
First created he was of all
creatures. He has held
Jonah three days
and nights. He is that
curling serpent that
in ocean is. Sea
fright he is, and the shadow
under the earth.
Days there are, nonetheless,
when he lies like an
angel, although a lost
angel, on the wastes
unease. No eye
of man moving, bird
hovering, fish flashing
creature whatever
who after him came to
herit earth's emptiness.
Froth at flanks seething
soothes to stillness
waits. With one eye
he watches dark of night
sinking last. With one
eye day rise
as at first over
foaming pastures. He
makes no cry, though
that light is a breath. The
sea curling, star climbed,
wind combed,
with itself. Still,
as at first it was,
is the hand,
not yet contented of
the creator. And he waits
for the world to
begin.
Ten million times for just
one soul. Even for that
boy there, he would die ten million
times. He will chase him
over the waters of sin. You doubt
that Jesus walks over the waters of sin?
This boy has been
chased, and he will be
redeemed. Jesus will never
leave him ever. Jesus will
have you in the end.
What are you doing parking in the middle of the road, son?
Pick your hand off
my shoulder. I'm reading that sign.
There ain't a person
or a whoremonger who wasn't
something worse first. That ain't the sin
nor the blasphemy.
The sin came before him.
Jesus is a
trick on bobs.
Well, will you get this goddamn out
house out of the middle of the road?
I don't have to run away
from anything, cause I don't believe in anything.
What direction's
the zoo in? Back the other
way. That's where you
escaped from.
If you'd like
to see other episodes of the
Ask Dr. Hal Show, they are freely available
for viewing on the internet
at PuzzlingEvidenceTV
where hundreds of
episodes can be
downloaded, including many of
our guest stars and other
people who have appeared
not only as guests on the show, but
as hosts in
recent times.
And also my wonderful
assistant K. Rob has put his many
monstrous monster
movie moments up on the
internet. They are also
available for your instruction,
delectation, and
edification.
Then PuzzlingEvidenceTV
has other things, important things
for the Church of the Subgenius. He's
I think got that famous
movie, Pipes of the Piposphere.
Also the making of
the Pipes of Piposphere.
Also the making of the
watching of the making of
the Pipes of the Piposphere.
And the famous Philo Drummond
movie that I can't think of the name of.
What's the name of that movie?
Philo's favorite movie?
Is it called Coffee Break or something like that?
Lunch Break? I'm sorry, I can't
remember. Bob's Lunch Break?
Bob's Coffee Break?
Bob's Lunch Hour.
Bob's Lunch Hour. Yeah, that's
the one. Bob's Lunch Hour.
And many things like that
are available at PuzzlingEvidenceTV.
Once you start watching that stuff,
you will never have any more
free time to yourself.
But I will tell you how to get your pot of pinks back,
if that's what they are. How?
Just take that golden egg and
you'll... Meanwhile,
Bruno was trying to coax magic out of
Felicia's pinks. Come on, pinks,
if that's what you are. Just one little trick.
Bruno, those are my pinks.
We traded. Take your chicken
and get out of here. Do I take the golden
egg too? Sure, take the
golden egg. Yeah, see?
Here's your pot of pinks. Give me my
chicken. I thought we traded.
We didn't shake hands on it. So Felicia
took back her pot of pinks and
watered it tenderly. And as she did,
a strange thing happened. The pot of pinks
turned into a handsome prince.
Kind maiden, will you marry me?
Oh, your highness.
Just call me Pinky.
So Felicia and the prince were wed.
And Bruno, well, he was
so insistent that the chicken really
did start laying golden eggs.
Anything to stop him
from bugging me. So they
all lived happily ever after, which just
goes to show the power of positive
thinking. Oh, as we call it,
the power of positive pinking.
Well, that
is fairy stories.
Oh, uh, well, there's a callers right
in the left. Some of our listeners may not know
that Dr. Hal is actually a well
known illustrator
and, uh, an underground
comic book artist. That's right.
I dipped my ink in the underground
pool some time ago.
He's one of the old timers.
And, uh, he has
a couple of books out, which I think we
are able to plug. Oh, gosh, thanks, Stang.
Now I can plug my books. Yeah, you can.
Boy, what a prince of a fellow.
That Ivan Stang. They don't come
any nicer. Well, folks, um,
it is true. I do have a few books out and they
sell horribly. So I
want you all to order a copy
through Amazon or even better,
there's something I like more, which
is called Bookstores. You might have
heard about this. These are actual places
where you can go. Now, if you look for my book
and it's not on the shelf, that's, uh,
well, that's about the way it usually is.
And so you ask them to order it.
What are the titles? Oh, okay, I'll give you some.
And how is the author's name spelled?
Oh, that's very important. Slightly unusual.
Well, I did write my book, The Meaning of Lost
and Mismatched Socks, under
the pseudonym Dr. Perditus
Pedale,
M.D., Ph.D.
But that is because
when given an assignment by my publisher
to write about lost socks
and where they go, I thought it would be better
to humanize the entire... He wrote that
lost socks book? Yeah, I wrote it.
Are you familiar with it? Yeah, I remember
seeing that. Well, I hope you like it.
Uh, and I illustrated it, too. All of
those pictures are mine. Furthermore, I came up with the
index, where you can look up anything
about socks,
sock perversions, people who eat
socks, it's a medical condition known
as pica, and other things.
Uh, but, um, the reason
my book is narrated
by this imaginary author is
one, so it gets me off the hook,
and two, because
the name Perditus Pedale,
for you Latinists who were just on,
means lost sock. Lost sock.
And he is a human lost sock.
So, by dehumanizing the problem,
we're all lost socks, looking for
the match, but the match can
be lost and disappeared.
You can be mismatched with another sock
and not be a true pair.
And furthermore, uh, oh well,
I'm not gonna get into the thesis of the book, too.
Now, don't, let's don't get lost in the dogma. What about your other book?
Okay, but that book is by me. It says I'm the editor
of this book. Actually, I wrote it...
And who are you again?
Uh, uh... Hal Robbins. What a devastating question.
Harry S. Robbins, and it's spelled
with one B. That's true.
You don't want to get lost in a world
of Robbins with two B's, like
Tim Robbins, or Trina Robbins.
In the literature world, yes.
Hal or Harry S. Robbins.
Especially not Harold Robbins.
Not Harold Robbins.
That's not me. No, it's, uh,
Harry S. Robbins is, uh, is me.
And then, a more recent book I did,
it's called Dinosaur Alphabet,
which is all about, uh, dinosaurs
that most people have never heard of.
Otherwise, uh, if you read most
dinosaur books, you think there were four.
The, uh, one with the
big fat body and the long, uh,
tail and head, the triceratops,
uh, the, uh, stegosaurs,
and the Tyrannosaurus rex. Well, none of those guys
made it into my book. They get, uh,
so much exposure,
it's, uh, really not fair when there
are so many delightfully
ornamental dinosaurs that have lived,
whose adventures I chronicled
in my poems,
which are in this book. I just don't know why
this didn't sell, but, uh, it was...
There's pictures and poetry about the dinosaurs.
And furthermore, there is an alphabet,
an alphabet which I designed,
uh, orthographically.
Each, uh, letter of the alphabet,
which stands for a different dinosaur,
from A to Z,
contains a medievalistic
inlaid picture,
like the P of Plateosaurus has a
Plateosaurus in it. But Plateosaurus
is one of the more common
dinosaurs, uh, compared to some of the
ones that I included.
And I think all humans
should know about dinosaurs.
And they should know that the reason
these elaborate doodads
are all over dinosaurs, uh, horns,
spikes, uh, plates, shields,
uh, uh, crests, all that stuff
have nothing to do
with protection from
big, bad theropods
like Tyrannosaurus, the way they always say.
The reason they had this stuff was
sex.
The reason they had this stuff was cause it looks
cool. And you're not gonna get another
dinosaur to mate with you unless you
look cool. And furthermore,
many dinosaurs look very much like
each other, so they needed
exaggeration of these special features
so the females, who let's admit it,
didn't have all the candle power in the world upstairs,
could recognize who you
were, and that you were a boss
bitchin' dude. With the biggest horns,
the longest spikes... Because of your peculiar features?
I beg your pardon? Because of your peculiar
features? That would mean that the dinosaur mating
ritual was... they were subgeniuses.
Well, you know why
I like them now.
And friends, uh, I assure you,
Dr. Howell draws just as
purty as he talks.
Oh, I have spent many a pleasant
hour enjoying both of those
books. Do I have to draw you a picture?
A lot of that time it is there in the bathroom, but it was a
wonderful, wonderful afternoon.
Well, good. They are bathroom books, where
you can browse, especially the index.
And you can find the index and
the logs and websites of everything
on this show and all previous episodes
since the 1990s anyway on
subgenius.com.
Thanks to Dr. Sinister and
CSB for letting us plug,
and praise the large
who whipped up most of the
collage-y clips this time.
The background music
is Free Cake
of Detroit, recorded live
at 12X Day.
Uh, thanks to Reverend Suds.
Praise Bob and
his face.
I don't need J. R. Bob Jobs, that's what I know!
Yes! And I said that,
you know, that face, that,
yeah, that face, that face that's right
with me. You need that
face, the face of Bob!