It's time for Bob. Say Bob, why the big smile this afternoon? What's so special
about today? Well there's nothing special. The Self Genius Power of Slack. Now we're rolling Bob.
Oh yes dear friends, this is your prayer partner Reverend Ivan Stang. Okay I'm recording this on
July 4th. Tomorrow is X-Day. If you don't hear from me after this that means I was ruptured up
onto the escape vessels of the sex goddesses on July 5th and I will have better things to do
than the hour of slack. If so, so long and thanks for all the fish. Meanwhile I have a lot to do in
preparation so here are the outtakes for today.
From last week's show. From PR News in Washington I'm in need of extra attention
after a brief illness and I'm so broad that I need to be braced. Joe Georgfine explains.
He says 45 babies. He says 25 babies. He says 15 of the babies came with the babies and will stay
with the babies until PR News. 19.7 percent and 49 percent or 13.7 percent or at least 100
55 percent. All right. 5.6 million point nine percent. All right but at least 21 percent. At
least 143 million point five percent. But PR News officials are watching it closely. The Dow was
1337. Credit monitoring company Equiftec jumped after disclosure of PR News Washington.
I'm going to have to go and do my stretches now with some monster movie on the TV and I'll probably
run sort of pseudo run run in place on a wee foot board that that is very sensitive to your
your body movements on it through your feet. And so I may run be running all over Woohoo Island
while listening to rock music and and doing spaz dancing for my other exercise. I have to do this
every day for the rest of my life if I want to do anything for the rest of my life. Thank y'all.
The evil that has fallen upon us is much more ancient and pitch black.
It has several characteristics that are important to know. This is a cult of death. It lives and
feeds on the evil of the dead. It is a cult of death. It is a cult of death. It is a cult of
death. It is a cult of death. It is a cult of the most terrible death agonies. When people were
killed slowly, torturers were enjoying themselves in front of other people. That's what the priests
of this cult do.
This cult came out of the ancient swampy forest, which practiced the cult of severe torment of victims and cannibalism.
This cult is poisonous. It's invisible. At the level of very visible vapors, it creeps into the souls of people.
A characteristic feature of this cult is that it does not care who's suffering it enjoys. It rejoices in its own deaths too, no less than others.
And its absolutely cannibalistic attitudes are the cause of its suffering even though, Gordon and I have been and know no other, as a hand that can make us bleed with our friends.
towards its own soldiers.
That was Onan Counterbite and some Russian.
That is, Onan made that on his phone, I think.
And, well, this is the first time I've sat down at Tarzan's radio station in at least a month.
In fact, I had to pull the dust cover off of all this stuff.
It's set up in my living room on a fairly small table, actually.
It doesn't take up much room anymore.
And, but it's...
This is a dry land.
This is a dry, dry land.
The Subgenius Foundation is located in Glen Rose, Texas, in north-central Texas,
about an hour southwest of Fort Worth.
It's, it is very rural.
It's, the Metroplex has not enveloped it yet.
And it's farmland, and it hasn't rained in many,
many weeks.
And there's no promise of it.
And we're having such a dreadful heat wave that's so unusual for June that I went out
and bought, I did end times preparations that I probably should have done long before.
The list came from when we went through the freeze here.
The whole Texas power grid came down.
And I made a list of stuff that I should have.
And then I didn't.
I didn't do anything about it.
And then, because I'm a subgenius, but then I did something about it because we were,
it looked like we were going to have another freeze.
I got a generator and some portable heaters.
Now I have, I've added a portable air conditioner because we have a 93-year-old in hospice in
the big downstairs bedroom with caregivers coming and going.
So this is a weird thing.
It's a weird kind of cult headquarters.
It's part hospital, part workshop, part house, part barnyard.
Very much a barnyard.
The livestock are all domesticated pet type animals, but they're huge.
106 Brushwood Homes
ları
New Le granted
& Carwyn
Washington
SAT
Products
弋
I said, holy dog, a World War passed through my brain
He said, nurse, get your pie, the boy's insane
I grabbed my arm, I said, ouch
I landed on the psychiatric couch
He said, tell me about it
Well, the whole thing started at three o'clock fast
It was all over by a quarter past
I was down in the sewer with some little lover
When I peeked out from a manhole cover
Wondering who turned the lights on us
Well, I got up and I walked around
Up and down the lonesome town
I stood wondering which way to go
I lit a cigarette on a parking meter
And walked on down the road
It was a normal day
Well, I rung me fallout shelter bell
And I leaned my head and I gave a yell
Give me a string bean, I'm a hungry man
Shotgun fired, no airbrushes
I'm a drunk and I'm a drunk
No way around
I don't blame him too much though he didn't know me
Down in the corner by the hot dog stand
I seen a man
I said, howdy friend
Guess it's just us two
He screamed a bit and away he flew
I thought I was a communist
Well, this bought me a girl before she could leave
I said, let's go play Adam and Eve
I took her by the hand and my heart was thumping
She said, hey man, you crazy or something
You seen what happened last time they started
Well, I seen your Cadillac window uptown
There was nobody around
I got into the driver's seat
And I said, hey man, you crazy or something
I drove down 42nd Street in my Cadillac
Good car to drive after a war
Well, I remember seeing some ads
So I turned on my car and I'll ride
But I didn't pay the con head bell
Said the radio host
The radio didn't work so well
Turned on my record player
It was Rockaday Johnny singing
Tell your ma, tell your pa
Our loves are gonna grow
I was feeling kind of lonesome in my car
I was feeling kind of lonesome in blue
I needed somebody to talk to
So I called up the operator at time
Just to hear a voice of some kind
When you hear the beep
It will be three o'clock
She said that for over an hour
And I hung up
Well, the doctor interrupted me just about then
Saying, hey, I've been having the same old dreams
But mine was a little different, you see
I dreamt the only person left after the war was me
I didn't see you around
Well, now time passed
And now it seems everybody's having them dreams
Everybody sees itself walking around
There's no one else
Half the people can be part right all of the time
Some of the people can be all right part of the time
But I'm not the only one
All the people can't be all right Ali pref if my lady
súper
que ,
yo
i
tr
costume reread a little bit from the uh...
Dobbs Town Mirror.
Let's see.
This music in the background
is from the
Trailer Park Boys Greasy Money
phone game.
And it'll just run like this
as long as I have my phone on,
apparently.
Imagine a word
that has never been spoken,
written, seen, or heard.
Now imagine a word that
one and only one person
has spoken, written, seen, or heard.
Between the two,
that word exists more in the
later and not at all in the
former. What exists only
for you is yours to rehearse,
review, polish, cherish, treasure,
abandon, rewrite, forget,
etc. Your delights
and your miseries, not
some other person. Just you
know what just you knows.
Some
tiny thing is ready
to fly away.
Are people around you making
trouble for no good reason at all?
Set off a
NMP bomb.
Not my problem.
And run. They'll keep
making trouble without you, and
they aren't listening to you tell them that life
has enough troubles on its own without
inventing new ones.
If
you would dance to the tune of
slack, you have to pay the
piper.
Adventure, romance, fast
luck you'll attract.
No more cause to be a
griper.
And friends, homeopathic
remote cupping services
are also available from the
Dobbs Town Mirror.
Seen at
Dobbs.Town.
And you know, friends,
on the scale of intergalactic
travel, flying saucers are seen
near nuclear reactors.
As much and as little as they're seen
near anything else.
But on the scale of finding yourself willing
or otherwise being lifted up into
a flying saucer,
intergalactic scales hardly matter.
It's all a
matter of perspective.
J.R. Bob
Dobbs will walk with you up the
999 steps of wisdom
and then down the
1,000 steps
of forgetting.
There are songs, or perhaps
films, or perhaps comic books, or perhaps
meh, that come into
your life not as entertainment
but as permission,
as instructions.
Go with it, all the way, man.
You're right, they're wrong.
And if they cannot take a joke, let them
mount up upon themselves.
I may not in each moment
have slack, but I am a person
who in each moment prefers
to have slack. And not every
one can say that.
Some people prefer to not have slack.
Some people prefer
compulsive displays
of happiness or
complaining without the enjoyment
of complaining. Slack is
not always happiness, nor is slack
always refraining from complaining.
But slack
is never a preference for
no slack.
I can derive slack from any circumstance
when I call upon
my subgenius philosophy.
Prefer slack.
Okay, and those are all
from the Dobstown Mirror,
which you can get from
Uncle Dr. Onan Canobite
at
Post Office Box 3,
Columbus,
Indiana,
47202.
Okay, friends,
you know, July 5th,
the end of the world,
is Tuesday.
At the time I'm recording this,
on Friday, July 1st.
X-Day is July 5th,
1998, but from
24 previous X-Day drills,
we now know that we don't really know
when now is.
So temporarily, we might call this one
DIY Day.
It takes place
wherever you are. If you decide
to host a local drill
in the form of a big party,
with all your subgenius friends and loved ones,
great! We'll help you publicize it
if you want it public.
We've stumbled upon a discovery
in the forbidden sciences that has blown our minds
in ways they've formerly never been fellated.
We're gassed to the point of flabber.
What's the letter in mathematics
that commonly indicates a variable?
X!
Maybe it's called X-Day because it's the variable.
We know from prophecy that the media will,
refer to the advent of the angelic host as X-Day.
But now that we're less certain about the planet
and the year, this day of judgment is now...
a variable.
The world ends on July 5th, 1998 at 7am,
but we obviously don't know when that might be.
It might be today!
Well, maybe tomorrow, but...
soon.
This year we're going to hedge our bets and
hold the X-Day party where you are,
and when you want it.
And you,
and you,
and you!
Yes, X-Day in place for 2022.
So-called 2022.
If the saucers get to you first,
remember the rest of us.
Just make sure you're synced up.
Do send in that last 50 bucks.
Re-up your membership and enter to win big,
big, big prizes yet to be announced.
Throw an insane party,
put a big X on your forehead,
and hang out at the courthouse.
Take a photo of the weirdest thing you could do.
And post it to the subgenius metaverse.
No matter how it pans out,
the Church of the Subgenius offers the best apocalypse.
And that's On Encounter Byte at P.O. Box 3,
Columbus, Indiana, 47202.
Actually, I don't know of any big parties that have been announced exactly.
I wanted to do one here in the middle of the year.
We've had big parties here, but this isn't the time.
And I can't go anywhere.
Because I'm looking after the farm, you might say.
The old ladies.
And Texas is in an emergency, sort of, any minute now.
So here we sit, brokenhearted.
Paid a dime, and we'll party anyway.
There may be something on Zoom.
I don't know.
I really don't.
There was an X Day party a couple of weeks ago called The Real X Day
in New York State at some lodge near a lake.
And it had Dr. Hal, and it had a whole lot of bands.
But I'm not sure what else it had.
On the streaming video that was kind of on and off, actually, I did not see an audience.
There was an audience, but in every case, it was the next band waiting to go on.
Isn't that weird?
So, and so now this.
Ladies and gentlemen.
This is your title.
Tonight, Sadat rumbles along a bushy-haired man in a loud mud-splattered sports jacket.
Yeah.
Huh?
Hmm?
Oh.
Who?
Yeah.
Meanwhile, in the nearby large city.
Two years, Sadat.
Getting there, mud-splattered, can you take on those flip-floppy places?
All right, sir.
Where is Sadat?
Where?
Well, yes and no.
This gun says you don't.
Well, I'm not sure.
Good evening.
No, sir.
Okay.
We're showgirls.
Oh.
Go ahead.
What for?
According to the latest FBI uniform crime report,
more than 12,000 people met death at that time.
Some, including you, were killed in the hands of killers during 1951.
If I can help?
Excuse me.
Can you hear me?
Well, I have the canoe, piece of pie, and the kisser.
All right, sir.
For the gunman.
Tonight, the music was accidental.
What's that?
Well.
I got, uh.
What's that?
i got everything running and ready to record and all like that in fact i have it recording
the dogs are making a bunch of noise is that yeti's tail no it's chippy's tail is beating a
little tattoo on the floor nice that's good i've had a dog that did that he'd get up next to the
wall and just be beat on beat on it you know for as long as he wanted sometimes yeti will light
next to or like a kitchen cabinet that's down near the floor and he'll be like scratching or just his
tail will be doing one beat but then his side is bumping the cabinet door so it clicks in a
counter point yeah lisa and i actually sang to that one time well it'd be great would be if we
can do dr
for wotan again sometime we can put the dogs on stage and have them beating on a box with their
tails well i'll tell you if i could get if i could figure out a way to make yeti talk on cue he is
great he goes all that stuff yeah and his voice is so deep yeah he's big and uh no it sounds great
they both do it they both do this thing but they only do it when they want to
yeah so what's what's up man you're thinking about did you want to read something or what were
we going to do okay um so are are we are we are you ready to go you don't need to go well let me
no i'm through maybe i should get my frop out though
could get my froth out i could drop live while we're while we're doing it yeah okay
so
top
Thank you.
Well, the Swingin' Love Corpses didn't break up
because of one band member going crazy
and becoming an egomaniac or anything.
It was because your job moved you, right?
That's right.
My job moved me,
but the Swingin' Love Corps
did never break up.
It actually still exists.
Still, to this day,
there's a Wednesday night practice
that happens most of the time.
Oh, yeah.
On Zoom, right?
It was on Zoom during COVID.
We managed to be on Zoom quite a bit.
But the practice is in St. Louis.
It's held by the local guys there.
Once in a while, I will join on Zoom or on the phone.
But, yeah, it's evolved.
Originally, it was a drinking and smoking club
that evolved into a band.
And now it's a band that has evolved back
into a drinking and smoking club
and barbecuing, more barbecuing.
Right, more barbecuing than guitar playing and singing.
Yeah.
Lots of comparison.
Lots of barbecue styles and things
rather than guitar styles.
Right.
So, sauce, recipes, things like that.
Much, much more important now.
Well, yeah.
Yeah, that's one of the reasons it's, you know,
why I...
Back in the day,
when I was an angry young man,
a dour slack was a good outlet.
I was still working for the pinkest,
the bosses in the Dallas business film industry.
Yeah.
And it was frustrating, and I had much hate.
It was...
Now I'm an old man,
and I'm so much more concerned with what's for dinner.
Right, right.
I don't care who somebody else...
I don't care who somebody else votes for
or who their favorite band is or any of that.
I'm more concerned with what is for dinner.
Yeah.
And is there enough for me?
Well...
Are you shorting me again?
Where's my share?
Yeah, so I think that the audience
is beginning to prepare themselves
for what's coming down the line here.
Yeah, but the numbers are all messed up.
I was thinking, well, yeah,
at the end of eight more shows,
it'll be 2,000 shows, but it's not.
We're on eight...
1989, not 1989.
Well, why don't we just add, you know,
add a special number of fake shows in.
Virtual, non-existent shows.
Virtual shows that existed temporarily in people's minds,
and now they're just...
Yeah.
...only exist as part of a numbering scheme...
Right.
...to get you to 1998 faster.
Like, maybe you only need one show.
What's the difference there?
Let's see here.
1889.
Yeah.
So I missed that.
Plus 1998.
So then you need like 109, 109 or something like that.
Yeah, that's a lot.
That's too many.
I don't want to do another 100 shows.
I'll be dead.
I'll be dead before I do it.
That's two years.
I think you should, like, cram 109 shows into one show.
How dare we, Gary?
Make it like a two-hour show.
Well, I could do it like Byron Werner
and...
In Rural War Room,
where you play 100 shows all at the same time.
Right.
That's what I'm thinking.
You do 100 shows all at the same time.
That way it gets your numbering scheme,
and your last show will then be 1998.
Yeah.
You go from like 1888, 1889, 1998.
I wonder how many...
And people will say,
how did you do that?
You say, well, I put 109 shows into that last show.
Right.
All at once.
Running simultaneously.
Every now and then,
two or three of them would both have Bill Cates
or Bleepo Abernathy going,
the hour of slack.
Yeah.
Now, you know,
I actually have a copy of a...
where somebody took all...
Maybe it was only six of them back then.
They had all of the Star Wars movies
running simultaneously.
Overlaid on each other
with the soundtracks.
It's the craziest thing.
You can't watch it for too long.
I don't think you could.
You might make somebody do it, you know,
if you needed to.
So they had like 10 movies running
all layered at like 10% opacity.
Yeah.
And they start at the same time
in such a way that you find out
that whenever the scroll happens,
it happens exactly at the same point
in time in the opening sequence, you know?
So you got all these scrolls
on top of each other and stuff.
It's pretty cool.
I'll see if I can find it
and send you a link.
Yeah, because we don't have enough stuff to watch.
We don't have enough stuff to do.
And I don't want you to get bored
just sitting around there not doing anything.
Yeah, just waiting for some show to watch.
Yeah.
I wish somebody would...
I wish somebody would just tell me
a good show to watch.
I get plenty of shows.
Even this one called Severance,
it's kind of...
I'm having to sort of make myself like it.
Oh, I love it.
I'm only on like the two and a half episodes in.
Well, I'm on the fifth one.
I'm on the fifth one.
I'm almost finished with the fifth episode.
So I'll give you a better opinion
after I finish this one.
Oh, I had a name for it.
I decided to call it
The Prisoner's Lunch Hour
because it's an uncanny,
like our production,
Bob's Lunch Hour.
Uh-huh.
And it's also like The Prisoner
in many ways.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
I like the whole idea
of the severance concept.
That's what suckered me in.
You know, that you could actually
split your brain into two personalities
that could be separated completely
and didn't overlap.
And all you'd need is a special device
to shift from one to the other.
Well, of course,
the fun...
It's a metaphor in a way
because some people are almost that way.
You know, they're one person on the job
and they're another person
when they're off the job.
Yeah, I like that.
That's kind of a thing.
And it's sort of like
in that other person,
they don't...
That's kind of the way I was
when I was a wage slave.
I didn't let my two lives connect at all.
Right.
You wore the masks of insanity
to look normal.
I played my role
and did the things
that they expected me to do
and then I never socialized with them afterwards.
You know?
I never went and drank with them.
Princess, we worked for the county,
the weather control
in Cuyahoga County
for almost 30 years
pretending that she liked those people.
Yeah.
At no point did any of them know
that she was a folk singer.
But ran a hippie music festival.
Yeah.
Was actually a peace protester
a lot of the time back then.
Yeah.
And unfortunately,
I wised her up about human nature.
And she gave up on ending war
because that's what countries do, you know?
Yeah.
And yeah, she never...
Her co-workers never had any idea
of all the interesting things
she was doing.
She was doing outside work
because some of them would hate her for it.
A lot of them.
Most of them are really uninteresting people.
Right.
But yeah.
So, I mean,
something like that would be weird to them.
But the good thing about it is
they still pay her.
She retired in 2008 or something
and she still gets that pension.
Now me,
I'm going to have to be assembling
and mailing out subgenius membership packs
until I'm a fan.
I'm a skeleton probably.
But you may not have to send out
any more hours of slack.
Right.
I'm not getting paid for hours of slack
hardly at all.
But you know,
it's important that people know
that all of those 1,898 hours of slack
are out there.
Out there in the ether.
Yeah.
Waiting to be heard
again and again and again and again.
And they...
All of them.
And being gleaned for their value.
For their Rudy Schwartz Project songs.
Yeah.
And Swinging Love Courts.
So,
this poor psycho skeletons guy gave up on me.
He sent me a letter going,
well,
I guess you're just not,
you're just retired now.
And that was a year ago.
I was like,
well,
sort of.
I was,
I'd moved to doing mostly reruns
just because I didn't have time.
I had some,
many other things
that we had to deal with,
you know.
And this,
well,
this was a guy
who was,
asking for a recording.
Is that what it was?
No,
the psycho skeletons.
He was a guy
that sent music.
He'd send me an MP3 every week
and they were quirky instrumentals,
mostly.
Very original.
He had his own style.
It wasn't like any other music,
really.
And it was,
some people really liked it.
And,
you know,
but,
yeah.
But,
I think he caught on early
that I was just getting burned out.
And that,
that's,
it's that.
That's exactly what it is.
Yeah.
You finally get burned out.
Even on,
not slack,
but the hour of slack.
Yeah.
Nobody can ever get burned out on slack.
If they do,
there's something wrong with them.
Yeah.
They're like,
you know,
they're weird.
They're pink.
No,
they're not weird.
I mean,
they don't,
it's not real slack.
It's false slack,
you know.
Yeah.
Totally pink.
I will spew them
from my mouth.
Right.
My people are destroyed
for lack of knowledge.
Hosea 819.
They're like lukewarm,
they're lukewarm
in their faith.
They are lukewarm
And I,
so I spew them
from my mouth.
I,
not just that,
I vomit them.
That's God talking,
right?
Yeah.
Jesus,
I think,
was attributed to him.
Of course,
we don't,
you know,
some other,
who knows who really said.
Some Roman copywriter.
Yeah.
Roman,
Greek,
Greek.
Well,
yeah,
but after,
but it was the Romans
that decided to make it
an official religion
because it was the,
you know,
there's some people who say
that the reason they did that
was because it was
the perfect religion
for slaves
and losers
and poor people.
But did they?
What,
the Romans?
Yeah,
they made,
after,
after throwing Christians
to the lions,
they eventually,
it was Constantine
or whoever,
made,
he decided everybody
was going to be Christians.
That was in 400.
Yeah,
that was a long time after,
I mean,
they,
they'd already had their ups
and downs,
like,
like America.
It was just one of the
mystery religions back then,
you know,
until somebody decided to say,
okay,
well,
we're going to make this one
official.
What was that guy's name again?
Well,
there's a whole bunch of them.
Jesus.
There was at least five
Jesuses.
Yeah,
right.
My dad,
right behind me on this bookshelf
is my,
my father's collection
of all the books
about how there was no,
really no historical Jesus.
I wish I could have,
I would have liked to,
you know,
talk to your dad
about all that stuff.
Well,
you know,
he,
he always liked you.
He always asked how you were doing.
Yeah.
He didn't call you Philo.
He called you Steve
for some reason.
I don't know why
people just call me Steve.
Yeah,
but he,
he was,
he always,
he always thought you were an okay guy.
But,
but you had,
had moved away
and,
you know.
Yeah.
Doc,
Doc Frop
hung out with my dad.
He was my lawyer.
That's right.
Yeah.
I wish he was still around.
He was good for you.
He was my lawyer.
Mm-hmm.
He didn't charge me anything.
Yep.
He showed up
with me in front of the judge
with his uniform on.
Looking official.
His Navy uniform or just?
I think,
no,
I think he just had a business suit on.
Yeah.
He just had a business suit.
My father walked into
the First World Subgenius Convention
with some of his buddies
direct from a Navy,
Naval Reserve meeting
of some kind.
And he was dressed
in full captain's outfit.
And his buddies were all,
you know,
had their officer outfits on.
And,
and the,
the younger subgeniuses
just about crapped their pants
because they thought they were cops.
You know?
And my dad had such a,
he was a gas for,
he was mainly freaking out his friends.
He wanted to show his friends
something really weird.
And, you know,
think about it.
Tentatively,
a convenience was there.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's enough weirdness
in one person.
Yeah.
That's a guy who doesn't have a haircut.
He's got mustaches
all over the top of his head.
Well,
he's since he's,
he tattooed a brain
all over the top of his head.
So now it's,
it would be mustaches
on top of brains.
That guy's actually
doing really well.
He was one of the ones
that you would think
would die young
because he did so much
dangerous art projects.
Yeah.
And like worked on,
you know,
committed his body
to science experiments
and things.
Yeah.
But he's,
he lives in Pittsburgh now
and he actually seemed like,
like a whole lot of the old,
the,
the core,
core subgenius people
mostly are still alive
and doing pretty well.
That's,
that's great.
A whole lot of them died,
but they were newer ones,
you know?
Yeah.
They didn't have,
they weren't,
they didn't undergo
that sodomy ritual
in,
in Malaysia
that the,
us real beginner old guys did.
Yeah.
That was horrible.
But worth it.
Having to do that
to all those people.
Balls and vice grips
in Dobbs town.
You're an overman now.
That was this Doctors for Rotan hit.
Yeah.
Balls and vice grips in Dobbs town.
You're an overman now.
One of our five hits.
Yeah.
Then there's the one about what you do with Moonies,
but we can't sing that one on.
No,
you can't even sing that on,
on the internet only.
Yeah.
It's a radio show.
Well,
you can,
but let's let it,
yes.
Yeah.
What would you do with a Klondike bar?
Is that how it goes?
I think it's time that I should prop again.
Well,
we've actually,
this recording is now 56 minutes long.
So obviously this is going to end up being two shows.
Wow.
Yeah.
Squeeze two shows out of 56 minutes.
That's awesome.
I did some other stuff before that.
Oh yeah.
That's right.
I have to put in about X day into dead people.
And well,
you know,
I've been posting shows little by little.
I've been going back and posting my old puzzling evidence shows out there on a anchor.
And of course they're on a whole,
I got 200 of them.
That's on Nick's cloud.
Right.
Puzzling evidence.
And then I have been posting,
I've got about 40.
I'm going,
I've gone to about 40 a year and I think I've got 40 so far on anchor.
So for those people that want to listen to that old stuff,
there is some there,
but I'm like you,
Reverend staying.
I just don't.
It's so hard.
And I got so many other things to do.
Right.
You've got a greenhouse to build.
I'm working in my greenhouse right now while we were talking,
working on it.
You know,
I did,
I did put up my shade,
uh,
tested my,
my shade.
Call that.
That looked pretty good.
Well,
there's no wind.
Uh,
it's just hanging on some poles that are stuck into pots of plant pots,
but it's fine as long as it,
the wind doesn't pick up,
but you know,
maybe that's okay.
I figured it's going to be lines,
you know,
stretch some guidelines across your yard,
like maybe you have to attach them to poles or something.
And then maybe you could,
you know,
like just take some clothes off,
clothespins or something.
Oh yeah.
That's an idea.
Right.
Yeah.
Just two,
two big wires that go across from something to something.
Yeah.
Hmm.
And then just get you some little clamps of some kind.
Yeah.
I'm using twisty ties on the poles right now,
but,
uh,
it looks pretty good.
It's like a little cave.
It's like a little,
little weird cave full of almost edible plants.
Yeah.
And you're just trying to keep the sun from burning those things.
I had one,
I had one eggplant that finally had fruited and it had a little,
you know,
it looked like we were going to have an eggplant finally out of eight
plants.
And,
uh,
I found it today on the ground,
half eaten by a dog.
Well,
that dog,
I think it's Yeti.
He harvests,
he loves cucumbers and.
He's a vegetarian dog.
I guess.
You know,
they're omnivores.
They like anything that they can eat that doesn't make them sick.
Right.
And they,
and they eat things that make them sick.
They'll eat things that make them sick.
It tastes good enough.
They'll hold a frog,
a toad in their mouth until they start foaming and doing that head shaking thing where God,
why did I do that?
Yeah.
I knew it was going to taste horrible and make my mouth drool.
They're funny.
But yeah,
it's like I got dogs that got to entertain.
I,
I kind of don't want to deal with those.
Yeah.
Those.
The subgenius listeners,
a nutless chimp or a one nutted chimp could do my thing.
I'm going to do my job.
Let them do it.
Yeah,
I think they should.
But I really think that the,
you know,
the subgenius is out there that everybody always wants something new and they forget
about this rich,
robust history that we can go back to anytime we want that are at the fingertips of everyone
any time of the day or night for free for free.
I actually,
I actually pay,
I actually pay 30 bucks a month to keep those things on that.
I send server.
You do 30 bucks a month.
Yep.
Whew.
You know how much I pay for unlimited bandwidth and unlimited storage on my website?
$155 a year.
Well,
but this is,
um,
this is a place that's set up just for streaming and all that.
And,
uh,
I don't know.
I know.
I used to pay a hundred and almost 200,
but they lowered my price for some reason.
Yeah.
Now,
now,
okay.
If I quit doing the show,
will I,
will I need to keep that server up?
That's one thing to think about is where would you want to migrate that stuff that would
be free,
right?
Cause you might want to have a plan that at some point that's going to go away,
but you'd want to have it already somewhere else when that happens,
you know,
I could put it on subgenius.com,
but I'd need to make an arrangement to get it.
I'd need to get more storage space.
It's full.
It's not full of storage.
It's full of too many files.
200.
Yeah.
They had a limit of 200,000 pages and it,
uh,
it hit that.
Believe it or not.
Quite a while back.
I found lots of stuff that I can go,
go in and erase,
uh,
the,
you know,
out of date things.
And,
uh,
yeah,
I think it's like taking my old webpage down.
I don't really need it up anymore.
And I was just going to put quivering brain.com.
Yeah.
Well,
I wasn't going to take the,
I'm not going to take the site down.
I'm just going to take the webpage.
I don't,
it doesn't make any differences.
I could leave it up,
but I mean,
I'm not adding any new web pages to it or anything.
Right.
And,
uh,
but I do use the backend storage areas,
you know,
and anytime I want to share something,
that's my personal cloud.
Yeah.
That's sub site used to be that for me,
but,
but like I say,
it filled up and I just haven't gotten around to calling them up and going,
Hey,
how do I get around this file number thing?
Cause I don't care.
I just don't care.
I don't care.
Don't care.
I'm sick of it.
Just have had enough of it.
Yeah.
I figure I'll keep that.
I'll keep that as long as,
you know,
even though I don't really promote anything there.
Well,
David Bautner keeps the really old shows on his,
you know,
first 500 or,
uh,
no,
all the way up to about 2000,
I think.
Oh no.
What am I saying?
Uh,
the year 2000,
I switched to digital,
but he has all the old tape shows on his server.
Of course,
you know,
he's,
he's one of these days,
it's going to dry up and go away.
He'll suddenly die and not pay his bills.
And which listener out there is,
has got the complete collection.
Hmm.
It would be interesting to know who has the complete collection.
Cause you know,
there are those completists out there.
They're going to want to have every book,
right?
Every,
every catalog permutation,
every,
every single stark fist,
all that stuff.
Somebody is going to want to have it.
Those are the smartest people in the whole world.
They are.
Cause they've seen the future and they know that the future is subgenius.
Yeah.
The only way you're going to be able to get a can of peaches is if you can trade them
of subgenius pamphlet times after the,
a can of peaches and a gallon of gas for one subgenius pamphlet,
your propane to keep your stove running your,
your medicine,
your insulin.
Well,
you know,
some of us are stockpiling stuff like that.
I just ordered water purification tablets.
In bulk hearing aid batteries in bulk and all kinds of things that I thought,
you know,
supply chain problems,
economic cataclysm that we used to joke about.
Isn't so funny anymore.
Some of us weren't joking about it for every staying.
Well,
I saw,
we thought it was going to happen from a long time ago.
Oh,
I did too,
but I didn't think I was going to live long enough to actually see it start up.
I didn't want to,
you know,
I don't know.
I don't want to read about the last gorilla.
We should on the next show we should do,
we should look at the dateline for dominance.
Oh God,
man,
that's frightening.
When you do that,
we predicted everything.
We should try to find,
you know,
like they do with Nostradamus now show that there's specific things.
It might be a little bit different,
but we should be able to,
I'm going to do that.
I'm going to get my one of those out and my look at it.
And I'm going to try to find something for almost all of those things.
Yeah.
I,
I did that proves that we were like profits.
Yeah,
but we had,
we had,
we said the dates wrong.
We had all of that stuff happened before 1998,
it ended at 1998.
And,
but it was all,
it was all stuff that was coming.
We just had the numbers wrong,
wrong.
There's stuff in there that that's happened now,
like in the last couple of years.
Yeah.
I'm telling you,
I did a couple of years ago,
I did a show and a Starwood speech based on that fact of Dateline for dominance from 1983
book,
uh,
showing stuff,
uncannily what stuff that,
yeah.
And it was the stark fist originally before them.
Yeah.
That was like 1981 or 82.
And,
and,
uh,
we,
we did add when we,
when they reprinted the book,
we added a few things.
Yeah.
For 1982 and 83 that made it seem even more accurate.
Like that was in the first book,
right?
Yeah.
Uh,
yeah.
If you look at the McGraw Hill,
the McGraw Hill version of Dateline for dominance,
is it quite as accurate for the intervening years as the later book is that Simon Schuster,
the sister version that most people see now,
I guess it's upstairs there.
Oh man.
That's a print on demand book now,
but at least it's still in print.
Yeah.
The other ones aren't.
That's another thing.
If I quit doing the show,
I can get those books reprinted.
Yeah.
Not just them,
but there's probably a whole bunch of cheaters,
Laverges out there that would love to have the subgenius and promoter on their book.
Yeah.
There was that guy,
a Reverend Zeno fact he's,
he's the,
uh,
on,
on Dobbs dot town.
He's been really prolific.
Great.
Yeah.
Great flyers and things that would go in a membership pack.
Actually,
there's some new people that need to get,
have,
you know,
have some of the,
have some,
some stuff promoted.
That would be awesome.
You know,
yeah,
that,
that I can personally sell.
And there's still the whole,
um,
you know,
once a year special,
our slack special.
You know,
the two hour.
Yeah.
The star wars Christmas special version of our slot.
Right.
Or,
or whatever.
Yeah.
Whatever horrible thing that they did on TV to try to ride the coattails or something.
And if they did it very poorly,
only we'll do it right.
This time.
Yeah.
It's like that.
Save the universe.
This time.
That's right.
Yeah.
Well,
I sure have enjoyed being here on the show with you.
Reverend staying.
Yeah.
We're going to save the universe this time.
I think.
Yeah.
It's,
it's going to need saving this time.
There's lots of stuff going on out there in the real world that we could probably ignore
better than anyone and teach others the same thing,
how to live in the horrible times and still have slack.
Right.
That's the key.
Well,
it's easy for you.
It's not going to get better.
It's a little easier for you and me to say on account of we,
well,
in your case,
you carefully saved your resources and bought a wonderful,
incredible farm where you can.
I looked for a place that nobody wanted.
I thought,
where's the state that nobody wants to move to that they would say,
what,
what are you going to move there for?
That's the state I'm going to move to.
Which one is it now?
And I went through that process.
Well,
see,
I didn't have to do that because my parents did.
And,
uh,
yeah.
And then,
then they died and my brother and sister didn't want to live in this maintenance nightmare.
They had their own newer houses already.
Yup.
And,
uh,
so here they,
they basically said,
well,
you can stay in that old rattletrap decaying mansion.
It's not really a mansion.
It's actually a four bedroom house,
but the living room has a mansion.
It looks kind of like a mansion.
It's kind of like,
it reminds me of,
uh,
do you remember that one that had,
gosh,
what was the name of it?
Had William Holden in it and Gloria Swanson.
And she played an aging.
Oh yeah.
Uh,
sunset.
Right.
That's a great movie.
Yeah.
In that closing scene,
when she comes out to get her set up,
Mr.
DeMille,
you know,
yeah.
Frame is to frame.
I think they're getting ready to take her off to jail.
Right.
Well,
she had a spiral staircase.
We have a,
was that an auto perimeter movie?
I don't know.
I really liked auto perimeter movies.
I think I'm going to go look,
see who did that movie.
Well,
anyway,
I'm going to turn off this recording and,
um,
you know,
then I have to listen back.
I'll probably go,
man,
I thought we were just blithering.
And this is actually pretty,
pretty,
this is pretty funny.
If you're philo or staying.
Yeah.
And that's all people that like to listen to us.
So anyway,
which is us.
Yeah.
Well,
even I'm getting tired of listening to us,
man.
I'll tell you.
All right.
Well,
it was fun.
Okay,
man.
I'll say.
You think it would take your mind off things if Blackstone showed us a trick.
Well,
how about a bit of hypnotism,
Alan?
Who's to be the victim?
Uh,
you are,
right now.
Look straight in my eyes,
sideways.
That's a sense.
It isn't as easy as you think,
Alan.
It isn't?
Ah,
just watch.
All right.
What do I do now?
And I'm not hypnotized.
That's right, Alan.
Then you give up?
Certainly do.
Well, just try to look into my eyes.
One on top of the other.
I wouldn't have a chance.
Well, for once, you're right, Alan.
I hope you like that trick, ladies and gentlemen.
And until next time, goodbye.