This is normally when we play the Hour of Slack, and I'm Dr. Sinister, as you may know.
And as anybody listening knows right now, this is New Year's Eve.
It's the most wonderful night of the year.
It's the one holiday that everybody has to observe, because we're all forced to flip
the calendar at the same time.
It doesn't matter what religion you belong to, we're all flipping the calendar tonight.
And we have a very special program on schedule for you here.
We're going to have some special guests up here later on tonight.
Jeremy, I just want to tell you that I'm really sincerely glad you're live, because there
are a lot of people who love you and care for you, and I'm one of them.
And besides, I don't want to lose a customer.
Although, yeah, I have two questions, though.
If you had died, would I have gotten any of your stuff, and do you have anything that
I would want?
I think the only things that I have that you would want are some archived shows from
the Muhammad's Radio Days that I have on CD.
Hey, stay on the line.
Stay on the line here.
We have another caller from out of state here.
Oh, good.
Hello, you're on the radio.
Well, hello.
Hello.
Quiet.
I'm calling from the great state of Texas.
I think you know a person who belongs in Texas.
You know, one of my exes lives in Texas.
I'm trying to look for Reverend Stang.
Is he there?
We have not reached him yet.
He has not yet called in.
No, not yet.
All right, I'm about 14 seconds behind, I think.
So I'm streaming on the audio.
You can call me Doc.
Doc.
Yeah.
I'm D-O-K, short for doctor.
Oh, okay.
That's me.
Oh, yes.
This town ain't big enough for the both of us.
I am Dr. Sinister.
And it ain't me.
Who's going to...
Yes, well, I'm Dr. Sinsomniac.
Oh.
I've been spelling doctor with a K since the 90s.
I'm trying to muscle it on my turf.
Incorporated with a certain belief system that I have.
Uh-huh.
And what belief system is that?
I'm going to try and...
Well, I'm going to try and work with the Church of the Subgeniuses teachings.
Hello?
Who do we know?
I can hear you.
Can you hear me?
It's all over.
Hello?
Okay, somebody hung up.
All right.
We are bringing another call right now.
Can you hear me?
You're on the radio.
Hello?
Hello, you're on the radio.
10-4, can you hear me?
Roger Dodger.
Hello, 10-4, can you hear me?
Yes.
Hello?
Greetings.
This thing is, in fact, on.
...from the force.
Hello?
Yes.
Hello.
It sounds like puzzling evidence.
There's about 16 things going on in my head.
That's what we're all about here.
Exactly.
That's the very definition of synesthesia.
I'm WCSB Cleveland.
All right, I'm back on the air.
How are we doing this evening?
Well, I have to advise you that portions of the following broadcast will be objectionable
to some members of the audience.
Therefore, WCSB advises solicited discretion.
The views and opinions expressed on this program are not necessarily the views of the audience.
The viewers are not intended to represent the views of WCSB or Cleveland State University
or anybody with their head screwed on straight, for that matter.
And other people just like you can call in to 216-687-3515 to join our all-star cast tonight.
For the New Year's Eve Extravaganza, we have just 22 minutes, I'm sorry, not 22, 28 minutes
left in this foul year of 2017.
Ooh, yes.
And we have some awesome people here.
Well, isn't that just fantastic for you?
Yeah.
How about, well, yeah, because we're...
Where are you calling from?
I'm a time traveler, and you're a concern, I suppose you could say.
Oh, you're calling from a different time zone.
Of course, I'm a year and one hour behind, because I'm a subgenius.
Or you're an hour ahead of everybody else in Texas right now.
Well, I hear that.
I'm an inch away.
I'm either an inch away from my skin or a year and an hour and a half away.
Ooh.
Amazing.
Hmm.
Why not both, though?
So, the reason I called, really, was to say, you know, I'm a time traveler.
I think it's a good thing that, of course, we all remember 2016, don't we?
Hmm.
When was that?
Almost two years ago.
Kind of.
Well, it's difficult sometimes to remember things, because I think something is going
on in this world.
These Illuminati are taking over Taco Bell.
A lot of people are catching on.
They're getting woke.
Got to stay woke.
Okay.
So, 2016 was terrible.
I don't think there are many people that can fondly look back on that year.
However, 2017, what the hell happened?
I don't know.
Tell us.
The drugs wore off.
I mean, we're looking at a reality show president.
Kicked in.
And everything is changing around us, and our heads are spinning so fast that we can't
quite keep track of every distraction that's going on.
Hmm.
So, did anybody catch the...
...soft UFO disclosure that the UFO committee did in the Pentagon, the government?
Anyway...
Yes, I did, and I don't believe it.
I don't believe a word of it.
If the government starts saying that they found UFOs, I am not...
That's the one time I'm not going to believe what the government says.
You can say mischief management.
If they deny it, I'll believe it.
If they deny UFOs, I'll believe it.
That's good management.
It's the management of mischief.
You get some cornball digging around asking too many questions, and then you just steer
it around.
You can't steer him around and use him for your own purposes.
I've got a question for the caller.
Is this caller seeing the movie Idiocracy?
We're living it, aren't we?
Isn't it a documentary?
Well, I guess that's kind of the direction I'm going with that.
Before this election, that might have seemed like a ridiculous movie, and after this election,
does it seem a whole lot more like a documentary?
Well, absolutely.
You can just see it slowly evolving.
I think it's a good thing.
Net neutrality.
Hello?
Yes, you're still here.
And hey, we also have Reverend Stang finally calling in here.
We have also some more guests in the studio here, the illustrious Will and a guest of
his.
Oh, and I just hit the wrong button.
I meant to bring Reverend Stang on the air, but I pressed the wrong button.
I'm sure he'll call back.
He knows how to do it.
And you know how to do it, too.
It's 216-687-3515.
And you are on the radio.
We're living in .
Hello?
Hello, you're on the radio.
Oh, good.
Oh, this is Reverend Stang.
My ears were itching.
I knew that someone must have been talking about this.
Yes, we were.
Well, I am...
Well, Happy New Year, everyone.
Happy New Year, Reverend Stang.
It's so good to hear from you.
Happy New Year.
I have to say, you've been a big influence on me as well over the years.
It's only been 30 here in Texas.
Right.
Yeah, you're stuck in the past, man.
Yeah, it's crazy.
But then again, I guess the Aussies could tell us the same.
We're looking forward to a glorious new year where America will be great.
Again?
From your mouth to God's ears.
Again.
And is that all right?
Did I do it right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's a gun to my head.
Uh-oh.
Don't pull the trigger.
Everything will be fine.
Am I screwing up again?
I'm just afraid of it.
It sucks.
Where are we going?
No!
You don't want to know?
I just had to change my mind.
I changed the first tag on an hour of Slack files on my computer from 2017 to 2018, and
it's such a joke because we don't even know what year this is.
That's right.
We know it's not 1998 yet.
We know that much for sure.
We probably don't really know what planet.
We've been taking their word for it, you know, for everything.
Was there really a World War II?
Was there really a 2017?
Oh, God, I'm afraid there was.
I don't believe there was a World War II.
I really don't believe that for a second.
Well, World War II was actually a false flag operation for when they transferred planets
from planet Mars to planet Earth.
I believe that World War I never ended.
Yeah, try telling people.
That may call you a conspiracy, too.
No, World War I is still going on 100 years later.
Not 100 years later.
The Earth was peaceful and beautiful, but it was actually in the area of Mars.
Then we almost destroyed it, and we used the false flag of World War II to cover our transportation
operation to the new planet Earth.
Yeah, well, that goes without saying for most subgeniuses, but most of the listening audience
doesn't know what any of that is.
It's what they're talking about.
I think it's about what the universe is about.
Oh, what the universe is about.
Oh, yeah.
I think it's about what the universe is about, and to them it's all fake news.
Well, perhaps it's time for people to tune in.
...fake news just happens to be the realest.
Oh, well.
So, I guess the best thing to do is just start spewing out news, and the good news
is it's a new year.
We're a ring-
Oh, I thought you said nudes.
A nude.
That doesn't make any sense.
Why not vote?
Oh, yes.
It was like X Day a couple of years ago with that deceptive advertising where you said women free.
I went there.
It was a couple of days until I found my free woman.
I thought they'd be at the door.
Well, they didn't have to pay to get in.
You know, sort of like a strip joint.
Exactly.
And we were making a point.
It was lost on everybody, but who cares?
Everybody had fun.
I tell you what, that's a wonderful place to go.
I really found my center there.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
It's okay.
I realigned it.
It's now off to the left like it used to be.
Oh, good.
I heard you scored.
That's the best.
It happened to a lot of people.
It never happened to me.
I'm married.
Huh?
I'm married on paper.
Hmm.
I was married 24 hours once.
Wow.
Other side of the map.
You know, I never even got it.
You know, all the years I spent going to X Day and participating in the Church of the Subgenius, I never once got a 24 hour marriage.
Even Steve over here.
It was beautiful.
Got a 24 hour marriage once.
Can you remember to what or who though?
Someone who was actually a guest on my show once.
Yeah?
Allison?
Hmm.
Uh, I'm not sure about that, but your memory might be better than mine.
One time she was up here.
She, uh, one time, actually, the last time I had her up here on the air, she gets a little
wild.
No, no, you're exaggerating.
Yeah, which is probably why she got kicked out of X Day.
But, uh,
I'm sure that's an exaggeration too.
That's all I'm imagining.
Chief over there, that microphone you're using, the last time I had her up here, she actually
fell off.
She farted directly into that microphone.
Oh, nice.
Yeah.
Mm, mm, mm.
Yep.
Is that what I smell?
Okay.
Are you guys talking about who I think you're talking about?
I think I know exactly, I think you know exactly who I'm talking about.
Yeah.
When, when, uh, when I was, uh, when we got back to Cleveland, I had to, uh, thank, uh,
our Reverend Stang profusely for, uh, solving, uh, that, that summer's, uh, problem for
me without any, any interaction from, from, from, from, uh, the, uh, the, the, the, the,
this is a Jordanianupa.
Yes.
Uh, and sometimes it they're saying nothing but, um, they're, they're saying nothing.
Up there.
You can, you know Berkley was always interested in experiments.
Do you?
Oh, of course.
Uh, I, we always go pick those and him.
Uh-huh.
See I told you I wasn't a big fan of Eric inera.
Has anybody else been to seawater Motel after yesterday's show?
Yeah.
I was actually in a band with her for like a day.
And she was going to be the singer.
And I wanted to call the band Attractive Nuisance.
But the name was already taken.
Okay, now I know who we're talking about.
For sure.
But that was my first...
I seriously doubt she's listening.
But if she is, seriously, I love you.
Don't take it the wrong way.
She was so beautiful.
She was a great improv performer for my wide-angle, wide-screen video camera,
One Starwood Dawn, after the Bond fall.
That can never, ever be on YouTube.
For about 50 obvious jiggling reasons.
At dawn.
At the Starwood Festival.
Privacy.
Yeah, privacy is important.
Man, it's a great little 20-minute, 15-minute...
There was the Discordian Joy Juice was being passed around.
And I had a...
Discordians.
Discordians are all posers.
Anguish.
Anguish elixir.
Yeah, that's right.
It was the Anguish Syringe, I remember.
Wow.
And she and also Fat Mandy helped distribute the Anguish elixir as kind of an antidote to the Discordian Joy Juice.
And there's this talk about inside jokes.
Old, ancient, fake cult.
But man, it was fun.
It was.
Yes.
And the stuff tasted horrible.
Oh, God.
It was...
Vanilla?
Flavored vodka.
Vanilla-flavored vodka?
Vanilla-flavored vodka with some kind of...
What was it?
Some kind of juice?
Orange juice.
Ooh, a flavored screwdriver.
In a nicely labeled jug.
And it was being handed out by a pair of nicely labeled jugs of at least two different helpers while I videotaped.
That's nothing...
Again, this is the kind of thing you can...
It's...
We have to wait until everybody...
Everybody's dead before we can release it.
But that won't be that long.
I can tell you the most disgusting thing I ever drank.
Mmm.
The most disgusting thing I ever drank.
And that was the exact diametric opposite of the new year.
It was the dead of summer.
And so we...
That reminds us that the arbitrary change of human-numbered dates is about to have a big...
numerical shift.
Right.
You know, I like this one holiday because everybody is forced to turn the page at the same time.
You don't have a choice.
It doesn't matter what god you worship.
True.
We all have to turn the page tonight.
Well, no.
I mean, the Chinese have all different...
No.
They have their own Lunar New Year celebration, but no, even the Chinese are going to start
calling it 2018.
In fact, they've already started because they're several hours ahead of us.
They're ahead of us.
Yeah.
In so many ways.
Damn it.
We've got to...
So it doesn't matter what country you're in.
Even countries that have different alternative calendars, they still use the Gregorian calendar.
Everybody on the face of the planet is turning a page.
This day, this night.
And that's why it's my favorite holiday.
After X Day.
We're all together as one.
Amen.
Turning the page.
We're all...
Everybody's going to be writing the wrong year on their rent checks tomorrow.
Yes.
Right.
Well, I'm not going to do that.
2018.
I'm going to...
I'm going to remember.
Bacon 8 instead of...
Very good.
Well, you know, it's actually easier to make a...
However, with the 7, it is easy to correct because you can draw a line from the top of
the 7 down to the bottom and zigzag it over to the end of the 7 and create your own fancy
8 and say, oh, I meant it to be an 8.
Mm-hmm.
Exactly.
If I make a mistake, I can...
I never have to...
That's what means...
Only your banker knows for sure.
That's how you know it's going to be an easy year.
My God, man.
For you guys, it's only like 15 minutes to the...
Pudge flipping.
I know.
Hard to believe it.
The countdown.
I have these people in the other room I really wish were in here with me now.
That's an hour and a half away.
Jeremy told us a hell of a story and...
I'm waiting for the future.
I didn't get to hear nearly as much out of Tabitha as I wanted to hear.
I have Buddha over there who has not said a word on the air tonight.
Aww.
We have Will who just showed up.
I haven't heard anything from him.
He's a jolly good fellow.
He hasn't said anything.
Are you talking about me?
Hello?
I'm talking about a Will who's physically present in the station right now.
I have a question for all the people in the studio.
Okay.
In the year 2018, name three people that you think will be dead by the end.
That's a ridiculous question.
Whoa.
What?
What, a postulation as to someone's demise?
Oh, my.
The whole Deadpool thing?
I'm not into that.
The people that we think will be dead, all of the 104-year-olds.
The vast majority of them.
That's my guess.
By the end of the year, all of the 104-year-olds will be dead.
Mmm.
But I don't believe that.
I don't believe that.
I think a lot of them are going to live.
You know, that's just a...
You know, it's not really that informed.
I don't believe that.
Mmm.
I think the world might lose a queen or a prince.
Oh.
Are you saying Queen Elizabeth or Prince Charles will die this year?
How about neither of these?
That's what I'm thinking.
Yes.
I'd be very surprised.
If it is either one, I'm claiming two of three.
You know what's really funny?
Like, Prince Charles is an example of, like, why cousins shouldn't marry.
Yeah.
Like, Queen Elizabeth and Prince Philip.
Prince Philip were good-looking individuals.
You know, they were very sharp-looking in their day.
That's because they outsourced their gene pool.
And then they have a child who's as ugly as Prince Charles.
Oh.
That's...
So, my new Star Wars fan theory is that Han Solo and Princess Leia are actually cousins,
which is the only explanation for how they could have a child as ugly as Adam Driver.
That's why he had the helmet.
Yeah.
Could a celebrity die this year?
Could a celebrity die?
Several have.
You mean they're mortal?
You think a celebrity might die this year?
I think we're going to see more than one day.
Could a rock star die?
Might one of them even die at the age of 27?
A classic movie star.
What about a classic movie star?
God, what if that happens?
I have another question.
Everybody's talking about it.
Oh, like the founder of Black Lives Matter just died at the age of 27.
Did anybody hear about that?
I can't remember her name.
Garner's daughter.
Erica Garner.
Yeah, yeah.
She just died at the age of 27 from a heart attack.
Hello?
Another 27?
From a heart attack.
That's hard to believe.
Is the word heart attack in quotes?
I don't know, man.
I could start putting conspiracy theories out there that the man is trying to silence her voice,
but I don't really believe that because she had a history of...
I've got a question.
What about that Vegas shooting?
That kind of guy.
That wrapped up quite neatly, wouldn't you think?
Well, yeah.
The guy shot a bunch of people and then the cops shot him.
Yep.
Or no, they shot himself.
That's all that happened.
And anybody that said otherwise mysteriously had a heart attack or car wreck or...
I like to joke.
I'm making jokes, man.
I can believe someone can die of a heart attack.
I can believe someone can die of suicide.
I believe all kinds of deaths to be perfectly natural.
Oh, that's a great thought.
Forbidden me.
Every year.
Oh, right.
Death.
I predict lots of death.
What kind of collisions will they come up with the next exciting episode of America versus the world?
I predict earthquakes, hurricanes, wildfires, floods, and lots and lots of people dying.
That's my prediction for 2018.
I also predict that a lot of babies are going to be born and they will grow up to ask why,
oh, why parents did you bring me into a world?
like this.
Because it's just going to get worse.
I never asked
that question, but then...
Well, your generation had it
pretty easy.
Aside from the whole Vietnam draft thing,
your generation had it pretty easy.
Oh, no kidding.
Oh, my God.
It's like being an emperor
or a king
in most ages.
Housing was cheap.
College was cheap.
Once it got past that,
wages were higher.
We had total, utter freedom
to destroy every single
people in your generation
to ever depend on.
You got to have free love
before AIDS came about.
That's true.
A lot of people in my generation
were warning.
They spent their lives
warning about all the stuff
that's going on now.
Hold on.
I don't know who hung up.
I don't know who we lost.
Okay.
I'll pick the right button.
Am I here?
Hello?
Yes, you're still here.
So we have...
I am here, but I would like to
ask one question
before I leave on this
wonderful dawn of a new age.
I have one question.
Why not both?
¿Por qué no los dos?
That's the best question.
I've heard this all the time.
¿Por qué no los dos?
Move to the front of the class.
And on that,
I would like to say
thank you for having me
on your show.
All right.
Thank you.
And all the members
of your cast and crew,
thank you for everyone
in the studio.
And I appreciate
every moment
that you've given me
some brief thought
or levity
or some distraction
from the unnamed crap
going on in my world.
Thank you for listening.
Thank you for listening
to your podcast
has made me feel
a lot better
about a lot of crap.
How dare you call this
a podcast?
This is a broadcast.
Damn it.
Podcasts are anathema
to what we do here.
I tell you what, sir.
I live in Texas
and your radio broadcast
is fairly difficult
for me to receive
on the regular.
But it's not a podcast.
It's a live stream
in your case.
When I listen to things
from your podcast, sir,
when I listen to snippets
from your show...
Oh, my God.
Listen, I don't know
which line you're on,
so I'm going to hang up
on somebody here.
I'm here.
I have found you
through podcasts, sir.
Okay, well, thank you.
And I would like to thank you
for finding your way
to my ears.
Well, it is my pleasure.
And for all the people
that have brought
some entertainment
into my life.
So you all
have a wonderful evening
and thank you very much,
especially Reverend Sting,
for being alive
and near to my heart.
All right.
I'm not sure
which line you're on,
so I might hang up
on the wrong person here
when you hang up.
All right.
Well, I will leave you all
by saying,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right.
Let's hope it's
the right button.
Good evening.
And...
Who's still there?
It hurts when they...
Yes.
It is.
When they pull out.
Oh, right.
I picked the right line.
Guys, we have...
We have...
How many minutes
until the countdown?
Five minutes
and 40 seconds
left in this year.
Good Lord, man.
It's hard to believe.
It really is.
The days and the years,
they just fly by.
So what's on your mind, Keith?
We haven't heard much from you.
I don't have much to say.
No, it's just another year.
Just another year.
Just another show.
Glad to be up here.
I'm glad to have everybody here, too, man.
Glad to have all the food
and glad to have...
Yeah, the last several New Years,
I've just spent, like, alone
in the dark, so...
I don't know what I've done
the last couple years.
You forgot?
That sounds like Princess We
in the background.
Hey, Princess We.
Hey, Keith.
Oh, I'm so glad.
Always a pleasure.
I'm so glad to see you guys.
We're getting all verklempt about it.
Uh-oh.
Who's verklempt?
You should steal some
of Shearer's antidepressants.
Yeah, I see Sergio
in the other room
is breaking out the bubbly.
Oh, man.
Wow.
I think we've got some
sparkling cider.
Some fine champagne.
Or something
in the next room over.
Oh, we're gonna have to celebrate.
Is there gonna be a countdown?
There will be a countdown.
I'm looking at the official
atomic clock right now.
Counting down until our balls drop.
Oh, yeah.
It'll happen in a year right now.
No, man, like, you know,
we'll, you know,
like I said, you know,
Times Square,
they drop the ball once a year.
Is that a sassyism?
Wasn't that his thing?
The balls, like,
balls dropping at midnight
or something?
It sounds like a sweet-ass
sassafrasis.
There's a long list
of sassies.
I still have.
I gotta be very careful
about violating sassies' words.
Because as we all know,
if you say the wrong thing
at the wrong time,
he might call you up
and threaten to bust your teeth out
and play him like a xylophone.
I believe that there are
certain terms that I coined.
And I don't remember ever
having heard a reference to,
what's the big deal?
They drop the ball once a year.
I drop the ball every week.
I believe I coined that.
Yeah, I've never heard
anybody else say that.
That's me, all right?
Like, we're better at dropping
the ball than the Browns are.
Like, it makes it look good.
Good.
And, um...
Also, I can't remember
anybody saying serial caller
before me.
I mean, I...
No, that's been around
for a long time.
That's been a long time.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Serial callers go back
to, like, Waynestead.
Okay.
Way back.
I've heard the term
being said back then.
There was a time then
when people, uh,
when the expression
fell out of favor.
Probably.
Because I,
I did not hear that
in the night,
like, the late 90s,
early aughts.
That's because we
developed gluten problems.
Uh.
And serial didn't agree
with us anymore.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
But the one thing
that you said...
Oh, yeah.
Como va?
It caught my ear.
You're gonna flip
the calendar.
I kept saying...
Hey, we have, uh...
Is Sassy coming down?
We don't have Sassy
here right now.
We have one more caller
coming in here.
You're on the radio.
How's it going, guys?
It's almost a new year.
Almost a new year.
We have, uh,
just, uh,
two and a half minutes
left here.
Oh, my God.
I'm counting.
Yeah, people are
actually not over here
in Cleveland.
All right.
Everybody, everybody
talk at once.
Okay.
I'd be happy to speak
here at once
and, um, say something
and accept...
New caller.
It doesn't work
when I'm the only one.
Oh, okay.
New caller,
what did you want to say?
I don't know.
I just wanted to get
in here and talk
with you guys.
All right.
Well, uh,
the program will be over
before too long.
But that's okay
because there's another
one starting.
Exactly.
This is an all
night rager.
Not a rager, really.
No.
We're actually being
very neat and tidy.
Mm-hmm.
Control your hormones.
We will leave the place
cleaner than we found it.
That's doubtful
because we can't get
access to the vacuum.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Really?
We did a vacuum cleaner now?
Well, I mean,
it's kind of...
Two minutes
to the new world.
The new age starts
in two minutes.
Two minutes.
It's a new age.
I mean, I'll go in.
What about the...
Yeah, what is the age
of Aquarius?
Anyway, I think
that's long past.
I'm sorry.
That one came and went.
It was a little bit...
It didn't quite live up
to its rep.
Really?
You mean astrology
proved to be incorrect?
Well,
well,
look,
the new age starts
in a minute and a half
or something.
I don't have a second.
Oh, we have...
We have one...
minute...
left...
as of now.
All right.
So our official countdown
is on.
Our official countdown
It's the last minute
of the year.
WCSB, synesthesia,
New Year's Eve,
spectacular, spectacular.
Ex-crap-a-ganza.
Oh, man,
we got crap
coming up next.
Don't you dare
turn off your radio
because the festivities
are continuing
well into the night here.
So,
anything anybody
wants to say
before the world ends?
Any last final,
really brief,
brief thoughts?
Uh, goodbye,
370.
If the radio
suddenly shuts off,
don't panic.
Yeah,
I can't wait
till this year is over.
Oh, yes, okay,
Tabitha, Jeremy,
back in the room
here with us.
This might be
the year that actually
is Y2K.
We're all together.
Or it might be
1997.
Where's Potsy?
Where the hell's Potsy?
He's the dog!
Or it might be
1997.
Ten,
nine,
eight,
seven,
six,
five,
four,
three,
two,
one,
Happy New Year!
Yeah.
2018.
Anti-regnant
stuff, man,
yeah.
Woo!
We made it.
Oh, you're not
going to be able
to play that.
Did I miss it?
Yeah, missed it.
Oh, yeah, missed it.
I saw a fight there.
Oh, yes.
Yeah, you're not,
you're late.
You're late for 2018.
Yeah, Sinister,
you can't play something
off the computer
while the audio file
is going.
Can we repeat it?
Yeah, hang on.
Rewind it for Potsy.
That's okay.
You can show up
once on
five,
four,
three,
two.
Tune up Chicago.
They got a thing
where they raise
something instead of
crying.
Oh, wow.
All right, folks.
Stars.
Thank you very much
for tuning in here.
This has been
Sinesthesia on WCSB.
Stay tuned for a very
special episode of
Crap Radio.
The New Year's Eve
spectacular
craptacular
continues
in just a moment.
I got to let you
callers go, okay?
Have a good one, man.
Don't go away.
We'll be back.
Thank you.
And until,
until next week,
until next year,
whatever,
keep it surreal.
Oh, yes, dear friends.
As you probably surmised,
that was the last show
of 2017
of Dr. Sinister's
Radio Sinesthesia.
And we called in
in the last half hour.
And now that that's done
and we want to put it out
on New Year's Day,
I needed to fill out
the rest of the hour.
And luckily,
we have a ton of new,
what you might call
media barrage
of media barrage
edits
that were sent in
on a CD
from our old friend
Cool Hand Chris,
also known as
Christian Blatter.
And he sent some,
some really weird music also
and a DVD
that we haven't seen yet.
But this is a pretty wild,
old school,
subgenius style
media barrage
from Cool Hand Chris
and happy,
whatever,
year this really is
to you
and all our listeners
and contributors
and J.R. Bob Dobbs himself.
Price Bob,
Hail Connie.
Let's go.
What do you expect us
modern mothers to do?
Quit trying to be butterflies.
Get back to the business
of being mothers
like your mother
and your grandmother
and generations of mothers
before them.
I haven't been devoting
enough time
to just being a mother.
Oh,
mother,
it isn't your fault,
it's mine.
Oh,
I've been so stupid.
It's all my fault.
I should have realized
something was wrong.
What was in that hypo?
Talk, talk, talk, talk,
talk a revolution
and you're out to entertain.
I have a message for thee.
Hypocrite.
Your soul is dead.
Don't give me
your political bullshit.
Something about revolution.
Put the knife in the back.
How can you fuck
the only people
who have a gift?
Feels like the guy next.
Stop it.
Your whole shit
sound like coward.
The world isn't quite as simple
as we'd like it to be.
But I hope it makes you
very rich.
You know,
does he really,
truly love me?
Oh, no.
I ain't getting no cut.
No percentage.
Zero percentage.
Zero.
No dough.
Bitch of mine
better not keep it done.
Life ain't fair,
you know what I'm saying?
Done.
I had part of the money.
She had part of the money.
That's like
a divided situation.
There might be
a rich man or something.
She don't even know
how to be around
this rich man.
She don't know
how to act or to seduce
this rich man
because it ain't been taught her.
He might want to
afford 50 bucks
or 100 bucks,
but he come in front
of my hoes,
he gonna get broke
for damn near
whatever he has.
What's happening here
is also happening
to some extent
at virtually
every other
American installation
in Vietnam.
Recent surveys estimate
that well over 50%
of the soldiers
in Vietnam
use marijuana.
You get really stoned.
Then, you know,
who like,
who cares about the war?
This war.
It is time
for an honest look
at the problem of order
in the United States.
So I pledge to you,
we shall have order
in the United States.
Star Wars Gangsta Rap.
A lie
Another Dark Jedi
He will join us or die
We got Jeff Start
Jeff Start
Man you know that we got it
Jeff!
Get your ass over here right now
from hooking around
with that damn Lance Beard.
Weren't the two droids
I asked you to clean, boys?
Clean your room!
My Lord,
Is that legal?
I won't let it little.
Show you I will.
You take a little butter.
It's just going to be you and me.
And make it all real nice.
Red leader, red leader, fuck it back.
Add a little bit of the force.
You know it feels alright.
Five, red five, stand by.
Three, two, one.
Yee-ha!
Alright kid, let's blow this thing and go home, alright?
Stay on target.
After the spell.
Everything is back to normal.
I think, I think I can go back to normal.
I'm trying to destroy the world again.
Would you consider yourself a revolutionary?
Well no, but I do believe corporations rob us of our dignity and independence.
And that these systems must be ripped down, burnt down, or leveled by any force necessary.
Everyone stay calm.
Because we're all doomed!
I don't make monkeys, I just train them.
Thank you, you are cleared through voice print identification.
Goose-stepping morons like yourself should try reading books instead of burn.
This is a hybrid, this is across bluegrass, Kentucky bluegrass, featherbed bent, and northern California, Sinsomea.
The amazing stuff about this is that you can play 36 holes on it in the afternoon, take it home, and just get stoned to the bejesus belt that night on this stuff.
It would appear that the government at the moment is practicing a lot of this wrong.
It's a religion in absentia for many folks.
It was a trendy thing.
Well we're actually the conspiracy, you've always heard of the conspiracy, right?
Yeah.
Well we're the conspiracy behind the conspiracy.
And we've decided to come out in the open.
You're the unnamed source.
That's us.
Well you certainly have heard of the Public Criminization Society.
The conspiracy has been trying to squelch abnormality since time began, practically.
It goes so far.
It goes so far back and it's so ingrained in our culture that it's gotten to where the conspiracy leaders don't have to do anything because it's an endless cycle of normalcy.
Even kids with latent subgenius genes are born, but they're raised by the conspiracy making them want to be popular, raising them to be happy with mediocrity, with everything being the same.
I am now learning to apply creative and corrective procedures,
and to bring back to normalcy the world of the conspiracy.
And to bring back to normalcy the world of the conspiracy.
I can easily do anything that I want to do.
I can.
I'm a winner.
Are you abnormal?
Then you are probably better than most people.
Yes, your kind shall triumph.
Yes, you tool shall молод.
Шатука towerけるэ
Ша каретей
Думал,
Джuto
comida
Thank you.
Your powers a weak old man.
You should not have come back.
You can't win.
I'm gonna kick your body, hit him on the side.
Oh, I want to see him on the side.
Oh, I say, oh, my side.
Oh, I want to kick your body.
You cannot win.
If you strike me down, I'll become more powerful than you can possibly imagine.
Show you I will.
Shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot, show you I will.
R2? R2?
Your mind is a bitch and you know it.
I want those plans.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
You've got a bad feeling about this.
Surprise.
I am your father.
No!
It's not true.
Oh, yeah, it is, baby.
What makes you qualified to be a reporter?
I'm willing to violate anyone's privacy for my personal gain and then claim with a straight face that the public has a right to know.
Only a fool tries to fool Mr. T.
Strength is irrelevant. Resistance is futile. We wish to improve ourselves.
We will add your biological intelligence.
We will add your technological distinctiveness to our own.
Your culture will adapt to service ours.
He don't know me very well, do he?
Now listen here, you mullet.
Why don't you just light your tampon and blow your box apart?
Because it's the only bang you're ever gonna get, sweetheart.
I was piloting the Black Ops missions in the jungles of North Vietnam where you were sucking on your mama's tit at Woodstock.
Don't lecture me about war.
Laugh for while you can, monkey boy.
Headline edition July 8, 1947.
The Army Air Forces has announced that a flying disc has been found and is now in the possession of the Army.
Army officers say the missile, found sometime last week, has been inspected at Roswell, New Mexico and sent to...
Bob?
...for further inspection.
I smell conspiracy in every nook, cube, and plasticoid cranny.
I smell conspiracy.
Lay your hands on the radio! Lay your hands on the radio and home!
At last I have control of your radio tubes!
And I do too.
Good. This is Ren Huat.
And this is Stimson J. Catt of the Ren and Stimpy Show.
And you're listening to the Hour of Slack.
Keep listening, you idiot!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Else I shall kill you!
Take four red capsules.
In ten minutes, take two more.
They think they'll see an assault coming.
You recognize that car?
Even their computer is safe from outside attack.
So they think.
They've added a commercial virus protection program to keep their files from being frozen or destroyed by an outsider.
They don't know that the real attack began weeks earlier at a government computer center.
Federal agents have already entered that farmhouse through the virus protection program itself.
The software update that loads the virus protection program into the farmhouse computer includes a so-called Trojan horse.
A set of hidden instructions that lodge in the computer.
This piece of software installs itself into their system and sends a copy of everything on their computer to the federal agents at night.
Along with the Trojan horse is a logical bomb.
It's another set of hidden priorities waiting to go off at the right moment.
That moment signals the start of the federal assault.
By flashing a new warrant on the farmhouse computer.
Telling the occupants to surrender.
And to throw the institution down and climb up the high пост yeah yeah.
It freezes on the screen.
The computer refuses to function further,
ignores all further keyboard and mouse commands.
The night passes without further event.
By morning, nothing much has changed,
but that, too, is deceptive.
400 yards away,
two snipers are lying out in the open,
disguised by metamorphic camouflage.
The chemicals in their uniforms change color
to match the light of the scene behind them.
Up close, there's only a slight shimmering effect.
From a distance, they're invisible.
As the two snipers move closer for the final assault,
their camouflage changes.
When they move from shade to sunlight,
the pattern lightens.
As they pass a shadow, it darkens again.
The modeled effect lets them neatly blend in
with their surroundings.
Even at 20 yards, the lookout sees almost nothing.
If he sees anything, he'll probably see nothing.
But if he sees something, he'll probably think
it's just rising heat waves.
I bet they can hear the noise coming from that engine
on that vehicle, even though they can't see it.
Underneath those waves is a light armored vehicle,
also hidden by active camouflage.
It's wrapped on all sides with millions of fiber optic cables
that send a picture to one side of the vehicle
of what's on the other side.
Meanwhile, a helicopter circles overhead.
That's nothing new.
Helicopters have been here for weeks, patrolling the compound perimeter.
The helicopter drops a canister behind the house.
Moments later, it drops a second canister in the yard.
A few hours later, after dark, a preset timer in one canister
sets off a brief crackling sound.
And behind that, a
suddenly, every electrical device in the compound goes out.
Lights, appliances, computers, they all flicker and die,
fried by a burst of electromagnetic pulse.
The occupants know something is happening.
Stay calm.
But what? There's another crackle, a burst of EMP from the second canister.
Every light in the compound goes out for good as the backup generator dies.
Inside the light-armored vehicle, the assault team gets ready for the final operation.
In their own camouflage, they quickly cover the last few yards to the compound.
Now that it's night, the two snipers who have been outside all day join them, working their way to the main entrance.
Instead of trying to break down the metal door, they spray it with a chemical that turns it as brittle as a cracker.
One push brings it down.
They toss in a flashbang, a distraction device that works like a giant firecracker.
A second grenade fills the interior with a sedative agent.
Before the occupants can regain their bearings, every corner of the room is filled with sedative-laden smoke.
The assault teams are protected by their jumpsuits and gas masks.
The chemical quickly subdues everyone, adults and children, or puts them to sleep entirely.
One man and one woman have been in another room, unaffected by the sedative.
An agent catches the woman with a snare net.
A stream of pepper-laced aqueous foam appears out of nowhere to cover the fleeing man.
He falls to the ground from the pain.
Inside, team members begin flex-cuffing their frightened, groggy targets.
Suddenly, one more man bursts from a closet.
Carrying a gun.
That shot was a liquid-filled 12-gauge round that bursts on impact, dissipating the energy and spraying the target with pepper spray.
Help!
Sir, it's just a tip.
If we leave this place early, there will be no end to myself.
We don't come to
No, come on, don't leave.
We give the top ру
What's it like...
What's it like there?
drinking 46 packs?
What's it like to be dead in a żyłowieus second?
not worth anything to yourself, and not worth anything to the rest of us?
What's it like...
How was it?
transformed and recovered?
You see things in life and you'd be surprised what you see.
Life, your whole life is changes.
You go through changes in your life.
One second, you got it made.
Next second, you're down in the dumps.
And it goes back and forth throughout your whole life.
One second, you got the most beautiful girl in the world.
Next second, you don't even have a girlfriend no more.
And it goes back and forth and back and forth, you know?
And this is life, man.
It's changes.
This is what you got to go through throughout your whole lifetime.
Never, never, never land.
Some believe that there may yet be brothers of man
who even now fight to survive somewhere beyond the heavens.
We realize that you have the ability,
and it's not below you people,
to decide.
Do something like erase all evidences.
Why do you have the press so far back?
You can give me any kind of crap you want.
I know.
You know.
The reason we're not talking to the press
is you people have got to cover your butts from what you did.
And that's what's going on here.
We interrupt this program with a special bulletin.
America is now under martial law.
All.
All constitutional rights have been suspended.
Stay in your homes.
Do not attempt to contact loved ones, insurance agents, or attorneys.
Shut up.
Do not attempt to think or depression may occur.
Stay in your homes.
Curfew is at 7 p.m. sharp after work.
Anyone caught outside the gates of their homes,
or in their subdivision sectors after curfew,
will be shot.
Remain calm.
Do not panic.
Your neighborhood watch officer will be by to collect urine samples in the morning.
Anyone caught interfering with the collection of urine samples will be shot.
Stay in your homes.
Remain calm.
The number one enemy of progress is questions.
National security is more important than individual will.
All sports broadcasts will proceed as normal.
No more than two people may gather anywhere without permission.
Use only the drugs prescribed by your boss or supervisor.
Shut up.
Be happy.
Obey all orders without question.
The comfort you've demanded is now mandatory.
Be happy.
At last, everything is done for you.
But you can learn more from subgenius.com
or write to our new address at the compound here at
Post Office Box 807-325-7000.
Glen Rose, Texas 76043.