Bio, bio, bio, bio, well, well, well...
You remember yesterday, nothing happened,
because this program hadn't started yet.
Well, today, having wrested Carl Morgan's gun from him
after making him think his shoelace was untied,
Julia Fairholme smiles evilly
as Carl attempts to dissuade her from taking his life.
Let's listen.
Julia!
That's right, Carl.
A piece of double bubble gum
with your thumbprint on the funny wrapper it comes in.
Julia, there's a bluebird on your shoulder.
What?
Take that gun now, if you don't mind.
Now, Julia Fairholme,
let's see how you like looking down the business end
of a .38 caliber Smith & Wesson revolver for a change.
Well, what's going to happen next time?
Don't fail to miss our next exciting episode
when we'll...
You'll hear Julia say...
Carl, you tricked me.
There wasn't a bluebird on my shoulder at all.
It was an owl.
In the expected confidence...
All too soon.
The show ends and the show begins.
Above all, we want you to be satisfied.
We want you to never forget.
That's right.
These awful shows.
The terrible wasted lives that you've spent.
The collective years of listening to this...
This rotten show.
Yes.
And you don't even get it.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
On a friendly basis.
Wait.
I don't think that's really it.
I think an alien has taken him over.
To a long and pleasant relationship with you.
Raining in the wings.
I don't mind...
Goodbye and hello again.
I don't know, but it's certainly worth investigating.
Why, that's crazy.
Ha!
Impossible.
Thank you for joining us.
We'll be with you in just one minute.
Wake up, puppet boy!
This is Doug Smith, radio operator.
I'm going to bring you a piece of that green cheese for sure.
I am Buck Larkin!
No trouble.
Let's get set and get going.
Amen.
According.
Everything's going fine.
No trouble.
Welcome, potential initiates.
And remain with us for the next 30 minutes.
Bob?
The message is now part of and registered in your subconscious mind.
And every time you say...
I see, hear, or think.
What about Slack?
That's your key phrase.
It will trigger the entire message without your being aware of it.
Here the watch in front of us blurs and distorts time.
Soon we will be deep in a hypnotic trance.
What wonders will we see?
Hey kids, get some money out of your parents' wallet.
And send it to Bob.
Here.
Pull up the level.
There you go.
Ladies and gentlemen, this is the Hour of Slack.
Boom!
The opinions expressed are not necessarily those of this radio station.
Before the sermon, a message concerning Bob Dobbs,
living avatar of Slack, and saint of sales on Planet.
You have to love Bob.
He loves you, but you love Bob.
You have to.
Or else what happens if you don't love Bob?
He'll kill you.
He'll bob you out.
He'll bob you out, folks.
You heard it here first.
If you don't love Bob, he'll bob you out.
Well, yes, dear friends.
And if you don't love Bob enough,
there won't be no more Bob on the airwaves here in Dallas, Texas, dear friends.
Yes, the pledge drive is going to continue.
And I know you love the pledge drive on this show
because you love Bob.
You love to give money, don't you?
Friends, the blanks and Phil, that's right, Phil and the blanks are all here.
And they were disgusted with the horrible turnout last week, friends.
We only made $750.
Now, we need, there was one person pledged $740.
And then there were two $5 checks, and they both bounced.
And now this time, friends, I don't want to.
I don't want to have any more of that.
I want you to call up.
And I know there's some poverty-stricken subgeniuses out there,
but most of you are probably fantastically wealthy compared to this station.
You can spare that $5 for the newsletter,
that $25 for the newsletter bumper sticker,
and the $30 for T-shirt and so forth.
If you will but call and pledge, friends,
give yourself to the feeling, please,
and call 823.
823-7490.
That's one number.
Get them pencils ready.
If you don't pledge pretty soon,
if we don't raise, oh, let's say, $50 in the next, oh, 15 minutes,
I'm going to have to get on my Casio and play for you.
That's right.
Just like Dr. Gene.
That's how he raises money.
He plays until they call in.
So call 823-8883.
That's a great year, friends.
That's when peace and love will reign over the whole planet.
We'll all have slack.
Instantly.
In the year.
823-8883.
But only, friends, only if you reach deep into that,
into your guts, into the most holy organ in your body,
your wallet,
and call and pledge us some money
or send us some to K-N-O-N, box.
Get that pencil ready.
Here's the box number, friends.
Give yourself to the feeling.
It's box 141.
1-9-9 here in Dallas, Texas.
And that's 75214.
Praise Bob, help me somebody.
Johnny, what can I do?
Give yourself to the feeling.
Johnny, Johnny, what can I do?
Johnny.
Johnny, Johnny.
Do your duty.
Do yourself to the feeling.
Johnny, Johnny.
Do your duty.
Do yourself to the feeling.
Still not done.
You ought to add art.
Another one, WE.
This time, baby.
No, no, skip it.
Much of the difficulty arises from hearing too many things at once.
Whoops.
This is a tape.
Yes, this is not live.
A tape, a tape, a tape, a tape.
You know, it's not real.
It's a tape, a tape, a tape, a tape, a tape.
It's a tape, a tape, a tape.
I've seen them, you know.
They do it.
They pee down the register.
That's how it registers.
They do it, you know.
You just turn the register on in winter
and this horrible white musk-like smoke spills out of it,
and you know they've been at work.
Now, is there any objection to this argument?
I thought not.
Yes, you, listener, are living proof that God does not exist.
You, the listener, are proof that there is no such thing,
nor could there be as a supreme being.
For were there a God in heaven,
he would not permit such pernicious vermin as you listeners
to exist upon the face of this tormented planet.
And here we are, we're starting the show.
We're beginning to be funny at this hour.
Is this the beginning of the...
This is the beginning of the...
Is this the real show?
This is the show.
I have heard of a true show such as this.
No, that's silly.
Show is our worship word, too.
But we'll be able to use it.
Don't worry.
Is this then the show that...
Is this the show that...
This is an actual show, not a test.
If this had been a test,
you would not now be listening to the Subdivis show.
All I can say is...
All teenage kids and hip groovers in the area listen to our show.
No.
Yes, we are so hip, so pop.
So, so, so where it's at.
Yes, we're so hip, so pop.
What is happening?
Where it's at.
So groovy, friend.
So, so, so K-N-O-N.
And it's gonna dry up if you don't pledge.
Oh, that's right.
You gotta call Phil and the Blanks
are dying to hear your calls, friends.
Because it's gonna take you.
Only you can help us.
This concludes...
Because people like you
are helping us stay on the radio.
You can't buy a miracle.
But you can certainly stand behind a miracle ministry.
Oh, that's right, folks.
You can, and people are standing behind.
Oh, listen to those phones light up
while I hear the great...
Praise Doug DelGrosso.
E-I-I-I of the Hidden Circle.
Whose tremendous pledge just came through.
And friends,
friends, we can't keep saving the world for nothing.
See, that's the bottom line.
There's these, we call them gimme bobs out there.
And that's what most of y'all are.
If you have never given any money to this station,
you're just a mere gimme bob.
I'm no gimme bob.
I give credit.
That music we were playing during the last rant
was by D.K. Jones,
the great band D.K. Jones,
Reverend Dennis Kelly in New York.
Yes, you've heard.
You've heard him before on this show.
And also a little bit of the show show
from Berkeley.
And I just praise Bob.
Friends, it's that number to call.
823-8801,
823-8883,
or 823-7490.
823-8880.
You're on the telephone.
I want some money here.
Come on, you guys.
Get on there.
We need money.
Call 823-7490.
823-8883,
and 823-8801.
You're on the telephone.
Help Stan.
Help Bob.
We need the money.
That's 823-853,
no, 823-7490,
or 823-7490.
823-88801.
Or we'll never quit playing this song
by Reverend Mark Mothersbaugh.
Thank y'all.
Hey, Bob.
Hey.
Welcome to Babylon, children.
Oh, yeah.
It's great to be here in the belly of the beast
tonight, before we get started with our second LA Divide.
If we could all please bow our heads and have a moment of sacred traditional noise.
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la, la.
Now, friends, see?
Oh, yeah!
Oh, it would have been a great devival if only you'd been there spending money, but
you weren't.
You weren't.
You didn't do nothing to help resurrect Bob.
And so what are we going to do?
All we can do is sit here on this, doing this show for a bunch of gimme Bobs.
I mean, we've only gotten one major pledge.
Now, there's been a bunch of small, measly $50 pledges.
We need a...
This is real, actually quite serious, friends.
The status of this show depends on your pledge, and the status of this station depends on
your pledge.
Thank y'all.
But remember, the end of the world may be much worse and take much longer.
Thank you.
Then you've fought.
The mere act of sitting in your home watching everything fall apart on TV may be too much
for even the stoutest brains to take.
In fact, the more alert and intelligent you are, the quicker you'll likely be driven
to suicide by the sheer hideousness of what you'll be seeing.
Will you be ready?
Will you still bring good with you millones of dollars?
be sane enough to laugh when that which must come to pass comes to pass will you ever get slack
break out of that glass box and join the church of the subgenius but we won't let you in a country
freedom of religion is guaranteed by the constitution anything is likely to develop
enter the church of the subgenius billing itself as the weirdest cult on earth what do they believe
in everything who do they believe in a mysterious character named Bob Bob is the culmination of that
to which man has aspired throughout his long and slack less history Bob is what will bring slack to
planet earth Bob founded the church mainly to help unmask the conspiracy we're talking about
the conspiracy just
believe in the power of the dogs
believe in Bob
reach out for him
feel the healing power
see friends you can't you can't feel the healing power there's no way unless you start to play
escort reverend stang out and lock him out of this place
in all reality help me somebody she ain't got no legs pull the lever down and go
my legs are on fire
I'm doing a challenge here all North Texas students listening to this wonderful show call up and pledge
pledge for Bob's sake please let me give you the phone numbers where you can pledge here
823-7490 823-8883 and 823-8801 fans of Bob please call if you're from North Texas please call now
Bob's sake please call if you're from North Texas please call now
by earning a dollar
our
personal
who won't
screw me
up
is praise Bob, Dr., let's call him Dr. Lazarus,
who just called in and pledged a mighty, mighty amount.
Praise Bob.
Oh, and praise Robert.
Yes.
We'll even praise Robert tonight, friends.
In heaven, everything's all right.
In heaven, everything is fine.
You got your money, and I got mine.
And if you don't pledge the 2-823-7490, Bob will die again, friends.
He'll suffer more, and it'll be all your fault,
and this will turn into a church of guilt and sin and hate
and intolerance for the weirdos because of you.
Sad and sickening, isn't it?
That's the praise.
Thank you.
Dr. Gross on that organ there.
Get on them phones.
Who wants some money here?
Right here, right now.
You too, Bob.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
Bob is a rock, and Bob is a tree.
Bob is a bear, and Bob is a bee.
Bob is truth, and Bob is lies.
Bob is cakes, and fruits, and pies.
Bob's my house.
Bob's my watch.
Bob's my sandwich.
Bob's my crotch.
Bob's my toothpick.
Bob's my brain.
Bob's an ugly yellow stain.
Bob's a cactus.
Bob's an itch.
Bob is take off every stitch.
Bob's my master.
Bob's my slave.
Bob will rob me.
Bob will save.
Bob's my toaster.
Bob's my fridge.
Bob's my liquor.
No, sister, a minch.
Bob, Bob will cost you.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob is free.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob's a rock.
Bob's the key.
In short, Bob's the man.
Who used your leg as a frying pan?
If your mind is a jar.
You can pour down a sink.
The subgenus church is the missing link.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob...
But let's leave things of this world behind.
and walk now down the path of Bob for this brief minute of slack from the Church of the Subgenius.
This is Reverend Ivan Stang with the Sorry Truth.
Now, friend, look around you and face facts.
The world is composed mostly of jerks.
All kinds of ignorant, dangerous, thoughtless louts are in positions of power and influence
while some of the most deserving people you know are slugging it out
in a thankless cycle of brain-breaking labor and mental paralysis.
Checks and balances? What a joke.
Friend, if you want to get slack, then you better uphold the Great Covenant, yes?
Before you were born, you swore you'd help in the great battle against them.
That's right, them.
The normals, the mediocrities, the Barbies and Kens, the pink boys, the somnambulax,
the cage men, the time servers, the Philistines, the witch burners.
Those who have made slack?
Taboo.
That's right, friend, there's only two races in this world, us and them.
Whose side are you on, eh?
Let there be slack.
Ah, yes, dear friends, it's true.
Listen, oh, it's getting cold here in the station.
It's gonna get colder if we don't get more money.
That's right, that's all we care about, friends.
Praise Reverend Felix.
He yields out there.
He's an honorary subgenius now.
Oh, we have to play music.
Whew.
All right, well, how about that last piece of music?
That was by Reverend Bleepo Abernathy, yes?
Have we got a new total here?
We have a new total here.
Oh, praise Bob.
A new total.
In suspense.
Praise Bob.
$100 plus 50 that you just received from Brother Larry.
We now have a total for the first half hour.
Of about $150 for the show.
Oh, praise Bob.
Praise Bob.
Whew, help me somebody.
It's coming in our hands.
90.9, that is Texas.
Yeah.
When I was playing K&L in 90.9, I was doing all that funny stuff, but now I'm gonna do
some of the stuff that isn't funny.
I'm gonna talk about things that isn't funny, things that are not funny.
All right.
When you're finished, I'm gonna go.
Oh, I'm gonna do a little joke.
Don't throw the peel on the underground.
Somebody can slip.
That's not funny.
Also, when somebody falls on the pavement with bare legs, when they're running, and
they have a booboo, that's not funny.
They should go inside and tell their mom.
This is a joke about a banana.
This is funny thing.
When people,
when people,
when people get dressed up like a clown
and act like a clown,
and they do something clowny and funny,
that's really funny.
If it falls down and not hold itself
and bump it on the head, that's not funny.
That's funny.
Isn't it?
Aren't you not having fun today?
Because you can't play outside.
You can't play on your swings up because you're sick.
When you're sick, it's not very fun.
That's right.
This is K and O and 90.9.
Listen to my tale then.
But why, why do you call me mad?
Could a mad man have written songs such as these?
I think not.
I'm not mad.
I'm merely an ordinary person seeking life,
liberty, and the pursuit of happiness.
My pursuit of happiness includes machine gunning 127
innocent children.
If that's mad, go ahead, lock me up.
Oh!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Just because I enjoy washing my face in the blood of infants,
is that any reason to lock me up?
Oh!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
I think not.
I've even got a piece of paper that says my mind is still OK.
Hell, I bet that guy down at the employment agency
wouldn't give me a job just because I've been locked up
one time.
Bet he ain't got a piece of paper that says his mind is
still OK.
Hell.
Oh.
I tried to tell them it was not me.
It was the green energy demons, but they merely laughed at me.
But now those green energy demons are ruling the planet.
They're not laughing, fighting so hard now, are they?
But that wasn't nearly as bad as that time they shocked
the living gee out of me.
Hey!
I tried to explain it was not me.
It was the brain, the brain of Arnold Palmer, which was
controlling my mind.
Via laser beam, via the FBI, via the CIA, via the Communist
Party, via satellite.
It was the demon, the demon that forced me to do the deed.
But that wasn't nearly dot, dot, dot.
But it wasn't.
I'm not insane.
I'm more sane than Son of Sam and Charles Madsen put
together.
How many people must I kill to prove I'm not insane?
You know what I mean?
I'm not insane.
That wasn't nearly as bad as that time they shocked the living
gee out of me.
I didn't mind when they shocked the living pee out of me.
In fact, I kind of enjoyed it when they shocked the living
zero out of me.
That time they ran over my face with a pickup truck.
Oh, yeah.
That was fun.
That time they cut me in half with barbed wire and then peeled a bandaid off my amputated arm.
Oh yeah, that was fun.
That time they skinned me alive and called me dirty names.
Woo-ha! That was a big ol' cocaine party.
That one time they converted my entire body into a wall of membrane whose only purpose was to feel pain.
That time they converted my entire body to a wall of membrane attached to a human brain whose only purpose was to feel pain and then applied the flame.
Oh yeah, that was fun.
That time they converted every cell in my body to the same nerve endings found in male testicles,
enlarged each cell to the size of a sun,
and then inserted huge sun-sized cells into my body.
Oh yeah, that was fun.
That one time they converted every cell in my body to a sun-sized male testicle,
enlarged each cell into a sun-sized male testicle,
And friends, what Reverend Jayner Hyperkleets, Saint Jayner Hyperkleets I should say, of Doctors for Bob,
is trying to tell you is that if you don't pledge money, we don't even want to talk to you, understand?
I mean, you can be calling in and I say, well, have you pledged?
Well, no, what do you want me to do?
Good Lord, friends!
Actually, actually we have raised a record amount on this show right now, I can't believe it!
Uh, praise Reverend Fields.
Ay-yi-yi-yi!
Reverend Perryman.
Atmosphere.
Oh yes, there's some mighty...
...good pills.
There's some mighty support going on out there, friends.
They had a needle that was so big, they had to lower me on top of it by helicopter in order to anesthetize me.
That's what's going to happen to you and Doctors for Bob.
This universe will end if you don't pledge that money, friends.
And by the way, here's a...
We have some friends in Los Angeles who do...
Well, they do mean things on the phone and this is one of their phone calls here.
I hope this sounds right for you.
Yes, uh, can I speak to the manager, please?
Uh, I'm the manager in charge.
Thank you, uh, I have a problem, um, well actually we have a problem.
This is Thomas Elkins calling.
And, uh, I was by the supermarket a little earlier and I was coming back from the lab where I work at and, uh, we had some animals with us, uh...
...I think it was a raccoon.
And the raccoon got loose and I think it got into the store and I was afraid to tell anybody at the time but, uh...
...I really need to get the raccoon back because it's sick.
And it could cause a problem for your...your store, uh...
Could you have somebody look for it, please?
You think it's in here?
Yeah, I know it's in here because it climbed in through the back.
I saw it enter, uh, through the back.
Through the back of the store.
It came inside?
Uh-huh.
How did it come into the back?
Uh, I don't know but I saw it...I saw it slide in.
It was like a...a crack in the door or something.
Maybe somebody was loading it.
How long ago was this?
Uh, this was within an hour.
Oh my God.
Yeah, the poor thing is really sick.
Where do you think...oh, shit.
Where do you think he's at in here?
Well, uh, I mean raccoons are animals and they eat food.
It's probably getting into your...your foodstuffs or something.
And those things...those things have like almost human hands.
They can undo packages and stuff.
Oh, great.
Well, what do you want to do?
Come down here?
Well, could you have somebody look for it?
I mean, I can...I can, uh...
This place is just...we're all jumping up here in the front busy.
Well, I mean, could you just have somebody check in the back quickly?
I mean, uh, the thing is...is kind of friendly.
I mean, if you pick it up carefully, it shouldn't be any problem.
I mean, it's...it's...it's only contagious if the thing eats something and leaves some food.
I mean, if you pick it up, you shouldn't have any problem.
Because, I mean, if you want to...
What part of the bag did it come in through?
Well, it's hard...I mean, I don't know your store.
It's really kind of difficult for me to say, but it just...
Where the trash cans are?
Right here on the side?
Um...
The...the side...you mean the side or the very back?
I think probably it was the side.
I mean, I...you know, I wasn't trying...I wasn't particularly paying attention, but I think it was like the side.
Yeah.
And he...you had him outside and he got in through the outside?
Well, the thing slipped out.
It was like a...a bad lock on the cage or something.
Ha.
Okay, can you call me back?
Well, uh, could you have somebody run back there and check right now?
Well, friends, we're not gonna tell you exactly what the outcome of that incredible call is unless...
That's right, we need to raise another hundred bucks.
See, we're going for a record tonight, folks.
I can't believe it, but we're doing real good on these pledges.
And the more money we get, the better J.R. Bob Dobbs, the living avatar of slack on this planet, looks.
Because, you know, when those aliens get here, friends, they're gonna wanna see figures.
They're gonna wanna see numbers.
They're gonna wanna see how much cash money you've spent before they'll let you board those escape vessels and...
And, uh, get away from this...this doomed planet before the tribulations really crank into effect.
So, keep calling. That's 823-8801.
Uh, 823-8883.
And 823-7490.
If you want to hear the rest of that incredible prank phone call in which our good friend, the Reverend, uh, Illuminati...
Yes, I can say his name on the air.
Uh, managed to convince the store owner that there was indeed a raccoon running around loose in the back of his store.
A contaminated raccoon, friends.
And that man spent hours and hours looking for it.
And this is but one of the incredible prank phone calls of which we have tapes that we can't play on the air.
Thank you.
Oh, and, uh, I don't know where Buck is, friends.
He called...I called him about an hour and a half ago and said, I'll see you down at the show.
And he goes, well, I was just taking a nap. I'll be down there.
So, friends, let's wake him up here with himself.
And if you don't, uh, if you don't call and pledge, friends, we'll never hear the end of that hideous prank phone call.
Praise Bob.
Hey, this one's called Wirehead Conspiracy.
It's about...it's about a dude I know.
I personally know who sold out to the UFOs.
Oh, my God!
All of us!
A light from the sky settled over them trees.
It left this wire in my head that customized me.
The wire in my head, it advised me.
Better living through bio-circuits.
Yeah, okay.
Hey!
The wire in my head found me new friends.
Bring it up!
We meet at the airport where the old freeway ends.
And we lay down our lives for the cowardly sin.
Ooh!
I got a wire in my head and so do my friends.
The wire, a big, big opportunity.
Ooh!
The wire, benefits me financially.
The wire in my head gives me good deals.
I drive a real solid car and I eat fancy meals.
And you can bet I kill any bastard who squeals.
I got a wire in my head and I like how it feels.
I got a wire for your head and I'm solid for the breeze.
Better living through surgery.
I got a wire in my head.
Ooh!
Oh!
Well friends, we're gonna try to put somebody on here.
That was buck-naked all by himself.
Praise money and Bob.
That was Buck in San Francisco, and now we should be on the phones.
Can you hear me, dear listener?
No.
No?
Can you hear me?
Where did that poor dear listener go?
Hello?
Hello, dear listener.
Which one is it?
Would that be number three up there?
He's off.
I'm sorry.
The poltergeist.
That's what it is.
Oh, please, Reverend Mathers, leave us alone.
Yes, friends, it's a dead DJ that haunts the phone lines here.
Well, there's only one explanation.
You didn't call 823-8801 with your pledge,
and that's why we have these terrible...
Hello?
Well, it looks like we may be getting that caller in any second now.
Hello, dear friend?
Nay?
Hello?
Yes.
I already pledged.
Well, then you may speak.
Praise Bob. Praise Bob.
Do you have any further testimony?
Any other testimonials for that great man, Bob?
Not tonight.
But I do appreciate the Hour of Slack.
I think it's just wonderful.
It makes the week go by so fast.
That's time control, sister.
And you know what can make the week go by even faster?
If you pull that watch off and smash it to pieces.
Oh, I'll try that next time.
Next week.
Well, you ought to come to one of our revivals next time we have one.
And we'll do that for you live.
We'll do that for you live on stage.
It's a beautiful experience.
One of the most beautiful rituals we have in our church.
When will that be?
I don't know.
Actually, I don't know.
We don't have one.
You see, they're sort of like floating crap games.
And it's very...
Are you a member of the church?
I'm afraid I haven't ever officially become a member.
Well, see, how can you expect to get the secret mailings and the decoder pin?
See, we give the messages out.
Uh...
And code every week on the show here.
But if you don't have the decoder pin...
Let me give you that precious box number, sister.
Where you can write for information on this.
Okay.
And this is as important as pledging to Kanoan.
That's Bob at...
No, not as important.
Almost as important.
Well, actually, it's thousands of times more earth-shatteringly important.
But we don't expect everyone to believe that.
Bob is at Box 140306, dear friend.
He's actually at that box?
Bob is inside that tiny P.O. box, and he's waiting.
It's the one with the little bit of smoke coming out from the edges of it as he puffeth on his mighty pipe.
What is in that pipe, by the way?
Uh, the sacred Tibetan herb, habafrop zipulops.
And I bet you thought it was tobacco or marijuana, didn't ya?
Oh, no. No, no.
I just couldn't pronounce that word.
Yeah, fromp, for short.
That's what Bob smokes in his pipe.
And people find that so hard to believe.
Uh, but, uh, in the meantime...
Well, thank you for your beautiful, lovely, testimonial, uh, sister.
You're welcome, Reverend, thanks.
And we'll, uh, slowly pop out of this phone call.
Thank you.
Bye.
Hello, Line 1.
Yes?
Ah, so we do have Line 1 here.
Yeah.
Yeah, okay, finally.
Well, what, what was the, uh, message?
Okay, the message is, is we have, we have a warning that should go out to all the viewers of Dr. Gene Scott.
Uh-huh.
Late nights on Channel 27.
Yeah.
Now, you see, I used to be a devout Dr. Scott addict.
Uh-huh.
I was Dr. Scott eight hours a night.
I mean, I, I, I sat up, my, my, my work went to the pit, I got divorced from my wife, and my, my life was going to the dogs.
I still, I still do that.
Uh-huh.
Now, here I am, I'm sitting here late one night, and all, all of a sudden, I begin to hear these voices.
And these voices are telling me not to listen to Dr. Scott.
They're telling me specifically, turn off Dr. Scott.
But I was so addicted.
I was so wrapped up in Dr. Scott.
That I just refused to heed these warnings.
Uh-huh.
I continued to listen to Dr. Scott.
Bob told, Bob told you to quit listening to him?
I'm surprised.
This is Bob speaking to me.
We're talking Bob in the flesh.
So, Bob and Dr. Gene, Dr. Scott have always been friends.
Uh-huh.
He's telling, he, he was telling me not to listen.
Well, but what about the rumors of Bob's death?
How could Bob be communicating with us on this plane and burning you and putting you in the hospital?
Uh-huh.
Well, you see, he was, I, I personally think that it was a communistic plot by Dr. Scott.
Well.
And I think, I think Bob was attempting to warn me.
I have an emergency 681-9738 from Amy in Tennessee, really.
Yes.
What was that?
I don't know.
Did, was that a conspiracy?
I think it was.
Well, listen, I, God, well, uh, have you ever sent your $20 to the Church of the Subgenius?
I pledged $50 earlier tonight.
Oh, tonight?
Yeah.
Well, how, how about for the church itself?
Was it for the church itself?
No, that's for KNON.
Oh.
How, how do I make a pledge for the church?
Oh, see, now, see, that's why you've been having these fearsome third-degree burns all over your body, friend.
Yeah.
We need to write to Bob at Box 140.
Well, let me get a piece of paper.
Let me get a piece of paper.
Yeah, get that piece of paper as we listen to the beautiful, uh, swinging love corpses.
Fantastic.
All right, what is it?
Oh, you ready?
Yeah.
Okay, it's, uh, Bob's death.
I'm gonna go to the PO Box 140306.
140306, Dallas, Texas, 75214, and you'll get that great package of information that tells
you how to get even more, but we can't tell you all about that right now.
And what's the zip code?
Uh, 75214.
75214?
That's right.
Now I'm gonna have to get off of these lines, because something weird is going on.
Oh, okay.
Huh.
Oh, my God.
We measure things by what we are.
To the maggots in the cheese, the cheese is the universe.
To the worms in the cooperation, theotto-personae are world.
The corpse is the cosmos.
Bob is the cosmos.
How then can we be so cocksure about our world?
Just because of our telescopes and microscopes and the splitting of the atom?
No. Science is but an organized system of ignorance.
There are more things in heaven and on earth than I dreamt of in your philosophy.
What do we know about the beyond?
Do we know what's behind the beyond?
I'm afraid some of us hardly know what's beyond the behind.
Blast 1. Your sensory and motility circuits are about to end.
Blast 2. Your sensory and motility circuits are about to end.
Stand by for initial processing shot to aid viral launchings.
Good morning, Laz.
Hello.
Doc, here we go.
I'm removing the protective central membrane from your preneal unit.
There.
Now, for just a few adjustments.
And...
Now you're ready.
Ready.
Yes, Laz. Now that you're fully activated and operational, you'll be leaving the factory for the first time.
You're unique, Laz.
You're the first robot programmed with the capacity for free will and emotion.
However, in order for you to feel, you'll need more than just knowledge.
We're going to add real experiences to your database.
Experience.
That's right, Laz. Human experience.
Choose the ones you'd like to have.
Search your database.
This is the fastest out there right now.
Fast and easy.
Friend, have you ever heard the expression, there's no slack in this world?
No.
A lot of people have to ask me what slack is.
And that's sad mystery.
They were born with slack.
Oh, yeah, you were born with slack.
But the conspiracy took it away.
The conspiracy made you want to be normal.
That's what the conspiracy is all about.
And conspiracy is a patchwork of different things.
Some are nations.
Some are products.
Some are hypnotic television shows.
Some are...
bad pills.
You'll find unless you find Bob!
And you better find Bob right now!
And no one has ever met Bob.
The leader of our church, no one has ever met.
Because as you know, all cults, their leaders are usually pretty hard to find.
And Bob is no exception.
Bob will help you.
Dig your own weirdness.
I was getting messages in the back of my brain.
And I just kept hearing the word, Bob.
Bob.
Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob.
They said you're my-
Hello darling.
Hello Darling.
Le Msimo Willy.
Hello darling.
Hello darling, let me kill your witty
Well I'm Reverend Cleve, the bassist on a blow fly
Dr. Rudy Ray Moore and my name's Steve Dolomite
I ain't the next, I know what's what
Babe, I like the shape and size and contour of your butt
So come on over here and give up the cash
Whip some scum on me, bitch, or give me all your cash
Return your honor to worry about your soul
Cause when the exits come, you'll be right on my pole
To dobson Malaysia we will go
When you drink the cool letter go ho ho ho
You'll be filled with enough pride to blow your time
You just wanna keep fucking and never stop
Now I might be lying there with a ice pack on my nuts
Or maybe I'll chase some other fine fucks
But at least you won't have to wear machinery
And you'll be free from the conspiracy
You can watch them fry up in your face
While we make our way to outer space
And while you're wishing upon a star
You'll probably lose me and some interstellar bomb
Ho ho ho ho
Come on Cleve, that's your 17th bottle of night chain tonight
Let's go home now before you pass out right here on the street
Woman, I can drink for you
And I can go wine and stay sober
And then all the heathens, Hindus in Asia
Yeah, I heard that before
Get your popsicle sticks and let's get your damn dead dick home
Damn, hope there's something good on TV
For whatever intimidation and injustice lie with decency and honor
Let the doctors arise
And arise they must
For within every one of us there is a doctor
A dormant doctor, a supreme arbitrator
Who can be summoned to intervene when crises threaten
The stabilities and well-beings of our hearts
And the lives of our loved ones
Yeah
Now let's party
Seeing someone sleeve job a 14 and a half inch John Holmes Wangdinger specials offensive
If nobody's sleeving yours or you're not sleeving anybody's
You know, that's the whole problem
When you give something up
You expect everybody else to give it up too
And I think that's worse than if you take something up new
You should expect everybody else to
Because obviously a lot of other people are already doing something
Because they want to or think they want to
Or they like to
Or they like to think they want to
Or they want to think they like to
Just because they want to swear and smoke and drink
And in your opinion go to hell
That's their business
Not yours
The only business that's yours is yours
And if it's yours and it offends you
You better pull it out and look at it closely
And find out why it offends you
Because I tell you
It offends you mostly because
It reminds you that you're missing out on something
And that's why sometimes
When we say things in the church of the subgenius
We offend people because
Because it reminds them that they're in the grip of the conspiracy
Because it reminds them they lead dreary, empty, stilted
Hungry lives of desperation and quietness
They don't like the way we talk
Because it reminds them that they've got sexual organs
And if they, if they would just make an effort they could use them
They don't like the way we talk because we remind them that we're all animals
And daily must fulfill our biological functions
And as they are something of which God almighty or whoever
Brought us here, gave us, we have no control over them
Therefore, they've been told, oh that's nasty
Put it in that little clean white bowl
That symbol of purity
Why do you have to flush away
Pure water
With nothing but biological salts dissolved in it
With five and a half gallons of fresh water
That somebody could be cooking dinner and drinking
Our friends
It's because
Some people don't like to be reminded
They pretend
That if they don't talk about it
And don't think about it
Then they can forget about it
And if they're not reminded that they have to squat down and
Like every other monkey on this planet every day
If things are working right
Then maybe they think they aren't one of them monkeys that's on this planet
But the big smart dumb monkeys with too much shit and not enough time
Yeah, talking about you
And all you other signifying monkeys
That's why people get offended
That's why they don't like to hear us talk about prairie squid
Oh God, how disgusting
To use an aphorism of that disgusting nature
But what they're missing is the point that we're saying is that
A prairie squid is just like any other wild animal
It's a natural thing
You can't cover up a prairie squid
Because it'll come creeping out some
And you stamp out the prairie squid
And you stamp out life itself
That's what we're saying
We're saying that our biology is what we are
And there's nothing we can do about it but enjoy it
That's why sometimes we offend people
That's why the church will never be
Something you'll see in prime time television
Because they don't want you to be reminded of what you really are
Because then you take a good look at yourself and realize
Then hell, what am I doing all this shit, them, for?
That's why they don't like for us to say these things
That's why prairie squid is a thing
Poo dog, poo dog
All those strange, strange cult references
They're all symbols as old as mankind himself
Just like Bob is a symbol of what is as old as mankind or older
If you believe everything a subgenius tells you
Or writes down for you
Hell, put it down in a book, I'll worship it
Hell, sit up here on the table at dinner time
I'll worship it
Hell, put it on sale, I'll worship it
Yeah, everybody's looking for bargain basement salvation
Uh-huh, well, Dobbs will be the first to tell you
You'd pay to know what you really think
As long as you believe
So here's what I want to tell you
Like this, when an old man tells you
Yeah, I mean do it
depende
What I want, I want you to know
the small dobstown in South America.
Yes, it used to be in Bolivia.
Now it's outside of Rio
where you can get to a Xerox machine easier.
And you think I'm pulling your leg, don't you?
You don't really believe there's a South American
emissionary outpost for the church, do you?
I'll be there and you won't.
Friends, let's get one last pledge in here, okay?
Just pledge that last five bucks you got in your pockets.
Why not?
It'll earn your way into subgenius hell.
And friends, when you compare that one
to some of the other heavens that people describe to you,
I think you'd rather be in that poor subgenius hell.
It's fun.
That's 823-8801 for subgenius hell
or 823-8883.
Friends, we have actually achieved our goal.
Praise Bob.
There is slack.
Oh, what other little pieces did I have in here?
We heard Pete Scott doing that wonderful song,
Let Me Feel Your Willie.
I don't know what that's about.
And friends, once again,
we're going to give you that sacred box number.
That's Bob, friends, at P.O. Box 148.
40306, Dallas, Texas 75214.
Order now.
Not available in any stores.
And your eternal salvation, friends,
or triple your money back, guaranteed.
You can't beat that kind of deal.
And you know, friends, where other religions
may offer you eternal salvation
from all your worldly goods,
why, for three bucks from us,
you can get that from the subgenius church.
Get yourself an excuse.
I can't tell you about that stuff.
You can get that if you keep listening to this show
and keep pledging, friends.
The excuse for everything.
That's right.
The excuse for every sin against God, man, nature,
woman, or child, or beast that you've ever done.
You can get that excuse from us.
Yes, friends, and send that money
and hang in there for norms.
The amazing...
Yeah, what...
That's right.
Okay, it's a two-headed show, friends.
Hang on for Monday Morning with...
What's his name?
Him, too.
All right.
That's it, friends.
And their guests, Lee Trench and...
Kathy Blalock.
That's right.
Kathy and Lee.
Praise Kathy.
From the...
From the Motor Video.
From Music, Dallas Music Video Show
on the Public Access Channel.
That's right.
The DMV...
The DMV Show.
On who...
On whose show?
Why, I've been a guest.
Norm's been a guest.
Hang in there for Monday Morning, folks.
We've still got two minutes to play the subgenius credits.
And for you to mail in that pledge.
That's right.
If you can put that...
That stamp on that envelope before this song ends
and get it down to your mailbox
before the next song ends,
then Norm will be on.
So you better do that quick.
Otherwise...
There's...
The end.
The day my coon dog died
Reading the pamphlet
Over and over again
I was drinking Budweiser
And Bob was on TV
The day that Uncle
Good kick
By Bob was on TV
I was with Cousin Junior
The DNA backfired
I was drunk
I was lonely
I was plastered
I was drinking Budweiser
And Bob was on TV
Drinking Budweiser
Watching Bob on TV
Swallowing Redman
The day my coon dog died
Reading the pamphlet
Over and over again
I was drinking Budweiser
Ped loyalty
Reading the pamphlet
Over and over again
BF-WATCH TV 2021