And good evening. You are tuned to Synesthesia on WCSB Cleveland at 9.3 FM.
And many views or opinions expressed on this program will not necessarily be those of WCSB or Cleveland State University.
And this is another special episode here where we have special guests here once again.
Reverend Stang and Princess Wee and Reverend Baby Bear have joined us.
Oh, we can't get home.
Oh, no.
Yeah, that's the only reason we're here.
We're trapped.
Why do I have to say all the funniest things when the microphones aren't on?
I know I can't prove that to you guys, but just believe me.
What I was saying is hilarious.
Everyone in here was just rolling on the ground.
I'm still catching my breath.
And as soon as the microphone comes on, it's like, oh, no, it's all gone.
Well, you know, what we were talking about is this whole daylight savings time thing.
And, you know, there's an old subgenius tradition.
Of?
Time control.
But daylight savings time is similar to false slack.
It is false time control.
Time control going out of control.
It is conspiracy time control.
It's the conspiracy trying to sell us time control after they've taken it from us.
It's exactly like false slack that way.
Taint fair.
Yeah.
Taint fair, they should be in charge of it.
Well, there's some places that reject it.
They don't do it.
Taint fair at all.
Taint fair.
Well, you know, the only states that reject it out of hand are.
Taint fair has been nearly as.
Has tainted in the last few years.
I used to love going to tank fair.
The display booths were disgusting, but still, it was interesting character.
You know, you shouldn't taint me talking about that on the air.
We were trying to have a high minded discussion.
Couldn't taint.
You had to drag it down.
Yeah, that's my job.
Praise Bob.
So to speak, high minded.
But you know what?
The upside, apparently, you know, when this this whole false time control conspiracy time control.
They're thinking, though, that it might be useful to combat global warming since the sun's going down an hour earlier now.
Yeah, right.
Yeah.
Also, if you want to combat global warming, everyone should just turn their air conditioners on full blast and open their windows so you can cool the outside.
Wow.
That's brilliant.
Yeah.
So these are some helpful life.
Pro tips.
Making.
You know, you're going to be a terrible face.
This is a public service.
We're doing this to help people.
That's right.
And the hippie campgrounds.
They get mad if you sit in your car running the air conditioning in order to cool down because it heats up people outside of the cars even more.
So why don't all the hippies just get in their cars and turn on the air conditioner?
I didn't get it.
Why don't you just move to a cooler climate?
Cooler than northern Ohio.
This is the coolest place ever, man.
Most of the hippies I know don't have a car.
They're not real hippies if they have a car, really.
But you know what I'm talking about.
I know.
Maybe like a VW.
But our customers, that's what we're talking about.
They don't actually most of them don't have cars either.
Oh, well, forget it.
You know who else I don't think has a car?
We are getting a caller here.
You're on the air.
No, no.
Don't.
Are you?
You're on the air.
Hello, everyone.
Hello, No Money Mark.
Welcome to the program.
Do you have a car?
What is the make and model of your car?
What color is it?
Whatever a make and model RTA has for their buses.
Okay.
That is a satisfactory answer.
You may speak on the program now.
We saw No Money Mark at the big party last night.
Yeah.
The WCSB Halloween.
He was hard to miss because it was he was in some sort of an intense orange outfit.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
See, the thing is, yeah, my brother found me this, I guess, orange hunting jacket at
a secondhand store and I'm using it as my winter coat now.
And everybody I meet seems to like it if they say anything about it at all.
And it is actually a good thing to have if you're walking or biking at night, which I
do sometimes.
I missed it.
I don't remember seeing it.
Well, you I can see how it would be useful in hunting and that you would not look like
a deer to the other hunters, no matter how drunk they were, even if it was Dick Cheney.
By the same token, it seems like it wouldn't be very good camouflage because that thing
really it was almost day glow.
We were up in the balcony with the projectors and I think it was it was blinding even from
up there.
How do I not remember this?
Also, who knew?
I don't know what what you don't know what no money mark looks like.
Well, no, that's true.
But I don't remember seeing the bright orange thing that you're describing.
But I was going to say, I don't know what spectrum the deers deer can see in.
Not deers.
I'm educated.
I know these things.
So how do you guys get to go up in the in the projection booth?
Because we're the projectionists.
Yeah, you have to have your union card for that.
Did you see me leering down?
On the crowd in my pig mask?
Well, I mean, I was mostly paying attention to the band on stage.
Okay, fine.
If you looked up the ceiling, there were these there were these projections.
I don't care of underwater movies befitting the underwater theme of the prom.
The high school.
I did see those.
Yeah, that that sort of Pink Floyd type stuff.
Yeah.
Well, that's my job.
I put together a collage of underwater stuff.
Usually done by me, by somebody else already on YouTube.
And I said I was going to help him.
But instead, I just stood up there and leered at people in a pig mask.
And he brings the projectors and he sets them up and he takes them back.
But anyway, so it was great seeing the two of you there.
Dr. Sinister, it was not so great not seeing you there.
What are you talking about?
I saw you.
Well, okay.
So what outfit were you wearing?
Come on, Mark.
I'm really starting to get sick of this game that you keep playing with me.
You seem to be such a big fan, but you never recognize me anymore when we meet.
I'm starting to wonder if your face blindness has come back.
It never went away.
I mean, I actually went up to a guy who was wearing a trench coat like you did one year
because I thought maybe he was you and he looked a little like you.
But I was like, I'm not sure.
I mean, so, well, if you were there, why didn't you say hi to me?
I did, Mark.
You must have too many of those Schwarz beers.
Those were good.
They were strong.
There were actually a couple people in trench coats.
There were two double team costumes.
One was Scully and Mulder, which was great.
And the other one was Agent Dale Cooper and a Laura Palmer wrapped up in plastic wrap.
Oh, yeah.
I missed those.
You guys didn't see that?
Oh, it was good.
We're getting some more callers here.
You're on the air.
Hey, guys.
How are you doing?
Good, Buddha.
Okay.
I got three of the best costumes that I saw there.
I got to mention them.
One was the tree.
Exactly.
Oh, yeah.
That tree was really good.
That was awesome.
I mean, you couldn't drink any beer because you didn't have any alcohol.
I was in my arms.
I felt bad for him.
It was like a walking tree.
She had a great knothole.
He didn't drink beer.
She couldn't tell if it was being used either.
Another one was inside it dressed as a barn owl or something.
Yeah.
It looked like an owl.
I never really quite got to see it.
It was hard to make out on that.
There was a real good odorous saliva.
It would be hard to make out when you're in that costume.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah, that would be.
He was dressed as one of the Drugs from Clockwork Orange.
One of the Drugs.
The ghost of Odorous Urungus of Gwar was there.
Right.
Of course, it might not have been Dave Brockie because anybody can wear the suit.
I mean, for the last three years of Gwar's tours, that wasn't really Dave Brockie singing
it.
Yeah, that was a nice one, too.
He retired.
He just paid some guy to go out and sing those Gwar songs.
Sick of you.
I was going to say sick of Gwar.
I'm so sick of you.
Oh, oh.
He was so sick, so sick of Gwar.
Well, the subgenius of that band got sick of it.
He got sick of taking pratfalls and getting injured.
The subsecutioner was a dues-paying subgenius.
He was the founder of the band, actually.
Really?
But he was the first one to retire because he was the Curly.
And it hurt.
Oh, God.
It got hurt a lot.
He almost drowned on fake blood.
Yeah.
He was in the blood.
A couple of times.
More than once.
Yeah, when he was in the O.J.
Simpson suit and they cut his face off, the blood hose was turned around the wrong way
and he was almost drowned.
Oh, God.
I got to work with that band for five days before we were fired.
Wait, blood hose?
It wasn't real?
They don't really do that stuff?
Baby Bear, some things that you see in rock and roll shows are fake and some are real.
The ones you see at the subgenius shows are real.
They really are sewing their lips shut and cutting their eyeballs out.
The GWAR was more like the Three Stooges in stinky, real stinky costumes.
Can I ask why you were fired?
Actually, we both were fired and quit at the same time.
It just wasn't working out.
This executioner thought he wanted to bring some highfalutin spoken word to the GWAR audience
in the form of Church of the Subgenius, which was a noble thought.
But basically, heavy metal fans aren't going to sit still for a preacher, no matter how
good the videos are or how much cussing the preacher does.
They're expecting GWAR to come out and cut his face off.
So I very quickly had to shift gears.
In fact, the first show we did at Cleveland, people threw stuff at me.
I'll tell you, 50-cent pieces hurt when they hit you smack in the forehead.
I got off stage and this guy goes, I hit you right in the forehead.
That was cool.
So after that, I realized, okay, I need to just keep it to 10 minutes and keep them thinking
that I'm about to leave.
The whole time?
Right, the whole 10 minutes.
Every minute of the 10 minutes.
And kind of do this stupid jock drive time DJ that comes out and goes, I was backstage
with Ben.
Are you ready to rock?
All that kind of thing.
I had to kind of do that.
Eventually, after five nights, first off, me and my partner, Jesus, went to the gym.
We're literally physically sick.
I don't know how you rock stars can tour like that, baby.
Oh, it's hard.
It's hard work.
And it obviously just wasn't working out.
And Odorous, meanwhile, had realized that I was getting paid more for 10 minutes of
baloney than he was for an hour and a half in that sweaty suit.
So he came lurching up to us and goes, we got to have a talk.
And Jesus and I said, yeah, we're going to get off this tour.
It's just not working out.
And he goes, what?
I was going to fire you.
You're not going to sue us?
No, no, no.
It's just, you know, duh.
It just didn't work.
You should have just come out with the bloodhose.
Sexy was crazy.
And he went, wow, you guys are cool.
You're not going to sue us.
You're the first ones that haven't sued us.
So, you know, we parted on very good terms.
And I shot all of their shows from, I had nice balcony places I could get to because
I was part of the show, sort of.
And I shot a bunch of those.
And I've seen them as bootlegs.
I've seen them as bootlegs.
I've seen them on YouTube with no credit to me.
Thank goodness.
So, yeah, some of the GWAR videos from the 90s, from the year of 1995, I think it was.
The Chicago one on YouTube was shot by me up in the balcony.
Oh, yeah.
One of the things that...
You guys, if you guys don't...
Go ahead.
One of the things I used to see people do, you know, the local country station is WGAR
and people would cut and paste the letters to turn it into a GWAR sticker.
GWAR.
Caddy. I did that on my Caddy.
I used to turn
Sound Warehouse bumper stickers
into Sound Whorehouse.
That was real easy to do.
And I can't even say, not even
after hours can I say what I used to do
to rock the vote
stickers. That was real easy
to change with some white out
and a black marker.
Rock can be
turned into another four-letter word really
easily.
Now remember, kids,
let's rock the vote.
Whatever that means.
Oh, by the way,
shake the ballot box
really hard.
By the way, one other thing.
Since reverse psychology
works on subgeni,
I would like to mention
that they should also not
donate to Radio Sound this month.
Oh, yeah, no kidding. Don't ever
donate, especially not to Hour
of Slack.
Or Synesthesia. Actually, we probably
don't, no matter what we say, they won't.
Last year was
atrocious for us.
The station as a whole did fine.
But our two shows, which
this is not traditional,
did punk.
So, I mean,
I don't know what's wrong with you people.
You listeners must not think we're
funny enough or
smart enough or
clearly enough or something.
Hey, if I'm not alienating
listeners, if I'm not alienating
listeners,
I'm not doing my job.
Kill the audience.
Sorry, guys.
It was funny.
To be my last show, I did pretty well.
And if I might do some
shameless self-promotion,
I will be back
doing my old slot
for Radio Sound.
Oh, you are?
Oh, good. You want to do my
slot, too? You'll probably raise
more money than we can.
We've already started
doing it now.
I just,
I just have to say that, to be honest,
Dr. Dark was not in town last year.
He gets the ball rolling.
It's like the magic thing.
When he makes his donation, then you just get,
they just start rolling in.
But because he was out of town...
Maybe we need to make up some
fictitious donors.
Maybe.
And start saying, okay, we got Joe from
Beachwood who donated.
I do that every year, too.
$200. Thanks, Joe.
And here's
Esmeralda from...
Maria. Thanks so much, Esmeralda.
But then people might think that you're doing really well
and be like, ah, see, they don't need it. They're doing fine.
But don't you want to be in on this?
Don't you want to be in on
what all the cool people are doing? And furthermore,
earlier in the week you donate. This is the selling point
I always make. Because there are some
gifts that we have available
for our donors that are only available
in limited quantities. So if you wait
all week to make your donation,
you might miss your chance to get those things. So that's
why you should donate during this program
or the Hour of Slack.
There's always some really good, bad films
in VHS and now, I guess,
in DVD form.
And there's only one of each
of those. I always read off all the titles
of them, and occasionally it prompts
a sale if the movie is bad
and sleazy.
By the way, I just read an article about how VHS
is coming back, at least
for all these low-budget
horror movies.
Right, yeah. Well, and it's like...
It would cost more to distribute something on VHS,
than by any other format that's been
in use in the last 20 years.
I have a VHS player because
it's really easy to find all of the
Disney movies for like 50 cents
at thrift stores, and there's no way I'm gonna
pay like $25 a disc
and have to wait until they come out
of the vault or whatever
stupid thing that they do.
I want Disney now.
I have to look at my VHS
because, you know, it's...
I got all these bondage flicks I still have to watch.
You know, so...
You have to.
That's right.
I want to.
There we go. Now we're getting
somewhere now.
The funny ones
are the 80s, where the girls
are supposed to be
making all this money and all that,
but their hair is two-toned
because they can't afford the hair dye.
Yeah, this subject is probably
a little out of my...
Sticks and stones may break my bones,
but whips and chains excite me.
I watched porn in the 80s.
Princess, you're kind of an 80s lady.
Kind of.
You must know something about that hairstyle.
You still have it.
Yes.
Old-fashioned.
Actually,
I just...
I actually gave it to a friend of mine,
a professional submissive.
On our Slack,
he did a song that was like that.
It was...
It was under...
These are my favorites.
These are my favorite things.
Ball gags and...
Dog eggs?
No, that might have been a...
Ball gags.
Yeah, that might have been...
That sounds like it might have been
a Phineas Narco.
Man, this reminds me of one of our radio buddies.
That does sound like Phineas.
Actually, I'll come back to that in the second hour.
The thing I was going to say.
By the way,
Reverend and Princess,
there's something I brought up on the show last week.
I'd like to get your reaction to it.
Flyer, I saw at a rapid station.
The one side says,
smile, God loves you.
And on the other side says,
but if you reject his love,
given a great sacrifice at Calvary,
it would be better for you not to have been born.
And then there's a bunch of Bible quotes.
Oh, that's too deep.
Well, I think that people should pick up on that.
So wait, is that...
Jesus died for your sins.
Is that advocating abortion?
Jesus died.
Jesus died on the cross
because he had a bit of a God complex
and he was just too proud to say the safe word.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
So if you're going to...
And it's okay to laugh at that joke
because if you know what a safe word is,
you're probably going to hell anyway.
So if you waste the sacrifice,
you shouldn't have been born.
That was what the gist was, right?
No, it says,
if you reject his love,
it will be better for you not to have been born.
Right, because you're going to live forever
in eternal damnation,
which apparently hurts.
So then, abortion?
Is abortion okay?
If the baby's going to reject Jesus' love?
Now, if...
And this is the thing I don't get on.
I did it.
I went there.
I'm already there.
They will say,
free will, free will.
And like, okay,
but does that mean that you can surprise God
with the choices that you make?
God needs a lot of help.
He is pathetically weak
and he needs the help of the little old redneck ladies
to pick on the people that are being mean to God.
Like me.
You know, God needs people to help him
in his battle against evil
because he really can't do much of anything
for himself, evidently.
And that's why he needs all those busybodies.
That's kind of like what the Pope was saying
earlier this week.
You know, we don't want to paint him as a wizard
with a magic wand who can do anything.
I thought they did.
I thought that was the whole idea.
What's been happening?
You know, irony died a long time ago.
Well, yeah, I heard that the Pope came out
and basically said,
hey, you know, you creationists are nuts.
Come on.
That's old church doctrine, actually,
which is one of the great ironies
of the history of Western civilization
that suddenly the Catholics seem to be more reasonable
on a lot of issues than the Protestants.
What, what?
Who'd have thunk it?
Hello, you're on the air.
Hey, how you doing?
Good, how are you?
I'm doing just fine.
I was just calling in.
I thought that was Thayton for a second.
So did I.
But there's no lisp, so it can't be Thayton.
You know, you're not,
this fake voice you're doing is not funny.
Sounds like Emo Phillips.
I can't.
Actually, you sound like an idiot.
That was, that's like,
that was a really pathetic,
yeah, really pathetic excuse for a prank call.
Yeah.
Bring back Thayton.
We demand Thayton.
I read this,
it's one article,
and it was talking about,
you know,
the birth of the nativity,
and, you know,
Jesus was visited by three wise men.
None of them were Jewish.
And so the one guy brought up,
so he was visited by three Alistair Crowleys then.
Because, you know,
back then wise men were,
you know,
basically, you know,
you're magicians and wizards.
Well, but Alistair Crowley was just a big mouth.
He wasn't a magician.
He wasn't a horror wizard.
He was just a con man.
I should know.
He knew how to kill people.
And on top of it,
one of them was a Zoroastrian,
I think, right?
The guys that worship Zoro and write Gs everywhere.
Now, you could argue that they were the first Christians
because they recognized the Christ.
Right.
Yeah.
And they brought him Frankenstein and Myrrh.
Gold, Frankenstein and Myrrh.
I actually,
I also like the Rosicrucians,
the guys who worship roses.
Well, the Rosicrucians,
no, actually, the Rosicrucian thing,
not that you could get a modern Rosicrucian to admit this,
but it was based on some satirical pamphlets made by a couple of wise guys
back in the 1700s.
I thought it was founded by Rosencrantz.
Yeah, he was a made up character.
He was a piece of clip art.
That was the amazing thing.
The thing was, the guys,
towards as they got older,
the two, the guys,
I can't remember their names.
That had penned this sarcastic pamphlet about,
it was basically about the new agers of their time and the mystics.
It was making fun of them,
but it had,
it was done with a straight face.
Sound familiar?
Well, people,
all these other smart asses of the period started going,
well, you know,
I know this is supposed to be a joke,
but this stuff is,
this is for real.
I can just tell it rings true.
And, and the guys who wrote it finally started going,
no, no way.
They,
we did that a long time ago.
It was just a joke.
You're crazy if you believe this stuff.
And yet now the Rosicrucian is,
is a recognized minor fringe religion,
but it's been around for a long time and they take themselves real seriously.
There's many books done written by,
let's call it trance writing.
I know how that's done.
They read,
this all sounds,
it's like golden plates out of the hat,
right?
Well,
that was my uncle.
That was my uncle,
my great uncle,
Joseph Smith that did the golden plates routine.
There are,
it is sickening how many existing religions were started as a joke.
Hint,
hint,
hint.
And it's horrifying to me.
You got them all riled up.
Can you,
can you blame me for occasionally like I did at the witches ball,
just popping the giant balloon grossly.
I have my fingers crossed behind my back,
you know,
but I,
there's just people who need to be deprogrammed from the sub genius cult.
Now that's a sick and sorry situation.
Oh God.
Someone get the jam,
get the jam for his nose.
By the way,
Reverend staying a trance writing.
Does that have anything to do with,
um,
uh,
ingesting copious quantities of alcohol beforehand?
That has never really seemed effective.
I mean,
I'm not saying that it's not effective to me for that purpose,
but you know,
I asked Condor S Thompson that question.
It worked for him,
I guess.
Well,
well,
but he wouldn't recognize it.
Wouldn't recommend it to anyone.
I want to say that it worked for him.
Oh,
I'm a coffee man.
My son's,
uh,
one more person has been calling in here.
I'm the froppet,
the coffee froppet.
I'm the profit.
Hello.
You're on the air.
People.
Yeah.
Sure.
Hello.
You are on the air.
Speak right up there.
Hello.
What's up,
everybody?
That's a full house,
right?
I'm doing pretty well.
I missed the gathering last night.
Yeah.
We missed you.
I know.
I didn't know what I was going to wear,
and I would have had to have hitched a ride.
You couldn't drive there yourself,
huh?
Well,
they asked to get one of those Google cars,
man.
You can get one of those Google self-driving cars pretty soon.
I didn't dress up because I was going to just wear nothing but inline pants.
I didn't dress up because I was going to just wear anything but inline skates and go as
a pool toy.
Or maybe, Bear, just so you know, our caller Keith is blind.
Can't you use a GPS, though?
Ours tells us to turn left, turn right.
It's never on.
It's always a little light, though.
It's always just a little off.
It's like we were talking about that.
If you were a blind person and you were following the directions of the GPS voice, we'd all
all be dead.
Because it tells you to turn when you're sitting at a light.
So, I mean, it doesn't know that you're
at a light.
It's only a robot.
It's just a little robot.
Actually, then I probably
get around better than
without a GPS.
Could be. Just randomly.
But no, I missed going last
night. Even though I had no idea what I was going
to wear, I was probably just maybe going to come and
drag.
Now that would have been interesting.
You would have been among...
Because on sale
a couple weeks ago, they had a special costume
by a certain
star
of a movie, which of course is my
favorite movie of all time.
The Wicked Wizard of Oz.
And I would have loved
to have worn that.
The Wicked Wizard?
No, the witch. The witch, of course.
Of The Wizard of Oz.
There were quite...
Quite a few characters from The Wizard of Oz.
Really? Oh, I would fit in.
Oh, yeah, there was a scarecrow and a derby.
And a scarecrow, yes.
I did not see a cowardly lion there.
I did not see a cowardly lion either.
Uh-oh. Oh, boy! And I have a fur coat!
There were a lot of...
I have to admit, there were a lot of people dressed
vaguely like Clark Kent.
Oh!
With glasses. Yes.
Kind of nerdy look. You know, they were...
What? Superhero? Me? No, no.
Thanks. I just figured out one.
That I kept seeing last night. I was trying to figure out
who it was. It was a Ned Flanders.
Yeah, there was a Ned Flanders there.
Yeah, there was the green sweater
and the purple shirt, and I was trying to figure it out.
And he had a mustache, and I was trying to figure... He had the glasses.
And I kept looking at it, and I was like, I know what that is.
I know what that is, and someday it's gonna come to me.
He actually had a sign on his... Yes!
For Shane Flanders.
Aw.
I did it. I figured it out. I won. What do I win?
He knows. I would have had to ask
everybody what they were wearing.
And then they would have
lied to you. Oh, I'm not wearing anything.
And then I would have to say, okay, well, let me fill you up
then.
Oh, geez.
Oh.
Well, that's amazing.
It's my...
Robot voice.
We are experiencing technical
difficulties.
Well, one thing
hasn't changed.
What happened?
That was a cool effect.
It was. Yeah, you know, you have to pay
extra for the plug-in
that does that on your audio program.
Absolutely. So who...
What costume won last night?
I blinked and
missed the costume contest.
Yeah, me too.
I don't remember the costume. I know they got up on stage
for a second, and they were talking about it,
and I just... I can't even
remember who the three finalists
were. I just don't remember.
The three didn't get on stage.
Aw.
It was a guy in some kind of inflatable suit
that I noticed finally deflated
towards the end of the evening.
I'm guessing that he had some kind of
a battery-operated pump that was
keeping that thing blown up.
Unless someone was blowing them off.
Depending on where he was wearing the pump
strapped onto him.
By the way, Keith, did you listen to the show over the radio?
Actually, yes,
I did.
And there was a lot of good
music.
What are we even doing here?
Yeah, I would like to do my impression
of X-Blank X.
There was quite a bit
of buzzing, wasn't there?
It's funny.
At first,
there was,
and I know several people, including
myself, started calling in,
and then it stopped.
And then they said, oh, oh,
okay, thank you. Must be interference.
Okay, we'll fix it.
The third band had a lot
of technical troubles. I was wondering
what they were doing at the station during all those
long...
I felt sorry for the band and
myself because it was a punk
band and their songs were only a minute and a half long,
but it took them two and a half to three minutes
between songs to solve
their issues.
At one point, I was up in the balcony and I went downstairs
and used the restroom and came back to the balcony
and they still hadn't started their next song.
And when they finally did, it was only one
minute long. And I had to stand in line at the
bathroom because it's a girl's bathroom.
But once it was fixed,
it sounded very good
and enjoyable.
How many people were there?
Um,
more than one,
more than one, less
than, um,
500.
You're kidding.
It was a lot smaller than last year.
I think Madonna was actually keeping
a tab on it.
And what'd they say?
I don't know. I left early.
Wow.
Trying to get on. Let's see how crazy we can get at this
show tonight. Hello, you're on the air.
You're on the air.
Hello.
Hello?
Just cut loose.
What?
Hey.
Hello?
Yes. Welcome to the program.
Huh?
What's happening, Dr. Stenister?
Not much.
What's happening with you?
Can you hear me?
What's going on?
Whatever you need to say, just yell it. Just say it.
Hold on one second here.
What am I supposed to hold on to?
We're all around each other.
Welcome to the program.
Yes, how are you?
I can't complain.
We're not allowed to complain.
How did we bash yesterday?
It was, uh...
It's what we've been talking about.
It was terrible.
Nobody came.
Nobody moshed.
I got injured horribly.
But the beer was really good.
Oh, the beer was terrible.
The beer made everybody sick.
They all went blind afterwards.
Oh, really? Oh, boy, then I'm not alone.
Good.
The moral of the story is you have to...
I had with the show last night
some moshy morons.
Ooh.
Oh, I was thinking that there should be,
like, a bunch of people.
some people who wanted to injure
as many people as possible.
No, actually, the moshers were so...
Oh, they're very polite.
...careful and polite that I joined them.
Of course, I was wearing a suit of armor.
Literally, I had a big metal shield with a dog hood on it.
And a sword.
And these kids would...
It was...
I made a really good target, and I kind of let them come charging at me with this shield.
I even got knocked down.
It was the first time I ever moshed.
I'm 61 or something years old.
I've been in the military for a long time.
I've never...
They had invented moshing when I was old enough to do it safely.
Even I considered doing it for a second, but...
And then I didn't.
You would have gotten stepped on.
Oh, no.
I've...
If I had...
If I were 10 years younger, you...
Oh, age is only a number, honey.
Baby Bear is actually a bass player in a rock and roll band.
Yeah, but I don't get down in the crowd and mosh.
Actually, I get super mad when all the punk kids show up at the metal shows and try to
mosh and just ruin everybody's good time.
I was thinking...
I actually thought about moshing with a cotton rinduant that I remembered.
I actually thought about moshin' with a cotton rinduant that I remembered.
No, I'm 55 years old.
This is not a good idea if I walk in the pit.
Oh, I'm 56 and I'm still young and kickin' it.
I actually had a great time down there with the mosh man.
I guess it was great.
Yeah, but Keith, if you were in the pit, you wouldn't know what you're in for,
would you?
I was thinking that what we need to do...
Like, you were talking about the mishearing.
You thought you were going for some nosh and thinking somebody should open a deli called
the nosh pit.
Exactly.
Yeah.
That's a true Yiddish word, noshing, of course.
Right.
Keith and I know that very well.
Is that where they got the phrase, he noshed his teeth?
He was noshing his teeth.
That's ganashin'.
Yep.
Ganesh.
I'm so mad at these.
Ganesh?
I could nosh my teeth.
Yeah, I gotta say with the mosh people...
Morphing words.
They were very polite young...
Yeah, with the mosh people, maybe I'm being a little overly sensitive.
It just ain't...
Uh-oh.
You are.
Yeah.
Why are you so...
They were nice young ultra-violent droogs.
Ooh.
It's just that, I mean, I'm not a fan of the mosh people.
I mean, I just don't like being jostled like that, even if only for a moment, even if
accidentally and...
Huh.
You're old.
Honestly, Mark, I can relate.
I never liked that either.
Now it's interesting for me.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't mind if they do it.
I just don't want to be part of it.
So when they start, I try to be elsewhere.
I used to, but now I've...
As long as our hands don't wander in certain areas, I don't mind anymore.
I'm gonna bring my suit of arms.
I've armored every metal show.
You know, Mark, I could teach you how to deal with him.
Yeah.
I could teach you how to deal with him.
What do you say?
I think the worst experience I had in the pit, it was actually, it was kind of a play
on words, you know, Fall Out-a-Looza.
It was the Butthole Surfers did a matzo ball pizza tour.
Oy!
And it was Fleming Lips, Stone Temple Pilots and them.
Yeah.
And I actually, when I got out of the pit, basically I was pantsed.
I can't believe it.
Long story short.
Yeah.
And it started this fad.
He was walking away with his pants halfway down and 10 years later, everybody's doing
it.
I used to have good times in the pit when I was younger.
I couldn't appreciate that.
I can't handle it anymore.
You're old.
I know.
I feel old.
I used to...
Oh, come on.
I used to be a little bit older.
I used to enjoy it so much.
I would get these big, huge, tall dudes to like do, you know, put their hands together
to make the little like step for, and they would, I would put my foot in it and they would
launch me and I would do all of that crazy crap was all about it.
That sounds fun.
You crazy kids.
Oh boy.
I missed out on a lot of fun.
Oh.
Well, that didn't happen.
I didn't...
That's pretty tricky to do that because you're like six foot five and point four, three-fifty
percent.
Yeah.
Those guys must have been huge.
Baby Bear is...
Ooh.
That's an ironic name.
She's actually really big.
Yeah.
Like the size of an actual bear.
She's...
That's where the nickname comes from.
If you think how big a baby bear is, they're actually pretty large.
Oh boy.
I didn't know the party was going to be hands on.
Ooh.
Now you just...
Look what you've done.
You just pulled down the whole thing.
What did I miss?
Oh boy.
It's conversation screeching halt.
Okay.
Bye guys.
Done.
Bye.
Oh boy.
Have you been...
Are you properly shamed?
Are you...
Are you done?
You're going to be good now?
Are you going to come out of the corner, take the dunce cap off?
That was Buddha.
But we got one more caller.
Hello you're on the air.
Hello?
Yes.
Oh boy.
I'm back again.
Oh, good.
You're back.
How are you?
Yay.
Anyway.
And so, moving on.
Yeah, he's actually getting close to the 11 o'clock hour right now, so.
Oh, my God.
I know I have to pop a pill.
I know.
Yeah, I've got another several hours of this here to go.
I will be filling in for Keith tonight.
Oh.
Really?
Yeah.
Ouch.
Man.
Yep, I'm doing some overtime.
Hey, well, why not?
Why not?
We all enjoy the shows and.
Yeah, all four of us.
Absolutely.
And all five of us listening in.
Oh, yeah.
No, I was including you guys.
Do you get time and a half for the overtime?
That's right.
Yeah.
I'm getting paid one and a half times what I usually get paid.
That's entertainment.
Oh, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Actually, we haven't checked in on the listeners at all, like, the entire time.
We've got 33 online right now.
We didn't hit the.
We didn't check for the hour slack.
Yeah.
I was hoping we could exceed the goal that we set two weeks ago.
That's all right.
We just have to.
Wait a second.
If we have 33 listeners online, this must be a sign.
Well, we had 40 last time Baby Bear was advertised as being online.
Yeah.
Because they know that she performs.
She performs nude on the radio.
Yep.
Really?
Really.
Even though she weighs 350 pounds.
Baby Bear.
Pretty good.
And the fur is not that thick.
Who is trying to control their clap-on lamp?
That is the sound of listeners masturbating.
Oh, wait a minute.
My lamp's always out.
Oh, okay.
Oh, yeah.
Play sex music.
What happened to Sean?
Oh, yeah.
What ever happened to masturbating Sean?
Did anyone ever...
Here we go again.
We're going to sit around and talk about all the people who used to call in.
But he was...
Just his name is funny.
You know, he's worth bringing up.
Remember that one guy?
Yeah, I remember that one guy.
He is great.
Boy, do I miss that one guy.
I miss him, too.
He was on for that one time a few years ago.
We can dream that he would call in again, maybe.
Well, let's take a moment to remind everyone that this is WCSB Cleveland 89.3 FM.
Portions of the following broadcast will be objectionable to some members of the audience.
Therefore, WCSB advises listener discretion.
Views and opinions expressed on this program are not necessarily those of WCSB or Cleveland State University
or anybody with their head screwed on straight for that matter.
Amen.
This is WCSB...
You're a little frisky tonight, Keith.
I've got to say, you are much more lively than you are on some other nights.
I'm in a good mood.
All right.
Glad to hear it.
Yeah, I'm in a good mood.
I had a good week.
I'm feeling good.
Good.
Good for you.
And we just have to be thankful for what we have.
I've had a weak week.
I'm feeling weak.
Seven days will make one week.
That's right.
Bad puns.
So let's...
Let's see.
Take another caller here.
That's 216-687-3515.
Hello, you're on the air.
That's probably...
Dr. Sinister.
St. Bernard.
Yes.
On Halloween, I yelled in a store and I canceled everything I had planned for that evening.
Really?
Because I'm on the cover of Rolling Stone magazine.
Because you are on the cover of Rolling Stone magazine.
Those of you who are on the cover of Rolling Stone magazine,
you could probably find out online.
You could probably find out online.
Thank you.
Okay.
Bernie reminds me of another, of Bernard.
Oh, that was Bernie.
Yeah, I thought it was for a second.
Yeah, that was Bernie.
I have a serial message lever.
Oh.
I thought I was, like, about to witness some serious, like, history in the making.
I thought you were coming face-to-face with Bernie for the first time.
Dr. Sinister has Bernie and I have Bernard.
I used to play Bernard's calls on Hour of Slack every now and then years ago, but...
It's too depressing.
He hasn't.
He hasn't stopped.
And he's so clearly...
If I was playing him, they'd be funny, but I'd be...
It's not funny.
He's sad.
I would be exploiting a mentally ill person.
That's why it makes me sad.
Oi, why not?
That's the whole purpose of this radio show.
Right, yeah.
Present company included.
But, yeah, it's...
Believe it or not, I have drawn a certain line where I won't exploit certain crazy people.
No matter how funny they are to everybody else, because they're not trying to be funny.
They're trying to warn you about the conspiracy, which is usually pretty personal with them.
Absolutely.
Yeah, they usually believe that the conspiracy has taken a personal interest in them.
And taken over.
Oh, yeah.
You know what?
Let me look up and see what's on the current cover of Rolling Stone.
Whatever it is, it's meaningful and has something to do with...
Call her Bernie.
I love the way that Bernie did not provide a URL or any kind of information about what he was talking about.
Wait, are you guys trying to say that you've been doubting this?
Right, it shouldn't be self-evident.
You guys sound like...
I don't...
I mean, it seems legit to me.
What's the...
You guys need to be...
Stop being so suspicious.
We've only been listening to Bernie for eons.
Well, Princess, you're adorable.
You're adorable.
They don't even say what's on the current cover anywhere on their front page of the website.
They want you to be surprised and buy it.
No, they want to discredit Bernie.
Maybe they're referring to Stephen King.
The headline is Stephen King, the Rolling Stone interview, and that might very well be on the cover.
And they've also got Paul Rubens.
Oh, yeah, Pee-Wee's coming back, right?
Yeah.
Pee-Wee's coming.
He's going to do a new Pee-Wee.
Will the Dobbs head still be in the Playhouse?
They took that out.
Yeah, that was only the first season.
Season two, they took that out.
Yeah, but it was for the first season of Pee-Wee's Playhouse.
He had a Dobbs head on the set.
It was put there by Gary Panter, who was mentioned an hour ago on the station.
And they used it in the title.
So kids saw Bob every Saturday morning.
When they tuned in to see Pee-Wee.
And one episode, Pee-Wee had the word of the day was OK.
He looked in the camera.
It was a close-up of Pee-Wee.
But Bob was visible prominently over his shoulder.
So all these four-year-olds saw Pee-Wee going, OK, with Bob right behind him.
OK.
And then later, their parents said, well, Pee-Wee was arrested for masturbating in a theater.
Oh!
Gay theater.
And the kids just went, so?
But Pee-Wee, but CBS didn't say, so?
They said, your career is over, buddy.
That was a shame.
I'm glad that Pee-Wee's coming back.
Although, you know, he still owes us 20 bucks.
He left a message on my answer machine going, this is Paul Rubin, also known as Pee-Wee Herman,
would you send me one of those subgenius memberships and bill me?
And I did.
But he never paid up.
So I figured that putting the Dobbs head in the minds of millions of children was worth $10 of his $20 memberships.
Paul, Pee-Wee, whatever you call yourself now, you still owe us 10 bucks, buddy.
Better pay up.
That means he's only half-saved.
I don't mean it that way.
Oh, you're not going to include interest.
You don't want to do that again.
Wallet, wallet.
Wallet.
His mug shot on the cover of our scene, the stark fist, with the phrase martyr or something like that.
He was in Mystery Men after that.
Yes, the spleen.
Yes, Mystery Men was one of my favorite terrible, terrible movies that happened.
You know, Bob Burden, who drew the flaming carrot that that was loosely based on,
was telling us all that this was going to be the movie that put weirdos on top.
He was saving.
Bob Burden was saving.
He was saving us all because Mystery Men was going to be such a big hit that all of us weirdos would be famous by glint of being, you know, part of his, or by dent of being his friends.
It was a really big deal to me.
I saw it and I was like vindicated.
Yeah.
I thought it was a really funny movie.
It was my favorite superhero movie for a long time because it was about what would happen if a bunch of losers thought they were superheroes.
Now, since then, there have been dozens of movies like that.
Most of which are pretty good.
About people who think they're superheroes or try to be.
And I don't mean the Kick-Ass series, although that was interesting.
Invisible Griff is one that not many people saw, but it was really good.
You know, I'm still not very good at throwing forks.
Huh?
I'm still not very good at throwing forks.
I've been trying it ever since I saw the Blue Raja.
You fork up?
I can't do it.
But I shovel.
I shovel well.
Yeah.
Oh, me too.
Neurodynamic.
But I am great at being invisible when no one is looking.
Yep.
I can do that too.
I can relate.
All subgeniuses have some useless superpower.
That's right.
And you are on the air.
What's your useless superpower?
Go.
Mine?
No, the person that's on the air.
Well, we did this two weeks ago.
No, the caller on the air.
Oh, yeah.
What's your useless superpower, caller?
Whip it out.
Oh, yeah.
You have two seconds to be funny.
Two, one, go.
Come on, man.
The red on the air light is on.
It's the unfunniest whistle ever.
It's like a deer in the headlights.
We made it so easy for him.
Ouch.
Killing the audience.
I think many people are still recovering from your party.
Hmm.
Maybe.
Princess, we and I didn't wake up until one o'clock but then later in the day, we
found out that we were still getting a little bit of sleep.
We found out that it was really, was noon because time had changed and they didn't
tell us.
Exactly.
You didn't fall back.
No.
In fact, it's really midnight for us now.
No, I don't think that you, I think that you didn't wake up until like two.
No, we got, we were, I got out, I'm pretty sure, well, two, no, two and yeah, that's
in yet another time change.
I'm lost.
Lost in time.
What time did everybody part ways last night?
Well, they kicked everybody out about one o'clock or so.
Yeah.
Oh.
Yeah, they, they, you know, the band's in, they show, you know, everybody has to
leave or clean, or help clean up.
We left.
Yeah.
Then they scatter real fast.
We cleaned up our, we cleaned up the balcony.
We took all of our beer cups out.
Sure did.
And I threw away a bunch of beer cans and other things that were on the floor.
So I.
Oh, that's a nice mark.
You're a good WCSB volunteer.
Yes.
A lot better than me.
Well, I did provide the video projections and I worked for at least a half a day on
that.
All right.
Let's take another caller here.
You're on the air.
How you doing?
For some reason, I can't hear you then, but I'm going to start with this.
My superpower is growing mushrooms all my own.
The reason why is because when I'm streaming it by myself, I can eat the mushrooms.
Now, can I hear you?
I don't know.
Can you?
Nope.
You guys are really bad on the connection.
Must be the cell phones or something.
Where do you hear all the mushrooms?
Now this is a.
Do you have cell phones?
What do you have?
I don't know.
Is she speaking English?
I'll tell you what.
I'd like to donate to your show because I'm a big fan of your show.
I'm a big fan of your show.
You guys need some updated equipment.
How do you?
Sound, sound.
That was.
It's the falsetto that's insulting the station.
Is the caller still there?
No.
Also, staying terrified.
He can't hear.
Can't hear anything.
Just so you know, like if you, if, if, uh, if you're, if you're eating the mushrooms
that grow on your own body, it's, it's not going to work.
You're still losing energy because the mushroom can only grow by eating your body to begin
with.
And then you're just going to have to, you know, get rid of the mushrooms.
Yeah, but it makes you a real fun guy.
I love mushrooms, but the ones that are growing not on me.
I was going to say that I'm sorry the caller is no longer there because I was going to
ask him how many in Pluto we're doing.
That was only sporadically funny.
I got to give you points for that one.
That was clever.
We need Dr. Dark.
Dr. Dark here.
Ooh.
She's channeling Dr. Dark.
I'm always in the dark.
We have a friend, Dr. Dark, who is really deadly with puns.
Yeah.
He's really, really good at, that's his superpower.
Right.
He can't stop.
I mean, was Dr. Dark, was Dr. Dark named after the villain on Defenders of the Earth?
No, he's, he's named that because he runs a drive-in at X Day Drills.
Ooh.
Oh, cool.
We have a three nights of, or two nights at least of night.
Yeah.
What was, what were the last ones he showed?
Machete Kills.
We've shown Big Man Japan.
That was a really, really weird one.
Oh, he had the double bill one year of Abraham Lincoln Vampire Slayer and Jesus Christ Something
Slayer and FDR.
Actually, I just remember one of the ones that they did this year and I don't think
I can say it on the air.
Uh oh.
Yeah.
The last one, the last one regrettably went up, but...
We gotta say, is that the first movie, what's the second one?
Is that lanerpeak after the end?
Yeah.
Well, and we talked aboutiti.
So, is that season three done?
It's not done yet.
When are we done?
We have the last two shows.
It's New Year's Eve.
What's yourbull ys doing now?
Well, it's January 3rd.
that they could say the title.
Yep, it's a real movie.
That's the only reason
for it to exist.
No, there's another good reason.
The other good reason was to have
naked ladies
that were
writhing on the floor
because they were being eaten by ants
that came out of a thing.
That was the thing.
It's a real thing that happened.
It's a real thing.
This certainly isn't appealing
to prairie interest.
You notice I didn't hit the button.
They used props.
I know.
They were plastic props.
It's like those Russ Meyer movies.
He could get away with...
The silly putty things looked really real.
Russ Meyer did these series of fabulous
some were comedies
and some were thrillers.
They were softcore porn.
What made them
legal was that
the male genitalia that was shown
was never real.
They were plastic and kind of obviously
made of plastic or rubber
and going boing boing.
The ladies
were real.
Because of that
at that time, which I guess
would be the 70s mostly,
you could then show them
and they wouldn't get an X rating.
They'd just get an R rating.
They could still be in...
semi-respectable theaters.
By the way, I gotta say that
Ant Farm Dickhole, based on the title,
that's the kind of movie I would pay
a lot of good money never to see.
No, man, do yourself a favor.
Just watch it.
Just do it, man.
Come on.
What's the matter, you're afraid?
We had to do it.
Well, you're afraid your parents,
your mom and dad's gonna find out?
If I had to watch it,
I'm dragging all of you down with me.
I'm not doing this alone.
I'm not.
I'm living with this.
I'll go, but you would have to
audio describe it to me.
It's pretty...
I wonder if it's one of those movies
that has one of those extra audio tracks
for the visually impaired audience.
Yeah, you'd be really confused, I think,
because you just hear a lot of screaming
and a lot of jerking off noises.
A line of ants are parading
from the urethra.
Yeah, that's basically what it's about.
The ants are climbing...
They're all over the woman.
It's a very...
It's an honestly titled movie.
You know, some movies you get a...
It's probably gonna make a good double feature
with the human centipede.
Actually, that's not a...
That's probably what they were hoping for.
I don't think I'd be able to sleep for a few days.
I downloaded the human centipede
and kind of skimmed through it,
and I was afraid to watch it.
I decided I didn't need to do...
I wasn't in the room when he skimmed.
I watched the South Park episode parodying it,
so I decided that that was enough.
I was done.
No, I actually want to see it.
You guys are...
Don't mistake it for The Human Centipede 2,
which is a completely different movie.
It's about a guy who saw the first one
and wants to make it happen in real life,
and he stalks and abducts one of the stars of the first one.
But, of course, that was just a movie,
but this guy really tries to do it.
And it's an amateur surgery.
He's a surgeon, not a professional mad scientist
like the guy in the first movie.
You're making this up as you go on.
No, I'm not.
It's for real.
That's really the sequel.
It's a real thing.
You know what the best thing is about being part of the human centipede?
I don't know.
The front part, I would think.
You always know where your next meal is coming from.
Oh, boy.
Princess Wee doesn't get that,
and that's working in her favor.
I'm glad.
I'm glad that she's too innocent to know what we're talking about.
She's cannibalizing itself?
You've been reduced to fart noises on the air.
Do you mean to say that the human centipede just cannibalized itself?
Is that what you're trying to tell me?
No, it's not a loop.
You know what?
That's it.
The guy in front is...
I sentence you to watching Ant Farm Dickhole.
This is your punishment.
Wait, where are we going today?
Whoa.
What?
Hey.
Whoa.
This is a good show.
Oh, hey.
Thanks.
By the way, I understand that that movie is going to be spun off into a sitcom.
The human centipede?
No, no, no.
The other one.
Mm-hmm.
Really, Sherman?
You mean to tell me you've never heard of the Ant Farm Dickhole Van Dyke Show?
Oh, man.
Oh, girl.
And on that note, I will take my leave for now.
Get out.
That's it.
You're out.
Yeah, I might call you back.
Strike three.
Have a great evening.
Well, thanks.
Good night, Mark.
You too.
Bye, Mark.
Night, Mark.
He made his mark.
Yep.
Have we found enough excuses to say the title of the movie?
I'm not going to do it again.
I'm not even doing it.
I'm going to let it go.
Sorry.
Drop it.
I'm being Dave over here.
I'm sorry.
You're beating a dead horse.
Beating off a dead horse.
Hey, it's hard to do that.
I do.
Okay.
Let's bring back one more caller here.
Hey, guys.
Sorry.
I had to cut off on you.
Aw.
Well, some cowboy Dave's...
You missed a really elevated conversation.
... asking me if I knew where he was.
Ooh.
Yeah.
Well, I was curious.
You know, I was talking with Stang before, you know, everything started and all that.
I saw Princess Wee, and I saw this very petite, short-haired woman there.
I don't know who you're talking about.
Oh, okay.
I know who it was then.
That's Baby Bear's baby.
Damn.
I'm sorry.
I don't know how old you are, but it was like, do you have a lot of children in here?
Oh.
Oh, you were cute, though.
But I felt guilty looking at you.
I was like, no.
This is a little girl.
Hey, nothing wrong with that.
Nope.
Screw you, man.
I'm sorry.
This is the only time, you know, I'm just gonna get a little bit more into you.
I'm not cool.
I can't help it.
If I go to a restaurant with my parents, sometimes they still give me a kid's menu, which I used
to get upset about when I was like 17, but now I just take it and eat off the kid's menu.
I got my first senior discount without asking for it.
Just with the white beer.
And I was only 55 at the time.
Yeah.
I got a coffee at McDonald's.
It really shook him up.
Yeah.
No kidding.
I got coffee at McDonald's.
We were driving away.
I went, it's only 75 cents.
What's the senior discount?
What's SR discount?
What does that mean?
There's nothing wrong with that.
There's this one guy.
I haven't been carded in years.
They're supposed to card you, and every now and then they do, and it's ridiculous, you know.
Well, we have to check everybody's ID.
They carded me at the con on the cob, and I couldn't even go into the party because I didn't have my ID card.
That's right.
Yeah, because you might be under 21.
I said, read the wrinkles and gray hair, sir.
And he said, I'm sorry, I have to see your ID.
Okay, I can't come in.
Well, don't feel that's odd.
It was about a year ago.
I went out with some friends, and I wanted some wine.
They carded me.
It's got to be like carding the oldest man in the world.
I've been rejected from buying beer because someone thought that my ID wasn't actually me.
If I hear that, I am flattered.
You're going to card me?
You're right.
It is a compliment.
Yeah, no, I really just wanted the beer.
I really didn't come in there for compliments.
I just specifically came in there just to buy the beer.
But they thought you had a fake ID.
Yeah.
Because I think I was like, I was wearing, like I had glasses in the picture, and I was like a sunburn because it's my birthday in the summer.
And they were like, yeah, no, this isn't you.
And I'm like, no, no, really.
Just give me some freaking beer.
When they card me, I say, thank you.
Well, that's true.
It's a compliment, but I think it's a compliment.
Are you serious?
Do you get carded when you buy games at GameStop?
Do they card you for the mature games?
Rated M for mature?
No, no, not.
They don't.
I had to do that when I worked there, and that was terrible.
People would get awful mad at you about that.
They just thought it was the.
That was the stupidest thing.
And I'm like, look, I'm sorry.
Why?
Just show me your ID.
I don't know.
I can't.
I have to do it.
It's not my fault.
I didn't make the rules.
It's my job.
I'd sell GTA 5 to a 10-year-old.
I don't care.
There's laws.
Rules.
The online version of this game is not approved by the.
The online version is never approved by anyone because they can never tell how many.
Yeah.
They.
You don't know what's going to happen once you step foot online.
Well, I know what's going to happen.
You're going to get called.
I don't actually.
I'm not.
I don't know the rules of what I can get away with saying.
So I.
You're going to get called what?
Get called a faggot by a 12-year-old.
Oh, my.
That's what will happen to you when you go online playing any game.
And that's just the reality of the situation.
Right.
My son warned me about that.
He says, Dad, you know, you're going to end up being.
Getting your.
Your ass kicked by 12-year-olds.
And when you hear their voices, you're going to be really horrified.
They're going to.
They'll be cussing like a blue streak.
Sounding like little girls.
Because they're.
They're mostly 12-year-old boys.
Actually, because there's so many 12-year-old boys.
When I get on the microphone on online games, they think that they do not believe that I am a girl.
They believe that I am a 12-year-old boy.
Yeah.
You know, this actually.
When you're talking about some of the.
Stuff you hear in those.
This kind of on a more serious note speaks to why I can't.
I never got into the online gaming community at all because.
I don't like gamer fanboys.
And I don't like the idea of having to play against them.
I don't like the idea of having to collaborate with them.
And on top of that, it becomes a great big echo chamber.
And there's a lot of all kinds of.
It's the absolute lowest of the low of our of our culture that you hear.
Yeah, it's it's pretty.
It's pretty terrible.
It's not fun.
I don't know.
We're going to get real.
People get real.
I had the.
You really get tired of hearing tits or GTFO like pretty fast.
Yeah.
And I have.
I had the misfortune of living in the same apartment building with with an avid gamer who was on some kind of Xbox.
Xbox Live or something like that.
And he would just be screaming all kinds of stuff all the time.
The only person I play on live with is an eight-year-old girl.
Oh, that's all right.
Filers.
Well, I'm new to video games.
I only play one monster.
And the only other subgenius in the whole world that plays it is Philo's daughter, age eight.
And I actually have to watch my mouth because I start cussing a blue streak when the monsters are getting the best of me.
And so I have to be careful with this little tender child.
And you have to watch how you talk about how she looks because her her character in the game is a grown woman.
Yeah.
No kidding.
One time she had to she had to leave the room and do something.
Her dad took over the controls.
So her dad was the good looking hunter hunter girl.
And I my hunter man walked over to where she was.
And I said, I'm standing uncomfortably close to inappropriately inappropriately close now.
And if I could hear Philo's voice in the other end, he goes, I know it's making me very uncomfortable.
And he was sitting there.
There are young woman's body.
So once his daughter came back, of course, I didn't do that anymore.
That would make me feel uncomfortable.
You got to be careful these days, you know.
Oh, boy.
What I miss, boy.
Well, I remember the day.
Get a copy of Monster Hunter.
Yeah.
Just go spend hundreds of dollars on all of this stuff.
Unfortunately, you do have to have a Wii U to play that online.
And it's that's a 200.
A hundred bucks right there.
Just just for this one day.
A lot of on the other hand, the real addicts like me will do that.
And we all did.
We all did.
When the new version Wii U or.
Hmm.
No.
Was it a princess Wii U or.
Oh.
Cornies.
I couldn't help it.
So we're getting close to the bottom of the hour here.
And it looks like that's running down over there.
So why don't we take a break?
Here.
And we will return for more around 1130 or so.
We'll see what happens next.
Thank you guys for your contributions.
And please, if you can stop that whistle.
You actually hurt my ears.
You're welcome.
Pregnant.
Uncomfortable.
Okay.
Talk to you guys later.
Thank you.
Talk to you soon.
This is synesthesia on WCSB Cleveland portions of the following broadcast will be objectionable
to some members of the audience.
Therefore, WCSB advises listeners to be aware of the importance of the use of the word.
Listener discretion, views and opinions expressed on this program are not necessarily those
of WCSB or Cleveland State University.