I'm sure I saw a flash of light in the sky.
Really?
The...
Self...
Genius...
Paul...
Of Spock!
Who are you?
My name is Naya.
Really?
Where do you come from?
Mars.
Really?
But that's preposterous.
You're not that poor.
It's Peppa.
Peppa?
Yes.
The Peppa Можно.
Peppa is an American...
In the universe.
From the top of the Empire State Building, and broadcasting loud to all time zones around
the world in stereo...
This is...
Alive...
It's alive!
Mom, Dad, it's evil!
Don't touch it!
Because Bob came.
Bob doesn't care about your sins.
Bob won't die for your sins because Bob's not the son of God.
Bob won't die for your sins.
Bob won't forgive you for your sins.
Bob will justify your sins.
First, I'd just like to say that it's really great to be here.
I mean, it really is.
It's real good.
Good God.
God, it's good to be here.
I don't know where to begin to tell you.
Damn, it's good to be here.
You cad.
You dirty swine.
I never cared for you not once.
I was always making a fool of you.
It made me sick when I had to let you kiss me.
I only did it because you begged me.
You hounded me.
You drove me crazy.
And after you kissed me, I always used to wipe my mouth.
Wipe my mouth.
You are a menace.
A walking pest.
I'm telling you, they can't get in here.
And I'm telling you, those things turned over our car.
Hell, how many good five men can do that?
That's my point.
Only there's not going to be five or even ten.
There's going to be twenty, thirty, maybe a hundred of those things.
And as soon as they know we're here, this place is going to be crawling with them.
The air attack warning sounds like this is the sound.
Are we men? Or are we just machines?
Slaved to an electronic beat.
A probability wave in space.
You are on the brink of extinction.
Seriously.
We are an army of strangely dressed, deeply confused, pseudo-individual conformists.
Look up and the ghost!
Smashing!
America, the number one nation.
And we're number one.
Hi, we're the Rusty's.
And we're from Gary, Indiana.
We're number one segregation.
And murder.
Hi, I'm Virgil Strickman from Claxton, Georgia.
We are number one in fruitcakes.
I'm Bill McNutt, Collins Street Bakery, 4th St. of Texas.
And we're number one in fruitcakes.
No, we're number one in fruitcakes.
No, we're number one.
No, we are number one in fruitcakes.
Who are these people?
Why do they enjoy spending their leisure unclothed among other nude people?
The tumor on her neck is definitely a fetus.
Friends and neighbors of planet Earth, I come to you from a long, long ways off.
I come from a planet that is similar to yours.
Your many fears, tensions, and frustrations are no longer ours.
I hate them with all my heart.
Pop.
Rock and roll is dead and pop is in.
Why not discover the excitement of the science of music yourself?
Thanks to the science of music, you don't need musical talent to make great music.
Just listen.
I created that just by pressing a button.
Synthesizers are the new wave.
Why work hard on difficult compositions when a machine can make music better than you've ever dreamed of?
You'll be the hit of the party.
It's perfect for in-restaurant entertainment.
Cover bands and funerals.
Make fugues funky and death marches danceable.
It's the science of music.
Remember, you don't know you're a musician until you try.
My fellow Americans, I'm pleased to tell you today that I've signed legislation that will outlaw Russia forever.
We begin bombing in five minutes.
The funeral program in this baby is really gone.
The functioning of our senses has been spiritually impaired and chemically corrupted by the...
We've got to put some food coloring in there.
They stole the election.
We had a cool day at town.
We prevented the hijacking and theft of the presidency of the United States.
We know the race is not to the swift, nor the bound to the strong.
Do you not think an angel rides in the whirlwind and directs this storm?
You're a freak, man.
What a way to go out.
If any of you are copying this, it is illegal.
And I hope you burn in hell.
But might I suggest you turn the cassette over?
This is, of course, a compact disc.
A brand new format heralding a new age of lasers.
An age typified by man and machine living as one with bangs.
From PR News in Washington, I'm Far From Functional in New Jersey.
The Justice Department says it has 209,000.3% of PR news in New Jersey.
PR reports police in Australia say President Trump has his New Jersey.
Israeli authorities say PR's reporting reports police are investigating bribery, fraud, and breach of New Jersey.
In New Jersey.
On Wall Street, 38.8, 38.7, 3.
The Prime Minister of Cambodia says thanks, but no PR news in New Jersey.
Thank you, Fernanda Nande-Lemur, for PR News.
Earlier, we heard some media barrage stuff that was cut up by Cool Hand Chris.
And now, the Rudy Schwartz Project.
We're in the South.
This is the Central Newsroom.
Great.
Thanks for coming.
Take care, everyone.
Have a good night, everybody.
Have a good night.
Bye-bye.
Thank you.
Now beware, have a care,
you're just filled with air.
A single pin
would rip your skin
and the pincushion man
in the forest there
would pop you both
if you don't take care.
Most is trash in the flesh,
I'll settle his hash.
I'll bust right in
and twist his chin.
I'll get rough, I'll get tough,
I'll just call his bluff.
No, no,
please don't go.
I'll bust right in
and I'll bust right in.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
I'm the old pincushion man,
terror of
balloony land.
Folks all hate me,
how they hate me,
tickles me the way they rate me.
Always have a pin
at hand,
that's the reason I am panned.
How I stop them
when I pop them.
Ha ha ha!
How I get to deliberately
I'm a one came,
I'm a fortune teller.
I'm sissy .
Not a thing believe to Fangs
before I live a few weeks!
I'm a grown up now,
Five c-quad Petанием.
Hey folks,
the one time is fine.
Thought you were looking for clippity?
꼭
約
Lo, looco, loo, loo, rouu, adaaargh!
have you settled, Auch!
こ、あи、 FPs, G sempre be careful, stop being talkative.
Thank you.
The tapes are okay, Doug.
We can go to bed tonight and sleep soundly.
As long as nobody's listening to them, everything's fine.
As long as they're not being copied or preserved.
This is a wonderful story because Gary had a Fostex
that we just brought to Doc's Dock.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Really nice recordings of silly times.
And then the Fostex died at one point.
And I was at the White Elephant sale
and found a T-Act of the same,
I think it's T-Act, right?
Tascam.
Boy crack, yeah.
T-Acts were better.
Same one.
And so now I can save those band tapes.
I was thinking I should just get that stuff back to you
and just go ahead and make four channel tapes
before that thing dies, too.
And then sell it to some 30-year-old who goes,
wow, tape technology.
I'm still looking for the buttons for my Rhino suit,
so I really can't.
I had to buy a fruit drying machine
to...
Yeah.
...bake my reel-to-reel tape.
No, no, really.
You bake old tapes...
A rice cooker, yeah.
...because you only get one last chance to play them
after their binder has failed.
Yeah.
You can heat them up
and the binder will hold just long enough
to run them through a machine one time.
But your oven is too hot for that.
So there's a certain level on this fruit dry,
this cheap fruit dry thing.
Yeah, they work in the back.
Yeah.
If you leave your tape there for two hours
and sure enough, it will improve.
What you're doing is making the binder...
Bringing the binder back.
You can do both the salmon and the tape.
The binder between the tape and the emulsion
and the heating makes it flexible again.
And Don swore that he could get a week out of it.
He could do it and still play a week later.
Yeah, but a Don week.
A Don week, yeah.
So it was Don Joyce for us, the late Don Joyce.
He turned me on to that trick.
His late week.
And he'd seen it.
It was a guy at Ampex over in the South Bay.
It was a huge Ampex place.
Oh, right, right.
And somehow he accidentally decided to make cookies
out of old tapes or something
and found out he could do this, restore the emulsion.
Were there gill or gill tape?
I always heard it attributed to Dr. Demento.
I thought it was like you pulled it out of the river.
It's like the story you have in your book.
I love that.
The man I was always taught started the Civil War,
with Edmund Ruffin pulled the lanyard
and fired the first cannon at Anderson's command.
Fort Funston, right.
Fort Funston, yeah.
And yet there's this whole story about somebody else,
some other guy fired a cannon,
and then the argument became this delicate thing of,
well, the first cannon was actually a flare that goes off.
Then there's another cannon that actually hurts people.
So they were just one of those great,
that's what history is.
But as a matter of honor and respect,
they did allow.
They did allow the northern soldiers to order out for pizza.
Yeah, yeah, because it was a pizza store.
Yeah, the Confederates in Charleston Harbor
were actually really,
as long as nobody wanted arugula and smoked chicken on their pizza,
they would allow the Union soldiers to order anything.
Well, okay, well, who started making the reel-to-reel tapes?
The Confederacy or the Union?
No, it was the Union because the Confederacy didn't have enough power
to get the little baker thing.
And they didn't know what the tapes were.
They just.
They had them, but they.
Plus the cotton threads would get caught in the heads.
No, but you know what's amazing?
Didn't they have a spy that took them to Jeff Davis
and he'd look at them for hours and hours with these other guys
and they figured out that it was just some sort of Yankee contraption
that they couldn't do anything.
You saw this movie, huh?
And then when they played the tapes back,
it was nothing but a bunch of doctor bands,
subgeniuses all talking at the same time.
Yeah.
Yeah, and they were all fat and stuff and had big ears.
Yeah, and were all successful and had huge ranches.
But we can't transfer tapes if you want to come by.
And the testers all crawl behind the console
and plug in all the plugs.
Yeah.
We do that as a free service of the church.
Did you ever use one of them sound-on-sound vehicles
where, like, if you keep bouncing tracks back and forth,
you build tracks?
Yeah.
Oh, are you kidding?
Of course.
That goes back to what we were just saying.
The early Beatle albums were done that way.
It's called ping-ponging.
Yeah, the early subgenius albums were done that way.
Yeah, everybody's early albums were done that way, yeah.
And especially cool because at that time you could mix for mono.
So until Spectre took over, you know,
you could just do a lot more,
and it came out of this one four-inch speaker
in the back of your car.
Well, you and Glass Madness had a way of making
double tracking on a cassette by covering up
one part of the recording.
The erase head.
Yeah, the erase head with a piece of a matchmaker.
I don't know how new that is, but in these newer ones.
The new what?
Digital recorder?
Yeah, the little digital recorder like this one
and a couple of companies I've looked at.
How do you get the match inside?
They have that in as a command.
You do a whole track.
You do what we're doing now.
Oh, really?
There's a way to go click, click,
and now you can just dump another two tracks
on top of those two tracks.
I didn't know you did that on a little handheld.
I'll have to read the instructions one of these days.
I think it's also kind of a new trick.
So you just push a button.
You don't have to stick a match head in there?
Exactly.
You stick the match head in electronically now.
This was the coolest trick ever.
Yeah, if you covered up the erase head,
then your track would be in there.
The tracks didn't go away, see?
And you could pile up until just like nine times
as a kid when you'd have it.
It just sounded like sonic soup.
You couldn't tell.
But over time, you learned to be careful.
I kind of did screwy four-channel thinking with it.
I'd mark with pieces of paper where the next verse started.
Yeah, yeah.
Then you dropped the microphone in the toilet.
No, the sad part was I lived.
It's a beautiful sound for like half a second.
Yeah.
I actually tried to make a waterproof mic
and then had like 300 feet of cord
and the beach was right there.
So I went out in the water and I yelled in the thing
and got home and nothing on the tape
because I didn't know anything about powering the signal or anything.
I just thought, oh, it doesn't work.
I'm surprised you didn't at least get some voices from the dead.
I probably did, but I just wasn't open to it.
Right.
I don't think you couldn't record voices from the dead before 78, could you?
Before 78.
No, back in third, by the time.
No, they had 78s with voices.
That's what I was going to say.
I mean, more people had 33s and 45s.
If you watch movies, White Noise 1 and 2,
that's all about finding the people in the white noise of a tape recorder.
And they were so lighthearted, too, at the same time.
That's why they had to smash.
They had to smash them with a mighty, mighty fist.
Oh, yeah, we're getting back to some of this theology here.
Yeah, that's theology.
Well, it's not everything, but it certainly is everything.
I mean, if you...
Well, we used to leave an open mic in a room with the tape deck on
and we'd walk away for an hour and we'd come back and listen for an hour
to see if Bob had said anything.
But the most we ever got was this real, real faint sort of...
I don't know.
If they can't take a show...
Oh, God.
Yeah, and then that's the whole thing.
That was it.
You have to listen really carefully.
That was 45 minutes in.
Yeah, so you have to listen...
That's a slack hour.
A couple of times to the whole 45 minutes
to make sure that's where the voice is.
Yeah, we did that three times a day for two years.
That was the only line we got there.
Amazing.
You know what it's like in social comparisons like masturbation.
If you do many times, you go blind.
Yeah.
Or perhaps you have a hard time hearing,
you become hard of hearing.
Yeah.
And that's really dangerous.
And you're taking a walk
and there's like electronic cars going by
because they could impair your visual optometry.
You know what I'm saying?
I'm not sure what you mean.
It's Ohio speak.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Neighbor world talk.
Once in a while, Vreedys will break into full-on Ohio speak.
Yeah, yeah.
And we'll have to slow down.
I'm not talking Pittsburgh young for talk.
Yeah, because we come from the fast coast,
you know, where everything's different speed
and different intonation
and completely different subject matter.
We're just too cool for ourselves.
Oh, yeah, you wouldn't be able to understand Youngstownian.
Yeah, not at all.
Not at all, yeah.
The Youngers.
You employ a translator for this kind of thing.
They say Youngers, the views are y'all.
They call people Youngs
and they say they're going downtown.
Stuff like that there.
Yeah.
Sounds like New Orleans.
Where I'm from, people talk about going pouch groveling.
Yeah.
Which is...
Oh, I could love such an event.
Yeah.
You might.
Yeah, boy, damn on the coast.
Yeah.
I would rate very high rating.
He is on the coast.
He's on the north coast.
Ashtabula's right on the lake.
On the Great Lakes of...
Did they move it to Wisconsin?
No.
No, no, that's very far north,
but on the Great Lakes.
Great Lakes due north.
Yeah, well, you can swim to Canada from Dave's house.
Really?
Let's do that.
Actually, you can drive to...
There have been people who drove to Canada
across the lake when it was frozen.
Wow.
But there are also many pickup trucks
at the bottom of the lake.
Huh.
It didn't quite make it.
We should go down there and salvage the guns.
There's plenty of them.
Yeah.
Yeah, because you drive out and go...
There was a great...
A true story.
These guys that went out fishing on the lake
when it was frozen.
I heard that one.
And they decided they were going to blow a hole
with some dynamite.
And they threw the dynamite
and forgot about the little dog.
The dog ran and picked up the dynamite
and ran back to their truck
and blew it up there.
And everybody died except for the idiots.
The dog and the truck and, you know...
The men ran, you know,
when they saw the dog come back.
And that was it.
That's the way to go.
Poor little Fido.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's a surprise.
I believe that that actually really happened.
You believe it happened.
I believe it.
I choose to believe.
I believe what I need to believe,
to quote Pappy.
On the corner of Pico and Sepulveda,
that's where you ground out your last delicious meal.
Pico and Sepulveda.
La, la, la.
La, la, la, la.
You guys are so old.
Yeah.
It's true.
Ob-spreen.
But I didn't learn it from...
From the 1930s movies.
I learned it from The Forbidden Zone.
Richard Elfman's movies.
So that makes it okay.
Yeah.
I'm not old.
It's ironic.
It's not historical.
Right.
Yeah.
I didn't just know it.
I'm not old.
Legitimately.
I knew it ironically only.
Yeah.
As a cultural bystone,
not getting stoned myself and liking it.
Yeah, right.
And like, what if you had all those different stones
like they do down in Georgia?
Yeah.
I would smoke marijuana
so I can hate the world instead of myself.
I said...
Oh, man.
What a great idea.
I wish I was...
I thought it was frop.
In the original thing,
let's get back...
Yeah, it was frop.
Let's smoke frop
so we can get back to hating the world
instead of ourselves.
Yeah.
I said that to Paul.
Marijuana?
Why would you...
Because I had not smoked...
Abused marijuana in a great while
and my friend Lies had some.
So I rushed over to his house
and I said, yeah,
now I can hate the world instead of myself.
Paul left real hard.
Uh-huh.
That's not funny.
No, that's sad.
That's too close to the truth.
Too close to the truth.
It's a little too real, man.
That's what show is now.
You're triggering me.
Listen, young people.
The show's going to be trickling down
to almost nothing soon.
So something really important
should be discussed here.
Okay.
Well, there's...
Oh, here's the next book
we're going to publish.
It's actually just the first chapter.
The blue folder?
I'm not mad.
Yeah, it's a science fiction story
which involves...
X day called Eyelash.
And it's really weird.
It's by a subgenius named
Nikolai Kingsley
who lives in Australia.
And that's going to be
our next novel
that we publish
as a print-on-demand thing
so it doesn't cost us anything.
Oh.
Dave, I think we sold like...
I think we sold like
75 copies of Neighbor World now.
75 copies?
Yeah, and I gave one to my niece,
the subgenius,
the one member of my family
who actually listens to Hour of Slack
besides my wife who's on it,
this one niece of mine,
my brother's daughter,
the one who left Glen Rose
and became an archaeologist.
You're related to a lot of people, man.
Anyway, she's a regular listener.
She's a...
In her points of duty.
She's listening right now.
Yeah, I gave...
She wanted a copy of Neighbor World
and I...
Dave, I just gave it to her.
I just handed it to her.
Yeah.
No commerce involved.
Right.
People are trying to get me to do that too
but I don't have enough.
I'm afraid to go ahead and go and...
Well, I got a new shipment of them, Dave.
I got...
I ordered 16 new ones
of which I have 15 now.
So, you know,
if you need one, tell me.
I can send them to you
or I can tell them to send them.
Well, I've got three I'd like to return.
At the local college library
might want one copy
because they publish local...
They...
You know, what you call local authors.
And you go there and you sign them
and stuff like that.
Yeah.
You should do that.
And there's some other crap like that.
The really lonely authors,
they go into bookstores
where they haven't been asked to sign them
and they go ahead and sign them.
I know this because I've done that
and I picked up a screenplay book
by Joe Esterhaus in Cleveland
and where he lives
and I got it home and it was signed.
I realized he did the same thing I did.
He found his book in the bookstore
and went,
I'm just going to go ahead
and sign this
and see if anybody believes it.
I got a letter from somebody going,
I was in a Barnes & Noble in Dallas
and I picked up Revelation X
and it said it was
Reverend Ivan Stang was here
and it had the date.
Could that be real?
I went, yes, that is definitely real.
That's how I signed them
and I did do that
in that Barnes & Noble
just because.
That's the noble.
Just because.
It's like, why didn't they ask me
to come in here and sign them?
God damn it, I'm going to sign them anyway.
Phooey.
Don't they know who I am?
I'm Reverend Ivan Stang,
author of this one,
of the only one copy
in the humor section.
Oh, well, I'll sign that.
Darn them.
I haven't seen one
in a bookstore in years.
But I haven't been
Do you smell the brownies yet?
What if you would have signed
a Bible of something new?
I smell the fairies
and the trolls.
Trolls, run!
I don't smell the brownies.
You don't smell the brownies?
No.
Boy, Dave, you smell the brownies?
I smell the Girl Scouts.
I'm afraid I'm different
than the rest of you fellows
because I can definitely
smell the brownies.
I smell the Girl Scouts
if I don't smell the brownies.
Well, I sniff the Girl Scouts,
but I definitely smell brownies.
I'm talking about chocolate,
gooey, delicious,
cannabis-laden brownies.
No, these are not,
that's not what we're talking about.
No, these are covered with ice cream.
Yeah, these are going to be,
these are just regular brownies.
You know,
when I hear on the show,
we like to pretend,
that we're on all high all the time
and on these drugs.
But really,
when you hear me sniffle,
it's because I have the sniffles.
It's not because I'm snorting anything.
Well, what about the eugenics part?
Do we have to sign that waiver
and release it for everyone?
Yeah, yeah,
because that's what we have to say legally.
You know, you have to sign
the wafer release
before you can take a wafer.
Before anybody will give you
a real wafer.
That's a good comedian.
First, you sign the thing
that says,
no, we didn't take,
anything.
Then they give you the stuff
so you can take it.
But first,
you have to say you didn't.
That's show business.
It's just FCC rules.
It's good legal jargonese, too,
because if you drive by
a licensed used car
or vehicle or automobile
or perhaps a gun of some kind,
then they'd have to throw you
out of the station
and put your pants down
right away.
I think the subgenius girls
ate all the brownies.
Really?
No, the subgenius girls left.
They went over to the house
of Anti-C, the rub genius.
That's my sister.
Really, look in the subgenius.
She's got a whole quote paragraph there.
Did they go there?
Her quote was,
someday I will be a large scar.
And that was a good prophecy
because that pretty much came true.
Folks.
Yeah.
My little sister is...
No, I hear noises in there.
Indeed.
I hear noises in there
indicating the staff is still with us.
Yeah, I was hoping they were here
instead of there.
Yeah.
No, nobody is...
Oh, that's right.
They had to come back
to take the brownies out of the oven.
That's the one,
just so the guys wouldn't have to...
Are they going to leave?
Okay, you guys keep talking.
I'm going to go check the brownies.
Okay, yeah.
Okay, see if the Cub Scouts
are out of the broiler, too, would you?
So I thought my idea was
that Doug Smith could play Bob Nelson
and see him be like the old show.
Yeah, that's right.
We'll pot him down
every time we want to say
something really funny.
And the best part is,
I never reminded him to play a CD,
so the editing is a lot easier,
but just voices
instead of having music
in the middle of all of it
and copyright problems
and lawyer fees and this way...
You think you can get him
to talk about that milking incident?
Probably not.
Yeah.
Because I think the family
was greatly embarrassed by it
for 130 years here in Smith County.
Well, you know,
the problem is now
that they have regular milking machines
and women are demanding
the right to be able to go
and pump,
as they call it.
Yeah.
And also,
you were talking to some other
owner of a plank
here in the county, right?
By the city hall there
the other day.
Of an appliance?
Yeah.
Isn't there a guy looking for bricks
with his family's name on it?
Oh, right.
That fellow.
Everybody goes downtown
and looks for bricks
with their family's name on it.
Yeah, you gotta look
Yeah, but none of those people
really live there anymore.
Well, some of them have come back.
And some of them
have their little plaque
that's gone.
Somebody actually stole
somebody else.
way to go with that problem.
The memory of someone.
Somebody else, yeah.
And I thought,
I'm nicer,
so I just assumed
the screws came loose
in the family
and the thing was gone.
The screws came loose
in a lot of families,
but they didn't
lose their plaque.
Yeah, once a family
loses their plaque
and they're standing downtown,
it's pretty much over.
See, there was probably
eight people from his family
there by the time
the sun went down.
Wow.
That's worth it.
Yeah.
Oh, now you lost me.
I thought,
I thought you were still
talking about the old
shoulder bags
that Stan was supposed to wear.
Yeah.
I don't know if he does
anymore.
Well, what happened,
you had people walking
down the street
by the old public square.
Right.
Yeah, a couple fire marshals
there and some
scene sailors.
And the metal statues
that came to life.
Right, right, right.
The talkie-talkies
you call them, right?
The metal statues.
Yeah.
Yeah, and they start
striding down the street
trying to tell you
about old history.
And, you know,
Hippas has its feed bag on.
Yeah, it was
a pretty normal day.
Yeah, well,
what about the sea bag?
That's what got
my conflating going.
I didn't understand.
Cowboy Dave,
have you ever been here
to the staying ranch?
No.
Well, come on down
right now.
Okay, you can,
we can pretend and stuff
or do I have to really
try and figure out
how to use this thing?
Well, if you think
there shouldn't be
brownies left
when you get in.
But now,
be careful, you guys.
We are having a party
next week,
but it's only for Texans.
Texas subgeniuses.
Man.
We really are.
We really are having
a party next week
and that's all
we've invited.
So, Ohioans,
forget it.
And we got to be
Well, they'd have to be
in Texas to come
to the party.
Well, that makes sense
if the party's in Texas.
Yeah, and
Actually, they can't even be,
they can't be from Dallas,
though.
They can be from
anywhere else.
You're from Dallas.
Huh?
Yeah, like the
Jack Ruby homunculus.
Well, no,
I'm not really from Dallas.
No, you're not really
from Texas.
No.
No, but I did grow up here.
That would be a bummer.
But I grew up in Fort Worth.
Oh.
That's better.
Yeah.
Why?
Because it's not Dallas.
Oh.
That's the only reason.
That was easy.
That's absolutely it.
So, did you know it
as a cow town?
Is it real, like,
steers still going through town?
No.
Is that gone?
When I was a little boy,
it still smelled like cow.
Cow.
Yeah.
Cow, cow.
Because I told my dad,
I went to
It smelled a little bit
like Gilroy.
When we did couch talk,
I told my dad,
yeah, I'm going to Fort Worth.
And there's this long,
silent,
because he'd seen it
only as a cow town
in the 1940s or something.
He'd thought,
why are you going there?
They ate all the cows.
Exactly.
The cows were all
eating them.
We or mailed them.
So, is the show over now
or what?
Yeah.
It's been over
for the last hour.
Yeah.
This is the good part.
The part where
you were reading
or we left you here,
that was the
that's all we needed.
Were you eating
or reading?
Both.
Oh, at the same time?
I was reading the brownies
and eating a book.
Yeah.
We started this show
by,
turning on all the machines
and then running away
and leaving Gary here
by himself.
And Gary's not very funny.
Oh,
from what I heard
from upstairs,
it was pretty,
pretty lame.
You were basically
going on and on
about how not funny
you were
and how awful
it was to sit there.
Yeah?
Yeah.
But,
I said,
okay,
I'm not going to cut the show.
This is not going to be
one of those edited things.
I'm going to start it
at zero o'clock
and at exactly
one hour
I'm going to shut it off.
Oh my God,
what time is it?
It's an hour.
It's been,
like,
it's 11 minutes.
It's an hour and eight minutes.
So,
actually,
it's been over
for eight minutes.
I've been taping longer.
In my world,
So,
it's an hour and 12 minutes
of my life is wasted.
Yeah.
And also,
don't you think
you should get
Eohippus here?
Eohippus?
Yeah,
there's an Eohippus
running around.
Well,
and Princess Wee,
actually,
and for that matter,
we love her.
Eohippus.
Princess?
Wee-mongus.
Cremongulous.
Here,
I can,
why don't I get up?
Okay.
Here.
No,
no,
you guys just sit.
No,
no,
you get there.
Wait,
wait,
you sit here.
I'll sit right on your lap.
It's just you and me
and,
uh.
But isn't the show over?
No,
no.
We're allowed to be on the show
now that it's over?
Yeah,
exactly.
Now that the show is over.
Well,
actually,
it was over an hour ago.
Okay,
so now it's okay for us
to be on it.
Yeah,
the queen,
and you should be on the show now.
So how does it feel
to be an Eohippus
and be on the radio
right now?
It feels just lovely,
like floating,
and having suddenly
a big,
a big
team of people
paper mache you,
and then you have this outside
that's all kind of,
whoa,
you know,
like paper mache
and you're floating.
That's how it feels.
Then they make a,
they make a pinata out of you
shortly afterwards.
Oh my goodness.
Lonesome Cowboy Dave
in your ears.
Oh really?
Um,
you don't have a bat,
do you?
No,
but I've been associated
with a number of people
who thought they were bats.
Really?
Yeah.
I don't know what that means,
but I think that sounds
very affirmative.
But why an Eohippus?
Why not any other kind
of extinct animal?
Why not Miss Lovely Lips
Mac and Jane Janet
the Hippocratic Oaks?
Use those headphones
and dance.
I'll,
I'll take this microphone.
I'll take the hippocampus oath.
I take the hippocampus oath,
which includes the hippocampus
and also the pituitary gland
and the infundibulum
and I,
I take that oath
to the hippocampus.
And it will give you
the cramps of the eye wigs
if you do not use properly.
Repeat after me.
I will not use improperly.
Yes.
You all can go in now.
Where are we going?
I was just,
I was just going to ask you guys
where you want to go
and neither one of you
had any ideas.
No.
Let's take that flying saucer,
that red flying saucer
with the yellow brim.
Oh, that's a good idea.
Okay.
I'll go with you.
Are you,
are you okay on that?
Yeah.
Am I okay?
I suppose I'm okay,
but I was kind of looking forward
to filling mignon
and potato salad on the side.
Do they serve that on the saucer?
If you so desire.
I thought that was part of the pitch
in the grown ham.
Yeah, you can get anything you want.
Anything.
Well, let's go up there.
It's only up a little ways.
You know,
we can scale the side
of this little wooden pegged surface
and we can get up
to the flying saucer.
Yeah.
That's ridiculous.
You can't do that.
That's totally
I'm doing it right now.
That's totally ridiculous.
That's totally cool.
Man.
Be careful, you guys.
If one of you slips,
that's a pretty long climb.
Oh, reaching.
Oh, man.
I never was good.
I never went to the climbing gym
like I should have.
I can't believe you're doing this.
Me either.
Man, my muscles are so weak.
I thought they were much stronger.
I put the climbing weight
over here, Janet,
and it looks like
they'll know.
Well, how's that?
Okay.
How's that saucer looking?
Oh, it's just there
a little bit farther
and we've made it.
Oh.
Well, you made it,
actually.
What condition is it in?
Do you think you can
get it started?
Do you know how to open
this thing?
Does it wind up
or how does it crank?
Is there a crank?
We have to find
a big, long strand of plastic
that's pushing this opening here
and then we pull it out
the other end
and then it'll go.
Where's the button
you push to make it open?
Oh, I see it pulls.
There's gears in there.
There's gears in there
that get triggered
by a strip of plastic
getting pulled through.
It's a magic plastic strip.
Do you have one?
No, I don't have one.
I heard somewhere
that you can get those
from the Church of the Subgenius
for only $35
from Post Office Box 807
Glen Rose, Texas
76043.
So get your magic plastic strip today.
And take off
in Flying Saucers
from Stang Ranch.
I just did that holding
an ear...
What do you call these little earbuds?
Earbud.
Against my hearing aid.
Oh, wow.
So the ear,
you can't put the earbud...
Hey, you guys took the headphones.
Puzzling left his earbuds.
Well, I've got hearing aids.
I can't get the earbud
into my ear
because there's a damn hearing aid.
The earbud's connected to the ear.
You hold a tiny bud
up against the hearing aid mic.
This is the first time
I've ever encountered this.
But it's the only way to hear Dave.
Without the hearing aids
and the earbud.
I can't hear that.
I find that very interesting concept
and I think if there was a way
I could capitalize on that,
make some money,
I'd gladly do it.
I'd do it in a heartbeat,
but since I have no heart
and no beat, no bone,
and in fact,
a form of sinewy meat
is all I own.
All,
all,
all I got
is a lot.
Never mind.
Do you have a patent attorney?
No, but I do have
a residual railroad
retirement program.
I'm on the plan
for five years now.
Wow.
I had no idea.
He's on the five-year plan.
Yes, comrade.
This is five-year plan.
We expect to get through
one year and that's it.
Well, that's a good,
pretty realistic plan there,
Comrade.
I can be prospectus
as far as I can see
and you know I'm half blind
to begin with.
Oh, good.
I'm half deaf.
We could be a super
half-villain together.
A half-villain?
Yeah.
Yeah, we can't be a super
half-hero.
Hemigod.
Yeah.
What's my name?
They're pansies anyway.
And Hemigod.
A Hemigod and a Demigod
versus one
versus two.
Together?
I'm going to be a right
Hemigod or a left Hemigod.
The right Hemigod.
I'm not listening.
That's not what I'm laughing at.
Well, that brought on
the surprising results
that I had never
predicted before.
Really?
What?
No.
Yeah, really.
Of course.
I'm not lying.
He wasn't expecting mirth.
I guess not.
You should always expect mirth.
I missed a bunch of that
but I
at one point
something about superheroes
and supervillains.
You know,
Philo started a new Facebook page
called
Bad Superhero
and Supervillain Names.
Oh.
And it's a brand new Facebook page.
It's like two weeks old
and so far it's mostly just
Philo and John Shirley
and some people whose names
I never heard.
But you and me contributed one.
It was like Repairman
was the bad superhero.
Oh, the loser
was the bad supervillain.
He was good at losing things.
The Repairman,
I think it was frankly
based on you and me.
I won't say which was which.
But another one I found here
that was
meaner than Dracula
but nicer than Trump man.
That's a villain.
A bad supervillain name.
Meaner than Dracula
but nicer than Trump man.
And then there's one
that Gary invented tonight
at the restaurant
very loudly.
Face fucking Batman.
And I'll leave it at that.
The,
the,
the broadcast radio audience
will have to guess
Holy complexion.
the first parts of the,
what led up to the Batman part.
But it's a type of Batman.
Holy antidote pudding.
FFB man,
you might call it.
Yeah,
holy antidote pudding Batman.
FFB man.
What's up that in the air?
Oh God.
Close your mouth.
Close your eyes.
Help my face.
Batman.
Holy.
Yeah.
Holy antidote pudding Batman.
Okay.
And on that note,
I think we can bring
a thankful close
to this hour of slack.
Number 1,670.
Three or two or one.
That's it.
Dave, are you okay?
I'm,
I'm going to sleep now.
That's the wise thing to do.
Sleep well, Dave.
Good night.
According to this week,
we ended the show
an hour and 18 minutes ago.
Sleep well, Dave.
Dave Sleepwell
has been our guest.
Thank you.
Dave Sleepwell indeed.
With Sleepwell tablets,
you'll be asleep
in no time at all.
Many Dave hearts
lie asleep in the deep.
Stop the rest of it.
Why are you being mad?
My grandfather wrote a novel
called Many Dave Hearts.
Oh, look, he's gone.
He went under.
He'll be back next week.
Don't worry.
I'm sorry that song ended up.
That was really going places.
Which song?
Earbuds connected to the
hearing aid.
Oh, God.
Hearing aids connected to the
Sick.
That's not funny.
How about Superman?
Superman.
Yeah.
Face meets versus
face fucking Batman.
Or super woman.
Well, there was a super woman.
They just haven't gotten around
to making that movie yet.
Superman.
Wake up, Superman.
Wake up.
Get us to fly.
Superman.
Where is Superman
when we need it?
Superman.
In the gutter.
Flat on his face.
Again.
Well, he's like
Filbert Desinex, you know?
Desinex?
Filbert Desinex.
I don't know about Desinex.
He's the alter ego
of Wonder Warthog.
Desinex?
He's a total miserable
failure at everything.
Oh, right.
Yeah, the narc.
Filbert Desinex.
Yeah, he was a cop.
He was like a DEA agent.
No, no.
That was the other.
No, there was.
Oh, there is the.
Yeah, Filbert Desinex
was like a cop.
Oh, was he the guy
who was trying to.
No, no.
There's the other guy
with the Dick Tracy chin.
Right.
Well, he was always
trying to bust
the Free Freak Brothers.
No, that was
Norbert the narc.
Oh, God, man.
I'm so out of it.
That was funny.
Please don't tell Gilbert.
Don't tell Gilbert, please.
Don't tell Paul either.
That was the.
You'll know I didn't study
my rip-off press
underground comic books.
I remembered it.
J.R.R.
I remember it.
Price Bob.
Are you sitting comfortably?
Then we'll begin.
Another day.
Another man.
The white hot heat
of a woman possessed.
Possessed of an uncontrollable
and natural passion.
So all consuming
is to make the flames of hell
mere glowing embers.
The insatiable depraved hunger
of a woman shorn
of her mask of fidelity
and respectability
and buried for what she really is.
A crazed female animal
on the prowl.
A dehumanized creature
grasping and clawing
for instant gratification
from any source.
Now you got to go out there
and you got to get the best ones
you can find.
And you gotta work them broads
like nobody's ever worked them before.
And never forget.
Anybody can control a woman's body.
See?
But the key is to control the mind.
Here I am.
I'm working my ass off
and he's spending my money
on some trashy white bitch.
You better be quiet
otherwise you go out.
There's a big difference
in having a baby
and us getting married.
I don't see why.
Because we're still brother and sister
and that's a fact.
You done it
and I know you did.
No.
It wasn't my secret, you hear?
And just what have you done
to deserve what you're calling love?
The girl stalked by men
fights like a wildcat.
Oh, I'm so horny.
Gotta teach her how to love.
Teach that chick a lesson.
Gonna give her a real scare.
That bad broad is never gonna mix up
a top stud again.
Why are you afraid of me, huh?
Tell me.
I mean, why are you so scared of me?
We're not gonna hurt you too much.
Just maybe a little at first
and then you'll see how good it is
being one of my girls.
Being one of my girls is good.
Gets you special favors
and keeps others away.
Yes, I got it.
Yes sir!
Yes sir, yes sir!
Yes huh!
Hahaha!
Yes sir!
Woo!
Yah!
Hehe!
I'm grateful, I'm grateful.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, haha!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Woo!
I began having vivid, detailed memories
of being used as a sex slave.
The truth is, that there are slave auctions
that very elite people attend.
to be able to own and buy the best mind control slaves that money can buy.
Jumping young teeny boppers get with it to the savage feet of the big blast.
A red hot mob of rambunctious tiger kittens on the prowl.
They are the fire that blows up your blood to the boiling point.
Masturbation has also been documented as a useful practice in the treatment of sexual dysfunctions.
If the woman has gonorrhea or syphilis, as she probably has, you must now do these things as quickly as possible.
First, urinate. Pass your water.
Second, wash your hands, your penis, and the surrounding skin and hair thoroughly with soap and water.
Third, get to the nearest prophylactic station for a treatment.
Hey, hey, now. Careful down there, ma'am.
If you bite it, you and I is going to have a set to it.
And if you don't, we ain't gonna have enough corn left for shocking.
Papel para mi culo.
Que necio.
Just think of pleasing him more and more and more.
Father, I feel scared and a bit funny.
Thank you, chief. Thank you, chief. Tell him I know I wasn't worth it.
Holy high five.
But...
Hip, hip, high-five!
Watch out forもし do you.
Hey, hey.
Sh unlikeuto, hey actually.
See, now ya got me.
You're fucking meaning it.
We'll be right back.
And that was Reverend Jimmy Ryan.
From PR News in Washington, I'm E. Noon.
Hi.
So, what do you do?
I do not.
Well, you're lucky.
Yes.
Yes!
Wow.
So, ready to play?
Yep.
Here is your first Twitter phrase.
I get wet.
I can't get.
Yes.
No, wait a minute.
Oh, right!
Here, Leah, is your next Twitter phrase.
I can now use my power.
You say that with such sadness.
All right, here is your last Twitter phrase.
A baby dog.
Yes.
Baby?
Your little idiotic baby dog is embarrassing.
Intelligent baby dogs tested scientists, and it turns out they are more likely to interact with idiotic baby intelligent dogs from the University of York.
Congratulations!
Thanks.
Now it's time for our final answer.
Bill, can you give us the score?
Three, four.
Go.
Right, go.
Fill in the blank.
Blank.
Right.
Blanked on Tuesday.
Good.
This week's a New York blank.
Another powerful blank.
I can now use my power.
Yeah.
On Sunday.
Blank.
Yes.
This week the big blank.
And this is true.
On Thursday.
Blank.
Uh, right on Tuesday.
Right.
After a contentious blank.
After passing a giant blank.
After blank.
Right.
This week a blank.
That's exactly blank.
Exactly.
And how do we know about blank?
Well, you're not gonna believe blank.
Right.
On Monday it was reported that blanks.
On Monday a government blanked.
Right.
According to new research blank.
Yes.
This week blank.
This week English blank.
Yes!
That's exactly right.
Bachelor scandal.
But first let me tell you that's a PR.
It comes from PR stations and dot dot com and Doug dot org.
Blank.
We must
High ground.
Cl unchained.
Welp.
Right.
Your derive
Tool.
道也者可须于礼也,可离非道也。
恃故君子戒这乌其所不足,恐惧乌其所不闻。
莫羡乌云,莫羡乌尾,祝君子善行行也。
喜怒哀乐之未发,未知终,发而皆终结,未知何。
终也者天下之大人也,何也者天下之大道也。
至终何天地未定,万物未天。
须须悲哀乐之未发,未知何。
恃故君子戒这乌其所不足,恐惧乌其所不闻。
恃故君子戒这乌其所不闻。
须须悲哀乐之未发,未知何。
恃故君子戒这乌其所不足,恐惧乌其所不足。
yba
Until now Lผม
Thank you.
And that was the Psychoskeletons.
And you can find more Psychoskeletons by googling Psychoskeletons.
The Psychoskeletons.
And now this.
My bathroom.
Oh, get me another woolly.
Because I don't want another woolly.
My bathroom.