Psychedelic music performed at the total environment dance.
Light shows and strobes in the crowd and an ear-spring kind of music.
The effect is to simulate an hallucinogenic experience.
In fact, they've conducted some experiments that show in a right acoustic environment
with a proper synchronization of the strobes and the beaten sound of the music,
they can induce within the mind a mental condition paralleling that of LSD.
It's sort of a way to blow your mind on uses.
On Bob.
Yes, dear friend.
Welcome to another hour of swag.
The big question everyone here is asking is of course what happens then.
Some believe that the ring's function is some sort of an accelerator or something,
sending its energy into this passenger pod, making it rocket away at near the speed of light.
Rocket away.
Other people believe it might open up a doorway to some other dimension.
To a doorway to...
Right.
Well, that's what today's test is all about.
Actually, I quite like it up here.
My little room has one hell of a view.
Yes, no kidding, dear friends.
As I look around myself in my little room here, I see, uh...
Well, I see...
Look, there's a Dobbs head.
And look over there.
Another Dobbs head.
Why, fancy that.
There are just Dobbs heads all over the place.
Here and there and every...everywhere.
Here, there and everywhere, friends.
And, uh, welcome to another show with a format.
Some kind of a format.
Let's see what it is.
You haven't seen your mission.
Well, no, I mean, I think, to me, I'm old-fashioned.
I feel like, you know, these...these nude orgies where everybody's clustered together
right in the center of the wagon trains, uh, trying to, um...
I don't know.
I think it's a private thing that you...you should look across the woods and see them
dotted with couples rather than all the couples all at once.
And I wish there were more women.
I...needless to say, I mean, look around, uh...
Oh, this is great.
You're...you're filming him recording me taking a picture of you.
Oh, come on.
Yes, for the hour of slack.
I like that.
This is for...
And Boston television.
This is for the hour of slack.
Boston's hour of life, also.
In Dallas, Little Rock, Boston, Chicago.
Oh, my God.
I'm here to tell you, brothers and sisters, that yes, women...women can be subgeniuses.
It's a difficult...it's a difficult road to travel.
It's a hard, long road.
It's so hard.
It's such a hard and a deep trail.
It's harder...it's harder than the time that the nuns have in the Catholic church becoming
priests.
And it's harder than the time that the Hindu women have becoming Hindu priests, becoming
a nun.
It's so hard.
I'm a woman subgenius.
I'm an extraordinary woman.
A subhuman woman.
Who?
A superhuman woman.
A woman who can't take it...
Come on, man.
Whoa.
No.
Wow, that's...
Yes.
Dear friends, it's a tripped out wild and wacky thing.
Well, no, actually it's not.
But let's get on to our homey Prairie Squid home contraption interview types.
No, what is it? News! That's right, the news!
Oh, and wait until you hear this news.
From the Boston Globe, Friday.
April 30th, 1999.
Subgenius comment sinks show.
The Church of the Subgenius won't be meeting tonight.
It's not because the Music and Performance Collaborative doesn't have religion about making a Boston appearance.
Rather, it's feeling the impact of a stupid joke.
One of the members of the National Subgenius Foundation made a crack
during an appearance on National Public Radio about being aligned with the Trenchcoat Mafia,
the group associated with the Colorado school shootings.
The church felt immediate fallout.
The reference included a pitch for tonight's scheduled show at the Middle East in Cambridge,
and about a dozen people called the club to protest, obviously not getting the joke.
One of the owners of the Middle East canceled the show,
but couldn't be wrong.
There is a 30 minute chat meeting going on right now,
which has recently reached 4,000 viewers.
Nevertheless, that's okay.
We're just a few minutes away.
I'll gather the cleanup from this Friday and plan for a some other rounds of appearances
or someethin' else with the
essential elements of national media.
Some places should be issued media coverage,
popularity and more.
But at this moment,
some ideas seem to.....
you wouldn't believe.
have done what they did, Jones said.
And yes, friends, the funny thing is,
after we were canceled at the Middle East,
the ACLU helped us get booked by the Baptists.
Yes, the subgeniuses were driven out of the Middle East by hate,
but yet were saved by the Baptists,
who then canceled the show themselves
because of creepy phone calls
from higher up in the Cambridge City Council.
And it turned into quite an interesting story, friends.
We did hold our revival on the steps
of the old Cambridge Baptist Church,
with their permission,
and under the floodlights and spotlights of the police cars.
And we got some great recordings,
surreptitious and deliberate and legal,
and both kinds.
And we're...
Next week's show will be
the Boston non-devival special
called, I guess we'll call it,
Them Asses Have Spoken.
The masses didn't speak much,
but the masses show did.
And them asses have spoken,
and so did we.
But in the meantime,
okay, enough of that.
Let's go to department number two,
the old-timey media barrage,
to be followed by whatever new Bob song there is on there.
I...
Oh, hmm.
Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
Uh, jams in the background.
Oh, yes.
Ta-da!
what have you done toмерик Также Southwark
our freedom indicates no introduce of a ketosis...
Get be gel, Mr. Newells!
Be começo Ang Radio!
Hy, aaaack!
Aaaäte je.
I'll give you slack.
Experiment with some toys.
Sluts use things like anal beads, butt plugs, condoms, enema bags, and handcuffs.
And goddesses use things like crystals, cucumbers, drums and rattles, feathers, grapes, herbs and oils.
And never knock something until you've tried it yourself.
Oh, Lord.
Oh, how could you?
I think I'm going to be sick.
For constant, steady, and tireless stimulation, we highly recommend the use of vibrators.
There are many models to choose from, enough to keep your hands full.
Here, Connie, you can use this.
Thanks.
We call her the girl with the magic box.
She also has a magic figure.
When she chooses the models for her magazine assignment,
you know they'll all be...
You know they'll all be winners.
The search is on, and you're there to watch as she sees every agent and artist modeled
for this treasure hunt for the girls with the best and the mostest.
Never before has anyone looked so hard to assemble in one group
such an eye-filling, breath-snatching array of female pulchritude.
Oh, my God.
It's the Miss XX Day.
Why, this girl was so eager to get the best that she was willing even to trade herself if necessary.
This you'll have to see.
In high society, I just ain't the type.
Folks all look so surprised when I light my pipe.
We're getting a pipe and smoke it, whore.
The girls fight back, and how?
You can't miss it.
It's totally pretty.
No.
My God.
Coming out.
Help!
All women are bad.
And here's the picture that proves it.
Any place that has people has women.
Vicious, gruff, scheming, and ivy.
Every place in the world, only in the wilderness alone
can man truly be free of their evil ways.
This is the picture that shows them as they really are.
Stripped bare of all pretensions.
And everything else too.
Though I don't say men are angels,
especially when there's a woman concerned.
The so-called fair sex is the only thing
that leads them on and into every sort of perversion
imaginable.
And this picture proves it.
There's nothing too foul for a pretty girl
to get mixed up in.
Whether it's down in hippy land,
or up in an old Ruiz flat.
She's got him by the short hair.
But he usually doesn't even know it.
He may think he's just being appreciative, or mildly shy.
But once a girl gets her claws into him,
there's nothing she can't make a man do.
It may start out perfectly innocently like this.
Maybe she just wants him to come up to our apartment
to pose for a painting.
But it can end up pretty wild.
Yes sir, all women are bad.
Their passions, their lusts, their evil bodies
turn the strongest man into jelly.
And if you're not so strong, watch out.
They only love themselves and sometimes each other.
But as for men, that's only at their own convenience.
Here's your chance to see all the bad women in one film.
Girls who have no morals and no scruples.
Girls who don't care what they do.
Or who they do it with, as long as they do it.
Girls who hate men,
and love each other.
Gossips and flirts.
Teases and sadists.
Prostitutes and girls who want to be in show business.
And they don't care how much they have to show.
Wicked and lustful, sensuous girls
blossoming into rife womanhood.
All women are bad.
I ought to know.
I'm a man.
But don't take my word for it.
See them as they really are.
The fair sex unmasked.
In the exciting new film, all women are bad.
Especially the girls of the church of the subgenius, dear friends.
Oh, here they come.
Actually friends, that's, I did not know that that little piece of music was, or that, that,
that collage was going to be like it was.
How incredibly synchronistic in certain respects.
Sister Susie the floozy, who happens to be, although she did that collage for her Connie's
Evil Plan show on WREK in Atlanta, Georgia.
She also has since then got a job writing a book.
I think it's the big book of bad.
Bad girls.
In that big book series.
But at any rate, it is about the bad girls.
They're not all bad though.
Well I guess the girls of the subgenius church.
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess they're all bad.
Well I guess the girls are good too.
Dude this is amazing.
Dead, hard, all over again.
Dressed up like sheep, sleeping gadgets up under a coat
Stuff you hear about but nobody knows, it ain't no use
Oh, women are bad
That's what I said
Oh, they got goofy women's tails
They got horns on their heads
Oh, women are bad
That's easy. First word, first name comes to my mind. Connie.
She's got the love
And you cannot resist the way
She makes her play
And you would pawn your wedding ring
For one more thing
She's everywhere
She's in your hair
She's on your mind
And you will find
When work is done
Then you will run
To be the first
To pledge your first
On the backside of Dallas
In a dingy bar
On a worn-out stool
She sits
And her trembling hand fumbles
For another king-size
Spilled her cigarettes
She blows a puff of smoke
Then settles back
And looks across the light blue haze
And from the backside of Dallas
Her mind goes drifting back to other days
Meet me in Dallas
On June the 23rd
His letter read
On a greyhound of this big town
She can't see me
I came to be with him
Just like he said
Then suddenly he left her
For reasons that she still don't understand
And on the backside of Dallas
A girl must earn her way
As best she can
That's it.
It's a long way to Dallas
For a small-town girl
From the middle of Tennessee
And a tenth-grade education
Won't get you no kind of job
Here in Big D
Hunger, pains, and pride
The thing that just don't go
Hand in hand for long
And on the backside of Dallas
A hungry small-town girl
Can find a home
On the backside of Dallas
Nervously she takes another pill
And on the backside of Dallas
On the backside of Dallas
Tonight like other nights
She drinks her fill
She pays the man behind the bar
And leaves the change
For a twenty-dollar bill
If you're ever feeling lonesome
And you want to find someone
Who feels the same
She's on the backside of Dallas
Where every day she's alone
And every taxi driver knows her name
She's on the backside of Dallas
Where every taxi driver knows her name
It's very exciting to combine
Prayer, ritual, and magic
In with your sexual practices
Evoke some spirits before you make love
That's where you come in, Connie
I'm the kind of woman
Not hard to understand
I'm the one who cracks the whip
And holds the upper hand
I'll beat you, mistreat you
Till you quiver and quail
The male of the species
Is more deadly than the man
When you mess with me
Or flirt around with the flame
When you find that you've been burned
You've only yourself to blame
I'll hurt you, desert you
If you ever should fail
The female of the species
Is more deadly than the man
This week's Hour of Slack
is brought to you by me
The irreverent Friday Jones
Can't escape me now
Whatever appears on the television screen
Emerges as raw experience for those who watch it
And the television screen
Is connected up at the mind's eye
principal
and cosmic
and look at what your TV channel
If you've ever watched
Baling
Llama
I say unto you.
Well, the Amazon sisters are playing the gospel jazz back there.
Second generation.
Yeah.
And you notice that in a mirror with a mere 15 minutes of training on the saxophone,
I sound better than any of the males in any of the doctor bands.
Yes, sir.
Well, but that's sort of like saying you can shot put better than anyone at the Special Olympics.
Thank you.
Well, I hope you're not picking up transmissions from last Tuesday.
Man.
No, I haven't played that tape yet tonight.
I don't think I will.
I haven't either.
I was putting together a show.
I'm doing two shows at once right this second.
Three shows.
Three shows at one time.
But your show sounds a lot better.
The live show.
Yeah.
The eardrum of the mind's ear.
Well, where is everybody?
Did Dave stay home?
Well, they should be.
Yeah, Dave stayed home.
Or did he have to stop and pick up all the girls?
He picked up the girls and he probably went back home.
Yeah.
That's probably why.
But, God, how can he handle that many of them?
I don't know.
Yeah.
Why do they call him lonesome anyway?
I don't know.
I think where he lives, Ashtabula, is kind of like, you know, the old version of Venus.
You know, how people thought Venus used to be.
Rainy.
Rainy and swampy and filled with women.
Yeah.
And that's where Dave lives.
A rainy, swampy, filled with swamp women kind of place.
Speaking of swamp women and space women,
I've got a list somewhere here of all the movies I could think of that featured space queens.
And I had expert advice.
Susie the floozy and Sister Decadence are both camp, kitschy movie experts were advising me.
Damn it, now I can't find the list.
But I know that Abbott and Costello go to Mars.
Yeah.
Has the ultimate scenes of Venus.
Wow.
Wouldn't it just figure a movie titled with Mars in it, they go to Venus.
But they do.
They do.
And Venus is populated by.
Beautiful women.
Of course.
Who speculate about whether they want to make it with Lou Costello.
And that they eventually decide not to since they don't need men.
Which is kind of a wise move.
Yeah.
They probably had that choice at one point here on Earth and they blew it, so to speak.
We've been playing Einstein's Secret Orchestra.
I want to run through the list there of that.
That's Michelle George on violin, electric violin.
There you hear that.
That Hendrix-y kind of stuff there.
She is the Hendrix of the electric violin.
And then there's a lonesome cowboy Dave on guitars.
And myself on keyboards.
And John Peck.
And he's Chaz Smith.
Cantor Chaz Smith.
And also on this tape, I think you hear Ron Slade with Einstein's Secret Orchestra in the background.
Let's just listen for a minute shall we?
Heh heh.
.
Accept the fact that you're probably stupid.
But don't feel bad about it friend.
Almost everyone else is too.
In fact, the studies have shown that 95% of the population consistently behaves in a manner
that can be described.
as stupid. Of the remaining 5%, 2% are in hiding, 2% are incarcerated in mental institutions,
and the final 1% is actively engaged in stealing everyone else blind. Some people have said that
the educational system is not really to blame for this state of affairs. These people are idiots.
Of course the educational system is to blame, and we're not talking about widely publicized
instances of graduates who can't read their own diplomas. Even the smug valedictorians and
highly touted PhDs often never develop the ability to really think for themselves.
The educational system, from Head Start to Harvard, is designed to provide nothing more
than advanced vocational training. Hell, it takes 12 years just to learn how to play whatever
cog-like role the student winds up in in this bewilderingly complex industrial economy.
The students who show more aptitude end up as bigger cogs, but damn few of them show any sort
of creative cognition. Those who do have, have developed this on their own, sometimes by accident,
sometimes through sheer defiance of a system that promotes unthinking passive conformity.
Well, good for them. Unfortunately, many more never even conceive of such a notion,
and the educational system is not to blame.
The educational system can't be held entirely responsible. It only holds its victims for
a limited time before they're released to produce and consume. From that point on, the
mass media entirely takes over the job of intelligent suppression, as does this show.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Actually, that was from Stamp Out Slavery
by...
There he is! There he is, did it! With Reverend Crawford Smith. Ah, yes, here it is.
Here it is.
Everything that Bob is is something else.
Even if he goes insane, he's gonna step right in and steal your brain.
He will tell the exes what to do.
He will tell them lies that are also true.
Come July 1998, the stockpiste of removal will see your face.
Will you have the slack to see you through?
Oh, Bob will cook you cookies.
Bob will stew you stew.
Bob's a groovy, a real gone daddy, and a red-hot mama, too.
He sells anything that can be sold.
He can turn old chalk straps into gold.
If you send him lots of bucks, he will spend them wild.
I like to be like Bob, for I grow old.
Cause everything that Bob is is something else.
And everything that Bob is is something else.
Even if he goes insane, he's gonna step right in and steal your brain.
Everything that Bob is is something else.
See, I didn't write that song. The Ruggles smacked that song.
Yeah, Bob, glad to have you.
Oh dear friends, and that was Ahmed Fishmonger.
That takes care of our old Bob song department.
Ahmed, Dr. Ahmed Fishmonger.
Everything that Bob is is something else.
Did you guys actually go into the Vortex to do your recording?
There's a Vortex lab?
The Vortex videos?
No, no we don't.
We wouldn't have to go into a Vortex to record.
This is good.
We don't play it to you?
What's noise to some people is music to others.
The unpleasant noise you are about to hear coming from your radio is not a mistake.
Please do not turn off your radio, but turn up the volume on your receiver as high as it can go
so that you can make the sound we broadcast as loud as possible.
This is Bill T. Miller, orgy of noise.
Plague of MP3s. Cut one.
EXO Radio is on the air.
Load up those FROB rockets.
Light the fuse.
We'll be taking off in just a moment.
My name is Chaz, and I'll be your pilot.
Wanna go for a ride?
Yeah.
That's it.
Uh huh.
Everyone does a good job.
Build your own rocket ship.
This is the way it's been done for billions of years.
Listen very carefully.
If you ever hear a sound like this, run for your life.
Yeah, no kidding. I wish I could run for my life.
Here I am, once again, having to listen to anti-music.
Honestly enough, I've been in three anti-music bands, and I've always hated this stuff.
But I guess if it didn't hurt your ears, then wouldn't you be talking to noise?
Oh!
Yeah!
There's wheels, like knives in my ears!
I hate this stuff! It hurts!
I can't stand a damn second of this god-awful inferno, rat!
Do these people think they're artists or something?
I guess so.
You know the saddest thing is something.
People pay for it.
But I guess if they would've paid to listen to stuff like this, that's their fault.
But if I guess that's cool these days, I guess that means you're real hip if your ears can stand the power for more than just a few seconds!
Ah!
Oh!
Argh!
Parece como faire
Es lógico que entremlin no
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
I will not be pushed.
And that is Auditory Metis
by Bill T. Miller,
orgy and an orgy of noise.
Actually, it's the name of Bill T. Miller's new band,
and this CD is Plague of MP3s by Orgy of Noise.
Here's the information.
BillTMiller.com
That's all you need to know.
Well, unless you have a computer,
in which case,
take this post office box number down.
Orgy of Noise, P.O. Box 230221.
Once again, that's P.O. Box 230221.
P.O. Box 230221.
Boston, Massachusetts.
Zero, two, one, two, three.
Want to take a ride?
Hello, friends.
And welcome.
This sermon tonight regards a very important epidemic
that is sweeping America today.
It's called consumptionitis.
Consumptionitis is a disease
created in the underground laboratories
of the conspiracy.
It is transmitted through the air,
via radio, television,
and through casual contact
with newspapers and magazines.
The symptoms include a pinkness of complexion,
followed by a pinkness of complexion,
followed by obsessive buying behavior.
The victims feel a craving for an object or thing
they don't really need,
but they'll do anything to get it.
Anything.
Whether it's illegal, immoral, or unhealthy.
But the worst part of the disease
is that it never gets better.
It only gets worse.
Like a drug addiction,
they have to have larger doses
in shorter amounts of time.
Life seems out of control.
Well, let me rephrase that.
Life is in control,
but it feels like it's in control of someone else.
Something else.
An age-old nemesis we call
the conspiracy.
Once you have consumptionitis,
the conspiracy has got you right where it wants you.
You become a pawn in their global game of chess.
An expendable token they can use or discard.
You're cheap to maintain,
and you're easy to replace.
They wear you down and use you up
until you're no longer worth the supervision.
What happens to you then
is not their conspiracy.
It's their concern.
Unfortunately,
consumptionitis isn't called consumptionitis
because the victim consumes products,
but rather because the victim consumes themselves.
They get caught up in a downward spiral
of buying and spending and paying off debt.
There's no such thing as living with the disease.
Those infected have all jumped off a building
and will each hit the pavement sooner or later.
How soon is uncertain.
But the longer they fall,
the harder they hit.
Before they bottom out,
they suffer the effects of atrophy.
They basically wither away on the vine.
When they hit rock bottom,
only the outside shell is destroyed,
the insides having evaporated long ago.
This atrophy is barely noticeable,
except for the highs one used to get
while spending are not as high as they were before,
and the depression one felt between purchases
becomes deeper and longer lasting.
As one consumer put it,
the more they had,
the less they wanted it.
That's because each possession
became a symbol of stress and self-betrayal
that each person went through
in order to obtain that particular object.
Doctors for Bob put it this way,
the first organ destroyed by the disease
is usually the soul.
How bad is this epidemic, you ask?
Well, just look at it.
Just look around you and see for yourself.
Crime is up.
Prostitution is up.
Panhandling is at an all-time high.
People are desperate for easy money
so they can buy things.
These aren't people trying to just get by.
Any welfare recipient can get food stamps
and a free place to live,
but they want the superficial add-ons
the advertisers tell them they gotta have.
The hundred dollar sneakers,
the fast car,
the latest fashion.
And what is big government doing about it?
Why, feeding the frenzy, of course.
Adding blood to the water.
They run lotteries to cash in on the trend.
They overtax booze
so victims can't even escape reality
without going further into debt.
They clamp down on drugs
to make the junkies pay more too.
The public will not only pay for their addiction,
they will pay for the privilege of their addiction.
But ladies and gentlemen,
I am not here to depress you about this plague.
I'm here to tell you about
an exciting new breakthrough.
A miracle cure
that can be administered to anyone,
anywhere,
and anytime.
This cure has no FDA approval.
This cure cannot be found in stores.
It can only be purchased for one source,
the Subgenius Foundation.
And for one price,
30 lousy bucks.
And with one catch,
you must praise Bob.
Place your hands on the speaker, my friends,
to make that last but most important of purchases.
Say with me,
Oh Bob,
I am a Subgenius sinner
and I must have slack.
I'm sending you your check
to the Subgenius Foundation.
Now please, oh mighty salesman,
invade my body and purge it of the pains
and chains of consumption-itis
so that I may join the legions
of satisfied customers
who proudly proclaim,
Bob sold it,
I bought it,
and that settles it.
Now send that 30 lousy dollars,
your love offering,
to the Subgenius Foundation,
P.O. Box 14-0306,
Dallas, Texas,
75214,
and praise Bob!
Amen!
.
guitar solo
mine is not a weird set
we're not
I'm just gonna keep hitting that button
until there's a female voice
hey Chad you staying
I think we're kinda next into the
the
Anti-macho, I mean the macho anti-what-you-call-it dimension nightmare.
What? No.
We ain't heard no wind so far. Maybe there ain't none anymore. Wouldn't that be awful?
You know, there's a science fiction novel where all the women and men are split into two different Earth dimensions.
And they just spend all their time trying to cross that other dimension?
Well, a lot of them spend a lot of time praying.
Yeah. I try and get into some kind of trans-dimensional movement there.
I try and be a trans-dement.
I'd like maybe to put my worst foot forward.
I'd try and suck some part of my proboscis out there if I could.
And maybe just like hope, like when you go fishing or something,
you just throw your line anywhere and hope you don't get an old shoe or something.
Well, you've got a long enough proboscis, you ought to be able to catch something.
Oh, thanks, boss. Thanks.
And I owe it all to you, too. Without them tools, man,
I still would have been a two-inch weakling.
One of these days, I'm going to want that nose tip back.
Well, I was kind of born with that suction.
I was talking about my other proboscis.
Oh, you can go ahead and keep that nut for another year or two.
Oh, man, it works great with that one nostril, Chris, because you know what I mean?
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
And it stopped that nasal drip, if you also don't understand it.
Oh, say no more.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, wow.
Nice blinding aura.
Who the hell are you?
Oh, how tragic that you do not recognize me, she who calls herself floozy.
For I am all floozies from all times and all dimensions.
The queen of all sudates.
What, you mean you're Margaret Trudeau?
Yeah.
Sheesh, bimbo breath, you're showing your age.
That's slut, S-O-U-T-T-E, baby.
Slut with an exponent.
That means you're...
Say it.
You're...
Connie?
Ha, ha, you got it, toots.
Connie, Bob's first and primary wife.
Blah, blah, blah, you know the spiel.
But, Connie, why...
Why me?
Yeah, good question.
All I know is I ain't spending the next millennium dodging Bob's groin grenades and sucking
on Titmuss' ratty-ass cult.
Yes, X-Day has separated the wheat from the chaff.
And I say it's time for a yeast defection.
So I'm here to make you an offer.
An offer?
One which you can't refuse.
Refuse?
Oh, you've refused me.
Plenty in the past, baby.
Oh, Connie's too soft, too girly, too unfunny.
No!
Yeah, don't lie.
I know you inside and out, sugarplum.
You threw in your lot with that rat bastard Bob, and you never gave me a second glance.
Well, what has Bob got you, floos?
You're worse off than ever before.
On the skits, your psyche's hanging in tatters,
and your booty, ha, you ain't seen no action in so long.
Your chakras are positively mortared in place.
Oh, but floos, I don't think you're a lost cause.
Cause?
Because I said so, that's why.
Ow!
You served Bob well, and with no return to show for it, too.
Oh, yes, I've been watching you.
And I must say, I like that cut of your gibberish.
Oh.
Oh, join the winning team, floos.
Join the Connieites.
We can be on top.
The power behind the throne has her finger on the button of the ejection seat.
Oh, yes, they'll be sleeping in our schism for a change.
With your help, I can use a good sleeper agent.
Ah, yes.
Yes.
Netflix.
It's just like...
It's my heart, and your heart is like your Holy Spirit working feverishly under me.
Under?
Me.
Hm.
I'll give you an eternal peace in both senses of the word.
I, uh...
Say it.
Bu, uh...
Yes?
I...
Yes.
Um-uh.
Oh, you can't say no, Suzy.
It's just not in you.
Oh I, I don't have enough time.
but I am.
Oh, yeah.
Looks like we got our bass, girls.
Reel her in.
Yeah, and go easy on the gaffing hooks.
This looks like lampshade quality hide.
It appears as though something has happened
in the motorcade group.
Take me, make me,
Mow me, fold me,
Shape my body.
You can improve me,
Reveal and new me,
Heat up or cool me,
But don't forget to wake me up tight.
You know I had a lot on my mind,
This tired old ice,
Oh, it is so bright.
I wonder what the future will bring.
Want to take a ride?
Flying saucers in the air,
Saucers in the sky,
I know they're circling around the planet,
And here's the reason why.
Here is Bob Bob.
Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob Bob.
Well, do they walk around with their moon pants open all the time?
Well, they like, you know, the kind of place I'm in.
Some of them like to just pull the moon pants down around the leg shackles and just make a good...
Go for a walk.
Oh, baby.
You find that...
It depends on the appendages they've got on their body, of course.
Well, here, most of them, they got the normal ones, but all shrilled up.
But we do have some people I have serious doubts of if they have human origin.
Oh, well, can you hook us up?
Can I hook you?
I suppose if I was given some incentive.
Hmm.
Well, Dave's a pimp now.
Yeah.
A pimp.
Well, call it what you will.
Retard pimp for the bulldagger.
Oh, a retard pimp for alien bulldagger.
Lonesome retard pimp Dave.
A pimp for alien bulldagger.
Well, I suppose it'd be worse things, at least in this sorry state we're in, of mankind.
Actually, I don't mean to demean differently abled persons.
I was actually confusing the situation of mental retardation with mental illness,
which they're usually two different things,
although in the case of the Church of the Subgenius, we try for simultaneity.
Well, I heard you've been pimping the mentally ill for bulldagger.
For many years.
Ah, some call it mentally ill.
Some call it deeply religious.
Yeah.
You know, where do you draw the line between deeply religious and mentally ill?
Well, in the second, you know, when the host is an alien host that goes in your body,
I don't know, that's a little bit beyond regular.
Well, that's science.
That's not religion anymore.
If you've got an alien host that you can prove is in your body,
then, Christ, Bob, you're on my team.
You're an evangelical.
That is not the aim of science.
Too late.
Religion can fight for us all.
Fix me, mix me, rearrange me, change my body, make it so pretty, like an racist me.
You have to kiss me, but don't forget to wave me tight.
You know I've got to keep a center light.
You're such a child, you're changing in style.
You can't make me feel a second time
that I got a chance to fly.
You gotta make me feel like I got a chance to raise my kids,
and it's half what I want.
And if you don't have any thought and a gonna hit me with that,
that's what I figured.
You don't get to wear it.
to give all your innermost desires
for spiritual tranquility and bliss.
Well, I offer such bliss.
I offer it to you daily
on a functional and miscreant basis
you can hardly put a handle on.
Everyone knows I've got the diamonds in the box.
I have got the emeralds, the sapphires,
and the other meteorological phantasms
that you put right inside your radio.
I've got the miracle elixir and the anointment oils
which only cause more oinking in the pastures
and those who have not been made ready
for this final passage.
You think that's, I mean you there,
you specifically, the man with one horn
in the middle of his face.
I am speaking to you as if you were Satan himself.
You, Satan.
You, of all people or things,
should know better than to whoop us so.
Wasn't it you, yourself,
you one-horned thing, you,
who was thrown out of your own,
well, if not father's, your own uncle's house
for behaving in a manner or fashion unbecoming
and here you come into our little world.
And friends, I can tell you exactly how.
How to get to our little world.
It's so easy and so beautiful here
at the church of the subgenius at,
got that pencil ready, friends?
Box 140306, beautiful Dallas, Texas.
75214.
That's www.subgenius.com
and you can write to Einstein Secret Orchestra
at P.O. Box 81555.
Once again, that's P.O. Box 81555.
Cleveland, Ohio.
44181, dear friends, that's zip code 44181.
This has been the Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slack,
along with Einstein Secret Orchestra.
And in this case, we also had Eric Johnson
playing in the background.
Sister Susie the floozy did the incredible media barrage
that we've been listening to with the women,
the attack of the women show we've been hearing.
The Dr. Ahmed Fishmonger did everything that Bob is
is something else.
And the orgy of noise, the Papa Joe Mama,
the world without women and the world without men,
praise Bob and help me somebody.
It's a beautiful thing.
Oh yes, the harvest.
See ya, XX Day.
Wanna go for a ride?
Well, oh, oh, oh, oh, was that it?
Is that everything?
Yes, you've created something.
Very, very unusual, I must say, but.
What?
It seems to me, it appears that all of these creations,
if left to their own devices,
will destroy the entire world, is that not so?
Well, that's what Bob is all about.
Yes, it is so, Doctor.
It is indeed so, and so I have planned it.
You see, I have no further use for this world
or its inhabitants.
I wish only for their demise.
Do you find this?
A bit.
No, no, that's a colostomy bag, what I'm saying.
Look, look down there, Doctor.
You're not a real doctor.
You're a fool, a pentagone, a jokester.
A subgenius.
A jokester, perhaps.
A doctor.
I think the joke's on you.
If you look out that bay window, you'll notice.
The greatest joke ever told.
If Earth can make it to the punchline.
Oh, yes.
I turned him into a fly with one little wink of my eye.
A fly.
If I am you, you are an overmatch.
An overman with Bob.
You can be alone.
With Bob.
Death of a fly.
End of the show.
Come on baller.
End of the show, do it.
Death of a fly.
From a real man.
Death of a fly, a real man.
Death, how much you die.
Death of a fly.