...programming for a test of the emergency broadcast system. This is only a test.
Oh my god, they're coming to get us! Run! The Russians! This is the end!
Nuclear weapons, everything they got! Water to New York! All gone! We're next!
Just a few seconds, it's gonna explode! Run to your shelter! Run!
Trap whole name! Builders put in! Screw your wife! Screw your children!
Eat every man for themselves! Red Trap terror! If you just see that deadly radiation, that explosion, you're gone!
It's curtains! Oh my god, what a terrible way to go! Your fingernails fall out! You're an air mouth!
You turn green! You vomit! You vomit all over the place! Just get in there and live!
Lock the other sucker out! You're the only one that matters!
President, that's all we got! Get with it, attack pack!
I wanna see the Russians blow off in a big smoke screen! I wanna see them die to save my women and I!
What's going on? I want my revenge! We're all gonna die!
We're all gonna die! We're all gonna die!
This was only a test.
The end has come for humanity. Not in the red of atomic fusion.
Not in the glory of interstellar combustion. Not in the peace of white cold silence.
But that! That creeping, grasping flesh below us!
It is a joke, eh, Lewis? A great joke! The joke of the cosmos! The end of all mankind!
Well, why?
Because!
The Self Genius Hour of Slack!
It is a psychological technique whereby you, seated in the auditorium, actually become part of the action you see on the screen.
Let me show you something.
You will feel absolutely no pain at all.
Feel.
Things are pretty weird here in Dallas.
As you can tell.
I don't have the radio or a tape deck on. This is just the sound effects of the
downtown street that I'm driving down.
It's pretty confusing, really.
You can see why the Subgenius Foundation had its, the church itself,
had its birth here in Dallas.
I mean, I don't even know whether I'm going forward or backwards.
Sometimes it almost feels like a freeze frame, you know?
And on top of that, I've been editing film all month.
You know, I don't know whether...
I mean, sometimes I think I can just rewind my own reality.
Maybe I can even stop it.
But on and on they climb toward their hills of calvary, bearing their punishment bravely.
What are you trying to pull?
Do you know what you are?
There's a very dirty word for what you are.
And a very dirty group of people running a very dirty business.
Oh yes, didn't you know?
We're highly organized.
The Church of the Subjeet.
The road of excess leads to the palace of wisdom.
Prudence is a rich, ugly old maid courted by incapacity.
The cut worm forgives the plow.
Dip him in the river who loves water.
For a pink sees not the same tree that a subgenius sees.
And a dead body revels there.
not injuries.
But if the fool would persist in his folly,
he would become wise.
Shame is pride's cloak,
and prisons are built with stones of law,
brothels with bricks of religion.
And the pride of the peacock is the glory of God,
the lust of the goat is the bounty of God,
the wrath of the lion is the wisdom of God,
and the nakedness of the woman is the work of God.
And the hour of slack is...
the...
snotty handkerchief of God, my friends.
Those were actually some Proverbs of Hell by William Blake.
Reverend William Blake, written about a hundred years ago,
and welcome to yet another hour of slack show, my good,
good friends and prayer partners.
We'll be, we'll be finishing...
our, uh, discussion of the fall of Mutantus
and the creation of the humans by the Yetis.
Uh, tonight, we've also got some very interesting recordings
that I think you, you may en-enjoy.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
I...
I can't...
Someone beat us to it.
Thirteen Catholic nuns on roller skates.
...Works out to be about $3300 dollars per man, woman, and child in this country.
Oh, it's a good philosophy.
Alright, I mean, the philosophy means a jaaast милли
Just keep out of that impenetrable sucking swamp bubbling with the sludge of credulity,
superstition and fanaticism.
So and as we travel along in our wonderful green and blue showmobile, even cooler than
Oscar Myers' Wienermobile, we shall avoid those flickering marsh lights, those false
friends, those unidentified and unhallowed floating or flying objects who weave and dart,
yawing and pitching their unwholesome ideology to each and every sapsucker and poebucker
who shuffles his size 12 brogans down the perilous and ever steepening pathways into
the foggy frog infested bog of no return.
Well, one of my terms here in which I've got to use on you guys is I've temporarily
got a disconnect here.
That's a sad term.
I don't care.
Yeah, we can see on the camera here.
Yeah, go ahead.
All right.
Well, ladies and gentlemen, pray for that, gentlemen.
Anyway, that didn't go out of order.
It went over the air, fortunately.
And it's unfortunate that we have jerks like that that will call and do that.
But you need to pray for them and pray that God will change them from a jerk to a born-again
person.
And anyway, moving right along.
Hi, Steve.
Hello, Jim.
Yes, how are you?
Yeah, I hate to say it.
I got bad news for you, sunshine.
It did, in fact, go out over the air because Jerry forgot to turn on the delay device.
Are you there?
Yeah, I'm there.
It's something that you really have got to check into if you're in the market for carpet.
Okay, thanks for calling.
Glad to be with you.
Okay, bye-bye.
Lines are filled.
Good morning, Bob.
You're on live at night.
Hello, Bob and Steve.
I'm awfully concerned about my wife.
She has joined somewhat of a cult organization.
I'm not sure if you've heard of it.
It's the subgenius organization.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
The new ones are being launched.
Every day is trying to keep up with them.
Yeah, no kidding.
Well, it's funny.
You're Bob, and I'm Bob, and...
We've had three Bobs tonight.
Three Bobs, yeah.
Plus our guests.
Well, their god is kind of called Bob, too, and that has a lot to do with it.
She's kind of become confused, naturally, as being involved in a cult organization and
recognizes me as being Bob, the Bob of their cult organization.
I don't know.
I don't really know how to go about solving the dilemma.
Maybe you can help.
Bob, let me give you just a couple of insights.
First of all, let me just ask you very directly, are you a Christian?
Yes, I am.
Okay.
Number one, Bob, is if you're praying for your wife and you're praying for these people,
if you're praying already, double your prayers.
Double?
Yeah, double your prayers.
You're moving into tough territory.
Number two, write a letter to Dr. Walter Martin at Christian Research Institute in Capistrano,
California.
I don't have all of the address, but you can get it here at KPDQ, I believe.
That's right.
Write to Dr. Martin and get his response, because he is probably the clearest authority
on even cults that I've never even heard of, and get some information, if he does have
information on this cult, and exactly the proper way to go about handling it.
He is the unsurpassed expert in that area.
Well, what kind of insight can you give until that time?
I mean, I'm not sure what this will lead to.
I don't think it will lead to directly in the next few days, and it could be anything.
All right.
First of all, the insight is pray, Bob.
And I've already told you that.
Pray.
Number two, understand that everything, every cult you deal with has a spiritual, or has
their root in the spiritual.
Everything God says, now I'm probably going to offend some people, but I'm going to tell
you what the Bible says.
Jesus said, you're either of your father God, or you're of your father the devil.
There's no gray area.
It's black or white.
It's, you know, we can say it that way.
And if you're not a follower of God the Father through his son, the Lord Jesus Christ, then
you're dealing with something that comes directly from Satan himself.
So you're on spiritual ground.
Pray.
And right now you may have to walk a little bit on eggs around your wife.
Don't antagonize her until you get more information in your hands and what you can do on this
particular thing.
Well, I was wondering, Bob.
What's the difference between a spiritual and a spiritual?
I don't know anything about the, the, the, do you know anything about this figure, Bob?
I don't.
I really don't.
No.
That's why I say write to Walter Martin.
In fact, you don't have to write to him, Bob.
If you want to invest in Long Distance Call, just call down there.
You can get information right over the phone so you know what you're dealing with.
Yeah.
Thank you, Bob.
I sure do hope things don't get too bloody before it all ends.
I'll give that guy a ring and see what happens.
Okay, Bob.
There are people praying for you and your wife, too.
Yeah.
Okay.
What's your wife's first name, Bob?
Um, her name is Betty.
Betty.
Yeah.
All right.
Thank you, Bob.
We'll pray for you tonight, Bob.
Thank you.
The fighting Jesus looked out over the bridge of the excess battle saucer, blood of Christ.
He looked and laughed.
He laughed and looked.
He looked and looked.
He angel laid it on the' upright rake wall.
He looked up at his電aroom.
Ferrari coming soon.
Will he get his luck card?
This impresC smart prisoner still has a single maintenant.
I ran out of conveyor doubt, and I didn't bring the key to the front...
There's no future withoutApple.
dat feff
Good!
Hey there!
In my into look this hot steeds I know myим
You burning a big sound?
You'd like to know all that?
Jesus was in a psychopathically elated state.
His face resembled many of the perverse icons the humanoids of the dust moat painted of him.
They prayed to these for the salvation of their souls,
as if they had any souls to save,
as if anyone would want to save them, which they didn't.
A whole disgusting religion now centered around his murder.
They had to gall to nail him up like a common criminal
and then paint pictures of him enjoying it.
And they thought he loved them for it, that he was forgiving.
Oh, the anticipation.
He was sick to his stomach with glee.
He would show them the true face of pain and sin.
It had taken him 2,000 long years to return here,
and now he would pay them back for the scars he still carried in his hands.
Sweet stigmata.
Even the slightest thought of the scars made them glow red through his fists,
through the boxing gloves.
The whole of the spacecraft was manned with angels of light,
personally lent by Jehovah One.
They supervised the demon teams operating on all tangible destruction spectrums,
all in attack mode,
Nagas, Orzuma, Shiva, Horus, Aeons, the dark bodies,
and at a time and a half too.
It was expensive to ravage a planet.
When we were born
Into this life
We were destined
To make it right
And it's pretty
Turnin'
And this is our fate
We're singin' this song
So you can relate
We are goin'
To save the universe
Goodbye!
Hi, good morning.
What's on your mind today?
Um, well, I have
a conversation
about, uh,
I've been listening
to your show for a while
and I heard
the gentleman, uh,
Bob,
call
about, uh,
the problem he had
with his wife
in this cult
of the subgenius
and, uh,
how it
worshipped
a deity
or whatever you call it
named Bob.
And this
reminded me
of a good friend
I have
who's a Christian.
Do you have a party line?
No, I don't.
Okay, I was hearing
other voices.
Uh,
uh,
I don't know, yeah.
Anyway, this
this made me think
of my, uh,
friend who has
a passive interest
in, in a cult
and I called him up
and he's awake
and, uh,
and he told me
about this,
this Bob,
this Bob creature
and he says it's
from the cult
of the subgenius.
He just happened
to know about it
and it's from
Revelations
and it's in, uh,
Revelations 13,
verse 1
if you have your,
your Bible.
Sure.
Revelations 13, 1?
Yeah, you can
read it.
Okay.
Read along.
I'll quote this
if I may.
Okay.
And it says,
and I saw a beast
rising out of the sea
with ten horns
and seven heads
with ten, uh,
diadems.
What are diadems?
Those are crowns.
Okay.
Upon its, uh,
horns
and a blasphemous
name upon its head
and that name,
according to my friend,
the name upon
the beast's head
is Bob.
Huh.
That's, uh,
that would have to be,
to be honest with you,
uh,
Rudy,
that would have to be
read right into Scripture
because that's not
given to us anywhere.
Yeah, I know.
It's not given to us.
That's just how this,
this cult has interpreted,
you know,
this is just,
this is really out of context.
Yeah.
It's just one small part of this.
And I,
and I am seriously
out of luck to explain
how this woman
has, um,
mistaken her husband
for this beast
with seven heads
with a bob.
Yeah.
Well,
yeah,
it's a,
it's a strange one,
Rudy,
that's for sure.
Thank you, Rudy,
for calling.
Bye.
I just said,
yeah,
just a little help.
I hope that man's still listening.
Good.
Okay, good.
Thank you.
There is noise
on that telephone line
and it's a mystery to me.
Yes.
Yeah.
Next, it's Gloria.
Good morning.
Yes, hello, Bob.
I'm pleased to be able
to be on your show
this evening.
Um,
I just wanted to mention
that as I was going
through my Bible
the other night,
I did happen to notice,
um,
some references
to the cult figure
that has been
popping out
throughout the conversation
this evening.
Um,
and,
Mark 1,
24,
or 23,
pardon me,
and immediately
there was in their synagogue
a man with unclean spirit
and he cried out,
what have you to do
with us,
Jesus of Nazareth?
Have you come
to destroy us?
But I know
who you are,
the Holy One of Bob,
but Jesus rebuked him
saying,
be silent.
Okay,
thank you for calling,
Gloria.
Next, Fred.
Good morning,
you're on KPDQ.
Bob,
this one's Coke.
Coke.
Well,
we're having a terrible,
I think you've just
broken the record,
Mike,
for taking,
uh,
strange phone calls,
but we hope we don't,
uh,
hear from him again
for a long,
long time.
Well,
it's interesting,
Jerry,
both times he's called,
he's mentioned cocaine.
Oh,
he did?
The first time,
he said,
lines of Coke,
and he hung up
it right there.
Yeah,
and he just called up
and he mentioned Coke again,
and,
uh,
obviously we're probably
dealing with a person
that may have a problem
in that area.
Uh,
very true.
I,
I did not catch that
until you mentioned it.
This gal calls in
all the time,
she says.
Aha,
so you know,
eh,
you must be a secret listener.
She says that,
but do you believe her
on a show like this?
All right.
Well,
of course,
your calls are recorded,
analyzed,
and shuttled into
a multi-index memory bank.
But you have to tell
what's not the key
to the caller
for the caller parade.
Jesus washed my skin away.
All this show
has to march
down the street
at 6 a.m.
Right?
Don't say the J word.
And now the caller police
are looking for you,
so you must join the parade.
And don't say the J word.
Hi, Don.
No, it's,
it's Dom.
Dom?
Yes.
Okay, hi.
Hi, how are you doing
this evening?
Fine.
Some fresh testimony
from Rich this evening.
I enjoyed that message.
Yeah.
Um,
I have a prayer request.
Mm-hmm.
Um,
um,
a friend of mine
has a girlfriend
who's in trouble.
Uh,
and I was just
kind of anonymously
and I was wondering
if we could,
if we could have a prayer for her.
Have a prayer for who?
For my friend's girlfriend.
What do you want me to pray?
Well,
they've,
there's been some sin
involved in the relationship.
Uh-huh.
Uh,
and I,
they have a big decision
to make coming up
and I'm hoping
that, uh,
the right things
are,
are carried through,
so.
Well,
are either one of them
Christians?
Uh,
both are,
yeah.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
And so what are they
going to be making
decisions about?
Well,
she's looking for
a good Christian abortionist
but her boyfriend,
uh,
doesn't like that idea.
Um,
thinks that,
uh,
she's looking for
a good Christian abortionist?
Yes.
Who's that?
There isn't any.
Uh,
well,
I was wondering
if actually you could help,
uh,
help recommend one for me,
but,
uh,
anyway,
we always get kind of,
you know,
jerks like that
on the air sometimes.
Uh,
I don't know why they call,
but,
uh,
pray for this guy.
Um,
he said his name was Dom.
I think I could give him
a different name,
but anyway,
we have still one line
available.
I don't know.
I think that's stupid.
I could be off
enjoying myself,
pounding my head
into a brick wall
over and over,
running down the street
with my brains
hanging out
in the back of my skull,
dragging on
the sidewalk.
Uh,
I don't know.
The male
out of place
is the female
displaced
and the children
misplaced
and ultimately
God replaced.
Come on.
Remember that.
So,
the lady now
feels to be
to get back
to that unconditional
love,
for love,
with God and with Adam she's doing everything to remain beautiful or to
stay please accept me I don't feel right I'm wrong I messed up hey let's cover
our shame by tying together our own fig leaves now God hadn't seen them yet so
they were hiding from each other who told you you were vulnerable who told
you you were under scrutiny they didn't even know they were naked
Robert I
praise the Lord
how are you doing this evening I'm doing pretty decent yeah just wanted to talk
about your theme of compromise of sin and justice I have a bit of a bit of a
problem I actually calling for a prayer request I have a tumor I need some
prayer for and I'm wondering how that kind of fits in with your discussion of
justice and natural
well seeing is that the adversary the prince of darkness and the temperature
has made his way into my very faculty for evaluating these kinds of subjects
okay well let's pray and where's the tumor in my brain okay I think did you
just find that out yeah all right so it'd be silly to ask how you're doing I
I would imagine you're doing all kinds of things,
sometimes being afraid and sometimes being peaceful
and sometimes being angry maybe or everything.
What?
I would imagine that you're experiencing a variety of emotions.
Yes.
Over it.
Yes, very much so.
Okay, Robert, let's pray.
Father, we just lift up our brother to you.
And, Robert, I am assuming you're a Christian.
Yes.
Okay.
Father, we do lift Robert up to you and just amen.
Amen.
Yeah.
I hope that we'll take care of the demon, of the monster, of the hellion.
Thank you, Jim.
Thank you, Robert.
Try a new salad dressing.
Okay, please stay in touch with us.
Thank you.
Okay, good night.
All right, let's see.
Hi, Velma.
Hi, Jim.
Yes.
Hi, this is Velma.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm not calling for something that has too much to do with religion, but with my grandchildren.
Okay.
And I just want to say I had them over for dinner last night, and I was serving a very nice dinner of beans and macaroni and pork chops.
Go ahead.
Oh, excuse me.
Okay.
Velma, you can go ahead and give me a call back if you get a chance.
I'd like to talk with you.
Nobody was listening, fortunately.
We can march on in cleanliness.
That's quite all right.
You know, no one ever listens to any of these things I say.
I try to tell them.
I mean, I got the wisdom of the ages right here in the multi-indexed memory bank, but do they listen?
Oh, nobody listens.
I don't listen to the show.
Oh, no.
No, I'm kidding.
You sure know how to hurt a guy.
I know that is real.
Boy, that was a tough sock on the chin.
That's how you always cut me off anyway.
What?
I never...
You're slap happy.
I'm going to snip it right in half, and all the colors go floating away into beautiful dark space.
No one?
Hi, Herb.
Hello.
How are you?
I'm fine.
How are you doing?
Well, I have this terrible pain, and you know that major surgery I had ten years ago, and the in-laws, and isn't the weather awful?
Now, hold on.
What major surgery did you have?
The world situation has me so upset and nervous, and oh, well.
We'll probably all be blown up anyway.
Well, that's, uh, you talk about...
Listen, that man is, uh, he is, uh, negative.
How?
Well...
And I'm not so sure that that was, uh, that could have been a crank call.
I, I would think it was more along the line.
I think I recognized his voice.
He's been on before.
But let's not be deterred by that.
No, thanks.
Let's move right on.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, that feels so good.
Oh, baby.
Go ahead.
Say it.
Say what?
You know.
Bob?
.
Come on, Bob!
to gerontology once i'm greta riddell this tape will introduce you to your tutors i'm sorry that
that neurotic woman got on the air but you know it happens sometimes they get by all means let's
i just can't believe someone would call in and have the nerve to say things like that about
prairie squid i know not only that but they call somebody else's show i know using our air using
and our area code for that matter that you can bet it's going to be charged to its name
in in berkeley out in california oh they're hip out there in california oh yeah they're so hip
they've got oh they've got their crack so to speak yes their drugs and their wild sex
but but have you ever heard a person from one of these hot tubbers talking about a prairie
squid friends have you ever have never they haven't heard about those they've never heard
of it those organic boys and the with their avocado dips and they're city folks yeah they
don't
know about. Oh, they know everything.
They know everything. But they don't know that.
And if you told them, if you tried to tell
them about it, they'd think, oh, how quaint.
He's talking with his southern accent.
How folksy.
He must be near to the earth
or something. Yes.
But I'm an artist. I don't have to
lower myself to those
demeaning... I'm involved with
such incredibly cerebral
machinations over the
politically correct
aspect of my art and how it
applies to Barry Squid that I
don't really have to think about the humorous
side of these things, if there is a humorous
side, because I'm serious. I'm from
California. I don't have to do veiled
juvenile humor guising as
some sort of high
faluting environmental concern
citizen satire.
I'm not that kind of person. Oh, no, no, no.
Of course not. That's what they'll tell you every time.
That's the line they'll spring on you.
The sophisticated line.
The conspiracy is...
Their bourgeois line.
The conspiracy is insidious, friends.
Incredibly, they make you want what they
have. And they make you feel stupid
because you haven't got it. Yeah.
And they make you think it's better than what
you already have. That way,
once they get your attention
directed at what they have, they can get
your slack.
Your slack, friends. That's right.
And you're a prairie squid,
too. And if, as long
as you're the kind of person that can
still, you know,
if you can find one, you can go out in the woods
and have a short relationship with one of
these harmless animals. Or a long relationship.
I mean, you know, like, it's not...
There's no limited time. The tantric sex
magicians in India and
the ancient cultures
of the earth have known of...
I mean, these creatures are not just common
to the continental U.S. That's right.
And Reverend Stang, I don't know if you know it or not,
but in Tibet, they breed
in the temples a special variety.
Oh, the fattened special
prairie squid. The special prairie squid.
They call it. Yeah, it's the one that the Dalai
Lama has. Uh-huh. And
they still breed them there, and they have to ship
them out to India, where the Dalai Lama is
now, you know, the Chinese. They're fed than almost
anyone in Tibet. They're better
fed than most of Tibet
put together. And
friends, when
you become a member of the Church of the
Subgenius, you become eligible.
Yes. Eligible, friends.
We'll give you your very own
prairie squid direction and
survival package.
Give yourself to the feeling,
friends. I don't know.
I think that's stupid. I think that's stupid.
I think I just made... I think that's stupid.
And, uh,
I guess it's time to
to tell you
what you've been listening
to for the last half hour.
First half hour, anyway.
Uh.
Oh, there's been lots of
uh, calls.
Yes, recordings of, uh, mighty
calls on,
some Portland, Oregon station.
Don't know who made those calls. I got
the tape from, uh, Jim Blanchard.
And, uh,
tip of the hat there to Reverend Blanchard.
Uh, amazing stuff.
The subgenius who made those calls,
as far as I know, it wasn't Reverend Blanchard.
Never sent us that tape.
Get it came into our hands.
It's in the, uh, pipeline.
The prank call trading pipeline.
Um.
Oh, starting from the beginning
there. Of course, there's interspersed with,
with the subgenius show from Berkeley.
We play lots of tapes from the
KPFA subgenius show
there, um,
uh, more than an hour. Less than a show
with Dr. Howell and puzzling evidence.
And, uh,
oh,
some, uh, readings about
the fightin' Jesus.
Uh, me, your host,
Reverend Ivan Stang, I read that, but it was
written by St. Palmer
Vreedies. Uh, we
heard a little clip of the Swingin' Love Corpse.
Uh, Saving the Universe.
Um,
some zoogs. The music, uh,
bits and clips of music
that you heard were zoogs rift.
The great zoogs rift.
Um, some clips from the good
Reverend Ott. Uh,
sent in by, uh, Reverend Jimmy
B. And
towards
the end there,
Dr. G. Gordon Gordon and
myself discussing, uh,
prairie squids.
And what we have coming up,
now last week we, uh,
I was, uh, beginning to read
from, uh, the new
Revelation X, the Bob Apocryphon,
our ever-unfinished
book.
And, um, was reading
this, uh, to you, the scientific
section about the fall
of Mutantis. And,
uh, actually it was
the section we were reading was
the creation of the humans
by our ancestors, the Yeti.
And the mistakes
that were made in that self-same,
those moments of creation,
uh, as the Yetis
had, had, uh, discovered
the, the, the humans' joy in
hairless, spherical appendages
and soft, round
things, um,
uh, we learned
in, uh, Revelation X
how, oh, by the way,
in this, this material, the Yeti material
is, was researched primarily
by myself with Dr.
G. Gordon Gordon,
uh, did quite a bit of the
scientific research, and also
uh, Princess
Weardo, queen of all
the UFOs, contributed a great deal
of, uh,
trans-channeling to these things.
And, uh,
as we'd been, uh, learning
last week, the Yetis had discovered
that they could make other things besides
soft, round
spherical appendages
tickle the male human
desire gland.
But instead of restricting
uh, inborn raw
need only to the
unfulfillable breed lust,
uh, the, it could also
be sublimated into
devotion to some chore
or even some mere
symbol of a reward.
So now we continue with, uh,
the fall of
Mutantis.
...
After blanking the whole
reward lobe and scouring
it smooth for etching,
Yeti owners could load
their humans with directives,
false memories, new instincts,
talents, and proclivities.
Reflexes for rote
activities.
Fears.
Implanted by intra-humanists,
uterine hypnosis, or even
simple repetition, anything
could be filled into that
blank spot in the brain
and used to trigger
the reward secretion.
Yeti mind
designers created
hypno-templates for countless
archetypal images,
command signals, and responses,
experimenting to find out what combinations
produce both the most
pungent soul-flavoring
and the most
most progeny.
...
Males and females were programmed
not to want the same sorts of things,
as some tension between them was thought to spice up the souls.
To create a deep conflict of interest and thus spur them on,
the females were made to want things that were difficult for the males to provide,
but which they had to provide if they wished to touch anything round and soft, such as
security, safety, the sharpest teeth on the strongest silverback, the warmest mud, the biggest spear, the most...
... goats.
Though the males were encouraged to enjoy the fantasy that they had some free will beyond the craving for feminine glandular outcroppings,
and this hardwiring kept both genders busy storing up pain reserves while simultaneously ensuring that the male's body was safe and sound.
...
... a high birth-rate.
The yeti considered such weird behaviors a kindness.
The humans would find vast fulfillment
in obsessively doing whatever menial work was assigned to them,
such as mining,
picking the ticks off yetiyung,
accounting,
differential calculus,
etc.
Otherwise,
the humans would have been suicidally miserable,
knowing they were consigned to an endless treadmill of senseless toil
for distant masters who, in the end, rewarded them by devouring their souls.
But, since they were designed for it from the beginning, such a life would seem perfectly normal to them.
They wouldn't comprehend that they were slaves because they wouldn't be capable of understanding what real freedom was.
In fact, they would strive desperately to avoid true awareness.
The craving to have someone else, some authority figure, make their decisions for them would be at the very core of their natures.
They would always seek someone or something bigger to submit to and something smaller to dominate.
The Yeti planned, by milking emotions out of their new herds, in a controlled and relatively merciful manner,
to pay off the Elder Gods in only five or six million years.
However, they recognized that without the divine Yeti spark,
the intelligence they'd given humans could make them extremely dangerous animals indeed.
Were they ever to somehow run loose with that blank spot in their brains, unprogrammed.
So, the Yeti keyed in susceptibilities to certain diseases to prevent the human population from growing out of control.
They thought their fail-safes couldn't backfire,
that they had made the humans far too strong,
that they were too small, frail, and stupid to live in the wilds without Yeti masters to guide them.
Their hairlessness alone, it was assumed, would prevent them surviving even one winter outside the corrals.
Needless to say, however, the Yeti proved themselves far too cocky in this respect,
too certain that they would always be there to maintain human domestication.
To them, the very idea that the sub-moronic humans could ever escape Yeti domination
was almost as silly as the notion that their source of infinite power, the Great Crystal, might someday cease functioning.
They didn't bother to make it genetically impossible for a human to crossbreed with a Yeti,
for what Yeti could bring itself to touch one of these shriveled, hideous, bald, stunted pink gnomes?
It would be like one of us having sex with a skin rabbit!
Only the most depraved mind would even think of such a thing.
Sadly, none in Mutantis foresaw the depths to which a certain frustrated, mentally impaired, hairless, deformed, dwarf albino Yeti would sink.
And now we have to play this little bit of...
well, from bedtime stories for little bobsters based on Prescriptures 190-378b.
Bedeen, the lonesome Yeti, paced in angry circles out in the Game Preserve
where he went to be alone with his precious pet humans.
The other Yeti avoided him, not because he was a stunted, hairless albino that appealed to them.
It was because he was so unpleasant and self-involved.
As he paced, he muttered to himself,
I... I could... I could... I could... with a... a human... and no one would know?
But it'd be like coupling with a flayed animal!
Am I that low? Am I an animal?
Yet... yet be... because of my birth defects,
these pathetic creatures think I am a human.
I am a mightier, nobler specimen of their own kind.
Why, even among the most brilliant of the humans,
I, the retarded Yeti, am as unto a god!
They'll be my... my children!
I'll be their king! Their culture-bringer!
I shall parcel out knowledge!
And so rationalizing, the embittered, runt Yeti laid him down
with the beasts of the field.
And that, dear friends, was the fall.
He was the traitor Yeti,
the sick one who committed the first sin
by contaminating the famed human seed
with the higher divine spark that the Yeti alone is meant to possess.
Alas, he was not the last Yeti sinner,
for even in Mutantis as today,
some of the youth were so jaded and spoiled
that in their decadence they mimicked the traitor's disgusting ways,
for they were of a reprobate mind,
given over to vile affections.
And so, millions of sins later came we,
the Yetinsani,
misbegotten spawn of the Yeti and Homo sapiens.
The traitor fell so in love with his adopted humans
that he plunged even further into depravity,
teaching humanity the forbidden sciences,
revealing to them many secrets of Yeti technology.
He convinced himself that they could actually think and reason.
He mistook monkey brightness for innate intelligence.
But humans can be only knob-twiddlers.
Incapable of original ideas,
they depend on the inventions of subgenius,
for all real technological progress.
Any new thoughts the pinks do have
are based solely on what occasionally vomits up
from the buried archetypes implanted by the Yetis.
The lonesome Yeti is therefore remembered as the Dark One,
he who deceived and led astray
the Prometheus of the Titans,
who in his vanity brought man fire and gave him thought.
And has been regretting it ever since,
chained up on some mountaintop,
getting his liver eternally picked by vultures,
cursed with immortality of the very worst kind.
But miscegenation and bestiality alone
would not have meant the end of Mutantus.
The first high Yeti, King Bob,
and his love police
could have taken action to halt the perversions.
But an unnatural cataclysm was to divert the attention of the Yeti
and allow the escape of the humans.
The events leading to the destruction of the Great Crystal
and subsequent disasters is a moving and tragic story,
unfortunately we can only encapsulate it here.
Suffice it to say that two Yeti in heat
got carried away while in close proximity
to that crystal which powered all of Mutantus.
This was an aberrant lust.
Mutantian law forbade the queen of all tarnation
to consort with a lowly high janitor
in the broom closet of the temple of the Great Crystal.
Worse, it was the wrong season
for these two particular Yeti sex-castes to mate.
But they couldn't wait, so enamored were they.
And while they enjoyed the throes
of a freakishly powerful illicit,
exogasm,
their orgasmatic radiations produced
violent, uncontrollable telekinetic effects
like poltergeists the size of the Transamerica pyramid.
The unleashing of these titanic forces
shattered the Great Crystal.
This triggered the great earthquakes,
volcanoes and other cataclysms
which caused the Earth's magnetic polarities
to switch places,
which in turn initiated another dreaded continental seesaw.
The great landmass of Tarnatia
began gradually to sink beneath the waves
and the surrounding seafloors started their dreadful rise
into the forms of the continents we inhabit today.
During the fall of Mutantus,
the humans, aided by the embittered,
mentally deficient dwarf albino Yeti,
bolted into the wilderness.
Despite their weakness and plank brainpans,
these Yeti-trained escapees,
who called themselves the Fweegors,
not only migrated away from the sinking continent
and survived,
but went on to mingle with less evolved hominids,
further corrupting the Yeti seed
and diluting it among every other
vaguely bipedal species they could get their hands on,
and then some.
The Yeti's ultimate mistake, however,
wasn't in creating the humans,
but in creating them to be dutiful slaves.
Once they'd fled the all-important guidance
of their Yeti masters,
the blank spot in the brainpan was wide open
so the humans could fill it up themselves,
usually with the first awe-inspiring thing they happened upon,
like a frightened animal,
their mom,
hallucinogenic berries,
a head injury or a medicine man in a scary headdress.
No matter how crazy it was,
they always thought they had finally arrived.
They achieved free will by way of this
a savior,
god,
or ritual behavior.
And inevitably,
the more wily ones found out how easy it was
to reload the blank brainpans of others.
If through ritual,
a human could fill his fellow's brain gaps
and thus convince them their lives meant something,
they could be coerced into absurd activities,
like building huge useless stone temples
and tombs.
Thousands of them could be made to mutilate their own bodies
just so they could be part of the same club.
But someone else would be giving other humans
an opposite set of commandments.
The various clans would ceaselessly fight each other
and punish themselves without ever really knowing
why they were doing any of it.
Once they started programming themselves,
the Hwee-gors were like a biological warfare.
They had just enough intelligence and ability
to manipulate tools,
but also sufficient frustration
to use those tools to tear to pieces
anything in their path.
As the humans spread across the earth,
most yeti became nauseated at a world blanketed with pinks
and voluntarily shed their mortal coils
to move on to some much higher plane.
But the Hwee-gors were not the only ones
to be killed by the Hwee-gors.
Others, the shameful missing yeti,
those who had sinned, fled earth.
None know where they went.
Possibly they were sent away by the Exus
as punishment for ruining the plan.
Forced to breed gas whales on Jupiter
or to change the bedpans of the vacated Exus bodies
in storage on Toxima Regulus.
A handful of devolved yeti remain here on earth.
Phase shifted halfway into the seventh dimension
so that we cannot see them,
appearing to us only rarely
and only when there are no witnesses.
reagents.
Stay tuned at Beamos.
I got a note,
Oh!
This is my first single 들rory recording
and here are the names of the haters theoted
all around the universe.
Neither coconut or liquid folding
nor something I use to thrilled as Patreon
the real Bat Под
covered in the book of the subgenius but basically in short the Uyghurs eventually
formed to their own empire Mu the Empire of the Sun which stretched across what
is now Asia and Africa with only a few hundred thousand within only a few
hundred thousand years after the fall of Mutantis they had hunted all the
dinosaurs to extinction Jehovah one could see where this was heading and
displeased with the quality of his breeding stock wiped the slate clean by
destroying the Uyghur Empire with another great magnetic cataclysm the
space god preserved a handful of sample Uyghurs who incidentally were physically
identical to modern man and teleported them 80 million years into the future
where they suddenly popped into existence in the early Stone Age the
majority of the Uyghurs were
the Uyghurs were
forced evolved back down to the primal and for focus stage and evolution took
over more or less as described in modern non creationist textbook it took another
80 million years for humanity quote-unquote to painfully re-evolved up
to the Neanderthal stage and at that point less than 100,000 years ago the
small army of Uyghurs from the past reappeared on earth by divine
intervention
and promptly massacred or enslaved and bred out almost all the Neanderthal the
modern conspiracy exists by exploiting that blank spot inserted in our cerebrum
by the Yeti it is still there and that is why all over the world religions and
nations keep descending to fiendish human sacrifice in one form or another
usually this brutality is not the only reason for the Neanderthal to be so evil and the Neanderthal is the reason for the Neanderthal's death.
currently as disguised as patriotism economic or fun
can exploit the fact that the yeti gene never completely disappeared and can still be hurt by
simplified the recording part for additional
pin those rare randy yeti couldn't resist sleeping out from the seven
dimension 2 seduce or a Energy We northeast odi
me
could give up
szintzi
years of yeti
lustfulness, persistence, and fiendish cleverness have maintained a constant small population
of Yetinsani throughout history.
The continuous family tree of we who carry on the taint.
We the revenge of the Neanderthals, the heirs of the Yeti.
Was then the conspiracy an accident?
Bob himself has suggested that the Yeti were patsies, victims of a double cross.
That the Elder Gods engineered all of it.
From the mistakes in designing the humans and the wrecking of the great crystal, to
the crazed degenerate interbreeding between Yeti and beasts.
The starvation, despair, and turmoil which envelop our planet now are exactly what the
Elder Gods have been lusting for all along.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
All of our accomplishments as a species, all our great art, philosophy, and culture.
For what?
Just to keep us fighting and overpopulating and polluting so a bunch of discarnate beings
in another dimension can cop a buzz off the pain stored in our souls?
No!
For Dobbs is he who takes advantage of us.
And profited from these great mistakes.
Only Bob has dared to stand up against the course of history and try to steer his people
back onto the true road.
Within our genes, we know that we are meant to cleave to the true Yeti blood.
To reawaken the divine monad.
To regain original slack.
That's the grail towards which we strive.
But we are frustrated at every turn except in our oozing and squirting.
There it can be found.
It's buried deep, but in the right circumstances one can access it.
One can neither create it nor uncreate it.
It is a matter of reaching it.
Of being able to perceive it.
Of tapping into it.
Simply to know that it exists.
To know.
To fully know it's there.
It's the first step.
Then, then one can worry about approaching it.
If you can conceive of it, you are practically free.
You can begin to step away from the landscape and exercise true self-determination like
a real subgenius.
Though it might be postponed.
Though it might be postponed, friends.
Your biological destiny cannot be avoided.
So, face it.
You possess the jaw and teeth.
The jaw and the teeth of an ape.
But the skull of a human.
You are Piltdown Man.
You helped create the conspiracy.
Now, 80 million years later.
You are Piltdown Man.
You must help to destroy it.
And dear friends.
You can help destroy the conspiracy bar.
Right away for free information from the Church of the Subgenius.
I'm going to give that post office box.
And all you gotta do.
If you drop us a self-addressed stamped envelope.
Addressed to Bob.
Why?
Well, you just have to see what you get.
But there's a lot more.
A lot more than this poor little radio show.
And you can get that from Bob.
Just write to Bob at post office box.
1-4-0-3-0-6.
Dallas, Texas.
752.
1-4.
Yes, that's Dallas, Texas.
752.
1-4.
And that post office box once again is box 1-4-0-3-0-6.
Ugh.
So beiiing rot everywhere.
I going to the pro wall.
timeframe.
Nochnagh.
God ngày.
¶¶