Hello there!
Haha, flying saucer.
Flying saucers.
Now, am I crazy?
Yeah, something like that.
So I'm crazy? Yes!
Okay.
I am crazy. Yeah.
Flying saucer.
I thought I was going crazy!
Yeah, why not?
Okay.
Within five years,
the United States, as we know it, will
cease to exist. We're living in
terrible, perilous,
chaotic times.
Praise the Lord.
And these times are not
going to get any better, my friend.
Amen. They're going to get worse
and worse.
What love
you
can bring.
People from this
earth have already
seen some of their spacecraft,
which they call
flying saucers.
And other
flying objects which they
cannot describe.
These objects
are real,
and are spacecraft.
Total collapse of world civilization.
July 5th,
1998, at 7am
to be exact, the men from Planet
X, as the news media will
call them, will arrive to
rupture the subgeniuses,
the true believer subgeniuses,
up into the escape
vessels of the sex goddesses.
Even to carry a few
fixed survivors of our doomed civilization
to a new life on
another world.
It's let's have a party.
Battle of the
planets! Battle of the planets!
Is it time for that big operation?
And uh,
you know, even if X doesn't work out,
that will go for sex day!
We want you to have a dance
into the new century!
Screw into the new century!
Sleep and eat your
way into the new century!
And that the very, uh,
the very door of
the day of the wrath of God
is at hand! And that if you
plan to get saved,
you'd better do it now!
In this temple lodge of the church
of the subgenius of Little Rock, and
before we begin this sacred
spouting, I think that
we should all bow our heads
and let's all have a minute of noise.
AHHHHHH!
AHHHHHHHHHH!
Okay, I know you all think, uh,
you want to know what's going on.
That's okay.
So I saw this thing coming...
I saw this thing coming to me!
I didn't know what it was,
I didn't know what it was, but, uh,
it looked funny!
It looked funny!
There were deceptions
which have surrounded our space program.
If this was indeed
an extraterrestrial spacecraft
with living occupants,
it must have been very disconcerting
for them to cross millions
of miles of space, only
to be hit on the head with rotten oranges.
Ah, yes dear friends!
Your host and prayer partner,
Reverend Ivan Stang here,
and at this recording time,
I'm driving through
Akron, Ohio,
in the pouring rain,
on the way back to
Wisteria Campground in Southern
Ohio for the start
of the Starwood Festival,
after having come
home from the
16X Day Festival.
Now, last weekend,
Dr. Hall and I came back to Cleveland
and did some radio
talking about the
wonders of 16X Day,
actually the 18th
X Day Drill,
and now
for this and future shows,
we're going back
to the start, before
16X Day, and we'll play
over the coming weeks,
the many wonderful
recordings that were made there,
bands and shows and ranting
and just
spouting
off stage,
behind the scenes,
in the pouring rain, spouting.
So we're going to start
with a show recorded by
Dr. Hall and myself,
Princess Wee and Lonesome Cowboy Dave
at WCSB Cleveland,
on June 30th,
before X Day happened.
That will
give me time to begin editing
and cleaning up all the
fabulous location recordings.
And so, here we are,
back in time, with
what turned out to be
hour of slack number
1421.
Praise Bob.
Spacecraft entered the Moon's
gravitational field in the sixth
segment of the flight.
The gravity of the Moon is one-sixth
of that on Earth.
The orbit around the Moon
was flown 66 miles
above the Moon's surface,
at 6,000 miles an hour.
At 10 after 9,
the beeping began.
Went down to the
reserve fence, watched through
binoculars, and we did see this thing.
Now it's about the size
of the Moon, with a small
crescent at the bottom that's well lit
like starlight. The top is
a dark gray mass.
It came down through the trees, whatever
it was. Have you ever heard of one?
Have you ever been in
one? Have you ever seen
one? Have you, but television,
ever seen one? If you
haven't, it's the greatest sight this
side of Heaven.
Two months ago, the Observatory issued a press statement that the world was coming to an end.
Now that's the same story
the cult of the Book of Revelations had been
preaching. Now when a scientist
backs that up, it's news. Our conclusions
have nothing to do with the cult.
Well, today we deal with Bible
prophecy. But the Word of
God tells us we can expect
nothing but trouble and turmoil
in the Middle East until
our Lord returns to be
the Prince of Peace.
Bob?
It's been noticed.
Yes, dear
friends, when our Lord
returns to become the Prince
of Peace, and I think this might be him now.
Yes, here he comes. Hello?
Hello? Lord? Hello? Is that
you? Oh. No, it's me. Is it the
Prince of Peace? It's Lonesome
Cowboy Dave.
Or Swine Boy.
Swine Boy is neat.
The Lord of something.
The Lord of Swine.
Lord of Swine. Remember in the Lord of the
Flies when they had that wild pig
head and they danced around it?
Well, I just got
done a little bit of that myself.
Oh, blasphemy.
We're gonna have a pig head to dance
around at Ex-Dagger Street.
That's right. The pig will be
killed and we will drink his blood.
What?
I thought we were just gonna eat of his flesh.
I didn't know we were gonna, like, have communion
that way. It's all in the, uh,
manual. Yeah, I thought
we were just gonna eat
his flesh. The manual has
just been published. In this way, he will
live again through
us. That happens
on July 4th. Make this world
what, uh, he would have wanted
it to be. Porcine transubstantiation.
Oh, Dave,
you'll be honored to know that
the pig this year has been named
Dave.
By some strange coincidence.
Well, I don't feel
affected by that, my friend.
I feel rather honored.
Yes, well, all will share
in Dave's bounty.
Except vegetarians,
if there are such benighted creatures.
And except Dave, unless somebody
shows up to give him a ride.
Hmm, that could be.
And he wouldn't
need a ride back, because we'll be
we'll have spaceships of our own.
Yes, they really cut the distance.
Or I'll be back in a crate full of packages.
Hmm, but such
peanuts as, uh,
no one ever dreams of on this plane
of existence. Little bit of
jelly and little bit of toast and
mmm, mmm, you're out of this world.
Yes,
part of this nutritious breakfast.
The good packing peanuts are
edible, aren't they? Yes,
they're made of corn something.
Corn starch. They're made
of corn starch? The good ones.
If you, yeah, if you lick them,
they dissolve. But if you
you mean like ethically good or their
their taste? They taste like
cardboard, I can tell you that.
But, but they won't kill you.
Probably. So they just have a
high standard to high moral. They can pass through
your entrails.
And do little damage.
Unless you've got a tail or two?
A little pig tail.
That would have to be a whale of a tail.
Now, you know,
uh, we're not just
barbecuing the pig
and having turducken
inside the pig. I don't know if we have to tell
the radio audience everything,
reference day. Well, ideally
what we're hoping to have is
blue whale
elephant hippo
cow turducken
sparrow
mingbird
mesium. With, uh,
uh, century plant, uh,
and whooping grain
heart salad.
Well, that's just to go with the blue whale.
Oh. We only need one blue whale.
We're not gonna deplete the world.
I mean, there's at least five more of them left, right?
Yeah, well, this one is
Brombo, though. He's been around for a long time.
And he's already been blown
quite a few times, so I wouldn't worry about him
being blue anymore. He's, uh,
rather pallid now. He's
kind of a lighter shade of gray, or whatever
they used to say. He's more gray
than a, a blue. It all depends
on the lighting, uh, conditions.
If we were really brave, we'd have
old sequoia
lion
turducken mesium.
Well, I don't know if old sequoia
would voluntarily give himself
up for such a
holy purpose as that.
And come to think of it... You're going to splice
some animals? Is that, am I correct in
understanding you're gonna splice up a few newies?
You're gonna take old, um, old turtle
and mix him, mix
his genes with, um,
some stone-washed genes from
another animal and perhaps
create a new kind of bacon or some kind of
meat. Now, you're giving me ideas.
I hadn't thought of that, but we
certainly have that option.
Yes, the so-called
Moreau option.
It's part of our biological program
still in development.
Well, I...
...to talk about on the radio, but
there you go. So, uh,
the whole idea is that the
genetic code need not be,
um, etched
in brass, uh, but is actually
malleable and, uh, changeable.
Like any formula, or...
...uh...
...like a string of snot or
DNA. I have been making
plans to
create a world
and populate it with monsters.
In fact, I'm
going to make my favorite
video game come to life.
As soon as I have the opportunity
to do so, with the help
of the men from Planet X and their
supercomputer, Mwom...
Mwom. Mwom. Mwom. Mwom.
...I will cause to be manifested
the world of my video game,
Monster Hunter. And I
will be the... I won't be
running some tall
brute of a hunter
through his paces. I'll be doing it myself.
I'll be...
...slaying literal,
live, real
giant lewdroths.
Man, I could see you in a loincloth,
like, stabbing those monsters
with thermonuclear
spears and stuff. No, you won't see me in a loincloth.
You'll see me in elaborate
armor.
All kinds of elaborate armor.
It's a rough-and-tumble existence
that requires some personal
protection.
Next I see a rollerball spin-off,
a monster dome
type of thing. Monster dome?
Probably in Texas, of course,
where all those places are.
Well, there kind of already is a
monster dome in Texas. It's
called the Capitol in Austin.
The Capitol building, Rotunda,
and it is full of monsters.
And monster hunters,
such as the great new subgenius saint,
Wendy Davis,
Texas state senator, who
stood there
as Mr. Sister
said, when Republicans do that,
you call it obstructing.
And when she does it, she's
a hero, because
she was fighting for the
abortion rights, essentially,
the Texas Republican
lawmakers were about to
change the rules
so that pretty much all the abortion
clinics in Texas would have to close down.
And she
filibustered, like
Mr. Dobbs goes to Washington.
She didn't
quite make it, but the
witnesses took up a chant
that extended, that
prevented the vote from happening until
it was too late.
Of course, they're
coming back to do it all over again.
Rick Perry vowed that they would
push it through the next time.
But that's ridiculous, isn't it?
Controversial public appearance.
So, once again, the news
cycle must recycle
through for
us to be clear of it thirty hours later.
They want us to row
and wait backwards.
I'm sorry, with hot dogs in front of our noses.
What's going to happen next? Well, stick around,
we'll be back in five,
four, three,
two, one. Well, we're back.
It looks like the problems
in Texas are continuing to be problems in Texas.
My fellow Texans,
we have,
we want,
we want a small government.
To quote Senator Baby Bear,
we want a government small enough
that it can be forced into a vagina.
Not only will it fit,
it will be forced in.
That's what we call
small government.
Operating the
We're a woman's control
from the inside out.
And we'll make friends with that little
fetus in there. We're not going to raise it
or pay for it, but we're going to
protect it.
While we're doing that, however, I would
like to celebrate the execution of the
500th female in Texas.
That's an adult female who's
guilty, probably, or of
something. Certainly
of something. Maybe not what we're
executing them for, but by golly,
this is Texas. That's what we do.
My God.
As long as Rick Perry's governor.
Now, when Wendy Davis is the new Ann Richards,
then things gonna change. My God.
I'm gonna move back to Texas and become
mayor of Stainesville, and
we'll wage war on Stephenville
and Granbury
and Cleburne.
Well, that's certainly enough for
vigorous retirement full of
events and adventure.
Right. Raising the
I was gonna name a couple of other Texas towns.
I was gonna name some other Texas towns,
but they're racially, they have racially
offensive names, still.
And they're still out there, eh?
Well, I did, they're not on
There's one on an old
map, and there's still
signs in a couple of places.
Drowned
Subgenius Creek was one. I found
that to be really offensive.
Oh, wow, man. And Rick Perry's
ranch was originally called Subgenius
Head. Yes, I knew that.
I think that was
generally known.
I forgot about Subgenius Dry Gulch,
where they took all those poor guys down there
and let them smoke to death.
Yeah, the
owl hoots and dry gulchers
and bushwhackers.
Yep.
Get on, get on, you doggies.
Let's ride on.
Let's ride on down.
This piece on the air
you've got right now is perfect for
calling the devil, I think, or something like that.
Grand Theft Palomino.
Let's
ride into Deadwood.
Show that owl swearing to a thing or two.
Okay, but...
Come on after me, you
Yankees and dirt worshippers,
celestials, and
good-for-nothing
speculators, lawyers.
This legend
spread across the land,
blazing like a burning
brand.
A burning forehead,
a mountain of steel around his
tawny body, and his
knees all buckling from the weight of
having to carry the universe around in his
back teeth.
And I carry the universe under
my chaps, partner.
Yep. And to keep it warm between
you and the saddle.
That water's... I can make
cheese with that there, saddle.
Yep, on the old
Rennet Ranch,
where renegades would gather for
cheesy fun outside
the law.
Back in the old wild
days,
the devil took the
hindmost.
But this group of bangity-bang
honchos didn't care, firing off
their guns in the air
right outside the church.
Of a Sunday morning,
these hooligans didn't care
whether they rattled the pastor
and the congregation
with their wild
buck hijinks.
Let's rob them subgeniuses, boys!
Who's with me?
Hey, let's go to the gambling
joint there and find us some
fillets, some cheroots,
and some
woman.
Let's find an engine and string them up!
Wide open town.
Hey look, there's somebody who ain't
related to me. Let's kill them.
Let's find a fetus and protect it at all
costs, while killing
all the women and children in town.
Hee-haw!
We're continuing to force-feed her with all we've got.
Mountains of mush and pieces of
little cowboy cheese.
They say
that was defeatist?
Somewhere over near Mush Mountain.
You can still get cowboy
toes? You can get that
by walking across a shower floor
where some guys who keep
their boots on a little too long
have been there before you.
On that long cowboy
trail through the...
What a delicious aroma.
Yes, well, it soon proves
itself. As it
is.
Uh, yes.
A self-pruning aroma.
I love this talker.
Cowboys in Texas is making me
feel right at home.
Well, that's good.
On the saddle.
Did you string anybody up today, Stanks?
I just strung
them along, is what I done.
You know, God almighty,
a day without a lynching
is a day without sunshine.
Orange sunshine.
From the blue sun,
compadres.
Yes.
If I'd have been born under a blue sun,
I'd have super powers.
Unfortunately, this yellow sun
weakens all of non-Kryptonian
parentage.
Makes your teeth green, too.
Green teeth are just
what'll take away
our powers.
If you just don't want to spin
that color wheel too fast.
Red teeth, on the other hand,
turns you into a bizarro.
Me bizarro subgenius.
Me not like slack.
Yes. Me bizarro subgenius.
Me hate Bob.
Me bizarro subgenius. Me have good job,
make money.
Be responsible citizen.
Not be art bum.
The bizarro subgenius
world.
Well, that is
the bizarro subgenius world.
This world is what we would call
There are indeed many icons
of Bob as a bizarro man.
Yes.
With that square jaw already built into his mug,
I would say he's perfect
for the part.
Well, we now know that his jaw
was not quite as square as is commonly depicted.
That's the one
place that the
actual physical
Bob differs from. Don't remind me.
Hal is bringing up a point of
doctrine that I've been successfully
avoiding for almost two years now.
A very painful point of doctrine.
Do you know what we're talking about, Princess?
I don't believe I'm aware of this point of doctrine.
Nor am I.
Are you aware of the
photograph clip art
found by
Paul someone?
Yes.
There are two or three different bits of clip art
from the 40s that show
Bob.
And it's the same Bob that's in
the famous halftone
True Dob said,
But it's a photograph!
It's a photograph from life!
It's a halftone.
Like Pickman's model, it proves
the ultimate horror is an absolute
reality.
That Bob exists?
Is real?
Yes, this was the actual flesh and blood
basis of the famous Bob
glyph, with only very
slight change in the contour
of the lower jaw.
And the ears.
What happened to this personality?
It drift somewhere in Chinatown out there on the west coast?
Well, that's the mystery.
We prayed
to know someday
where that original piece
of graphic came from.
The portrait of Bob.
And
watch what you pray for, friend.
Yes, this is the most disturbing
appearance in the news.
The atmosphere.
We got an answer,
and it just raised a more profound
mystery.
Well, it turned out to be exactly the way
the sacred scribe
Ivan Stang wrote,
a model for a series of advertisements
in the 1940s
and 50s.
Just exactly as written
in the original book of the subgenius.
Yes, friends, it's a mystery, but we will
pierce the shroud
around this mystery. We show
it to the world.
We find our way to the golden secret
at the heart of the mystery
of the heart of J.R. Bob Dobbs.
If we have to cut his heart out
and hold it up to the
sun gods atop some
pyramid.
We'll cut his heart out at its side
to make it feel both cold and heat.
... a testament to a race that came
before all other races on planet Earth.
It's difficult to ascertain
for certain, but one thing
is clear. But I tell you, we should!
We shall have Dobbstown
in our hearts. We shall not just
in our hearts. We shall be
at Dobbstown. We will
be there this week
when the saucers land,
my friends. And Bob
himself steps down that
ramp, welcoming us on board.
Okay, what's this? I didn't know
we had to stop at Dobbstown.
This is the first time I've heard of that.
That we have to stop at that
place? Dobbstown?
This is the cosmic
Dobbstown. Not the place we had to
shut down in Malaysia, or the place they
ran us out of in Brazil.
The one in Bolivia that was so
diseased. And the one full
of monsters in the Mongolian desert.
Nay! This is the real Dobbstown,
my friend!
For Dobbstown
is a
true place. A place of
the mind, a place of the heart.
A place of the groin!
A place
you can eat! A place you can
move into! A place you can sit on!
Where the mortgage rates
are low and gasoline goes for two
bucks a gallon.
Yes, your Dobbstown.
Dobbstown. With a mall on every
corner. Great architecture.
One place for the entire
family.
Lowest sub-basement.
And now that that
Ennio Morricone music is over, I don't
have to yell.
When I hear that piece
there, it's something, something
of gold from Good, Bad and the Ugly.
Right. Arch Stanton
and Eli Wallach running around going
Blondie!
Whose
Arch Stanton was the grave that was
the actual grave in it? Well, that has nothing
to do with it. Oh, really? Was that the name on
the grave that was supposed
to have the gold in it? Oops.
Spoiler!
Oh, well, you don't expect this
radio audience will remember.
That movie is
so old! Or even have ever seen any of these films or will see any of these
films because most of the listeners
to all radio, and myself included,
are severely
mentally handicapped.
Well, there you have it.
That movie is so old that
when Eli
Wallach yells at
Clint Eastwood writing off, he goes
Blondie, you son of a
boi-wee-oh!
Wah-wah-wah!
Because you couldn't say
Blondie, you wo-wo-wo-head!
If we were on a commercial radio
station, I'd go ahead and say that.
Yes, it's still the 60s here on this
radio station. Yeah.
Well, a bitch is a female dog in here.
Well, it's 1984.
That's not a dirty word, it's just a statement
of... It's a... Knock it at your door.
It's 1984
at the KPFA
radio station. Yes, it's true.
I'm not trying to
sound critical in
this regard. Simply noting
a fact. They got more cameras in there
than a post office does. That's true.
We are under constant surveillance.
The slightest
motion is observed
by a secret body. Doesn't that make you feel
violated, Dr. Howell? Doesn't that make you
feel like your underpants are being sniffed
by a large mastiff with very large
teeth? Well, you
know, I had nothing to do with
these changes. You got used to it.
And after all, we have adapted,
which is the ultimate
evolutionary strategy.
We've drawn gills in the third eyeball.
Now we cower
submissively in the parking lot
outside
to enact our ancient ritual
rather than relax on
lawn furniture on the
spacious patio.
No more rocketing away.
Now they just crawl away.
Tails between their legs.
Like four reptiles crawling
on the bosom of the ground.
No more pre-pita for the third
collar in a row, whatever that means.
In a row, I suppose the third
collar is different than if they were to line up
in a row. The collars are always getting in a row
as if there was anything to fight about.
But they do. That's
just what they do. That's like the internet.
Trolls, flame wars,
pyroflatulation.
And when the daytime
comes, they don't turn to stone.
There
is a pyroflatulation channel.
There's a blank lighting
secrets channel on the,
not the internet, but on cable TV
now in a last effort to keep
cable afloat. Hmm. Well, who's the
one who cares if you like blanks? They're not
going to go off. They're blanks. Oh, you
meant crepitations.
Yes. Excreted inflations
as they used to say in French.
Dr. Sinister has just strolled
into the radio station. Oh, how delightful.
Join us for this
marathon run.
Now we can see Sinister
throw open the
discussion to
more topical concerns.
I remember Sinister when he had mountains and mountains of hair
on his head like a young man.
Mountains.
Mountains. Give me
men to move my
mountains.
The mountains
fall.
I cringe and hide
my head.
I never sent
in my thirty-five
bucks. My soul
is thrilled
with dread.
The saucers
are coming. The saucers are coming.
The end of the world is nigh.
Pucker your lips for
apocalypse and kiss your ass
goodbye.
It looks
like doomsday in the apocalypse
got married and had a baby
and it's damn ugly.
Ugliest infant
you ever saw.
Squalling and mewling
and puking and
as red as a beet. Why do
people think babies are cute?
Well, some of them are.
They are not cute.
If anything, they're vile and handsome
and full of robust flavor, but there are
no cute subgeniuses.
Well, yeah, I guess there are.
There are a couple cute in that way, but...
You can't eat them before at least
their first birthday
because you gotta give them at least a year to
ripen. Not without pickles, for crying out loud.
Or you can render them into the
always valuable commodity of
baby oil. Delicious.
I mean, well, it works for sunburn sometimes.
Makes good popcorn, too, but
uh... Is that where baby oil
comes from?
What about baby powder?
Yes, I know.
Well, baby powder is a separate...
I did a few lines of that New Year's Eve
and I tell you, I ain't been
the same since. Some babies did
take a powder. They were seen making
a break for it, crawling out of the
nursery on hands and knees down the
corridor on the security cam
film that we have
and wear these
malfeasor juvenile
infants have crawled to
is still not known to the
The malfeasor? Yes.
What the hell is a malfeasor?
It's a little miniature malefactor.
An infant criminal,
as it were. It's a shame
that such a category has to exist.
They're the opposite of a benefusor.
They say the Cleveland subway
tunnels, the abandoned subways
and sewers are crawling,
literally crawling with feral
babies. Feral infants with unchanged
diapers and weird glowing
eyes that you sometimes see by the side
of the road in your car's headlight.
And they are radioactive as well, yes.
But if you clean them and cook them properly...
They are active on the radio even as we are,
but fortunately their infantile
chatter is hardly
effective for the time
being. Much like what you're hearing
now. Yes. Well, you know.
Infantile chatter is highly
ineffective. I did have it correctly
that you can, if you know
how to get rid of the ducts and glands,
you can prepare them, you can
cook them up like any other form of
feral vegetable that you find in the
basement. Well, you're
right. You have to be very careful to remove
the scent glands. And the fat
carries an especially
high price on the market if the
baby has not been baptized yet.
Oh, I didn't know that.
Baptized, you mean, don't you?
Some of our more traditional
communicants
follow the old ways and
they have to drink the blood
of the unbaptized, the
unbaptized. But, you know,
everybody says today,
we have got to accept
them into the human family, understand
they have a condition that makes them
different from the rest. The old days
of pounding stakes through the
heart and all that stuff are
simply not
what anyone would
do today in an area
of understanding.
No, it is far beyond
understanding. It's totally beyond
comprehension. But what they're doing
is basically deep down in the tunnels
below the earth in these labyrinths
of stone and steel. The sunlight's
bad for them. They have to be in the
subterranean realm. Yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes. As you said.
And they must be tended to. They must
be cattle prodded occasionally
if they don't move in the right direction.
They must be kept in large, large
compound. I wouldn't recommend doing that.
Like salt is a compound,
I believe. See, what is this music
in the background? It's Ghost Babies
in the Sky. It's about a, uh,
hardened cowboys riding along
and seeing a
herd of mad
slobber mouth
ghost babies climbing through that
Just like he's doing
in the sky.
They whip them doggies along, you know,
for the long time they're going to San
Antonio. When they're
whipping them doggies along,
there's some genius babies
and they are liking it every step of
the way. Hey, shut up for a minute. Let's listen to Dick
Dale for just a second.
This is Dick Dale.
When's it gonna stop?
Never.
...
I predict it will stop in
uh, 41 seconds. How do you do that?
You're so accurate.
Brian Jones Color
Deuce
such fantastic
deductibles. I think it's
the third nostril giving it all away.
I think that's where he gets his information from.
You would not believe
the booger I picked out of my third nostril
this morning.
It's always in the morning, too.
Dr. Drummond pointed out today
in fact that every time you
pick a booger, a devil gets
its wings. I like
that.
Oh boy.
Have I created minions of
hell or have I created minions
of hell? Plenty.
Everybody's doing it.
Picking it and chewing it.
Pick a booger.
Not full-blown devils.
They're imps. They grow to
devils. They can become devils eventually.
You don't get a full
size impressive devil
from some incredibly petty
crap like that.
Dr. Sinister, do you hear that noise again?
The ocean in the background?
Yeah.
Our phone lines have had this problem for over a month.
That's still... Line 1 is still
doing that. It's not just Line 1.
We hear problems when you get other people
on the other lines as well. Oh, right.
Yeah, no, we've had this problem
with our phone lines for over a month now and
who knows what's causing it.
Listen, you hear the grating roar
of pebbles. You know, my office
phone died
last, of course,
people are desperate to find out
how to be saved.
This
subgenius office phone dies.
And I
learned in the
course of trying to get it repaired,
I learned that AT&T's
phone
robot
is in need of repair
and out of order.
Their repair
robots are
dead. So even the phone
company's phone is messed up.
Their repair robot
needs repair.
Why can't you just
settle back and give in to
reluctantly, of course,
grand mal paranoia and assume
that it's not only the
SPT and the STP and all
those different name groups and stuff,
those anagrams. I'm the opposite
of paranoid. I think people actually like me.
But they like
you in what way?
No, not really. It's delusional.
Yeah.
I don't want so many.
That's part of the fun is Rob's delusional.
So drop
the telephone and go back to the
heliograph. Problem solved.
Drop the helium bag and get out
on the backyard and
moak some fish with grandma and grandpa.
That's right. You can shuffle off to Buffalo.
And we'll be shuffling
with them pretty big shoes.
They do. They do
it, but that's because
they can be buffalo. To their own kind.
Uh-huh. That's what
the syllogism says. Yeah.
That's true.
Uh,
but you have to be willing to be
buffaloed, to be buffaloed
by buffalo, buffalo.
All you have to do is be shaggy
and horny and big.
And you're buffalo arch.
You're forgetting the hump, I think.
I never forget the hump, my friend.
I feel like hanging up after you said that.
Well, no, no, no.
Keep your shirt on there.
That's, uh, no problem.
You touched a nerve there, pal.
Well, I guess a lot of us
have gotten nervous in the
service.
Well, I've had more humps
since then, so I don't
really care. Well, uh, that
was the source of the, uh,
best part of the buffalo
critter. You know, the hump was
good. Also, the tongue was good. Tongue, yeah, I was
gonna say, the tongue. Tongue was good. Well,
uh, you, you know, buffalo
is, is, is quite good, really.
I recommend it. And the soul is small,
but it's, mm, mm, mm.
Buffalo, buffalo have souls?
Yes, very small soul.
The buffalo, the buffalo
had a horrid snuffalo,
and not a single Indian
chief would lend the beast a
handkerchief, which goes to show
how very far from courtesy
some people are.
I've heard that
the Indians used to call buffalo
Tishue.
Which Indians?
The Ukabala Pongas.
No, no, no, the European.
No, that's what their enemies called them.
It meant snake in the grass. They called them
themselves the true, the one true race
of humans, like
every tribe called themselves
since my ancestors
in England and Germany.
You have
ancestors in Germany?
They were, yeah, they were, they were native,
uh, natives of that place.
They wore the, the grass skirts
and the fig leaves and the coconuts
on their breasts and everything? Yep, built
teepees and everything. And then God
asked them, who told you you were naked?
Oh, and then the Romans came.
Came in and made them wear real
clothes. Yes, woven
by, uh, looms of, uh,
slaves in Brundisium.
Brundisium.
A great place for the garment
trade.
The invention of work.
Around Mare Nostrum, our
ocean, the whole Mediterranean.
It belongs to Rome, don't you know?
Yep, it certainly was at the time.
Now it belongs to
old Grandfather Smacky, better known
as Uncle Stan. Yes, there
are messing with Gibraltar.
If you look at the screen here, you can see the, uh,
several Romans, or Italians anyway,
running around, uh,
crazy, dressed up in clown suits.
Oh, yes, they're chasing the
Palpatini, which was another evil tribe
which grew in the backs of
their throats.
And I, I'm not saying that the tribe grew
in, never mind, it
was a disease that killed
many, many humans.
I was just thinking of this,
uh, that movie by that famous
Italian director, Peach Bellini.
And which movie was it?
Uh, uh,
Eight and, uh, a Third.
Oh, yeah, right, exactly.
A prequel. They, you know, it was a rip-off of
Eight and a Half, but they had to do a prequel.
There have been a number of Johnny-come-lately,
uh, comments
on that movie.
Have there? I'd be interested.
Dave and I were discussing
Eight and a Half a couple of shows back.
Because he was in love with that, uh,
that giant prostitute that lived
on the beach.
No, I liked the song, and I could play it on the accordion
with my teeth. It didn't mean that I liked
Sarandina. She was scary to me
because I was young enough to hear it.
It all fails before the Fellini sequence
in Boccaccio 70.
I missed that one.
You, you must know
the one with the giant, towering
Anita Ekberg?
I've heard of it, and I've never seen it.
It's the best thing ever. I bet.
It's, it's quite wonderful.
You should Netflix it or
whatever. It's only about half an hour
to watch. You should watch it.
It's good. Yeah.
I'll have to Netflix it then.
I'll have to get Netflix.
It's in the weird
category of men
being sexually tormented by
giant women.
Uh, more explicitly than in
say, the 30-foot Bride of Candy
Rock with, uh,
Bud Abbott and Luke Costello, with just Luke
Costello, uh, and, uh,
the attack of the 50-foot... I've always wanted to see that.
...50-foot woman, uh,
both, uh, original with
Alison Hayes and the Daryl Hanna, uh,
remake, but this, uh,
features a giant, uh,
Anita Ekberg, you know,
who grabs the squirming
anhedonic, anti-sexual
protagonist and actually
forces him between her
gigantic, uh,
uh...
Yes, exactly.
I was seeking a euphemism, but I wasn't
fascinated. No, this, this is a
fascinating movie, and he tries to get the Vatican
to condemn the, uh, giant
billboard of Anita Ekberg that
faces his house, but...
Right as a Vespa zips by and some
more cool music starts.
The Nino Rota music, which plays again
and again through this segment, is actually from
a milk commercial, which,
uh, is the reason that giant
Anita Ekberg is there.
But it comes a nightmarish time when, during
a thunderstorm, she steps down off
the, uh, billboard
and pursues the scuttling,
moralist, uh, through the street
with giant steps. I remember the song.
Uh, uh, you know, every, uh,
everyone should see this
film, but, uh,
anyway, what more... It's got
subtitles, though. I ain't gonna watch that much
subtitles. It's probably not even
3D. It's, it's
nice because it's not from
planet America. It has a different
outlook.
Drink your milk every day.
Every day, drink your milk.
Something like that.
Yeah.
Well, we were driving through Little Italy on the way here
and all the Italians were very little.
There were no giant women.
Not drinking their milk, you see.
That's the thing. There's no large Swedish
bread to dissolve.
Giant, hulking, corn-fed Americans,
you know, are also
subsisting on a dairy diet
and they grow enormous
because of the large amount of
growth hormones they secondarily
accumulate.
From America's grain-fed
belt-busting interior.
Uh, and that's why
these huge, doughy specimens
are recognizable across the
terraqueous globe as true
Americans. That, that is correct.
A race of milk-fed giants
with tiny little pituitary
glands and little teeny
pineal glands and teeny teeny
teeny teeny tiny tiny tiny tiny
It's an...
Americans, we are the cream.
That's right. We are plump and...
oily and we rise to the top.
You know, it's a condition of being
exceptionally well fed as well as
getting all those, uh...
Isn't that what freedom means?
Freedom means getting fat.
Is getting the resources of all
the rest of the world and consuming them
in front of the starving rest
of the world which is watching it all on TV.
Well, they can't...
They got an off button. Oh, that's right, they don't.
No, that's right, they don't.
In Russia, TV turns you off.
And those factories, they keep TV on. All the time.
All the time.
So, uh, there is
that, but, um...
things will
shortly change.
We are hours away from the end
of it all.
The very, very end?
Yes. The final slate? Recess is about
to be declared.
You can all put down your papers and examination
books and race outside
screaming and
giggling to run and play
on the endless meadows.
And the flowers on the
sidechamber.
School's out forever?
Yes.
It's the end of the term.
Except for the pinks.
Well, they have to be
educated. The pinks are just about to start getting
their education. They're really gonna have it
pounded into them.
Because they have been neglecting their
studies. You see, the rest of us will graduate.
Magna cum laude.
Oh, yeah.
And everybody else is gonna...
Well, we could call it interning.
Yes, the new world will be
exceptionally kind to subgeniuses
and fellow travelers. Those who have
smiled on us will
be rewarded a thousandfold.
While, unfortunately, those who
have made life difficult in even
the slightest degree
shall have endless grief and
woe hammered on
their skulls by the wrath of an
insane, senile god. But it will be good grief.
That's why I can't pay my bills?
I'm making a list and checking it twice.
I'm gonna
rise from the dead, those
who were naughty and not nice.
This is all done automatically, too.
It's not a question of we'll do this
or we'll do that. We have gotten with
the program. We are simply going to slide
along on its effortless
curve. Exactly.
The computer knows who you want to wreak
revenge on before you even think of it.
Yes, the gigantic brain
has every bit of information
on everything you ever did.
You can ride around on the shoulders
of that giant Anita Eckberg
while watching your fifth grade
teacher be tortured by devils.
Mrs. Darden,
are you listening?
I think she heard you several times.
You remember that?
Wow.
Yes.
That's what she must die for.
My one chance at the national spelling bee,
she asked me to spell the word
serval, which
I was, I was
I spelled S-E-R-V-I-L-A
and then later they corrected me
and said C-E-R-V-I-L-A.
Just like we said, serval. S-E-V-E-R-A-L.
Serval.
Like in, I have serval puppies
with me at home.
This is another reason why
Texas will get special treatment.
And that's why they had so many problems
with the serval-cocoon cancer bill
because everybody was going around
excommunicating 16-foot tall
Swedish women. And the thing about
Texas, and like they're talking about
the big abortion filibuster that
happened there this past week.
Praise Wendy.
I will take fetal pain
laws seriously
when they start mandating
anesthesia for circumcision.
Well Cleveland should know about these
these uh,
in vitro fertilization laws when
the guy who kidnapped all those girls
isn't he still charged with committing
adultery or something?
Or grand mal seizure?
Are you conflating several news stories?
We don't want to talk about
Philo like that. He's not here
and he can't defend himself.
He wouldn't be able to defend himself anyway
even if he was here. What we say is
it's just his way. You know?
It's just his way.
No we can't say that. Oh we can't?
You know who said that once.
So that means we can't say it.
Yes well I would like to, there's something
I've been meaning to mention but I guess
since it concerns that person we can't
mention it here? Oh go ahead. I don't care.
Go ahead and talk about it.
This person that we're talking about called
Paul while I was off, maybe
while we were both off performing
in the Chicken John
unauthorized cacophony
uh, show. I wondered where he
was when that was going. He called
Paul to say that he
had tried out for
uh, some reality
show. America's Got Talent. America's Got Talent
and been booed out of the audition.
Yes. Out of the talent audition
and it was on TV and it would be on
on Tuesday night so please watch it.
But it wasn't. Well I never saw it
but I'm busy on Tuesday night.
Yeah we would have heard about it.
The way Phineas Narco
told me uh
the uh, the over
cleats one was
walked into the audition
and this is according to him.
He told Phineas that he walked into the audition
and they said now don't do your
shtick yet. We just want to talk to
you as a regular person first then you can
do your shtick. Well he
of course immediately went into
his shtick. Of course.
And they had to make him
leave. As we
all have had. It's like how do you get him
to shut up? You have
to push him out the door and
slam it and lock it.
And he'll still be out there going
you call
me a boy? What do you mean a boy?
Who do you call a boy?
A boy. Oh well.
That's a shame. Terrible.
It is. I mean because I
think everybody would have enjoyed seeing him
on television. Really I
I was afraid I was going
to miss it actually but I guess since
it didn't happen I missed nothing.
He was beaten with his own
shtick. No you missed it anyway. It may have happened in
another dimension and you'll find that out
pretty soon next couple days. On an alternate
earth. Yes.
Wouldn't that be frightful to discover
that they somehow put
him in charge as being more
subgenius than the rest of us and
we must all serve him.
And worse than
Billy Moomy subjugation.
He might be
more of a subgenius
than we are. It is possible.
As Onan pointed out
it's
were Philodrummon and me
the best people to help Bob
get his cult off the ground?
Maybe not. But we were the ones
that showed up.
Yeah. Well there you go.
Just like Woody Allen said you know
that's the most important
thing is showing up there and you guys
did make the scene so to speak.
I meant that you actually
fashioned an ideograph in your
mind of a social
cultural scene.
Well
and look what came
to pass. Really?
Yeah.
This radio
show. This
benighted radio show which comes
to an end in less
than five minutes.
This bleeding piece of earth.
Five minutes?
This radio show.
The hour of slack number
one thousand four twenty one.
This has been hour
of slack one thousand four twenty one.
However I believe that we
are planning with
Dr. Sinister's permission to
hijack radio
synesthesia as
hours of slack number one thousand
four hundred twenty one and twenty two.
Double or triple because I get two hours.
It's so hard to keep all these programs.
As I said yeah there would be two more.
Yeah. Which would triple
the hour. Oh make mine
a triple too.
Yeah we're all in need of a triple right now.
I was born on third base and thought I'd be the triple.
Okay
sure that's the trifecta.
Well we've enjoyed serving you
haven't we? Etherettes
and rocket rookies.
Just like one of those little subgeniuses.
It's a phone book!
Yes now they
will have your number for
all infinity.
That's five five five five five five five.
Bob! Bob!
Does not count!
Because he's already got your number.
How about that?
How about them apples?
Yeah I mean repent.
Jesus may have to count how many prayers
he's getting every day.
Mohammed has to count how many virgins
he's gonna dole out to each martyr.
But Bob does not count
because he's already got your number.
Buddy.
I believe that
new line was
channeled by a relatively
new minister.
I think Reverend
Howard. A relative eh?
Yes I think I might have
heard that on the hour of slack about
three years ago.
Oh really? Well then if I said it
then you better pick up on it.
Well I'm saying you're going through your temporal
dysfunction thing again right now. You know what's
recently this happened? No it
happened twelve years ago.
And time often gets out of joint.
This is nothing that
isn't covered by the warranty.
Oh it's an LSD flashback again.
Oh it's an
LSD flashback again.
LSD flashback again. And another locust
came and carried away a grain of wheat.
I don't know why that struck me
funny but
I could just see like
piles and piles of locusts
consuming everything.
The idea of the LSD flashback is a bizarre thing.
Because an LSD
trip in and of itself is a series of
flashbacks. Another locust
came and carried away a grain of wheat.
Now how do you know about
things like that Dr. Sinister? You don't
look like some sort of hippie type.
I have ways of knowing things.
LSD. I have ways of
knowing things.
When you take the LSD it is a
super conscious state.
Infra dignitatem.
Marijuana is the gun
and LSD is the
Bob.
You might even hear that soon.
We all know that Bob has killed far more people
than all the guns that ever were put together.
That's right and he's
an object too. Many of your
conservative sociologists like
Jumbo Reality and SimGar and
Slappy and all those guys like that
they contend that
they're not just
Okay, the show's over.
You have been listening to the Hour of Slack from the
Subgenius Radio Ministry,
Post Office Box 181417, Cleveland Heights, Ohio 44118,
subgenius.com.
Thank you.
Well I suppose I should call back
here in a brief moment.
Welcome futurists,
cyberphiles and the rest of you
shapeless wonders.
And now to push this convention into hyperspace,
the man who put
Star Wars, a real bird in the Darth Vader's
saddle, Bob.
Bob. You still got it Bob.
Hello and welcome.
Our topic today is UFOs.
Of course that's just the start.
Throughout recorded history,
human society has been haunted by
reports of unidentified flying objects
in our skies. Many of
which have defied all attempts
at scientific explanation or
understanding. What are these phenomena
and how can they be explained?
With me today is Terence McKenna,
a philosopher and thinker of note
in the area of altered states of consciousness
and alternative realities.
Yes, well the ordinary approach
to the UFOs has been to
view them as visitors
or intruders from a nearby
star system that have
come in metal ships
for reasons of trade
or scientific investigation
or military conquest
or missionary activity.
Or missionary activity. Let me tell you,
you're not the missionary type. You never last.
And incidentally, you want to do mankind
a real service? Tell funnier jokes.
And therefore
it is threatening.
This is one of the reasons that
I think it relates to the psychedelic
experience. Because the psychedelic
experience is like a
UFO encounter on
demand.
Whoa,
another acid flashback.
half your yellow
will lift you into orbit.
Real rocket man.
I'll take two.
That would probably chill a horse.
I said I'll take two.
Whatever.
They decide to have this curious
symmetry breaking kind of experience.
What I have tried to say
to the UFO community is
I know, I know what I'm doing.
I'm after God.
Hey mister, do you need some help?
Let him go, Ralph. He knows what he's doing.
We will not really have a deep
understanding of what the contact
experience is until we
include data from the psychedelic
experience as a legitimate
data
to be included when looking at
the problem. The UFO
phenomenon is a modern
manifestation of pixies,
elves, fairies,
sprites, demons, whatever you
wish to call them.
Angels.
I love you.
I do.
Angel baby.
My angel baby.