When Princess Wee and I drive home from WCSB, we hear Dr. Sinister talking about how crappy our show was.
Yeah, he does that a lot. I hear that a lot.
And what show is it, Ivan Stang?
It's the Hour of Slark!
The voice of the Church of the Subgenius!
With your host, Reverend Ivan Stang.
And special guest, Lonesome Cowboy Dave!
Dave!
And now...
We are no queen of all!
Oh, wait, we can do that again.
Oh, wait, that was take one.
And now, it's the Hour of Slark!
Praise Bob!
With your host, of the Subgenius!
No, we got another take. Let's try it again, try it again.
No, it's not gonna work.
We can cut it.
It's not gonna work.
We can cut it together.
Yeah, we'll fix it in the lab.
We'll fix it in the lab. Don't worry about it.
The lab will fix it.
The lab gets it right.
This won't even be on the air later when the people are actually hearing it.
And now...
The Subgenius Radio Ministry Hour of Slark!
With your host, Reverend Ivan Stang.
And special guest star, Lonesome Cowboy Dave.
With the beautiful Princess Wee Ardo, queen of all.
The UFO.
And now...
Here's Ivan!
That's pretty good, huh?
Okay, that's a wrap.
That's a good...
We'll put that one right in the can right now.
Here's a can.
Stick it in there.
I rinsed it out.
I know it was a cat food can, but it'll still work.
Just stick it in there.
That was a really excellent shout-out.
I must say, Reverend Stang, my mother has been a supporter of KPFA forever and ever and ever.
Really?
She lived in Ohio.
She sent money every month to KPFA.
Yes.
Ah, that's so nice.
So good to give a shout-out.
Yes.
Well, she's a snowbird like us.
Traveling, flitting from good weather to good weather.
Mm-hmm.
Just hither and thither across this great land.
Ours.
Or this land of ours.
It's not great.
I know we're supposed to hate it, but...
It's wonderful.
I like the land.
I feel for those people in the flyover states.
I see them as real people.
You feel them?
Yes, I feel for them.
You feel them, playa?
I feel...
Do you feel me, playa?
I do the feeling for them because they're just flyover people.
They're not real.
Not like people on the coast.
The great coast.
It was for a month.
The great terror, planet terror.
Yeah, I like this.
There's Death Valley.
You could go there.
We could go to Death Valley.
But we have to get on a plane and go home.
There's no time.
It's so sad.
Did you know that it was 10 degrees below zero?
Windshield factor.
At your house?
At your house.
How high at my house?
Now, is there someone...
You have, like, there's a bunch of minions there guarding your stuff.
You know, within...
Until tomorrow.
Actually, there are.
Weaponry, right?
In fact, there is a plumber carpenter who is staying there and working on...
And you know what?
You know about plumber carpenters.
They have sharp tools.
They can use to defend...
Oh, and Mr. Sister.
They can use...
Defend the staying household.
Going in, guarding the house.
I'm wearing the...
I'm displaying the radio.
Yeah, there he is.
Mr. Sister.
T-shirt.
There really is.
See?
Puzzling evidence.
The Mr. Sister.
Mr. Sister.
Nice.
And this was done by Reverend Imager, the greatest troll in the world.
The greatest troll.
Who...
Reverend Imager.
It's in Polish or Russian or something.
It says, Mr. Sister, pork products.
I get it.
So, you see, when...
So, what is it?
The subgenius cult has become so inside joke that at the New York Revival, when the ladies
at the front desk of the hotel said, hey, you're the third person walking with that guy
on this shirt.
It wasn't Bob.
It was Mr. Sister.
And then Mr. Sister himself walked in and they thought, oh, my God, Dom DeLuise himself
is here.
I thought he was dead.
Ah, yes.
This is a great, great country.
Guess where one cult can replace another cult overnight?
At one funny looking face.
You know, for three years, instead of mutating dog's heads, they've mutated pictures of
G. Gordon Gordon.
Yeah, the old...
The subgenius has got so tired of worshipping one true God, they started worshipping his
bodyguard.
And called him that.
Yeah, that.
That.
Not to be confused with that guy who is a jerk.
Not to be confused with who?
That guy.
There's that and there's God.
And then there's this jerk named that guy.
And there's also...
No connection.
But there's also another guy that's not connected, but similarly named as that one guy.
Oh, that one guy.
Remember him?
Yeah, people.
Sure.
That one guy, we never...
From that one time that we all got together, remember?
That one guy was there.
We had to kick him out.
That was awesome, man.
That was so cool.
I remember that.
You know what, though?
What?
There was a tape of him trying to get that 14-year-old girl to have fun.
And not only was there a tape of it, but Ed Strange played it on his subgenius show up in Pennsylvania.
Really?
Yes.
Where'd that tape come from?
Sex is work, folks.
The kids who called that one guy.
Wow.
And they were taping the attempted...
What did they call it?
Sexual molestation of a child.
Over the phone.
Yeah.
Taped it.
This was long before to catch a predator.
Yeah.
In fact, this was...
That reality show, To Catch a Predator?
I saw that for the first time.
I've watched television this week.
I've been amazed.
They still have commercials and everything.
Did you see the one about the teenage mother?
I was a teenage mother or something.
That's a reality show about unwed mothers.
I've read about...
I've seen pictures of her on the superficial.com.
Man, that one rocks.
That was so hot.
I get all my news from a celebrity website.
A celebrity basher.
I've seen a bashing website called the superficial.com.
I was looking at it earlier tonight.
I get all my...
I just make up my news.
I don't even get it anymore.
It's like, I waste time getting it.
What bothered making up?
You can see it when you check out the grocery store.
I just make up news now.
I mean, anytime I want.
When I think about news, I just think in my head.
Earthquake in China.
Yeah.
There's one right now.
We said it on the radio, so it'll happen too.
Disease wipes out all bats.
I hate...
We have to be careful about what we say because things will come true.
And then we'll be sad.
We don't just write the news.
We make it.
And when we can't make it, we make it up.
And when we can't make it up, we steal it.
And when we can't steal it, we plagiarize it.
When we can't plagiarize it, we go out into the hallway and we find a magazine
and we just start taking words.
Words from page one.
And then some words from page six.
And then some words from page one again.
Isn't that how you wrote the lyrics to your last album?
It was just, you know, a little William Burroughs cut-up technique there.
I can't say I...
You guys weren't even doing that.
I did that myself.
The last time I saw Dr. Drummond singing in a rock band...
What happened?
Six-Fisted Tales of Connie.
He was...
The lyrics of his song were the ingredients of soda pop cans
and instructions for Linux installations.
And I was like, what the hell?
They were singing them in death metal style.
We were really innovative that night.
Coming in at the Reverend Angry Larry.
Hey, did you hear the amino acids had broken up?
Yeah, I did hear that.
The only place they will ever appear again is subgenius shows.
Yeah.
They will be at every X-Day.
What a case.
They will be at every Devival that they can be at, but no other...
But no other...
Those aliens will not play for humans anymore.
Any...
No humans.
Only subgenius.
No more human audiences for the great amino acids.
Yeah.
They will be in blocks.
Well, that's okay.
He's got...
You know, you can only do...
That's all right.
They got other things they got to do with their time.
And being with humans is a hard thing to actually have to do, you know,
with regular humans.
When I hear this music, I think of women that have machine guns for legs.
No way, it's for legs, yeah.
Was it a machine gun or a shotgun?
I can't remember.
It was a machine gun.
Is that what this is from?
One of those grind cows?
Yeah, Planet Terror.
I'm so jealous of that Robert Rodriguez guy who cut his fingers off to keep him from editing.
Yeah, I'm with you.
I'm so jealous of South Park guys.
I'd like to cut their ears off so they can't hear me.
I'd give you the scissors.
I'm so jealous.
I'd hold your coat while you cut.
No matter what it is, Philo will give you the scissors.
I got lots of scissors.
Actually, Philo, a few years ago, I asked you, I said,
do you ever watch South Park get jealous?
Because we were kind of coming, you know, since we invented that.
Yeah, since we did.
And Philo said, no, not at all.
I feel like they're living my life for me.
What a slackful attitude.
Saving me money.
Thinking all the money I don't have to spend on those fancy houses
and cool clothes.
Cool clothes.
Cool editing equipment.
I don't have to make those choices.
I can just, you know, make my regular choices.
Cool Korean animation company.
Think about that.
It's slack.
It's total slack.
I do not have to do that.
I do know how it is.
I'm on an hour of slack number.
Those guys don't really have fun.
Got 1,290.
They don't really have fun.
They hate what they do.
They wish they were free of it.
And, you know, I can't cuss.
I can't cuss on the air.
But aside from that, I'm not beholden to any commercial.
I'm not beholden to any audience.
It's not like there's anybody I have to worry about listening.
No.
It's not like I have to worry about some sponsor getting angry
or some listener getting offended because that's not what it's about.
Because I'm a true artist, like the Jackoff artist.
He works only for his own benefit.
His own truth.
His own satisfaction.
He doesn't care what others think.
He's a true artist.
Yeah, a true artist doesn't care for any type.
It's all about expression.
In a saxophone.
In a sax.
That's what I like about those.
That sax is so nasty.
Why did you quit Morphine?
The band Morphine.
You used to play sax in that, right?
Yeah, I did.
Yeah, for a little while.
Yeah, why did you quit?
Dana.
Yeah, Collie.
You know, got the gig after me.
He was a little better.
Actually, he was a lot better.
Didn't he die for you?
I wonder what he did after.
No, actually, the guitarist, Mark Sandman, died of a heroin-related death on stage.
That's what, okay, I knew one of them.
Died on stage.
What a way to go, man.
Wow, that is, now talk about cool.
Doing the things he loved.
Talk about cool.
Of course, he was only like 37 or something, you know.
Whoa, that's even cooler.
If only he'd been 21.
Go out.
Like the only subgenius rock star.
Go out like a flaming candle.
Sublime.
You know, we actually had, there was a guy verging on being a huge rock star.
He was a massive subgenius fan.
And he did some cool songs.
Some really cool tunes.
Yeah, Sublime albums are great.
They were the only CDs that my daughter and I both liked.
He had a Bobhead tattoo, didn't he?
And he had Bobhead on their first album.
Yeah.
You know, we all knew him for it.
That's how we heard of it.
Yeah.
And they paid, then Jesus called up their manager, the record company.
Record company said yep, sure enough, that's your trademark.
Call the band.
They have to pay for it.
Because we're the record company and we screw the band.
So, we called the band and the bass player answered the phone.
And Jesus said you guys used our Bobhead and didn't ask us for anything.
He goes, yeah, our lead singer was really into that, but he's dead now.
We don't know what's gonna happen.
Yeah, it was sad.
He was.
How much would you charge him for the album?
We said, oh, about two grand.
And they sent us two grand.
Yeah.
That was the most we made.
We made more off of that guy's death that year than we did off anything else.
What was your one biggest money-making item of the year?
Was the money we blackmailed him into giving us the Dobbs head?
We made more money off of out-of-court settlements of Dobbs head rip-offs than we did off of actual sales.
We'll probably do that this year, too.
It'll be one of our biggest items this year.
Oh, man.
If only Steve Spielberg.
It's in the projections.
I mean, we have to do it for budget considerations.
We put that in our projections for our revenue projections for later in the year.
You know, in that family court, we took that child away from the subgenius family.
Right, right.
And we made more money that year because it made so much news.
Publicity and stuff.
I've got a brilliant idea.
We've got to do it to another family.
Exactly.
Yeah.
You know?
I'm thinking of.
Who?
Spiridix.
A nice family.
They're at X Day every year.
Happens to have a nice little child.
Happens to be a nice-looking mom.
Milf, who's been in some pretty compromising photographs on our website.
Got to have all the ingredients there.
They live in a small town.
Don't say their name.
They would be big news in the computer world.
We've got to clear it with them first.
Huh?
No, no.
Well, it doesn't.
This has to be done anonymously.
Oh, God.
That's right.
I just blew you.
I'm a certain kind of gringo that I'm not going to say what kind I am.
You just so told everybody.
But fans of the movie Sorcerer will know what kind of gringo I am.
What's the highest during the day?
I'm a fan of the movie Sorcerer, and I can't remember that.
I'm a big fan of it.
Gringo.
Sorcerer, the guy's driving the truck.
Are you driving the truck?
I love that movie.
I actually have it.
Roy Steiner is being harassed by this cop in a little Central American town at this sheriff guy.
And he goes, why are you doing this to me?
And the policeman says, because you are a stupid gringo.
And every day I find myself telling Princess Marie,
you know, you're married to a certain.
And I think you know what kind I'm talking about.
Yeah, I know about that.
Man, that was a great movie.
When they're driving that truck, those truck driving scenes are just great.
They're driving that nitro, that old truck in the rain.
It's based on an old French movie called Wages of Fear.
Right.
Which has a much better looking native booker.
Really?
Yeah.
But does it have a William Peter Blatty in that?
No.
What did he have to do with that movie?
Nothing.
William Friedkin.
Yeah, William Friedkin.
Also.
I knew it was a William.
One of those Williams.
He knows a popular name.
The Exorcist and Bug.
Bug.
If you haven't seen that, you need to.
Really?
Bug.
That William Friedkin.
It's a beautiful.
Yeah, I'm surprised.
There's something about Sorcerer that is just.
It was beautiful.
It was beautifully filmed, I believe.
That truck was.
Driving that truck.
Yeah.
Across that bridge.
That one bridge.
That dynamite in the background.
Nitro.
Yeah.
How do you know?
Is this Alvin and the Chipmunks doing?
Yeah.
Everybody does Beautiful World now.
That's what I thought.
Yeah.
You checked out the new Alvin.
Have you ever seen this one yet?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
That's what it is.
Oh, that's D 2.0.
Yeah.
So it's really Alvin and the Chipmunks doing it.
All the young people.
You know, the plastic hats.
The way it was.
I know for me.
Yeah, I know.
Whatever.
Yeah.
Hey, I'm at the.
I had a copy of this book.
I couldn't listen to it more than once.
I would go to that every year.
They're a lot of fun.
Yeah.
Really great.
I would think so.
That's a good audience, man.
A couple of years ago, Bob Casale cooked dinner for everybody at the Devo-tional.
Really good chicken curry or something like that.
I'll be.
Yeah.
That was a lot of each other.
I know.
The Devo's are nice fellas.
Yeah.
They're nice.
All the ones on there.
They cook chili.
They're nice fellas.
Chili is as good as ten mothers in the theater.
Well, it sure has been great having you guys here in the.
Yeah.
Sorry you have to leave tonight.
On the show tonight.
Or this morning or whatever.
Yeah.
Tomorrow night we'll be back.
I'll be back at.
I'm tuning in WCSV to make sure they play the right.
The right.
Yeah.
You got to do that.
Keep on top of them.
We'll be back just in time.
And that's if we can dig our car out of the snow in the short period of time.
The long term parking lot.
Yeah.
I hear that.
They're not.
Chipping in from the ice.
Worrying about that.
They're just going to let them melt.
You find mammoths in between the cars.
Let their minds melt?
It's like you can't get it now.
Do you ever want to.
Meld.
Yes.
They're going to quit plowing.
Make mine a double.
Okay.
Call her your last few minutes here.
Make it good.
Yeah.
Oh, sorry.
Sorry.
I've heard her before.
Yeah.
What am I supposed to.
She calls a lot.
I didn't take any notes.
What do I do?
The radio.
You push button A.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
Slider one.
Yeah.
Turn down my mind.
I'm at the beach now.
Part three.
Dave, I'm fighting you out now.
Dave.
Dave, I am fighting you out.
I always hate that part.
Because little Dave disappears.
Goodbye, little Dave.
Yeah, I don't think I like to have Dave fade out.
Well, we don't have Dave here tonight.
No, no.
He's here.
No, it's just the virtual Dave.
He was just here.
Yeah, he was just here in the mix.
So, that's a wonderful thing.
It's so cool.
It's a beautiful world.
It is.
For you.
It's such a sarcastic song.
It actually is a beautiful world for me.
Yeah, it's a beautiful world for you, too.
I have slack.
I didn't always have slack.
I had to earn my slack somehow or accept my slack, actually.
You don't earn it.
No.
You simply accept the slack that you were born with.
And for me, most of the time, it is a beautiful world.
You have to accept it much like you put on a jacket or a coat.
I may be cursing bitterly in five minutes from now.
I may be cursing bitterly in five minutes from now and feel like it's a terrible life.
But right now, it's great.
It's a terrible life.
For you.
Not for me.
You interrupted our recording session, man.
Keep going.
On top of the grill.
Okay.
See you next week.
Yeah.
Bye.
This was great.
I'm ready for donuts.
Donuts and show.
Oh, yeah.
You're right.
The show's going very slowly tonight.
It's like one minute.
It's going really super slow.
One minute left.
Sand is slipping through the eyes.
Ah, okay.
Well, I'm going to go get a head start on the donuts.
No, I didn't say one line from my script here.
I'll do one.
Here.
I'm going to do one line from my script.
Okay.
Every day is X day when you have a billion dollars.
That's true.
So true.
I've done one line from my script.
Excellent.
That was my line, too.
Think of what it could have been.
Really cool.
The words of Ivan saying you're on the show and goodbye.
Riveting.
I can't turn off Queen of UFOs.
It would be like Dave disappearing.
This is the Hour of Slack number 1296.
That was the last 20 minutes of the Puzzling Evidence show of January 28th, 2011.
And what follows is the first 38 minutes of the Puzzling Evidence show of February 4th, 2011.
A broadcast from KPFA in Berkeley, which is not the station you are hearing now.
And the phone numbers of which you should never call.
And now, the news.
Farms?
In Dobstown?
Hello?
Yes, it's true.
In historic Dobstown, now agricultural production is up 20%.
The year 2011 promises to be the year of the world.
It's to be the brightest one in a series of bright lights on the horizons of international agriculture
and the great financial transfer made possible by their success.
And a direct score on the show.
In other news, scientists have determined that the solar system is filled with many black holes
the size of the atomic nucleus of peanut butter.
Junkie or smooth?
Smooth.
And where are they?
Near us?
I hope not.
I don't want to be a mean man.
Ha ha ha.
Philo Drummond, Dr. Philo Drummond has just now noticed that I, Van Stang, have confiscated his microphone.
I, yes I'll admit I lied last week.
We said that we were going to get it on a plane last Sunday and take off.
But, uh, that's actually this week.
We didn't want to advertise the fact that the Slacker Mansion was empty for that whole week.
But, we'll be home tomorrow evening.
Uh, back in our crop circle where we live.
The one with the...
The giant blue concrete gorilla brought in front.
Yeah, yeah.
I repainted that gorilla, by the way.
The giant concrete gorilla.
I thought it looked good the way it was.
You can't improve on perfection.
Well, it wasn't perfection.
It actually had been so covered with bat droppings and bird droppings that it needed cleaning really bad.
Well, it made it look like it was a silverback.
I know just how that silverback felt, too.
Good night, Doc.
I wish somebody would give me a bath.
The shipments here at Dock Six.
Shipment at Dock Six.
Just a moment.
Uh, don't worry.
This gorilla can't possibly get loose, Captain.
These chains are made of chrome steel.
A bath suggestion was good.
We've got him locked up good and tight.
Uh...
Helicopters are being deployed.
Yes?
What do you need those helicopters for?
I don't quite get you...
Can you?
Hong Kong lives.
While we're undergoing guerrilla transfer, it's probably a good time to remind our listeners that safety is always an important thing to keep in mind.
The moments slip, and you could be sorry for quite some time.
Just a message from the National Council of Worrywart Subgenius Usulianus.
Yeah, be careful, kids, and take missions.
Remember, when you go mountain climbing, you should always do it alone.
And if you encounter a mountain lion, you should pretend, act like his prey, and either flee or cower.
I think we covered that last week.
Under the bad advice of Dr. Howell.
By the drum of the overman, God, Dr. Howell.
Special guest stars, Ivan Stang, Princess Weave, and the UFOs.
It's the subgenius show of the stars.
It's also the hour of slack.
And don't forget Bishop.
Joey.
I did?
Oh.
This time, maybe he won't be voted off the island.
And we have a roster of surprises for you that you'll remember for the rest of your life.
If you can dare to listen to the Puzzling Evidence Radio Program.
So where's that?
No one will be admitted during the last five minutes.
Just yak, okay?
Okay.
So where's the fancy Puzzling Evidence Radio Show?
Look for the fear flasher and the horror porn.
And now, in the big sky.
Introducing.
But you know, there's a lot of room in the band for all kinds of radio stations.
In projectile vision.
So, Ivan Stang, what happened on X-Day?
And Rumble Rama.
What happened on X-Day hasn't happened yet, obviously.
Oh, that's right.
It's almost.
X-Day will happen on July 5th, 1998.
And we will be able to start dating our calendars correctly.
Okay.
Moment.
Dating a calendar girl, eh?
Hey, dude.
So, that's some tricks.
Dating our calendars in the correct fashion.
Well, these calendars have to be post-dated.
Bishop Kelly, what happened on St. Stupid's Day?
Oh, so many things happened on St. Stupid's Day.
I can't even begin to describe them, but I will.
So, the first one that happened was I showed up.
And then the next one that happened was other people showed up.
Now, that's 90% of it.
And then we went for a walk.
So, who's playing Lonesome Cowboy today?
And where's the queen of UFOs?
She's here.
Isn't she?
I don't know.
You can hear her snoring in the background just then.
Oh, it is a difficult show.
But that's that captive yeti.
It's on a pretend 3 a.m. hour on Earth.
I tell you, this is no ape.
This is the lost, abominable snowman, the yeti himself.
Why won't any of you believe me?
All the evidence can only point to that.
We don't have much time.
While analyzing the stool samples, doctor, I can't but concur.
Smell this.
It's getting the radio going.
Good lord, that is wonderful.
Can't but concur.
How does that, how do you, how do you, this but concurrence?
These fumits definitely presuppose the gram-inifera diet of all full-blooded yetis.
These strange rituals these young children are performing these days.
I'll just take some of this sample.
You're not young people.
Call in, 848-442-50.
And I suppose that concludes our session for today, doctor.
Good.
Can we go home and sleep now?
Of course.
I think that might not be a bad idea.
But remember, while even one of these creatures is on the loose, we won't be able to sleep well.
Keep that in mind, too, gentlemen.
If they bring a sword, I'll bring a hatchet.
They just want to live in peace in mountain fastness.
Far away from civilization.
If they bring a scimitar, I'll bring a broadsword.
And the bursar of human action.
And the scimitar of human activity.
Not to be back to the purity of nature's bosom.
But what if they bring a lawyer from Lawyer's Island?
Not Lawyer's Island!
Those who go to Lawyer's Island...
Oh, no.
Never.
Why did you say the L word?
You can't say that word.
That's one of the seven deadly words of pride.
We must confront the deadly word of the lawyer.
Lawyer's Island.
Hey, man.
The very worst place in the world to bury...
Sheet music for my best song.
...your treasure.
Don't bury your treasure on Lawyer's Island.
Double trouble on Diamond Island.
I'm interested to hear how you interpret those pipe notes.
Oh, those notes piped by the piper at the gates of dawn?
Yes, we've all heard the pipes a-playing.
That wee piper out there capering in the meadow...
Oh, my God.
...with the goatish...
...leaf legs and tiny horns.
Ear horns, maybe.
That's a fawn.
Better than horny ties.
Yes, he is, isn't he?
Well, the thing is, you see, he is the product of certain...
The product of his conservative up-and-coming...
...lifestock, not wisely, but too well.
And then, in the foaling time, a tiny wee fellow would caper among the new lambs,
one with features of both human and...
How can one...
Goat.
...feel...
...this way?
Love is a many-splendored thing, like the gleaming polyhedron of ancient lore.
I'm telling you, it is a bright marble.
Oh, at this moment, I've got a call.
I'm going to jam for a little while here.
I'm on drums.
Oh, jam.
Oh, yeah, great.
Me and Bishop Joey, we're going to jam.
Yes.
So, how...
How about it, ladies and gentlemen, Mother and Father America and all the ships at sea?
Isn't it a time that you got in lockstep with Dr. Howland Owl's renowned worldwide course in sex and real estate?
Ask your doctor if Dr. Howland's course in sex and real estate is right for you.
Side effects may include acute tightness, pedomorphia, erectile dysfunction, partial or complete blindness,
some hair loss, loss of bladder and bowel control...
...loss of bone density and massive loss of identity and memory.
Go 1.2 miles and turn evil.
Then go 3.5 miles and turn invisible.
Turn green.
Turn into a bat.
Go 3 miles and turn invisible.
You are a werewolf.
A werewolf?
A bear to the right.
A bear?
In 0.2 miles, turn and run.
In 0.3 miles, turn the other way.
This will kill you.
Your playing is so passionate.
In 4.3 miles, turn into Mr. I.
I.
In 0.9 miles, turn into a zombie.
Some folks say this is a way that was haunted.
Only ghosts and skeletons and spooks go down this way.
In 2.1 miles, turn inside out.
I'm not sure I like this boy.
In 2.5 miles, turn off the radio and do nothing.
Now we can relax and get in touch with our inner feral child.
That's not what that is.
I think we throw it overboard.
He can only communicate in a series of grunts.
His behavior at the table is most shocking.
We don't want him to escape.
We don't want to throw the feral child with the bathwater.
Grouching on the floor and grunting for hours.
Is that what that is?
Sure.
unintelligible, bestial fashion.
Simple electroshock clears him for a new life.
Here in the Institute,
the Kasperhauser Institute,
rudiments of social behavior,
balls, I say, balls,
discipline and firmness.
And then the great day comes,
graduation day,
when he leaves the wrought iron doors
of the Demilitar Institute
to go out and search for a job
in the real world
and the great shining new economy
of that economic dynamite.
Dynamo called America.
Wow, cool.
Hi, caller, did you get your job yet?
Sorry, job's not available.
Hi, other caller, did you get your job yet?
Did you get your job?
Get a job.
State short job, please.
Did you get your job?
You need the patience of job.
Did anybody get you a job?
Oh, I see.
Hey, guys, it's a secret subgenius signal.
What job is that?
Is it?
Is there more than one opening?
Sure, but somebody else has to get you a job.
Oh, get the job.
Yeah, the government has to get you a job.
What do you know?
Obama has to get you a job.
Oh, no, someone has to get you a job.
It's all about jobs, Obama.
It's all about getting you a job, though.
It's all about jobs.
What kind of a job are you looking for, my boy?
We've got plenty on the force.
There's no job with Bob.
I've got a job.
I'm down with jobs.
I've got a job for someone.
With slobs.
Oh, all right, with miniskirts.
Yes, exactly.
Wasn't that the way it went?
Something like that?
I'm down with jobs.
Well, you're supposed to repent, slack off, and quit your job for Bob.
March off that production line.
Assert your inner Yeti purity.
I don't want to.
I want a factory-built job.
I want to make my own job.
Well, don't let us keep you back, Mac.
Have you got the parts for me to build my own job?
We can provide the motive power, the inspiration that comes from our transliteration of the
Dobbs principles.
You do understand I'm looking for a good thing for that.
I'm dreaming of a wide history.
Just like the one I used to know.
Did anybody there at the studio bring a poop dog hat for me to wear?
Is anybody actually at the studio?
No one is actually there, as you understand it, at the studio.
Where there is.
There is no there there, Gertrude Stein wrote famously of Oakland.
There is no now here.
Did you bring a poop dog hat for me to wear?
Yeah.
I'm going to cuff the poop dog hat.
Yes.
What is this?
What of the poop?
What did and what has become of the poop dog hat?
Who is this king of glory?
How did we?
That's ancient church managed to forget the poop dog hat.
And we'd have to call Stern to normalize on that one.
So all the stories.
Byron, because he's a historian.
All but stories.
Lord Byron and Pope Stern.
Comrades.
They're staying in the middle of the country because it's the safest.
You know what?
the beginning of the end of the world.
They have a little while longer to store history
than we do on the coast.
The coast of the lakes or the coast of the ocean.
The high coast of the...
I live on the north coast.
That's what they call Cleveland.
The north coast.
City of light, city of magic.
Cleveland is city of magic?
Cleveland, you gotta be tough.
That actually was a motto
of the city, the official motto
during its darkest days.
Which weren't very dark
because the river was
brightly lit on fire.
The Cuyahoga?
The Cuyahoga River was flammable
in the 70s.
And so was the mayor's hair,
oddly enough.
Just like Michael Jackson?
One slogan they had,
the brightest nights in Ohio.
But those days are past
and now there's at least
three fish in Lake Erie.
And you can swim in there
if you really, really, really dare.
What about those pleasure saucers?
Oh yeah, I hear that a lot.
What about those pleasure saucers,
Mr. Dobbs?
We're ready for the finals, Mr. Dobbs.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It is a solution to all our problems.
You know, one might as well
live life normally until,
until the advent of the saucer people.
The message of X-Day is obviously
that we know not when that hour may come.
It could be tomorrow.
You put your shoes on today,
but the Undertaker may be
yanking them off tomorrow, yes?
Will you be yanked off by the Undertaker?
There's only one way to avoid that,
and that is to be in the Book of Life.
Have your name listed in the Book of Life,
which is the book of life.
Which actually is implicated
in a little program on my laptop.
And the underwear,
the underwear taker is usually preceded,
preceding the Undertaker too, so.
You won't enter the next world with clothing on.
I have a Jack Van Impey movie
in which the devil is going to put,
he makes everybody get the PCD disk,
and then they'll put it in their computer
at the X-Day moment of the bad devil.
All the PCs will come alive
and make you, uh,
that was the first, uh,
the first Macintosh virus.
That happened.
In 1984.
It was by Jack Van Impey and his wife
who show up on a TV in a couple scenes.
I don't know why.
That's just to provide sheer authenticity.
Jack still providing the word out there on the TV.
For Dr. Reverend.
I thought a piano fell on it.
Well, this is,
this is the peepos to talk to about that church.
That's right.
Is this one of the tiny collars
or the large collar?
I have a note.
I've had a note.
A magnetic body collar.
That said,
email the large.
Cause I didn't mean to fool the large last week
when I said we were about to leave town.
A little gas.
I actually wanted to meet the large.
Well, it might be the large.
Who knows?
But all I know is he's got questions
for the Reverend Stang.
Stang.
Yeah, Stang.
Reverend Stang.
Base fornicating bats.
Totally new.
A totally new idea.
A base fornicating bat.
The first time anybody's ever brought this up.
Well, on our show, yes.
We don't go in for such grisly details.
I've heard some stories about them
and I want to know if it's true.
They are simply a part of nature's mystery, my boy.
It's a circle of life.
The circle jerk of life in some cases.
You see, they have to get rid of this sexual energy of theirs somehow.
They depend on it, of course, for their survival.
Oh, my God.
Bringing that complicated package of germplasm forward.
When the bat delivers germplasm.
What the bat delivers into, obviously,
there's no obvious reproductive reason
for a bat to deliver its seed down a human's gullet.
The bat that flits at close of eve.
There's a parasite in the seed of the face fornicating bat.
Okay.
And this parasite,
requires a human host.
And it can only survive in a human host
that occasionally smokes a pipe.
It's a life cycle of some complexity.
The pipeless ones are likewise
probably free of the face fornicating bat parasite.
It's all about the pipe.
At this time, the...
Well, some things are worth it.
...still believe that he's speaking to live people.
...private pleasure of a good...
He's actually speaking to a computer.
...soul food and soul.
He's speaking to the pudding.
It's actually...
Pudding people where they want to be.
...to kill the parasite
before it can lay its parasitical eggs all over your hair.
...horrible, writhing...
That's the kissing sound of the face fornicating bats.
Have you seen Alien...
Echo location.
If you saw Aliens, you saw the whole thing.
Because they'll try to make out with you before they get serious.
Well, they are amatory, certainly.
...blending all the...
There...
Uh...
They're innocent creatures just trying to return to their cave.
And when you're standing on a hilltop with your mouth open, your mouth looks like a little cave.
It does indeed, especially after they've been there for a while.
...looks like a bat house to me.
They're like little guys stepping out of the...
...a...
They don't wish to choke the philosophical esophagus with the roughage of knowledge.
Thank you.
I think that's my job.
These insects are not in a sect that is in...
...I don't really think you are.
...in a...
Or, although they are of the brethren of the chitinous arthropod...
...they are also, as we are, residents of our own teraqueous globe...
...the planet Telos or Earth.
We welcome our space friends at any time, but particularly around the time of extinct.
Do you see the space friends?
...since the confusion of the years...
...where we are now?
Not when 1998 might actually advent upon us.
Oh, brethren in space, descend upon us with your giant saucer vessels
and transport us to our true home as subgeniuses among the stars.
This has got to be the most disorganized religion I've ever heard a radio show of.
Many are called, but few are chosen.
Now you can get this.
Your dose goes on forever.
Is there nothing your little box won't do?
Maybe $3.98 on your local cash.
What's that?
I see Princess Wee.
She's like signaling over there.
Is she done getting?
Oh, she needs a microphone.
Show us your microphones.
Well, do the talking.
See if I can figure it out.
There you go.
Now I hear you.
You have to do the talking part.
This show's just crazy.
I mean, this is crazy stuff.
It doesn't make sense.
It just doesn't make any sense at all.
I mean, it's just supposed to be funny.
It's just supposed to be a joke.
I mean, it's just like some statement that the world is ridiculous or absurd.
I mean, what is this?
It's just like theater of the absurd.
It's just like.
Stream of consciousness.
I mean, is this supposed to be funny?
Was that funny?
Okay.
Look at the Mellotron.
Did you ever have a Mellotron?
Whip out your Mellotron, America.
Dude, you're harshing my Mellotron.
You took too much.
You are seriously harshing my Mellotron.
Hal explained everything.
And once Hal explains everything, nothing's clear.
He's just saying the danger of overindulging in this new designer drug.
Your headphones might be.
Tee hee hee.
You should.
I thought of this new drug.
You might turn up your headphones if you can't hear.
That's kind of broked it, but I can use them.
We can hear you.
So I'm talented that way.
It was concocted by the CIA.
Oh.
Tee hee hee was originally invented by the military, wasn't it?
It was.
But it only lately escaped into the civilian world.
Where it has marched through many territories, taking their prisoners, investing in garrisons,
and consolidating political power.
The only good thing you can say about the drug Tee hee hee is it has put the Jinkum cartel
out of business.
That's right.
That was some dirty, dirty business.
Well, they call it green Jinkum.
And then there was the design of the drug.
The designer Jinkum and the Franken-Jinkum.
Yes, those kinky euros always have a way to twist and pervert.
What parents don't understand is that the Jinkum of today is 400 times stronger than
the Jinkum they might have smoked in college or in pale.
It can be apprehended from literally blocks away.
Please feed the baby.
And as often as you feed the baby, the baby produces the mountain of wings.
The taste which continues to flavor the monumental mountain of original human effluent.
I can hear those tubes making noises.
Doctor, I need more Tee hee hee so I can get off the Jinkum.
Please feed the baby.
I'm sorry I can't write you a prescription for a controlled substance as you really ought
to know, but although I never told you this, well, here's a phone number.
Oh man, I'm jonesing.
I'm jonesing for the day.
J.
Now get on that honker and call the Dutchman.
I need the jank, man.
And you never got it from me, get me?
See?
And the children walk down the hill together.
What on earth?
Pick yourself up.
Is this the way you act in front of the children?
Oh my.
Just a second, it's my favorite song they're gonna play.
What is it?
Pew!
That's awful.
Pew! Pew! Pew! Pew!
Twirling lollipops are really vibrating and getting in my eye and getting in my optic stream.
A caller was asking earlier about the church of Pew!
Well, did that caller get sorted out, ship-shaped and squared away?
Well, you know, there's been a big schism between the church of Pew!
Oh, schism all over.
And the church of Pew!
Somebody ought to clean this up.
Well, that was the original Orthodox church.
It was a little too messy.
Oh my gosh.
Yeah, because sometimes people without control could have a bowel movement accidentally.
Opus 12.
There it goes.
Loot splashed away.
Mafioso.
That's horrible.
That is just absolutely horrible.
The thought of that is enough to make me have projectile vomiting.
Oh, please, please, please.
I want to watch.
That's what we call a Cleveland steamer.
Now in act two.
There it goes.
It sounds like I'm a chirping bird.
From her serving lady, Dulcinea, that Rodrigo has not been true.
In vain, she rushes to the battlements to throw her off, only to be apprehended by the adoring
footman, Gascon.
So that's 8484425.
Do you want to talk to Ivan Stang?
Yeah, we're not going to play the opera right now.
KPFA 94.1.
Drumming the overman, Bishop Joey.
Or even puzzling evidence.
Your show host, Berkeley.
KPFA in Berkeley, 89.3.
88.1 Fresno.
And of course, all over the world.
And in France at 7 a.m. on KPFA.org.
An incredibly powerful signal.
And you're like the world's premier knob twiddler.
Ah, yes.
There are many.
There are many right here.
And I think I speak for all of us when I say we welcome our Chinese overlords.
Get your hands on the controls.
I never want them to be anywhere else.
I was hoping for Mexicans because I like their religion better.
I was hoping for Mexicans because they have an exciting religion.
That's Santeria religion.
It's really hoping.
Frozen ocean in the month of May.
I was just wondering if you guys saw you opposing Cleveland.
You would be the person to talk to about that.
You sound like you're talking to me from Cleveland right now.
Underwater?
Oh, okay, yeah.
It might be those headphones.
Cleveland's flats in St. Louis' Clabber Alley, Boston's North End.
But this is the really nice part of the show.
Yeah.
This is the cuddly and family-friendly, accessible part of the show.
This part of the show is the twinkle in the eye of a red-faced old geezer who hands you
your first cup of coffee in the morning.
Because there's nothing friendlier than down-home radio practiced by those who've been cooking
up the big cauldron of it for all these years.
And it still hasn't stopped.
The crud rising to the top.
Mm-hmm.
Smell.
Smell that show.
Smell that crud of cooking.
Now they're going to dump in a couple of rucksacks full of brown sugar.
You've almost got it rendered down into a gradu-like form.
It's kind of thick, and this is the candy-like, you could say.
This would be a good time to wake up your children and make them listen to the show.
Like the primordial earth itself.
We'll wait here while you do that.
A brilliant blazing ball of molten magma.
Wait, wait.
How don't they?
I've got there now.
1,000 degrees.
Oh, jeez.
There goes the town.
I miss the big news about the planets.
Oh, what are they up to now?
I'm going to see Pete Goldie go on and on and on about the planets.
Is it centripetal?
I want to go.
I want to get off this planet.
Get off this dirt ball.
It's a conspiracy.
Just a conspiracy.
You don't get that option.
Generally, that's not one of the options on the menu.
The scientists.
I never saw the get off this dirt ball checkbox.
Just telling us that, man.
So we think.
I did.
You did.
Yeah.
Did you check it?
What happened?
I signed my name to that check.
And I sent it in.
Post office box.
One in the floor.
Oh, you can't ask for money.
That one.
Yeah, I know.
That's why I didn't give the P.O. box.
Well, you know, they don't have a P.O. box in space.
The post office will not deliver your mail there.
I guess we won't be able to get there for some time to come.
I personally don't really want to be in outer space.
It'll boil your blood right away.
I would love to have my own planet that I could direct through.
How are you going to get there?
You know, you've got to get there.
I know how to get there.
Planet one to planet two.
And the answer is with patience.
Here's your stateroom.
And if you've got any problems.
Wait and have faith.
Talk to the captain on the intercom here.
I'm your steward.
You should be on the show.
I'll be giving you all you want to make your voyage a comfortable one.
And we hope that you'll fly into space with us again.
Why don't you be on the show now?
Well, I guess we have to work on Mars first and work our way up.
Yeah, Mars has to be fixed up.
We've got to kick Mars into shape.
Mars is falling behind.
But we can do it.
We've got that get up and go.
That oomph.
That drive.
That zest for living that brought man out to touch the face of Mars.
When you get up and go, done.
Got up and went.
What do you do then?
He has slipped in surly bonds of earth.
What if you walk out of the station and there are big bugs everywhere?
Then like eat through the top of Mars.
X-ray delta one.
This is A-OK.
And when you're driving across country, you're just ahead of him.
You have liftoff.
Waves of big bugs that are eating.
Because the storm ship trooper thing didn't work.
Roger on that.
This is your radio operator, Doug Smith.
We'll be bringing you a piece of that green cheese for sure.
Cheese?
Oh, boy.
Decades have gone by.
No green cheese.
And there it goes, ladies and gentlemen.
Up into the stratosphere.
That contrail of fire showing where...
Is that the little fake Don Joyce?
Recording everything going fine.
The little tiny blooper of over the years.
Of outer space.
Oh, gosh.
It's gross.
I could never live here.
There's all those over the edge bugs everywhere.
Yeah, and little leakage of...
Yeah.
Disgusting life forms.
What's with that?
But didn't we learn in our last episode that Don Joyce, host of that show, doesn't have
an FM radio in his car and so never hears your critiques?
He may be listening right now though.
You'll never know.
Because he could be at home.
Well, he could be.
That's fine.
Doesn't he have better things to do than listen to the puzzling evidence?
Yeah, yeah.
He could make his own show.
I know I do.
What am I even doing here?
Well, that's an existential type of question.
That's the whole question.
There's the laugh track.
Oh.
Even though your heart is breaking, laugh clown, laugh.
What are you doing here?
But you must surely know more than anyone else that radio is an unparalleled opportunity
to present your views to the public in what you consider necessary.
What a big deal.
What are you doing here?
That they might know.
So, continuing in your educational mission, what announcement do you have for many interested
followers that you might reveal here in a typically awesome fashion on our radio show
on this historic and ceremonial occasion?
Friends, as we stated a little earlier, X Day could be any second now.
Any second.
Are you truly ready?
Is he saying something?
I'm ready.
You may think that you've got it all together for 2012 and ready to see the world out with
a bang or a whimper, whatever your plan may be.
But the evidence in front of us, twiddling the knobs, convinces us that, in fact, we
know absolutely nothing.
We know absolutely nothing.
But we do know absolutely nothing about the future except what Bob has chosen to reveal,
and that is that X Day comes July 5, 1998.
And that obviously hasn't happened yet.
And so, but we do have a wonderful party, where we get together to practice for the
end of the world.
And this party is also known as X Day.
But it's not really, they're really drills.
They're not to be confused with the prophesied worldwide event called X Day, during which
most of you listeners will die in the process in the form of a
horribly, if you're lucky, it will be quick.
Most of these listeners are not listed in the book of life.
They may be big contributors to KPFA.
They may have, they could be like Gandhi or Mother Teresa,
great hypocrites who were sainted by the PR of their actions.
But in fact, all of that is meaningless compared to having the little minister's card from the church of the subgenius.
That's it.
Damn straight.
Why couldn't he remember the name?
What's happening here?
I don't know.
There's this bleed over that's coming in.
What was that about?
The church of rub fog.
Bleediness.
The clutch.
Birch of the.
Punch.
Menius.
What?
The crutch of the.
No, I know.
Evil genius.
Of the crutch of the.
Menius.
Dub.
Oh, no, it's.
Church crossover.
The.
That's the.
That was the first half of the puzzling evidence show of February 2nd,
and the end of this Hour of Slack number 1296,
which, like 1295, was assembled partially in a car,
in fact, in the I-van of Wild Princess, we and I were on the road.
For more about puzzling evidence, see kpfa.org or quiveringbrain.com.
For more on the church of the subgenius and the Hour of Slack,
you may wish to see subgenius.com.
Next week, we will hear more of the temporarily endless puzzling evidence show.
Thank you and praise.
Bob.
Yeah.